Previously on heroes...
[Grunts]
As long as i have breath,
anything you love,
I will lay to waste.
[Gunshot]
Jessica wasn't the strong one.
It was you.
Adam was dangerous.
So we locked him up,
we threw away the key.
Two weeks ago, he escapes.
And now he wants revenge.
Who are you?
What's your name?
I don't know.
Peter petrelli?
I'm from new york.
Who's that?
I wish i knew.
Someone knew i was coming.
The name adam
doesn't ring a bell?
No, and i don't know
about any company.
Please tell me who i am.
What the future holds.
I was in montreal in 2007.
Next thing i know, i'm here.
All these people
died from the virus.
You can change history.
I can't.
You must!
Don't let them take me!
No!
Caitlin!
(Mohinder)
it is man's ability to remember
that sets us apart.
Caitlin!
(Mohinder)
we are the only species
concerned with the past.
Our memories give us voice.
They bear witness to history
so that others might learn.
So they might celebrate
our triumphs.
And be warned
of our failures.
Adam. Adam--
I don't know any adam.
[Rustling]
Peter, what the hell
was that?
Do you know me?
Of course i know you.
Peter, it's me, adam.
Don't you remember?
Together we're going
to change history.
Sorry, i don't...
So the haitian's taken liberties
with your mind.
Haitian.
That explains why you fell
off the face of the earth.
You can get back
your memory.
I know how.
How?
Healing.
You can do what i can do.
Which means the mind
has to repair itself.
How do you suggest
i go about doing that?
Think about
what matters most to you.
Do you know what that is?
His name is nathan.
Nathan?
Nathan.
(Nathan)
you saved the cheerleader...
So we could save the world.
You gotta let me go,
nathan!
You go, i go!
No!
I'll be okay.
You can fly, i can't!
What do you mean?
It's taking everything in me,
All my power
not to explode!
Let me go!
Peter!
[Yelling]
Sanders!
Nicole sanders?
Here.
Is my husband okay?
The bullet was less
than an inch from his aorta.
The surgery was successful.
He's a lucky man.
Thank you.
[Church bells ringing]
[Merengue music]
*
[Speaking spanish]
[Passionate moaning]
[Yells in spanish]
[Yelling in spanish]
[Choking]
Alejandro!
No!
No.
[Gasping]
[Speaking spanish]
Maya!
Help!
Please help!
Help.
Keep him alive, okay?
Do whatever it takes,
you understand me?
Officer?
Officer, can you help us
over here, please?
[Yells out]
Did you have to use
the full blast on him?
He can take it.
He's not a toy, elle.
He could be.
[Gasping]
Where am i?
Someplace safe.
[Breathing heavily]
My brother--I was
in a hospital.
We have the finest doctors
in the world
Working on him.
But his situation is dire.
So who are you?
What am i doing here?
I am an old friend
of your parents'.
Yeah, i've seen you before.
And as i said before,
you're safe here.
But your brother...
That's a different story.
He almost died.
Because of you, peter.
Hey, it's not like
it was your idea
To go nuclear and take out
half of new york city.
Oh, you know about that?
Yes, as long
as your abilities
Are in control of you,
You will always
be a hazard to yourself,
To your family...
The whole world.
Believe me, if i could
turn them off, i would.
Don't worry,
We've done that for you.
At least for now.
How did you...
My colleague here
is able to suppress
The abilities
in people around him.
(Peter)
i don't understand.
What is this place?
You are in a facility
designed to help people
Just like you.
Peter, we can help you
go back to a normal life.
30 years ago,
we had to shut down
Research on a vaccine
which could
Disable your powers.
But due to recent events,
We have reinstated
that research.
And i'm very happy to say
that we're very close
To finding a cure for you.
Forever?
You will never
have to worry
About hurting anyone
you love again.
How long
until it's ready?
Good!
You're making
the right choice.
[Bob laughs]
good boy.
You have had
a terrible accident.
[Softly]
peter...
He's missing.
He's missing, nathan.
The coast guard
is searching
100 square miles
of the ocean.
But you're lucky
to be alive.
No.
Oh, no no no.
Dad!
Oh, big guy.
I thought i lost you.
Girl, i told you.
You're never
getting rid of me.
Mrs. Sanders...
I'll be right back, okay?
I'll be here.
Dr. Brooks.
Um, i wanted you to know
that we don't have insurance.
But i'm sure
that we can come up...
You don't have to worry
about that.
It's all been taken care of.
I don't understand.
How?
Who paid?
Uh, that'd be me.
Do i know you?
Call me bob.
Did you happen to see
a morning newspaper?
What?
No, why?
Not a mention
of what happened last night
On kirby plaza.
Or the untimely death
of our friend mr. Linderman.
Who the hell are you?
Someone who wants to help.
Linderman made a mess of things
And i'm here
to right the ship.
So to speak.
Okay.
You've done that
by paying our bills.
No, i meant helping you
with your illness.
I know you think
jessica is gone.
How do you know about that?
But we've discovered
That when
these abilities manifest,
The way the mind deals
with the new reality
Sometimes results
in a fracture of sorts.
A split personality.
No, i'm finished
with jessica.
How do you know
a new personality won't emerge?
I can get you
all the help you need.
The best care in the world.
Uh-Huh.
What's the catch?
The catch is you have
to leave your family
And enter the program.
I just went through hell
To get my family
back together.
I'm not leaving them now.
There is medication
you can try at home, but...
But what?
It's not
without side effects.
And as you just said,
You've been through
so much for your family.
Do you really wanna risk...
Losing them all again?
So i just take these pills
every day?
Yep.
It's a little cocktail
They cooked up here
in the lab.
It controls the abilities.
Dampens them.
Like that guy who was
standing in the corner
Of bob's office.
The haitian.
Yeah.
Sorta.
So let's just call them...
Haitian pills.
Bye, peter.
Ow!
That hurts.
You'll get used to it.
And then
you'll start to like it.
Hello?
Who said that?
Me.
(D.L.)
* he's a jolly good fellow
* it's micah's birthday
today *
All right!
11 years old.
Almost the man
of the house now.
Mom?
Did you make a wish, baby?
(D.L.)
Don't tell us.
'Cause you know
it's not gonna come true.
You both already know
what i wished for, anyways.
Micah, we've been
over this.
But i've got it
all figured out.
I could make the car radio
pick up the police band.
We could go to the crime scene
and be heroes.
Or the police
could just take care of it.
We could be like
the fantastic four.
Minus one.
But still.
Micah, i wanna
be a hero to you.
And i finally figured out
how to do that.
I think i got a job.
A good job.
Doing what?
Something that's gonna make you
proud of me,
I promise.
Come on.
I promised
i'd take you bowling, right?
Let's go.
Mom, you coming?
Your mom's had
a long day, micah.
Go get your jacket.
All i want is to smile
at my boy on his birthday,
And i can't even do that.
They said it's just
gonna take a little while
For the medication
to level out.
I just don't know
how much longer i can do this.
I wanna say
things'll get better.
But i know how that sounds.
The truth is, they will.
You know,
it's been a month.
You still
haven't told me your name.
Please, i just
wanna be left alone.
You came to the right place.
I have to warn you,
though,
It does get a bit old.
Let me guess.
You were living
a perfectly ordinary life.
Until one day
you discovered you could do
Incredible things.
I bet it was wonderful
at first.
You thought perhaps
you could save the world.
And then you realized,
tragically,
That you were dangerous.
I'll let you talk to me
after a decade.
Oh, actually,
talk to me after three.
If they wanna leave me
in here forever,
That's fine by me.
You've been through
something awful, haven't you?
I'm sorry.
I'm peter.
Hello, peter.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm adam.
...
I'm not in the mood today,
elle.
Just a little one?
I'll up your dose.
I'm fine.
Just a little one.
Oh!
Not that a fistful of pills
everyday isn't fun, but...
It's been two months now
and i still don't know
A thing about you.
I was just thinking...
Maybe there's more to you
than the whole
Sadistic lightning thing,
that's all.
What's your story?
I liked you better
when you just laid there.
So you're not gonna tell me?
What are you, afraid?
No.
You just
like to be in control.
I get it.
I figured as much.
Sorry i asked.
Won't happen again.
I accidentally
set my grandmother's house
On fire when i was six.
Caused a blackout
In four counties in ohio
when i was eight.
I spent my ninth birthday
in a glass room
With an iv
of lithium in my arm.
I've lived in this building
for 16 years.
Ever since the shrinks
diagnosed me
As a sociopath
with paranoid delusions.
But they were
just out to get me
Because i threatened
to kill 'em.
I'm 24 years old,
and i've never gone on a date.
Never been
on a roller coaster.
Never been swimming.
And now you know everything
there is to know about me.
I don't have the luxury
of being more interesting
Than that.
Later, alligator.
(Adam)
word to the wise, friend.
I would keep my distance
from that one.
I caved in a desperate moment
six years ago,
And i'm still paying
the price.
Don't worry.
I don't want anything
from her
Except the drugs.
I'm sorry,
i keep forgetting.
You still believe them.
What do you mean?
This cure of theirs.
They've been days away
from perfecting it
Since i got here
30 years ago.
Bob's not trying
to fix you, peter.
No.
They created this facility
to help us.
You're not
in a facility, peter.
Look around.
You're in a prison.
You don't believe me?
Why don't you
try getting out?
...
Oh, i'm sorry.
Are you all right?
He said it was all a lie.
What happened to him,
and...
To peter,
and the car crash.
I take it he told you
he thought he could fly.
And the plot
to blow up new york.
That peter was a bomb.
It must be
the pain medication.
You deserve to know this.
I tried to keep it
from you and the boys.
What?
There's a dark secret
in the petrelli family.
It started with their father.
Delusions of grandeur,
Paranoia.
It lead to his suicide.
But sadly...
That disease
has obviously been passed down.
My god.
Now...
Nathan's a great man.
And his life is gonna
be very complicated.
He really deserves his dignity
and his...
His privacy.
So i hope you understand
That this
has to be kept secret.
Can i count on you
for that, heidi?
Hi, what can i do to get you
inside a--
Hi...hi.
What can i do
to get you
Into a brand new car?
Hi, what can i do...
Depends on what
you're gonna do to me
Once you get me inside.
I got a great feeling
about your first day.
My butterflies
have butterflies.
Nik, i am so proud of you.
I knew that medication
would work out.
You were right.
I'm gonna take micah
to school.
Okay.
You have a great day
at work.
And when i get home tonight,
We're gonna celebrate.
(Gina)
he's gonna know you're
not taking the stupid pills.
Go away, jessica.
I don't need you anymore.
What makes you think
this is jessica?
Remember me?
That summer
that you ran away to l.A.
And told everyone
to call you gina?
You're not real.
Oh, you're gonna sell cars?
I'm going back to l.A.
To go play.
No, i'm in control.
If i can handle jessica,
i can handle you.
Then why aren't you
taking your meds?
[Niki banging on glass]
no!
No! No!
No!
Look, i need to see my family.
Just for a day or two.
Yes, i-I think that would be
absolutely possible.
Just not right now.
Why not?
They don't even know
i'm alive.
Look, i could let you go,
and you could explode again.
You could blow up
half the east coast.
Okay, so dose me
with some drugs
And i'll be back
before they wear off.
It's perfectly safe.
I'm sorry, peter.
You're just not ready
for that yet.
Okay, so send someone
out with me.
Elle, maybe.
Uh, no.
No, no,
i'm sorry, peter.
Um, that's just
not gonna happen.
I'm never getting
out of here, am i?
Suddenly the room
starts to feel like a cage.
I don't understand.
If they're not gonna help us,
why are we here?
To keep us
from being out there.
Why, because we're dangerous?
No, peter, it's because
we could save the world.
Years ago, i tried
to take my abilities public.
I thought
that if everyone knew
That my blood
had curing powers,
I could help.
How naive i was.
That's why
they put you in here.
Well, if it were possible
to kill me,
They would have,
i assure you.
Instead,
i'm locked up in here.
When i could be curing
your brother.
Nathan.
How?
Just a small amount
of my blood
Could help to heal him.
End his pain.
Even after everything
you've put him through.
So how do we get out?
My daughter is still in there!
Please!
Hawkins!
Hawkins, get out of there!
Please!
[Crying]
mommy!
Mommy!
Thank you!
(Man)
yeah, good one, d.L.
Good job!
(Male anchor)
this is kcei channel 9 news
Reporting on a house fire,
We've just heard,
in the clark county district.
Near tragedy was avoided...
Dad!
Hey.
I saw you on tv!
They keep on playing it
over and over!
You really are a hero.
I guess i am.
Where's your mom?
I don't think she's gotten home
from work yet.
Jessica.
You're not gonna give me
a little jolt?
Why, you want one?
Like you said,
i'm starting to like 'em.
Starting to like you.
Fine, since you asked nicely.
Enough fun for one day?
Day number five
without the meds.
(Adam)
then i think
it's time to try.
Come on, peter.
You can do it.
It's nice
to finally meet you.
You know, for 400 years,
You've held up
pretty well.
Come on,
let's go heal your brother.
[Speaking spanish]
...
Excuse me, chief.
I'm looking
for this girl.
Uh...
She's over there.
Thanks.
Jessica!
Guess again.
Dude, the chick
doesn't know you.
She's my wife.
This is us.
Stay out of this.
Come on, man.
Where am i?
Let's go.
We're going home.
How did you find me?
I told you,
you ain't getting rid of me.
I love you, baby.
Not as much as i love you.
Hey!
Man, let it go.
We're leaving, all right?
Can i play with it?
Damon, come on.
Why would you ask him that?
Don't be so silly.
You're gonna be all right,
aren't you, sugar?
I don't know.
I think i need
to get some help.
Anything you want,
you just gotta ask.
You know that, don't you?
Thank you.
I've taken care of everything.
Plane tickets, money.
Now this.
I'm so sorry, nathan.
How long
until it starts working?
We don't have time
to find out.
They're going to assume
that you'll come
To see your brother.
This is the first place
they'll look.
Come on.
Adam, look, look, look!
(Adam)
good.
Come on.
(Peter)
that was incredible.
His skin was starting to heal
right there in front of us.
He'll be as good as new
by the time he wakes up.
Here, passport.
Plane ticket.
Here's the plan.
You disappointed me, peter!
And just when i thought we were
getting to know each other.
There's a warehouse
in montreal.
121 rue saint-Jacques.
Meet there.
Ugh!
Go after him!
You take me back there,
I'm just
gonna keep escaping.
I'm not taking you back.
You deserve a better fate.
Your mother helped me
when i was in need.
So now you're helping me?
You must start
a new life, peter.
I fear
this is the only solution.
Your secret
is safe with me.
Go with god, my friend.
(Mohinder)
there are many ways
to define
Our fragile existence.
Many ways
to give it meaning.
But it is our memories
that shape its purpose
And give it context.
The private assortment
of images, fears,
Loves, regrets.
Thank you.
Yeah.
(Mohinder)
for it is the cruel irony
of life
That we are destined to hold
the dark with the light,
The good with the evil.
Success with disappointment.
This is what separates us,
What makes us human.
And in the end,
we must fight to hold on to.
I remember.
I remember everything.
Good, then.
Shall we save the world?
TLF