Previously on
...
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't
tear open your head right here.
Because you'll never find your dad.
We need to show progress.
These are our targets.
Hunt them, track them,
and bring them home alive.
If you kill me,
I'll get exactly what I want.
- And what is that?
- They'll see what I've been telling.
They'll know just how dangerous
you people are.
Daphne's alive, Matt.
They have her, alive.
- You're lying to me!
- No, no, no. I won't fight you.
Your mother wants me to move out
of the house for a while.
She's right.
We keep too many secrets
in this family.
- They're just locking people up?
- Believe it, it's happening.
Somebody sent me to warn you.
You must be on a list or something.
I can breathe under water.
You're in danger, we need to get out
of here immediatley.
We're out of whole wheat.
Sorry.
Whatever.
I'm starving.
My mom's going to the market soon,
so hopefully she'll take Lyle.
You can come downstairs,
stretch your legs a bit.
Well, that's a good thing.
I'm starting to stink.
Look I've got the cash. There's a train
leaving for Albuquerque tonight.
Albuquerque?
I don't know anyone in Albuquerque.
That's the point.
You could start over,
become a new person...
- Where no one could find you.
- Yeah, but I never agreed to that.
My family's here, my friends.
My life.
Do you want them to find you?
- Make you disappear forever?
- They're gonna find me anyways.
The government has those spy satellites.
They're probably watching us right now.
- No, we're fine.
- Yeah, but you don't know that.
You're not Harriet Tubman, all right?
And this isn't the underground railroad.
You're just a high school girl,
and you're in way over your head.
If it wasn't for this high school girl,
you might already be dead.
So you want to survive, you'll have
to do exactly what I tell you, got it?
I need to speak with you.
- Hey, mom. What's up?
- Our house money's gone.
You know, the money I keep
in Mr. Muggle's rubber sneaker.
Any idea where that went?
- Maybe Lyle took it.
- I already grilled him.
Per usual, he has no clue.
Okay, fine, I took it.
I was was gonna pay you back.
Claire, I don't get it.
You have a nice allowance.
What do you need $300 for?
- Are you in some kind of trouble?
- No, I just...
What is it, Muggles?
What's under the bed, boy?
What is it?
What is going on with you, Claire?
Nothing.
Nothing, I swear.
I didn't hear anything.
Mrs Bennet, right?
Hi.
Home sweet home.
Not anymore.
Got a one-bedroom in Dupont Circle.
You don't mind that we're
keeping an eye on your daughter,
making sure she's behaving herself?
Claire's a big girl.
She makes her own decisions.
If she does something wrong,
she can live with the consequences.
Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention, please.
Peter Petrelli
has joined Matt Parkman
as priority one.
Charged with kidnapping, assault, and
attempted murder of federal officers.
Both of these men are considered armed
and dangerous, and should be taken down
by any means necessary.
Short of lethal force.
Actually, Senator, my men
have been given the go ahead...
- shoot to kill.
- On whose authority, Danko?
Mine.
Back to work.
Do you really want to push my hand?
Your brother came into my house,
- put a gun to my head.
- I saved your life, if I remember.
You made this personal.
Now I do what I need to do.
- Keep an eye on him for me, will you?
- Matt and Peter kidnapped me
and threatened my life.
What makes you think
I won't shoot them myself?
Sir, we have a lead.
Manhattan.
Matt, you need to stop. Matt.
Matt, you need to stop!
- Stop. Stop.
- What happened?
You've been painting the same image
over and over again all night, okay.
I'm guessing you're trying to find
some answers how to stop this.
- Oh, God.
- Look, we need to leave, okay?
It's too dangerous here.
We gotta go now.
The only thing that matters right now
is finding Daphne and getting her back.
One life at a time.
Look, Matt, when you were
in Bennet's head,
could you see... could you tell
where Daphne was?
- Anything?
- I don't know. I don't know.
I mean I didn't see much.
I saw a hallway.
Did you turn that on?
- Who the hell is Rebel?
- I have no idea.
- Address...
- Daphne!
Someone's listening
to our conversation.
No. He's just hacking in.
This could be information.
- We need this information!
- We don't know who this is.
How can we trust this person, huh?
What if this is a setup?
And what if he's telling the truth?
Go! Go, go, go!
They're gone.
We just missed 'em.
I think
I know where they're headed.
www.Heroes-France.com
This is our last release.
To the Heroes community: thank you.
And keep sharing.
Mom, this is Alex.
He's...
He's my new boyfriend.
That doesn't explain
why he's hiding in your closet.
Right.
We're...
You're really gonna make me
say it out loud?
Absolutely.
We're having sex.
And I know it's wrong.
Very, very wrong.
You do understand that
my daughter is only 17.
I haven't touched her.
Okay?
I barely even make eye contact.
The truth.
He's like me.
He has an ability.
You can tell her.
I can breathe underwater.
He has a power?
And you brought him here?!
Dad was after him.
I didn't know what else to do.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous this is?
Yes, I do, but what was I
supposed to do, just let him...
And on top of that you lied to me!
I am so disappointed.
The agent still there?
Pretty sure you lost him when
you skidded off onto the dirt road.
But just to be sure...
we're clear, officially,
off the grid.
No communications within 50 Miles.
- You sound disappointed.
- Maybe I am.
I mean, the way I see it,
agents catch up with us, we just...
charbroil 'em from the inside out.
I don't want to leave the trail of dead
bodies directly to my father's house.
Why are you doing this?
Parents suck.
You never get what you want
from them.
When I was a kid, I just wanted
my dad to take me fishing. He used my...
arm as an ashtray instead.
Seriously, look.
I have the scars to prove it.
- You should have worn a seat belt.
- Dude, you're hurting me.
- Why don't you want me to see my dad?
- I just... I don't get it.
You don't need to get anything.
My father's the only one with answers.
You're the most powerful dude
on the planet.
I mean, what could you
possibly need?
We don't need anyone.
- What?
Hey, what are you doing?
What the hell?!
If you're hungry, there's
a burger place up the road.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I should have told you about Alex.
What you're doing is extremely
dangerous. Do you understand that?
They were gonna
lock him up for no reason.
And they'll do
the same thing to you.
This is not a game.
Mom, I have to do this.
I know that it's hard for you. You want
a normal life, a regular family.
But that's why Dad and I have to lie.
So we can protect you.
Why?!
Because I'm some fragile
creature in need of protection?
- No, that's not what I meant.
- I know what you meant,
and I've got news for you.
I'm strong.
Much stronger than either
you or your father think.
And I know more
than you think I know.
For example, I know that right now,
there's a van parked outside
on the street.
They're watching us.
They're watching you.
You think she's hiding
the Woolsley kid?
Absolutely.
I'm telling you she's helping him.
Those pool cleaners have been
parked out there for four hours.
Nobody's pool is that dirty.
This is bad.
How you gonna save Alex, Claire?
You can't go out there.
You gonna keep him
up in your closet forever?
No, I'll come up with something.
I have a plan.
I just haven't thought of it yet.
I have an idea.
- You do?
- Yeah.
And you can either
keep me in the dark,
and lie to protect me,
or you can let me help.
I say we definitely let her help.
All right, Mom...
what's the plan?
We're not gonna have a lot of time. Get
in there, do your mind-control magic,
and then we get Daphne
and we're out.
It's impossible. Look at this building.
It's gotta be jam packed full of people.
There are only so many minds
I can control at any given time.
You're right.
What are you doing?
What is that?
- I just borrowed your power.
- Great!
- Now, we can watch each other's backs.
- And you can't fly now.
Which basically rules out
our rooftop escape plan.
See, we gotta get
into the building first.
And two guys pushing thoughts
is better than one.
Come on.
Top floor.
I love doing that.
Right?
Makes it a lot easier.
Cameras are everywhere. Let's go.
In here. Come on.
- You're not allowed in here.
- You're gonna finish your lunch
in the hall and make sure
no one comes in.
I'll just finish my lunch
in the hall.
The plan was to find Daphne.
Gotta know where to look, huh?
Sir, take a look at this.
Okay, this is a problem.
How the hell did they get in here?
Targets are in Operations. Shut down
the computer systems, everything.
- Can't. Someone's hacking in.
- Damn it, just shut it down!
- Let's go!
- Wait.
- Hell with that.
- I wouldn't go out there if I were you.
You're not me.
Son of a bitch.
- What?
- How'd you do on your history exam?
- C-minus.
- Right. You're grounded.
Drivers license, please.
Now.
Thank you.
- That was harsh.
- He's a terrible driver anyway.
To disappear,
you need a new identity.
Trick is
to remove the photo
without tearing it.
There.
I cannot believe you know
how to make a fake I.D.
Where did you learn that?
- Dad?
- No.
Claire, believe it or not,
I was a teenager once.
And an enterprising one,
not unlike you, young lady.
There was this band once
I just had to see.
Def Leopard.
Oh, my God, Rick Savage.
Bass player. So cute!
- What I would have given to...
- Mom!
Sorry.
Alex, you need to change your looks.
Probably using
facial recognition algorithms.
That I learned from your father.
You can find a change of clothes
upstairs.
I appreciate everything
that you're doing.
You know I didn't mean
to drag you into all of this.
You were gonna do it
one way or another, Claire.
Just thought I might help.
I'm sorry for being the way I am.
Making everything so much harder.
Sometimes I just wish I was normal.
Why on earth would you want that?
It would just
make everything easier.
Maybe you and Dad would
still be together.
Honey, your father and I had issues
long before you came around.
- Why'd you marry him?
- 'Cause I fell in love with him,
warts and all.
He was dangerous, handsome.
I accepted everything
that went with that.
But now...
I'm tired of being lied to.
I can't see my marriage anymore.
So it's...
over. You guys are gonna
get a divorce.
I don't know.
Maybe.
But whatever happens
between your father and I
has nothing to do with you.
Okay?
So what are we looking for?
Something happened here.
Yeah, like a million years ago.
I've been here before.
How do you know?
I remember.
My father was here too.
Hello?
Where did you just go?
I can remember my father.
Are you sure?
Positive.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
I still don't know why
you're doing all this for me.
Well, we're an endangered species.
I'm just...
doing my best to try to save us.
Hell, I didn't even know
there were others like me.
- I remember that feeling.
- So...
how do I look?
Like an exceptionally cute boy
who can breathe underwater.
You're special, Claire.
And not just because of the whole
immortal healing thing.
I don't know. Maybe if...
things were different,
we could have gone out or something.
We could have been hiding in your
bedroom for entirely different reasons.
Even if things were different,
I'm not...
really into the whole
relationship thing right now.
It just seems like everyone
who gets married gets a divorce.
Okay, I think it's more like a half
of all marriages
get a divorce or something.
Yeah, but who knows how happy
that other half is.
I don't know.
I still think it's worth it.
Why?
For moments like this.
When someone gets you the way that
no one else does.
It's definitely worth it.
Those agents are coming toward the
house. Alex, come with me. Come with me!
Go.
- Come on, in here.
- They're gonna look here first.
No, you have to whack it. Watch.
Now get down here
and push it with your foot.
Your dad used to store guns, files,
god knows what else in there. He doesn't
think I know about it... careful.
That's right, now close it.
Close it behind you.
Just another day
in the Bennet house.
- Let's go. Let's go!
- That is so weird.
You're not supposed to be here.
I'm off limits.
Top floor is clear.
I told you,
you're wasting your time.
Oh, come on, Claire,
we both know what's going on.
Hot guy, just your type.
Where is he?
He's here. I know it.
Well, that would be wrong,
wouldn't it?
If you two are finished here,
I need you to get the hell
out of my house.
That was close.
I cannot believe the way
you stood up to that bitch.
Let's not celebrate yet.
They're not gonna give up so easily.
The train's leaving soon.
We need to find a way
to get you to the station.
You have both done enough.
Maybe I can slip out back.
Make a run for it.
- No, they'll catch you.
- Maybe not.
We're gonna give him a head start.
- I think I got something. Millbrook?
- Daphne?
She's not here anymore, Matt.
Transferred to a medical facility.
Damn it.
Of course.
Wait, hold on a second.
Look.
- Your friend is back.
- Rebel?
Tell him he screwed us.
Daphne's gone.
He's opening up a file. I think there's
something he wants us to see.
- What is it?
- Come here.
That's us.
That's the entire operation.
They got the whole thing on tape.
- What you doing?
- Copying the files.
What for?
- To expose them.
Look, American citizens
rounded up like this. No warrants.
No trials. This is gonna look great
on the evening news.
Nathan's not gonna know what hit him.
We'll use this as leverage.
Daphne's not here, Matt. There's no
guarantee that we're gonna find her,
- but if we have this...
- We can make a deal.
- Everything we've got for Daphne.
- One life at a time.
Parkman's a telepath.
Incredibly powerful.
But when he uses his ability,
his senses become raw nerves,
and he becomes susceptible.
We exploit that...
- we can disrupt his thoughts.
- That just might work. Let's do it.
- Can't focus. We gotta get outta here.
- I need more time!
It's done! I got it!
Matt!
- What?
30 seconds for what?
It's off. Come on, let's go! Go!
Wait. You do not want to shoot us.
Hey, wait.
Down. Down. Good, good, good.
Don't do it!
This is only gonna end badly.
Don't do this.
- I'll hold 'em, you go.
- What about you?
There's no time.
Go. Go. I'll hold 'em.
You know me.
Nice and easy.
Something terrible happened here.
What are you talking about?
It's a toy car. What's the big deal?
My father did something to me.
Something I forgot.
That's a good thing, right?
Not remembering all the crap
that happens to you when you're a kid.
It eats away at your soul.
Mommy.
So you didn't find Peter?
You're not helping him, are you?
Don't be ridiculous.
Someone's out there
calling themself "Rebel."
Knows we're building 26s.
How it runs.
So I see.
You have all that information too.
Tell me this isn't you.
Of course not. First of all, I don't
know the first thing about computers.
But you could hire someone for that.
And beyond that, I know
who's keeping me safe, Nathan.
I can live my life in peace,
thanks to your generosity.
I would never betray you.
Look, Peter...
he stole a dangerous file.
And there are people
that want him dead because of that.
You're in charge.
You can protect him.
I'm doing all I can to contain
and control these people with abilities,
but there are other people
that want to see them all dead.
Yes, dear. I've had a bit
of experience with all this.
- Hello?
- It's me.
- Pete, where are you?
- Is he okay?
I'm only gonna say this once.
You know what I took.
I've got evidence against you
and your entire organization.
What you've been doing to us.
- What do you want?
- A trade.
Matt Parkman and Daphne Millbrook
for everything that I've got.
That's it?
- Two people? I don't understand.
- Look, if anything happens to them
or me, all the information I've got
goes directly to the nightly news,
do you want that?
- So do we have a deal?
- Fine.
Where do you want to meet?
My son and I are going to a movie.
That threaten
the Federal Government?
You okay?
Yeah. Fine.
You can get off of me now.
Oh, God.
We gotta go.
That way.
End of the block.
Think I see 'em.
- We all set?
- Town car's ready.
Ten minutes to the exchange.
- Your boys know where they're headed?
- Exactly where your brother wants.
- 4001 North Nebraska Avenue.
- Next to the network news.
- I don't suppose that's a coincidence.
- Peter's no dummy.
Daphne and Matt ready for transport?
No, Senator, they're not.
We're not making a deal.
What's he talking about?
What the hell are you talking about?
I have another plan.
You realize if my brother's harmed
in any way, copies of those files
are gonna make their way to every
news organization in this country.
Our entire operation
will be compromised.
I'm aware of the situation.
Then get Millbrook
and Parkman released right now,
put them in the car,
and get them down to the parking lot.
Or do you want to disobey
a direct order?
I'm following orders,
Senator, just not yours.
The United States Government will
not make deals with terrorists.
Those were the President's
exact words.
Despite your endless protestations,
your brother's a terrorist.
Terrorist?
My brother's not a terrorist.
Target spotted
approaching parking lot.
I'm en route.
Hold your stations.
Just stay out of my way.
Let's go.
Just remember,
Peter can hear your thoughts.
Where are they, Bennet?
Matt, Daphne.
- Listen to me.
- Are you in there?
- Come with me.
- Matt?
And nobody has to get hurt.
Peter... listen to me!
They're not here.
You're being set up.
Time to die, Petrelli.
Just a little further.
Gimme the kill shot.
I'm trying to save your life.
Get out of here, he's gonna...
Are you all right?
- It's just a scratch. He'll be fine.
- What do you want, a thank you?
Why... are you doing this, Nathan?
Doing what, saving your life
or trying to save the world?
Perhaps there's
a better way of doing it.
This hasn't turned out
exactly the way I wanted it to.
Okay? I'm aware of that. There's
a lot of different agendas going on.
All leading to killing us.
You realize you're responsible for that.
Yeah, I do.
It's out of control, and it's my fault.
But I can fix it.
In fact, I'm the only one
who can fix it.
- Why? 'Cause you're one of us?
- Because I'm the only one
who really cares if
you're alive or not, Pete.
Come with me, okay,
and I promise you'll be treated well.
- Don't do this, Nathan.
- It's okay.
Ma, please.
You have my word.
- I know you'll take care of me.
- I will.
Because you love me.
Pete, I'm just trying to help.
Bye, Nathan.
No, Nathan, don't.
You give me one good reason why
I shouldn't go after him right now.
Because the game has changed.
I've seen it,
and you need to be ready.
And we have some
breaking news for you now.
Rumors have surfaced
that the U.S. Government
has recently broadened
the reach of the Patriot Act.
Thanks, Brian. Well, tonight sources
have provided our news bureau
some startling footage
taken directly
from an unnamed government
agency right here in Washington.
Now, this video shows
American citizens
in hoods and restraints in what
appears to be a clear violation
of their constitutional rights.
Is the government running
a secret military organization
with the authority
to disregard civil liberty?
So what, we're just gonna
stay here all day?
The guy's an ass, plain and simple.
All right, I told you parents su...
He killed my mother.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I mean, I've been trying
to tell you that he's a jerk.
You've been trying to tell me, really?
When did that happen?
'Cause all I can remember
is the cute little stories
of you two bird watching
around the neighborhood.
You made him sound like
Mr. freakin' Rogers.
I was just waiting
for the right time.
Hey, I got an idea.
Why don't we drive up to Canada,
because we're close to the border.
We could rob some old ladies.
That's not gonna happen.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because you're here,
and I need to express my feelings.
You used me
for some joy ride, an escape.
I got news for you, kid.
There is no escape.
There is only pain.
And you can never outrun it no matter
what you do, no matter where you go.
Go home to your mother, Luke.
You're not gonna kill me?
Seems a little on the nose.
Where you going?
To find my father.
'Cause now that
I've seen the truth...
I want him to die.
What the hell are you doing?
Must've realized there'd be
consequences for your actions.
Yeah, when that story breaks,
you're exposed.
And the world will see
what you're doing.
You're hunting innocent people.
You're not innocent.
The world just doesn't realize
how dangerous you are.
Now
they will,
and they'll beg me
to hunt you down and kill you.
The enemy has a face, Parkman.
It's you.
No, I don't want to hurt anyone.
Really?
To me...
you look exactly like a terrorist.
Why did you...
You gonna miss having
a cute guy in your closet?
A little.
You were incredible.
Nice to know I still have
a few tricks up my sleeve.
I love you.
Just the way you are.
I wouldn't trade this life
for anything.
Me either.
So I made popcorn.
Figure we could watch a movie.
Some sappy love story.
Ah, sounds perfect.
I'll be right down.
Hey, Barbie.
You!
I got a message from
someone named Rebel.
I need your help, Barbie.