Torchwood. Outside the government,
beyond the police.
Tracking down alien life on earth
and arming the human race
against the future.
The 21st century is when everything
changes and you've got to be ready.
Diane Holmes, pilot.
Please, don't go.
Come on. Aaargh!
I didn't want saving.
This programme
contains some strong language.
CAR HORN BEEPS
TOSH SPEAKS JAPANESE
It's my grandfather's
88th birthday today.
I thought you'd done this for me.
88 is a joyous year
for the Japanese.
I'm off to London
to watch men throw rice.
You get that in the Balti
after stop-tap.
OK, down to business.
What have we got?
The Ritz Dancehall.
It's been derelict since 1989
but someone's complained about
hearing music...
music from the 1940s.
Shhh!
Listen.
MUSIC PLAYS SOFTLY
You coming up?
WINGS FLAP
Wow!
Look at the chandelier.
No neon lights back then.
Just dashing young soldiers
and pretty young ladies.
And as they danced, the girls
would look into their partners'
eyes, smile softly and say...
Jack! Mind my laptop.
I was thinking more along
the lines of, "How long
before you head off to war?"
MACHINE BEEPS
Come on. There's nothing here
but memories and dust.
BIG BAND MUSIC PLAYS
VOICES CHAT AND LAUGH
They look so real.
They're not ghosts.
It's a simple temporal shift.
And it's beautiful!
We should get out.
Do call again. I would love to.
It's night!
Where's the SUV?
Has it been stolen?
No.
We have.
ALARM BEEPS
What the hell is that?
Tosh's rift monitor programme.
She set it to alert me if there
were any further movements.
The rift's been opening
more and more recently.
Yeah, well, I've noticed that.
Doesn't take a genius.
Tosh reckons the equations
are forming a pattern.
I should call her.
She may have readings her end
and this is over my head.
Um, why wasn't I told about this?
Well, you've been off, haven't you?
The line's dead.
It's no use. It's dead.
I can't get through to the Hub.
Let's get back inside.
That's where we were
when we crossed.
'Gwen, can you get down
to Sage Street?'
Yep. What's up? 'We need Tosh.'
The rift monitor sounded. She's
with Jack but their phones are dead
and we can't access her files.
'OK, I'll get down there now'.
We really are in 1941.
What if we can't get back?
Flotsam and jetsam slips through
all the time. We'll get back.
Look on the bright side.
Gives you one hell of an excuse for
your party. I have a life there.
And they can't help us because
I have the latest readings in here.
People are staring at us.
We need to try to blend in.
It's easy for you to say.
I'm the only Asian here. Don't worry.
You're with the Captain.
Hey. I've got into Tosh's files,
all her reports.
See there, December 24th.
That's when Diane
flew through the rift.
I had to let her go.
You were in love with her,
weren't you?
If Tosh knows a way
of opening the rift,
maybe we can get Diane back.
Jack would never allow it. Opening
the rift could devastate the city.
# My love is true
# And just for you
# I would do most anything
at any time... #
Water, please, and a brandy.
I haven't seen you in here before.
Three and six, please, sir.
I'll, er...
get them.
Thank you. On one condition. What?
# Come to me,
my melancholy baby... #
Why's George dancing with a Jap?
The SUV's here.
They must be here somewhere.
Jack?
Tosh!
MUSIC DRIFTS DOWN
Jack!
# Come to me, my melancholy... #
Do you mind?
I'm only borrowing her, mate. Maybe
she doesn't want to be borrowed.
You want to make something of it?
You can always dance with me.
OK, I'll lead. You follow.
Come on, Tosh.
CROWD GASP
Jack!
Jack, we're meant to be blending in.
Cut it out, kiddo.
Sorry about that.
The men are a bit lively tonight.
It's last day of OTU tomorrow.
Apologise to the gentleman, George.
I was only dancing.
I think it was your fist
he didn't like, not your foxtrot.
I'm sorry.
It's OK. You barely got me.
I think the lady also deserves
an apology.
I'm sorry.
Apology accepted.
Let's get a drink, George.
Hey, are you a volunteer too? Yeah.
BOTH SPEAK AT ONCE: I'm Captain...
You go first. I'm Captain
Jack Harkness. 133rd Squadron.
Look this way, please.
Right, the Ritz Dancehall,
opened in 1932, shut down in 1989.
Due to be demolished in one week.
Now, the reported music
is from the 1940s.
Why is a ghost job taking them this
long? All those young soldiers...
Owen, look.
There.
One more for the record, sir.
I insist.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I should be heading off..
Hey, I didn't catch your names.
Toshiko Sato.
I'm Captain James Harper. 71st.
71st, that's where I'm hoping
to be posted. What's your poison?
Maybe later. My friend and I were
in the middle of something. Sure.
Why does that man have your name?
I'm lost enough here
without you holding back on me!
It's not my name.
It's his.
I took his.
But I didn't realise he was...
so hot!
Jack!
I know too much.
Then...share.
You wouldn't want that. Trust me.
We have to get back.
What's in here?
I've got half the equation in here.
The other half's back at the Hub.
If I can find some way of getting
these figures back to base,
they can combine them, open the rift
and bring us back through. Come on.
I heard music earlier.
If I can hear them,
maybe they can hear me.
They've got to come back.
WINGS FLAP OVERHEAD
Jack!
Tosh!
What?
I thought I heard my name.
OK, so we use Tosh's information
to open the rift
and bring them back.
We can't.
Half the equation's missing.
It can't be. It must be somewhere
else. Let me try. It's not there.
It might be in her laptop. Which
she never goes anywhere without.
Shit. Shit!
No-one here. Come on, quick.
It works! LAPTOP: 'Your battery
is running low'.
Just take down everything,
in case it dies.
I'm not used to writing with these
things! Don't press so hard.
Oh, no. LAPTOP: 'Your battery
is low.' Can you read that?
Plus one over five a...
sine two eight X.
LAPTOP: 'Your battery...'
You got everything you need? I just
need the coordinates of the hall,
so I can integrate them
into the equation.
Then we need to get the information
back to the Hub.
What are you doing in here?
Who are you?
Captain...James Harper.
And this is Toshiko Sato,
friend and mathematician.
I'm Bilis, the manager.
You're not in full uniform, Captain.
On leave.
48 hours.
That's an interesting camera.
It takes photographs instantly. I
didn't know they could do that yet.
And I didn't know they made
an attache case out of metal.
CLOCK CHIMES
Where did you get it?
London. I'm from there.
I should go back, dear.
They're coming for us now.
I've had a good look around
but the doors were locked.
MUSIC RESUMES INSIDE
Can I help you?
I'm the caretaker.
Bilis Manger, at your service.
Hello. Could you open it all up
for me? I think some of my friends
got locked in. Follow me.
Thank you.
Pearl Harbour, Jack. Doesn't happen
till the end of the year.
Granddad stayed in London
but he was persecuted.
If I stay here,
what will happen?
I'll take care of you.
This period,
you look like you fit in.
Have you been here before?
Yeah.
I can't explain
but I served in the war in 1941.
I was undercover.
I needed a false identity,
so I took...his name.
Who were you
before you took his name?
Why him? It was convenient.
But if you chose his identity
to steal, then he...?
Dies, in battle.
When?
Tomorrow.
And I say, "Look, love,
it's raining bombs and fire,
so get down that cellar."
And she says, "I can't,
there's rats down there!"
So, who's the best navigator here?
Tim. He can't fly for toffee,
but at least when he goes down,
he'll know exactly where he is.
Why don't we chat over here?
HE WOLF-WHISTLES
I give the public schoolboy
a fortnight.
That boy's come a long way
in five weeks.
As long as you boys remember
your training, you'll be all right.
Glad you came. Shall we sit down?
Why were your friends in here,
anyway? Just a silly dare.
Someone said it was haunted.
You look worried, dear.
I'll make you a nice cup of tea.
The sun rose this morning at 08.12,
21 by 7 degrees.
I note it down every day.
It's a bit silly, I suppose.
It's fantastic.
You must have seen some action.
Let's just say the enemy comes
in many guises.
Yeah, I can't wait
to give Jerry what for.
How many did you kill in the Battle
of Britain, sir? 26, wasn't it?
You've read that story
countless times.
No-one's as fast as him.
Hasn't lost a man yet.
Care for a drink, Captain?
I'll just have water, thanks.
All right.
Hello, Jack. I know you're having
a night with the men
but I thought I'd look in,
if that's all right.
Yeah.
Good to see you.
Is anyone expecting you?
Yes.
Perhaps you should call them,
otherwise they may think
you've disappeared too.
I'll put the kettle on.
CLOCK CHIMES
Anything your end?
There are no more photographs
of Jack and Tosh after that night.
That's encouraging.
Yeah, unless the bombs got 'em.
The manager, Bilis Manger,
kept them for posterity.
Bilis Manger?
That's the name of the caretaker.
Can't be the same guy, can it?
Not old enough.
But he does look a bit
out of his time. He wears a cravat.
Gwen, he's in the photo
with Jack and Tosh.
He's the answer. He came through
the rift. Find out what he's doing.
No. Get out, Gwen. Wait for backup.
We can't lose him. Nor Gwen!
Maybe this is a trap.
He could be sucking us
back through time one by one.
Get out of there, Gwen. I'm sorry
but who put you in charge?
I've got what I need.
Now all I have to do
is find a way to leave a message
for the team on something
that will last across time. OK.
I haven't seen you two here before.
Is she with you?
Nah, she's after Tim.
Why else would she let him
bore her to death about navigation?
Maybe she's a spy. The Chinese are on
our side, aren't they? I'm Japanese.
You're hardly an ally, then.
Leave it, Audrey.
So whose side are you on?
What's in the bag? Nothing.
If you've got nothing to hide,
open the bag! She can't.
Her work is top secret.
She's a decoder for the Brits.
Without her, we'd have no way of
defending the country. To Toshiko.
Toshiko!
I need Bilis's camera.
Photographs last, don't they?
Sure you don't want me to come with
you? Oh, you can't run out on me.
I've just got you a drink.
I'm fine. You carry on.
To a fellow captain.
So, what brings you down here?
I had to rest up.
Injured my back bailing over Kent.
That's his excuse for not dancing.
Mind if I join you?
Sure. Why not?
Starting to be a habit.
I just wanted to try it out.
This little beauty is very unusual
and rare, not unlike yourself.
Don't go without this.
I could think of better things
to photograph than numbers, my dear.
Do call again.
What are you doing?
Owen!
We haven't got the missing numbers.
We'll improvise with
the Rift Manipulator. We can't.
It's risky enough with the equation.
If we don't do it properly, anything
can happen. Bombs are falling.
They're stuck in the middle
of the Cardiff Blitz.
It's our duty to get 'em out.
JACK'S LAUGHTER ECHOES
Jack?
Open the rift and the world could
suffer. We could all get sucked in.
Who knows what will come out?
This is about Diane! When will you
accept she chose to leave you?
Whereas your cyber-girlfriend
stuck around. Not that she had
a choice, wired in the cellar.
That was different. Yeah. Mainly
because Diane didn't try and kill us
and she also happened
to be a human being. Stop it.
Not some monster. I thought
she was still Lisa. I loved her.
You only knew Diane for a week.
And it wasn't enough.
Maybe the Manipulator
can calculate the missing figures.
It isn't working. Good.
Jack would never have wanted us
to use it this way.
There's a piece missing.
We've got to find it.
Maybe you should go home.
You don't have any power over me.
OK, Ianto, we'll play it your way -
safe and boring.
BUG BAND TUNE FINISHES
PEOPLE APPLAUD
So, what's your next mission?
Careless talk costs lives.
I should go anyway. No, I didn't
mean that to... It's all right.
I can get a lift if I leave now.
I'd better stay here.
Aren't you leaving tomorrow night?
You sick of us Welsh already?
Yeah, that's why I'm still
fighting for you.
I'll be in touch
when I'm next on leave.
Nancy...
it's been a good few weeks.
Was that it?
She's a sweet kid, but I need
to look after my men tonight.
It's their last day tomorrow.
Go after her.
Kiss her goodbye.
Anything can happen tomorrow.
It's just a routine training
exercise. I'm hardly gonna die.
That's when they catch you,
when you least expect it.
You don't know what's ahead.
Kiss her...goodbye.
Nancy?
I love you.
That just made things
20 times worse.
Now she thinks
she's in love with me.
Hey, her falling for you
is hardly my fault.
Play it coo in front of your men,
but not me. It's OK to be scared.
A captain has to keep his head.
A captain needs to explain risks,
tell his men what to expect.
So what do I do?
Tell 'em I saw a young boy
get shot in the eyes mid-flight?
I understand.
Do you? Did you hear him on the
radio, yelling for his mom,
while the Messerschmitts shot him
blew his plane apart?
All I can hear on the radio...
Is screams.
I went to war when I was a boy.
I was with my best friend.
We got caught crossing the border
over enemy lines. They tortured him
because he was weaker.
They made me watch him die.
And they let me go.
Who were they?
The worst possible creatures
you can imagine.
I persuaded him to join up.
I said it would be an adventure.
He hadn't lived.
Have any of us?
OK, team...
I hope you like treasure hunts.
No sign of Bilis leaving the area.
Er, where are you off to?
The dancehall.
Bilis's office.
He must know how the rift works.
Maybe we'll find a clue there.
What would Jack and Tosh do?
How would they try and help us?
Bilis!
I need more equations, Gwen.
What happened here, Tosh?
No.
AIR RAID SIREN WAILS
BOMB WHISTLES THROUGH AIR
THEY SCREAM
Toshiko!
Toshiko! Jack!
This way!
I didn't get the first part
in the photo. The rest is outside.
If they find it, they'll
keep looking, won't they? Yeah.
IANTO: 'Be careful, Gwen.
Bilis is still around'.
Owen, where are you? 'I'm in the
building. Where's Bilis's office?'
It's at the far end of the corridor.
I'll keep looking out here.
Yes!
BOMBS BOOM OVERHEAD
Thing is, you could be
the last girl I ever kiss.
I've got to finish the message.
Pencil will fade.
I need to find something else.
Airtight. This'll do.
# There'll be bluebirds over
# The white cliffs of Dover
# Tomorrow
# Just you wait and see... #
OK.
Shit!
CLOCK CHIMES
ALARM CLOCK BEEPS
Timepieces.
I didn't find any equations.
Um, I'll get back to the Hub.
I'll keep looking here, then.
Yeah, you do that.
Yes.
Of course I'm scared.
I'm going to check everywhere
for the other figures.
I'm not going to leave Jack now.
# There'll be bluebirds over... #
SONG FADES
ALL-CLEAR SIGNAL WAILS
Let the dancing continue!
ALL CHEER AND APPLAUD
I've finished.
The rest of the equation is hidden.
What happened?
I slipped. I've got a first-aid kit
in the van.
Scotch, Captain?
I'd like some time in private
with Captain Harper.
Ianto? Yeah, it's me.
I've found it.
It's written in blood.
Gwen's found the rest
of Tosh's readings.
What's she got for us?
Cos sine squared, axcx = x over 2.
No, I need at
least three more numbers, Gwen.
They must be somewhere else.
'No, they're not'.
Well, how do you know?
Somebody scraped out
the final numbers.
Tosh has written
a message at the end.
It says,
"Tell my family I love them."
Why did you make me
kiss her goodbye?
I just think you should live
every night like it's your last.
Make tonight
the best night of your life.
You're alive -
right here, right now.
Your men are fine.
What are you trying to say?
Go to her.
Go to your woman
and lose yourself in her.
Maybe I should.
Yeah.
Is Toshiko your woman? No.
There's no-one.
Go to her.
It still won't work. There's a piece
missing. Bilis had it all along.
We still don't have
all the equation.
Maybe the machine can work it out.
MACHINE BURSTS INTO LIFE
Owen!
MACHINE ENGINE SPLUTTERS OUT
There must be something in the safe.
We need better instructions.
You can't open it. You've no right.
I'm second in command.
I have got every fucking right.
There's stuff we don't know about.
That's how Jack likes it.
I won't play with his toys, Ianto!
"Rhea Silva,
the god of war's missus."
And a nine-digit number.
Not so clever, Jack.
Blueprints for the Rift machine.
I thought you'd gone.
This could be your last chance.
That's why I came back.
I might have to leave
before the night is over.
Well, then make the most of now.
WOMAN LAUGHS
We need lovers' corner,
if you don't mind, boys.
Of course. I was just discussing
strategies with the captain.
We'll go somewhere else.
No.
You've told me all I need to know.
There's instructions in here.
This isn't a random act of madness.
It's a trap!
Bilis wanted you to find it. Why?
To provoke the rift. To incite
total chaos and destruction.
All the reports of the haunted
dancehall were anonymous.
What if it was him?
Please, listen to me! I'm tired
of being in awe of the rift.
I'm tired of living with Jack's
secrets. We don't even know who he
is. He's our leader. Not any more.
Get out of my way.
Ianto! Ugh!
Tomorrow is their last
training exercise,
just another day.
They go out on a sortie
and are surprised
by two formations of Messerschmitts.
He destroys three of the enemy.
His men listen to his whoops of joy
over the radio.
Then it all goes quiet.
He can't bail out
because his whole plane is on fire.
But his men
all make it back to safety.
Put the key down.
Or I'll shoot.
Who were you?
A conman.
That's why I took his name,
falsified his records
so it seemed he was still alive.
How did you end up in Torchwood?
Someone saved my life.
Brought me back from death.
And ever since then, it's been like
they're keeping me for something
and I don't know what it is.
I'm sorry for dragging you
into this.
It was my choice.
I'll look after you.
But there's nothing I can do
for him.
You have to let Diane go.
Like I did with Lisa.
Don't compare yourself to me.
You're just a tea boy.
I'm much more than that.
Jack needs me.
In your dreams, Ianto.
In your sad wet dreams when
you're his part-time shag, maybe.
That rift took my lover
and my captain.
So if I die trying to beat it, then
it will all be in the line of duty.
Aaargh!
MACHINE STARTS UP
You don't know what you've done.
# That certain night
# The night we met
# There was magic abroad in the air
# There were angels dancing
at the Ritz
# And a nightingale sang
in Berkeley Square... #
# ..I may be right
# I may be wrong... #
What's he doing?
# ..But I'm perfectly willing
to swear... #
RIFT BLASTS OPEN
Jack!
Jack, we need to get out!
Jack, you have to!
We need you!
I have to go.
It's my duty.
Oh, you made it! You made it!
You made it.
Oh, Tosh, come here, come here,
come here! I'm fine!
GWEN LAUGHS
I knew we did the right thing,
opening the rift.
Still no sign of Bilis.
World didn't end after all, did it?
Good job you're a crap shot.
I was aiming for your shoulder.
It was wartime, I know,
but it was beautiful.
There were angels dancing
at the Ritz.
- Jack...
- Let me.
He would have been so proud
that you took his name.
Because here you are,
saving the world.
To Captain Jack.