My name is Michael Westen.
I used to be a spy until...
We got a burn notice.
You're blacklisted.
when you're burned,
You've got nothing...
no cash, no credit,
No job history.
you're stuck in whatever city
They decide to dump you in.
Where am I?
Miami.
you do whatever work
Comes your way.
you rely on anyone
Who's still talking to you.
a trigger-happy
Ex-girlfriend...
Should we shoot them?
...an old friend who's
Informing on you to the FBI...
You know spies --
A bunch of bitchy little girls.
...family, too...
Is that your mom again?
...if you're desperate.
Someone needs your help.
bottom line... until
You figure out who burned you,
you're not going anywhere.
for most people,
A night out at the Miami clubs
is a chance to see and be seen.
when you're under
Government surveillance,
it's a different story.
you still want to know
Who's watching you,
but the reasons are
A little different.
Looks like
You've had visitors.
Took them long enough.
sprinkle a mixture of flour
And dayglo powder on your floor
before you go out,
and you'll know whether
You've had any visitors
and what they were after.
A three-man team?
Sounds about right...
Two sneakers and a loafer.
They're not terribly careful,
Your surveillance.
you don't always have
To get that clever, though.
sometimes they want you to know
What they're up to.
They weren't hiding.
I miss your FBI detail.
They were really kind of sweet.
The feds were errand boys.
But these guys,
On the other hand,
Might actually know
Something useful.
Honestly, I don't know
Why they bother.
They should just put a bullet in
Your head and be done with it.
Apparently, I'm more valuable
Alive than dead.
But I'm sure they'll take it
Under advisement.
You think
They're listening?
Yeah, mom.
Michael, there are men here
Outside the house with guns!
What?
What men?
I don't know.
They've been watching.
They're coming inside.
Call the cops.
Call them right now.
Take the van
And cover the street.
Not a problem.
Stop right there.
It's okay.
Mom?
Mom!
14 minutes?
Aw, I figured you for 12.
It's probably
Those causeways, though.
You'll have to forgive
My sketchy Miami geography.
I'm new in town.
We nearly got lost
Coming from your place.
Mom, you okay?
They cut the phone lines.
I couldn't call the police.
They broke in...
It's okay.
You want to tell me
Who you are?
I'm the new man
In your life.
It's okay.
You pissed off
A lot of people,
Getting your hands on
The homeland-security directive
Authorizing
Your burn notice.
You're
A private citizen now.
You're not supposed
To touch that kind of thing.
I asked nicely.
You wanted attention
From someone
A little higher up
On the food chain.
That's about right.
It's your lucky day.
Here I am.
And here I will stay...
Until you back off.
Michael,
Why are they doing this?
Are you in some kind
Of trouble?
Not now.
Not now, mom.
Your problem is with me,
Not with her.
You have no business
Coming here.
Oh, no, but we do.
See, you're a major
Security risk.
You just assaulted
Two federal agents.
Go ahead. Arrest me.
I'd like to take a look
At the indictment.
Wouldn't you, now?
Yeah.
Listen, you be a good boy,
And I'll get out of your hair.
Until then,
I'll need to keep looking.
God!
Sorry.
You can't be too careful.
there are two kinds
Of government surveillance...
the kind that's there
To look for something
and the kind that's just there
To make your life difficult.
Http://www.ragbear.com==-
Mike, you get problems
Like that, call me.
I still got pull
In that department.
Maybe I can get them
To go home.
I don't want them to go home.
I need this guy in town.
I need to know who he is
And what he knows.
I can help you
With that, then.
I tried.
I got your voice mail.
Yeah, sorry about that.
It's the new lady friend.
She puts a lot of demands on my
Time, if you know what I mean.
I don't, and I don't
Want to know.
Well, at least
I'm off your couch.
So, who do you think
Was at your mom's?
They sound like charmers.
You tell me. What are
Your FBI friends telling you?
Nothing.
They'd be pissed
If they found out
Somebody pulled rank
On them.
These intelligence outfits...
They're springing up
Faster than frickin' starbucks
These days.
Let me know
If you hear anything.
Mmm, where are you going?
I got to scrounge up a job.
My mom's house
Needs remodeling.
I might have to call lucy.
What about
My s.e.a.l. Buddy,
That thing
I was telling you about?
Is that a job or a favor?
No, it's a job.
It's real money.
He's a great guy, Mike.
He saved my ass several times.
He's a boat-repo guy.
It's a tough job.
He just needs some muscle.
Muscle? Great.
Hmm.
There she is.
There you go, Sammy.
Thank you, doll.
Plant one right there.
You sure I can't
Get you anything?
No, thank you.
I have out-of-town guests
I need to attend to.
You have fun.
Mike, call me, now.
you can tie up
A lot of resources
by keeping
A bugged phone line open.
as long as it's open,
they're supposed
To keep listening.
you have reached the consulate
Of the commonwealth of belize.
leave your message
After the tone.
D-d-7-2-4-7-8.
say a few cryptic
Things now and then
and they'll be stuck
In their little van,
trying to figure out
What the hell you're doing.
5:00 p.m., march 15th, 20%.
they can't go home,
Can't grab a bite to eat,
can't take a leak.
...and a limited number
Of viewers
who are also gonna be
Lucky enough to buy...
and the longer they're stuck in
A van with a set of headphones,
the more you can find out
About them.
just look at that round
Cut... Brilliant.
Appreciate you coming, Mike.
Sam's told me a good deal
About you.
Really?
Come on, Mike,
Don't be like that.
Virg is one of us.
S.e.a.l. Teams,
Panama, iraq, china.
Last time I checked,
I had top-secret clearance.
But I haven't checked
In a while.
Sam tells me
You're some kind of spy...
...or used to be.
Y'all want a beer?
Yeah, I'll take one.
I knew you'd want one, Sam.
What about you, Mike?
It might be hot
In that jacket.
No, I'm good.
What's the job?
Pain in my ass.
I was supposed to repo
A donzi 27 zr
For a guy who's done me
A few favors.
But I went
To pick the thing up,
And a couple of jamaicans
Tuned me up but good.
Damn embarrassing.
Oh, come on, they had 30 years
On you and a baseball bat.
Well, I am
On blood thinners.
Goddamn pills
Make me light-headed.
Oh, hell, that's no excuse.
Anyway, now I'm in a bind.
Word gets out I can't hack it...
Ffft!... I'm done.
I'm not one to ask for help,
But there it is.
That's a fast boat.
Smuggling?
It's a high-performance
Speedboat
In a crappy, little hellhole
Of a marina.
What the hell else
Is it gonna be?
Maybe cuban cigars,
Maybe grass...
Problem is,
These guys have guns,
And they like
To wave them around.
Listen,
Just pick the thing up,
Point "a" to point "b,"
Ffft!
Oh, is that all?
Point "a" to point "b"?
Well, when you put it
That way...
All right, look, I'd go
Down there with you guys,
But these guys know me.
2 grand each,
Cash on delivery.
My buddy mason
Is gonna be waiting for it
At a repair warehouse
Up on 23rd.
Mike, we get Fi involved,
We got a three-man team.
Do it just like that personnel
Carrier in bulgaria.
I mean, look, I got to get my
New lady friend something nice,
And you sure as hell
Need the cash.
Free gator steaks in it
For you...
Best in the everglades.
I'll think about it.
You're towing my car.
Hey! Yeah.
There might be evidence in here.
Evidence?
There's a busted 8-track
And one of my mom's lamps
I'm trying
To piece back together.
Well, I guess
We'll find out, won't we?
Oh, by the way,
We noticed suspicious activity
On your phone line,
So we took care of it for you.
Oh, thanks.
Alas, you won't have
Phone service for a while.
Hey, you want a stick
Of gum?
Yeah, thanks.
I didn't catch your name.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, Sam, about that job...
I'm in.
Oh, oh, and tell virgil
I need to borrow his truck.
Mmm, he's cute.
We're gonna take his boat.
I doubt he's gonna
Give you his phone number.
Who knows?
I've had stranger dates.
So, what's
Your cover i.d., Mikey?
I think I'm gonna go with...
Devoted employee.
How's...homer?
Homer.
I like it.
as a rule, spies don't like
Dealing with cops.
covert ops are illegal
By definition.
if they were legal, they
Wouldn't need to be covert.
Want me to set up
That one, Mike?
The sailboat?
Yeah, that's good.
still, the police
Can be useful
if you need a little insurance
Against people shooting.
Yeah, hi.
Um, boy, I don't know
If this is the sort of thing
I should be calling
The police about, but...
Oh, I'm at the marina
Down on waverly street.
Yeah, I saw some men
Loading bags full
Of white powder into a sailboat.
Kind of creeped me out, you know?
Hey, there!
Can I help you?
Yes, sir.
I'm here for that boat.
Oh, you're with
The repo man, huh?
My boss, hell of a guy.
He's like a father to me.
You beat him up pretty good.
Yeah, that was unfortunate.
I tried to explain
The situation to him, you know?
But he forced me
To clarify my position.
This is my property.
We've got paperwork
That says otherwise.
Hmm, well,
That paperwork is misinformed.
Hmm. Why don't we ask the police
To sort this out?
I mean,
They're right over there.
I could holler over to them
Right now
And ask them
To come sort this out.
That's a nice piece.
You gonna shoot me with it?
Probably gonna have to
Shoot her, too.
It might be tough to explain
To the cops.
Or I could just
Start screaming.
The way I see it,
If this is your boat,
These guns are registered,
And you're 100% squeaky clean...
You have nothing
To worry about.
But if not...
All right.
You're making
A serious mistake, man.
You do this...
There's no
Turning back, you know?
I can't leave
Without the boat.
So, if you're gonna shoot us,
Get it done.
Otherwise,
We got places to be.
You know, we'll deal with this
Another time,
When I got a little bit
More privacy.
Ooh, leather seats.
I can see why
You're so attached to it.
Pretty lady,
Don't get too comfortable.
I'll see you soon, huh?
I promise.
Easy now.
Whoa!
What you looking for
Back there?
He was confident
He was getting his boat back.
I want to make sure
There's no surprises.
Well, people get attached
To their vehicles.
I had a cadillac eldorado once.
That thing was part
Of the family.
Gps tracker.
That's how our jamaican friend
Was gonna find us.
Son of a bitch.
Sam, how well
Do you know virgil?
You trust him?
He's like a brother, Mike.
I mean,
The guy saved my life.
when you're going
Into a meeting cold
with people
You know nothing about,
you have to be extra careful.
pay attention to every detail.
map out an escape route or two
Just in case.
and never, ever show up
As yourself.
You mason?
Yeah.
Who the hell are you?
You waiting
On a boat delivery?
Yeah, where's virgil?
Oh, he can't make it.
He sent me instead.
I'm one of virgil's drivers.
My name's homer.
Hold on, homer.
Not coming?
What do you mean?
He's supposed to be here.
You know how he is.
Well, I got your boat outside
With my team.
Team?
You got other guys outside?
another thing you look for
is people who seem overly upset
That things have changed,
details that shouldn't
Matter so much.
Damn! Wow! That is
A twin supercharged sterling.
Whoo-wee! I got a 400 horsepower
Back at home.
I work on it a little bit.
some tip-offs aren't so subtle,
like a detonator
Sitting on enough chloride
to incinerate a city block.
Why don't we move this along?
What do you say?
All right,
Let me go get your boat.
Well, we're all gonna
Go get the boat.
No need to get gun happy.
Calm down.
Put it out!
It's clear.
I don't think
They followed you.
It got pretty hairy
Back there.
How well do you know
These clients of yours?
You mean mason?
Like I said,
He did me a few favors.
He had all the paperwork.
It seemed
Like a simple delivery.
Mason and his friends are cops,
Dirty cops.
What are you
Talking about?
Oh, I wouldn't lie to me
Again, virgil.
They had department-issue glocks
On hip holsters,
A late-model crown vic
In the parking lot.
In fact,
I think they knew you.
You know what it sounded like
To me?!
they do know me!
From some boat repos
That went bad.
They came to me!
I got a daughter in tampa!
They took pictures!
They said they'd hurt her
If I didn't help!
Why do they want that boat
So bad?
How the hell do I know?
It's a donzi 27 zr.
They were ready
To incinerate it and you.
I mean, it's a nice boat,
But it's not worth
Killing the four of us
And blowing up a boatyard.
Sam, you know I wouldn't
Do this to you.
I may be a son of a bitch
For dragging you into this,
But if I had
Any other choice... Come on!
Please. Please.
Hey, Mike.
You know how I told you virgil
Saved my life and all that?
The truth is it's...
It's more complicated.
Back in '84,
I was in east germany.
I made some mistakes,
Mike...
Did some stuff
I shouldn't have.
Virgil gave me
A second chance
When I sure as hell
Didn't deserve it.
I owe him, Mike.
Sam...
It's his daughter.
Look, if you're not in on this,
I got to handle it myself.
You can't handle this
By yourself, Sam.
Yeah, I know.
We need a place
To stash him.
And my third tour,
I was laid up for six months
With infected feet and some kind
Of agent orange disease.
Oh, that's horrible.
Hurt all over,
Kind of achy.
They thought
I was after disability.
I know tone  they don't bel
Exactly.
So, when I got back,
I got into boat repo,
And that was fine
For a while.
Till, of course,
My wife passed away,
And then things
Went downhill.
I think we can skip
The life story.
Virgil's only going to be here
A night, maybe two.
Where's the hatchet, mom?
Try the utility drawer.
I don't want to be
An imposition.
I can sleep out in the back
If you need.
Oh, no, I don't mind,
Really.
I'd never see Michael
At all
If he didn't bring
His friends over.
I know what that's like.
I don't get to see my daughter
Trudy very much, either.
Oh, yeah.
If was worse
After he went overseas,
And Michael's father died
In '98.
How did you lose your wife?
Cancer.
She was a nurse at the v.a.
Of course,
That's how we met.
Find anything?
No.
Tore the seats out.
I'm working on the carpeting.
Nothing yet.
Check under the subfloor.
Mike, I got a hatchet
And a vise grip.
Okay.
I'll work something out.
Call me
If you find anything.
My surveillance has had
A good 14 hours
To get into my place again.
I got to get back there.
Say "hi" for me!
you can turn an old tv
Into an oscilloscope
with about $150 worth
Of hardware.
it'll electrocute you
If you're not careful,
but it makes a decent
Bug detector.
if you don't want to tip off
Anyone who might be listening,
you have to be prepared to keep
Talking for a few hours.
Oh, another "no confidence" vote
In the italian parliament.
Any thoughts?
As interested as I am
In european politics,
I was thinking
This would be a good opportunity
For us to discuss
Why exactly you left me.
of course,
When you have to keep talking,
it's an opportunity for someone
To hijack the conversation
for their own purposes.
Oh, I think now
Is the perfect time.
It was a difficult time.
There was an important reason.
It was years ago.
We should...
Let me gather my thoughts,
And we can talk about this
Another time.
Not even a goodbye,
Michael?
If you remember,
I made you dinner that night.
Well, had I known
It was the last supper,
I would have chewed slower.
If you recall,
My cover was blown.
You could have left a note.
Leaving notes
Is bad tradecraft.
It could have put you
In danger.
you ran away in the middle
Of the night for my benefit?
believe it or not, Fi,
Yeah, it was for your benefit.
And yours.
Yes, Fi, and mine.
Thanks, Michael.
A little honesty is...
Refreshing
Let us take some pictures
To celebrate this special night.
What a great idea.
the optical bug
Is a high-tech toy
that shoots a light beam
In a window.
it picks up vibrations
From the glass
and translates it into speech.
How's that one?
Can I see it?
Yeah.
you can't see the beam
With the naked eye,
but take the infrared filter
Off a digital camera,
and it shows up nicely.
as high-tech as a laser Mike
Is, they're not hard to defeat.
they pick up vibrations
On the glass,
so you supply
Your own vibrations.
You had to do that now?
I didn't say
I'd help you for free.
You found the eavesdropper.
I'll go over
To his little listening post,
Wait till he leaves,
See where he scurries to.
You think he's the one
Who burned you?
No, but he came here
To show me who's boss.
He's one step closer.
We should do this
More often.
Yeah, Sam.
Mikey, I've been calling
All night.
Yeah, it wasn't safe
To talk earlier.
What's up?
You better get over here... Now.
Mom, where's virgil?
We need to talk.
He's still asleep.
Have you been up all night?
Yeah. Virgil!
Where is he?
He's in my bedroom.
Ugh.
He's lonely, Michael...
And so am i!
It's been a long time
Since your father died.
And sometimes
I think it would be good
For us to have more
Of a family.
Oh, with virgil?
He lives
In a beat-up trailer.
Half of his meals
Come from roadkill.
Stop being so judgmental,
Michael!
All right, your father
Had problems, too.
Wake him up!
Have him meet me
Out in the backyard.
It's important.
I ripped her open,
And there it was.
I'm guessing about $10 million,
Give or take.
But nobody ever thinks
Of packing it
In something
With a goddamn handle.
Is this money real?
Oh, yeah.
It's probably headed
Toward aruba or anguilla...
One of those caribbean
Money holes.
10 million reasons
To want us dead.
Come on, Mike.
That's a glass-half-empty way
Of looking at it.
Mason probably stumbled upon
The money-smuggling operation,
Didn't want to risk
Pulling the heist himself,
You were the cutout,
You deliver the boat,
He shoots you,
And 300 gallons
Of burning methyl chloride
Cleans up the mess.
Jesus.
What do I do?
Well, for now...
Dump the boat.
You have any way
Of reaching these cops?
I got a number.
Naw, this ain't virgil.
This is your buddy homer.
Remember me?
No, he ain't around.
Y'all have to deal with me now.
And I want a meeting.
when working a cover identity,
the safest thing is to let
The target take the lead.
you've got more information
Than he does.
you want to keep that edge.
Hey, you brought
Your friends.
We got a little party
Going on here, don't we?
You want some fries?
How would you like
To die choking on them?
Oh, they're good.
Not that good,
But they're good.
Now, see,
That is just unfriendly.
Where's virgil?
Seems a shame
Just to dump it.
It is a nice boat.
Yeah, it's a nice boat.
It's a nice boat with a great
Big hole in the deck
And a bunch of guys with guns
Looking for it.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you, Sam.
Yeah, virg,
When this is over,
If we're not dead,
Thank me then.
All right, Sam.
I don't know where he is.
He's holed up somewhere.
Listen, we got
A real problem here.
Well, that's right.
We want out of this.
But those guys
We took the boat from...
They're coming after us.
If you could see your way
To helping us...
That's your problem.
Well, seeing how
We have your $10 million,
I guess that makes it
Your problem, too.
Now, I know you guys didn't
Want to get involved in this.
You wanted us to do
Your dirty work for you.
It's $10 million.
I know you must
Have big plans for it.
All right, fine.
You give us a time
And a place,
Put the jamaicans there
With my money,
And we'll handle it.
And then we walk away?
'Cause if I see
Another barrel of chemicals
With my name on it...
Let me put it this way...
You bring me my money,
And you got nothing
To worry about.
Then you can disappear.
Talk to the jamaicans.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Virg, get down!
Virgil: how the hell
Did they find us?!
Must have had
A backup gps tracker.
What happened?
You look awful!
Trust me, sweet thing,
You'd rather not know.
I can't believe we didn't find
That other tracking device.
Andre's good.
And that's bad.
Do you want
Something to drink?
Yeah. That sounds good.
Maybe a scotch.
I wouldn't mind a little
Something if you're gonna...
Sam! Not now.
We need to talk alone, mom.
We need to set up a meeting
With andre and the jamaicans.
Hey, mason just showed me
The boat.
I don't know those guys.
Yeah, and when we saw them,
There wasn't a lot of time
For conversation.
Call the marina,
Leave my number.
Andre knows
What he's doing.
He'll have everyone
From the harbormaster
To the guy emptying trash cans
Looking for us.
I'll see
If I can stall mason.
Right on time.
Yep.
Fear brings out the best
In people.
Look, I brought you some fries
Now that we're friends.
I haven't had time to talk
To the jamaicans yet.
That's not good, homer.
That's not good at all.
I repo'ed their boat.
It's not like I can go down
To the crab shack
And have a beer with them.
I don't give a damn
About the Jamaicans.
That's your problem.
I just want the money!
I'm doing the best I can!
I just need a little more time,
That's all.
Well, here's a little incentive
For virgil.
His daughter got picked up on
A traffic warrant this morning.
They haven't
Searched her car yet,
But if they do,
They just might find drugs
Under the backseat.
Pretty girls don't
Do very well in jail.
The other girls tend
To ugly them up real quick.
Don't know how long
The poor thing would last.
You'll have your money
Tomorrow.
So, this is Sam's new ride.
His girlfriend loaned it to him.
He loaned it to me.
Love is a beautiful thing.
Anyway, are you sure
These guys aren't gonna show up
And surprise me?
You probably
Have a few hours.
They're setting up surveillance
Cameras at your place.
Which room is his?
215.
I followed him here
Last night.
The guy looked
A little pissed.
After that business
With the personal massaging,
You sure you want
To upset him?
He's here
To make me behave.
I do that... He goes home,
I never find out anything.
I need him here.
If I can't
Make him a friend...
...the next best thing
Is an enemy.
anyone with a security
Clearance is going to know
not to leave anything
In a hotel room.
they'll keep the important
Stuff with them.
usually it'll be
In a secure laptop
with a few layers
Of encryption.
means you can't break into it.
but if you're just looking
To make somebody angry,
you don't need
To break into it.
put a big enough magnet where
That laptop's going to be,
and you can turn it
Into an expensive paperweight.
Hello?
Andre, it's good
To hear from you.
doctors are well-known
To be the worst patients.
similarly, anyone
With special-ops training
is tough to protect.
they think
They can handle anything.
Wow.
That shirt
Looks so good on you.
You're the same size
My husband was.
Oh, I don't wear
This kind of thing much.
I'm glad you like it.
I do.
Thank you.
Are you sure
This is all right?
Michael said you weren't
Supposed to be out.
Don't worry.
I can handle myself.
It's fun sneaking out, though,
Isn't it?
It is.
Have a drink, man.
Relax yourself.
No, I'm relaxed.
You know, you caused me
Quite a lot of trouble.
At least do me the courtesy
And have a drink.
All right.
Flo, let me get a rum punch
For my friend here.
So, the money you stole...
That was a payment
For a debt,
A large quantity
Of merchandise
Delivered from one very
Powerful man to another.
It's my job
To deliver this money.
Listen,
I don't want any...
I take my job
Very seriously.
I stay in business because,
When someone trusts me
With their funds,
I don't let nothing
Or no one
Come in the way
Of a safe delivery.
I make a promise
To my clients...
I would sooner cut my own throat
Than leave a debt unpaid.
Do you think I would hesitate
To cut yours?
I just wanted to know
What Michael was doing
Or where he was
All those years.
Take it from me, sweetheart.
I've been there.
Half that classified crap
Is so boring
You'd tear your hair out,
And the other half,
You don't want to know.
I think I could handle it.
I put up with his father
For 30 years.
Don't be too hard on him.
You get into that line
Of work...
Sweetheart, something real bad
Is about to happen.
I need you
To keep your head down
And pretend
You don't know me.
What?
I don't want you to get hurt.
Do that for me, please.
So, now that we understand
Each other, where's my money?
We want to give you
Your money back.
We just need to arrange
A time and a place.
So, we come and get it,
And what else is waiting
For us when we get there?
Now, andre, you're just
Gonna have to trust us.
Stop!
You come with us now!
Excuse me.
Yeah, mon.
Good. Good.
Put him on the phone.
It's for you.
For me?
Hello?
It's virgil.
I was out to dinner
With Madeline. I'm sorry.
They must have had eyes
On the street.
So, we do this tomorrow at noon,
9th street bridge.
We'll exchange virgil
For the $10 million.
Everything go well, you'll both
Get to go home alive.
If not...
Enjoy your drink.
I calmed your mother down.
I gave her enough sedatives
To knock out a trucker.
Did you ask her what the hell
She was doing out?
I told her
To keep him inside.
Oh, go easy on them,
Michael.
They snuck out.
A woman needs
A little danger.
So, what do we do about the cops
And mason, huh?
Well, I expect they're gonna be
Very disappointed
When they find out we're giving
The money to the jamaicans.
But we don't have
Any leverage.
They got virgil's daughter,
Mike.
One problem
At a time, Sam.
First virgil,
Then his daughter.
We could take
Some of the money...
Hire her a lawyer.
That could take care of it.
That could take care
Of us, too.
I doubt
They'll miss it, Mike.
Hello?
You think you can play with me,
You son of a bitch?
You destroyed all my files!
Oh, it's good to hear
From you, too.
I'm right in the middle
Of something.
You broke into my room.
Well, I just wanted
To get to know you better.
Now then, I'm Michael Westen.
And you are?
You don't need my name.
I came down here to bring you
A message... Back off.
People get fired all the time.
Leave it alone.
Oh, good.
A message from who?
I just wanted to send him
A thank-you note.
Dream on, pal.
Fi.
Yes.
My new friend just discovered
I paid him a little visit.
He'll be moving hotels.
I'll stay on him.
when something serious
Is going down,
it's a good idea
To show up nice and early
so you can see the ground
And assess the situation.
Mike, I should go.
Virgil's my buddy.
You don't owe him anything.
They know me and Fi.
If you show up, they'll think
Something is wrong.
Just cover us
And keep an eye out.
All right.
Good luck.
It's cute...
This loyalty of Sam's.
I really like
This side of him.
Thanks for doing this, Fi.
Oh, I'm not doing this
For you.
I promised your mom
I'd bring virgil back alive.
Hey, they're right
On time.
Let's make this trade,
Make it quick,
And get out of here
Before things get...
...interesting.
Yeah, Sam.
Your hunch about mason
Was right
'Cause he and the boys
Just showed up.
Yeah, okay,
I'm ready for them.
The cops are coming.
All righty, then.
when enough people hate you,
sometimes the only move
Is to just stand in the middle
and hope they kill each other
Before they kill you.
Hey!
What you doing, man?
What are you doing?!
I said stop it!
Stop it!
anyone who's ever handled large
Amounts of cash can tell you,
it's one of the toughest things
In the world to move.
it's heavy and dense...
Dead weight.
if it's on fire, of course,
that complicates things
Further.
Freeze! Drop it!
Hey, you get back!
You calm down! Calm down!
Boys, boys, boys,
Calm down.
We have a little bit
Of business first.
Andre, let virgil go.
Andre, let virgil go!
I'm gonna find you, boy,
And I'm gonna kill you.
And then you'll cut my throat.
I know, I know. Let him go.
Andre, it's the fumes
That ignite.
I don't even
Have to touch it.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Okay! Okay.
Have you two guys met?
You have a lot
To talk about.
Andre, detective mason.
Detective mason, andre.
Get down on the ground!
You ain't a cop!
You a thief!
Okay, on the ground.
You ain't no cop.
Get on the ground!
Go on, call for backup!
You call for backup!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on, Mike,
You'd think we'd be able
To keep a little more
Than this.
We took what we needed.
My daughter called.
She's pissed at me, as usual.
But she's home.
They dropped the charges.
They had to
With the jamaicans dead
And the cops in jail.
But unfortunately,
You're going to have to get out
Of town for a while.
With this all over the papers,
There are still a few people
Out there
Who want to put a bullet
In you.
Well, I'll just
Get the boat fixed up
And go down to the bahamas
For a while.
Great.
You sure
You're not just trying
To keep me away
From your sweet mama?
Hey, virg?
Don't push it.
Okay.
I'll go make my goodbyes.
Gentlemen.
I think you're even, Sam.
Yeah.
Whew.
Oh, by the way,
I made some calls,
Talked to a buddy of mine
At the FBI.
Looks like
I got the charger back.
Let's just call it
A thank-you gift.
You're welcome, Sam.
Okay, I need a beer.
getting information
Out of someone
who doesn't want to give it up
is all about upsetting
The target's emotional balance,
impairing their judgment.
fear's good for that.
Anger's not bad either.
Hey, buddy.
I thought we could spend
Some more time together.
You really don't understand
The situation here, do you?
You're out, man.
That's it.
You should be in jail.
Jail?! That's interesting.
Why jail?
I don't remember ever
Doing anything jail worthy.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, don't get cute.
I want to know
Why I got burned.
Show me the burn notice.
Tell me why.
You know damn well why.
I've seen the dossier.
I'd like a look at that dossier.
You have it?
Get off!
Take your hands off me!
Okay, all right.
All right. All right.
Fine.
sometimes,
Intelligence gathering
involves sophisticated
Techniques
and a lot
Of high-tech equipment.
but sometimes it's as simple
As picking someone's pocket.
How'd we do?
Good to meet you,
Agent bly.
Http://www.ragbear.com