Previously on Veronica Mars
- Stop by the office and we'll finish up.
- Finish up?
- I'm referring to the reward.
- Veronica and I had an arrangement.
I'm a murderer and a rapist now.
I slept with you.
- Well what about that is so wrong?
- 'Cause you're my sister.
I know you were with Abel Koontz at the time
he supposedly murdered Lilly Kane.
- You think they're serious.
- It won't last long. My mom's in rehab.
When she gets cleaned up, she's coming home.
If you think you're going to lay a hand
on her the way you did Lilly...
Don't you even say her name.
- You learned that from Lilly.
- No, Lilly learned that from me.
Now, let me make sure I'm hearing this correctly.
Abel Koontz couldn't have killed Lilly Kane
because at the time of the murder,
he was in the company of Miss, um·
Cheyenne.
- Cheyenne.
- Deborah Collins, yes.
Keith, even if I did believe your story which,
at the moment I don't,
there's no way top brass
would risk a story like this.
If is turned out to not be true,
we'd become a national joke.
Well, we tried.
It is true.
I'm serving up the story of your lifetime, Lloyd.
Look, Keith, I can't risk my career because
of testimony, all due respect, of a hooker.
Well, there's more, a lot more.
You read it.
If you think there's merit,
talk to Miss Collins here.
Thanks.
Hi Dad. This is so stupid.
No, I'm telling you. No tears.
Keith, the radio,
like old times.
It works, see.
* SONG: Where the boys are *
Keith, tacos.
What?
It's just funny to me how you always have to
have your music match your meal.
It is called setting a mood.
Of course.
Connie Francis is spaghetti bolognaise
with a crusty bread and a nice Chianti.
Uh, sans the Chianti.
Okay, say we were having
hot dogs and Tater Tots?
Late seventies southern rock,
Skynyrd, maybe Creedence.
- Pork chops.
- Country, old school.
Unless it's fried,
then it's Elvis, the early years.
* SONG: Por Ti Sere *
There you go, how's that?
* Bamba bamba *
Perfect.
Tell me this is a joke.
You want to sue the Kane family.
Yes.
Please tell me there's another Kane family
in town. Maybe a Boris and Gilda Kane?
They'll settle.
Oh, they will. Well, that's good to hear.
Seems like you have this pretty well sewn up.
Anything you need me to have notarised?
There's phone records, man.
An-an-and how do you-
how do you explain the shoes, huh?
It doesn't mean jack.
You need to chill out, Beav, right now.
To the grave, man, that's what we said.
Since his removal from office, Keith Mars,
the ousted sheriff, has tirelessly and
single-handedly continued his own investigation,
despite being shunned by the community at large.
You'd think it might be gross to read a love
letter to your dad, but I kind of enjoy it.
All I know is if I were him right now,
I'd be I-told-you-soing all over Neptune.
My blonde-pulling-me-into-the-
girl's-room fantasy?
Ruined!
Do me a favour?
Go outside and tell me when Logan's gone.
Okay.
How much longer
do you think you can avoid him?
I mean, believe me, the last thing
I want to do is hurt you.
If there's a chance to keep my family together,
I have to take it.
I just don't know what else to say.
You're really doing this?
Is it really what you want?
Everything okay?
Oh, it's fine.
I just had to tell Alicia
that my situation is changed.
Sorry. I know how much you care about her.
Yeah.
She's got to understand, though, right?
I mean with Mom coming back?
Yeah.
Don't seat the entertainment people next to the
corporate people. Right? Let's keep it civil.
Jake, honey, when did we become Republicans?
We haven't, we're, uh, we're going with the flow.
Besides the, uh, governor's, uh, very popular and,
uh, honestly, it's going to be good for business.
- And his social policy-
- No. Just spare me.
So, anyone read the paper today? Garfield.
I mean, will he ever learn?
Oh yeah, and there was this other thing.
I guess Abel Koontz didn't kill Lilly.
Let's open the floor for discussion on that one,
what do you say?
It's hogwash, Duncan.
It's an invention of Keith Mars.
The woman was a prostitute, for god's sake.
- Stop! Quit lying to me.
- Duncan, please.
Dad, I can't take it anymore. All the lies.
Does anyone ever tell me the truth? Ever?
You treat me like I'm six years old,
you always have.
You wanna know, Duncan?
You want to know everything?
Jake, no!
Yeah, I wanna know.
You did it, son. You had a fit.
You killed your sister.
Duncan. Duncan, come inside.
Duncan!
Lilly?
Look, it was an accident, Duncan.
We know it was.
You didn't know what you were doing.
You loved your sister.
We've done this for you, son,
so you could have a future.
Keith Mars is suing us. We've been served.
Hello?
Beaver?
It's, uh, it's Cassidy. My real name's Cassidy.
What can I do for you Cassidy?
Well, there's something that you should know,
it's for your own good.
Spill.
Well, the weekend that Lilly was killed, me,
Dick and Logan, we were down in Mexico, surfing.
I know this.
Yeah, well Logan, he, uh, he got-he got
all worked up, you know, talking about
how he that Lilly was seeing somebody new.
Yeah.
So he got up early that morning,
the day that Lilly was murdered,
he drove back to Neptune to see her.
Beaver said that Logan had bought
Lilly a shot glass
that he found in a tourist shop down there.
Does that seem odd to you?
Not that odd. Lilly collected shot glasses.
Beaver said it said "I got baked in Ensenada"
and she would have loved it.
Are you all right, honey?
Yeah, just Logan.
Baked in Ensenada! Veronica!
* SONG: C'mon baby be my bad boyfriend *
What are you looking for?
This. It's an inventory of everything
in Lilly's bedroom, everything in Lilly's car.
Shot glass.
Baked in Ensenada. It's here, it was in her car.
You know what this means?
Means Logan found Lilly.
* SONG: I've got something special
for my bad boyfriend*
Hey.
Oh. I exist? Thought I felt different today.
I've been avoiding you.
Really? I hadn't noticed.
I'm sorry. I freaked out.
That night in the guest house, we were like
crossing over into something and I-I don't know,
all of a sudden I just felt really weird and guilty
and I started thinking about Duncan and about
Lilly and
it wasn't the easiest night to begin with.
I know.
I just couldn't deal.
Well, you could've told me.
No, I mean even if you just said
I can't deal but you bolt
and you dodge me for a couple days
It's what I do.
When things get out of control, I need to be alone.
Listen, you know, I am freaked out, too,
you know, this whole Abel Koontz thing.
Knowing what we do about Duncan.
I don't want to believe it could have been him
but it's-it's like the only thing
that makes sense, right?
I don't know.
I have this feeling that things
are gonna get really bad.
Yeah?
Don't run out on me again, okay, I mean,
if you need to do whatever, you just let me know.
I need to do whatever.
Just for a couple of days and then I'll be
back to normal or as close to normal as I can get.
Okay.
You know where to find me.
It's me. I just ran into Logan. I know, I know.
I couldn't help it. He's trying to pin it on Duncan.
Any news on Tijuana?
The Border Patrol got back to me.
Logan's car crossed the border at 8:57am
on the day Lilly was murdered.
Beaver was telling the truth.
He had plenty of time to get back
to Neptune and kill her.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Hey, are you okay?
No, I'm fine.
Love you.
Love you too.
That's not what it sounded like.
It sounded a lot like Logan killed Lilly.
These rich boys think they can
get away with anything, don't they.
Miss Mars may have agreed to help find your son
but it was Mr Mars, a licensed private investigator
who located him and ensured his safe return.
I'd be happy to give Mr Mars a cheque right now.
And the condition?
Veronica relinquishes any future claim
to the Kane estate.
Contracts are prepared;
all we need is your daughter's signature.
Future claims? So what, she slips and falls
outside Kane Enterprises; tough toenails?
Yeah, I guess now is a good time to protect your
assets with the Abel Koontz witness coming forward.
I'm sure you'll encourage your daughter
to do the right thing.
Oh, believe me, I'm willing to make this deal.
But I'll let Veronica make the decision
once I figure out how to explain it to her.
Keith, we both know your daughter knows exactly
why she's being asked to sign this.
And we both know it's better
for everyone if she does.
You're not trying to burn a hole through a stack
of paper using only the power of your stare again?
Hey, sweetheart.
Have a seat a minute;
I have to talk to you.
I met with Celeste Kane today.
She's paying you double and
sponsoring our club membership?
Well, she actually agreed to pay up
but only if you sign this contract that says
that you'll never sue them again.
She wants you to waive any claim
on the Kane fortune.
What? Was I supposed to sign in blood?
Do you know what you just signed away?
There's nothing that I want from them.
Nothing. You didn't sign away a thing.
Veronica, I am without a doubt your father.
Oh! Yeah, you are!
You think that charm of yours is
learned behaviour? That's genetics, baby!
I say we put a dent in that
fifty grand and celebrate.
Actually, honey, this new information we have
on Logan, his alibi is completely blown.
I think we can finally go to the authorities.
Um-hm.
Afternoon, sir.
Sheriff. Can I help you with something?
You can show me to your son's room.
We're gonna need to search it.
What do you want with my son?
Some new information has come up
regarding the Lilly Kane murder case.
We're gonna follow up. Routine.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. You can't just barge in here!
Now, come on now.
You've been in like, what, thirty cop movies?
Hey, make sure you check
the air conditioning vents.
Got you, boss.
Our snitch says these crafty little buggers today;
they hide things in the vents.
Wait a minute, wait a minute. W-where's my son?
Logan Echolls?
Yeah. What's going on?
We'd like you to come with us
down to the station, please.
We have a few questions we'd like to ask you.
You said you were in Mexico
the day of Lilly's murder. Why?
How many episodes of "NYPD Blue" did you have to
watch to get the finger tapping down?
- I asked you a question.
- And I ignored it and moved on. Keep up.
Do I look like I am playing around with you?
So how 'bout that phone call, huh?
Whoops.
What, you didn't read the manual?
Okay, I get a phone call, it's the law.
Your daddy's already sending a lawyer.
Go ahead.
Hey, it's me.
Hey, I'm in kind of a jam.
Yeah, I'm here at the lovely
sheriff's department, being grilled·
Without representation I might add.
Hey, do you think, uh,
you could track down my father,
maybe work some of that Veronica magic
that gets people out of these things?
Sure. I'll do whatever I can.
Thanks.
Well, I'd love to chat, but I have a guest.
Talk to you later.
Okay, bye.
You called Veronica Mars.
Yeah. What's it to you?
Ah, it's funny, that's all, I just mean,
she's the one who came to me
with information about you.
Keith Mars, line two.
Keith. What can I do for you?
The Echolls kid. What'd you find out?
Among other things, I'm pretty sure·
He's dating your daughter.
That, uh, girl of yours...
She's pretty hard-boiled, huh?
Logan. Where is he now?
We let him go on account we didn't
have much to hold him on. He lawyered up.
You know the deal.
Lianne, where's Veronica?
She took Backup out.
So, I guess we broke up, huh?
What do you want me to say, Logan?
"Logan, I'm gonna go home and put my head
in the oven because I can't go on living
knowing what a heartless BITCH I am."
Something like that!
So you're saying you want me dead?
One word from me and Backup goes for your throat.
Is that what you'd do, boy?
You'd tear out my throat?
Who's a man killer, huh? Who's a man killer?
You know, I,
I knew Lilly was seeing someone.
It was driving me crazy.
When I left for Neptune, I didn't know if I was
gonna scream at her for treating me like dirt
or beg her to take me back.
And I saw her at the carwash.
I didn't see you there.
Well, I just parked across the street
and watched her.
And this feeling came over me, you know, I don't
know how to describe it but I just knew it was over.
So I sat in my car and I wrote this note to her,
explaining it.
Did you give it to her?
Yeah, I left it in the car.
With the shot glass.
Yeah, with the shot glass.
You know, if you read that letter,
you'd know I'd never hurt her.
Hey! Get away from her!
You get away from her, now!
I keep thinkin' that
things can't get worse, you know?
You know what? She's all yours.
You two are dating?
Not anymore.
Dad says that though his deputies found the
shot glass Logan left for Lilly,
the break up letter Logan says he wrote was
never discovered.
If Lilly wanted to keep it a secret,
I have an idea where she would have kept it.
LILLY: Veronica, you have to check this out.
That guy I met in Italy last summer?
Yeah?
He sent me some pictures.
Doing some rewiring?
Celeste is a bit on the nosey side.
Yuck.
Tell me about it. I'm getting even, though.
I left phone numbers on matchbooks for Tyrone
and Leroy and Chico around the room.
Give the woman a little drama in her life.
Wait...who's Tyrone and Leroy and Chico?
Beats me, but they seem to really upset Mom.
Lilly, those are naked photos.
They certainly are.
If Lilly kept Logan's letter, that's where
she would have hidden it.
Now, what does one wear to meet the governor?
Hi, the number to the
Hazelwood Facility in Soquel?
Wouldn't plan it without you, of course.
Dear, just take it over there.
We'll talk to you later.
The crab puffs are fantastic.
Smoked salmon, and the same·
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing in here?
Duncan, Duncan, it's me.
Veronica! What are you doing?
I'm looking for something.
Well, shouldn't you be looking in my room,
I mean, that's where
all the clues would be, right?
Yeah, yeah, come on.
You didn't put on a whole costume,
an-and sneak into my house,
just to leave empty handed.
- Duncan, stop.
- No, come on let's see what you can find out.
Really, I want you to. Find out everything.
Uh, maybe I left a confession
on my Etch-A-Sketch.
Duncan, Duncan, calm down, okay.
I don't think you killed Lilly, Duncan.
I think Logan did.
No, no way.
He wasn't in Mexico the day she was killed.
Dick and Beaver lied for him.
He came back early because he found out
Lilly was seeing someone, Weevil,
I think and he admitted that much,
but he said he wrote her a letter on
the day she died that would prove his innocence.
I remembered Lilly
used to hide things in her air vents.
Let's see what's in there.
Well?
There's just these.
I've got a camera we can play 'em on.
Where's this?
Logan's. The pool house.
That's her pep squad outfit.
This is the day she died.
Come here, lover. Time to earn your keep.
What?
See the other tape.
This one's dated October 1st.
Oh my god.
Mr Echolls?
I've got a secret. A good one.
Veronica?
I know what happened. I know what happened.
Oh, you dirty dog.
Lilly.
I want those tapes back!
Mr. Echolls, hi! Sorry, Logan's not here.
I am not playing with you.
Oh, really. Well, you're usually
very interested in playing with me.
Lilly, give me the tapes, now.
Like, what, you don't see yourself
enough on film?
I want those tapes, you stupid little bitch.
Oh, I'm the stupid one?
Well, now you can just watch the tapes on
"Access Hollywood" along with the rest of America.
Lilly! Lilly!
Oh my god. No, no, no, Lilly,
Lilly. Lilly, Lilly, come on. Come on.
Lilly, wake up! Lilly, wake up. Wake up.
My god, wake up. Lilly, wake up.
Duncan!
Duncan, what have you done?
What've you done?
Lilly! Honey, baby.
What have you done?
- No!
- What did you do?
- Honey, honey!
Could he really do it?
He's psychotic.
I watched him beat a guy into a bloody mess
and then ask Logan how his school day was.
He beats Logan, you know?
He's here. Now. He came to meet the governor.
I have to get these tapes to my dad.
Will you help me?
You keep Aaron in your sight at all times
- until I call you.
- Yeah, of course.
Hey!
Be careful, okay.
My dad had a paternity test.
I'm not your sister.
Hi, sweetheart.
Dad, it's Aaron Echolls. He did it.
I have video of Lilly in his bed
on the day she died,
they were having an affair.
Where are you?
- I'm just leaving the Kanes.
- No, you stay put. I'll be right there.
No Dad, he's here.
He's talking to the governor.
Duncan's gonna keep an eye on him,
I'll be home in ten minutes.
All right, you come straight home,
you don't stop for anything.
Okay.
* SONG: I've Got a fever *
* Come check it and see *
* There's something burning and rolling in me *
Answer Phone:
You've reached Logan and
here's today's inspirational message:
Adversity is the diamond dust with
which Heaven polishes its jewels.
Seriously, what do you-what do you think
you can do to me, huh?
I'll think of something.
Hey.
I can't find him.
Did you ask around?
I've been asking everyone
but no one knows where he is.
Thanks, well call me if you find him.
Let me know when you get home, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
Keep driving.
Nuh, uh, uh, uh. Driving.
Oh. I've been looking for these.
It's Veronica. Leave me a message.
Is everything okay, Keith?
Yeah, it's fine. I'll be back soon.
Hello! Hello! Is anyone home?
Help me, please! Hello?
Hello? Is anyone here?
Hello? Let me in! Let me in!
Please, open the door. Please, let me in.
Please, please let me in!
Veronica? You're an odd duck.
Hey, how many teenage girls
keep walkie-talkies in their car?
What have you done to me?
Veronica, dear. Where are my tapes?
I'll let you out as soon as I have my tapes back.
No, thanks. Honestly, I feel safer in here.
Well you know, you shouldn't.
You wanna know something about
Joan of Arc, Veronica?
Huh? God didn't really talk to her.
Uh-uh. It's true, I saw it on TV.
You know, it was one of those historical forensics
programmes. And they decided she had a brain tumour.
Burned alive. What a waste.
She thought her death meant something.
But all it meant was she was crazy.
Think about that. Veronica. Where are the tapes?
Where are the tapes?
Veronica, where are the tapes, Veronica.
You know,
Lilly never told me
where the tapes were hidden either.
I-I kinda think
there's a cautionary tale in that, Veronica.
Something like I'm not going to let
a seventeen year-old piece of ass ruin my life!
They're on the roof, I put 'em on the roof.
Please let me out of here.
KEITH: Veronica! Veronica!
Dad?
She's in the fridge, Keith.
You might want to check up on her.
Dad!
Hang on, honey.
I love you. I love you so much.
I knew you'd come, I knew you'd save me. Dad.
Grrrr....
I'm sorry, man, I didn't see you,
you were in the middle of the street.
Oh my god, you're Aaron Echolls.
Help me.
Don't touch him.
Do you have a cell phone?
- Yeah.
- Call 911. We need an ambulance,
the police and the fire department.
RADIO: Rescue one. Engine five one respond.
You mean the world to me,
do you understand that?
Are you listening to me?
Hey,
who's your daddy, huh?
I hate it when you say that.
Aaron Echolls, you have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say will be used against you in a
court of law. You have the right to an attorney.
If you can't afford an attorney, one will be
appointed to you. Do you understand these rights?
You killed my daughter.
You killed my daughter!
- Sir!
- And you're gonna pay for it.
I'll watch you frying. I'll destroy your family
and everyone you ever loved.
You killed my daughter!
- Jake Kane.
- You killed my daughter!
- I'll watch you fry, Aaron.
- You are under arrest for obstruction of justice.
You have the right to remain silent.
My daughter, my daughter.
INTERCOM: Harriet Monk, physiotherapy.
Dr Harriet Monk, physiotherapy.
He'll be fine.
When?
Eventually, just be patient.
And you need to get some rest.
I won't let him wake up and find himself alone.
Is there anyone that we can call?
Honey? What happened?
Are you okay? Where's your father?
- He's in the hospital.
- What Happened?
He's gonna be okay.
What, Veronica, what happened?
It's over now and I'll tell you the rest
in the morning. But first I need you to pack.
What? What do you mean?
You can't be here when dad comes home.
- Veronica.
- I know, Mom. I know you're not through drinking,
I know you didn't even finish rehab.
You checked yourself out
and that was my college money.
I bet on you, and I lost.
I've been doing that my whole life. And I'm through.
Veronica...
it's not easy.
I know it's not.
Hey you.
Veronica didn't want you to be alone.
* SONG: Lily I hope you
picture me in your dreams *
Isn't it better, like this?
So much better.
This is how it's supposed to be.
Totally.
This is how it's gonna be.
From now on. Right? Lilly?
You know how things are gonna be now, don't you?
You have to know.
Just like this. Just like this.
Don't forget about me, Veronica.
I could never.
I was hoping it would be you.