Previously on Veronica Mars...
God, Lilly, I see the Prozac's working.
I've got a secret. A good one.
Socially, she seems to be a bit isolated.
I'd say Veronica's doing pretty well,
given the circumstances.
I know how close she was with Lilly Kane.
The truth is gonna come out.
It doesn't add up.
- Lilly?
- What? You forgot about me already?
- What are you doing?
- Why do you have Lilly's name on your arm?
- You really wanna know?
- Yeah, I really wanna know!
My husband gets a lot of
disturbing letters from fans.
I swear, I don't know you.
The word is out.
Our illustrious Guidance Counsellor
has received a grant
to study the long term effects
of grief in adolescence.
She's demanding an audience with
each of us hardest hit by Lilly's death.
I was going to decline a session,
then I had a thought.
Well there's something
you don't see everyday.
Yeah. I cannot wait to get out of Neptune.
MIT, huh?
Early admission.
Bet you're gonna miss
this place when you're gone.
- Not really.
- I didn't think so.
Veronica? Sorry to make you wait.
Come on in.
Do you remember when we talked
last year, right after Lilly's death?
You were...inconsolable.
I'm really hoping that this year,
you're able to talk about it.
You know, you're never going
to come to terms with Lilly's death
if you keep all that pain bottled up inside you.
Wow. I have that exact same
platitude-a-day calendar at home.
It's how I know beauty comes from within.
Look, Veronica, for whatever
reason, I don't think you...
care for me very much, so if you
prefer talking with someone else, that's...
Sorry, that was rude.
It's not you. It's the talking.
I don't want to talk away my grief.
I want to turn it into something else. Fuel.
I know how I'm gonna feel better and
it's not by talking about how sad I am.
Veronica!
Yeah. Nervous habit.
So how is it you're going to find, uh,
and I really hate to use this word
but it is appropriate...closure?
I'll find closure when Lilly's killer's
rotting away in prison.
Miss Jeffries?
Rick! You're wanted in the office.
- The Sheriff is here to-
- Morning, Rick.
How's your head this morning,
a little bit of a hangover?
That's nothing compared
to how your buddy Tim is feeling.
Tim had to have a tube put down his throat
so they could pump his stomach.
He's in a coma, Rick.
Oh my god.
According to a surveillance tape,
your evening ended at 1:30am
when you dropped, and I mean dropped,
an unconscious Tim outside
the Neptune Memorial ER.
I-I didn't have a choice.
Right.
Someone must have put a gun to your head,
forced you on a pub crawl?
By the way, how did you get into those bars?
We got fake IDs.
You and half the kids in Neptune.
These things have been popping up
all over the place. The way I see it,
they're coming from your school.
I think you owe it to your friend
to tell me who's making the fakes.
Look, Rick.
The three of us?
We're not leaving this cosy
little room until you give me a name.
Veronica Mars.
Sending out the big guns
in the morning. I'm flattered.
Veronica, the Sheriff wants
to have a look inside your locker.
Course he does.
Just out of curiosity, what are
you gentlemen hoping to find in here?
Al Capone? The Lindbergh baby?
We have reason to believe that
you are manufacturing and distributing
fake driver's licenses.
- Ooo, that's a new one.
- It's a second degree felony.
Lord knows, I hate to disappoint you boys...
Wait a minute, those aren't mine.
I'm gonna need to search your purse
as well. Either we can do this here...
Or down at the station?
Lilly Kane's driver's license.
Driver's license for a twenty two
year old Veronica Mars.
A San Diego State student ID.
- Licensed massage therapist.
- Oh yeah. Those are mine.
- You really don't have to do that.
- You're right about that.
But I'm going to anyway.
And Veronica, don't bother coming back
to school for the next three days.
You're suspended.
You better call your daddy, Mars!
Ah, it's your turn, huh? Ha ha.
Gosh, I hope they use
that shot in the yearbook.
Season 1 - Episode 12
Clash of the Tritons
I know an adequate one
who just posted your $500 bail.
They take Diners Club here?
- Seriously, Cliff, thanks.
- It's quite all right.
It's all part of my full
service legal counsel.
Is there any way you could
not tell my dad about this?
- Why didn't you call him?
- He's busy chasing a bail jumper in Arizona.
Trust me, your dad's gonna
find out one way or the other.
Besides, I may need to sic him on you
if you don't show up at the courthouse.
Next Tuesday, 9am.
So, are we gonna beat this wrap?
Well, possession, they've got
you pretty cold on that one.
The stuff in your wallet is Mickey Mouse.
It's the IDs in the locker
that they care about.
- They were blank.
- Right.
So until the coma guy wakes up, the only
thing they have tying you to this supposed
fake ID ring is the testimony
of the other kid.
- What other kid?
- Your buddy...Rick.
Excuse me?
Howdy, Rick.
Do I know you? No.
Then why'd you tell Sheriff Lamb
I sold you a fake ID?
It's...it-it's what they told me to say.
- Who's they?
- No way.
- They're everywhere. They will destroy me.
- I'll destroy you worse.
- I can't talk about it here.
- Tomorrow in school, we talk.
No! I just- I told you, it
has to be done in secret.
Oh, it will be.
- You'll be hearing from me.
- I thought you were expelled?
La femme Veronica.
I heard it took three officers and a
stun gun to haul your butt outta school.
You must be the only student who didn't
see my walk of shame in person.
I grabbed your books.
- And your homework from the teachers.
- I need to ask another favour.
This mission better involve
me seducing the head cheerleader.
I need you to poke around
and see if you can get me a fake ID.
If you must seduce the head cheerleader
in order to accomplish your mission, so be it.
No sweat.
- How do I do that?
- Play on her insecurity.
- I meant the fake ID part.
- Okay.
Let's pretend for a moment that this
mythical head cheerleader of yours
has just asked you out on a date.
In exchange for seven minutes in heaven,
you have to get her into the hottest
nightclub in Neptune or
at least buy her a pack
of strawberry wine coolers.
The stakes are high,
Wallace Fennell. Think, now.
How would you do it?
Hey, Veronica?
Yeah?
I need you to get me a fake ID
so I can get some fake
action from a fake cheerleader.
- Wallace?
- Yeah?
Please find out who else
at school is making them.
If you're breathing, then you've heard
about Aaron Echolls getting ginsued
at his own Christmas party.
Explain to me why a guy who's
married to Lynn Echolls would want
to bang the frigging help.
It's like the old saying goes,
show me a hot chick and I'll show you
a guy who's tired of hitting that.
- Logan!
- Yeah. Be right there.
In my humble opinion,
your mom's totally hotter.
You shut the hell up.
Big mistake, son.
Break it up! Break it up.
- Get off!
- It's enough.
To tell you the truth, I-I...
I really don't remember that week.
You don't remember being in this office?
You slammed the chair
against the wall, Eli.
The last time that we met it seemed
that Lilly's death had affected you
in quite a profound way.
Well, yeah. I was mad.
You know, the same day Lilly Kane died,
a little girl went missing
in my neighbourhood.
They found her body three months later.
Where were the cameras when she went missing,
where was the grief counselling for her?
What happened to Marisol Reyes
was a tragedy, Eli. People do care...
Right now I just want
to talk about Lilly, okay.
Oh, well then, why don't you call
some of her rich, white friends in here?
I want you to listen to something.
It's a letter you wrote.
"You tore my heart out.
You can act like what we had together
meant nothing to you,
but you can't stop me from loving you.
For the rest of your life, wherever
you go, I'll always be there,
just out of sight, in the shadows."
You know, I-I don't
remember cc'ing you on that.
Lilly wanted to be transferred out
of your PE class last year,
she was having trouble with a boy.
She gave me these to prove it.
I never would have hurt her.
Look, the cops already rubbed my nose
in those letters so what-what...
Lilly and Weevil?
Look, Eli, I didn't bring you
in here to embarrass you.
I invited you in here to talk about
why you wrote these things.
Her and Logan had just broken up.
And uh, Lilly swore to me that
she'd never go back to him but then...
one day that punk snaps his fingers and...
all of a sudden it's like, like, we
don't even know each other any more.
And...she was someone
I could have loved, you know?
And she felt it too, I know she did.
Why didn't Lilly tell me about him?
Was Weevil her big secret?
- Hello?
- Back parking lot, fourth row.
Where are you?
- Is anyone watching you?
- No, I don't think so.
Slide on in.
So where were we?
Right! Who framed me?
They're called the Tritons.
It's a secret society at school.
Why haven't I heard of them?
Stupid question. Keep going.
The Tritons have been around
as long as Neptune High.
Six new members are inducted
in junior year by the six seniors.
Tim and I were among their pledges.
Who's in charge?
No one even knows for
sure who the brothers are.
Then who invited you to join?
Two weeks ago, I found a note in my locker.
- So this was all part of a hazing ritual?
- The twelve labours.
The first few challenges weren't so bad.
But on Friday when I opened up my locker,
I found a fake ID with
my yearbook picture on it.
The instructions said we were supposed
to go to a bunch of bars
and have a shot at each of 'em.
Let me guess. Twelve?
Tim passed out at the eleventh.
All the other pledges freaked out
and left me there to take care of him so I-
I threw him in the car and I took him
to the hospital as fast as I could.
If they're so secret,
how do you know all this?
My dad was a Triton.
So were my two older brothers.
Blame Veronica Mars
All I cared about at that moment
was staying on their good side.
If they found out that I betrayed their
secrets, let's just say I'd be better off in jail.
These guys will destroy your life,
it's their mission statement.
So that's your defence?
That you were just following orders?
That doesn't cut it, Rick.
I know that now and I'm sorry.
You've gotta believe me.
After what they did to Tim?
And now his family's threatening to sue me.
I can't even talk to my own dad about it.
He calls me a coward
and a traitor for what I did.
But how can I belong to a club
that almost killed my best friend?
All I want now is for the Tritons to go down.
- So, who are the other pledges?
- Anyone who's anyone.
The Tritons supposedly chose the best
guys in everything: academics, sports...
they're pretty much
the six guys you'd expect.
I want their names.
Harry Diddon, Steve Argo, Matt Barron,
Duncan Kane.
So if I follow Duncan,
I can find the Tritons.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
- Logan, let's go.
- How long did I get?
You're not being suspended.
The Vice Principal wants all three of us
back here on Friday
for a disciplinary conference.
Listen. I'm not happy
that you were fighting
but I am proud of you
for sticking up for your mother.
- You're proud of me!
- Yeah.
Oh great. Good. I can die happy.
You keep smarting off
and I'll help arrange it.
Is everything okay?
Sorry Cliff, I'm late.
Hi, Dad. Their case is
fuzzy and circumstantial.
You know the odd thing?
Those were also her very first words.
I think I've got a good lead
on who's making the fake IDs.
It's a secret society at
school called the Tritons.
Rick told me that he was
bullied into turning me in.
I'm positive they're the ones
who set the blanks in my locker.
Look, Veronica. The criminal case
is the least of our problems.
- Tim's parents are suing.
- Us?
And pretty much everyone else involved
in their son's night of debauchery.
Every bar in town is gonna
be named in the suit.
The thing could be worth millions.
Aaron! Come on in.
Thank you.
So, how's it going?
Do you need anything?
Uh...yeah, some water would be good.
So, I, uh, I guess I should have
cancelled that party after all, huh?
So. How you hangin' in.
This I can handle but these...
I've been trying to
regain my family's trust.
And I meant what I said when I told you
that I was going to give up all of that...
but these stories. I mean
they're tearing my family apart.
My daughter Trina's the only one
who will talk to me anymore.
I can't blame Logan or his mother, I just...
Any idea who could know
such intimate details about you?
Paparazzi. But then again they would
have printed the stories right away.
- Someone on my staff?
- Jealous boyfriend or husband?
That's a possibility.
Well, let me dig around.
Listen.
My wife's really fragile.
I don't know how much more
scandal she can take.
Let me see what I can do.
Triton, son of Neptune,
the god of the sea:
with his great horn Triton commands
the dark waters and all the creatures within.
- Trick or treat.
- What's the news?
Nobody I talked to at school
knows anything about fake IDs.
But then, this afternoon, a kid from
my biology class comes into Sac'n'Pac,
buys a six pack from my boss, like it was no problem.
Did you figure out where he got his fake?
Slow down. This is my story.
Followed him out to the parking lot
and I was like "Yo, fella, check it out.
You're on "Candid Camera"
Gave him the four-one-one on
our video playback capabilities,
you know, leaned on him.
Like I was Shaft or somethin'.
Shut yo' mouth!
Long story short.
The guy claimed that there's
a mystery locker at school.
- Ooo, I like it already.
- Here's how it works.
You put your name and two hundred
and fifty bucks in locker one-ten
first thing in the morning.
Come afternoon, brand spanking
new licence that says you were born
in 1983 arrives in your locker.
Are you willing to put $250 into some
strange locker just to see if this works?
Hell, no. I'm using your money.
How many times have I walked
through the main hallway?
And how many times have I not noticed
that our school's insignia includes
Trinton's conch shell.
According to Wallace, locker one-ten
isn't assigned to anyone in school
but clearly someone has the combination.
If all one has to do in order to procure
a fake ID is slip cash into locker one-ten,
it stands to reason all I have
to do is see who opens said locker.
This is made tougher, though
not impossible, by my suspension.
Then Wallace will drop the
two fifty in the mystery locker.
Thanks for coming in, Logan.
Thanks for getting me out
of a calculus class, Becky.
It's Miss James please.
So the week Lilly died would
have been our second anniversary.
We were together since junior high.
Off and on?
Yeah, off and on.
- And at the time of her murder you were-
- Off!
Temporarily.
Why were you broken up?
Uh, we were supposed
to go to this party.
And, uh, Lilly was pissed
at me for something,
I can't even remember what, you know.
And, uh...Lilly stands me up.
I end up getting pretty hammered and
...wind up kissing this other girl for like three seconds.
- And Lilly saw you two?
- Nope, someone else did.
You must know her.
Word is you're real close with her dad.
You could do better.
You need to leave my personal
life out of this, Logan.
Yeah, let's not get personal about this.
You know what, it sounds
like you blame Veronica.
You know Veronica was my friend too.
And if she hadn't ratted me out...
...then Lilly and I would have stayed together.
And Lilly wouldn't have been alone that day.
I would have been there.
So, yeah, I blame Veronica.
And I blame myself for being stupid
and I blame Lilly for being
a bitch that week.
You know there is another
of looking at this, Logan.
If you'd still been together,
you might be dead too.
And what is so great about living.
Hey, Wallace. How was practice?
I was on fire out there.
Three point line, hand in my face,
fade away like Jordan! Boom!
Great.
'Course you're not listening to word I say.
So I might as well have said,
"blah blah blah, blah, blabbity blah blah."
How'd you like to go on a little field trip?
Duncan's on the move and if we hurry,
we might be able make it for the
branding and the blood sacrifice.
Actually, I planned on hitting a few bars.
I found this little beauty in my
locker after seventh period.
Let me see that.
The ink is bleeding at the edges,
the hologram is missing and
...the photo...is that your
yearbook picture, Wallace?
So what?
So this is a $250 piece of crap.
Now I'm not just falsely accused,
I'm genuinely offended.
All right, all I've heard, these guys
are bad news, so I want you to be careful.
I'm afraid, Veronica! I'm afraid!
I'm sure the Triton leaders consider
this initiation painful for their pledges
but honestly, aren't we the true victims?
Nice performance, Duncan.
I was wondering if you could introduce
me to a few of your Triton buddies.
Brawny gods just flocked up
to quiz and vex him.
If you could just tell me
who's in charge then I can
personally thank him for
putting fake IDs in my locker
and getting me hauled off
to the sheriff's department.
Quick wafting zephyrs vex bold Jim, I...
That's very illuminating.
Forget about me for a second.
Tell me about Sunday night, you do know
that the Tritons are responsible for
putting a kid in the hospital, right?
Tim is in a coma right now because of
what your secret club forced him to do.
Can you live with that, Duncan?
The quick brown fox jumped
over the lazy dog, I...
Let's get out of here.
This is going nowhere.
Heads up. Looks like your
boy's having second thoughts.
Are you ready to talk?
The judges hold the vital scores.
You shall hear my voice
once I've heard yours.
The Great Triton.
Aw, what's up? What's up?
Next up we have... Veronica Mars!
Sing! Sing! Sing!
This song goes out to my
friends in the Tritons.
One way or another
I'm gonna find ya
I'm gonna getcha, getcha, getcha, getcha
One way or another
I'm gonna win ya
I'm gonna getcha, I'll getcha
One way or another
I'm gonna see ya
I'm gonna meetcha, meetcha,
meetcha, meetcha.
One day, maybe next week
I'm gonna meetcha.
I'm gonna meetcha, I'll meetcha.
I'll walk down the mall,
stand over by the wall
Where I can see it all,
find out who ya call
Lead you to the supermarket check out
See some specials and rap then
Get lost in the crowd
One way or another
I'm gonna getcha, getcha,
getcha, getcha
Getcha, getcha, getcha, getcha
One way or another
I'm gonna getcha, I'll getcha
I'll getcha, getcha, getcha, getcha
One way or another
I'm gonna getcha, I'll getcha
I'll getcha, getcha, getcha, getcha
One way or another
I'm gonna getcha, I'll getcha
I'll getcha, getcha, getcha, getcha
One way or another
I'm gonna getcha, I'll getcha
I'll getcha, getcha, getcha, getcha
One way
Thank you.
- Let's here it for Veronica Mars!
- Nice job, V.
Meet me in the bathroom - alone.
Hello?
The Great Triton is listening.
I wanna know why you planted
all those fake IDs in my locker.
The Great Triton did that
to you because he's great.
Yeah, you're a real pal unless
you need a ride to the hospital.
The Great Triton...
doesn't really know
what you're talking about.
- Who are you?
- Jeff.
- What are you doing in here?
- Some dude, he gave me twenty bucks.
He said he wanted to pull
a prank on one of his friends.
Veronica! They found out.
I don't know how but they must have
found out I've been talking to you.
Easy! What happened?
Last night, there was a knock on the
door. When I opened it, I found a rat.
They nailed the thing alive
to the front door.
Pull it together, Rick.
We've a seven figure
lawsuit to worry about.
There's no doing this thing halfway.
We have to make sure what happened
to Tim never happens again.
You missed our last three appointments.
I'm sorry. I've been buried.
Thanks for waiting around for me.
Lilly used to make this face
when my mom was railing on me
that would make me lose it.
So I-I'd try not to look at her but I
could like, feel her making the face at me.
And that's what it's like, all the time.
I think she's watching me.
It's like whenever I do anything,
I-I can feel her there and
she can see me. It-it's like
I'm never, ever alone.
I sound like a total psycho.
- You sound like someone who lost his sister.
- And his mind.
How long have you been feeling like this?
Since I stopped taking my meds.
Uh, does your physician know about this?
Have you had any episodes?
Oh, I only stopped the anti-depressant.
I'm still taking the old stand-bys.
- What kind of episodes?
- I'm not stupid.
What kind of medication?
It does explain a lot.
The medication...calmed you.
Maybe even prohibited you from
fully processing your sister's death.
You know, all that turmoil was suppressed
for the past year, maybe it's...
finally making its way to the surface.
- What, you don't agree?
- I don't know.
I think she's mad that I don't remember.
Are you starting to forget
things about Lilly?
Oh, I remember Lilly. I-I just don't
remember what happened.
I remember being at soccer
practice that morning.
Then I was in the back of a limo and...
it was three days later and Lilly was
dead an-and all that time in between was just...
gone.
Aren't you forgetting something,
Wallace? The secret knock?
Hey! Hey!
Hey, Wallace, whatcha doin'?
Uh-huh. No, I haven't seen that one.
Yes, Dave Chapelle is great.
Listen, the real reason
I'm calling? Funny story....
Thanks, Wallace.
Uh, Veronica? I'm assuming you didn't
accidentally lock yourself in the trunk?
I'll tell you all about it later, Wallace.
Right now I have to track down Duncan
and figure out where the Tritons
are meeting tonight.
Triton. Son of Neptune.
Rise up from the wine dark sea.
Oh great one.
With your horn, we summon you
from beneath the terrible waves.
With your horn, we summon
your awesome powers.
your unrivalled wisdom.
Congratulations.
When you began this journey
twelve days ago,
you were told that it would be perilous.
I am pleased to say that this year,
all the pledges have passed
the Great Triton's test.
Oh yeah? Except for kid who
almost drank himself to death.
And the kid that you
almost scared to death.
Now that our scared number
is again complete,
you may look upon the other
Tritons as your brothers.
Hi everybody! Say repressed homosexuality.
Gotta boogie!
Man! Did you see me lay
rubber in that LeBaron?
Don't get carried away.
All right. All I have to do now is show
that the Tritons are the ones operating
the mystery locker.
Match one of their faces in these shots
with the frame of whoever picked up
the two-fifty for your fake ID.
Piece of cake.
This doesn't make sense.
Someone had to open that locker.
How else could they have gotten the money?
How else could they have
gotten Wallace's name?
Veronica, I'm still here, you know?
- One-ten is a top locker, right?
- Yeah.
No one goes near it.
I know how it went down.
Great. Can I go home?
Aaron, thanks for stopping by.
No problem, I, ah, gotta be at school
at nine for a parent conference.
You were on the way.
I found out who's been
selling the pictures.
You're not gonna like it.
It couldn't get much worse
than it already is.
Your court date isn't until
next Tuesday, right?
We might as well go ahead and
cancel that while I'm here.
Really? Why's that?
Well I thought, for a change,
you might be interested in having
the real criminal stand trial.
In the meantime, I'm gonna
have a seat in your lounge,
learn how to turn men into jelly
with a new way of walking and
wait for the bad guy to turn himself in.
I don't have time for your games.
And I don't have time to wrongfully
tamper with a government issued document
if I'm stuck here in your office.
I'll make you a little deal, Lamb.
If I don't deliver the person who put
Tim in the hospital by 5pm today,
I promise to walk,
with a little something extra,
into the courthouse on Tuesday and plead
guilty to anything you want to throw at me.
What do I have to do?
Just pick a name.
Write the name of any
student on this post-it,
put it in the envelope and have one of
your minions drop it into locker one-ten.
By the end of the day,
that kid'll have a fake ID
and you'll have yourself a crook.
And I'll be sittin' over here,
chillin' like a villain.
Hey, Rick. I'm down at the sheriff's office.
Hey, they're hauling in the
real bad guy this afternoon.
Oh, and I found out who the Tritons are.
You don't want to miss it.
I'm going to nail 'em to the wall.
So... What was the plan?
Embarrass me?
Destroy my career?
Soften up public sentiment
for a generous divorce settlement?
Turn me into Costner?
Course, you'd think of your career and
your money before you'd think of the obvious.
Did it ever occur to you, I just want
to hurt you like you've hurt me?
- You had private detectives following me.
- Only on location.
The women here I've always known.
Gosh, Mom. Gee, Dad. Will I be
going to live with Grandma?
Listen to me.
If you try to divorce me,
I will leave you with nothing.
No house.
No career. No club memberships.
No maid and no friends-
Dad, you say another word
to her and I will kill you.
I cannot take this anymore.
The thing about a felony charge is,
it doesn't get wiped off your record
just because you turn eighteen.
It's like this black eye that you
have the whole rest of your life.
- Is he here yet?
- He just arrived.
Uh, it's just like she said.
Found the fake in his locker.
Process of elimination. I didn't do it.
What, me? Are you crazy?
How else do you explain
the two fifty in your wallet?
Cough it up.
Big deal, this money's mine.
It doesn't prove anything.
Why don't you take a closer
look at the one on top.
Read what's written over Grant's head.
Veronica Mars is...
- smarter than me.
- Oh, you stop it!
So this is Rick's locker that Deputy
Sacks put the envelope in this morning?
Not exactly.
The night Tim went to the hospital,
he and Rick were using their own fake IDs,
buying their own drinks and
enjoying the profits of
their own fake ID biz.
You were never hazed.
You tried blaming the Tritons because
you were pissed off at them.
Your dad and your brother are Tritons
but you didn't measure up, did you Rick?
You weren't even invited
to join their secret society.
So when you were called into the office,
you dumped a bunch of blank
IDs and you blamed me.
But why me?
Was is just because people
would believe that I did it?
All right. Since you asked.
Last year your dad was hired to track
down a hedge fund manager for embezzlement.
That was my father.
Only the newspapers never mentioned
that his company cheated him out
of his bonus three years running.
They took our house, they took our cars.
Eventually, my parents got a divorce.
You must be proud.
Hey!
These are for you.
You look kinda cute in one of them.
Surprised but...cute.
Your secret's safe with me.
- I heard that guy Tim came out of his coma.
- Yeah.
Look, I never should have
doubted you, Duncan.
I'm sorry I came after the Tritons.
And who are the Tritons?
Another hole in Duncan's memory?
At least he can joke about it.
To pass him in the hallway,
you'd never guess that anything was wrong.
But I heard it out of his own mouth.
So what exactly is your
mystery illness, Duncan?
And what other pills are you taking?
Dispatch, this is G12 requesting assistance
for possible jumper on the Coronado Bridge.
The abandoned vehicle is a red Dodge Viper,
licence plate ECHOLLS 2
blocking the northbound lane.
Roger that, 12.
Synchro: Cfontain
www.forom.com