Previously on Veronica Mars…
Later, Deputy.
- Have you met someone?
- Alicia and I talked about it-
Wallace's mom!
I know you blame me for your mother's death.
She was your mom, my stepmom.
Dad could have used you there.
So now you're worried about Dad's welfare.
Isn't he the big bad wolf? Cigarette burns, broken noses…
I never would have hurt her.
Lilly and Weevil?
Lilly is dead. Her killer is in jail.
Abel Koontz didn't kill Lilly.
You think I killed Lilly.
You haven't seen Duncan tonight, have you? He's missing.
Bob sells a house for $136,000.
If he makes 5% commission for every house he sells,
how much money did Bob earn on this sale?
All I know is, if your boy Bob only gets 5%, um,
he's pushin' the wrong product.
I get something to write with here?
First fundamental of fundamentals of math?
Always carry your writing utensil.
So I heard, uh, Duncan Kane took off, huh?
I believe the official story involved a sick relative in Chattanooga,
but, yeah, he took off.
Well the word is he bolted 'cause you accused him of killing Lilly.
Well, word is wrong.
But, you don't think they got the right guy.
Hey, honey.
Eli.
Sheriff.
I'm just giving Weevil a refresher for his quiz tomorrow.
Well, I guess I'm refreshed.
See you at school.
Honey, do I need to recap my Concerned Dad lectures?
No running with scissors, no candy from strangers,
no smartening up the local criminal element.
He helped me out in the past. I'm just returning the favour.
What say you call it even.
I'll be at home.
With the only sane member of the Mars family.
The one who eats from the garbage and keeps bringing me dead birds?
That's the one.
Chester!
Chester, come here boy.
Come here, baby.
Chester!
Oh! Hey.
Hey.
So, uh, what do you think?
Like... in general, or is there a specific arena in which you'd like my opinion?
Do you think Duncan, uh, is just cooling off or is he, like, holed up
in some hotel room pouring peroxide on his hair and trying to file his fingerprints off?
Honestly, I have no idea.
I got the call from Celeste today wanting to know where, uh, I thought he might've gone.
What'd you tell her?
The truth.
That I don't know.
See ya.
All righty, Logan.
We'll just skip over the two minutes in heaven we had.
You wanna pretend it never happened?
No argument here.
My lips, for all intents and purposes, are sealed.
Sorry. This was on your…
Thanks.
You're Veronica Mars, right?
Sometimes.
Do you think I could, like, hire you, or something?
To help me find my dog?
That depends. Was he cheating on you?
Lost dogs aren't really my speciality.
Oh. Okay. Well, thanks anyways.
You know maybe I could make a couple phone calls, uh, maybe help with signage.
Excuse me a sec.
Breaking news. Record this date in history.
First time Wallace Fennel got the 4-1-1 before the little birdy got it to you.
Do I have to tip you over or are you gonna spill it on your own?
Clemmons just got a call.
Weevil broke into the Kane house last night.
Neighbourhood security patrol caught him in Lilly Kane's bedroom.
Hi. How are ya?
Better. Now.
I haven't heard from you in a couple days.
About to show up at your place with my tools of restraint.
Wouldn't recommend it.
Dad usually likes to have a guy to dinner at least once before he cuffs me.
So what can I help you with, Miss Mars?
My schedule? Sure. I'm off Thursday and Friday.
Um, I'm actually here to see Weevil.
Do you think I could get a minute with him?
What is it about bad boys?
Um, tattoos, leather, parole violations. Total good-girl bait.
I'm doomed.
Hey, you were here when Weevil was brought in, right?
What did they find on him?
The bad-ass standards, $0.17, a couple of condoms, a pen
Do  you have that nail file and the J-Lo poster I asked for?
Why were you in Lilly's room?
What better house for some B&E?
I know about you and Lilly. I know about the letters.
Yeah?
Well, whatever you know, that's not all there is to it.
I tell you that I'm close to finding Lilly's killer and two hours later,
you're breaking into her room. What do you expect me to think?
Look,  I told you what I was doing there. Now if you don't wanna believe me, that's on you, okay?
You gonna help me or not?
No.
All right, all right, hold on!
Diamond ring.
You broke in to steal a ring?
I was trying to get it back.
It's my mother's and she was saving it for me as an engagement ring.
At one time I was dumb enough to think I wanted Lilly to have it.
Find it?
No.
Look, uh, the Kanes want me crucified for this and now that I'm 18...
Good-bye juvie.
Hello community soap.
Yeah.
Now I see how crappy mine was.
It was heartfelt crappy.
So tell me more about the night Chester disappeared. Your front gate was open?
Oh, not mine, the McDades. I baby-sit their son Ryder twice a week.
They let me keep Chester in their yard.
- How far do you live from them?
- Far. I'm more like an 02er.
So, you put up flyers. Did you check the pound?
Well, I called and I left them my number.
You should go down there. Give 'em a flyer.
If they meet you, they're more likely to remember you and Chester if he comes through.
Sweetheart. Stay close, okay? Barry's gonna be here any minute.
Research for your next role?
No, Phil Jackson gave me this.
He said it would change my perspective.
Maybe you could option it.
Nobody  seems to believe me.
Not even my own children.
I'm done acting, Trina.
It's behind me now.
What if something so great came along.
There is nothing greater than living in the moment,
being here with the ones I love.
That's my job now.
Lynn's death was my wake up call.
Push in on our hero.
Natural light frames his handsome,
weathered face as he passes sage advice to his doting daughter.
The music swells.
Important your family is. Hm, hm.
But Daddy, there's this terrific part.
It's the villain in this independent feature my boyfriend Dylan's producing,
"Escaping Your Past". You'd be perfect. Two days work.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on, Trina.
Thank you for thinking of me, really, but,
but this,
this is what I want to be doing now.
I'm not sure if you're aware but Lynn updated her will a few weeks before her… death.
Aaron, you were removed.
Well I didn't know that but, uh,
well, doesn't surprise me.
It's cool, Barr. Dad's accountants didn't give Mom much of an allowance.
All right, I'll skip to the relevant paragraph here.
To my son Logan, I bequeath my art collection as well as all of my personal effects in the house.
In addition I leave him the balance in my investment account,
held with JP Morgan, totalling $115,000.
And me? She took me out too?
I'm afraid you were never in it.
We're looking for a lost Jack Russell terrier, Chester.
Any chance he's come through?
Pure breed Jack.
Hadn't come through. Sorry.
Veronica Mars? J-dub, this is the coolest girl in Neptune High.
Uh, she was gonna get expelled for planting a spy cam in the teacher's lounge
but she had so much dirt, they just let her off.
Is that so?
Have you seen my dog?
Uh, man, no.
Aww, I wish I had though, what a cutie.
Keep an eye out, okay?
We'd really appreciate that.
- Thanks…
- Hans.
Hans.
You really hid a camera in the teacher's lounge?
I have no idea what he's talking about.
Good morning, bro. Pop tart?
Hm, a tart from a tart.
He of the sickle wit. Can I ask you something?
Will you look at that? There was a string attached to my pop tart.
Yeah, well, I'm in a little bit of a jam. I could use a loan.
Twelve hours to hit me up for my dead mother's money.
Hm, I wonder who had that in the pool?
You know I wouldn't ask if it wasn't important.
Oh, I do.
I do.
Could I just borrow… ten grand, just for a little while.
Ten grand?
Will you just hear me out, please.
My boyfriend Dylan spotted me some cash a few months ago and…
now he's bugging me about it. I can't get him off my back.
Did you try standing up?
Thanks. Knew I could count on you.
This  afternoon we should post at the pet stores.
Pet owners are more likely to call with any tips.
Hello?
Yes I did.
Oh, you have?
- What happened?
- Nothing.
Someone was just playing a stupid trick.
Lenny Sofer. I had a crush on him last year.
I put his picture in my locker.
I never told him but somebody did.
He's gone out of his way to be mean to me ever since.
Oh, Veronica, please, don't worry about it. Really, it's not worth it.
Oh, it's so worth it.
- You prank-call Mandy?
- What if I did?
Well, I want to congratulate you. Shake your hand.
Congratulations! You've been named the world's biggest cockroach.
This award is given in recognition of your unparalleled lack of decency and humanity.
Bravo! You're gonna die friendless and alone.
Hey, everybody knows you're the biggest-
Shut up! If I want you to speak, I'll wave a snausage over your nose.
If you use Mandy again to try to convince yourself that you're not a loser,
I will ruin your life - got it?
You got it?
Okay, geez.
I can't believe you did that.
I can't believe that you didn't.
If you want people to leave you alone, Mandy, or better yet, treat you with respect,
demand it. Make them.
Hey, buddy, you wanna go outside?
Okay.
- Hello.
- Veronica, it's Hans at the pound.
I've got some bad news.
One of our guys found Chester by the side of the highway on his way in last night.
He'd been hit by a car. They had to put him down.
I found this,
saved it for you.
Backup and I walk by here almost everyday.
This used to be covered with band flyers and surf boards for sale.
Now every inch of space is covered with lost dog notices.
Hi. I was calling about your missing Yorkie?
Oh, you did. Great.
How did you find him?
Three weeks.
No, I haven't seen him, just a concerned dog lover.
How much is the reward?
Hi, is this Bridget?
Hi, I'm calling about your toy Spaniel, Louie. Is he still missing?
I'll definitely be on the lookout for him.
Good luck.
Only the owners who've offered big rewards have gotten their dogs back.
What happens to the dogs who don't bring a high enough price?
Do they end up like Chester, just left by the highway somewhere to die?
I can't do anything for Mandy but if someone is stealing dogs in Neptune,
they need to be brought down, hard,
then beaten with some sort of tyre iron, and dumped into the nearest body of water.
What did you say to Duncan?
Where  is he?
Excuse me?
I think you know why he left.
In fact, you're probably the reason he left.
What did you say to him, Veronica?
Let's start with what I didn't tell him.
I didn't tell him that his mother threatened to kill me.
I didn't tell him that his mother drove my mother out of town.
I know you think I hate you but I don't.
I just can't stand to look at you.
Every time I see you, I see everything that's wrong in my life, in my family.
I see my husband's infidelity, your mother in his office, in his hotel room.
I see your father trying to destroy us.
What are you doing here?
I… needed to ask your daughter a few questions.
You don't need to ask her anything. You just leave her alone.
You don't scare me, Keith.
If you were such a great detective, you would have seen
what was going on right underneath your nose.
Wait.
I'll help you find Duncan if you drop the charges against Weevil.
You want the intruder caught in Lilly's bedroom released.
I'm sure I should be surprised but I'm not.
Nothing was stolen, nothing was damaged.
I might have an idea where Duncan went, that's my offer.
Truth is, I have no idea where Duncan might be but she doesn't know that.
As for the whereabouts of lost dogs,
let's see who bites when I increase the reward exponentially.
Is Dad still at dinner?
Yeah.
But he's not far. I'm sure if you really tried you could blow smoke up his ass from here.
Hey Trin,
if you take your top off before you get on the mechanical bull, you won't fall off.
- What happened to you?
- Nothing.
Don't you have some homework to do, little brother?
That wannabe producer boyfriend do this to you?
What's his name, Dylan?
Dylan what, what's his last name?
- It doesn't matter.
- It does now! Tell me.
You've made it clear that you have no interest in my problems, Logan.
Don't be wishy-washy.
It's so unattractive in a guy.
I walked in on 'em making out on the couch last night.
- She was sittin' on his lap.
- Hey, hey, hey!
No discussing parental PDA at lunch! It's your rule!
Sorry. I can't be the only one with that image burned in my brain.
I had to share.
Hello.
Yes, this is Bridget.
Wonderful!
Yes, the reward is still a thousand dollars.
How 'bout this afternoon.
Great, um, I'll send my brother to meet you.
Dog Beach, three o'clock.
Thanks, buh-bye.
So I'm your brother?
I didn't mean brother like, brother.
I meant brother like...
you know.
Yeah, I know. And where are you gonna get a thousand bucks?
If you rollin' like that, you really been holding out on a brutha.
Tú, eh...lost dog.
Sure did. Hi there Louie. How you doin' boy.
I missed you.
Oh yes, I did.
Where was he? How'd you find him?
No hablo ingles.
Oh. All right, then.
Thanks man.
Gracias.
Come on.
He just ran from me, that's so weird.
- Está loco el perro.
- Sorry.
Tag, you're it.
Now it's time to play follow the dog thief.
You're walking.
Oh crap.
You stole the dog.
And it's time for the international language of...
Okay, now who stole the dog?
A dog man?
Does he drive a white van? Do you know him?
Do you know his name? ¿Su nombre?
Sure. Let's play dirty charades with the gringa.
Okay, ah, Muchas gracias.
So there's a dog man who hires these guys to return dogs.
He drives a white van, or maybe a white horse,
and he likes to spank busty women.
Basically, that's any male living in Neptune.
Come on, Louie.
All right now, please be hot, grateful, single…
Hi. I was wondering if you lost Louie.
You found him.
I sure did.
Thank you so much.
Hello, ladies.
What the…
You kill dogs?
What are you doing in my van?
I know what you're doing.
You're kidnapping 09er dogs, holding them at the pound
and then waiting for the offer of a big reward.
You break into my van and you're accusing me of stealing.
So I guess when Mandy and I came looking for Chester, you realised you screwed up,
dognapped from a poor girl.
So you just cut your losses and threw him to the side of the road.
Actually, I rounded up 101 of them.
Some crazy lady's makin' a coat.
Now get out of my van, you lunatic.
How old are you, anyway, Hans?
Eighteen. Why?
Community soap.
Always gettin' out the back of some dude's van, aren't you?
- You're out.
- Yeah.
How many get-out-of-jail-free cards do you have up your sleeve, anyway?
Pretty sure that was my last, so you might keep your felonies to a bare minimum.
I am what I am, V.
Leopard, spots, you know what they say.
- Hi.
- Hey, I need your help.
Would it be weird for me to start my own drinking game?
Like I have to do a shot every time someone asks for my help?
I need you to track down Trina's leech-of-the-week boyfriend.
Why? What'd he do?
He beat her up.
I plan on returning the favour.
All I know is his first name, Dylan
and he's producing this steamer.
Easy.
Hey.
Going out?
Oh, not at the moment but just in case, gotta have the game face on.
Camera's prying eyes are never far away.
Hey, what do you feel like for dinner?
I think I'm gonna cook.
Yeah,  I'm not really hungry.
Are you okay?
Just boyfriend stuff.
No big deal.
You know even if it's a small deal, um, you can always talk to me about it.
Well, I sorta got his hopes up about you doing his movie.
And now the financing is falling through and he's freaking out.
Trina, you gotta talk to me before you go making promises to anybody.
Dad! I so don't care about Dylan.
This is me thinking about you.
This is a career defining moment you're passing up.
I mean, hello, Travolta, "Pulp Fiction".
Really.
It's that good?
It's better than that good.
Well, I guess I better hear about it then.
Why don't you have your boyfriend come by later.
Thank you so much, Daddy.
Hi, I'm calling from Todd Russell's office at CAA. He read your script,
"Escaping Your Past" and he went nuts over it. Have you sold it yet?
Really?
Who's producing it?
Is that G-o-r-a-n?
Great. I'm sure he'll want to speak with him.
Maybe we can get you guys a deal.
Okay, we'll be in touch.
Thanks. Bye.
Dylan Goran.
Is there really an agent named Todd Russell at CAA?
There could be, maybe.
Looks like Trina's Romeo has had a little trouble with the ladies.
Two women have filed restraining orders against him in the last five years.
Dad, hey, I need Trina. It's important.
Oh, hey son. She's in the shower.
Her boyfriend's coming over later to pitch me a part in his movie.
Aren't you retired? I thought you were reconnecting with your family.
Trina is family, I'm helping her out. It's what dads do.
Oh listen. Trina's boyfriend, he's got-
Dylan's on his way to the house.
And Dad's cooking for him.
Dad. This is Dylan Goran.
Dylan, my father, Aaron Echolls.
Mr Echolls. It's a pleasure.
I'm so glad you decided to meet.
Please, call me Aaron.
Hey, taste this for me, will ya?
Perfect.
Nya, not quite.
So, Dylan.
Tell me about this part.
You'd be playing a hit man.
A junkie hit man.
It's only two days of work, three tops. You'd be in and out.
If you said yes, they'd have a green light.
A strung-out hit man, huh?
With a conscience.
He's on the junk because he's tormented.
It's the only way he can get out of his head.
Escape the pain.
You know, it sounds a lot like my old man.
He used to beat me and my mom and then…
try to drink the demons away.
Yeah, yeah. It's a lot like that.
You could definitely draw from that.
Yeah, hell, yeah.
He used to beat my mom 'til she passed out.
Then she'd cake makeup all over her face,
wear dark glasses around the house but, you know, I could always recognise the signs.
Then, finally, I got the courage up to try and stop him, but,
man, I'm just a scrawny little kid, he's built like a wall.
He put a cigarette out on my hand. Said, "Nice try, kid."
Hey, you know you can still see the scars. Look.
Wow… wow.
You see 'em there?
Uh, no. I don't.
Come on, it's right there. Right there.
Daddy!
Think you could hit my daughter, huh?
Daddy, no!
My daughter!
Daddy, stop!
Daddy!
Daddy, no!
Oh, hey son.
How was school?
Hey, you know what.
I considered your offer.
I think I'm gonna pass.
Logan.
Will you see this young man to his car, please?
I'll be happy to.
- Wow.
- Father knows best.
Do you think Lilly loved Weevil?
I don't know.
Um, Lilly never mentioned anything to me about Weevil.
I was wondering when you were gonna ask me about that.
Yeah, well.
I don't know. When he's caught in her bedroom, you know, I guess you gotta think.
You're handling it a lot better than I thought you would.
I loved Lilly
and Lilly loved guys.
- Logan, you know that she-
- You know, she used to say that her...
her parents worshipped Duncan and tolerated her.
And if she couldn't please 'em,
she was gonna go out of her way to piss 'em off.
Weevil must have been perfect for that.
I know Lilly loved you.
Well, it's just not like I loved her.
It's okay.
No, uh, you know, it kinda let's me off the hook, you know,
I don't know, I don't have to feel guilty anymore.
Feel guilty about what?
Moving on.
What are we doing?
No idea.
- We need to talk about this.
- I know.
Maybe we should just keep it to ourselves for a while and see what happens.
Meet in mop closets? Pass each other secret notes in the hallway?
Come on, I'll drive you home on the back streets.
Oh my gosh, look what I found in my cereal box this morning.
It's a spy pen.
What's a spy pen?
How covert ops of you!
I'm gonna use it to pass secret messages to all of my lovahs.
This is going to be a very busy little pen.
You okay?
Hi.
I'm going down to the city pound tonight. You wanna come with?
What? Why?
Because I believe that guy Hans and those guys from the pounds
are dog-napping pure breed dogs from the 09er zip
and holding them there until the owners offer rewards. I plan on proving it.
Do you think there's a chance Chester might still be there?
I wouldn't get my hopes up.
Listen, it's stupid and if you don't want any part in it-
I'm in.
I need to talk to you.
Me.
Finally, me.
I can't date you anymore.
Whoa, okay.
Trust me, you don't want to date me.
I'm a train wreck. Seriously.
The first guy I ever loved just dropped off the face of the earth,
probably because of something I said,
and the last guy I dated turned out to be a drug dealer,
and I just made out with my dead best friend's boyfriend,
who, incidentally, I hate.
So. Train wreck.
But, Leo, you are the sweetest-
Please. Don't tell me how sweet I am.
Well, you're also seriously hot so you'll be single for about three and a half seconds.
See. Now that's more helpful.
I'm sorry to dump this on you. I just…
I genuinely care about you and I wanted to be honest.
So, my response is supposed to be what?
Thanks?
Probably overshooting a bit, huh?
You could tell me that you understand.
And that we could still be friends?
That'd be cool…
'cause I need to follow this confession by asking for a favour.
Open up, Sheriff's Department.
We need to take a look around.
What for, look her dog's not here.
Take us to the back, now.
You wanna show me a warrant?
What are you kidding me? This is a public county building,
you're a county employee, I'm a county deputy sheriff.
Don't make me wake up a judge.
Come on.
Like you were told, missy, your dog's dead. He's not here.
Well, what's in this room here?
What's in that room?
It's locked.
It's where we keep dogs with serious contagious diseases.
You go in there you could infect other-
We'll risk it.
Your dog's not in there.
Well, lookie here.
It's Bucko
and Rufus
and Shakes
and Lola.
He's not here.
Chester's not here.
I'm sorry.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used against you-
Wait, you cannot prove that I had anything to do with this.
Please. Resist arrest, please.
- Look at me.
- Come on.
That was my dog, you killed my dog.
- Do you see what you did?
- Stop, stop. Hey, hey.
- He was my best friend.
- Stop, stop.
He's not dead, I swear. Please stop.
He's not dead?
We sold him.
We sold the dog when we couldn't get a reward.
Thank you, Leo.
Forget about it.
It was fun.
Can I ask you kind of a weird question?
Do you ask any other kind of questions?
You said Weevil had a pen on him when he was arrested.
Are you sure it wasn't a pencil.
It was definitely a pen.
Pretty girlie one too. Big, pink, plastic.
So much for your bad boy.
Honey. I know you don't always have a curfew these days
but you're starting to make me look bad.
So, you knew Weevil stalked Lilly. You questioned him.
What convinced you he wasn't the guy?
We searched him, his home, DNA, all that stuff, nothing came up.
He also had an airtight alibi.
I'll show you.
All this time you've had Lilly Kane research
in a box marked "Playboys" in the closet?
Well, I figured it'd be safe there.
It's the closed files, it's just the non-essential stuff.
You think you're slick, don't you?
Only 'cause I am.
Okay, Weevil was on community service detail.
A dozen people saw him from 8am to 2pm.
His time card confirms it.
And now that we know that Lilly's time of death is well after four?
The Kanes covered up Lilly's murder.
We know that. You think they'd go through all that for someone like Weevil?
You've come this far.
Hi, I'm Mandy.
I think my friend Veronica talked to you earlier.
Chester! Oh!
Oh, hello.
Weevil,
the night you broke into the Kanes, I gave you a pencil.
You were found with a pen.
There was no ring, was there?
You found exactly what you were looking for.
You mean this?
You can have it.
Any messages inside when you found it?
Messages from you, perhaps.
Now if I told you, it wouldn't really be a secret message pen.
Would it?
Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -