- Ow! Easy, jackass.
- You want it easy, quit moaning.
- l got to change these bandages.
- Try not taking my skin off with them.
How'd l score
the house call, Dr. Quinn?
- Trying to ease your conscience?
- My conscience is fine, thanks.
Of course, what have you got
to feel guilty about?
l mean, you just let that
damn Arab torture me.
Stood by and watched.
Now you figure you'll patch me up
and buy you a ticket into heaven?
Only reason you're here...
l'm here because no one else
wants anything to do with you.
She does.
Change your own bandages.
Looking for someone,
or just admiring the view?
lt's been two days
since Sayid took off on his own.
l keep thinking
l'm gonna see him.
He'll come when he's
found what he's looking for,
- the French transmission.
- He wasn't looking for anything.
- He left because of what happened.
- lt was an accident.
Well, accidents happen when
you torture people, Jack.
Sayid's a trained soldier, Kate.
He can take care of himself.
[loud snapping]
[screaming]
[screams]
[insects chirping]
[speaking in Arabic]
[groaning]
- [rustling]
- [gasping]
Hello?
[woman] Ew! Get him out of there!
He's drinking our water.
- What's going on out there?
- [sighs] You know, the usual.
People yelling at each other.
Doc, what do you
think this is, this...
...this rash?
lt's bad, right?
- Some kind of a tropical disease?
- lt's hives.
What's that?
ls that like poison ivy?
lt's a common rash,
sometimes brought on
by heat and stress.
- Just try to relax. lt'll clear up.
- Right.
- Try to keep your mind off it.
- Okay.
What is that?
ls that like aloe?
lsn't that for sunburn or something?
''Try to keep your mind off it''?
What else has that guy
got to do but stress?
l have enough without having
to treat hypochondriacs.
That's like my point, man.
We're all fried.
l mean, have you taken
a look at everybody out there?
Everybody's way tense.
Dude, l'm just saying,
it... it'd be sweet
if we could have...
l don't know, something to do.
We're surviving here, Hurley.
And that's my main concern,
is keeping us alive.
Things could be worse.
How?
[creaking]
[man] Ou est Alex?
Where is Alex?
#Dónde está Alex?
Ou est Alex?
[shouting] Where is Alex?
Where is Alex?
Ou est Alex?
#Dónde está Alex?
[voices continue]
- [Sayid] What?
- [man] Where is Alex?
- Who are you?
- [woman] Wo ist Alex?
- Where is Alex?
- [Sayid panting]
l don't know
what you are talking about.
- [electrical buzzing]
- [groaning]
[Sayid shrieking]
- [woman] Where is Alex?
- [gasping, groaning]
- Please, let's not...
- Where is Alex?
l don't know any Alex.
[electrical buzzing]
Stop!
[man speaking in foreign language]
[speaking in foreign language]
And all the pain will stop.
Your Shiite friends have already
implicated you in the bombing.
You planted the device
in the headquarters!
You killed two soldiers!
Confess it, and perhaps
it will only cost you your hands
instead of your life.
[coughing]
[vomiting]
[Sayid] He doesn't know anything.
- Your sources were wrong.
- [man] Perhaps.
But that's really not the point, is it?
- You handled yourself well in there.
- [Sayid] Did l?
[man] l put in for your reassignment
to intelligence division,
- if you still wish it.
- Yes, sir. Very much so.
Good. But stop calling me ''sir''
when it's just the two of us.
You're my superior officer, Omar.
For now.
[Omar] And l'll enjoy it
while it lasts.
That reminds me,
in addition to your
increased responsibilities,
a promotion is commensurate
with your move.
That is, if you won't miss
being a communications officer.
- l am willing to make that sacrifice.
- Good.
- Hi.
- Yo.
- What's this?
- They must have fallen from the plane.
What are you doing
in the jungle at night?
- Best time to hunt.
- Ethan here has some experience.
He spotted tracks that might be
a rabbit or some other rodent.
Rodent. Yum.
People are getting tired
of boar meat.
You got that right.
All right, well,
l'll take a look at these,
- see if there's anything useful.
- Okay.
Mr. Locke.
Are you going back out to hunt?
- For a bit.
- Can l go with you?
l mean, l just want to learn
how to do what you do.
[Michael] Walt!
l was... l was talking
to Mr. Locke about...
l know what you're doing.
Not gonna happen, man. Get back to bed.
Whoa, dude...
- [Sayid screaming]
- [electrical buzzing]
Please just listen to me!
l keep telling you
l don't know who Alex is!
l'm a survivor of a plane crash.
l found the wire on the beach.
l followed it.
[panting] l thought it might
have something to do with
a transmission
we picked up on a receiver.
A recording, a mayday
with a French woman
repeating on a loop for 1 6 years.
[woman speaking French]
[continuing in French]
Sixteen years.
Has it really been that long?
You.
You just happened
to hear my distress call?
l know what you are.
[Sayid groans]
Rousseau.
- How do you know my name?
- l read it.
There, on the jacket.
What is this place?
Those batteries wouldn't be able
to produce enough power
to transmit your distress call
all these years.
Broadcasts from somewhere else.
But they control it now.
They?
You. And the others like you.
[sighs] l...
l don't know who you think l am.
l've already told you. l am not...
Sayid?
- How...?
- My name was on a jacket.
Yours is on the envelope you carry.
Who is she?
The woman in the photographs.
Nadia.
Her name is Nadia.
[Omar] We cannot tie Noor Abed Jazeem
to the bombing,
but we know her sympathies.
She's a known associate
of Kurdish and Shiite insurgents.
She knows who orchestrated
the bombing?
That, my friend,
is exactly what you will find out.
[door slams shut]
Noor Abed Jazeem.
l'm going to ask you
some questions.
lf you refuse to cooperate,
l'm going to hurt you.
Nobody calls me Noor, Sayid.
You of all people should know that.
What?
You don't remember me?
Am l so different from the girl
in the schoolyard
who used to push you in the mud?
- Nadia.
- And your mother would tell my mother,
''Why must you pick on little Sayid?''
And l'd answer,
''Because he ignores me.''
You had enough attention,
with your family's wealth and...
your charm.
Such things matter little to children.
But then, you always were
older than your years,
weren't you, Sayid?
Not old enough to understand
that being pushed
was a sign of affection.
Now you're a traitor
to your country.
Tell me what you know
about the bombing, Nadia.
Tell me, or l swear
l will hurt you.
Hmm. Oh, l know, Sayid.
This is not my first interrogation
by the Republican Guard.
This is where they
burned me with acid.
They pierced my hands
with a drill.
Would you like to see
the soles of my feet?
Where they flayed the skin off?
These are handiworks of your friends.
The people you swear allegiance to.
lf you were innocent, l'm sorry.
But this bombing
is a different matter.
- Nadia...
- Go on, Sayid.
Do your work.
l'm not going to
tell you anything.
Then l'm going to hurt you.
l know.
[Rousseau] You have a bullet wound.
l was a soldier.
You were?
And are you still?
lt was a long time ago.
Tell me more about her,
the woman. Nadia.
Alex... who is he?
[Walt] l'm bored.
Can l take Vincent to the beach?
Um... l'll take you later.
l'm in the middle of something.
But there's nothing to do.
Well, you got to figure out
stuff to do.
You got to find a way
to entertain yourself.
[Hurley] Come on.
Come on. l know l saw it.
Yes.
- Hurley, uh...
- Hold on, man. l'm busy.
- Dude, can l borrow this?
- What?
- Thanks, man.
- [Jack] What are you doing?
So you heard my transmission,
- came looking for me, for answers.
- l didn't know you were alive.
- Still lying.
- l'm not lying.
Lies! Like this plane crash
that you survived.
- There were others?
- More than 40.
Then why are you alone?
- l left them.
- Why?
There was...
l did something.
Something l'm ashamed of.
And Nadia...
...you left her too?
She wasn't on the plane.
She's dead.
Because of me.
l'm so sorry.
l want to show you something.
[Michael] See, this junction here
reroutes some of the spring's water flow
into suspended basins.
Pop in some holes,
you got showers.
You keep the drinking water separate.
This is... You drew this?
- l was an artist in a previous life.
- l thought you were in construction.
- l am. l mean l was. Long story.
- [Charlie] Hey, Jack!
Hurley's worked up about something.
Said we should see it.
[Hurley] Welcome...
...to the first and...
...hopefully last,
lsland Open.
- What?
- lt's two holes, for now.
- Three par, and no waiting.
- [Jack] Hurley...
You built a golf course?
Rich idiots fly to tropical islands
to whack balls around.
All the stuff we got
to deal with, man,
this is what you've been
wasting time on?
Dudes, listen. Our lives suck.
Nerves are stretched to the max.
l mean, we're lost on an island,
running from boars and monsters...
- Freakin' polar bears!
- Polar bears?
You didn't hear
about the polar bear?
lf we're stuck here, then just
surviving's not gonna cut it.
We need some kind of relief.
We need some way that we can...
...you know, have fun.
That's right, fun.
Or we're gonna go crazy, waiting
for the next bad thing to happen.
[Rousseau] lt's a music box,
but it's broken.
Has been...
...for a long time.
lt was a gift from my love
for our anniversary.
You mean Alex.
Robert.
lt was such a comfort to me
the first few years here.
l could fix it for you.
l could take a look at it
if you freed my hands.
l'm fairly good
with mechanical things.
l'll need my hands.
What is written on the back
of your photograph?
- What are you doing?
- Did she write it, or did you?
Perhaps you don't want to tell me
because it causes too much pain.
Rousseau...
You don't need to do that.
- This is a problem, man.
- Yeah.
l mean, l know what l'd do, but...
...it's gotta be your call.
Okay.
- Give me a 7 iron.
- Got it.
[Jack] Hey!
Heads up over there!
- [Charlie] No chance!
- [Hurley] Don't blow it!
[Charlie] You won't
get anywhere near us!
[man] Hey! Doc!
There you are.
Somebody said
you went this way.
Listen, that rash of mine
is starting to spread.
lt's like the size of a grape...
What are you guys doing?
- [Jack] Uh...
- Are you playing golf?
Yeah.
Can l play?
[grunts, panting]
Sorry about the sedative.
lt was the only safe way
for me to move you.
You offered to fix
my music box.
After all l've done to you.
Striking you, shocking you.
Why?
Do you want me to fix
your music box, or don't you?
Yes. Yes, please.
Then l want to know your name.
Your first name.
Danielle.
My name is Danielle.
And how did you come to be
on this island, Danielle?
[sighs]
We were part
of a science team.
A science team
armed with rifles.
- Was Robert on the team?
- Yes.
And Alex, was he, too?
Our vessel was three days
out of Tahiti
when our instruments malfunctioned.
lt was night.
The storm...
The sounds...
The ship slammed into rocks,
ran aground,
the hull breached
beyond repair.
So...
...we made camp.
Dug out this temporary shelter.
Temporary.
Nearly two months
we survived here.
Two months before...
Your distress signal.
The message l heard.
You said ''lt killed them all.''
We were coming back
from the black rock.
lt was them.
They were the carriers.
Who were the carriers?
The others.
What others?
What is the black rock?
Have you seen other people
on this island?
No.
But l hear them.
Out there in the jungle.
They whisper.
You think l'm insane.
l think you've been alone
for too long.
[door opening]
l'm sorry.
This is all l could find.
l'll try and bring you
some fruit later on.
Are you ready to talk?
That depends on what you'd like
to talk about, Sayid.
Books?
Weather?
Since l've seen neither
locked in this cell for weeks,
l'm afraid my conversation
will suffer.
We have two suspects
in custody.
Have a look at these photographs.
All you need to do is nod.
lf you prove you're willing
to cooperate,
l think l can get them to free you.
Then l won't have these visits
to look forward to anymore.
This isn't a game, Nadia.
Yet you keep playing it, Sayid.
Pretending to be something
l know you're not.
- [Boone] You'll never believe this.
- You learned how to tie your shoes?
Funny. Someone at the caves
built a golf course.
- Are you high?
- Seriously, a golf course.
Jack's playing right now.
[Kate] Jack?
- ls golfing?
- That's what l hear.
l don't know about you,
but l'm gonna check this out.
Wait for me, bonehead.
Doctor playing golf.
Whoo! Boy howdy,
now l've heard everything.
- What's next, cop eating a donut?
- lf you want to come, you should say.
Think l'll pass on that, Freckles.
Not big on crowds.
And let's face it,
crowd's not too hot on me, either.
One outcast to another, l'd think
about making more of an effort.
Duly noted.
[music box playing]
You see?
Some things can be fixed.
[gasping]
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
[laughing]
Danielle,
please let me go.
Go?
Back to the people
l told you about.
You can't. You have to stay.
- lt's not safe.
- Not safe? What's not safe?
You need me. You can't leave.
Danielle.
[roaring]
Where are you going?
- lf we're lucky, it's one of the bears.
- lf we're lucky?
[snarling]
[Sayid] lt might be
that thing out there.
The monster.
There's no such thing as monsters.
- [Omar] You have to execute her.
- What?
The Jazeem woman
has given us nothing.
This will send a message
to others who will not talk.
l just need more time with her.
You have had more
than a month, Sayid.
Now bring her outside
and shoot her,
or l will.
ls this a problem?
No.
- lt's not a problem.
- Good.
[door clanging open]
What did you bring me today?
Put it on.
Are you going to hurt me, Sayid?
Ugh!
- [Hurley] Dude, l think you stuck it.
- [Charlie] Lucky, lucky.
This thing have a ladies' team?
- Hey.
- When'd you show up?
- While ago.
l almost didn't recognize you.
You're smiling.
l have to watch that. [chuckles]
So, how'd you come up with this?
Wasn't me.
lt was all Hurley.
l've been going crazy
to make everyone feel safe.
l haven't been sleeping
'cause l want everyone to feel safe.
He builds a golf course,
- and everyone feels safe.
- Aw, crap! Do-over.
lt's a Mulligan.
[Charlie] A gentleman's sport.
You got to get the words right.
- Dad.
- Hey. Check this out.
- You want to...
- Let me.
- Get away!
- All right.
You left me alone at the caves.
What? l left you with Claire.
She's sleeping.
Oh, man, l'm... l'm sorry.
l just... l just got caught up.
l'm really sorry, Walt.
l screwed up.
l'll make it up to you.
Hey, you wanna play?
[laughter]
[Charlie] You're breathing out.
When you go up...
Nah. There's other people waiting.
They won't mind.
You want to take a swing?
[Charlie] Michael, it's your shot.
Okay, cool.
Uh, so we'll play later, okay?
[rustling]
Put the gun down, Danielle.
Put it down on the ground.
Don't.
[door slams]
l'll take it from here.
[door shuts]
What... what's going on?
Forty meters outside this door,
there's a supply truck
that will be leaving.
They don't check them on the way out.
Only coming in. Get inside.
Cover yourself any way you can.
They won't reach the city for
30 minutes. That's enough time to hide.
Come with me.
l can't.
Desertion.
They would kill my family.
l don't have your courage.
You have more than you know.
Nadia, you have to go.
[Omar] Sayid?
What are you doing?
Don't.
- Guard!
- [Nadia screams]
Sayid! Now you have to come
with me! They'll kill you!
No. You escaped, you stole my gun,
and you shot him.
And then you shot me.
[gunshot]
Sayid!
[Sayid groaning]
[panting] Take it.
Please, Nadia.
Take it and go.
[truck driving away]
[Sayid] Please,
l don't wish to hurt you.
You already have.
Don't.
[gun clicks without firing]
The firing pin
has been removed.
Robert didn't notice
it was missing, either,
when l shot him.
- But you loved him.
- He was sick.
Sick?
lt took them...
...one after the other.
l had no choice.
They were already lost.
- You killed them.
- What would have happened
if we were rescued?
l couldn't let that happen.
l won't!
l'm not sick.
l know.
Then why kill me?
l can't let you go.
Don't you understand?
To have someone to talk to...
...to touch.
''You'll find me in the next life,
if not in this one.''
What?
The writing on the back
of Nadia's photograph.
l know what it's like
to hold on to someone.
l've been holding on for seven years
to just a thought.
A blind hope that somewhere
she's still alive.
But the more l hold on,
the more l pull away
from those around me.
The only way off this...
...this place, is with their help.
Come with me.
You don't have to be
alone, Danielle.
Your people,
the ones you're determined
to get back to.
Watch them.
Watch them closely.
Danielle!
Who is Alex?
Alex was my child.
[laughing]
Guys, please.
l've never made par
on a course before.
- [Charlie] Ah! No!
- [Hurley] Dude, you were robbed.
[Charlie] Bollocks! See that?
Okay, Jack, it's up to you.
Sink this, you get the blazer.
No pressure.
Yeah, no pressure.
Five bucks says he sinks it.
[laughing]
- You betting against me?
- Sorry, dude,
- but you're a duffer like me.
- Make it ten.
l don't have any cash,
but l'll bet my dinner on the doc.
[man] Oh!
[Sawyer] l got two tubes of sunscreen
and a flashlight says he chokes.
[Kate] l'll take that action.
[Boone] Yeah, me too.
You just bet on Jack, dumbass.
We need the sunscreen, princess.
Does your father
know you're here?
Can you teach me how to do that?
[wind howling]
[whispering]
[fluttering, whispering]
[whispering continues]