[narrator]
Previously on Lost:
Do you think he's gonna live?
- Do you know him?
- He was sitting next to me.
[Sayid] You think they
would have come by now.
- Who?
- Anyone.
What is it, like checkers?
Not really.
lt's a better game than checkers.
Two players. Two sides.
One is light. One is dark.
Walt...
...do you wanna know a secret?
Don't trust her.
She's dangerous.
- Try not to move, man.
- l have to find her.
- l have to bring her back.
- Yeah, you keep saying that.
Every time l ask who you have to
bring back, you pass out on me again.
Since your fever's pretty high,
l'm guessing you have no idea
- who the hell you're talking about.
- My cuffs.
My handcuffs.
- Where are my cuffs?
- What?
- My jacket pocket.
- l don't...
- Jacket pocket!
- Okay.
Dangerous.
She's dangerous.
- [Boone] lt's getting dark.
- [Sawyer] Pick up the pace.
- Hick.
- A little louder?
[Sayid]
We should make camp.
- What, here?
- Yes, here.
[Sawyer] l'm not stopping.
Have a nice cookout.
- Walk through the jungle in the dark.
- Afraid the trees will get us?
No. What is knocking
down the trees will get you.
You're so worried, how about
you give me the clip back?
Put your gun in your pants.
Sayid's right. Keep walking,
you're not gonna make it to the beach.
Yeah, why's that?
Trust me.
[Sayid]
This is Australia.
- This is us.
- Nice stick.
Two days ago,
we take off from Sydney.
We fly along the same northeast route
every commercial airliner
bound for Los Angeles does.
The pilot said he lost
communication with the ground?
Yeah, six hours in.
He turned around and headed for Fiji.
So we changed course.
Regrettably,
no one knew we changed course.
The turbulence hit.
We know the rest.
The pilot said we were
over 1 ,000 miles off course.
[Charlie]
They'll find us.
They have satellites that can
take pictures of your license plate.
lf only we were all
wearing license plates.
- Aren't you the pessimist.
- Basic photography: point and shoot.
Satellites can shoot,
but they must be told where to point.
Oh. Bollocks.
Okay, really enjoyed
the puppet show. Fantastic.
So we're stuck
in the middle of damn nowhere.
How about we talk
about that other thing?
The transmission Abdul
picked up on his radio.
The French chick that said,
''They're all dead.''
The transmission's been on a loop for...
How long, freckles?
- Sixteen years.
- Right.
Let's talk about that.
We have to tell the others
when we get back.
- Tell them what exactly?
- What we heard.
- l'm not a stupid translator.
- No one tell them anything.
To relay what we heard without fully
understanding it will cause a panic.
lf we tell them what we know,
we take away their hope.
And hope is a very
dangerous thing to lose.
So we lie?
- Was it a dinosaur?
- lt wasn't a dinosaur.
- You said you didn't see it.
- l didn't.
So, how do you know
it wasn't a dinosaur?
Because dinosaurs are extinct.
Oh.
Yeah.
So, what's his story?
He looks kind of...
- ...dying.
- He's not gonna die.
- He's yellow.
- His wound is infected,
- but the antibiotics will fight it off.
- What if they don't?
- His body will shut down...
- [Marshal groaning]
...one piece at a time.
His abdomen goes rigid, then...
- He looks like he's in pain.
- [groaning continues]
Yeah.
What's this?
Uh... Dude?
Uh...
- What do you think she did?
- None of my business.
- She looks pretty hardcore.
- Hurley.
What are you doing?
l'm standing guard.
You heard what they said's out there.
You took my gun off me, boy?
He doesn't believe in guns.
He goes on marches.
- l don't.
- Give it back.
- Aljazeera will protect us.
- Aljazeera's a network.
- l'll keep the damn gun.
- We should give it to her.
- Yeah. Kate should hold the gun.
- Fine with me.
Well?
[gun cocks]
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- You're sleeping in my sheep pen.
- Sorry.
- How'd you get here?
- l walked.
- You walked?
- Yeah.
- From where?
- Town.
- Nearest town's 1 5 kilometers.
- Maybe that's why l'm exhausted.
What's your name?
- Annie.
- You hungry, Annie?
So, you want to tell me why
you're trespassing on my property?
l ran out of money.
You're an American?
Canadian. l graduated from college
and figured l'd see the world.
Australia was top of my list,
so l hopped a flight to Melbourne,
but l don't know anybody here,
so l figured l'd walk for a while.
Melbourne's a hundred
kilometers from here.
l like walking.
And you just happened
to wander onto my farm?
l like farms too.
Do you know how to work one?
Yeah.
My wife died
eight months ago Wednesday.
She left me with too many chores
and a hell of a mortgage.
lf you help me with the first one,
l'll give you a fair wage
and a place to stay.
Deal.
Uh...
l'm a lefty.
[chuckles]
Dude. Dude!
Hey, dude, they're back.
[Sayid] As you and the others know,
we hiked up the mountain
in an attempt to help
the rescue team locate us.
The transceiver failed
to pick up a signal.
We weren't able to send out
a call for help.
But we're not giving up.
lf we gather electronic equipment,
your cell phones, laptops,
l can boost the signal,
and we can try again.
But that may take some time,
so for now,
we should begin
rationing our remaining food.
lf it rains, we should set up
tarps to collect water.
l need to organize
three separate groups.
Each group should have a leader.
One group for water.
l'll organize that. Who's gonna
organize electronics? You?
Rationing food?
Okay.
And l will need a third group to concern
themselves with the construction...
- Hi.
- Hey.
l, uh...
l need to tell you something.
Okay. Sure.
- [Sayid] ...stay out of the sun.
- We couldn't send out a signal
because there was
another signal blocking it.
The other signal, we heard it.
lt was a distress call
from a French woman.
She said that the others were dead.
That something had killed them all.
She was alone on the island.
lt's been playing for 1 6 years, Jack.
l wanted to tell you.
Anything else?
How is he?
The man with the shrapnel in his side.
- He's touch-and-go.
- Did he wake up?
Just for a few seconds
during the surgery.
He say anything?
No.
[Hurley]
So, what did she say?
[Jack]
She didn't say anything.
But you told her you knew.
l don't know anything.
Well, you kinda know
she's in that mug shot.
And we found those handcuffs.
And that guy keeps mumbling
''She's dangerous'' over and over.
lt's not my business.
Not my problem.
Yeah, you're right.
We'll let Johnny Fever take care
of her when he gets better.
He's not getting better
if we don't get stronger antibiotics.
- That stuff from the luggage...
- For ear infections and foot fungus.
We went through everything.
What about that luggage
in the overhead compartments?
- That's inside the plane.
- Yeah?
But the bodies are in there,
and they're all... dead.
- l'll handle it. Keep an eye on...
- Great. Yeah, l'd love to. On it.
[thud]
[banging]
[creaking]
Boo.
- [sighs]
- [chuckles]
- What are you doing in here?
- Trick-or-treat. Same as you.
You're looting.
Ah, you say ''potato...''
- What's in the bag?
- Booze, smokes, a couple Playboys.
- What's in yours?
- Medicine.
Well, just about sums it up, don't it?
You do this back home too?
Steal from the dead?
Brother, you got to wake up
and smell the gull crap here.
Rescue ain't coming.
You're just wasting your time,
trying to save a guy who,
last time l checked,
had a piece of metal the size of my head
sticking out of his breadbasket.
Let me ask you something.
How many of those pills
you gonna use to fix him up?
- As many as it takes.
- Yeah?
How many you got?
You're just not looking
at the big picture, doc.
You're still back in civilization.
Yeah? And where are you?
Me?
l'm in the wild.
[grunting]
Whoa. Whoa.
Hey, l got it. l got it.
Thanks.
l got it. l got it. Yeah.
Well, look on the bright side.
Whoever's this was is
probably better off than we are.
l got it.
[speaking Korean]
- How's the baby?
- lt's okay, l think.
Good.
So your...
Your husband,
was he on the flight?
Oh, no, l'm not married.
Oh.
l know. How modern of me.
Well, who needs men, right?
Bloody useless.
So you guys hiked all the way up
that mountain for nothing, huh?
Hey. Sorry.
l was gonna get some more water.
We haven't met. l'm Kate.
- Hi, Kate.
- Hi.
Hurley.
l was looking for Jack.
l thought he might be there.
Yeah, no.
He went to go get some medicine.
Over there.
- Where, in the fuselage?
- What?
Yeah. Yeah, in the,
uh, uh, uh...
You know,
l got to go get that water.
[thunder rumbling]
[people chattering]
[door opens]
The bank would have
given you a heck of a toaster
if you'd kept that
in a savings account.
What do l need a toaster for?
You're hiding your wages
in a tin can.
l mean, l would have
held onto it for you.
l got trust issues.
- Weren't you gonna say goodbye?
- l wrote you a note.
You've been here
almost three months,
and every time
l ask you about yourself,
you get that look in your eye.
Yeah, that one.
So l mind my own business.
l figured maybe you got off on
the wrong side of a bad relationship.
Maybe you ran. l always knew
you'd leave here someday.
l guess l hoped it wouldn't be
in the middle of the night.
- l'm sorry.
- Yeah.
So am l.
Annie, why don't you
just stay one more night?
l'll drive you to the train station
first thing in the morning. l promise.
- Okay.
- Good.
l get it, you know.
Everyone deserves a fresh start.
- [grunting]
- [gasping]
- [Kate choking]
- Damn it! Let her go, damn it!
- No!
- [choking]
- [grunting]
- [coughing]
Breathe! Come on!
Come on. Look at me! Look...
[gasping, coughing continue]
What did you do?
l was just checking to see if he...
He jumped on me.
He grabbed me.
ls he... okay now?
He's not responding to antibiotics,
he's bleeding internally,
and his fever's pushing 1 04...
...and his abdomen's rigid.
He needs water.
So, what are you gonna do about it?
- About what?
- About him.
- l told you, he needs water.
- Will he suffer?
- What?
- Will it be quick?
No, it won't be quick.
- Two, three, maybe four days.
- And he'll feel it?
Yeah, he'll feel it.
Can't you put him out of his misery?
l saw your mug shot, Kate.
l am not a murderer.
[~ Patsy Cline on radio:
Leavin' On Your Mind]
Do they listen to Patsy Cline
in Canada?
They listen to Patsy Cline everywhere.
- You hungry?
- l'll eat on the train.
You sure?
A little place up here
makes a mean burger.
- What are you looking for, Ray?
- What?
l'm not. Just...
How long have you known?
Couple of days.
l saw your picture in the post office.
l guess they knew
you were Down Under.
Why?
The reward's $23,000.
l told you when l met you.
l got a hell of a mortgage.
lf it makes you feel any better,
it was a hard decision, Annie.
My name's not Annie.
[tires screeching,
engine revving]
- Who's that you were hanging out with?
- What guy?
- You know, the bald guy.
- Oh, Mr. Locke?
Mr. Locke.
- Mr. Locke got any kids?
- He didn't say.
- Yeah, what did he say?
- l don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know? What did he say?
Some of it's secret.
He tell you not to tell me?
- No.
- Then what's the secret?
Mr. Locke said
a miracle happened to him.
Yeah, well, a miracle
happened to all of us, Walt.
We survived the plane crash.
- l don't want you hanging around him.
- Why not? He's my friend.
Hey, l'm your friend too.
lf you're my friend, you'd find Vincent.
Walt...
Look, l haven't given up on your dog.
l'm gonna do everything
l can to find him.
- You won't. You don't care.
- Yeah, l will.
l'm gonna get your dog back
as soon as it stops raining.
Listen to me.
l'm gonna get your dog back.
[rain stops]
Yeah.
''As soon as it stops raining.''
Good. Nice.
l'm gonna find your dog.
Yeah, l'm just gonna go walking
through the haunted damn jungle,
- looking for your...
- [rustling]
Vincent?
[growling]
Vincent.
- That you, buddy?
- [rustling]
- [growling]
[roaring]
[Sun gasps]
Oh.
Something was, uh...
chasing me, so, uh...
Yeah, l don't hear it now. Uh...
But y-you should probably, uh...
...head... back.
Uh...
l-l-l didn't see anything. Uh...
You know,
i-if you're worried about it,
l-l didn't see anything.
[sighs]
[Marshal groaning]
[groaning continues]
What are you making?
A whistle.
l used some tribal flutes once
in a recording session.
l'm in a band.
[groaning continues]
l wish he would just die already.
Real humane, Shannon.
Anything l can do to help?
No, l'm good. Thanks.
The others are getting upset. They want
to know what's going on inside the tent.
l'm trying to save his life.
Rumor has it you can't.
[groaning continues]
Need a light?
Came by to thank you.
- You gonna ask what for?
- What for?
- For taking that gun away from me.
- l didn't take it away.
Stickin' out of your denims, ain't it?
Sure wouldn't want to be
the one with that gun right now.
Everyone who's sitting there listening
to that poor boy scream all night
knows what's got to be done.
Only one that can do it...
is the one with that gun.
Don't act so surprised. Heard
you tell the hero the same thing.
Hell, there's only one bullet left.
Be damn near poetic.
[Marshal coughing,
hyperventilating]
- [groans] Listen to me...
- No, you need to keep quiet.
Listen to me.
No matter what she does,
no matter how she makes you feel,
just don't...
trust a word that she says.
She will do anything to get away.
- What did she do?
- l want to talk to her.
- Tell me what she did.
- l want to talk to her alone.
She got to you too, huh?
[Marshal groaning]
[engine revving]
[horn honking]
[tires screech]
[Kate grunting]
[horn honking]
[coughing]
Hey, Kate.
What was it?
- What?
- The favor.
l don't know
what you're talking about.
Last thing l heard before the crash,
you wanted a favor.
[bell dings]
[woman] The captain has switched on
the ''fasten seat belts'' sign.
Return to your seats
and fasten your seat belts.
- l have one favor to ask.
- Really?
This ought to be good.
[alarms beeping]
[woman screams]
Well?
l wanted you to make sure
that Ray Mullen got his 23 grand.
What, the guy who...
ratted you out?
He had a hell of a mortgage.
Kate...
...you really are one of a kind.
You know, you would have got away
if you hadn't saved him.
ln case you hadn't noticed,
l did get away.
You don't look free to me.
Kate, l'm gonna die, right?
- Yeah.
- So...
...are you gonna do it...
...or what?
[Hurley] Yo.
So, where's the fugitive?
ln the tent.
You let her in there alone?
What's she gonna do?
She's 1 20 pounds soaking wet.
Yeah, but she's got that gun.
- What?
- She's strapped, man. l saw it in...
...in her...
Kate.
[gunshot]
[Jack panting]
- What did you do?
- What you couldn't.
l get where you're coming from,
being a doctor and all.
But he wanted it.
Hell, he asked me.
So l don't like it
any more than you do...
- ...but something had to be done.
- [coughing]
Oh, no way.
Guys.
[Marshal gurgling]
Oh...
- You shot him in the chest?
- l was aiming for his heart.
- You missed.
- Man, is he still breathing?
You perforated his lung.
lt'll take hours to bleed out.
- [choking, gurgling]
- There was...
- l only had one bullet.
- Get out.
Get out!
Oh, boy.
[choking, gurgling continue]
Damn it!
[groaning]
[gurgling]
[gurgling, groaning stop]
[rustling]
[barking]
Shh.
l found your son's dog.
- What?
- Vincent?
l tethered him
to a tree just over there.
l know that Walt lost his mom.
l thought that you should be the one
to bring his dog back to him.
- Hey, thanks.
- Welcome.
l want to tell you what l did.
Why he was after me.
l don't want to know.
lt doesn't matter, Kate,
who we were,
what we did before this,
before the crash.
lt doesn't really...
Three days ago, we all died.
We should all be able to start over.
- Okay.
- Okay?
[~ Joe Purdy: Wash Away]
~ I got troubles, Lord,
but not today
~ 'Cause they're gonna wash away
~ They're gonna wash away
~ And I have sins, Lord,
but not today
~ 'Cause they're gonna wash away
~ They're gonna wash away
~ And I have friends, Lord,
but not today
~ 'Cause they done washed away
~ They done washed away
~ Oh, I've been cryin'
~ And, oh, I've been cryin'
~ And, oh, no more cryin'
~ And, oh
~ No more cryin' here
~ We get along, Lord,
but not today
~ 'Cause we're gonna wash away
~ We're gonna wash away
~ And I got troubles, Lord,
but not today
~ 'Cause they're gonna wash away
~ This old river
gonna take them away ~