Previously on
Battlestar Galactica...
The Threes, the D'Annas,
they were boxed
after the battle on the algae planet.
Why?
D'Anna saw the faces of the Final Five.
But if we unbox her,
she can reveal their identies to us.
The Final Five have been to Earth.
If we help find them,
they can help us get there.
So what could possibly
motivate us to trust you now?
The boxing facility resides
within the Cylon resurrection hub.
This hub controls the functions
of every resurrection ship.
We destroy the hub,
Cylons lose their ability to download.
The Hybrid on the baseship spoke
of an opera house and a dying leader.
We're going to talk to the Hybrid.
And why would you require my presence?
Because you're in my visions.
President Roslin was apparently
aboard the Cylon baseship,
along with Gaius Baltar
and many of Galactica's pilots
when it jumped away.
Hub's gone.
We're getting radiation signatures
from multiple nukes.
Baseship fragments.
The President's baseship was destroyed.
It's a different baseship.
Waiting alone in a Raptor
as the rest of the fleet jump away,
that sounds a lot like suicide, Dad.
- Why are you doing this?
- Because I can't live without her.
Plug it in. I need to talk to it.
- Let God's will be done.
- Shut up.
It's time to get some answers.
Jump!
Elosha.
Oh, my Gods.
Filters...
Filters the sublime elevation...
Why did it jump? Where are we?
I'm more concerned about why we're here.
Why don't I talk to the Hybrid?
Find out why.
- She can just do that. She can just...
- Jump!
Will you walk with me?
Galactica.
It...
What's going on? It's empty.
It is.
Feels bigger this way, doesn't it?
It's so quiet. It's strange.
A lot of things are strange.
BATTLESTAR GALACTICA
Season 4 - Episode 9
Subtitles
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )= -
Transcript
- =( Swsub.com )= -
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )= -
Wing beats of a dove drown out
the heartbeats of those who follow.
- The Six is back in the stream.
- That's unusual.
To jump again so quickly.
- What do you think it means?
- Look, it knows me.
It trusts me.
I think...
I think it even likes me.
You're getting information
from this liquid?
The Hybrid is disorganized.
It's panicking. I don't know why.
Tell me. Why are you jumping the ship?
The Six...
The Six who went among the makers
is no longer.
End of line.
Back in the stream that feeds the ocean
that feeds the stream.
The Six.
She means Natalie,
the Six who was our leader.
She's either been hurt or killed
back on Galactica.
That's why the Hybrid's panicking.
So she's upset.
Okay, fine. Can you... calm her down?
- Can you tell her to jump back?
- It doesn't work like that.
She makes her own decisions.
And we can't unplug her because now
she's wired herself into life support.
All right,
then why don't we give this a go?
Hey, stop jumping the ship, all right?
Calm your mind.
Cease countdown, cease countdown.
Circulation, ventilation, control.
Filters.
- Filters... The sublime elevation...
- Did you see that?
I just opened myself up to it,
on a spiritual level...
Jump!
Don't you just hate these people?
No.
But you don't love them either.
The people in this room are
the closest thing you've got to family,
and you...
You've been their President.
Watch them try to comfort each other.
At least you haven't taken that
away from them...
yet.
You didn't rob them of their empathy...
You just don't make room
for people anymore.
You don't love people.
Is that clear enough?
Practical enough for you,
Madam President?
I think we're going
towards the resurrection hub.
I think the mission is still on.
You sure there's no ETA at the hub?
No, the hub is jumping
and our Hybrid's jumping after it.
Sometimes we're showing up
six hours after it's moved on.
Sometimes, like, six minutes.
And one time it'll be within
one jump-length and we'll catch it.
But we don't know when.
So we'll have to assume that any jump
could be the one
that drops us in next to it.
They're gonna read our heat signatures
the second we fire up the first Viper.
Hell, they'll read our electronics.
Yeah, if we could only mask that.
Go in cold.
No electronics at all.
We'll send the Vipers out dead,
towed by Cylon birds.
They'll never see it coming.
Take out the hub's jump drive,
then settle in for the long fight.
Yeah, good, okay, okay.
But you and me, we've got to get
onto the hub in the middle of that mess
and try to find D'Anna.
We can do this.
No, I don't know.
It's crazy, isn't it? We're putting
ourselves right where the action is.
It's not a great plan.
There's no time.
Let me help you.
Athena, my wife, she learned to do that.
She never did that when I met her.
What?
I got curious about Athena.
About her and Hera and you.
So I accessed her...
Her memories from her last download.
You have her memories.
Yeah,
and they're mine now too.
They're as real as my own.
I know this must feel like
a violation of trust or something, but
I don't...
I don't want it to be strange,
okay?
Right.
Right, sure.
Madam President?
Sir?
Hope I didn't wake you.
Come in.
Thank you for the use of your Raptor.
I needed some familiar surroundings.
Don't worry. I'll give it back to
Lieutenant Pike the second you need it.
About that.
This mission, it's very risky.
If there's even a chance
that we can go in and blow up that hub
and end Cylon resurrection
for all Cylons forever,
we must take it.
I cannot back away from that.
Yes, sir.
If
and when D'Anna
comes back from the dead,
bring her to me.
I think the Cylons think
that she'll be interrogated
by both groups together.
I'm sure they do.
Bring her to me.
She knows the identies
of the Five Cylons
in our fleet.
It is a matter now of human security,
and I will not
let the Cylons have audience
to that discussion.
I want to talk to her alone.
Yes, sir.
Good.
Welcome home, D'Anna.
You told me I'd never
have to go through this again.
I lied.
You thought
you were putting me away forever.
So what changed?
War.
A genuine Cylon civil war.
Ones and Fours and Fives
against Twos and Sixes and Eights
that objected to your retirement.
Now your supporters are working
with humans against all the rest of us.
All in your name.
Boomer's an Eight.
Shouldn't she be on the other side?
Boomer's my pet Eight.
She's seen the light of reason.
And an Eight can make a passionate ally.
Till she sees something shiny.
Why'd you bring me back anyway?
I brought you back to heal us, sister,
and end this shameful war.
Since Cylon pilots don't use call signs,
we're gonna be painting
unique identifiers on all their birds.
It's a relief.
You address them, use that number, okay?
Should've scrubbed
this frakkin' mission.
Everyone, listen up.
These heavy Raiders
aren't like the other Raiders.
They aren't gonna make any hinky moves.
They're under control of their pilots.
The Cylon pilots
are in charge of their birds.
- There are tiny pilots inside of them?
- We do our jobs.
- Training is just as good as yours.
- Oh, yeah?
Twenty-some of you
I've taken out weren't that good.
Redwing.
Redwing!
Now let's talk about
the surprise element.
First wave of Vipers are gonna ride in,
engines cold, dradis and comm off, okay?
You're gonna come in towed
by cables from the heavy Raiders.
- We're rigging 'em up now.
- Captain, I don't know,
if they're all tied together here,
kissing their gasholes so to speak,
and they tap on the brakes,
we're gonna smash right in the back.
They won't. It'll work, you guys.
Really. When you're close enough,
the cable's gonna disconnect.
We're mounting
explosive charges to cut it.
Hold it, hold it.
- We cut the cable, right?
- Cylon pilots cut the cable.
Then you sling out of their birds
and you turn your power on.
You're gonna be gunning
directly at the hub's FTL.
Then it's an all-out fight until
we get there with the nukes.
So if the Cylons don't lift up,
we're toast?
No, look, I'm serious.
Pilots!
You've flown with Cylons.
You've flown with Athena.
You put your life in her hands
and she hasn't betrayed you.
Well, I am the same as her.
Now all of these Cylons here,
all of these people,
they're pilots like you.
And they're gonna be out in the soup
with you taking out other Cylons,
just like Athena does
every time she's asked to.
And when that hub is taken out,
all of their lives will be at risk.
Just like yours.
So you might want to think
about how you're gonna work together.
Because we're all dead if you don't.
Moving on.
Just go and ask it already.
I've been told that you said
something about an Opera house, and I...
- Because it seems pointless.
- Look, there was an Opera house.
An Opera house.
Are you listening to me?
Apparently I was in the Opera house.
I had a vision.
I was chasing after a little girl.
I came to a door. I saw
Dr. Baltar and the Six take the child.
And... She's not listening.
Protect the child.
She said, "Protect the child."
- That's what Caprica said.
- I was the one holding the child,
so obviously I was the one
protecting the child, wasn't I?
- In the opera house...
- No.
It wasn't at all clear
what you were doing.
- Let me listen.
- Booting up.
Obviously you've done this
a thousand times before.
- I'm doing the same thing you're doing.
- No, you're not actually.
Because if you'll watch what I'm doing,
I'm actually focusing on her, all right?
Tell us what happened
in the opera house, all right?!
The only thing you're doing is yelling.
- Such a format will close the doors.
- "Close the door". No, open the door.
I want to open the door! Do it again!
I'm going for a walk.
Love to see you do any better.
- All right, I'll do it. Open the door!
- Three!
The Three is online.
- Accessing data. Loading data.
- The Three is D'Anna. D'Anna is online.
- D'Anna... D'Anna's back in a body.
- Booting up.
Jump!
Why are we doing this again?
<I don't want to see this again.
The ancients used to say:
"a people is only as strong
as the body of its leader."
If I follow that thought,
are you saying that humanity died
because I died?
If you're my subconscious,
I've gotta say
you're a little full of myself.
Humanity didn't die because you did.
The ancients got a lot of things wrong.
The body of a people is not the same
as the body of its leader.
But the soul and the spirit might be.
Oh, I see, so you're only laying
morality at my feet. Well, that's okay.
I can take that.
There are a lot of people who have sins
far greater than mine.
You're thinking of Gaius Baltar.
"Then I dug into the stump
"and pulled rocks from the ground
until my fingers bled.
"I collected seeds
from the few fruits the island offered,
"and planted them in long,
straight furrows,
"like the ranks of soldiers.
"When I finished,
I looked at what I had done.
"I did not see a garden.
I saw a scar.
"This island had saved my life,
"and I had done it no service."
I can see a real hierarchy around here.
And I have to tell you, you're on
the lower end of the scale, my friend.
Yes, you are.
Which is odd
when you think about the Cylon god.
They told you about God, didn't they?
I'm not even really sure if the Hybrid
was referring to D'Anna,
but if it's true...
- It certainly would make it easier.
- How so?
Well, we...
wouldn't have to find a...
Find a body.
Yes, good. Okay.
Go get her and bring her here.
Something else?
It's just once you have what she knows,
I can't help feeling like you could try
to keep Earth for humans only.
And I just...
Madam President, that doesn't seem...
What?
... honest.
You're supposed
to be conducting a fair deal here,
and instead you're taking D'Anna off
by yourself.
- Taking what she knows.
- Slow down, Captain.
At best,
D'Anna knows the identies
of the Cylons in our fleet.
And at best,
they know a way to Earth.
So you're not denying you'd keep the way
to Earth to yourself if you could.
I'm not saying that's true.
I will say
that if the Cylons had the option,
that's exactly,
exactly what they would do.
No, I don't think so.
Not the Sharons, the Eights.
Captain,
you are not married
to the entire production line.
I cannot afford
to be sentimental right now,
and I cannot afford you
to be sentimental either.
If you can't do this job,
find me someone who can.
What is that?
I think we're there.
Something's going on.
Another baseship, unscheduled.
You've gotta speak
to the Twos and Sixes and Eights
and tell them they've gone too far.
No.
Why don't you ask about the final five?
You never ask about them.
Because I don't believe
we're meant to know them.
Well, I'll tell you.
I will tell you.
I'll start shouting out their names.
Why do you risk it?
Are you going to help end this war
or are you useless?
25 heavy Raiders just launched
from the new arrival,
heading our way.
Come on, let's get this carpool started.
Now!
Cut the frakkin' cable now,
you frakkin' bastard!
The inhibition's been lifted.
- I sense it.
- It's the rebel baseship.
I think they're gonna attack.
- They're gonna blow the hub.
- That would be mass murder.
Death would be permanent for all of us.
They've gone insane.
Permanent death?
Well, that makes this all
the more meaningful.
Helo, we've blown their FTL.
That hub's not going anywhere.
Okay, take us down.
Well, he's your god as well.
And God doesn't want
any of his creations to be...
slaves.
Not that you're a slave...
Exactly.
Go.
This place is gonna go. Grab her.
Run!
Hardball, Pike. I'm hit.
My attitude control is down,
and I can't even program
any frakkin' ordnance.
Pike, hardball.
Man, don't jump.
You'll never make it to Galactica.
You know how many jumps that is?
I'm out of here.
Okay, I'm jumping back home.
Karl...
Come on, let's go.
Go!
There was this dog, see,
and the master had placed a bit of food
on the edge of its snout.
And the dog had to wait
until he was told he could eat it.
I know.
Pathetic.
Pathetic, isn't it?
Put him over there.
Wait.
Easy, Smith.
Easy, easy.
Okay.
- Find out what's going on!
- Yes, sir.
Thank you.
- Easy, easy.
- Thank you.
Good.
Okay, wait.
Sorry.
You have this...
you have this big hole in your hide,
as Cottle would say.
Okay.
All right.
I'm gonna do this again.
- Thank you.
- It's the least I can do.
I think you're gonna live... as usual.
You know something?
- What?
- You're very pretty.
Man, that morpha worked fast.
Still.
Do you know why I'm so serene right now?
You're doped out of your mind?
Because I know God.
You need God, Laura.
Really, you'd be a different woman.
I know God.
Therefore, I know myself.
Truth is...
I was harboring the most awful,
desperate guilt.
A heavy, dark...
unimaginable...
soul-breaking guilt.
Now it's gone.
Now it's gone, it's...
been transformed into...
I have been transformed.
What was your guilt about?
I have no guilt.
I gave the access codes to the Cylons.
They wiped out most of humanity.
Of course, I didn't know that's what
I was doing at the time exactly,
but that's what I did.
And when I realized what I had done,
the magnitude...
In that moment, I was saved.
I was loved...
by God.
Looking back...
I think I was rewarded.
Rewarded.
Pythia talks about the flood
that wiped out most of humanity.
Nobody blames the flood.
A flood is a force of nature.
Through the flood,
mankind is rejuvenated, born again.
I was another flood,
you see.
I blamed myself.
But God made the man
that made that choice.
God made us all perfect.
And in that thought,
all my guilt flies away...
Flies away like a bird.
I can give you that peace,
Laura, that freedom.
Pray with me.
Okay.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- It's all right.
You're fine.
Don't do this to me.
Don't do this to me, please.
We have D'Anna on board.
We are clear of the hub.
Commence nuclear strike.
Repeat, nuclear strike is a go.
And with a whimper, every Cylon
in the universe begins to die.
Yes, that's right.
And it's a good thing, D'Anna.
Because now there's no difference.
We can all start trusting each other.
Don't do this to me.
Don't...
Don't do this to me, please.
- Please.
- No.
I'm not saying Baltar's done more good
than harm in the universe. He hasn't.
The thing is,
the harder it is to recognize
someone's right to draw breath,
the more crucial it is.
If humanity is going to prove itself
worthy of surviving,
it can't do it on a case-by-case basis.
A bad man feels his death
just as keenly as a good man.
What do you want from me here?
Laura.
Just love someone.
Love...
You go.
You go to your rest now.
I'm not gonna be selfish anymore.
You go.
Rest.
No.
No...
No, please, no.
Stop bleeding.
Stop the bleeding.
Okay, good. Don't go.
All right, we've gotta get D'Anna
to the control room.
No, that's not the plan.
What? What plan?
Interesting.
Please don't go, Gaius.
Please.
I don't know how...
All right, put it in.
I have to take her directly
to the President. No one else.
That wasn't the deal.
I'm just doing
what she told me to do, okay?
Double dealing.
It's very human.
You never got that, Eight.
No more.
No more, don't go.
Please don't die.
Live.
I'm not saying I agree.
I'm saying it's my orders.
So I pretty much just made
a prize fool of myself, didn't I?
Trust.
Can we go find the President now?
Gaius?
Gaius, it's me.
The hub's been destroyed.
Good.
Don't let anyone in here
whatever it takes.
Thank you.
He's injured,
but I think he's going to survive.
I think it's gonna be
a long time jumping back.
I've got time.
Is that right?
You went to a lot of trouble
to bring me here.
Deceiving your so-called allies.
I suppose you've got
some questions for me.
Yes, I do.
I'd like to talk
about the five Cylons in my fleet.
So you know about the Final Five.
I know they're supposed to know
the way to Earth.
But you don't know
that you're one of them?
Your face!
It's ridiculous! No, look,
I'm not giving you any names.
Not until I feel like I'm safe.
Cause information is all I got, sweetie.
I'm mortal now.
In fact, I'm the only Three
in the whole darn universe.
So I gotta worry
about protecting myself.
I'll tell you who the Final Five are
when you take me back to your fleet.
And by the way, Laura,
I would've said the same thing
if you'd have met me
with a whole lot of Cylons,
cause I don't trust anyone right now.
So all this deception,
complete waste of time.
To remove the pump
with the attached hose and wiring,
simultaneously release the three tangs
while pulling the pump
out of the retainer
along with the line and wiring.
You lied to me.
Did I?
I thought I was earning
humanity's right to survive.
It's not a vending machine, Laura.
You don't save a life, and then...
cue the celestial trumpets...
Here's the way to Earth.
I know.
Jump!
Disorienting, isn't it?
All these little limping steps back.
I like it.
I'm used to it.
Every jump brings us
a little bit closer to home.
Galactica.
My home.
Maybe there's something there for me.
Maybe even closer.
Missed you.
Me too.
I love you.
About time.
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )= -