Thus shall it come to pass.
The dying leader shall know
the truth of the opera house.
Where did you hear that?
Who told you that?
The Hybrid from the baseship,
before they unplugged it.
I've got to find out
about these visions.
Plug it in.
It's time to get some answers.
Can I see what you drew?
Hera!
Get away from my child!
You are never gonna take Hera.
Jump!
Heavenly father...
Give me the strength,
the wisdom, and above all...
Quickly.
All right,
on three. One, two,
three, lift!
Keep some pressure on that wound
until I can get to the artery.
Mask on.
- The President's been kidnapped?
- Baltar was with her.
- Are you saying he's responsible?
- I heard it was the Cylons.
- No, my people say she was shot.
- What are you talking about, Roslin?
No, one of Adama's marine shot a Cylon,
that is how this entire thing has begun.
- Where's Zarek?
- I don't know.
- Where is Zarek?
- Who's in charge here?
Vice-President Zarek is still waiting
to talk to you. What should I tell him?
Sir?
Deck crew says they just shipped over
the last of the Vipers.
That means we're down forty birds,
almost as many jocks.
We're gonna have to reconfigure the CAP.
Rethink our defense posture.
- Where is she?
- Clamp.
- Marines are holding her.
- My quarters.
Nobody has told us anything.
- No, no, no.
- All right, everybody.
Mister Vice-President,
we have some questions for you.
Thank you. Just calm down please.
Everybody, everybody,
just calm down, please.
Mister Vice-President,
it's really important that we know,
is the President dead?
- We have no information...
- She was assassinated by the Cylons?
There's no truth to that,
at least as far as we know.
- Then what the hell do we know?
- Clearly, our first priority
is to get out as much
verifiable information
as we can to avoid a general panic.
To that end,
I asked Admiral Adama to come
and answer our questions directly.
Unfortunately, he wouldn't take my call.
At this time, when...
However...
Please, just a moment.
President Roslin
was apparently aboard the Cylon baseship
along with Gaius Baltar
and many of Galactica's pilots
when it jumped away,
after one of their own leaders was shot
aboard Galactica.
We have no idea
when or if they will return,
if the President or the other captives
will be subject to reprisals.
For now,
under the powers granted me by law,
I have taken over as President.
Hear, hear.
By refusing even to meet with Zarek,
you're simply helping him
fan the Quorum suspicions.
Their suspicions don't concern me.
Look, maybe
he's not the man we hoped for,
but he's next in line.
The fleet needs reassurance
and stability,
frankly the kind that only
its military commander can offer.
If this fleet needs reassurance,
then you reassure them.
That's your job, now.
You can tell Zarek
he can go to hell.
Why?
- Sir.
- Do you hate your people so much,
did you look for any excuse to kill one,
or did you deliberately try
to sabotage this truce?
No, sir, of course not.
Then you tell me why.
You make me understand why you did this.
They were gonna take her... the Six.
She was gonna take my child.
There were too many witnesses.
They all said the same thing.
Your daughter was lost.
The Cylon merely kneeled down
and was talking to her.
Maybe that's what it looked like, sir.
- But I know...
- You knew better.
I had a vision.
A vision where the Six and Baltar
were taking Hera away from me.
A vision!
It was more than just a vision, sir.
When I saw them together,
I knew that they would take her,
that they would take away my child.
You murdered
an unarmed woman.
And by doing so,
you put the lives of every single person
in this fleet at risk.
And quite possibly,
cost the lives of the President
and your husband.
You disobeyed the direct orders
of superior officer.
But more importantly,
you betrayed a promise to me.
I trusted you.
I will accept any form of punishment
that you think I deserve.
I just ask
that you please don't take away Hera.
I'm afraid the brig
is no place for a little girl.
Guards!
- Get her out my sight.
- Yes, sir.
At one time, Admiral Adama
supported Gaius Baltar's administration.
Is there a chance he'd support yours?
I'm afraid
only Admiral Adama can answer that.
Then I will address this question
to Delegate Adama.
Do you think that your father will
hand over power to this administration?
No.
BATTLESTAR GALACTICA
Season 4 - Episode 8
Subtitles
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )= -
Transcript
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )= -
Fine.
Recon Raptor just reported back.
The resurrection hub's gone.
No sign of the baseship
carrying the President,
assuming that's where they were headed.
They were determined
to resurrect the Three.
The one we used to call D'Anna.
To do that, they gotta go to the hub.
You find it and we'll find them.
- Easier said than done.
- Maybe.
We've got other problems.
Starbuck's having trouble fielding
enough planes to fly a standard CAP.
She wants us to consider
having the fleet bunch up tighter
so it's easier to defend.
Means counting on a bunch of civies
flying close formation.
Yeah.
Organize it.
I got you appointed
to this job.
Pulled strings,
called in favours.
All because I thought
you might do some good.
Now, you're advising me
to step aside from a position
that by law
is mine.
- A position I was elected to.
- But you were never elected President.
But I was elected to office!
Which is more than Roslin can claim.
Why do you think
she kept me on in the first place?
To thank me for rolling over?
No.
No, to help legitimize her coup.
In the military,
we used to talk
about facts on the ground.
Well, the facts on the ground are these:
Right or wrong, Adama will never
recognize you as President,
and we need someone he will.
Now, the Quorum has the legal authority
to appoint interim President
in a time of crisis.
And I suppose you have someone in mind.
No.
No, not yet.
Which is why we need
to form a search committee
and start looking for a candidate
as soon as possible.
Well,
good luck with that.
So Zarek, do you really believe
that this government's in danger?
Let's face facts. What we had these past
five years isn't a true government,
but a tacit agreement
between a military strongman
and a political strongwoman
to rule together by fiat.
I heard you asked the Quorum
to authorize
the creation of a civil defense force.
After what happened
during the last military coup,
we don't want to depend on Galactica's
marines to guarantee our safety...
You see the problem?
Lampkin's first rule of legal dynamics.
When an irresistible force
meets immovable object,
stand aside
and wait for the class action suit.
Except I'm not sure
if it's to anyone's benefit
if we just sit around,
waiting to pick up the pieces.
This thing's heading for a showdown,
there's gonna be bloodshed, unless...
Unless you can find someone else.
Someone your father won't reject,
someone the Quorum will approve of,
someone to take Tom Zarek's place
as interim President
until the next round of elections.
Don't take the case, Counselor.
It's a loser.
I have to.
We have to.
No one on the Quorum
is going to lift a finger.
Zarek's got them inhaling fear
and exhaling anger.
But you have taken
the pulse of the fleet
and you know character.
And frankly, you need a reason
to get out of this room.
Unless you want to start discussing
what's been keeping you here.
So you won't be dissuaded, will you?
Not even when you hear my fee?
- Fee?
- Appearances to the contrary,
I'm actually in this for the money.
I have a reputation to maintain
after all.
Okay, so what did Roslin offer you
to defend Baltar?
Room with a view.
Well, I'm not sure
I can improve on that.
Then pro bono it is, Counselor.
A word to the wise.
Sometimes it's better to settle
for what you've already got.
Colonel Tigh.
I understand you've
developed a relationship
with the Cylon prisoner.
That's not the word I'd use,
but she has been more cooperative.
See if she'll tell you
anything about the hub.
Bill.
We'll find her.
We'll find all of them.
The resurrection hub. How do we find it?
- I'm sure the others have told you.
- You tell me.
Only our hybrids can locate it.
And then,
only after it completes a jump.
Even they can't anticipate
where it's going.
You're holding back something.
I know it.
- You're lying.
- I have never lied to you, Saul.
Why don't you trust me now?
Because there are
too many lives at stake, lady.
Your buddies took off
with half an air wing,
not to mention the President
of the frakking colonies herself!
She's the real reason you're so angry.
So worried. I can hear it in your voice.
Why?
Why is a dying woman
so important to you?
Not to me, godsdamn it, to the old man!
Admiral Adama?
Saul?
- Do you love me?
- What?
Be honest with me.
I've been honest with you.
I don't believe this.
You're asking me if...
Attention.
Set condition 1 throughout the ship.
This has gone too frakking far!
I don't know what kind of mind games
you are playing with me, lady,
but it ends here!
What do we got?
One of our missing Raptors
jumped into dradis range.
- You sure it's ours?
- Transponder checks out.
It's one of the Raptors
that boarded the rebel baseship.
No radiological signature.
Racetrack and Skulls
are on their way to intercept.
Actual, Racetrack.
I'm eyeballing our bird now.
Looks shot to hell. Venting fuel and O2.
Still no response to hails.
Someone had to jump that bird.
I can't see a frakking thing from here.
Skulls, take the wheel.
I'm going for a walk.
Decompression check okay. Opening hatch.
Safety line secure.
Moving toward the Raptor.
I'm seeing major damage to the canopy.
Looks empty inside.
I've got the hatch open, but it's stuck.
Grav field's off.
It's Pike.
He's dead.
This is the shuttle
she took over to the baseship.
Laird was able to salvage
the flight data recorder.
Puts the originating jump point deep
in sector Delta 9.
President Zarek called again,
he heard about the Raptor
- and he's waiting to be briefed.
- Recall the CAP.
Spin up the FTLs.
- What about the fleet?
- Let's go.
We are essentially looking
for an understudy. The quandary is...
One doesn't generally
get the chance to...
wield political power
without the ambition
to actively seek it.
Easy, Lance.
That same ambition
often compromises the unselfish motives
that begat the quest.
In other words,
a battle of Id versus Ego
that Ego rarely wins.
Roslin never sought power.
Exception that proves the rule.
One could argue that Laura Roslin
is a study in repressed ambition.
Just like you, Mr. Adama.
Never seeking out a job
until it's handed to you.
Flight leader, Battlestar commander,
Quorum delegate.
A man doesn't carve out
a path like that through life without...
All right, enough of the psychoanalysis.
Let's get back to the job in hand.
Does your father have some other place
he wants to go?
What?
Where the hell did they go?
And why didn't they tell us?
Galactica, Racetrack. We've located
the source of the transponder.
It's Sandman's Viper all right.
- But no Sandman.
- Affirmative.
Keep searching.
We're getting radiation signatures
from multiple nukes.
Baseship fragments,
other debris
indicative of resurrection technology.
I'm afraid
it paints a pretty clear picture.
They found the hub
and they destroyed it.
Looks like our pilots helped.
Question is, where'd they go from here?
You are way too close to this.
The President's baseship was destroyed.
It's a different baseship.
We'll search every square inch
of this debris field,
- until we come up with a clue.
- What, and leave the rest of the fleet
back there with their asses
hanging in the wind?
Detail four Raptors to stay behind.
They keep searching
until they find something concrete.
Give my order.
People, listen up.
What are we gonna do here?
All right, everybody.
Gather around, please.
- Mister President.
- Please, please...
Sorry, Admiral Adam will not be coming
to answer your questions.
I did learn, however,
that he contacted the fleet's Captains
to inform them that several
of their ships will be requisitioned
to expand the search for Laura Roslin
and the missing baseship,
while our tylium shipments will be
diverted to support that mission.
But he's bypassing us completely!
I understand... We're doing the best...
I understand.
We're trying to get some communication.
Captain Franks.
I was impressed by her gravitas
during her turn as judge
in the Baltar trial.
That and her vote, naturally.
No. She's already been approached to run
for office. No interest in politics.
Sadly, now she really impresses me.
Gods.
You ever feed that animal?
Where is he, anyway?
Come on, Romo.
Let's put our heads together.
Who would Adama respect as President?
What does this...
search for paragons net us anyway
except greater guilt
at our own failings?
Or worse.
The idiot's illusion of a clean slate,
a fresh start.
We haven't ruled out
all these names yet.
This one's a looser.
An exercise in futility.
Lawyers...
How this is gonna affect the President?
The break in her treatment?
Assuming no other changes
in her circumstances?
Yes.
Doloxan really kicks your ass,
so she actually
might feel better at first.
But any break gives the cancer
a chance to regroup.
Makes it that much harder
to beat it back.
Plus she's taken a hit
to her immune system
so she'll be vulnerable to infections.
How long?
The sooner you get her back here,
the better her chances are.
And while you are digesting that,
I have some other news...
I ran some tests on your Cylon prisoner.
Guess what I found?
Raptors are due back in a few hours.
Granted, if they'd found anything
we would have heard from them by now.
Still,
once we correlate their reports...
I'm not interested...
in the search.
You're not?
I know that you've been spending
a lot of time interrogating the Six.
But now, the brig guards tell me
that every time, you order them out,
and you turn off the cameras.
I'm not torturing her
if that's what you're worried about.
I'm not.
That I could almost understand.
This I can't.
Cottle tells me she's pregnant.
What the frak
have you been thinking, Colonel?
Do you deny it?
You don't.
You can't!
What the hell have you been thinking?
Who is interrogating who?
How many  secrets
have you told this thing?
How can you even ask me that?
Question my loyalty?
Your loyalty?
I need more than your loyalty.
You're my first officer.
I need judgment.
I need your competence.
I'm through jeopardizing this ship,
because of your weaknesses.
- Yes, your weaknesses!
- You're risking all our lives for what?
Our missing pilots? No, for a woman.
- For a frakkin' woman!
- You watch what you say about her!
She's the President. Not some skinjobs
that I've been banging.
What do you think Ellen
would say about this?
- Leave Ellen out of this.
- What would she say about her husband
impregnating a frakking Cylon prisoner.
You mother frakker!
You know how many times
I've had to repair this thing?
What are you gonna do with that woman?
What are you gonna do about Laura
if you ever find her?
I don't know.
Have the Raptors and the civilian ships
begin the search
from Phantom's last known position.
Is that a problem?
Sir, respectfully,
I've already got two missing pilots,
and hardly enough birds
left to protect this fleet.
Now you're asking me to send
the Raptors out on a blind search
looking for a ship
that very well may be destroyed.
My people are gonna feel like they're
being asked to go on suicide missions.
I'm not asking.
You're dismissed, Captain.
Admiral Adama?
Mr. Lampkin, what are you doing here?
Writs of forfeiture
for the ships you're borrowing.
The captains want
to be absolved of any blame,
should anything untoward happen.
One of the less ennobling consequences
of a legal culture.
No one wants responsibility.
Lee said you once gave him something,
before a mission.
A lighter, was it?
Belonged to my father.
Foolish to think a hunk of metal
could keep him safe.
And yet, that's what we do, isn't it?
Hang on to hope
in every hopelessly irrational way
that we can.
But not like those poor bastards
giving away their luck
just when they need it most.
It's like they've given up.
If you've never been in combat,
you have no idea what they're thinking.
I always imagined you
a realist, Admiral.
Not one to indulge a vain hope
at the cost of lives.
But then...
everyone has his limits.
"Sine qua non", as they say.
Without which not.
Yes.
Those things we deem essential
without which you cannot bear living.
Without which life in general
loses its specific value,
becomes abstract.
You may have a point, Counselor.
Then while I'm on a roll...
Tom Zarek may not be an ideal President,
but we could do worse.
You're right.
There are limits to my realism.
Goodbye, Counselor.
I can't give up on her.
I can't let her go.
I've lost my objectivity.
And now that I see that,
I have no choice.
Tell the Quorum that I'm relinquishing
command effective immediately.
No man is perfect.
No man is less perfect
than a candidate for high office.
And thus...
the ranks of likely suspects
is winnowed to none.
What if we're going about this
backwards, hey, Lance?
What if instead of picking names
and finding fault,
that we ask ourselves
the qualities that we want...
No.
No, what we need
is a new chief executive
and see who fits that bill.
Honesty, of course.
The wisdom to recognize the correct
from popular choice.
As well as the courage
to see it through.
Experience.
When the wrong choices cost lives
and the right ones save.
Tall order.
We might as well spell out one name.
Just one.
One we knew from the start.
Sometimes you take on a losing case
and you make yourself a believer.
Other times,
no matter what you tell yourself...
in your heart...
you know the outcome is fixed.
The verdict inevitable.
Lance, defense rests.
Come on.
Apologies.
I couldn't wait to tell you.
- Tell me what?
- We found our candidate.
Someone the Quorum won't hesitate
to approve
even over Zarek's objections.
Someone the Admiral can't help
but accept.
Yeah? Who?
Congratulations, M. President.
My name was never on that list.
Of course not!
That would be too blatant.
But it is everything
you always wanted, isn't it?
Why you had me cross
47 names off that list.
Come on.
Admit it.
Savor your victory, M. Adama.
'Cause you'll never get
the chance to serve.
- What are you doing?
- Why?
'Cause you're perfect for the job,
of course.
'Cause after the vicious aberration
that was Baltar's presidency,
and the bitter disappointment
that was Roslin's,
you are
a shining beacon of hope.
Only hope is the last thing we need.
We're a doomed race.
And it's time that we made our peace
with that essential truth.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- Why?
You wanna know why?
Open it!
Frak!
That's right.
They killed my cat!
- They?
- They!
Those debased dregs of humanity
out there.
Our lost tribe in search of a new home
so they can roost and rot again.
Romo, how long has the cat been dead?
How long?
It's irrelevant, it's immaterial.
- Since it wasn't even my cat!
- Romo.
- It's been dead for weeks.
- It belonged to my wife.
I just retrieved it
from a vet on Geminon
when the bombs started to fall, and fate
presented me with a choice.
I could get back on that shuttle or
I could run home and...
try to save my family.
- How do you think I chose?
- Romo,
we've all had to make difficult choices.
You don't think I know?
Your wife's name was Faye.
You had two daughters,
Jennifer and Katie.
There were over 200 passengers
on that shuttle.
Only a handful chose to stay behind.
Right, it was in your file
when you handed the job
as Baltar's council.
But no one blamed you, Romo,
because at a certain point
we all made decisions
that saved our lives
at the cost of others.
You think you're unique, Romo?
- Think your sins are so special?
- Is that it, Counselor?
You're gonna rest your entire case
on that pathetic little bit of insight?
No...
on this.
The clean slate, the fresh start,
maybe they are illusions,
like you said.
But at a certain point,
faith in ourselves,
in our right to survive,
as a species, as a people,
that's not a given...
That's a choice.
Well, I've made mine.
And if you can't stomach that,
then you had damn well
better squeeze that trigger right now.
Go on.
What are you waiting for?
Or you can make a choice.
Put your past behind you.
Put the gun down.
And help me.
Because I'm telling you,
I'm gonna make a difference
in this fleet.
Is that your final word?
That's up to you.
Then swear it.
I,
Leland Joseph Adama,
do now avow and affirm...
That I take the office
of President
of the Twelve Colonies of Kobol
without any moral reservation
or mental evasion.
That I take the office
of President
of the Twelve Colonies of Kobol
without any moral reservation
or mental evasion.
This is a frakking joke.
You're the only man I can trust
to command this ship.
Maybe you're crazy enough
to pull a stunt like this
but you can't be crazy enough
to leave me in charge.
In case you forgot, my last term
at the helm was a complete disaster.
That was a long time ago.
You're not the same man you were.
You're not even the same man
who came back from
New Caprica.
You found out a lot about yourself.
Been tested in ways
that I can't barely begin to imagine.
You're ready.
Besides,
don't count on this being permanent.
What if it is?
Put these on...
and you lead the people
to Earth, the best way you can.
The fleet has stayed here too long
already.
Any other last orders?
Just one.
Give Athena back her daughter.
She needs her family.
We all need our family.
Take care of this one.
All right, let me see the changes
before you get this out to the press.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Mr. Lampkin.
Romo.
One day in office and
you've already got a first pet.
Jake here is a genuine
hero of the resistance.
Aren't you, Jake? Unfortunately,
his previous owners had to let him go.
Jake, meet Romo.
Romo, meet Jake.
Your new best friend.
If there's one thing I hate
more than cats, it's dogs.
See, a new pet for you to loathe.
I knew it would be the perfect gift.
Good luck, Jake.
I hear you're keeping Zarek
as Vice-President.
I can use the advice.
And as long as he knows he's heard,
I think I can trust him.
I don't know if I agree
with your thinking.
Well, I could say
the same thing about yours.
The only difference is
you're gonna be President,
I'm just getting in a plane.
Waiting alone in a Raptor,
while the rest of the fleet jumps away,
that's not just getting in a plane.
That sounds a lot like...
It sounds a lot like suicide, Dad.
At least this time
I'm only risking my own neck.
So I guess it won't matter
if as President
I order you not to do this.
I don't know
if I ever told you this, but
one of my first missions
was a solo recon.
Me alone in a Raptor
in enemy space.
I'm not gonna lie to you, I was scared.
Told myself that I was doing my duty,
and ultimately I faced my fear.
That's a good memory.
Why are you doing this?
Because I can't live without her.
And Laura's gonna get
to the rendez-vous point.
I have to believe that.
- Admiral.
What do you hear, Starbuck?
Nothing but the rain, sir.
Grab your gun and bring the cat in.
Yes, sir.
Keep a light on, I'll be back.
You can count on it.
Galactica, this is Husker,
I'm in position.
Affirmative, Husker.
All fleet ships,
this is Galactica actual.
Commence jump.