So, it's truely
what they say -- Mars"...
there's a new sheriff
in town?
Until the special election,
anyway.
Do you like movies?
Let's go.
I know what i like.
Why waste my time?
Like why bother
with something not good
Just because
it's something?
I was thinking
of asking parker out,
And i wanted to make sure
it was cool with you.
Of course.
Thank you for asking.
Sure.
I know we're friends.
See ya.
Good luck.
Uh, coffee with cream.
Uh, actually,
could i get a couple of them?
Thank you.
Here. I hate to think of you
undercaffeinated.
Danke.
It's 8:00 a.M. Shouldn't you be
in a wetsuit somewhere?
Early poli-Sci.
And you're
actually going?
I even bought
this amazing pen
That accents text
in neon colors.
[ Gasps ]
a highlighter!
Lots of advancements since
the last time i buckled down.
How about you?
Uh, violence
in early adolescence.
Need me to autograph
your textbook?
Thanks, but...
so, what do i owe you
for the joe?
Eh,
just pay it forward.
Hey, by the way,
I'm throwing a birthday party
for parker this weekend.
I've been studying up.
I watched
"my super sweet 16."
You don't know where i can get
a dozen eunuchs, do you?
Not offhand.
I could make some calls.
If you're not busy,
I know she'd really like
you to be there.
We both would.
Think about it.
Is mr. Mars in?
No. Sorry.
We've shut down for a while.
You own babylon gardens,
don't you?
My dad and i get takeout there
all the time.
I went to high school
with your daughter.
Our restaurant
was vandalized --
Rocks through
our window.
They spray-Painted "terrorist"
on our door.
Is there someone
who can help us?
I believe there is.
Jimmy.
Hey. Your tab.
Hey. Come on.
Sign it and hit the road.
[ Tires screech, horn blares ]
Veronica:
tomorrow i'll set the cameras.
Tonight, it's
the old-Fashioned stakeout.
I took this case
so i wouldn't have time
To dwell on parker's
birthday party,
And now here i am
sitting in a car
With nothing but a whole lot
of dwelling time on my hands.
Veronica mars?
Amira...
long time, no see.
Yeah.
Like,
since my senior year,
When y made
my pirate points worthless.
Wow.
Good memory.
I heard you were at hearst,
but i haven't seen you.
Yeah, different circles,
i guess.
What are you doing
out here?
Your mom hired me
to watch the place
In case there are
any more...incidents.
My mom hired you?
Yep.
Have a blast.
I just got off the phone
with county.
The kid's
never gonna walk again.
Any idea what a 19-Year-Old
was doing drinking in here?
His i.D. Said he was 21.
Yeah, i saw it.
It also said he was 6'3",
220, and blond.
You can go home now.
We will pay you
for the time that you put in,
But it was a mistake
for my wife to hire you.
It was not a mistake.
You fall asleep out here
in your car.
You work too hard to be able
to stay up all night.
This is the mars girl.
Her father
is the acting sheriff.
Have you thought
about nasir?
Besides,
this is no job for a girl.
What choice did i have?
I knew you would react
this way.
Surprise.
[ Tires screech ]
[ Operatic music plays ]
a long time ago,
we used to be friends
but i haven't thought of you
lately at all
come on, now, sugar
bring it on, bring it on,
yeah
just remember me when
we used to be friends
a long time ago
-- captions by vitac --
www.Vitac.Com
Why is this happening?!
Not a great time to be arab
in america.
20 years we've been
in this country!
Huh! 20 years
we've been americans!
I'm a yankee doodle
damn dandy!
And now this?!
The license plate
was removed,
But i caught a glimpse
of a bumper sticker.
It should be enough
to go on.
Amira: really?
Unless it was a "hello,
my name is..." sticker,
How's that gonna do
any good?
The person who owns that pickup
has a child
Who's an honor student
at neptune middle.
Do you want me
to track him down or not?
Look at these ads.
"Twofer tuesday,"
"it's raining gin,"
"Dollar-Shot night."
Let me change first.
Man, you party hard.
It's a college paper.
Only a quarter of the students
at hearst are 21.
I'm not sure where
this rant is going.
A 19-Year-Old kid was drinking
at a bar called the break
With a gum-Ball level i.D.
He stumbled out,
and a car hit him.
It looks like
he'll never walk again.
"Bucket o' beer bonanza"?
You have any idea
If they're known
for allowing underage drinking?
"Famous for"
is more like it.
It's nicknamed "the cake"
for how easy it is to get in,
But most of the campus-Area bars
are pretty lax.
From what i've heard.
'Cause the only buckets
i order
Come in original
and extra crispy.
I have it on good authority
that the break
And other campus-Area bars
on the list you're receiving
Are knowingly serving
underage students.
I want surprise checks in
every one of these bars tonight.
Looks like
my credit-Card statement.
What's the priority level,
sheriff?
Well, obviously
if you get a call, take it,
But otherwise i want these bars
scared straight.
[ Light laughter ]
Gentlemen,
jim wilson was 19.
I want this taken seriously.
You used to work for him.
Is he always like this?
I wouldn't test him.
We have a guest
in honors homeroom today.
Miss mars is doing a survey
about gun awareness
For her college
criminology course.
I trust you will give her
your full attention,
As honor points
are in effect.
What does
a criminologist do?
Oh, grads usually go
into work in law enforcement.
I'm considering pursuing
a career at the fbi.
You're a girl.
Ronald.
Actually, ronald,
did you know that, on average,
Girls develop
faster than boys
And have higher levels
of cognitive functioning,
Including math calculation,
written language,
And verbal fluency?
So?
Well put, ronald.
We need firemen, too.
We all know guns
are dangerous,
But i also study the dangers
and implications
Of the impact of toy guns,
like pellet guns,
Bb guns, or paintball guns.
Raise your hand
if you have a family member
Who owns a pellet or bb gun.
Now, how about paintball guns?
Okay, now, whose family has
a big yellow pickup truck?
Miss mars?
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure i understand
where this is going.
Yeah. Me either.
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[ Gunfire, explosions ]
Yo, bitch, what up?
It stings.
I know, because you shot me
last night.
Oh, yeah!
Afri'm closegot
some with the local sheriff,
And he simply hates hate crimes,
self-Hate in your case.
Dude, she shot you.
Keep up, towelie.
"Self-Hate"? What?
Spray-Painting the front
of babylon gardens --
Ringing any bells?
What?
Say "what" again. I dare you.
I double dare you.
What?
Aah!
God, someone wrote "terrorist"
at babylon gardens?
Check out the big brain
on brett.
I'll give you a hint.
It was you.
We didn't do
anything like that.
I can prove it.
Look -- White people.
Thanks for all your help,
by the way.
Check it out.
Two hot chicks
i met on myspace --
Both in play, both eager to meet
the dickster face-To-Face.
Question -- And i need you
to dig deep here.
Which one do i invite?
Um...
lazy eye might work
to your advantage.
Ha! Trick question.
Just goes to show
how whipped you are.
The correct answer
is "both."
And if they both show?
Then i do
a quick heat check.
Whichever's engine's
running hotter gets dick.
You mean "whomever's."
Whatever.
Gills: what can i say?
We hit them all.
Full sweeps --
They were clean.
Deputy gills,
you don't find it strange --
College town,
surprise inspections,
And not one of my deputies
issues a single citation?
Not really.
Those bars do a good job
of keeping the minors out.
I hate to say it,
But the kid who got hit --
He's the exception.
What are the odds?
Veronica: so let's see
how babylon gardens
Survived the night without me.
All seems well.
Who is this guy, and what's
he doing skulking around?
"Sneed batmen"?
Does "sneed batmen"
ring any bells?
For some reason
it sounds familiar.
Hello? Mac? Sneed?
Sorry. Bronson and i went
on a hike this morning.
I'm wiped.
A hike? You?
Yes.
Morning? You?
I wanted to see
what it was like.
And?
It's sunny.
Sounds like things are good
with bronson.
Any better and he'd have you
jump through fiery hoops.
You ready?
We can offer them our table.
Sure.
Hey, guys.
Thanks for the table.
It just takes me back to
high school. Remember, logan?
We'd sit at the same lunch table
and make fun of the fat kids.
We went
to the same high school?
Uh, yeah.
We ran over that fisherman
And promised to take
the secret to our graves.
I remember the fisherman.
You bet your friends
You could turn me into
a superhot prom date as a joke,
But you ended up
falling in love with me?
Nope, lost it.
Please stop.
Oh. Got to split.
Sorry. Late.
Hey, my birthday party --
You can come, right?
You know me.
If there's a birthday party,
i'm wearing a pointy hat.
[ Chuckles ]
You and logan
seem chummy.
I never thought much of the guy
when you two were dating.
The surly thing, you know?
But since he's been around
so much lately,
I've seen his sweet side.
Probably theide
you saw all the time.
Oh, yeah, that side.
So, about parker's party --
If i must go...
you must.
You must.
...what do you say
i swing by your place early
And you hit me on the head
with a hammer a couple times
Before we go?
Not that i wouldn't love
to cross that off my to-Do list,
But i promised parker and logan
that i'd help them set up.
Want to come?
Rain check.
I'll find reinforcements
elsewhere.
It's like the new
"rocky horror."
At one point, people throw
plastic spoons at the screen.
You have to check it out.
It'll change your life.
Uh-Oh.
Relax. I'm here
to invite you to a party.
Saturday night?
Rockin'-Good time?
The catch?
There's no catch.
I just need
a couple wingmen.
It's parker's
birthday party.
There's strength in numbers.
You soldiers up
for mission: morale support?
Okay. Cool. I'm in.
But i think piz has to go --
No, piz is in.
It sounds like fun.
Maybe before, you could come by
the room and --
Cool. Okay. Uh, sorry.
Got to boogie.
Thought you were going
to yo-Yo taco on saturday.
Yo la tengo.
Yeah.
But, you know,
this sounds more fun.
What?
You're like
one of those guys
Who stands behind the players
at the poker table
And pretends he's playing.
Sorry, i've never been to vegas.
What exactly --
Every once in a while,
you got to go all-In.
Right. Will do.
Excellent.
I don't know
what that means.
It means
we're going out tonight.
You're gonna talk to some girl
who knows you're alive.
Wait, actually, that's not what
it means, but it's a start.
Sorry to bother you.
"Sneed batmen" -- What is that?
The batmen arel
the intramural softball team.
Oh.
Um,
this is embarrassing,
But i sort of flirted
with number 11
The other day
in the library.
You wouldn't happen
to know his name?
Sure. Jason cohen.
I found out jason cohen lives
at the zeta epsilon house --
A jewish fraternity.
Curious.
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
What the hell?
Okay. Peeping tom in a tree
takes off on a bike.
I feel like i stumbled
into a "benny hill" sketch.
Um, amira, you mind telling me
what's going on here?
Better question --
Why the hell are you here?
Of jason skulking around
your parents' restaurant
Last night after closing.
He wasn't skulking.
Jason's my boyfriend.
Oh,
i'm gonna kill nasir.
Who?
Nasir.
He works at the restaurant.
His student visa expired,
And my parents agreed
to give him a job.
I was supposed to
marry the guy.
Really?
Don't ask.
Those pictures
will literally kill my dad.
Are they x-Rated?
It's not the nudity.
It's my costar -- The jew.
However long it takes
to get those photos developed
And pedal over
to my dad's house --
That's how long it'll be
until i'm disowned.
There's only two one-Hour
photo places open this late,
And nasir's on a bike.
I'll see what i can do.
[ Clears throat ]
hi.
Um, my boyfriend...
...is a tad embarrassed
To pick up the photos
we just dropped off.
There are a few...
"special moments with
special friends"-Type shots.
Men --
It's all rah-Rah-Rah
Until you find yourself
in an all-Night photomat.
Um,
how much do we owe you?
That's your boyfriend?
Yeah. It's like i'm dating
a young omar sharif.
Desert fever --
What are you gonna do?
Um, are they ready?
I'm on the last one.
I've had some problems
with the machine jamming.
Okay.
Sorry,
do you have the time?
11:15.
Thank you.
Wow.
Arab men -- So macho.
[ Chuckles ]
Nasir.
See you back at the apartment.
Don't be late.
My photos --
Are they done?
Your girlfriend
just picked them up.
Girlfriend?
I don't know that woman.
You gave her my pictures?!
Sir, count to 10, please.
I am not the enemy.
I still have
a few of the prints
That were only half-Developed
when the machine jammed.
It's worth losing 20 bucks
just to get to talk to her.
We came here for me,
remember?
Yeah, that was
before i saw her.
No, you don't.
Judas.
I got 20 bucks
says you can whip my ass
And make me like it.
Well, i do like
a confident man.
Look what i found.
[ Gasps ]
thank you, veronica!
Oh.
I must say...
your spurned suitor --
He may be crazy,
but, oh, my.
If i didn't mind
being treated as property,
He might be tempting.
[ Knock on door ]
Explain this.
Now!
Nasir says that this boy lives
in a jewish fraternity.
Is he a jew?
Being with this boy is
what has caused all of this --
The threats,
the vandalism.
The community has obviously
found out and turned against us.
When you say "community,"
do you mean jewish or arab?
Either. Both.
I don't know.
The restaurant is
no longer your concern.
You're fired!
Leave.
I work for your wife.
If she wants me fired,
she can give me a call.
Keith: mr. Murphy,
one of my deputies
Told me you wanted
a private audience.
I was
in the neighborhood.
You know why people enjoy
going to bars, sheriff?
They can drink at home.
People want to relax,
let their hair down.
That's not easy to do
when, every 10 minutes,
Uniformed deputies are
showing up and harassing them.
The funny thing is,
i always backed the badge.
In fact, i usually buy
an especially large amount
Of sheriff department
raffle tickets every year.
Sheriff lamb,
god rest his soul,
Really appreciated
his relationship
With local businesses.
So how many raffle tickets
do you think
The break should buy
this year, sheriff?
You know, just to make sure
that we keep working together.
10 bucks a pop --
Maybe 500 tickets.
We won't be having a raffle
this year, mr. Murphy.
The hospital is having
a pancake breakfast.
Perhaps you could better serve
the community by giving to them.
You sure
you're thinking this
All the way through,
sheriff?
Your boys really enjoy those
new uniforms every year,
Tournament fees
taken care of,
Postgame pitchers
of beer on the house.
It's like
i'm one of the team.
Keith: wallace.
Mr. Mars.
Last time i saw you,
you were 19,
And that was
just a couple weeks ago.
Murphy: i i.D.'D
these boys myself.
You can check it.
If they're not legit, i'll shut
this place down right now.
Wallace, stosh...
mind if i see
those i.D.S of yours?
I guess i don't have to ask
where you got these.
You recognize the work?
[ Sighs ]
Out of 37 citations
yours truly wrote
In six campus-Area bars
last night,
No fake i.D. Could hold a candle
to your standards.
You may not want to
believe this, honey,
But there are mistakes
you can't take back.
What if
they had gotten drunk
And stumbled into the street,
like jim wilson?
Would you want to explain that
to their parents?
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Hello?
It's happened again.
I'll check the camera.
I'll be right over.
I've never
seen this man.
No problem.
I can track him.
I just wanted to see
if you knew who he was first.
Fortunately,
the vandal took the bait --
One arabic scroll
with a tracer stitched inside.
[ Beeping ]
[ Beeping quickens ]
[ Van approaches ]
Can i help you
find something?
Look what i've got.
It's a surveillance photo
from babylon gardens.
It shows you painting
"terrorist" on their building.
Well, you ain't a cop.
So my response is gonna
have to be, "so the hell what?"
Why did you do it?
If you have to ask,
you ain't been paying attention.
That's it?
You're just
another close-Minded redneck
Who thinks
it's his patriotic duty
To harass innocent people?
Not quite.
I know
where you live now.
In about five minutes,
i'll know your name.
The family you're harassing
is gonna press charges.
Derrick,
what have you done now?
This girl
here wants to know
Why i spray-Painted "terrorist"
on that restaurant.
You really think babylon gardens
is a terrorist front?
As a matter of fact,
i do.
Sorry
about my little brother.
He's been pretty worked up
since i came home like this.
One of the dudes
who works there
Was passing these out
by the mall.
Iraqis laughing
at dead americans?
If that ain't
terrorist propaganda,
I don't know what is.
Generally, the satisfaction
of nailing someone
For a crime like this
is its own reward.
So where's the sugar rush
of sweet justice
I should be feeling right now?
Hi.
Hey.
So, his name
is derrick karr.
He admitted to
vandalizing your restaurant
After
he was handed this...
...by nasir.
He was distributing them
outside the mall.
Derrick followed him
back here.
Derrick's brother
was shot up in iraq.
His brother
was a soldier?
Yeah, but he had no idea
what derrick had done.
I did some checking.
Derrick's on probation
for stealing cars.
If you press charges,
It'll most likely
mean some jail time for him.
I want to
meet this man.
Uh, mister --
Sheriff mars.
Hello, stosh.
What do you say we head out,
have a few beers?
That's one of those
trick questions, isn't it?
I've got some new i.D.S
for you.
Wallace.
This picture
is jon bon jovi.
Yes, it is.
Wallace:
biggie smalls?
We don't really
all look alike, mr. Mars.
I know that, wallace.
Now, let's go out
and get our drink on.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Nonalcoholic beer --
All of the peeing,
none of the fun.
Quit complaining.
One night of this,
we're off the hook.
Plus, if things work out
with miranda,
This could be
one of those cool
"First time we met"
stories.
What about it is cool?
And by the way,
You invited her
to join us to logan's party.
Your lack of pimp juice
is gonna cost you, son.
All right, let's have
all you finest minds of socal
Put your i.D.S in the air
And wave them around
like you just don't care.
Thank you,
and good night.
This waste of time
has been brought to you
By your temporary sheriff
of balboa county.
You get that,
mr. Mars?
Got it.
S>
Last night, i ordered
asmith, jones, taylor, gills...
clean out your lockers --
You're fired.
You're firing us?
You're the substitute teacher.
We were hired by don lamb.
I know these guys
better than you do, keith.
You try to pull this stunt,
we all walk.
Fair enough.
There's the door.
You don't
have the stones --
Leave your badge
on the desk
And get the hell
out of my station!
[ Indistinct talking
on police radio ]
[ Knock on door ]
You.
I've got some people
who want to meet you.
Rashad, sabirah krimani,
this is derrick karr.
They own
babylon gardens.
I wanted to meet you,
talk to you.
Lucky me.
If they report you,
it's off to jail.
So i end up in jail.
My brother ends up
in a wheelchair,
And these foreigners
are free to spit on america
And everything
it stands for?
What it stands for?
Do you even know
what it stands for?
Saying you love america
is easy.
It's easy until someone
spray-Paints "terrorist"
On your door.
It's easy until
you are handed a flyer
That mocks the sacrifice
of your brother.
We all came
from somewhere else.
We all are trying
to make it.
In america,
whatever you stand for,
You're supposed to
get a fair shot.
That is what your brother
was fighting for,
In case
you wanted to know.
So turn me in, ali baba.
It makes no difference to me.
[ Door slams ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Dog barks ]
He'll be in jail
in an hour.
No, no, don't --
Don't turn him in.
I suspect that our troubles
with mr. Karr are over.
I'm glad that i had a chance
to speak with the man.
You're sure?
Okay.
I'm so proud of you.
Your words
were so inspirational.
I was wondering --
Do they apply
to your daughter, as well?
[ Sighs ]
I guess
i should meet the boy.
And what do we do
about nasir?
Well, he didn't break any la
handing out the flyer,
And i support his right
to exercise free speech.
But that doesn't mean
That i have to support him
or shelter him.
That cartoon pissed me off.
It was un-American.
Nasir ben hafayid,
you're in this country
On an expired
i-20 student visa.
In accordance
with i.N.S. 214,
Any statements you make
can be used in a court of law,
Immigration,
or administrative proceeding.
Hey, honey. Just in time.
Are you hungry?
No, but the food's free.
Wallace called.
He and piz are gonna
meet you at the party.
He said you'd understand.
They're ditching me?
I warned him
you wouldn't understand.
Score one for dad.
By the way,
you didn't tell me
I made the front page
of the lampoon.
This had to have been
Tough on you
the last couple of days,
Having your old man
back as sheriff.
Actually, it's been tough on me
knowing i let you down.
I'm sorry
about those i.D.S.
I vow to use
the mars powers for good
Rather than evil
from now on.
There's never a stenographer
around when you need one.
Things i'd rather do
than attend this party solo --
Seven minutes in heaven
with scott peterson...
dick:
hold the door.
...ride the space elevator
with dick.
Always the lady.
You came.
Good for you.
I thought something like this
would be,
You know,
unbelievably awkward.
Your fly's open.
I know.
Party ritual.
Veronica mars...
what's that line
about the beginning
Of some sort
of friendship?
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Later.
Why are you looking at me
like that?
Sorry, i was afraid
you were trying
To get back at logan somehow
by coming as dick's date.
Ooh, yeah,
nothing says "i'm over you"
Like dating down.
[ Gasps ]
couch opening.
[ Sighs ]
Okay, this couch
is our social foxhole
For the next 60 minutes
of the battle.
Defend it at all costs.
Hey, veronica.
And friend.
Sorry. Right.
Max, this is my friend mac.
Mac, max.
Where are my manners?
Sit, defend,
Decide which one of you
is changing their name.
Hey, bozos,
we had plans.
You were supposed to
be my wingmen.
What mission could be
more important than that?
Here you go, boys.
I see.
Battle of the bulge.
Veronica mars,
miranda affeld.
Hey.
Hi.
I loved the quote
You have up
on your myspace page.
What was it again?
"The dude abides."
I don't know about you,
but i take comfort in that.
[ Chuckles ]
What else
do you take comfort in?
Drinks.
Be right back.
[ Glass clinking ]
Can i, uh, get everyone's
attention for one minute?
Now, i had this whole
"my super sweet 19" thing
Planned for tonight,
but, well, it turns out
The hotel has a policy
on bengal tiger rides.
There is one ludicrous thing
i was able to pull off
That i hope makes up for it.
[ Cheers and applause ]
You remembered!
[ Laughs ]
You're kidding.
My dad does
half the team's taxes.
We should go
to a game sometime.
You can spend halftime
in my private box.
Awesome!
Would you
give me a few minutes?
I have some party
responsibilities to attend to.
Hey, there.
Isn't he yummy?
I know.
You just want to...
eat him up.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sighs ]
Thank you.
Me? You're the one
dishing out cake.
I was worried
that things were gonna be weird,
And you're
just a class act.
I'm happy for you guys.
In fact,
i've never seen him...
on a cake like this.
Feel free
to just hack in anywhere.
Okay.
Here you go.
[ Max laughs ]
That's brilliant --
An online purity test.
So, basically, you got people
to detail their sex lives.
And be scored accordingly.
Then i sold their sexual secrets
to their peers
For 10 bucks a pop.
I like how you think.
Veronica busted me
but kept quiet.
We've been friends
ever since.
Checking out
the talent?
How is it you have
so many friends?
You don't
even like people.
And yet,
they adore me.
I guarded myself for seeing you
with a date tonight,
Proof you weren't
pining away.
All the periodically
good ones were taken,
And i pine for no man.
Maybe you should try
branching out.
Who knows?
Maybe there's a consistently
good one here tonight.
So, you sell tests?
Sorry. "Study guides."
Yeah, it's not easy.
Undergrad courses
change quarter to quarter.
Visiting professors
switch up curriculums.
There are t.A.S to bribe.
It's exhausting.
Tell me
you're a business major.
Philosophy.
No lie.
I think, therefore i am.
[ Laughs ]
Okay...
seriously,
did my friends hire you?
Hey, the host says
you're a big-Time swing dancer.
[ Exhales sharply ]
Dude, you're not
gonna believe this.
Hottie internet chicks
found out about each other,
Talked it over,
and they're into it.
Into it?
Doublemint, baby.
They're becoming twins?
What? Dude,
i don't have time for this.
They sent me
on a plaything scavenger hunt.
Do we have
any peanut oil?
Here, in the room?
I didn't think so.
What about an ice bucket?
Hey, what's up?
W-What's going on?
Lisa is a friend
of mine.
Who's lisa?
I'm lisa, dipwad.
When you're perving
my online profile,
You should look
at the friends list, too,
Not just the pictures.
Just thought we'd come by
and say hi.
Great party.
No. Don't go.
No way.
I've heard your show.
Maybe, um, you could
dedicate something to me?
Yeah, absolutely.
I mean, even though
it's a talk show.
I'll dedicate a segment
On campus neighborhood
zoning to you.
There you are!
This is a "break glass
in case of emergency" situation.
I need you to pretend
to be my boyfriend.
Oh, sorry.
You're right, babe.
Bad boyfriend.
Fresh drink
coming up, okay?
[ Sighs ]
Could you
give us a second?
Sure.
You need to listen to me
right now, okay?
What you're doing
is cruel.
Are you kidding?
When i told him my name,
He did that whole
"banana fanna fo fanna" thing.
Not him. Piz.
If you don't know
he has a thing for you...
piz doesn't have --
You're smarter than that.
Be a good person.
Just put him out of his misery.
There's my sugar.
What?
Nothing.
Got to get back to miranda.
Do you
want to get some air?
I owe you an apology.
You do?
I do.
You've been
so sweet to me,
And i really like
hanging out with you.
You're great.
I've just --
I've been so focused
on my own romantic drama,
I've kind of been blind
to everything else.
Basically,
what i'm saying is
That i think your head
may have been in one place,
And mine's
been in anoth--
look around, you see
there's nothing to say
but the things i know
i got nothing to say
Just friends.
I get it.
Hey, i'm taking off.
Hey, where are you going?
What happened?
I went all-In.
lying on yo
young girl, curl your hair
You seen piz?
He just took off.
You're leaving?
Yeah, well,
i'm a fan of the dramatic exit.
Truthfully,
i don't know how the night
Could get any better
than that.
You sure about that?
it won't happen at all
shifty eyes pay attention
dirty talk, talk,
talk louder
just as long as you're gone
i won't leave you alone