During your first year,
things begin to feel different.
You've arrived. You know?
You just start to feel...
I'm open.
- ...cooler.
- My God!
- Turk, that was amazing!
- Woman, shush.
It's a lot cooler
if we don't make a big deal out of it.
Hang on, Ma. It's him.
- Whatever.
- JD!
The point is,
we've found our stride.
We know all the ins and outs.
Shall we? And...
My God!
Which one of you two did that?
- My bad.
- That was me.
- Both of you?
- Player!
Could we have an agreement?
No enclosed spaces.
- Morning, doctors.
- Morning, sir.
Mrs Winston,
it's back to the home for you.
- Elliot, that is disgusting.
- Seriously.
Sweetheart, consider a change in diet.
Fine. I hate you guys.
I hate you, I hate you.
Let's face it. We've earned
the right to be a little cocky.
- Jerome!
- What up, dawg?
My man!
Who the hell's Jerome?
And I gotta tell you,
nobody can take this feeling away.
Nobody.
Thank goodness,
it's the Mod Squad.
After months of doing
everyone else's scut work,
we're finally not the lowest
people on the totem pole.
Look at you three, all excited.
Today we get
our very own med students.
Welcome to Hell.
Gimme some hungry chicken.
Not hungry enough.
Give me some more.
There you go.
Look how scared they are.
It's like we're cheetahs
and they're a pack of gazelles.
I'm Dr Bob Kelso,
and I'm your Chief of Medicine.
I want to encourage you all
to think of me as your safety net.
Because I promise you,
we're a family here.
Let's go get 'em, doctors.
They're buying it.
''The Devil's greatest trick was
convincing the world he didn't exist.''
Baby
Girl
- You two are dorks.
- I gotta go.
I gotta go meet up with
my med student up in Surgery.
Know who you're getting?
Nope, but it's probably someone black.
- Sugar darlin'
- Girl
So, I want someone
I can be friends with, you know?
I hope I get a jerk. I took
so much crap as a med student
that I've been waiting for the day
I get to make someone suffer.
Listen, nurse.
I'm looking for a Dr Elliot Reid.
I'm Elliot Reid.
Guy's name,
guy's job, guy's clothes...
Anything else you wanna tell me?
Goody! You're a jerk.
Just remember to breathe,
and you'll get through the day.
Josh?
Hi, I'm Dr Dorian.
I know what this looks like, but...
I do that all the time.
Do you ever part
your hair on the wrong side
to see what you look like
to other people?
No.
It totally messes everyone up.
Do you have any questions?
What's the babe
situation like here?
Easy, tiger.
Have you seen a med student here?
Yeah. Me.
Cool. Nice to meet you, ma'am.
Actually, the only people
that call me ''ma'am'' are nobody.
No. I use ''ma'am'' all the time. Watch.
What up, ma'am?
- See? It's my thing.
- Yeah, right.
Come on. I'm here to learn.
Listen up, kid.
Lesson number one:
All surgical interns?
They're dogs.
- Not a problem.
- Hey, baby.
This overbearing machismo is usually
just compensation for a lap-pinkie.
That's cold!
What just happened?
Don't worry about it.
It's all good in the 'hood.
I'll tell you what I expect.
You parted your hair on the other side?
You're gonna do H & Ps,
write admission orders...
What are you doing?
I can't walk and write at the same time.
- It makes me nauseous.
- A famous doctor once said,
''Show me a med student that only
triples my work and I'll kiss his feet. ''
Philip, I need you to shave his groin
so I can place a femoral triple-lumen.
I'm not so much with
the ''shavin' a guy's curlies''.
If you get just one
bad evaluation from me,
it'll torch your class rank,
so do what I tell you.
And if I ask you to shave a groin,
thank your lucky stars
that I said ''shave''.
I'll tell you what.
I'll lather you up,
and you think about baseball.
Natural redhead.
I'll need you to change the dressing
on the fem bypass in 402,
and DC the staples
on the gastroplasty in post-op.
I have no idea what you just said.
I'm kidding.
Looks like you won
the med student raffle there, pal.
- Introduce me.
- Excuse me?
You give me her name
and tell her my name,
or you go her name,
my name, my name, her name.
No. You like Carla.
Do you actually listen
to yourself when you speak,
or do you find you drift in and out?
Fine. Then I'm gonna go ahead
and continue to focus
all my energies on Carla.
Listening, watching...
...waiting.
Dr Cox, Kristen.
Kristen, Dr Cox.
Josh, I asked you
to get this guy's history an hour ago.
It should've taken five minutes.
We were just talking.
This guy, he is the bomb!
OK. Bye-bye. Moving on.
Help someone else. I'm sorry about that.
Relax, Bambi. Be nice to Thumper.
He wrote ''The guy sweats
when he exercises.''
- I do.
- I'll call Ripley's!
Relax. It's just one mistake.
Relax, Bambi.
It's just one mistake.
- Good night, Thumper.
- Cool! Great first day, Dr Dorian.
Yeah, it was.
- Relax. It's just one mistake.
- Yes! They're each one mistake.
Put 'em all together,
it makes four million.
Did you just snap at me?
Because I think he just snapped at me.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, you are.
Carla, I gotta go home.
You have to co-sign all these orders,
fill out a vascular consult on bed three
and get a tox screen for Mrs O'Brien.
- But Josh did all this.
- Honey, I don't think so.
Mrs O'Brien, I'm afraid
I'm gonna need a urine sample.
I hope you're taking
very good care of my hospital.
You're darn tootin'.
Jackass. Dr Reid, say hello
to Whitaker Chambers.
- What up?
- ''What up''?
Whitaker Chambers is the CEO
of the corporation
that owns this hospital,
so I suggest you stop
acting like LL Cool Reid
and start acting like Dr Reid.
You dig?
- Why would he want to meet me?
- Hey, Dad.
Hey, son!
Poopies.
- It was really nice to meet you.
- Same here, doctor.
I'm sorry. Dr Cox,
I was gonna take Kristen
out for a beer after work.
Would you like to join us?
No. I can't do it.
No!
- Is he OK?
- Not really.
Dr Dorian?
Your roommate let me in.
Cool dead dog. Can I pet him?
Is he kidding?
I came by because I know
I didn't do so great yesterday...
What is it that tipped you off?
Was it your inability to
perform even the simplest task?
I'll bet it was that
I got home 20 minutes ago
because I spent the entire night
cleaning up after you.
I'm sorry.
I was just really scared.
You know what, Josh?
You should be scared.
Because I gotta be honest with you.
I don't think you got what it takes.
Do you?
I didn't think so.
I'm still not gonna feel bad
about what I said to Josh.
You don't scare me, woman.
I'm so sorry. I'll apologise at rounds.
Nurse Roberts, have you seen Josh?
The tall skinny one? He quit.
Nice job, Bambi.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
I didn't.
You don't have to apologise to me.
You will have to answer to Jesus.
After what happened,
I did what any good person would do.
I went looking for confirmation
that it wasn't my fault.
Here's what happened.
He was screwing up constantly.
I didn't force him to quit.
I don't think it's my fault he quit.
Most of the bad things
that happen here are your fault.
- I was talking to her.
- I won't say what you wanna hear.
Nurse Roberts says he's the most
incompetent doctor she's worked with.
Laverne, what'd you say about JD
when he first started working here?
He was the most incompetent
doctor I ever worked with.
- It's not my fault he failed.
- You failed.
You're supposed to be his teacher.
See, to me that sounds like
it's your fault. I don't know.
Shocker. Yeah.
Where you going? Stay and play!
So you're having trouble
asking out Kristen.
- No problem.
- Whoa, Curly.
I got no problem. Wanna have a drink?
- No.
- See? I'm fine.
You know how men are always
talking about themselves?
Women like to talk
about themselves more.
Thank you.
You've touched me deeply.
You can be cynical,
but I'm telling you,
get Kristen to talk about herself,
it's on. It's on and poppin'.
- If that doesn't work, do what I do.
- Which is what?
- Show her the booty!
- No. You put that away.
Think of the children.
Doctor!
Philip, I was wondering if you could
write out this discharge summary.
Where's the fun?
- Excuse me?
- From now on,
when you're wondering whether
I'll do something,
ask yourself, ''Where's the fun?''
lt'll be a timesaver for both of us.
I'm betting that
if you were really honest with yourself,
you'd realise how unsatisfying it is
to ride on your father's coattails.
No, I'm OK with it.
Josh, this is completely crazy.
You told me I shouldn't be a doctor.
Kidding... Josh.
You know what? Forget all of that.
You have to hang in there.
Now, I promise you,
I am gonna help you.
Here we go.
You're doing it.
Yeah, you are!
You're doing it!
- So, what do you say?
- I know what you're trying to do.
My whole life,
people have felt sorry for me.
- Why would anyone feel sorry for you?
- I'm clumsy,
I'm always throwing up,
I don't even have an ass!
Those are the same things I was
dealing with when I started here.
Except for the ass part.
I actually have a great ass.
It's firm like mutton.
I'm not buying it, Dr Dorian.
But thanks for trying.
- So, where you from?
- Chicago. You?
- Pittsburgh. Family? Brothers, sisters?
- One older brother. You?
We're gonna keep the focus on you.
Are your parents still together?
Yep.
Do you have any idea how hard
you're making this on me?
No, but I wonder if someone
slipped something into my soda.
He has that effect on everyone
the first few weeks.
I gotta go. We'll pick this up later.
Pick what up?
What up, dawg?
Not a strong move
with the tighty-whities.
If you won't help,
go wait for your trust fund to mature.
- Dr Reid, can I see you a minute?
- Dr Kelso, I am so, so sorry.
I just got so frustrated,
plus I'm PMSing.
Well, the pill plays havoc
with my cycle. I'm like...
Dr Reid?
You talk too much. It's a problem.
Why are you doing
your med student's work?
- Well, his father...
- I hate his father.
But I'm the one who has
to suck up to him, not you.
For God's sake, woman,
show some cojones!
It's hard trying to figure out
how to reach somebody.
The thing is to think
of someone I look up to,
and remember
how they got through to me.
The only way you could
be less productive
is if you were the wall
on which you're leaning.
But then you'd be providing some jackass
with a wall on which to lean
and reflect on what a jackass he is.
I know. Here it's a conundrum.
But don't you worry about it.
I'll tackle that one right upstairs.
In the meantime,
you could pretend
to be doing some work.
And, even though
you don't have your basket,
it's just a terrific time
for you to skip away, Shirley.
Skip away.
Skip away. Go ahead.
- Hello, Philip.
- Lemon head.
Yeah, I get it, cos of the hair.
I was hard on you from the start,
but, on the other hand, as you know,
you're an incredible tool.
So I'll lay off if you drop
the attitude, and we'll start fresh.
- What do you say?
- I don't wanna.
But, if you've got a problem with that,
go see my father.
I think I'll do that.
Wait, Dr Reid.
I had some time to think about it and,
what the hell? Let's start fresh.
Philly...
I don't wanna.
Sorry we got interrupted before.
- It's OK.
- Where were we?
I told you my parents were
still married, you yelled at me.
Right. Of course I did.
That's me all over.
- Why are you washing your hands?
- I don't honestly know.
I guess I don't have
anything of interest to say.
I got something to say.
Dr Cox, you are an attending,
so you should know
it's inappropriate for you to be
sniffing around this woman all day!
And you! You are a med student
who should be learning from me,
but every time I turn around,
you're talking to him.
So I'm telling you, I forbid you
to get involved with that guy.
Sorry, doctor.
You do realise that you just effectively
signed your own death warrant.
Dude, do you, like,
know any women at all?
Hi.
I know we're not supposed to be
seeing each other, but...
Why did you page me?
I don't know why I still
have this thing on.
Put your gloves on, Josh.
I need you to get an ABG.
- I can't.
- Newbie, wait.
''Newbie''?
You're the only one who knows
if you wanna be a doctor.
But right now I got my hands full. OK?
What do you say you put some gloves on,
Shirley, and get the hell in here?
Now, locate the radial pulse.
Josh, look at me. You can do this.
It looks good.
No way.
What do you want, a cookie?
Put your scrubs on and get back here.
Go, go, go!
Go ahead.
That's it.
- Could you redo that?
- Yeah.
Could I get some more wine?
Puh-lease, keep drinking.
I'm throwing myself at you, and
you're still trying to get me drunk.
Well, baby, you gotta
play all 48 minutes.
- Cheers.
This is fun.
I love the part right before
we start hating each other.
- Really?
- You wanna know something?
What?
I feel like I'm using you
to get past another person.
That's not as sexy as you think it is.
It's this nurse.
This unavailable nurse?
I swear...
Look, Kristen, I think you're great,
but this whole thing's
just not fair to you.
If it's OK with you,
I think I'll go ahead
and decide what's fair to me.
That works for everybody.
Perry?
Actually, I prefer ''Dr Cox''.
You like strong women, don't you?
Are you kidding me? They're
the only ones I let ruin my life.
- This is way too easy.
- Bring it on!
Stop talking.
Dr Reid, I wrote out your admission
orders and got the blood cultures.
Good. Now, beat it. I'm eating.
- Elliot, you ball-buster!
- I know! Isn't it great?
A lot of us freak out
when med students come.
It feels like being forced
to accept new people into your family.
It changes everything.
Me, I was more struck by how
these newbies made me look at myself.
Who I used to be,...
...who I am now,...
...and who I might
some day become.
But hopefully, not too soon.
- Player
- Hold me down
- Such dorks.
- My God!
''My God!''
www.V2.Frigorifix.com