OZ, THE NAME
ON THE STREET
FOR THE OSWALD MAXIMUM
SECURITY PENITENTIARY.
OZ,
WHERE AFTER MONTHS OF
TENSION, A RIOT ERUPTED.
( screaming )
( Augustus )
THE UNIT KNOWN
AS "EMERALD CITY"
WAS OVERTAKEN
BY ITS PRISONERS.
THE GOVERNOR ORDERED
HIS TROOPS TO RECAPTURE IT
BY ANY MEANS
NECESSARY.
( gunshots )
WHEN THE SMOKE
CLEARED LITERALLY,
SIX PRISONERS AND
TWO CORRECTIONAL
OFFICERS WERE DEAD,
34 OTHERS
WERE INJURED.
SOME OVERCOME
BY THE GAS,
SOME FROM
THE BEATINGS,
RIFLE WOUNDS.
( gunshots )
AMONG THOSE SHOT,
TIM McMANUS,
WHO INVENTED
EMERALD CITY,
AND SOME SAY, RAN
IT INTO THE GROUND.
THE REST OF THE PRISONERS
WERE MOVED TO GENPOP,
( loud commotion )
YOU FUCKING BITCH !
( Augustus )
EXCEPT FOR THE
RIOT LEADERS,
WHO WERE DROP-KICKED
INTO SOLITARY.
BY DAWN, PEACE
DESCENDED ON OZ.
YEAH, RIGHT.
LET ME JUST SAY
THIS ABOUT THAT.
I'VE ALREADY STARTED TO PUT
TOGETHER A GUBERNATORIAL
COMMISSION
TO INVESTIGATE, ONE:
THE CAUSES OF THE RIOT,
TWO: THE CRIMINAL ACTIVITIES
OF THOSE PRISONERS INVOLVED,
AND THREE: THE
APPROPRIATENESS OF
THE RESPONSE TO IT
BY WARDEN GLYNN.
GOVERNOR, WHO WILL
CHAIR THE COMMISSION ?
I'VE JUST SPOKEN TO ALVA
H CASE, DEAN OF FERBER
UNIVERSITY LAW SCHOOL.
HE'S AGREED TO LEAD
THE INVESTIGATION.
TO MY MIND THERE'S
NO MORE RESPECTED
JURIST IN THE STATE.
R
I CAN ASSURE YOU HIS
FINDINGS WILL BE FAI
L.
AND COMPLE
TE AND IMPARTIA
FUCK YOU, GOVERNOR.
WHAT ? AM I
ASKING SO MUCH ?
YOU WANT ME TO COME
OUT ON YOUR SIDE,
YOU WANT TO CLOSE DOWN
EMERALD CITY PERMANENTLY,
YOU WANT ME TO SAY
THAT THE PRISONERS ARE
GUILTY OF EVERYTHING,
AND YOU WERE JUSTIFIED
IN BRINGING IN
THE S.O.R.T. TEAM.
OF THE BLOOD OF
THOSE EIGHT DEAD.
.
MY HANDS ARE CLEAN
, MY CONSCIENCE IS CLEAR
THEN BACK OFF AND LET ME DO
WHAT YOU APPOINTED ME TO DO.
OKAY.
BUT KEEP ONE
OTHER THING IN MIND,
MARVIN SUTTL
E IS STEPPING DOWN
AL.
AS STATE'S
ATTORNEY GENER
IM.
I'M LOOKING FOR JUST THE
RIGHT MAN TO REPLACE H
COME IN, WARDEN,
WE'RE DONE.
FIND THE TRUTH, CASE,
'CAUSE THE TRUTH
SHALL SET YOUR FEE.
"THE TRUTH."
WHAT IS TH
E TRUTH, LEO ?
?
IS DEVLIN GUILTY
ARE YOU ?
LEO,
,
DEPENDING ON
WHAT I DO FIND
YOU COULD BE THE
ONE WHO GETS FIRED.
YEAH,
AND YOU MAY BE DOING ME
ONE HUGE FUCKING FAVOR.
HOW THEY
HANGING, VERN ?
C.C. !
YO, SOMETHING'S FUCKED !
OH, GREAT, MORE
EM CITY PRAGS.
YOU FUCKS HAVE
A HISSY FIT,
NOW THE REST OF US GOTTA
SLEEP ON TOP OF EACH OTHER ?
HEAR ME, BOYS,
AND HEAR ME GOOD.
THIS IS MY CELL.
THIS IS MY BUNK.
YOU GOT A PROBLEM
WITH THAT ?
NO.
( mumbling )
HEY, HEY...
I'M TALKING
TO YOU.
Y !
HE
?
EITHER OF YOU HE
AR WHAT HAPPENED
TO DOBBINS OR VAHUE
SHUT THE FUCK UP.
?
ARE THEY IN
THE HOSPITAL
I  WAS ONLY IN ER,
I COULDN'T SEE
INTO THE WARD.
!
SHUT THE FUCK UP
BEECHER !
SHUT THE FUCK UP !
TITS... !
BEECHER !
SHUT THE FUCK UP.
( Wangler )
TITS !
CHILL, LITTLE BROTHER.
WHO THE FUCK YOU CALLING
LITTLE BROTHER, MAN ?
GET OFF ME, MAN !
!
LET ME GO
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
LET US NOW PRAY.
PLEASE STAND.
LORD,
WE PRAY FOR THE
SOULS OF OUR FRIENDS
AND COLLEAGUES.
OFFICERS EDWARD HUNT
AND ANTHONY NOWAKOWSKI.
AND WE PRAY FOR THE SOULS
OF THE SIX PRISONERS
WHO DIED AS WELL.
( mumbling )
WE PRAY FOR THE RECOVERY
OF OFFICERS
JOSEPH MINEO AND
JASON ARMSTRONG,
AND FOR
TIM McMANUS.
AND, LORD,
WE ASK YOUR BLESSING
ON THIS PLACE.
WE ASK FOR
UNDERSTANDING.
WE ASK FOR PATIENCE.
WE ASK FOR THE
STRENGTH TO FORGIVE.
WE ASK TO BE FORGIVEN.
( Devlin
) I SAY NO
NEGOTIATIONS.
Y.
WE CUT OFF EM CITY'S
WATER AND ELECTRICIT
WHEN THEY'RE SITTING
IN THE DARK, WE FIRE
TEAR GAS IN THERE.
( McManus )
WHAT ABOUT
THE HOSTAGES ?
HOPEFULLY THE SORT
TEAM WILL REACH THEM.
SO THAT WE MIGHT
RENEW OURSELVES IN THIS
IMPORTANT WORK THAT WE DO.
AMEN.
AM
EN.
AMEN.
BLAME IS
A BEAUTIFUL
THING, BABY.
BLAME KEEPS THIS
WHOLE PLANET SPINNING.
YOU CAN POINT YOUR
FINGER AT THE NEXT MAN.
YOU CAN SHIFT THE
WEIGHT ONTO HIM.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO CARRY
THAT SHIT AROUND YOURSELF.
.
YOU CAN SLIDE INTO BED
AND GET A GOOD NIGHT'S NAP
YEAH, RIGHT.
MR. McMANUS ?
ALVAH  CASE.
OH, YES.
OR.
OUR GRAND INQUISIT
THIS IS NOT AN
INQUISITION, SIR.
IT.
BULLSH
DEVLIN'S BEEN TRYING
TO DISMANTLE EM CITY
SINCE THE BEGINNING.
.
THIS IS HIS CHANCE
OOH, LEO TOLD ME
YOU'D BE TOUGH.
HE SAYS YOU TWO AREN'T
ALWAYS IN AGREEMENT.
BUT HE ADMIRES YOU
R VISION, YOUR IDEALS.
WHAT IS IT YOU
WANT EXACTLY ?
I WANT TO ASK
SOME QUESTIONS.
I HAVE NOTHING TO SAY.
GOVERNOR IS BUSY PICKING
THE OTHER MEMBERS
OF THE COMMISSION.
IN THE MEANTIME, I'M DOING
SOME PRELIMINARY INTERVIEWS.
I HAVE
NOTHING TO SAY.
LOOK,
ULTIMATELY IT'S GO
ING TO BE UP TO ME TO DECIDE
IF EM CITY
EVER REOPENS.
I HAVE
NOTHING TO SAY.
MINISTER SAID ?
ASALAAM ALAIKUM.
ALVAH CASE.
I'M HERE TO INTERVIEW
YOU ABOUT THE RIOT.
?
IS THAT INTERV
IEW OR INTERROGATE
I GUESS THAT DEPENDS ON
WHAT YOU'RE GUILTY OF.
T.
THERE WAS NO RIO
OH, REALLY ?
LE
THERE WAS A
RIGHTEOUS STRUGG
AGAINST REPRESSION
AND INJUSTICE.
RIGHTEOUS OR NOT,
THERE ARE STILL
EIGHT BODIES
ROTTING IN
THE MORGUE.
I GRIEVE
THEIR DEATHS.
DO YOU MIND ?
PLEASE.
I UNDERSTAND THAT FROM
THE MINUTE YOU CAME TO OZ
YOU STARTED ORGANIZING
OTHER MUSLIMS,
CONVERTING STONE-COLD
KILLERS,
ALL THE WHILE SOWING
SEEDS OF DISCONTENT.
I SPOKE THE TRUTH.
THEN SPEAK IT NOW.
OH, COME ON, SAID.
YOU TALK A GOOD GAME
ABOUT THE TRUTH.
BUT HOW COME IT DOESN'T
INCLUDE TAKING RESPONSIBILITY
FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE ?
I DIDN'T FIRE
THOSE RIFLES.
DID YOU CREATE A SET
OF CIRCUMSTANCES
THAT CAUSED THE
RIFLES TO BE FIRED ?
.
THE JUDICIAL SYSTEM CREATE
D THOSE CIRCUMSTANCES, NOT I
SE.
YOUR COMMISSION
IS A FRAUD, CA
GOVERNOR DEVLIN,
THE ONE MAN WHOSE ACTION
S SHOULD BE INVESTIGATED
IS THE MAN THAT
APPOINTED YOU.
THAT'S LIKE ME GETTING
TO PICK THE JURY
AT MY OWN TRIAL.
YOU WANT TO
LICK MY BALLS ?
)
( singing
( reporters yelling )
JUDGE FEE AND MR. BALLING
WILL FOCUS ON EVENTS
LEADING UP
TO THE RIOT.
R
BISHOP CALLAHAN AND MR. DODGE
WILL DEAL WITH THE BEHAVIO
T.
OF THE INMATES AND T
HE STAFF DURING THE RIO
MRS. EIDUSON
AND DUDLEY FRIED
WILL CONCENTRATE ON
.
THEIR DECISION
TO SEND THE SORT TEAM
( reporter
) MR. CASE...
HOW LONG DO YOU ESTIMATE
THE INVESTIGATION WILL
TAKE ? DAYS, WEEKS ?
WELL,  IT WILL TAKE
AS LONG AS IT TAKES.
AND YOU'RE ?
L.
AUGUSTUS HIL
HILL...
HEY, CAN I A
SK YOU A QUESTION ?
OT.
TWO PRISONERS
GOT RELEASED ON THE RI
EUGENE DOBBINS
, JACKSON VAHUE.
?
DOBBINS WAS HURT
PRETTY BAD. YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM
MY QUESTIONS
FIRST, HILL.
SO TELL ME IN AS MANY
WORDS AS NECESSARY
WHAT YOU THINK
LED TO THE RIOT.
THEY'RE VIOLENT,
ALL THEY KNOW
IS VIOLENCE.
THE C.O.s, MAN, THEY
TREAT US LIKE SHIT.
SOMETIMES
THE INMATES
GET BORED.
.
THEY TOOK AWAY CONJUGALS
. THEY TOOK AWAY SMOKING
NO, IT'S MORE
THAN THAT.
YOU  DENY A MAN HIS FREEDOM,
HIS FAMILY, HIS PRIVACY,
HIS DIGNITY, THEN ALL HE
HAS LEFT IS TIME TO SIMMER.
THEN EVENTUALLY THE
SIMMER BECOMES A BOIL.
WE'VE BEEN HEARING
WHISPERS THAT THE MUSLIMS
WERE GONNA START TROUBLE.
THE ARYANS
ARE PARANOID.
( Augustus )
WHAT CAUSED THE RIOT ?
TWO BRAIN-DEAD
CRACK-HEAD MOTHERFUCKERS
PLAYING CHECKERS.
AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN
THE WORLD IMPLODED.
FUCKING COCKSUCKER !
WE TREATED THE
HOSTAGES GOOD.
THEY TREATED
US LIKE SHIT.
WE TRIED
TO NEGOTIATE.
THEIR DEMANDS
WERE RIDICULOUS.
AND THEN THE
LIGHTS WENT OUT.
AHHH !
THERE WAS
TEAR GAS.
GUNS.
TIM McMANUS GOT
SHOT IN THE CHEST.
I SAW THE SIDE OF RODRIGO'S
HEAD GET BLOWN OFF.
K.
HUNT AND NOWAKOWSKI
WERE BOTH HIT IN THE BAC
WHAT ABOUT
SCOTT ROSS ?
WHAT ABOUT HIM ?
WELL, ACCORDING
TO THE AUTOPSY
HE WAS SHOT
THREE TIMES.
ONCE IN THE HEAD,
ONCE IN THE HEART,
AND ONCE IN
THE TESTICLES.
YE
AH.
I WAS CURIOUS.
BULLETS FLYING RANDOMLY
EVERY WHICH WAY
AND HE GETS SHOT THREE TIMES
IN THREE VERY PRECISE PLACES ?
.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT
( Augustus )
THEY SAY CURIOSITY
KILLED THE CAT.
WHAT THE FUCK
WAS THE CAT SO
CURIOUS ABOUT
THAT GOT
HIM KILLED ?
( singing )
( Augustus )
SOLITARY SUCKS, MAN.
IF YOU REALLY WANT
SOME COMPANY,
YOU JUST GOTTA GO
THROUGH WITHDRAWAL.
JUST WHAT I LOVE, MY
PRISON IN LOCKDOWN,
CRAWLING WITH OUTSIDE
INVESTIGATORS
AND TV CAMERAS.
WHAT ARE YOU
AFRAID WE'LL FIND ?
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU'LL FIND BUT
THE WAY YOU FIND IT. THESE
QUESTIONS STIR THINGS UP.
AND GOD KNOWS EVERYONE'S
STIRRED UP ENOUGH RIGHT NOW.
LEO, WHO WAS
SCOTT ROSS ?
ROSS ?
WELL, HE WAS A
BIKER, DRUG DEALER,
THREE STRIKES LIFER, WHY ?
WELL,
I'M NOT SURE YET
BUT ROSS MAY HAVE
BEEN MURDERED.
WHAT ?
DURING THE SORT
TEAM'S ATTACK
HE MAY HAVE BEEN
KILLED DELIBERATELY.
WHAT MAKES YOU
THINK THAT ?
HE WAS SHOT THREE TIME
S, ALMOST EXECUTION STYLE.
s,
AND THE BULLETS IN
ROSS' BODY WERE 9mm'
S,
NOT DOUBLE-OUGHT
.
WHICH WERE
IN SORT RIFLES
THE SORT TEAM USES
9mm IN A HANDGUN.
RIGHT.
SO SORT TEAM MEMBER A,
HE ENTERS THE COMMON
ROOM IN EM CITY,
LOWERS HIS RIFLE,
ROSS COMES AT HIM
FROM OUT OF THE DARK,
HE RAISES HIS HANDGUN,
FIRES, THAT'S NOT MURDER.
YOU THROW A BULLET
IN SOMEONE'S BRAIN,
YOU PRETTY MUCH
FIGURE HE'S DONE.
MAYBE HE SHOT HIM
IN THE HEART FIRST,
G.
OR THE BALLS A
ND ROSS  KEPT COMIN
YEAH, BUT THE BULLET
FROM ROSS' BRAIN
WAS IN THE WALL BELOW THE
COMMAND CENTER BY A TV.
AND THE ONE THAT WENT
THROUGH HIS HEART
WAS EMBEDDED
IN THE FLOOR.
SO UNLESS HE DIED
FALLING UPWARDS...
IT'S MURDER.
( grunting )
( blowing whistle )
( Augustus )
IN ALL THAT CHAOS,
WHAT A PERFECT
CHANCE TO OFF ROSS,
AND GET AWAY WITH
IT, SCOTT-FREE.
THAT'S HIM
OVER THERE.
OFFICER HEIM ?
THE BULLETS THAT
KILLED ROSS
CAME FROM THE
SAME BOX
AS THE ONES THAT YOU
PUT IN YOUR HANDGUN.
SO ?
S.
SO YOUR GUN WAS
USED TO KILL ROS
UH-HUH.
YET YOU DON'T MENTION FIRING
AT HIM IN YOUR REPORT.
I DIDN'T.
?
THEN WHO DID
I DON'T KNOW.
( gunshots )
?
DID YOU HAND YOU
R GUN TO SOMEONE
NO.
?
WAS IT IN YOUR HOLST
ER WHEN YOU ENTERED EM CITY
YES.
AND THEN ?
IT DISAPPEARED.
DID YOU FEEL
ANYONE TAKE IT ?
NO, THINGS WERE CRAZY
IN THERE, YOU KNOW ?
HAPPENING
PRETTY FAST.
SO YOU'RE TELLING ME
UN
THAT SOMEONE
LIFTED THE HANDG
G ?
OUT OF YOUR HOLSTER
WITHOUT YOU KNOWIN
THAT'S RIGHT.
TTY
WELL, HOW COME YOU DID
N'T MENTION THAT LITTLE DI
IN YOUR REPORT ?
BECAUSE I FOUND
IT ON THE FLOOR.
IM,
OFFICER HE
DO I LOOK LIKE A STUPI
D FUCKING IDIOT TO YOU ?
NO, SIR.
!
THEN C
UT THE SHIT
YOU SORT GUYS LOVE YOU
R WEAPONS MORE THAN PUSSY.
IT
YOU'D DIE BEFORE
LETTING ANYONE TAKE
AND YOU'D SURE AS CHRIST
KNOW IT WAS GONE.
?
WHO ARE YOU
COVERING FOR, HUH
SCOTT ROSS WAS A
LOW-LIFE SCUM FUCK
JUST LIKE ALL THOSE
OTHER SCUM FUCKS IN THERE.
THEY HURT
ARMSTRONG AND MINEO.
BECAUSE OF THEM, HUNT
AND NOWAKOWSKI DIED.
ARE YOU SERIOUSLY
GOING AFTER SOME C.O.
BECAUSE THEY WHACKED A
FUCKING PIG LIKE ROSS ?
WHO THE FUCK'S
SIDE ARE YOU ON ?
THE LAW, I'M ON
THE LAW'S SIDE.
.
NOW YOU CAN GO
THANK YOU.
( Augustus )
I NEVER LIE.
NOT 'CAUSE I'M
SO HONEST BUT,
'CAUSE I HAVE
A BAD MEMORY
AND YOU CAN'T
BE A GOOD LIAR
IF YOU GOT
A BAD MEMORY.
WANGLER,
YOU OKAY ?
I NEED SOME TITS,
HELP ME...
TITS IS THE LAST
THING YOU NEED, MAN.
HEY, COME
ON, WAKE UP.
GET UP FOR
A SECOND
.
NO.
COME ON, M
AN.
NO, FUCK YOU.
N,
SUCK MY COCK, MA
COME ON, MAN,
SUCK MY COCK.
.
COME ON, M
AN, SUCK MY COCK, PRAG
FUCK YOU.
( sound of heavy blow )
GET UP
.
ALRIGHT.
GO.
LET'S
COME ON, WHAT
THE FUCK, MAN,
LET'S GO.
OKAY, OKAY.
H.
COME ON,
COME ON BITC
YEAH,
AH.
OH, YE
AHHHH !
( alarm )
( screaming )
AHHH !
YOU STILL ON
THE JOB ?
YEAH.
SO ARE YOU.
WELL, WE HAD A COUPLE
OF INCIDENTS TONIGHT.
ANYTHING I SHOULD
KNOW ABOUT ?
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE ?
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE
THIS ROSS THING THROUGH.
EFT
THERE WAS
SIX HOSTAGES L
D.
WHEN THE S
ORT TEAM ATTACKE
McMANUS, WITTLESEY
, MUKADA, D'AGNASTI, HUNT,
.
AND NOWAKOWSKI
NTS
NOW HUNT AND NOWAKOWSKI
DIED DURING THE FIRST MOME
,
OF THE ASSAULT AND
McMANUS WAS SHOT
SO THERE'S LESS OF A CHANCE
THAT HE KILLED ROSS.
WHAT MAKES YOU SO
SURE IT WAS A C.O. ?
WHY NOT A PRISONER ?
ROSS WASN'T EXACTLY BELOVED
BY HIS FELLOW INMATES.
HT.
OH, THAT WAS
MY FIRST THOUG
Y
THAT SOMEONE USE
D THE OPPORTUNIT
TO TAKE REVENGE
ON A GUY.
M,
BUT AFTER TALK
ING WITH OFFICER HEI
WHO BY THE WAY, LEO, I
S LYING THROUGH HIS TEETH,
N.
I REALIZED HE'D
NEVER COVER FOR A CO
.
HE'S PROTECTIN
G ONE OF HIS OWN
D'AGNASTI.
OR WITTLESEY.
OR MUKADA.
NOW STOP !
FATHER MUKADA
WASN'T INVOLVED.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
( Case )
HOW DID ROSS
TREAT EVERYONE ?
HE WAS A CONDESCENDING
LITTLE PRICK.
DID HE DO ANY HARM TO YOU,
PERSONALLY, PHYSICALLY ?
NOPE.
WHAT ABOUT OFFICERS
WITTLESEY OR D'AGNASTI ?
I DON'T REMEMBER.
I'D  BEEN BEATEN PRETTY
BADLY AND I WAS...
TERRIFIED.
ANYTHING ELSE
YOU REMEMBER ?
MY NOSE ITCHED.
.
BUT BECAUSE OUR HAND
S WERE TIED BEHIND US,
I COULDN'T SCRATCH
STAND IN A
STRAIGHT LINE.
WHEN THEY COME IN,
YOU GET HIT FIRST.
( Mukada )
THROUGH IT ALL,
THROUGH THE TEAR GAS AND
THE GUNFIRE AND THE
FEAR AND THE ADRENALINE
IN OVERDRIVE,
,
THE ONLY THING I
COULD THINK OF WAS
?"
"CHRIST, WOULD SOMEONE
PLEASE SCRATCH MY NOSE
( Wangler )
TITS !
TS.
I NEED SOME TI
SHUT THE FUCK UP
FUCK YOU,
YOU FAT FUCK.
YOU HEAR ANYTHING
ABOUT DOBBINS
OR VAHUE ?
!
I'M ASKING YOU A
QUESTION, D'AGNASTI
I NEED
SOME TITS !
NO.
( Augustus
) THANK YOU !
OW !
( D'Agnasti )
YOU JUNKIE FUCK,
SHUT THE FUCK UP
BEFORE I KICK THE
SHIT OUT OF YOU !
I.
D'AGNAST
I, D'AGNAST
WHAT ?
CAN I ASK YOU A FEW
MORE QUESTIONS ?
I'M WORKING HERE.
F.
I'LL BE BRIE
?
ALL OF THE HOSTAGE
S WERE BOUND, RIGHT
?
HANDS BEHIND Y
OUR BACK WITH ROPE
YEAH.
WHEN DID Y
OU GET FREE ?
SOMETIME AFTER
THE SHOOTING
STOPPED.
WHO TIED YOU UP ?
WHICH PRISONERS
IN PARTICULAR ?
SCOTT ROSS.
( inmate howling )
SETTLE DOWN
WANGLER !
SS.
YOU DIDN'T LIKE RO
WHAT WAS THERE
TO LIKE ?
SHUT THE
FUCK UP !
ET.
PRETTY QUI
WHAT ?
,
WELL, COMPARED TO YOUR LAS
T ASSIGNMENT AT EMERALD CITY
ET.
THIS IS PRETTY QUI
( alarm beeping )
WHOA, WHOA,
CAN I HELP YOU ?
YEAH, I'M HERE TO SEE
MY HUSBAND, BILLY KEMPF.
I'M SORRY, WE'RE
IN LOCKDOWN.
NO, NO, NO, OKAY ?
I DROVE 312 MILES.
LOOK, LOOK.
IT SAYS I'M SUPPOSED TO
SEE BILLY KEMPF TODAY.
?
WE HAD A RIOT HERE,
MAYBE YOU HEARD ABOUT IT
YES, I HEARD ABOUT
IT. I ALSO HEARD THE
FUCKING THING WAS OVER.
YES, IT IS.
SO YOU LET
ME SEE BILLY.
YOU WON'T BE
SEEING HIM TODAY.
YOU DON'T GET IT, HONEY,
I DROVE 312 MILES... !
CAN I HELP Y
OU WITH ANYTHING ELSE
?
YOU CAN OPEN THOSE FUCKING...
CAN I HELP YOU
WITH ANYTHING ELSE ?
I DON'T HAVE TO STAND
FOR THIS BULLSHIT ! WHO
DO YOU THINK YOU ARE !
I DROVE 300...
THIS IS BULLSHIT !
L.
MAYBE IT'S NOT S
O QUIET AFTER AL
NED
NOW, DIANE,
WHAT HAPPE
FROM THE POINT
THE SORT TEAM
ENTERED EM CITY ?
I TOLD YOU
THIS ALREADY.
I KNOW, DUMB-ASS ME,
I LOST MY NOTEBOOK.
WELL, THE TEAR GAS
MADE IT HARD TO SEE.
TIM McMANUS AND I, WE
DUCKED BEHIND A COLUMN.
WE HEARD GUNFIRE FOR
WHAT SEEMED LIKE FOREVER
AND THEN SILENCE.
WE THOUGHT
IT WAS OVER.
TIM LEANED OUT
AND HE GOT SHOT.
HE FELL TO
THE FLOOR ?
YES.
U ?
AND YO
I CRADLED HIM IN MY ARMS
UNTIL HELP ARRIVED.
WHAT KIND OF PRISONER
WAS SCOTT ROSS ?
WHAT KIND ?
MODEL, TROUBLE ?
AVERAGE.
,
( Ross )
YOU AND ME
WE'RE JOINED
AT THE HIP
AND THERE AIN'T NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT THAT.
U.
THANK YO
U, THANK YO
( Augustus )
YOU ASK MOST PEOPLE,
THEY'LL TELL YOU
LYING IS WRONG,
AND THEN IMMEDIATELY GO OU
T AND LIE LIKE A MOTHERFUCKER.
BUT THAT'S COOL.
WE ALL KNOW
LIES ARE NECESSARY.
Y ?
I WAS TALKING TO
THEM YESTERDAY.
WHAT'D THEY SA
THEY SAY TIM WILL
BE OUT OF BENCHLEY
MEMORIAL NEXT WEEK.
OH, JEEZ,
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
I'VE ONLY BEEN OVER
TO SEE HIM ONCE.
( Diane )
HEY...
HI.
THIS GUY, CASE,
HAS HE BEEN
TALKING TO YOU ?
YEAH, HE INTERVIEWED
ME YESTERDAY.
OO.
YEAH, ME T
DID HE ASK
ABOUT ME ?
O.
NOT IN PARTICULAR, N
UMM-MM.
OKAY.
ON.
( Augustus )
HEY, JACKS
YOU OKAY, MAN ?
HOW'S DOBBINS ?
HE'S DEAD,
MAN, HE DIED.
FUCK.
E.
THERE YOU AR
YOU'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR ME ?
AY.
EVERYWHERE. BALLIN
G AND I HAVE BEEN TRYI
NG TO MEET WITH YOU ALL D
I'VE BEEN WORKING
THIS MURDER ANGLE.
.
OH, CHRIST
ALVAH, FORGET
ABOUT THAT,
.
REALLY
YOU DON'T WANNA
CONCERN YOURSELF WITH
THINGS LIKE THAT.
BELIEVE ME, YOU'RE LOOKING
IN THE WRONG DIRECTION.
IT'S ALL PART OF
THE STORY, JUDGE.
IT'S ALL PART
OF THE STORY.
WELL, WE SEDATED
ADEBISI PRETTY HEAVILY.
HE SHOULD BE OUT FOR
A COUPLE OF HOURS.
OH, GOOD.
.
I COULD US
E A BREAK ANYWAY
AND HOW ABOUT
YOU, YOU EVER TAKE
TEN MINUTES ?
OH, SURE.
OD.
GO
?
CAN I BUY YOU
A CUP OF COFFEE
I DON'T THINK SO.
T ?
WHY NO
YOU MAKE ME NERVOUS.
WHO, ME ?
LISTEN, I'M
THE SWEETEST GUY
ON THE PLANET,
ASK MY MOTHER.
YEAH, WELL, IF WE WENT
OUT FOR COFFEE TOGETHER
I WOULDN'T BE
SURE IF YOU WERE,
INTERROGATING ME...
DR. NATHAN,
I SWEAR,
I'M FAR LESS DEVIOUS
THAN YOU THINK.
I'M A COLLEGE PROFESSOR
FOR PETE'S SAKE,
I GIVE LECTURES,
I GRADE PAPERS.
YOU TRAIN LAWYERS.
YES, OKAY.
S.
I'LL STOP BEING ADORAB
LE AND JUST ASK MY QUESTION
MR. ROBSON,
THE TIP OF YOUR PENIS
HAS BEEN SEVERED.
?
HOW'S YOUR
DICK, MAN
( inaudible )
...ABSOLUTELY SEVERED...
YOUR DICK HAS
BEEN SEVERED.
SEVERED, SEVERED,
SEVERED...
?
HOW'S IT FEEL
WEIRD.
IT.
OH, SH
( chanting )
( banging )
AHHHH !
GET THE FUCK
AWAY FROM ME !
GET OFF ME !
JUST ANOTHER JUNKIE
ASSHOLE SPIRALING OUT.
E !
GET THE FUCK OFF M
THE PUBLIC OUTCRY AGAINST
GOVERNER DEVLIN'S DECISION
TO USE FORCE AT
OSWALD REMAINS HIGH.
EVEN AS A GUBERNATORIAL
COMMISSION SEARCHES
FOR ANSWERS.
GUYS, HELP ME
OUT HERE.
WHAT THE FUCK IS
TAKING SO LONG ?
YOU WANT THIS DONE
RIGHT OR FAST ?
BOTH !
I WANT ANOTHER PRESS
CONFERENCE, GIVE
THEM AN UPDATE.
I'M TIRED OF SAYING
BE PATIENT, AND I AM
TIRED OF TELLING THEM
THAT I HAVE ABSOLUTE
FAITH IN YOU, 'CAUSE
FRANKLY I DON'T.
WE'D BE MOVING A LOT FASTER
IF ALVAH COULD JUST STAY
FOCUSED ON THE BIG PICTURE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
HE'S OFF SOLVING
A MURDER
THAT ISN'T A MURDER.
IT'S MURDER.
WELL, IF IT IS,
IT IS ONLY A SMALL PART
OF OUR OVERALL MISSION.
I DISAGREE.
I THINK IT'S ENDEMIC OF
THE WHOLE PROBLEM HERE AT OZ.
YOU ARE SO
FULL OF SHIT !
GIVEN THE LAST
THREE DECISIONS
YOU'VE HANDED DOWN
FROM THE BENCH,
YOU'RE THE EXPERT
ON FULL OF SHIT.
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN
?
DON'T FUCK WITH ME.
GUYS, GUYS !
THAT'S FINE, FORGET
IT, I'LL RESIGN !
NO, I'LL RESIGN !
NO ONE IS
RESIGNING !
THE LAST THING I NEED IS
FOR THE MEDIA TO HEAR THAT
THE COMMISSION IS FIGHTING.
BACK TO YOUR CORNERS
AND BACK TO WORK.
THE SOONER WE
GET THIS DONE,
THE HAPPIER
WE'LL ALL BE.
( moaning )
ER.
SWEET DREA
MS, MOTHERFUCK
( mumbling )
YOU KNOW THE LAST TIME I HAD
A WOMAN TIE ME DOWN LIKE THIS,
I MARRIED HER.
WELL, IF SHE'D KEP
T YOU LIKE THAT,
YOU MIGHT STIL
L BE MARRIED.
I FEEL GOOD.
YOU CAN LET
ME GO NOW.
WELL, BEFORE THAT HAPPENS,
YOU, SISTER MARIE AND I
ER.
NEED TO SPEND A
LITTLE TIME TOGETH
HEY, DOCTOR, MY
DICK IS HARD.
IS THAT GOOD ?
YOU TELL ME.
WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING FOR ?
YOUR IMPRESSIONS
OF ROSS.
YOU'RE A TEACHER,
RIGHT ?
I USED TO BE, NOW
THAT I'M A DEAN,
M.
I SPEND LESS AND L
ESS TIME IN THE CLASSROO
YOU KNOW HOW TEACHERS GET
FAVORITE STUDENTS SOMETIMES,
GET A REAL
AFFECTION FOR THEM ?
OH, YEAH.
I COULDN'T WAIT FOR ROSS
TO LEAVE THE OFFICE.
U ?
DID HE FRIGHTEN YO
THAT AND HE
HAD A TERRIBLE
HYGIENE PROBLEM.
DID HE EVE
R MENTION HAVING A
SEXUAL RELATIONSHIP WITH
ANYONE ON THE STAFF ?
AS YOU'LL SEE IN THE FILES,
HE SAID A LOT OF THINGS.
HE WAS A COMPULSIVE LIAR.
DO YOU EVER COUNSEL
STAFF MEMBERS ?
SURE.
DID ANYONE EVE
R TALK OF ROSS,
?
I MEAN NEGATIVELY
SURE.
WHO ?
EVERYBODY.
CAN YOU BE A LITTLE
MORE SPECIFIC ?
COME ON, YOU KNOW A NUN
DOESN'T REVEAL THE CONFIDENCE.
YOU'RE NOT
A PRIEST.
.
THE SILENCE OF
THE CONFESSIONAL
DOESN'T APPLY HERE
AS A PSYCHOLOGIST,
IT DOES.
.
THEN WE MAY HAVE TO LE
T A COURT DETERMINE THAT
WELL, THAT'S FINE.
I WANT THOSE FILES BACK WHEN
YOU'RE THROUGH WITH THEM.
ANYTHING ELSE ?
NO.
RYAN O'REILLY.
YO, YO, THAT'S
ME, MAN.
VEHICULAR MANSLAUGHTER
, RECKLESS ENDANGERMENT,
S,
POSSESSION OF
CONTROLLED SUBSTANCE
POSSESSION
OF A DEADLY WEAPON,
VIOLATION OF PAROLE.
THAT'S AN
AMAZING LIST
OF CRIMES.
YEAH WELL, YOU KNOW,
I APPLIED MYSELF.
,
STILL, I MEAN EVEN
WITH ALL THOSE TALENTS
YOU MUST HAVE HAD A
HARD TIME ADJUSTING
TO LIFE IN OZ.
NO, I CAN TAKE
CARE OF MYSELF.
AT.
YEAH, I CAN SEE TH
BUT HOW ?
I'M LIKE THE LORD
OF THE FUCKING DANCE.
I GOT MOVES.
YEAH, I'LL
BET YOU DO.
T,
OF ALL THE GUYS
THAT LED THE RIO
YOU WERE THE ONLY ON
E WITH NO FIRE BEHIND YOU.
YET THE OTHERS
INCLUDED YOU
IN ALL T
HE DECISION MAKING.
I HAD NOTHING TO
DO WITH THE RIOT.
OH, I GUESS
I WAS MISINFORMED.
I GUESS YOU WERE.
E
LIKE I HEARD FRO
M WHAT I THOUGHT WAS
A RELIABLE SOURC
THAT YOU AND
ROSS WERE CLOSE.
CLOSE, NO ?
.
THAT YOU AND
HE WERE LOVERS
NOW, WHO THE FUCK
TOLD YOU THAT ?
E.
ROSS POURED HIS HEART
OUT TO SISTER PETER MARI
HEY, LOOK, I'M
NO FAG, PAL.
BUT IF I WERE,
I WOULDN'T PUT MY
DICK ANYWHERE NEAR
ROSS'S SCUM HOLE.
THAT COCKSUCKER WOULD
FUCK ANYTHING ON
TWO OR FOUR LEGS.
YEAH, WELL
WHAT ABOUT C.O.s,
DID ROSS EVER
FUCK ONE OF THEM ?
HOW ABOUT SOME
HELP GETTING ME
OUT OF THIS PLACE ?
E
SORRY, YOU'RE NO
T GOING ANY PLAC
UNTIL THE
INVESTIGATION
IS OVER.
WELL, THEN HOW
ABOUT A CIGARETTE ?
OH, THIS IS GOOD.
WHEN I'M DONE
PUFFING ON THIS,
I CAN SUCK ON MY OWN
SECONDHAND SMOKE.
,
SO
ROSS HAD A THING
FOR WITTLESEY.
?
YEAH
YEAH.
HE CLAIMED THEY KNEW
EACH OTHER ON THE
OUTSIDE. IT MAKES SENSE.
THEY WERE ALWAYS
SNEAKING OFF AND
WHISPERING TO EACH OTHER.
?
WHAT'S THE MATTER
THIS GUY, CASE, HE
GIVES ME THE CREEPS.
WHY ?
YOU GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
HE'LL DO HIS INQUIRY,
HE'LL BE GONE.
YUP.
RIGHT ?
YEAH, I GUESS.
THEY ALSO SAY IF YOU REPEAT
A LIE OFTEN ENOUGH,
IT BECOMES THE TRUTH,
OR AT LEAST YOU
CONVINCE YOURSELF
IT'S THE FUCKING GOSPEL.
YOU RUN THE ARYAN
BROTHERHOOD, MR.
SCHILLINGER ?
O.
I USED T
YOU HAVE A PAROLE
DATE COMING UP.
YUP.
YOU THINK YOU GOT A
CHANCE OF GETTING OUT ?
O,
I HOPE S
MY SONS NEED ME.
WELL, I'D BE HAPPY
TO PUT A LETTER
OF RECOMMENDATION
IN YOUR FILE.
T.
IF I HELP YOU OU
THAT'S RIGHT.
SCOTT ROSS.
POOR SON-OF-A-BITCH.
SO YOU WERE FRIENDS ?
( laughing )
DID HE EVER
MENTION HAVING A
SEXUAL RELATIONSHIP
WITH OFFICER WITTLESEY ?
RE.
SU
.
ROSS AND WITTLESEY'S E
X WERE IN THE SAME BIKE CLUB
ROSS SAID HE NAILED HE
R BEHIND HER HUBBY'S BACK,
BUT THEN AGAIN,
ROSS WAS SOMETIMES
A LYING SACK OF SHIT,
SO WHO KNOWS
IF IT'S TRUE.
DID ANYTHING GO ON
BETWEEN THE TWO OF THEM
SINCE HE CAME TO OZ ?
S,
ACCORDING TO ROS
.
HE WAS BANGING
HER PRETTY REGULAR
YOU THINK HE WAS
LYING ABOUT THAT ?
PROBABLY.
Y.
THANK YOU FOR GETT
ING ME PERMISSION TO
COME TO THE LIBRAR
LOCKDOWNS CAN BE BORING
WITH NOTHING TO READ.
OH, NO PROBLEM.
THEY TELL ME YOU
KNOW EVERYTHING
THAT GOES ON IN OZ.
THEY EXAGGERATE.
DO YOU HAVE ANY
IDEA, IF ANYTHING,
WHAT TRANSPIRED BETWEEN
OFFICER WITTLESEY
AND SCOTT ROSS ?
CIGARETTES.
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
CIGARETTES WAS WHAT WA
S GOING ON BETWEEN THEM.
WITTLESEY SMUGGLED
THEM IN, A CARTON A DAY.
SHE GAVE THEM TO ROS
S TO SELL. EVERYTHIN
G WAS GOING SMOOTHLY
UNTIL McMANUS
FOUND OUT.
HE MADE WITTLESEY SHUT
DOWN THE OPERATION.
SO ROSS HATED
McMANUS FOR THAT.
AND BECAUSE WITTLESEY
AND McMANUS STARTED
SLEEPING TOGETHER.
HEY, GOT A
CIGARETTE ?
YEAH, WHY WOULD
YOU ? ROSS IS DEAD.
IT'S FUNNY
, YOU KNOW,
WHAT A GUY CAN
SEE WITH ONE EYE,
AS.
IN THE DARK,
THROUGH THE TEAR G
DON'T WORRY.
I DIDN'T TELL THAT NIGGER,
CASE, A FUCKING THING.
SO WHAT DO YOU
WANT FROM ME ?
WELL, I GOT A
PAROLE HEARING
COMING UP.
I THINK MAYBE THE
BEST THING FOR YOU
E.
WOULD BE FOR M
E TO BE OUT OF HER
SO YOU THINK
WITTLESEY
KILLED ROSS ?
SHE HAD MOTIVE,
OPPORTUNITY.
I'VE KNO
WN DIANE FOR YEARS.
DON'T WALK IN HERE
AND TALK ABOUT MOTIVE
AND OPPORTUNITY !
GIVE ME SOME
EVIDENCE.
IN THE HEAT OF THE RIOT,
MAYBE SHE JUST LOST IT.
T.
NO, IT HAD TO BE A MORE
SPECIFIC REASON THAN THA
ROSS HAD TO HAVE DON
E SOMETHING AT THAT MOMENT
TO GET HER TO
PULL THE TRIGGER.
( phone )
O.
HELL
YEAH, OKAY, OKAY.
OFFICER SAYS A PRISONER
WANTS TO TALK TO YOU.
WHICH ONE ?
TOBIAS BEECHER.
HEY, CHIEF.
YOU ASKED
TO SEE ME ?
I GOT A SECRET.
ABOUT ?
SCOTT ROSS.
TELL ME.
IF I TELL YOU, IT
WON'T BE A SECRET.
WOULD YOU EXCUSE
US PLEASE ?
OKAY.
I BIT THE TIP OFF
A GUY'S PENIS.
.
SO I HEARD
YOU'RE NOT AFRAID ?
WELL, I'VE GOT
MY PANTS ON.
( laughing )
I USED TO BE A LAWYER,
YOU KNOW THAT ?
.
UH-HUH
I WENT TO HARVARD.
SO DID I.
RAH, RAH, CRIMSON...
I'VE BEEN UNDER A LOT
OF STRESS LATELY.
I HAVEN'T BEEN
BEHAVING VERY NICELY,
LIKE THIS BITING THING.
BUT I'M USING
MY TIME IN HERE
TO TURN MY
HEAD AROUND.
WHEN I GET OUT OF
HERE, I'M GONNA BE
A BETTER PERSON.
THIS WHOLE
BITING THING
JUST ISN'T WORKING
FOR ME, YOU KNOW ?
SO AS A SIGN THAT I'M ON
THE STRAIGHT AND NARROW,
I'M GONNA TELL YOU
MY LITTLE SECRET
AND THEN I'LL BE ON
THE ROAD BACK, RIGHT ?
YEAH, YEAH.
I SAW THE
SHOTS FIRED.
WHICH SHOTS ?
CHECK THE BULLETS.
THE BULLETS THAT
KILLED ROSS ?
NO.
CHECK THE BULLETS
IN McMANUS.
HEY !
m
McMANUS WASN'T
SHOT WITH A 9m
UN.
FROM THE S
ORT TEAM HANDG
m,
THE STRIATIONS SHOW
HE WAS HIT WITH A 9m
ER.
PROBABLY FROM A
GLOCK OR A SIG-SAU
SIG-SAUER, WELL WE
KNOW THERE WAS A SIG-SAUER
IN EM CITY DURING THE RIOT.
?
WHOSE WAS IT
KAREEM SAID.
YOU SHOT
TIM McMANUS.
NO.
WELL, IF YOU
DIDN'T, WHO DID ?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU HAD A SIG-SAUER
IN YOUR POSSESSION.
N.
IF I SAY YES, THAT'S
ANOTHER NAIL IN MY COFFI
?
DO I LOOK LIKE
A FOOL TO YOU
ARE YOU
COMFORTABLE HERE ?
'CAUSE YOU KNOW
IT'S UP TO ME
WHEN AND IF YOU GET OUT
OF SOLITARY CONFINEMENT.
NOW I KNOW HOW
IMPORTANT IT IS FOR YOU
TO BE AMONG
YOUR PEOPLE,
LEADING, GUIDING,
NURTURING THEM.
THAT'S GONNA BE HARD TO DO
THROUGH EIGHT TONS OF STEEL.
YOU'RE AN
ACADEMIC, RIGHT ?
YOU KNOW ABOUT HYPOTHESES
AND THEORIES, RIGHT ?
WELL,
THEORETICALLY
SPEAKING,
D,
IF I HAD A GUN WHEN
THE SORT TEAM ENTERE
HERE'S WHAT MIGH
T HAVE HAPPENED.
I MIGHT HAVE BEEN
UNDERNEATH THE CONTROL PANEL
AT THE COMMAND STATION
HOLDING THAT GUN.
WHEN THE SORT TEAM
MEMBER CAME IN
AND STARTED
TO BEAT ME,
AND IN NOT WANTING
TO KILL ANYBODY,
.
I MIGHT HAVE THROW
N THAT GUN OVER THE SIDE
WHERE SOMEONE ELSE
PICKED IT UP.
THEORETICALLY
SPEAKING, YES.
ME,
I KNOW YOU'VE GOT
NOTHING TO SAY TO
.
BUT I HAVE A COUPLE OF
THINGS TO SAY TO YOU
FIRST, YOU'VE
GOT BALLS.
ITY
YOU VOLUNTARIL
Y WENT INTO EM C
TO NEGOTIATE THE RELEA
SE OF THE INJURED OFFICERS
AND DIANE WITTLESEY.
+YOU TRADED YOURSELF FOR
ARMSTRONG AND MINEO,
PUTTING YOURSELF IN WHAT
COULD ONLY BE CALLED
N.
A JACK
POT SITUATIO
NDS
ESPECIALLY KNOWING THAT
YOU'D FALL INTO THE HA
OF SCOTT ROSS, A
MAN YOU DESPISED.
HOW IRONIC IS IT
THEN THAT HE WAS THE
ONE WHO SHOT YOU.
ANY LAST WORDS ?
SUCK MY DICK.
WHO TOLD YOU ?
?
THAT ROSS WAS
THE ONE THAT SHOT YOU
YEAH.
YOU JUST DID.
YOU KNOW, OZ,
IS JUST LIKE
ANY PLACE ELSE.
EVERYBODY LOVES TO GOSSIP
ABOUT EVERYBODY ELSE.
NOT ME.
OU.
OH, BUT THEY
GOSSIP ABOUT Y
E
WELL, MAYBE IT'S 'CAUS
YOU'RE ONE OF THE
FEW WOMEN AROUND.
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE
THERE'S TRUTH TO
THE RUMORS.
E,
LIKE, FOR EXAMPL
THAT YOU WERE SMUGGLING
CIGARETTES IN
LL.
THAT ROSS COULD SE
R.
AND THAT YOU AND
McMANUS HAD AN AFFAI
YOU ACCUSING ME
OF SOMETHING ?
YES, YES, I AM.
YOU, YOU KILLED
SCOTT ROSS.
ME ? HOW DID I DO THAT ?
N.
ROSS PICKE
D UP SAID'S GU
HE FIRED INTO
McMANUS'S CHEST, BANG !
YOU TOOK OFFICER HEIM'S
PISTOL AND SHOT ROSS.
BANG, BANG, BANG.
THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
MY HANDS WERE TIED
BEHIND MY BACK.
NO, THEY WEREN'T.
YOU MANAGED TO LOOSE
THE BINDS BEFORE IT
ALL CAME DOWN.
YOU TOLD ME THAT
AFTER McMANUS FELL
TO THE GROUND, YOU,
QUOTE, "I CRADLED HIM
IN MY ARMS," END QUOTE.
HOW COULD YOU
CRADLE HIM
WITH YOUR ARMS
BEHIND YOUR BACK ?
HAVE YOU EVER
BEEN IN A RIOT ?
NO.
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S INVOLVED.
THE IDEA OF BEING
A HOSTAGE, THE
MOB MENTALITY,
YOU GET CARRIED AWAY,
YOU STOP BEING HUMAN.
YOU BECOME PART
OF SOMETHING ELSE.
I HAVE MADE EVERY
MISTAKE THERE IS.
I HAVE FALLEN IN LOVE
WITH THE WRONG MEN,
I HAD A BABY
OUT OF WEDLOCK,
I DRANK TOO MUCH,
I SNORTED TOO MUCH.
I HAVE DONE THINGS
TO MAKE MONEY,
INCLUDING THIS JOB,
WHICH MAKE ME DREAD
GETTING OUT OF BED.
BUT EACH TIME I
MADE THE CHOICE.
I CHOSE TO DRINK,
I CHOSE TO STOP.
WHEN MY HUSBAND GOT
ABUSIVE, I CHOSE TO WALK.
I REFUSE TO BE
ANYBODY'S VICTIM.
THESE MISTAKES I'VE MADE,
THEY ARE A PART OF ME.
THEY ARE LIKE MY SKIN.
AND I DO NOT REGRET
WHAT I'VE DONE.
DO YOU HEAR ME ?
NO REGRETS,
NO REMORSE.
I JUST KEEP GOING.
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ?
WHEN I KNOW,
YOU'LL KNOW.
SHE HAS A YOUN
G DAUGHTER, A MOTHER
IN AND OUT OF CHEMO.
SO WHAT, LEO,
SO WHAT ?
TH,
SO IF YOU
EXPOSE THE TRU
YOU DESTROY THIS WOMAN'S
LIFE AND HER DAUGHTER'S.
AND FOR WHAT, SCOT
T FUCKING ROSS ?!
E.
COME ON ALVAH, PLEAS
WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO SAY, LEO ?
TO SAY THAT ROSS DIED
LIKE THE OTHERS,
M
FROM BULLETS FIRED BY
A MEMBER OF THE SORT TEA
IN THE PERFORMANCE
OF HIS DUTY.
I JUST READ THE PRELIMINARY
DRAFT OF YOUR REPORT.
WHAT'S WRONG ?
YOU RECOMMEND NOT FILING
CHARGES AGAINST SAID
AND THE RIOT LEADERS ?!
FROM A LEGAL STANDPOINT,
THE EVIDENCE IS
CIRCUMSTANTIAL.
FROM A MORAL STANDPOINT,
IT'S LAUGHABLE.
LOOK, GOVERNOR
, AS FAR AS I CAN SEE,
WHATEVER THEY
DID CAME ABOUT
AS A DIRECT RESULT
OF YOUR ACTIONS !
.
YOU'VE EXONERATED ME.
OH, YEAH, YEAH
YOUR COMMISSION BEHAVE
D LIKE GOOD LITTLE BOYS.
S.
BUT YOU CAN'T
HAVE IT BOTH WAY
IF THE PRISONERS ARE
GUILTY, SO ARE YOU.
THIS IS NOT THE KIND
OF ATTITUDE I EXPECT
FROM AN
ATTORNEY GENERAL.
YEAH, WELL, I'VE
THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
ATTORNEY GENERAL.
I WANT TO BE GOVERNOR.
WHAT ?
I'LL SEE YOU
ON THE CAMPAIGN
TRAIL, DEVLIN.
NOW, I'VE GOT A PRESS
CONFERENCE TO DO.
IT IS THE CONSIDERED
OPINION OF THIS COMMISSION
THAT THOUGH
THE RIOT ITSELF
AND THE DEATHS THAT
FOLLOWED ARE TRAGIC,
NO ONE IN PARTICULAR
IS AT FAULT.
( reporter chatter )
WE DO FEEL THAT THERE
ARE CERTAIN MEASURES
THAT CAN BE
TAKEN TO INSURE
THAT AN EVENT LIKE THIS
DOES NOT HAPPEN AGAIN.
BITCH.
( Augustus )
SO, AS IT TURNS OUT,
NO ONE WAS TO
BLAME FOR THE RIOT.
IN FACT, IF NO
ONE WAS TO BLAME,
THAT MEANS NOTHING
BAD HAPPENED.
NOTHING AT
ALL HAPPENED.
SO LIFE CAN PRETTY MUCH
GO ON AS IT HAS BEFORE.