This is Dorris Archer,
she's the third woman to go missing
In Boise, Idaho, this year, along
with Paula Renmar and Samantha Rush.
They went missing roughly
2 months apart.
Hello.
Did you join a boy band?
No.
OK, so what are we looking at here?
Late 20s, early 30s.
All single, though two are in committed
relationships. All living on their own.
Looks like normal suburban houses.
Gives the unsub privacy.
The differences are more striking than
the similarities. Different hair colors,
- different body shapes.
- What about his M.O.?
That's why we were invited in.
The abduction sites are pristine.
There's no DNA besides
the victims, there's no sign
of forced entry or a struggle.
The victims aren't reported missing
until 2 or 3 days
- after they're abducted.
- 2 or 3 days...
Women like this don't just vanish
without somebody noticing.
Yes. Which is why
I asked Garcia
to dig into their lives.
And when I took a look at their
online activity, I could easily see
- how the unsub is doing it.
- Social networking sites.
Facebook, Twitter. You name
an online life-sharing time suck,
The victims were on it.
If you look at each of their last posts,
They say kind of the same thing,
going out of town,
going on a business trip,
going on a vacation.
But when you look at the time
and date stamp of each of these,
cue the twilight zone music,
'cause they were all posted
the morning after each of them
went missing.
- The unsub posted them.
- Social networks are an easy way
For an unsub to target his victims.
These women were especially open.
They posted everything
they were having for dinner to
where they were going on dates.
So this unsub friends his victims
And then uses that
as a cover once he takes them.
That means he can hack into their
accounts. He's excellent with computers.
Definitely profiles as patient
and organized. He's obsessive enough
to remove all forensic details,
but also patient enough
to wait 2 months before abductions.
He can afford to be.
He gets 3 days
to do whatever he wants
to these women.
That means we need to assume
these women are already dead.
The question is what he does
while he has them.
Criminal Team
http://experts.heberg-forum.net/
"The single biggest problem
with communication
"is the illusion
that it has taken place.
George Bernard Shaw.
So if this unsub is using social
networks to find his victims,
can't we use that to find him?
If these women each had 100 friends
following them, then the unsub
would pop up on each of their lists,
right?
The Detective in charge,
John Fordham, he looked into
their groups. Everyone checked out.
Social networking sites are
surprisingly insecure. Facebook recently
tried to update
all privacy settings, and in doing so,
they made everybody's profiles viewable.
Can somebody explain to me
the appeal of these sites?
"Eating Sushi tonight. Yum."
"Boss is keeping me late at work."
Whose life is so important that we'd be
interested in this kind of detail?
I guess that's the running joke,
right?
I mean, nobody is.
But we'd all like to believe
there's actually an audience out there
that wants to follow our every move.
Some sites actually
have a GPS feature built in.
You can tell exactly where someone
is every time they post a new comment.
This is telling us how
he's finding them,
But it's not telling us how
he's getting into their houses.
At the very least, I believe that
he has copies of their keys.
Dorris Archer
had a home security system installed,
but the disable code was entered
at 1:56 A.M. So he knew that, too.
He also found a way to deal
with her dog. A German Shepherd
she adopted from the pound last year
went missing the night that she did.
So this guy's gotta be in
and out of the house
well before the night
of the disappearance.
He comes up with some ruse,
talks his way inside,
then once he's familiar enough with
the house, he knows he can come back
and kidnap them
without disturbing anything.
What about the people who come into your
house that you don't consider a threat?
Home repair guys, dog-walkers.
Detective Fordham
looked into that, too.
No one even came close
to being a killer.
Morgan and Prentiss,
start with the last abduction sites.
See if anything point to his M.O.
Dave, you, Reid, and JJ
go back over the women's lives.
Start with their friends
on the social networking sites.
If this is how the unsub
is finding them, Maybe
they're connected to him
without even realizing it.
Detective Fordham.
- Agent Jareau?
- Yeah.
These are SSA Hotcher, Rossi,
and Dr. Spencer Reid.
Thank you for coming.
We can really use your help.
Did you find anyone willing
to talk to us about the victims?
The problem wasn't who to bring in.
It was who not to.
The man we're looking for
might have found your daughter
through her social networks.
Did Paula mention
anyone new in her life?
- No.
- No one who started following her
as a friend,
someone she didn't recognize?
I don't really know how those work.
Someone sent me an email
Congratulating me
on Paula's promotion.
I didn't even know.
And when I asked her,
she said,
"Mom, I put that on my wall last week."
She was gone 2 days later.
Samantha was rigorous
about keeping her status updated.
She's obsessed with those sites.
So I'm assuming she knew
who followed her, then?
God, no.
She had over 1,000 friends.
- Why so many?
- We both worked in real estate.
She saw it as the perfect way
to promote herself.
Even though she told
all those people
what she was doing,
she didn't know who was following her?
You ever have so much email,
you feeling like you're drowning in it?
Actually, I don't have email.
Seriously?
Then let me break it down for you.
These websites are like email
on crack.
It's impossible to keep up
with everybody.
We just have a few more questions
about your girlfriend's disappearance.
Did Dorris ever mention
letting someone in her home?
Like who?
We're just trying to figure out
who would know
the code to her home security.
It must have been someone
she trusted with the combination.
No.
She was smart.
She took precautions.
That's the whole reason
she got Bruno.
- Bruno, the dog. So he was a guard dog?
- Yeah.
She trained him for like 6 weeks.
I know these are hard to look at,
but do you see anything different?
Something he may have done
to get himself inside.
This isn't right.
- What's that?
- The photographs.
This is when we first started dating. The
one on the right should be on the left.
. And she wouldn't have rearranged
them herself?
No.
She arranged them
a certain way to tell a story.
It was how we fell in love.
OK, JJ, I got it.
You see it?
Actually, yeah.
Looks like he did try to hang something
on the wall.
There's even
a little residue left over.
Let me call you back.
- What do you got?
- I got one up here, too.
What would he try to hang
on that part of the wall?
From here,
I have an unobstructed view
of the second floor and down the stairs.
It's the same thing down here.
You can see the entire entrance.
Cameras.
He put up cameras.
We think this is what he's using
to spy on his victims.
They're small, they're cheap,
and they're easily hidden,
behind photos, books, or plants.
The footage they record
can then be transmitted anywhere.
Website of your choice,
even your cell phone.
He can toggle between cameras to see
everything that's happening in the house.
You found 5 of these
at different points in the house?
Upstairs, downstairs,
bedroom, even the bath.
A ruse gets him in the door,
but it doesn't buy him enough time
- to put up 5 of these.
- Right. That's why we think
he starts with one camera facing
the front door.
That tells him when it's safe to enter
the house, when she comes and goes,
when the dog-walker comes, and what
the combination to the house is.
It fits his M.O.
It he learned their every detail
on social networks,
he will be just as obsessive
in his surveillance.
And once he learns their routine,
all he has to do Is pick the lock,
put up the rest of the cameras, he got
their whole life at his fingertips.
What does he do with the video?
Maybe he keeps them?
If he's a voyeur, yes.
Voyeurs are rarely violent.
Their excitement comes from spying
without the object
knowing they're being watched.
And by abducting his victims,
He's removing the outlet
of his sexual release. Reid is right.
So he must have some other
agenda with these cameras.
He might be sharing the
footage with other people.
We need to have Garcia dig into
surveillance In illegal video websites.
I'm going to take
this with us. Why?
We originally profiled there
wasn't any facial similarity
Between the victims,
but I'm not so sure that's true.
I want to compare Dorris'
picture with the other victims.
These videos the unsub took,
it looks like
One of them he posted online,
which may help me nab him.
If he puts it on the Web can't you track
that back directly to his computer?
Normally, yes. Normally,
in like in 17 seconds
I can get you the network he's using,
Get a physical address of his modem,
And presto change-o,
no more bad guy,
But this unsub is a creepy
computer aficionado.
Do you guys know what
a proxy server is?
It's an Internet relay.
Precisely. Kids use them to
get around blocked sites.
Now, usually one proxy is plenty,
But this piece of work is
using dozens of proxy servers.
He's bounced his signal
off of China, north Korea,
Russia, South Africa...
Garcia, can you trace
him back to Boise?
Of course I can,
and that's what I'm doing?
Time is the unfortunate
ingredient I need, though.
This just in.
Looks like one of the proxy
servers archived what
he was streaming on the night of
Dorris archer's disappearance.
Can we see it?
Pulling it up now.
Well, Prentiss and Morgan were right.
He knows the house.
And the dog knows him.
please don't hurt that doggie.
How many trips inside the
house would that take?
A dozen?
See that? The camera's attached to him.
It's his point of view.
So he can relive it
over and over again.
Ok, can someone tell
me when this is over?
Please.
Not yet.
He's tender to her.
She means more to him as a
corpse than as a living person.
Garcia, we need to find the unsub's
network. Even if it's a rough area,
it'll help narrow the
geographic profile.
Sir, that's totally
what I'm trying to figure out.
there is something else kind of huge
you need to know about. Do you see..
...this line of code there?
Yeah, what about them?
It allows the user admin,
and in this case, the unsub,
To set up a chat room.
People were watching this
on the night of the murder.
We thought he was posting these
after the fact. He's not.
He wants people to
experience it with him.
He wants an audience.
He has fans.
Can you freeze that?
He's acknowledging the camera.
Tip of the hat to his fans.
He knows they're watching.
Classic narcissistic behavior.
He's performing for his audience.
We know the m.O.
The question is how.
What kind of job gives him
access to the victims' houses?
It has to be network and I.T.S, the guy
you let in to hook up your Internet.
Gets him in their house
and on their computers.
I went through all the women's
Internet service providers
With a fine-tooth comb.
They all used different companies
And no overlap with sales reps.
What about onsite tech support?
clean as a whistle.
They all had alibis with
no criminal records.
What I don't understand is,
Why does he take the bodies
with him after they're dead?
it'd be one thing if he took
them while they were still alive,
But he's accomplished his task.
He murders them and he
completes the performance.
So why take the risk of
carrying a corpse to your car?
Well, there must be
some postmortem behavior
Or signature or something
we're not seeing.
we're not seeing. Well, think about
that for a second.
He's sharing this murder
with a crowd of onlookers.
What could he be doing to
these bodies just for himself?
Hey, guys.
Garcia's got something for us.
Go ahead, baby girl.
Ok, friends,
I have some good news,
But first, here is
the thing that sucks.
I located the network the
unsub is using in Boise,
And it is the
victims' own wireless.
So does he hack in before
he starts with the murders?
Hacking is obscenely
time-consuming.
I just make it look easy because
I'm a genius. But he's not me.
So my guess is that he's got
to lurk around their network
For at least a couple of days
to a week before he kills them.
That's pretty
brilliant on his part.
he knows when we
follow his online paper trail
That it'll lead us right
back to the murder site.
What's the good news?
Hackers are very loyal to
their spoofing techniques,
And if they think no one's watching,
hey'll  use the same roads over and over
Ok, so if he goes through Russia,
China, and north Korea again...
I have flagged those servers, And if
he uses them in the same order,
I will catch him so fast.
That's only going to help us
if he commits another murder.
Yes, that's also true.
Excuse me.
Garcia, if he does
stream this again,
How much time will you
need to find the network?
that's hard to guess with all the
international pinging. I--
Ballpark.
7 minutes?
That's not fast enough.
He's in and out of the house in 5.
I'm going to have
to trim my time down, then.
Garcia, get it done. JJ,
we need to call a press conference.
Now that we know how
he's killing these women,
We need to get it out there.
all right, I'll prescreen
the journalists I call on,
Hope we don't get anything
out of left field.
Good.
I know what connects the victims.
I was staring at
pictures of the victims
And I knew there was a
pattern connecting them,
But I couldn't tell what it was until
I broke it down mathematically.
Why are we so drawn
to celebrity faces?
Because there's a
symmetry to their beauty--
The eyes, the ears, the ratio
of the forehead to the chin.
The more balanced they are, the more
appealing they are to our eye.
These women aren't
celebrities, though.
No, but there are
similarities between them,
And it wasn't until I
scanned their pictures
And got it to the guys at Quantico
that I had a full breakdown.
All right, strip away eye color,
hair color, and skin tone,
And what are we left
with geometrically?
They're all slightly dystopic.
The left eye is slightly lower than
the right eye on all the victims.
All the noses are narrow.
The forehead has the same Ridge.
He might not even be aware
that he sees it in them.
There have been studies that suggest
that we pick our spouses subconsciously
Based on a facial symmetry
that we recognize.
So consciously or unconsciously,
When he recognizes it,
he has to destroy it.
Which means he only has interest in the
bodies as they relate back to him
Maybe...
They're a reflection.
Remember what he did at
the end of the video?
He wiped the tear away.
Another act of compassion
he's not capable of.
His narcissism
prevents him from that.
In the Greek myth,
narcissus was so self-absorbed
That he fell in love with his
own reflection in the water.
Exactly. He finds women
with the same face,
He strangles them, and then
stares at them after they've died.
But whose image
does he really see?
His own.
Thank you.
Most of us take the
Internet for granted.
We forget about
texts that we share
Or updates we put
on social networks.
But the Internet never forgets.
Once it's out there,
it's out there forever.
Now, we all know about the horrific
deaths that get shown on the Web.
The murder of a journalist.
The stoning of an Iranian dissident.
Those murders are immortal.
And this unsub craves
that same immortality.
He recognizes his face on theirs
And he kills them
as a way of saying,
"This is what I look like."
We think this also informs his
compulsion To take the bodies with him
He takes them to a
secondary location
Where we believe
he preserves them,
So that every time he looks at them,
He sees his own ego reflected.
Fortunately for us, this means we have
a good idea of what he looks like.
Based on the shape of
the victims' faces,
We have a rough composite sketch.
This unsub is an expert with
computers and home networks.
So look into criminal records of men
with extensive computer training.
We know you've already looked into
the victims' computer I.T. Settings,
So we'd like to expand the search.
Look into electronic stores,
Computer distributors, I.T.
Departments where the women worked.
We overuse the term
narcissistic in our culture,
But we're going back to the
psychological definition.
Every aspect of this man's life
Has been constructed around
an inflated sense of self.
Unsubs like this are
particularly vulnerable
To what's called
narcissistic injury.
If his self-worth is attacked
or damaged, he will lash out.
So, if you find this unsub,
do not challenge him publicly.
Say you just want to talk him, See if
he knows anything about the
the brilliant mastermind
Who's stalking these women.
Under no circumstances
should you denigrate him.
As difficult as it is,
we need to talk up his exploits
As if we respected him.
Searching for wireless
server found kitgirl29
This is a sketch of the
man we're looking for.
He is a white male,
Roughly 5'10".
He's highly skilled with
computers and networks.
We encourage everyone to
monitor the information
they post about themselves
On social networks.
Do not document the
details of your day.
Don't post pictures of yourself,
friends, or family.
All right, we'll take
some questions. Yeah?
How did the FBI generate this sketch
if there were no eyewitnesses?
It's a approximation based
on a video we recovered.
Ok, yeah, what's your question?
Can you comment on the rumor he
has some sort of facial
symmetry with his victims?
Does he look like them?
Right now the Boise police are
pursuing several theories.
That's not a no.
Why would he target
women who look like him?
It's too soon to speculate on how
or why he chooses his victims.
Well, what should people
do to protect themselves,
change their face?
No, just update
your online security
And be vigilant
about what you post.
All right, we're
done with questions.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hotch.
Somebody leaked our profile.
The press started asking
questions about facial symmetry.
It must have been one
of your officers.
Look, my guys were checking their
cell phones, but that's just habit now.
All right, I can talk to
the press independently,
I can keep this off
the 10:00 news, but--
I know. It went out live.
Well, what are the
chances he didn't see it?
Not good.
Oh, your crafty little sicko.
Sir, it's fantastic you called.
I just figured out--
How are you doing on
pinning down the networks?
Ok, that's what I'm
trying to tell you.
Remember how I said he was spoofing
his signal off different servers?
Well, it turns out some of those
are a decoy meant to waste my time.
So does that mean you
can find him faster?
Totally. Totally. I can write a program
that filters out the decoys--
Oh, crap.
Is that him?
Yeah. Uh...
Ok. It looks like I'm gonna
have to filter this on the fly.
Can you send us the feed?
I think I can intercept
it in Ukraine.
He's going live.
Look at the way he's moving.
He's not slow and deliberate.
This guy's pissed.
All right, what do we see?
Determining markers.
A one-story cottage.
It could be anywhere.
Is there a number on the house?
No, and he's already at the door.
Garcia.
He's using twice as
many proxy servers.
Wait. This window here on the bottom-
is that the chat room?
There she is.
He's in the house, guys.
He's completely changed his m.O.
It is way too early.
There's too much light.
What happened?
Someone asked the wrong question
at the press conference.
Oh, my God, turn around.
Just turn around.
Maybe she can fend him off.
New kitchen appliances.
Can we track them through work orders?
He'll be gone by then.
Garcia, give us something.
I'm stateside now.
I'm almost to Idaho.
You're not gonna make it.
I just need more time.
Yes, I will. I will. I--
Forget the unsub. Can you run
a trace on everybody in the chat room?
I can't do both, sir.
Let me do this.
Garcia, tag the viewers.
That's an order.
Baby girl, it's gonna be OK.
No, no, it's not. It's bad enough
That there's been so
much death around me,
But this guy is all up in my turf,
And he's really good at what he
does for really awful reasons.
That's why you're gonna
find the perverts
That watched it happen in that chat
room, and we'll nail them to the wall
And they're gonna
give up the unsub.
No, no, that is not good enough.
I want to watch him suffer.
I want to watch him bleed.
Oh, God, I just scared myself.
Good. That's a good thing.
Because if there's one thing
I've learned the hard way
Is the last person you want to
tick off is miss Penelope Garcia.
Ohh...That's a compliment, right?
Yes, it is.
We will beat this guy.
Believe that.
Now, I'll call you when
we've got something. Ok.
Her name was Allison Kittridge, 29.
This was her first house.
All right, so this unsub accelerated
his timetable and his m.O.
He was moving faster
because he was angry.
Yeah. The press conference told him
something about himself he didn't like,
So he rushed. Which
means he made a mistake.
Now, what was it?
Well, it wasn't the cameras.
He remembered to
take those with him.
It wasn't the body.
He took that with him, too.
Hey, did, uh, Garcia find anything
unusual with Allison's wireless?
No. Records show that it was
a basic DSL installation.
Hey, Prentiss.
Yeah. Help me move this table.
What do you got?
You see this line right here?
Yeah.
This is what brings the Internet
from the street into the house.
Ok. So? This isn't DSL.
It's not?
It's a fiber-optic cable.
Completely different
type of connection.
We just found his mistake.
If there's already an Internet
connection in the house,
Why does he bring his own with him?
Is it the upload speed?
Fiber-optic allows him to
stream large amounts of video.
And maintain a chat room.
That's dozens of computers
connected to him at once.
He'd need a lot of bandwidth
for something like that.
We checked all the ISPs.
Why didn't he turn up?
I get mail, phone calls,
people knock on my door all the time
To see if I want to upgrade my
Internet. Yeah, I get them, too.
And they'll offer to come
inside and demonstrate
How much faster
their connection is.
You think that's the ruse
that gets him in the door?
It makes sense.
During his demonstration, he would
have access to his victims' computers.
On his way out,
he asks for a glass of water,
A distraction, something to buy enough
time to plant that first camera.
We need to find out what
company owns this cable.
Detective Fordham's
already hunting that down,
And there's an I.D. Number on it,
so it shouldn't take long.
We'll have JJ and Reid follow up.
I need you two to track down
who was in the chat room.
Garcia finished her sweep?
Yeah. Most were international.
3 were local.
I bet one of them knows the unsub.
FBI.
We have a warrant.
Help you gentlemen?
Austin Chapman?
Yeah, that's me.
FBI.
We need talk to you about a
video you watched last night.
I'm sorry. What video?
This is a warrant for all the
computers in your possession.
You're under arrest for
accessory to murder.
Accessory?
Watching a murder happen online
and doing nothing
about it Is a felony.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
What murder?
Yes, this is our cable.
Mrs. Hightower,
we went over your records,
And it turns out that
none of the 4 victims
Signed up with your service.
4? God, those poor women.
We think it's an employee
using your cable as a ruse
To get into the house.
Can you think of any--
Mac Jones.
Uh, he worked on one of our trucks
As we laid the fiber in
with the regular phone line.
And you're certain that it's him?
We caught him hoarding it.
He said it was for a home project.
Until we got angry phone calls
that he was going door to door
Offering free fiber-optic
installation.
We fired him on the spot.
We need his information.
Absolutely.
Ladies and gentlemen,
meet Mac Jones.
That isn't the I.D.
We got from the phone company.
That's because last year Mr.
Jones had his identity stolen.
The unsub took his license
and his credit card,
Used them for 2 weeks,
and then moved on.
I can't tell you who the
unsub is pretending to be now,
But since a picture's worth
a thousand databases,
I can tell you who he was.
Robert Johnson, 3-time loser,
Arrested for possession
of torture videos.
Spent some time in a halfway
house before he disappeared.
I found a blog of his online.
Here's a quote--
"Next time you won't
be able to stop me."
That's his narcissism again.
Furious that he got caught and
he remakes himself as a killer.
It allows him to free the
impulses that were always there.
Garcia, is there a pattern to
the identities that he steals?
No. He's really
disciplined about it.
Once he burns through an identity,
he never uses the same one again.
You know how I describe some
suspects as being off the grid?
This guy is totally the opposite.
He's all over the grid.
He's manipulating the grid.
And he never stays in
one place for very long.
So how do we find
out who he is now?
I don't think we're going to.
The man known as Robert
Johnson is in the wind.
If he's this flexible with his name,
his real name, forget it.
But there's another
way we can find him.
Which is?
His online name,
His hacker handle.
That's the name
that matters to him.
Wait. Wouldn't he have
hundreds of those, too?
Most definitely. But remember
how I said hackers are loyal?
They stick to certain names.
That's how you identify
yourself to other hackers.
That's how the FBI caught me.
So if we find the handle...
I'll get you the unsub. I promise.
Look, I wish I could
help you find
the guy posting these videos,
But I never visited that website,
man. Right.
Maybe somebody broke into
my computer or something.
See, Scott, we think it was you.
And we found some pretty
interesting movies
in your hard drive To
back up our theory.