Lorraine.
- There you are.
- I'm sorry that I'm late.
I was about to call you.
I should know better than
to keep a beautiful woman waiting.
Oh, laying it on thick, aren't you?
I've been looking
forward to this.
- Got a prospectus for you.
- Food first.
Do you like crab louie?
- I do.
- It is so good here.
They use stone crab fresh
from the bay.
The filet is wonderful
if you're in the mood for meat,
or the Osso Bucco.
Henry.
Hello.
Sorry.
Um...my head is still at work,
making sure I deposited
a check for a client.
Well, I'm a client, too.
And you're on my time now.
- You have my full attention.
- I better.
I have something you want.
This is all you have on him?
We have the back of his head
from a few CCTV angles,
nothing that helps.
He's careful to avoid
being seen on camera.
Out of all my cases, this guy was
never flagged as top priority, but...
this murder changes everything.
You were right to call us.
We'll explain why.
Everyone,
this is agent Russell Goldman
from the San Diego White Collar Team.
You've already met agent Hotchner.
These are agents Rossi,
Morgan, Prentiss, and Reid.
A pleasure.
- So we're working a white collar case?
- Not exactly.
I've been following
a con artist for 5 years.
Two nights ago,
I think he killed someone.
Carla Marshall of Miami was
found dead in her home.
Asphyxiation by strangulation.
She also had trauma wounds to the head.
Why do we think
the con man killed her?
Last week Carla contacted
a fraud website to report a scam.
The complaint ended up
on Goldman's desk.
We spoke on the phone at length.
Her story matched my guy to the "T."
She planned on confronting
him that night.
I told her to cease
all communications
and wait for me, I'd fly
to Miami and set up a sting.
But that never happened.
Do you have physical evidence
confirming it's your guy?
No, but for her to be murdered
the night that we spoke,
I don't think it was a coincidence.
There was no sign of forced entry,
theft, or sexual assault.
And judging from the M.O.,
the motive was personal.
- What's his hustle?
- Investment fraud.
Basically, he's a smaller madoff.
To give you an idea
of how convincing he is,
this is a sampling
of his work going back 14 years.
He's prolific.
He's scammed hundreds
of thousands of dollars from people,
but he's never been violent before.
Con men usually don't murder,
but when they do,
it's to conceal their crimes.
- Con man's a nice name for these guys.
- They profile as psychopaths.
They see their cons as theater
and themselves as a sort
of puppeteer.
They have to have absolute
control over their victims and their cons.
Maybe that's why he starting killing,
because he lost control?
The question is,
how out of control is he?
If he's spiraling, he's a danger
to everyone around him.
And because he's so charming,
the victims never see it coming.
Who do I make it out to?
Grant Dale Investments, Inc.
Hunter Portland advisors,
incorporated.
Henry Moffet Hedge funds,
Henry Moffet...
Hedge funds...
Inc.
This is a lot of money.
It'll be the best decision
of your life.
Criminal Team
http://experts.heberg-forum.net/
"If I am what I have,
"and if I lose what I have,
who, then, am I?"
German psychologist Erich Fromm.
I can't believe
you guys have your own jet.
We take turns piloting.
You want to give her a try?
Really?
No.
What kind of forensic countermeasures
does he use to hide his trail?
Fake I.D.S, disposable phones, prepaid
credit cards, foreign bank accounts.
You can't track
his accounts overseas?
We can, but it takes months
to get the records,
and it only takes him seconds
to transfer money again and again.
By the time you figure out it's
in the Bahamas, he's already moved
- it to Switzerland or somewhere else.
- I've always been too far behind him.
Well, we're a lot closer
now because of Carla.
What made her suspicious
in the first place?
She needed to get her father
into a retirement home,
and when she called this guy
Grant Dale to free up her money,
he never returned her phone calls.
A con man's first instinct
is flight, not fight.
What makes him kill, though,
isn't financial, it's psychological.
That's what we need to concentrate on.
Why Carla and why now?
Morgan and Prentiss,
go to her house.
Agent Goldman,
why don't you join them.
I sent his case files
to the field office.
Shouldn't I stay with you
and help you sift through them?
I'd like to go through
them independently, come up
with our own theories,
see if any behavioral patterns
emerge that'll help us
get ahead of him.
Agent Goldman's files are
in that room down the hall.
Thank you.
- Let me know if you need anything.
- Thank you.
You're kidding me.
We have to go through all of this?
White Collar cases often
come down to a paper trail.
Maybe it won't be so bad.
I mean, at least it's well organized.
That's his job.
He sits at a desk all day
and accumulates paper evidence.
OK. Dave, you work victimology.
Reid, see if you can find anything
in his travel patterns. JJ, let's get
a timeline up on the board.
She was a real estate agent.
She was doing well for herself
until William came into her life.
Why do you call him that?
He introduced himself as Bill, Billy,
or Will several times in his early cons.
My guess is that his real name
may be some form of William.
So most of his victims
were very wealthy, right?
You should see some
of their mansions.
Well, I'm looking around this house
and it's nice, but no mansion.
She didn't invest as much
as his other clients either.
I wonder why he targeted her.
She may have been useful
to him in some other way.
Hey, Goldman. What was the alias
he was using with Carla?
- Grant Dale.
- Come check this out.
He set up a website.
Why didn't the detectives
find this before?
The locals wouldn't know
to look for it.
Well, it's only one page.
Generic investment information.
I mean, there's no contacts,
there's no picture of himself.
No, just photos
of nice cars and houses.
So he's selling the fantasy
of success.
His web design is pretty basic.
I mean, it's like a standard template.
It would be fairly easy to set up.
Maybe he created others.
I'm gonna call Garcia.
Hey, baby girl, it's me.
You're on speaker.
Sug, I don't care who hears it.
It's always been you.
Listen, I just emailed you a link.
Got it.
- It's the unsub's website.
- Do you want me to find out how he paid
for his hosting services,
track him down that way?
We'll run into the same
backstopping trail.
- You are right. That's untraceable.
- All right, we'll forget that.
Can you do a search for websites
containing the same content?
And searching... and searching...
there are 1, 2... 9 identical
websites, same written content,
same pictures,
just different names.
These are all new aliases.
And he's never had 10 at once.
This is all new.
I'm Henry Moffet.
You lied to me about everything.
- What are you talking about?
- Your name is not Grant Dale.
God, why are you doing this to me?
- Just calm down. Listen to me.
- No, just leave.
- You're not giving me a chance to explain.
- Leave or I'll call the police!
Grant...
I'm Henry Moffet.
Henry Moffet.
The CIA assigns an agent
2 or 3 aliases at most.
Any more than that,and it's difficult
to keep the names straight.
This guy's juggling 10.
Being all these people, that's gotta
start fracturing him somehow.
If his memory is strained,
it could be causing him to lose control.
We have the current aliases. We just
need to know who the clients are.
Got Carla's phone records.
She made several calls
to an unknown number the night
she died. I tracked the number.
It was a disposable phone
that hasn't been used since.
That's gotta be the unsub's number.
He tossed it after he killed her.
Over the past few months,
she routinely called this number
really late at night.
- How late?
- Like bedtime late.
You don't do business with your
investment manager at bedtime.
So, when are we gonna do this again?
My husband's coming home, so...
I won't see you for a while.
I'll miss you...
you lied to me Grant.
About everything.
Leave or I'll call the police!
Grant, are you ok?
Henry, are you ok?
I'm gonna miss you, too.
So Carla never mentioned anything
about an affair with him?
No, but it's always been a challenge with
fraud victims to be totally forthcoming.
They're so embarrassed about being
duped, they don't tell you everything.
Detective Goldman.
We'd like to compare notes.
Shoot.
I'm looking at the victimology.
We say affinity groups.
Same thing.
It refers to victims
with shared interests.
Ok. We're in your world,
we'll use your terms.
Your files point to specific
affinity groups he targeted
in the first few cities.
- Does this look accurate to you?
- Yes, it does.
Once he got beyond San Diego,
his victims are all over the place.
No shared interests.
I came to the same conclusions.
So he stopped using affinity groups
and found his victims somewhere else.
Where, I don't know.
That's where we start.
I'm Randy Summerland.
Make us some money, ok?
I can do that.
Now, how do I spell
your name, again?
M-o-f-f-e-t.
Henry Moffet Hedge funds,
incorporated.
Who is Henry Moffet?
who is Henry Moffet?
It's my partner.
You didn't mention anything
about a partner.
I didn't?
And this isn't who I made
the check out to last time.
He's been my partner for years.
Then why am I making
the check out to him?
There's a simple explanation.
So, the unsub
and the vic are having drinks.
The vic has a checkbook and pen out,
check's dated, but that's it.
The unsub got that close
to getting his money,
somehow failed, and then did this.
And this is overkill.
He bashed his head in.
He's completely unhinged
and devolving fast.
Only he doesn't know that.
He's still trying to go to work
and he doesn't know he's in danger
of losing it at any minute.
Like a functioning alcoholic.
The unsub channels all
of his energy into these cons,
and when the con falls apart,
this is how he handles it.
How long have you known Randy?
We spent a lot of time with him
in the last couple of months.
He was helping us invest.
How much money did you give to him?
He just kept saying we needed
to be aggressive in this market.
this is all my fault.
What do you mean?
I met randy.
I brought this man into our lives.
Mrs. Mckelson,
is there anything more
to your relationship with Randy?
We're gonna find out eventually.
Find out what?
Randy wasn't who he said he was.
Randy wasn't even his real name.
We think this man is using
his looks and his charm
to target women.
So there's others.
I laid in bed next to the man
who killed my husband.
Did they have transgressions?
She's pretty beat up over it.
Randy, who is Henry Moffet?
Daddy?
You're home!
Good morning, buddy.
Let me look at you.
You're a handsome devil,
you know that?
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
When did you get in?
Just now.
How was your trip?
It didn't really pan out.
Sorry. What happened?
Can we, uh, talk about this after
J.D. goes to school?
I want pancakes.
Really? You do?
Well, then pancakes you shall have.
You're not enjoying this, are you?
I like a good paper trail.
I find it meditative.
Is it really that hard for you
to be normal just one time?
He just burned another alias.
You know, if this guy's on a mission
to eliminate all these aliases,
he's gonna systematically
assassinate his victims.
Carla lived in Miami.
This victim, frank Mckelson,
lived north in Ft. Lauderdale.
The victims could be
anywhere in south Florida.
If he's working harder
because of the economy,
it makes sense that he would
expand his operating zone.
Prentiss and Rossi are on their way back.
We need to give the profile.
There's something else
about San Diego.
I noticed in his earlier crimes
he only stays in each city
an average of 14 to 18 months.
Then he's in San Diego
for 3 1/2 years
and then never in the same city
for that long again.
All right, so what is it about
San Diego that made him stay longer?
Keep following that, Reid.
See where it takes us.
Are you sure?
I wouldn't be doing this
if we didn't have to.
J.D. was just starting
to make new friends.
What do you want me to do?
The money has dried up here.
Maybe you could take a break,
spend more time with J.D.
Ok, then how am I supposed
to raise a family
if I don't have enough clients?
Baby, I hate seeing
you so stressed out.
All right, now,
this economy is killing me.
I can get a job, too.
No. No, I can take care
of us myself.
Well, we have to figure something out,
because I don't want to move again.
Listen, we are moving to boston.
End of discussion.
Honey, what happened?
Now start packing.
This unsub
is a white collar con man
who embodies what behaviorists
call the dark triad...
narcissism,
machiavellianism,
and aberrant self-promotion.
What that means is that everything
revolves around this guy.
He manipulates and exploits
others using dishonest tactics,
and he's become
a menace to society.
I'm hunter Portland.
He's also what we call
a casanova con man.
He seduces women
to get to their money.
It's standard behavior for him to
have casual sex with multiple partners
and then use that as a weapon
to accomplish his goals.
We have his sketch.
And here on the board
are his aliases.
He frequents high-end venues...
country clubs, hotel bars,
and membership-only establishments.
And notify the banks.
He's constantly moving money,
opening and closing bank accounts.
He's active in
Miami and Ft. Lauderdale,
but he could be in other
wealthy communities, too.
Look at places like boca raton
or coral gables.
He has too many aliases
in his head right now
and it's causing him
to fracture mentally.
And it's this loss of control
that triggers his violence and
makes him dangerous to be around.
And any additional stress will
make him more likely to attack.
I don't have to go this
long without seeing you.
I could fly to wherever you are.
You would just distract me.
We'd just be spending
all day in bed together.
My husband's gone for a week.
Why don't you stay tonight?
I... I can't, gorgeous.
I got to deposit your check in
the bank before the market closes.
Do you think that
we could be happy together?
I could leave my husband.
Slow down.
Hunter.
Hunter, not now.
I gotta...
I gotta take this.
Don't be mad at me,
but I want my check back.
I got another call.
Don't go anywhere.
Yes, I'm here.
I need you to pick up J.D.
from TOD's
and drop him off at piano.
No, I can't.
My car broke down.
Help me out here.
Fine.
Henry, I'm really sorry, I just...
I don't want to move forward.
Look, I can guarantee your money.
Why, what do you mean?
Well, I don't do this
for just anybody,
but since it's you, I can,
protect you from any risk.
I'll pick you up in a little bit
and we'll talk about it, ok?
Ok, Henry.
I need you to listen to me.
I'm pregnant.
It's yours.
Grant Dale.
Agent Jareau said
you have something.
I spoke to his victims. Before
San Diego, they described him
as driving exotic sports cars. After
San Diego, they described him as driving
larger sedans and SUVS.
Before San Diego,
he lived in condos,
referred to them as bachelor pads.
After San Diego, spoke of living
in gated communities
with large yards.
What forces a man to stay
put in one place for a while,
downgrade his car,
upgrade his house?
You think he has a family?
These are lifestyle changes
a new dad would make.
Why would he start a family?
Because he wants
to appear normal,
and a family does that
for a psychopath.
Wives usually serve a purpose,
as a caretaker or homemaker.
They value their offspring as
an extension of themselves
and it also feeds
their narcissistic ego.
These are interesting theories,
but how does this help us?
As a forensic countermeasure,
con men put everything
in their wives' names.
Bank accounts, cars, homes.
And if his wife isn't
complicit in his crimes,
she'll still be using her real name.
If we find the wife,
we can find the unsub.
Thank you, for the drink
and for guaranteeing my money.
It's all gonna work out.
I just got scared.
I understand.
You pressed the wrong button.
Dad?
Daddy?
Hey, that's me.
Can I talk to you about something?
Yeah, of course, buddy.
Do we have to move again?
I like it here.
You know, I'm really
disappointed in you.
Sorry.
I'm really disappointed because
you didn't say something sooner.
You know, if you want something in life
as a man, you need to ask for it.
Now, let that be a lesson.
So you really like
it here, huh, big guy?
Well, I think I may have found a way
for us to stay for a while.
Serious?
I just need to dump
my client list and start over.
So we can stay?
I'd do anything for you, kiddo.
What is that?
Just hang out here
for a sec, all right?
Watch your video.
What is it?
Spare tire came loose.
Don't worry.
I'm fixing it.
Massive blunt force trauma
to the head,
same as the others.
Does it make sense for him
to dump her like this?
He's killed 2 people in 2 days.
His fracturing is intensifying.
When a criminal devolves like this,
they're capable of anything.
JJ said a man reported
his wife missing last night.
Description matches the body.
Name's Lorraine Horton.
Do we know anything about
her investment history?
The team's looking
into it right now.
Ok, so he killed his first victim
in Miami and then left town,
came to Ft. Lauderdale,
killed his second victim here,
but he didn't leave
town for his third.
Is there a significance to him
staying in Ft. Lauderdale?
Guys, what if his family lives here?
That's why he's trying to
eliminate threats to himself here,
'cause this is his home where
he needs to protect his identity.
Hey, Garcia.
I feel like I've been
sent on a wild snipe hunt.
Do you have any idea how
many women in south Florida
lease luxury cars and rent mansions? I
will answer. Too many. That's how many.
Ok, narrow the search down
to Ft. Lauderdale only.
Look at women who moved
here 8 to 12 months ago,
see if any of them have any
history with san diego.
Ok. I'll call you back when
I find the elusive snipe creature.
This is gonna be good for us.
I don't understand.
I thought you would be happy.
Just yesterday you were hell-bent
on moving us immediately.
Yeah, and then you and J.D.
both said you wanted to stay,
so I found a way
to make it happen.
How?
I just did.
What is going on with you?
You know what?
I thought I was doing you a favor.
I don't have time for this.
Good afternoon.
I'm Stuart. You asked
for the bank manager?
Agents Rossi and Jareau, FBI.
We need some information
on a client named Lorraine Horton.
Is Ms. Horton ok?
Can you check her
recent banking activities,
see if there's anything unusual?
Maybe a check written
to a person's corporation.
I know she recently came
into more money.
Her mother passed.
They sold the house
and she got a pretty
good sum for it.
She sold a house?
Yes, sir.
Wasn't the first victim
in real estate?
We've been asking ourselves
how he finds his victims now.
We just found out Lorraine
got a large windfall
from selling her
mother's house.
Carla Marshall, the first
victim, was in real estate.
When you sell a house,
your property becomes public record.
Your name goes on these lists.
Lists compiled by lead brokers
and sold to the real
estate companies.
Hey, pen.
Man, it is raining
snipe all up in here.
Did you know that your boat
owners Frank and Dina Mckelson
sold a house in Hawaii
about 8 months ago?
Do any of them have a direct
connection to Carla Marshall?
Carla generated these letters
advertising the swanky
beachfront condos
her company sells...
stay with me...
Lorraine Horton, the lady who
was murdered this morning,
her address, along with
the mckelsons' address,
are buried in a spreadsheet
in Carla's laptop.
That's how the unsub
found his victims.
He used Carla to get her leads.
That's why he targeted her.
She gave him access to a list of people
with a large amount of liquid assets.
We need that list.
Already flying to you.
But that is not all, folks.
I think I may have
found the wife.
I did I search on women
who've lived in Ft. Lauderdale
for the last 8 to 12 months,
who rent houses and cars
and have a history in San Diego.
Came up with about
a dozen names, but...
ooh, la la, only one
of them works in real estate.
Who?
Her name's Rebecca Hodges.
She has a 9-year-old son,
John Davison Hodges,
born in San Diego,
father on birth certificate
listed as William Hodges. William.
I got the address
of the house she's renting, too.
Let's head over there.
Morgan, pull the son out of school.
JJ and Reid, go over the list
of potential victims.
If anybody knows the unsub,
send units to them.
Ok, so I'm gonna go deal
with this client.
Will you call me later?
Yeah, I will.
Did you forget something?
Are you a client of Bill's?
Who?
Don't do that.
I saw him leaving here.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You should leave.
I saw you with my husband.
Do you know we have a son?
His name is J.D.
You didn't know bill was married?
I didn't know his name was Bill.
Again, this is agent Jareau.
It's very important that you
call me back. Thank you.
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks so much.
I just confirmed another potential victim.
I sent a unit over.
I can't get a hold
of this one couple,
Hector and Brooke Sanchez.
Hurry up. Dad,
where are we going?
We're going to get mom.
It's a surprise.
What kind of surprise?
We're going to Boston.
But you said yesterday...
just get in the car, ok?
Hurry up.
Do you know you pick
your nails when you're anxious?
I've never been in a bureau
car chasing a killer before.
You ready to meet
William face to face?
It's about damn time.
Dad, where are you going?
Quiet. Just shut up
and let me think.
Daddy...
I'm sorry, kiddo.
I didn't mean to yell at you.
Where's mommy?
That's a good question.
That's him calling.
Well, don't answer it.
We need to talk.
I am pregnant.
It's his.
Oh, my god.
Come on, pick up.
Ok, we're going to, uh...
go hang out somewhere and wait
for mommy to call back, all right?
Ok.
What about that
one couple from earlier?
His office said
he's out of town.
I haven't been able
to get ahold of her yet.
- It's Morgan.
- Hey, Morgan.
Yeah, Reid, listen,
I'm at the son's school.
Principal says that J.D. Hodges
was pulled out
of class 45 minutes ago.
By who?
The unsub.
They're in the wind, kid.
He's gonna try
and leave with his family.
All right, thanks,
I'll let everyone know.
Garcia?
What up, JJ?
Can you find out
if Rebecca Hodges has a cell phone?
We want to try and track
where she is right now.
"Uno momento."
Something's weird.
What?
The wife has 2 cell
phones listed in her name.
One could be hers,
one could be his?
He put them both in her name.
Yeah, but they're both active
in the same quadrant right now.
Where?
Some posh Ft. Lauderdale neighborhood.
Wait a second.
A couple on our potential victims
list lives in the same area.
Hector and Brooke Sanchez.
That's the woman
I can't get ahold of.
Hotch.
Ok, got it, Reid.
Direct everyone
to the Sanchez house.
Thanks.
What's the wife doing
at a victim's house?
Were we wrong about her?
Do you think she's complicit?
I don't think so. If she was,
he'd use her in the con.
He told me his name
was hunter Portland.
How long have you been seeing him?
We vacationed in St. Croix together.
What? When?
Last month.
He said he was in Boston
on a business trip.
Brooke, you here?
You must think I'm an idiot.
It's not true.
How could you do this
to your family?
I provide everything for my family.
Were you just after my money
this whole time?
No. No, I told you I was
gonna take care of you.
All those times
you traveled for work...
are there other women?
God, what are you even doing here?!
Daddy?
I told you to wait in the car.
J.D., come here.
Please, just let him come here.
You think that
I would hurt my own son?
Well, you're obviously
capable of anything.
Please, Bill,
he doesn't need to see this.
How long did you think you were
gong to get away with this, hunter?
Bill, let's just leave. Just
stop talking, both of you!
Bill. Shut up!
We got a car down the street
and one in the driveway.
Both plates match the wife's name.
Remember,
there's a 9-year-old boy in there
and I wouldn't put it past
him to hurt his own family.
Or himself.
Ok, we'll take the back.
You ready?
Bill!
You really are
a son of a bitch, hunter.
Bill...
whatever!
Bill.
Let's just go.
Let's go!
Shut up!
Daddy!
Stop. No.
J.D.!
FBI. Put your hands in the air.
Oh, my god.
Please step back.
Bill, let him go.
Let the boy go to his mother
and put your hands up.
You must be tired,
keeping up with all these lies.
You don't need to do this anymore.
Let him go.
Bill, please let him go.
Daddy...
J.D...
go to your mom, ok?
Go to your mom.
Sweetie, come here.
Put your hands up.
Don't do that!
Take your hands out of your pockets!
Don't!
"What a tangled web we weave
when first we practice to deceive."
Sir Walter Scott.
Do you think
my husband did all this?
I'm afraid so.
The man I lived with for 10 years
was loving and gentle.
He isn't capable of this.
There's more about
him that we don't know.
You should be prepared.
You're going
to be interviewed in detail.
Right now I want
to take my son home.
Ok. I'll have someone drive you.
Mommy!
Mommy's here, baby.
You know your daddy loved you
more than anything, right?
I know.
So where do you want these?
I don't care.
Are you ok?
I thought he had a weapon.
Yeah. That was a justified shot.
Why did he do that?
He had a wife, a son.
A guy like that,
he likes his car,
his house, his lifestyle.
He knew he wasn't going
to do well in prison.
So he decided his own fate.
I never even found
out his real name.
Does it matter?