Run, you can make it!
Run! come on!
Next.
Uh, darrin call.
Oh, i don't have anything.
No, no, no.
i've got a refill left.
Could you just--
it's call.
Can you just
check that again?
I have one refill.
No, no, i'm sorry.
It's not--that ain't good.
That's not good.
that's not--it's just--
Are you ok?
Make it stop! just--
Make it--
I need to make it stop!
Mr. call--
Aren't you gonna help me?!
Here--yes, here.
i'm sorry.
Just please--
please stop. stop.
That's not it!
That is not it!
[groans]
Hey.
i just--
I just, uh--
hey.
Relax.
It's ok.
i just--
Uhh! uh!
Aah! god!
Uhh!
woman: oh, my god!
Oh, my god,
are you all right?
Look what you've done!
Uhh!
Please, somebody help him!
Aah!
[grunting]
Put the knife down, now.
Aah!
Uhh! oh!
Uhh!
[all groaning]
He's not in yet.
What?
You've been walking
past hotch's office
for an hour.
Emily's picking him up.
Hotch told me
he was cleared to drive.
He is.
She wants to do it.
What's going on?
He's only had a month off,
rossi.
Technically, 34 days.
And you think
that's long enough?
You don't? tell him.
No, thanks.
i like my job.
You like him more.
What if he's got ptsd?
He was evaluated.
Come on, rossi,
we wrote those questions.
Hotch knows exactly
how to answer them.
So what are you gonna do,
Pick apart
everything he does?
How long should he be gone?
a year? 2?
Every day that foyet
is out there, hotch loses,
And you know that.
You know what
that makes hotch?
Distracted.
Motivated.
Derek.
He's coming back
because he has to.
He needs to know
we've got his back.
He knows that.
Then we don't let him
forget it.
Reid: thanks.
Does it hurt?
It really only hurts
when i think about it,
Which is pretty much
all the time.
No, no, no.
What?
get away, you.
These are for hotch.
I get shot in the leg
and i don't get any cookies.
You know he's gonna hate
the attention.
It's cookies, not cake.
He's probably gonna pretend
like nothing happened, anyway.
Well, it doesn't mean
we have to.
I think maybe we should.
I don't roll that way.
I've been thinking about it?
The entire time
i've known hotch,
I don't think i've ever
seen him blink.
I know.
It's weird.
Classic alpha male behavior.
Do you think
he stared down foyet?
Maybe. if it would
save his life.
Do you think he stared
the whole time,
like with each stab?
I have no idea.
Is he ok?
I wouldn't be, but...
I'm a blinker.
Spence, there you are.
Grab your go bag.
what's going on?
Turn on the news.
Which one?
It doesn't matter.
Just after 8:00
this morning,
40-year-old darrin call,
A lifelong resident
of louisville,
Assaulted customers
at the pharmacy
On the corner of main
and truxton avenues.
Eyewitnesses saw him
walking east on main street
Minutes after the attack.
He has not been seen
since then.
We're going to louisville.
He was wearing
a blue shirt, jeans,
And a light-gray jacket.
Within the hour, the governor
has called in all sources
For a manhunt.
Despite these statewide efforts,
The suspect has eluded
law enforcement.
The body count is rising.
3 are confirmed dead--
[knock on door]
Including
an armed bank guard
Whose gun was used
in the attack.
Another 2 remain
in critical condition.
The assailant
is still out there.
We are going back
to eric jennings
Who's been talking
to residents of louisville--
[turns off tv]
Hey.
hey.
What do we know about
this case in kentucky?
Uh, there's no connection
between call and his victims.
Louisville p.d.'s
covered the city,
But there hasn't been
any sign of him
Since he left the pharmacy.
You check his house, family?
Locals are on it.
Start with
his most recent history.
Find the stressor.
Uh, don't move.
[setting alarm]
Ready?
Are you?
So our point person
in louisville
Is lieutenant
kevin mitchell.
Good morning.
Good to see you.
You, too.
You look well, sir.
thank you.
How long
do you have that?
I'm not really sure.
welcome back.
Thank you.
Any other attacks?
Um, no, not yet.
Call's proven
hard to track.
He's never had
a driver's license,
So he's most likely
still on foot.
Jj: or public
transportation.
He's not gonna take the bus.
His face is everywhere.
Hotch: has anyone
found a stressor?
He just lost his job.
He's worked at a factory
since 1990.
Made appliances
since forever and not
a single promotion.
That's a long time
to be bitter.
Reid: or he doesn't care.
Not if he's got
a family to feed.
Garcia: actually,
he's of the hermit variety.
As far as i can tell,
he's got no one.
No wife, no kids,
no parents.
Nothing to live for.
So why hasn't
he killed himself yet?
Sprees usually end
in suicide.
If he's got nothing
to live for,
why hasn't he ended it?
'cause he isn't finished yet.
We know he has displaced anger.
He took it out
on the first victim.
Well, the stock boy
represents someone.
we need to know who.
Is he military?
Negative.
Well, he's lashing out
for a reason.
This guy's got anger,
endless targets, and a gun,
And he's just getting started.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Hotch: emily dickinson wrote,
"one need not be a chamber
to be haunted.
"one need not be a house.
The brain has corridors
surpassing material place."
All right.
We've got checkpoints
at the state line
On both i-64 and i-65
And within a 20-mile
radius of downtown.
We think he's still on foot.
It's been just under
3 hours with an average
walking speed
Of 2.5 miles per hour,
which rounds up
To an approximate
8-mile radius.
Now, we've concentrated here.
First responders
started a hard-target search
Of businesses and residences
within that 8 miles.
You're gonna join 'em.
you know what he looks like.
Go find him.
We dug up all we could
on darrin call.
Even went to his apartment.
didn't find much.
We've got agents
over there now.
Don't worry,
we'll fill it in.
What's your strategy?
We try to figure out
where he's headed next.
Huh. you got a crystal ball?
Most spree killers are
outwardly aggressive.
We've studied
call's behavior,
and he's defensive.
Jj: first victim--stock boy.
Boy, there's nothing
defensive about that.
Actually, there is.
Call doesn't react
until he's touched.
And that's what set him off?
Happens every time.
Contact, then stab,
Contact, stab.
So you're saying he didn't
mean to hurt these people.
He didn't go in there
with a weapon.
Well, now he's got 2.
I just put his face
all over the news.
People are gonna stop him
themselves.
How soon can we have
a press conference?
The camera crews
are out front.
Great. let me call hotch.
Who's that?
Our supervisor. he's at
the crime scene already.
What is it about this kid?
Reid: that's what
we need to figure out.
Call's apartment
is 5 minutes from the pharmacy,
But there's no sign
That he came here
to wash off that blood.
How's he still
on the street,
looking like that?
Maybe he's not.
Garcia said he's got nobody.
where would he go?
Call gets up, he makes his bed.
We're sure
he wasn't military?
It looks like one neat aspect.
Maybe he was hospitalized.
i'll call garcia.
Then he's probably
got the same routine
every day.
Except today.
He finished his cereal,
walked to the pharmacy,
And killed 3 people.
Why?
Mr. call was always so quiet.
He's been coming here for years.
Morgan: had he ever had
a run-in with the stock boy?
John was new here.
i waved him over.
I didn't know what else to do.
no one else was helping.
He didn't turn violent
until you gave him
his prescription?
Well, it wasn't his.
You handed him a bag.
It was somebody else's.
I just wanted him
to calm down.
Jj's press conference
is in 5 minutes.
Hotch, we might have
something else here.
Why didn't you give him
his own medication?
Well, he didn't have
any refills left.
For what?
Uh, alprazolam.
But, uh, he used to be on
thiothixene.
He was on
an antipsychotic?
Well, that's why i wanted him
to calm down.
You said he used to be.
how long has he been
off of them?
At least a month.
And when were you
gonna tell us this?
He's armed,
he's delusional.
who's his doctor?
Uh...
I don't remember.
my computer.
Hotch: great.
I'm sorry.
great.
Excuse us.
Hotch.
Call jj and tell her
about the meds.
This is not her fault.
Morgan, he's in a psychotic
break. it changes everything.
You want to talk
about this?
No! i want to find him.
garcia,
He's been off his
antipsychotic for a month.
What else did you miss?
I'm sorry, sir. i didn't get
his medical records yet, so--
Well, find them.
find everything.
Yes...
Sir.
[groaning]
[rattling doorknob]
Excuse me.
[pounding on door]
I'm in a session!
I need the pills.
Darrin, what's wrong?
What happened?
He had a--a knife.
Who?
It's just like
in the nightmares. he--
[groaning]
He's doing it again.
He can't hurt you.
We talked about this.
You want to remember.
It's why you're off the pills.
You said i would get better.
You are.
Does it look like
i'm better?!
Darrin. darrin.
I gotta...make it stop.
Make it stop!
Just make it--make it...
darrin...
Calm down. that's it.
just look here.
Make it--make it--
Just breathe.
Take a breath.
Prentiss: he was unarmed.
he didn't mean to hurt anyone.
All he wanted
was his medication,
But he didn't get it.
He needs help.
Who's call's doctor?
State appointed psychiatrist
charles cipolla.
Hotch and morgan
are on their way.
Where's his office?
Camden and third.
cipolla's not picking up.
Gps says were 5 minutes away.
Ok, rossi, we're 5 out.
tell mitchell
to meet us there.
[grunts]
[telephone rings]
Darrin?
uhh! uhh!
[ring]
Uhh! no!
No! get it out!
darrin.
No!
Darrin!
get it out!
No, get it out!
Can't get it--
I can't get it out!
I can't--gotta--
I gotta get it out!
darrin--
Darrin, darrin, here. here.
Darrin! darrin, here.
Take my shirt.
just take it.
There you go,
that's good.
No! don't touch him!
No! oh, my god!
No! darrin, no! oh, my god!
[siren]
[tires screeching]
All right, get out of here
and check the perimeter.
do it now.
We're too late.
Hotch!
He cleaned up,
changed his clothes,
Could have dyed his hair
for all i know.
Call's suffering from
a psychotic break.
He's not dodging us
on purpose.
Oh, come on.
Trust me.
If he was psychotic,
Why would his doctor
take him off the drugs?
Call has no history
of violent behavior.
Cipolla couldn't predict
that would happen.
Look at this place.
Yeah, it's a mess.
no, it's more than that.
Call was looking for something.
Yeah, the drugs.
Doctor doesn't keep
the drugs here.
Scrip pad is still
on his desk.
My guess is he came here
for help.
His file's missing.
[cell phone rings]
Yeah, baby girl,
what's going on?
Where's hotch?
he's not answering.
He's outside.
he's all right.
Are you sure?
Yeah. what's up?
A mystery.
Come on,
not today, garcia.
I know. here's the deal.
When i missed
the antipsychotics--
Listen to me.
that was not your fault.
You are ever my champion, sugar,
But i believe it was.
Anyway, when i did that,
i went back to the beginning
For call, except there is
no beginning.
Wait a minute.
Rossi.
Say that again.
What are you
talking about?
Darrin call didn't exist
like from 1969 to 1975.
There's no birth certificate,
no social security,
No identity, nothing,
until he was 6 years old.
Was he abandoned?
My least 3 favorite words
strung together--
I don't know.
My guess is
neither does he.
I should have seen
the blinking on the video.
Well, it could have been
a nervous tic.
But it wasn't.
it's a classic sign
Of long-term antipsychotic use,
and i missed it.
We all did.
Well, regardless,
those men died.
Garcia's got something.
May 1, 1975,
a 6-year-old darrin call
Was found roaming
in the middle of nowhere
and was picked up
And was in state care
for the first few months.
Did he tell the cops
what happened?
No. because he didn't talk,
Not for over a year.
and once he started talking,
He only knew his life
as darrin call.
That's awful.
So is this. little darrin
was never claimed.
Jj: maybe he wasn't
from the area.
There wasn't a thriving
missing children's network
in 1975.
Call is wearing
cipolla's clothing.
You think he's lucid?
No, mostly likely
he's just freaked out.
Either way, we should
update the public.
You should
be there, too.
What is this?
Call's timeline.
he left louisville?
3 times.
Always came back
to the same 10-block radius.
Why?
Victims are often drawn
to the scene of
their first trauma.
Part of him
wanted to escape,
The other part probably
struggled to find answers.
Was he hospitalized?
Uh, 1985 for 2 years.
Garcia: yeah. and again
in '95 for a few months,
Both at the state facility
in fayette county.
You know he doesn't drive.
You think he'd walk
all the way out there?
He's desperate.
he'll find a way.
Well, then i'll tell
the sheriff in fayette.
When did he start
the prescriptions, garcia?
In 1977, and it looks like
he tried them all.
I've got a list.
Alphabetically, alprazolam,
Clonazepam, diazepam--
Just send it.
yes, sir.
His doctor weaned him off
the prescription for a reason.
Now, that's a big risk,
so the reward
must have been greater.
Prentiss:
he needs the truth.
He took his file.
He's got some answers.
And a head start.
Well, we need to catch up.
[screaming]
[indistinct chatter]
Jj: records from child services
Has him extremely
physically abused.
No signs of sexual assault.
Garcia: that's a miracle.
Either way, the trauma
was debilitating.
Was he running from
an abusive home
or an abduction?
Wouldn't there be a paper trail
if it were a kidnapping?
Garcia, look for unsolved
missing children's cases
from the 1970s.
Now, there was a case
In hollow creek.
kids were dead, though.
Found them in pieces.
When was this?
'75.
Nobody talks about it
'cause they never
found the guy.
You think call
walked away from that?
It's possible.
Garcia, send me everything.
Done.
Can you find the case file?
I'll do what i can.
[groaning]
Boy: you're it!
Second boy:
come on, wait up!
[kids chattering]
Is there a suspect list?
It's in here somewhere.
Reid: he was known as
the hollow creek killer.
3 bodies were found,
some never identified.
Oh, god, he used lime
to dispose--
There's a survivor.
call?
No, a 12-year-old boy
named tommy phillips.
Parents said he'd been
missing for 2 weeks,
Came back a different kid.
Of course he did.
Let's see. the family
left louisville
After tommy told police
where to find the bodies.
He also said the suspect
was a white man in his 30s
And drove
a red pickup truck.
We need to find tommy.
He'd be 46 now.
His parents probably
changed his name
And got as far away
as possible.
Garcia can find him.
Don't get your hopes up.
Garcia,
everything you can find
On a tommy phillips.
Reid: the victims had cuts.
The stock boy's blade
Is what set him off
in the pharmacy.
If this is what call's
been running from,
It's no wonder
he's blocked it out.
Since he's clean now,
there's no medication
To block his memories
and he wants answers.
Where would he go?
To what he knows.
He doesn't know anything.
That's the problem.
He's beginning to.
1975, sterner orphanage.
It's where he became
darrin call.
[knocking on door]
[knocking]
Yes?
There was a nice man
here, mr. cureton.
I need to see him.
I'm sorry,
he retired years ago.
Well, where did he go?
I don't know. i'm sorry--
you gotta know! he--
He didn't just leave.
I'm sorry, sir,
but i told you,
he's not here.
Come on, kids, homework!
Come on.
Would you please leave?
the children are coming in.
please.
Come on. come on.
straight to the books.
Right to it.
straight to the back
and we'll sit down.
He's here.
Who?
What are you
talking about?
Nobody's here.
he's here.
I just--
Oh, careful, ryan.
Come on, you can make it!
Come on! come on, come on!
Tommy, tommy,
We gotta go.
Stop it!
no, wait--
Stop it! stop it!
aah!
Stop it!
Come on, tommy.
Go, go!
somebody help!
Somebody!
Go, go!
Thank you.
He called the boy tommy.
Is that
what set him off?
She thought it was
his reflection.
Whoever hurt him
years ago
Might have been
the same age he is now.
He might have seen
the similarity.
What about the boy?
His real name is ryan.
She said he's quiet
and submissive.
Is morgan
getting anything
Out of the other witness?
Not yet.
A minivan was stolen
one block from here.
Call's never driven
in his life.
You think he's still
not running from us?
Which way?
Eastbound. i got roadblocks
set up everywhere.
He's not getting out
of this county.
You're wasting your time.
He's outnumbered.
You think he's gonna
just disappear?
I think he took
the boy for a reason.
I don't care why he took him.
You should.
Call's memory
is no longer suppressed.
He's reinventing his past,
And unless
we understand how,
We're not gonna find
either of them.
Well, i'm not gonna
just sit around and speculate.
Then don't.
You don't think
we should chase him either?
We need to get ahead
of call.
There's a kid missing.
They don't need
the extra manpower.
Since when?
If we'd studied
foyet's initial crimes,
We would have known
that a survivor
didn't make sense.
What does he have
to do with this?
All we had to do was stop
and look at foyet's history,
And we didn't, and we lost
two couples and a bus
full of people.
And i'm not making
that mistake again.
Ryan: they're gonna find us.
Where? you saw 'em?
where?
Who?
Where did you seem 'em?
where did you see 'em?! where?!
Please, just let me go.
I'm sorry, tommy.
Just--
We just gotta--
we gotta--
Just--ohh--we gotta--
We gotta hurry, tommy,
'cause he's gonna get us
and we just--
We just gotta--uhh--
[groans]
So what do we know?
There were only 4 suspects
in the hollow creek case
And they're all dead.
The kids were taken
in 1973, '74, and '75.
And all on the way
home from school.
Different school districts.
He waited for them
to be alone.
That takes patience.
He must have had time off
in the afternoons.
He lived or worked
near the schools.
That's a lot of doors
to knock on.
You think call's
going back there?
I think there's
a good chance.
I'll tell mitchell.
Where's the secondary
location?
He needed seclusion
to do what he did.
[beep]
Go ahead, garcia.
you're on speaker.
I found tommy. he goes by
james thomas anderson now.
Is he local?
One county over. address
and bio are coming...now.
Hotch: thanks, garcia.
What does darrin call
have to do with me?
We think he survived
the hollow creek murders.
Nobody survived that.
You did.
There was another boy.
He was 6.
No, that's not true.
We don't have time for this.
I'm telling you,
i was alone.
Just like now?
Excuse me?
Have you ever been married?
Any relationships?
any family?
What does that have
to do with anything?
Or are you afraid
you'll abandon them, too?
Or was it because of
your alcoholism?
I would never leave a kid.
Did he cry too much?
Was he too slow?
what was it?
How could you leave
a 6-year-old all alone?
I was only 12 years old.
He's been taking medications
to deal with the trauma
That suppressed
his memories.
That kind of amnesia
is a psychological defense.
He's gonna wish
he never remembered.
We know what you told
the police.
We need to know
about the boy.
He never talked.
Hey! hey, kid.
Hey, kid.
Is the old man
passed out yet?
Can you reach those?
Good. good. good.
Good.
Ok. bring 'em. please.
Bring 'em here.
Go ahead, you can do it.
Right there. good.
Ok.
Come on. come on!
Come here.
Grab the shovel.
Hey, come here!
[groaning]
Quit struggling!
Come here.
Get out of there.
Go on!
Uhh!
Ah!
Come on.
Come on!
Come on, you can make it!
[grunting]
Come on!
Aah! go, tommy! run!
Go, tommy! run!
I'd never heard
his voice before.
He told you to go.
He was a kid.
So were you.
Call wasn't in
the back with you.
No, he was in the cab.
He gave you water.
Got the keys.
Why wasn't he locked up?
Maybe call
wasn't a victim.
Call's reflection.
Oh, god.
His father was
the hollow creek killer.
His own kid?
No wonder
he was never claimed.
How did the father explain
his son just disappeared?
Could have said
he ran away.
The mother would have
reported him missing.
Maybe he said
the boy died.
She'd want a funeral.
What if there wasn't one?
Morgan, call garcia.
ask her to check death records
From 1969 to 1975.
For who?
For the mother.
[breathing hard]
[grunting]
[panting]
Go, tommy! run!
Go, tommy, run!
You think you can get away?!
Is that what you think?!
You stupid little bastard.
Uhh!
[screaming]
[horn honking]
[honking]
Hey!
[grunting]
Morgan: have you
narrowed it down?
Oh, 6 years is a long time.
i need more parameters.
She lived within
that 8-mile radius.
She was married.
she was most likely
in her twenties.
He was probably
her only kid.
The husband drove
a red truck.
Ok. this could be one.
Here we go, doris jarvis.
died in childbirth.
And let me guess--
she had a boy.
Yeah.
Baby girl, i'm gonna
put you on speaker.
Guys.
Garcia: ok, so doris jarvis
Was married to bill jarvis.
He owned a machine shop
just outside the city.
That could be
the secondary location.
It closed in 1980.
He hasn't done anything since.
i guess he laid low.
He had a red pickup until 1976
when he bought a black one.
I know that because
that's what he was driving
When he was arrested for duis.
He was locked up
from '77 to '80,
And i'm sending
his picture now.
And that could certainly
be darrin call's father.
Where's jarvis now?
In the same house.
1457 hitchens avenue.
Let's go.
[gate creaks]
[crowd cheering on tv]
...that's gonna do it.
There's no energy
shortage here.
His third shot
of the 1975 season.
We'd like to remind you--
You're late.
of the game of the day.
[indistinct tv announcer]
Patterson still walking
around the mound.
We're not quite sure
what is happening.
[announcer continues]
[crowd cheering on tv]
He's behind
the count now,
Three balls, one strike,
With a man on first
and second
Here in the bottom
of the eighth.
I knew you'd come home.
Lieutenant.
The kid's in there.
we've got this.
Tactical teams
are covering the exits.
Call needs a distraction.
He's focused on the old man.
For now. but we're gonna
have to figure out
The safest way
to get that kid out.
I've got a team in the back
and one on the way.
We're going to infiltrate.
You do that
and someone else dies.
Either call
or a child murderer--
Flip a coin.
It doesn't have to end
like that.
We get a confession
out of jarvis
and he goes away,
And call gets
his answers.
No one else has to die.
Hotch.
Hotch!
What the hell is he doing?!
Let him go.
Rossi, i'm not letting him
go in there solo.
We have to trust him.
We can do this together.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Get out!
My name's aaron.
This is between us and him.
I know.
Then you leave us alone.
I know what he did
to those boys.
I know about hollow creek
and the cage.
And tommy.
You know about tommy?
Come on, you can make it!
Come on!
come on!
We're gonna get him back
for everything
that he done, tommy.
Every single thing.
Let him go. tommy
doesn't need to see this.
He should die.
He should.
but if you kill him,
You have nothing,
and i thought
you wanted some answers.
What's he doing?
Stalling.
He's got nothing to lose.
Go ahead, darrin,
ask him.
[whimpers]
Why did you do that
to those kids?
What kids?
No!
The ones that
we buried. why?!
You're confused.
No! unh!
Jarvis, why didn't you move?
This is my home.
You sure it's not the view?
Darrin, come here.
Come take a look at this.
He sits on the porch every day
and watches those kids.
He can't help himself.
You got the shot?
Man on police radio:
negative.
Damn it.
What's he doing?
Man on police radio:
bringing the boy out.
Let's get hotch out of there.
That's his call.
We--we drove around
in that truck.
[panting]
You made your own son
Sit in front so the other
boys would feel safe?
You--you kept them
in cages.
I burnt their clothes.
And when you finished,
you'd bury them
And you made him help.
And--
Get up.
pretend you're a man.
You like little boys,
don't you?
But they can't be
too small,
'cause that would be wrong.
What was it about them?
they make you feel strong,
Make you feel like a man?
You shut up.
Is that a yes?
Darrin.
please--
Please.
we're surrounded here.
The police are gonna
storm in here any minute.
They will not shoot you
if you are unarmed.
You need to put
the gun down now.
Don't--don't--
Tell me what to do!
Uhh! don't--uhh--
[gunshots]
Go, go!
What happened?
I couldn't stop him.
Rossi: it's over.
For now.
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you.
There's someone
i think you should talk to.
Hey.
Tommy?
I'm so sorry.
What for?
For running away.
We both ran.
Yeah, but i left you behind.
He could have killed you.
He didn't.
'cause i wasn't afraid
of him anymore.
You've changed
everything, tommy.
You're the one
that i waited for.
that saved me.
[engine starts]
Hotch: "there is no witness
so dreadful,
"no accuser so terrible,
As the conscience that dwells
in the heart of every man."
Polybius.
[knocks]
Hey.
I know what you want
to talk about.
2 months ago we wouldn't
be breaking down
hotch's decisions.
There'd be no doubt.
2 months ago he had everything
to live for, rossi.
Now his family's
just been taken away.
How is he supposed to think
about anything else?
How long is he gonna
let foyet win? hmm?
I mean, come on,
by the time we catch this guy,
Hotch could be more scarred
on the inside than he is
the outside.
Hotch took a risk.
But we saved that boy.
He put his life at risk
in there,
In ways that we are never
supposed to, and you know it.
I'm not about to stand by
and watch this man kill himself.
And you won't.
Rossi...
If hotch is gone,
Foyet's got no one else
to torture. hotch wins.
But if hotch lives
but doesn't get to watch
his son grow up,
Hotch loses.
[alarm beeping]
You didn't have to walk
me up here, you know.
I know.
[resets alarm]
So you think call's
gonna be ok?
I don't know.
He got his answers.
He killed the man
who haunted him.
And what else is there?
The years of torture.
Think he'll get over that?
How could he?
But at least he doesn't
have to feel like
he's alone anymore.
He doesn't have anyone.
He has tommy.
He's not alone.
Get some sleep.
You, too.
[sighs]
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com