How are you feeling today?
You let me smoke.
What more can I ask for?
Most patients have a hard time
coping with new surroundings.
They probably believe
they'll be released.
I'm not so naive.
You don't believe you'll be getting out?
Would you let me out?
I'd like to talk about adam.
He's still missing.
So I've heard.
- Will you help us find him?
- No.
Why not? What more do you need to hide?
I'm not hiding anything.
And I think the better question would
be,what are you looking for... Dr. Reid?
I think you know what I'm looking for.
I want to hear you say it.
I am looking for adam.
Just because you caught me
doesn't mean you'll find him.
You're not that smart.
This isn't about being smart.
This is out doing the right thing.
I did the right thing.
*******
***********
Chandler,looks like I got
the night off after all.
Yeah,what she don't know only
makes it that much better.
Yeah,sounds like a plan.
Right. I'm gonna change and
i'll,uh... I'll hit you back.
Hey,i saw you earlier,didn't i?
My name's dan.
Adam.
Adam!
Where's madison? I thought you were off.
Oh,she wasn't feeling
well,so I sent her home.
Listen,we had another early checkout,so
could you turn it over before you clock out?
What,I'm a cleaning lady now?
I'm your boss,and you'll be
whatever I want you to be.
Ok. What room?
319.
daniel keller,21,a junior at
benjamin franklin university.
He was killed last night while
spring breaking in south padre island.
c.o.d.asphyxiation.
He was the second victim to be
murdered there in the past 3 nights.
The first was william browder,also
on spring break,c.o.d.asphyxiation.
They were both sexually
assaulted prior to death.
Men being raped and murdered on
spring break? Well,that's a twist.
So far the deaths have
been localized to one hotel.
The hudson street hotel.
Initially,the hotel was filled to
capacity but lost 20% occupancy overnight.
We should get a list of
everyone who works there.
There's a good chance one of them is the
unsub,at the very least has interacted with him.
Yeah,gaia's already on that.
Both victims were
discovered by hotel staff,
the last after online checkout
indicated the room had been vacated.
So he wanted the bodies discovered,and
sooner rather than later.
Look at the way they're posed--
naked,cowering in the fetal position.
He's sending a message.
Something about this
is important to him.
We just need to figure out what.
And we need to do it soon.
The police suspect the unsub could
be another vacationing student,
Though I'm not willing to
rule out local involvement.
Makes sense.
If the killer is a student,they could be halfway
across the country by the time we're onto them.
If he's a local,we could lose him
as soon as his victim pool dries up.
Either way,we're almost out of time.
South padre spring break
season ends this weekend.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Criminal Minds
Season04 Episode20 Conflicted
"light thinks it travels
faster than anything.
"but it is wrong. No matter
how fast light travels,"
"it finds the darkness has always gotten
there first and is waiting for it."
Terry pratchett.
National media has
picked up on the story.
We're gonna have to make
a statement when we land.
We want to make people aware
without obviously causing panic.
Stress hypervigilance,the whole
buddy system,yeah,I'm all over it.
I just don't think
anyone's gonna listen.
What do you mean?
Come on. Drunk college students don't exactly
want to hear they shouldn't talk to strangers.
Right.
Was there any dna left on the scene?
Uh,yeah. Too much dna.
This portion of the garcia show will be
brought to you by the letter "i" for icky.
The lab has recovered over
100 different trace samples,
as multiple guests
create a cesspool of dna.
Also,there is no way to determine
the exact time of "secretion"
or to eliminate anyone
actually working at the hotel.
Were you able to find any connection
between the first two victims?
No. They grew up in different states,
The went to colleges on opposite coasts I did
the whole cross-reference credit card thing,
couldn't make it connect.
- So the hotel's the only common denominator.
- Yeah.
And it should be noted that the
first victim,william browder,
wasn't exactly a registered guest.
Well,that's a popular thing to do.
I mean,youngsters do it all the time.
They rent a room,they pack in as
many kids as possible to save costs.
We could be dealing with
hundreds of unregistered guests.
We need to check every guest,whether
they were on the books or not.
Male raping male.
So are we presing our unsub
or victims could be gay?
That's not necessarily true.
In male rape,sexual preference
typically has less to do with the crime
than the power And dominance the
attacker feels from the act itself.
Still,it's a question we should ask
the families when we interview them.
It could help us determine
how the unsub met the victims.
We got a lot of work to do.
Emily,jj,and I will go to the
local p.d.and start victimology.
The rest of you,there's your new home.
You must be the fbi.
David rossi. These are
agents morgan and reid.
Julie riley. I'm the manager.
You were on duty when the
latest body was discovered?
That's right.
Did you happen to notice
anyone out of the ordinary?
I'm afraid not.
You see so many faces during the spring
break,pretty soon they all start to blur.
We need to set up interviews with the
rest of your staff as soon as possible,
also talk to the hotel guests.
Of course.
How many cameras do you
have on the property?
Not enough.
We have all the main entrances
and the garage covered.
But the hallways and the
service tunnels aren't equipped.
Can you show us the room
where the last body was found?
Um,i'll start rounding up the rest
of the staff for you to talk to.
Thanks.
No signs of struggle reported.
Everything seemed normal
when housekeeping arrived.
Look at this.
Scratch marks on the footboard.
The victims were bound
before the struggle gan.
Well,that would make sense. Both
victims were in pretty good shape.
Probly needed them tied up
in order to control them.
The question is,was it
consensual or was it coerced?
Reese evans.
Agent hotchner. These are
agents prentiss and jareau.
Hello.
Well,thanks for being here.
If it's all right with you,we'd like to talk to
the victim's friends and family as soon as possible.
Of course.Michael browder,the
father of the first victim
has just arrived to
claim his son's body.
And the second victim's girlfriend
should be here within the hour.
Does,uh,mr. Browder know the
details of his son's murder.
Not everything.
I mean,there were certain matters I
didn't want to bring up on the phone.
If you don't mind,we'd like
to handle that ourselves.
We're gonna have to ask him a few
difficult questions about his son.
Honestly,i have been
dreading it all day.
- I'll talk to the girlfriend.
- Right this way.
So if I'm the unsub and it wasn't
consensual,how does this work?
You'd have to have a weapon.
A gun to the face means
he doesn't scream out.
Look at the distance between
where each of the arms were tied.
There's no way he could have
tied that second hand himself.
Which means the unsub did it for him.
Which would be risky,because if he knew he was in
danger and he saw the opportunity,he would take it.
Then why not drug him and then
tie him up? Eliminate the risk.
The tox screen came back negative.
So it's either consensual
or he has a partner.
- He's also learning fast.
- What do you mean?
He hides the body in the closet and then
indicates that the guest has checked out.
Which means when the
housekeeper gets here...
everything looks normal And she
starts cleaning,wiping everything down.
Erasing any fingerprints or dna which
could have been left on the scene.
We need to talk to
whoever cleaned this room.
Maybe they saw something that can tell
us who was in here with dan keller.
Mr. Browder,did your son have
any history of drug abuse?
Marijuana,methamphetamine,anything?
None. He w an athlete in high
school and college. Tested regularly.
Did he mention anything about meeting someone
here in south padre? Old acquaintances?
He came down with some
friends from his school.
They wanted to blow
off steam before finals.
Mr. Browder,was your son gay?
He had had sex with
a man before he died.
Knowing whether or not it was consensual
will help us determine how he was targeted.
Adam jackson? Your manager
said we could find you up here.
Uh--i--i get
migraines.
- You discovered the body last night?
- Yeah.
Had you ever seen him before?
Or noticed anyone he may have been with?
I've never seen him before in my life.
Since I opened the closet,i
can't get him out of my head.
Adam,what about the first
victim,william browder?
Have you ever seen him before?
Never seen either of them.
Let me ask you this-- is there anything you remember
about the room before you discovered the body?
It might not seem like much,but the
smallest detail could really help us a lot.
It looked pretty normal.
I mean,until I opened the closet door.
Did anything stand out about the body?
Or,uh,for that matter,anyone
at the hotel last night?
No,man. You seen one drunk
frat guy,you seen 'em all.
Adam,i thought you said
you didn't recognize him.
I didn't. I just--that girl from
corpus christi across the******
They walk around like they
own the place,you know?
They think they can
do whatever they want.
How long have you worked here?
6 months,i guess.
- Appreciate your time.
- Thank you.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah.
You've seen bad stuff,right?
I have,yeah.
How long before you can close
your eyes without it being there?
I'm afraid I still don't know.
Morgan and reid are
finishing the interview.
What did you learn?
It doesn't look like either
of our victims was gay.
Dan keller's girlfriend describes him as
overtly sexual and aggressive towards women.
It caused quite a few
problems in their relationship.
And his friends said they were
out partying prior to his death,
And he was definitely willing to overlook
the fact that he had a girlfriend.
Does that match with what
you found at the scene?
Yes and no.
What do you mean?
The victims were both big guys,yet
there were no signs of a struggle.
We profile it as either
being consensual or...
The unsub had a partner.
Sounds right. What's your hesitation?
- What if it was both?
- How so?
Well,even if he was confronted by two men,the
first reaction of an alpha male would be to fight.
- But not if it were a woman.
- It's spring break.
She lures the victim to her hotel
room,ties him up,then once he's subdued...
Her partner arrives.
That could explain the
posing and the rape.
The victims are alpha males with
aggressive sexual tendencies.
The unsub treats his victims
the way they treat women.
So we have a team.
A woman who lures them back to
their hotel room and ties them up...
And a man who rapes and murders them.
********
Thanks,man.
Oh,look at that.
Whoa ho,where are you going?
Don't worry about it.
Your unsubs have changed hotels.
What can you tell us?
The vic's name is carl
cade,another spring breaker.
Any witnesses?
His friends saw him last night leave a
party with a brunette in a green dress.
Both had been drinking
for most of the day,
And he only caught a glimpse of
the girl before they left the party.
And he found the body
posed just like the others.
It sounds like our theory
about the partners was right.
Woman lures the victim back,she offers
up a little kink,then ties him up.
Only this time the unsubs ventured
outside of their comfort zone.
They changed hotels.
Ok,so what's he doing,getting
bolder or smarter?
Well,the local police are
on alert,the fbi is here.
They probably changed pattern
to avoid getting caught.
Or because they saw
us at the other hotel.
We need to go back to hudson street.
We believe at least one of our unsubs
Is either a guest at the hudson street
hotel or possible an employee there.
We have agents in uniforms
recanvassing the entire property.
But we all know kids on spring break.
They migrate from place to place.
We can't be sure that the
killer's still on site.
Which is why we need you
to circulate this profile.
We believe we're looking for
a dominant/submissive team,
a man and a woman probably in their 20s.
We are looking for a heterosexual male who
most likely is submissive in his everyday life,
With everyone except his partner.
To her he becomes dominant.
His submissive female partner
will be socially awkward,
of average intelligence,and
emotionally unstable.
Look for women who are reclusive,have
a problem with authority,
and can't interact with
dominant personalities.
This form of male rape is
about power and dominance.
It is not about sexual
orientation. So victimology is key.
This team targets alpha personality males
who think that women are their right.
Add drugs or alcohol to the equation
and now we're dealing with eager victims.
Even with the mention of rape,an alpha
personality fueled by intoxication believes
That he can control the situation
and eventually gain the upper hand.
We'll need to blanket the beach with
fliers,talk to other hotels and bartenders.
We have got 2 days until the spring
break season ends,so let's get to work.
Hey,hotch,i think we got something.
Check this-- no report male
rape anywhere in the area.
It's not surprising since it's like one
of the least reported crimes on the books.
I also looked at video surveillance
for the hudson street hotel
on the days of both murders,and zip.
Tell me there is a "but" coming.
But,i also looked at the days
leading up to both murders,
And,wouldn't you know
it,jackpot of jackpots,
that would be william
browder,aka victim number one.
I would like to call him jerkface,seemingly
making advances at damsel in distress,
aka hotel employee madison cooke.
See jerkface grab damsel,
see adam jackson-- Let's call
him white knight--intervene.
See jerkface knock white knight down.
See white knight pause.
See whe knight go postal.
- Didn't the maintenance man find the second victim?
- Yeah.
And he told reid and morgan that he'd
never met either of the first two victims.
So why lie?
Garcia,i need everything
you can find on adam jackson.
- I'm already on that.
- Dave,are you still at the scene?
Good,we've got a possible.
Where's adam jackson?
I don't know. What's going on?
The day before the first murder,u
had an altercation with the victim.
It's spring break. It
comes with the territory.
- Adam stepped in?
- Yeah.
He doesn't strike me as the
type to stand up to a bully.
The guy was being a jerk.
Adam happened to be there.
And you didn't think it was weird that
the same kid ended up dead the next night?
It wasn't adam.
Then why hide the fact that he got
into a fight with one of the victims?
Julie told us not to.
She was just trying to protect us both.
- Where's adam?
- I don't know. Honestly.
He's supposed to be on duty,but
he disappears sometimes.
He might be on the roof.
Morgan,check the roof.
Adam jackson's life reads like
a "how to make an unsub" manual.
Born in corpus christi,biological
mother rosemary jackson.
In and out of hospitals--
broken arm,broken rib,exhaustion.
The polite way of saying spousal abuse.
Exactly. And then she died
suddenly when adam was 5.
Father unknown.
Adam was left in the custody
of his stepfather,mark harrison.
Then it became adam who was in
and out of the emergency room.
He was eventually foster-homed in dallas until
he was granted emancipation at the age of 16.
I would bet you if we could
see mike harrison back then,
He would bear a striking
resemblance to our unsubs' victims.
Good work,garcia. Keep digging.
Adam!
Come here. Come here.
What's happening?
- You're coming with us. - I--i
don't understand. What's going on?
Let's go.
He doesn't really look like the
dominant partner type,does he?
No.
- He's our guy.
- What makes you so sure?
It's a classic profile.
He grows up with an abusive
stepfather,somehow manages to escape.
Suddenly he finds himself back in the
exact same area where his abuser lives.
He's surrounded by nothing but a bunch of
alpha males that mirror that type of behavior.
He snaps.
Did he have a problem with you as an
authority figure when you interviewed him?
He backed away as if he
was a little skittish.
And reid?
Reid was a little less imposing
and he opened up about his life.
Where's julie?
We're trying to find her.
She's gonna go ballistic.
You're in a lot of trouble,adam.
But I think you know that,right?
The only thing that I did wrong was
leave work without telling my boss.
I--i need to
talk to julie.
Adam...
Why don't you tell me about the
fight you had with the first victim?
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
No.
Adam,i really want to help you out,but you'
gonna have to do a lot better than that.
Please...
I just need to talk to julie!
Hotch.
I just got off with garcia.
So,adam jackson doesn't
just work at the hotel.
- He lives there,too.
- What have we got?
When adam was kicked out of school for
bad grades,drug possession,And petty theft,
he started staying at the hotel.
Julie riley pays his bills.
- The manager?
- Yeah.
She's bailed him out of jail
twice in the past 4 years.
She's also the one that told madison to cover up
the fact that adam had a fight with the first victim.
What's the connection
between julie and adam?
Uh,it turns out when julie was in college
she volunteered at the foster care facility
adam used to reside in between homes.
She befriended him and became the
surrogate for the absent mother.
And now she's his boss.
He owes her everything.
Adam's not the minant,julie is.
- Garcia.
- Yes,sir.
I need you to track any
movement on julie riley.
Cell phone,credit card,atm withdrawal.
I need a last known location.
Julie riley used her
credit card 15 minutes ago.
I'm tying the address
to your gps... Now.
Let's go.
Believe me,kid,this is your lucky night.
***********
******
********
*****
*********
*************
******
*********
Adam,let's talk about the fight you had
with the first victim,william browder.
There's nothing to tell.
He grabbed madison,i tried to stop him.
That guy was pretty big.
So?
Adam,guys like you and I aren't,uh,we
aren't exactly the fighting type.
Well,madisos a good person. She
didn't deserve to be treated that way.
You see,now I'm really confused,because you
just told me that you don't remember the fight.
I don't. I mean,i--i
don't,but i--i do.
You don't,but you do. Can--can
you explain to me how that works?
I remember he grabbed at
madison,i tried to stop him,
the next thing I knew,julie
was pulling me out of the pool.
Why did you tell your
employees to lie to my agents?
Adam has a record.
He found one of the bodies.
I didn't want you to take the easy
way out and pin the murders on him.
Why do you look out for him?
Why did you bail him out of jail,pay
his rent and all of his bills?
He's had a rough life.
And do you take advantage of that?
No.
Safe to say he'd kill for you?
- No!
- Then ela it to me.
What exactly is the relationship?
We've been friends
since I was just a kid.
Are you lovers?
No.
Well,then why does she pay
for everything you have?
It's not like it's a handout. I mean...
I'm working at the hotel
so I can pay her back.
Does she pay for the drugs also?
I--i told you,i
get migraines.
So,ke a prescription.
I thought you were different.
What does that mean?
Do you see something in adam's
past that reminds you of yourself?
I don't know what you mean.
In 2003,you reported a sexual assault.
And from the look of the file,the police
didn't do a very thorough job looking into it.
I don't want to talk about that.
I'm gonna ask you one more
time,would adam kill for you?
No.
Then prove it.
You know a polygraph is not admissible.
If we catch them in a lie,it
could help us get a confession.
And we change interrogators so they can't
get into a rhythm with their answers.
State your name.
Julie riley.
Adam jackson.
What color are your eyes?
Blue.
Where were you the night
carl cade was killed?
- At work.
- At home.
Who is the current president
of the united states?
Barack obama.
Did you murder dan keller?
Did you murder william browder?
- No.
What is 32 minus 19?
Would you kill for julie?
You lied about the altercation
with william browder.
Is there anything
else you've lied about?
- No.
Did you murder dan keller?
What time did you leave work the
night william browder was killed?
I--i don't
remember.
Have you ever had a sexual
relationship with julie riley?
- Have you lied about anything else?
- No.
- Did you murder carl cade?
- He's just a friend.
Using the formula y equals mx
plus b,what does b represent?
- Would adam kill for you?
- No.
- Did you murder carl cade?
- Did you murder william browder?
- No.
- Absolutely not.
- Would you kill for julie?
- No.
What are you looking at?
I'm not sure.
- Well,they both passed.
- How is that possible?
Not only that,they
passed with flying colors.
The only spike I got on adam was a control
question regarding geometric equations,but...
Honestly,i think I just flustered him.
Either way,we got nothing.
Well,i think my couch is calling.
Sweet dreams.
What about you?
Clean the pool,change the a/c filter,fix
the heat lamps by tonight. I got it.
Yeah,thanks.
So... Where are we?
Honestly? Nowhere.
We just watched our two most
viable suspects walk out the door.
If adam isn't our unsub,he has all
the makings to become one someday.
Reid?
Tell me the question that he
spiked under in the polygraph.
It was a control question
to set the baseline.
It was a geometric equation?
Reid,i really think he
was just intimidated.
He tried,he got it wrong,but he wasn't
supposed to know the answer anyway.
What if he lied?
What if--what if he knew the answer to the
question but intentionally got it wrong?
I--i
don't know.
Why would he do that?
Because he realized that he
wouldn't know that answer.
You're losing me,kid.
Adam,are you in here?
Adam said he wasn't getting any rest.
He takes midday naps because
he's always exhausted.
He has a history of
blackouts,reclusive behavior,
Prolonged repeated abuse suffered
at the hands of a dominant male
Who transferred abuse from his female
spouse to his prepubescent child.
Where are you going with this?
What if our unsub couple
isn't a couple at all?
Dissociative identity disorder.
You think adam's a multiple personality?
Well,it fits.
Recurrent physical abuse,knowledge he
shouldn't have. We've seen this before.
Look at this. All right?
The first intervention is timid.
It's apprehensive,right? But
then he gets knocked down...
There's a moment of calm,and then
his entire body language changes.
I saw this exact same transformation
when adam left the station,
only it wasn't rage,it was,uh,arrogance.
Like the alter ego wanted me to know.
- Why?
- I don't know. Power,control.
All I know is the person that stared
me down over there was not adam.
He's not assertive like that.
He doesn't make eye contt.
So you think the stress of the interrogation blurred
the line between adam and his alter personality?
I think the unsub
surfaced for just a moment.
It knew the answer to the
question,realized adam wouldn't,and lied.
So adam and the woman in the
green dress are the same person?
We profiled the duo accurately,only the dominant
personalities and alter are inside of adam.
And adam has no idea he
killed all those people.
You could argue that adam
didn't kill those people.
A separate person inside of him did.
I don't even know what we do with this.
We take him into custody,we
let the courts decide.
I thought you were heading home.
I found this in your room.
- You went in my
room? What? - Yeah,i--
you don't remember the
fight with william browder,
You disappeared before
dan keller was killed,
- and you won't tell me where you've been.
- What are you saying?
Why do you have this?
It's not mine.
It was hidden in your closet.
Julie,this is
crazy! Ju--ohh!
Did--did a woman get
you involved in this?
No!
If you turn her in,then I can help you.
I didn't kill those people!
I want to believe you,adam.
Believme!
I think that we should
go to the police together.
- No!
- I'll be right there with you.
We'll figure this out.
Or i'll go by myself.
I said no.
Adam... What's going on?
You shouldn't be up here.
Adam... You're starting to scare me.
My name is amanda.
If you're in some kind of
trouble,hon,i can help you.
Adam doesn't need you anymore.
No! No! No!
Reid and morgan,take the roof.
We've got adam's room.
Hotchner! In the back!
Ok,guys,let's back up! Back up!Come on.
- Excuse me.
- Move,move!
We've got a woman down
at the back of the hotel.
Send medics as soon as possible.
Julie,can you hear me?
- Adam...
- Ok.
Look,help is on the way.
I need you not to move.
It wasn't... Him... Strange.
Julie,did he say where he was going?
- He called himself amanda.
- The alter personality.
Reid,you were right. Where would he go?
Not he. She. Amanda,she panicked.
She knew we would connect this to her.
Ok,ok,so she's feeling the pressure. She
obviously knows she's running out of time.
Where would she go?
She's gonna go after the
man these victims represent.
Garcia,please tell me you know
the whereabouts of mark harrison.
The skeezy wife-beating,child-abusing
scumbag never left corpus christi.
Sending his address to your p.d.
Go.
Medics!
- Amanda.
- Stay back.
- Put the knife down.
- Stand back or i'll kill him.
You do not want to do that.
You don't know what he did.
When adam's mother died,his stepfather needed
a new outlet for his aggression,didn't he?
He put adam in dresses. He
beat him. He touched him.
Adam was too weak to go
through all of that alone.
He was just a little boy.
He needed you to protect him.
I could take it.
I was stronger than he was.
He deserves to die.
Amanda. Amanda. That's
not for you to decide.
I swear to god,if you put
him down and you come with me,
I will get you and adam
the help that you guys need.
Adam will be sentenced
for what I've done.
No... I can't let that happen.
Amanda. If you kill
yourself,you kill adam.
I don't see how that's protecting him.
And you know what I know?
I know that all you want to do
in this world Is protect adam.
it's all I've ever done.
Then why don't you and
I help him together.
You can't help him.
I'm the only one.
I know what I have to do.
I will keep him safe forever.
Adam.
Reid. He's gone.
It's time to go,kid.
Reid. What's eatin' you,man?
We've taken the victim into
custody and let the abuser go free.
I don't really-- I don't
sethat as much of a win.
A lot of lives are gonna be saved now that
amanda's off the street. You know that.
Yeah,i just...
I wish I could have noticed
the signs in time to save adam.
Come on,don't do that to yourself.
None of us could have noticed.
Our profile was right.
We just never considered that the team dynamic
could be locked inside one person's mind.
I should have.
Talk to me. What is this?
Tobias hankel.
Tobias hankel drugged and
tortured you for 2 days.
He almost killed you.
No,he didn't.
The alter persona of his
father did those things to me.
The real tobias hankel saved my life.
He brought me back from the dead.
And you think because of
tobias,somehow you owe adam?
I just--i know that he's still
locked in there somewhere.
Kid.
You're gonna have to accept the fact
that sometimes we can't save everyone.
Tell me,dr. Reid,how long will
you keep visiting me in here?
Until I find adam.
Why do you care?
He deserves a life. It's his.
So you're trying to... Wear
me down and release him?
No. I'm just waiting for
you to do the right thing.
Well,I'm afraid you'll be
waiting for a very long time.
Stephen king wrote,"monsters are
real,and ghosts are real,too."
"they live inside us.
And sometimes they win."
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
www.tvsubtitles.net