Look at you.
- Sorry I'm wet. I'm...
- I'm sorry to make you drive in this.
It sounded urgent.
It's really good to see you.
It's been forever.
Johnny, what's goin' on?
It's about Matthew.
- Benton?
- He's dead.
I didn't wanna tell you
over the phone.
How?
His parents said
that he had a heart attack.
I'm sorry.
- Had you seen him?
- Yeah.
A couple of times.
- How was he?
- He was Matthew.
He was rambling, a little chaotic.
- He was using.
- I don't know.
Probably.
There's something
you're not telling me.
The last time I saw him,
there was somethin' different.
He was talkin' crazy, but the...
the fear... I can't quite explain it,
but I know it was real.
What was he saying?
He said,
"Johnny, they're gonna kill me."
- Who's "they"?
- He wouldn't say.
He said they already murdered
a guy from Georgetown named Tommy "V"
- and made it look like an accident.
- Do you know anyone named Tommy "V"?
Look, he's probably
just being paranoid,
but with what you do
for a living now...
You're one of the only people
he ever trusted.
My lord, it's kitties
and poodles out there.
- Did you hear it might even snow?
- Can you find anything on Tommy "V"?
If by chance you mean
Thomas Valentine, age 35,
found dead in his home
from dehydration, as a matter of...
- what's going on?
- Is Hotch still here?
- I'm pretty sure he lives here.
- Thanks.
What's wrong?
I just found out that...
An old friend of mine died.
I'm sorry.
Do you need to take some time?
There's a chance
that he could have been murdered,
and there might be a second case.
What do you need?
- Just some leeway to check it out.
- Of course.
Anything.
Thank you.
Emily, if you wanna take a few days
and let us look into it...
Matthew was...
incredibly messed up,
and I hadn't seen him in a long time,
but he was important to me.
At least let us help.
Thank you.
Leonardo Da Vinci said,
"he who does not punish evil
commands it to be done."
- Thanks for coming in early.
- Where's Morgan and Prentiss?
They're at the morgue
examining this man,
Matthew Benton, a friend of Emily's.
She believes that his death
- may be connected to that man's.
- Thomas Valentine.
Dehydration?
- Did she know him?
- No,
but Benton seemed to think
that someone was after both of them.
One death was a heart attack.
The other was from dehydration.
- What's the connection?
- I don't know if there is one.
- Are the police investigating?
- No, right now,
- we're just helping a colleague.
- So we talk
to the families,
see if there's anything suspicious.
- Is Emily OK?
- I don't know.
That's why I sent Morgan
to go with her.
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
It'll be all right.
Hold my hand?
Always.
Is it possible someone
could have induced the heart attack?
The easiest way to stop the heart
is an injection of potassium.
- I would have found traces.
- There's no other way?
I suppose it's possible he could
have been injected with epinephrine.
It wouldn't register,
because clinically, it's identical
to the natural adrenalin in the body.
- Was he tied?
- The wounds are superficial.
Anything else out of the ordinary?
He bled heavily from his nose,
but with the damage to his septum,
My guess is that it was prolonged abuse
of cocaine or methamphetamine.
- and what about the other autopsy?
- He died of dehydration.
There were traces of prescription
antipsychotics in his system.
I understand from his family,
he had a history of mental illness.
- Are these ligature marks?
- Considering
the self-inflicted wounds
and the history of mental illness,
the police didn't suspect foul play.
So you have 2 bodies
with ligature marks...
- Each superficial.
- But you just dismiss them?
There's no medical reason
to connect these deaths.
I don't understand why the FBI
is interested in our son's death.
We were investigating another death
recently under similar circumstances,
And we just wanted to make sure
that there's no connection.
- He suffered a heart attack.
- It's just routine.
There's nothing routine
about investigating a heart attack.
Andrea, it's OK.
I assume your investigation
is drug-related.
We're just trying
to rule out foul play.
May we come in?
Of course.
When I came in the house,
I found him here in bed.
- You two don't live together?
- I'd taken the kids to my mom's.
We'd been gone a few weeks.
The doctor said he must
have been in bed for days.
May I ask why you took the
children somewhere else to live?
My husband was hearing voices.
He was cursing God.
I needed to protect them.
Of course.
Do you believe in the soul?
I do.
Well, I believe Tommy's
is finally at peace.
Do you mind my asking
if you've been burning incense?
After Matthew died,
I burned some in the room
- to cleanse it.
- So he was living here with you?
We were hoping
he could turn his life around.
We were in New York for the weekend,
and when we came back,
we found his body here.
My son's soul was
in the possession of evil.
Do you have any experience
dealing with drug addiction?
- We see a lot of it through our work.
- It's an impossible thing
to watch happen to someone you love.
Were you aware
that in the days before he died,
Matthew thought
someone was going to kill him?
Where did you hear that?
One of our team members,
agent Prentiss.
- Emily Prentiss?
- Yes, ma'am.
She's the reason you're here?
We'd like you both to leave.
Now.
I told you not to mention me.
You didn't say
it'd get us kicked out.
Is there something we should know?
Matthew and I met
in Rome when we were 15.
My mom was posted there.
His parents didn't like us hanging out.
- And they still hold a grudge?
- They were extremely religious.
- They thought I was a bad influence.
- You?
And that's it?
That's it.
We saw scuff marks on the floor
underneath Thomas Valentine's bed,
Almost as if someone had been
tied up and struggled to get free.
We saw the exact same marks
in Matthew's bedroom.
Has anybody been able to find
any connection at all between them?
According to my snooping,
both Benton and Valentine
traveled to Galicia, Spain,
over the same week 4 months ago.
- That mean anything to you?
- No.
I did the quick guidebook thing.
There's a church there,
Santiago de Compostela.
It's visited by over 100,000
religious pilgrims every year.
Did his parents say anything
about him going on a pilgrimage?
No, the opposite, actually. His mom
said his soul was possessed by evil.
What?
Matthew had a thing
about challenging the church.
He could push it.
When we were in high school,
his mom and dad consulted a priest
Because they were afraid
he was possessed.
I think in this case,
she was talking about drugs.
Are you sure?
There's a pattern here.
The talk about evil
and the soul
and scuff marks on the floor.
What are you driving at?
Drug addiction and schizophrenia
are two afflictions most likely
to present as demonic possession.
- You think these were exorcisms.
- I think it begs the question.
Look, I know the bible
just as well as anyone,
I know there's nothing more open to
behavioral interpretation than religion.
Meaning what?
I think it's dangerous for us to wanna
find a connection between these deaths.
Wait. Was Thomas' wife religious?
She was concerned
that he had been cursing god.
Exorcism ritual can
take days to complete.
It's possible the stress induced
could cause a heart attack,
Especially in someone
with a history of drug use.
That would explain the timeline
of someone dying of dehydration.
Look, I'm willing to say
that we might have an unsub
who ritualizes killings
as if they were exorcisms, maybe,
but right now, we don't know
if we have a crime yet.
Morgan's right.
We need to step back.
Let me talk to someone before
I have us all telling ghost stories.
You know, they count
all that stuff, Jimmy.
Stranger.
I know. It's been too long.
So maybe after we speak,
you'll let me take your confession?
- Gonna strong-arm me?
- You bet.
So, how can I help you?
What do you know about exorcisms?
Well, they're controversial.
The Vatican issued a new...
exorcism rite in 1999,
so nobody speaks out against it,
but if pressed,
not every...
priest believes
in demonic possessions.
Do you?
Let me put it this way.
You believe that evil exists.
- I've seen it.
- So if children
are born innocent,
at what point does evil enter them?
How common are exorcisms?
Conservatively,
I'd say 400 or 500 a year.
Has anyone died in one?
What's this about, Davey?
I'm looking
into the deaths of 2 men.
Both were troubled.
Each recently had made
the same pilgrimage to Galicia, Spain.
Each died within the last 2 weeks.
And why do you suspect exorcism?
Well, it's just a theory.
One of our agents
knew one of the men.
She was afraid there
might be some foul play.
You agree?
Would you know
if one took place here in D.C.?
If it's sanctioned, probably.
If not?
Then it's not a true exorcism.
Thanks, Jimmy.
The agent,
did the information
about the case come to her directly?
Why?
You open yourselves up to...
understanding the worst monsters,
and you invite
evil into your lives.
It's a vulnerable position.
Meaning what?
Take good care of her
and you.
- Are you OK, buddy?
- I'm getting out.
- We're not even halfway there.
Man, close the door!
Holy virgin of virgins...
All holy angels and archangels,
all the orders of blessed spirits,
St. John the baptist, St. Joseph...
- How the hell did you get in here?
- I'm here to help you.
Get the hell out of here.
I cast you out, unclean spirit...
I said get the hell out of here.
Do not lay hands on me.
Garcia got a call.
38-year-old white male
found dead in his bed
by his fiancée.
- What's the connection?
- She ran the name.
Patrick Cavanaugh was in Galicia,
the same week
as Thomas Valentine and Matthew.
- Do you know him?
- No.
- Seriously?
- Yeah. What can you tell us?
White male, been dead for hours.
Medics think it was a brain aneurism.
- You mind if we take a look?
- Knock yourselves out.
This is kind of startin'
to freak me out a little bit.
Let's figure out if we have a crime
before we start freakin' out.
- Obviously we have a crime.
- How does an unsub induce an aneurism?
Could be caused by stress.
Yeah, like if you were restrained
on a bed
while someone tried to banish
the devil from their body.
All I'm sayin' is I think
we should go easy.
Can I help you?
We're with the FBI.
We're investigating a series
- of unexplained deaths.
- I don't understand.
Had Patrick been acting
erratically lately?
He had a brain condition.
He was getting headaches,
wasn't acting like himself.
Were you aware of a trip
he took recently to Galicia, Spain?
There's a church
there called Santiago de Compostela
we think he may have visited.
My fiancé traveled a lot for work.
I don't know everywhere he went.
With all due respect, ma'am, I don't
think you're telling us the truth.
Excuse me?
Did you believe
Patrick was possessed?
I'd like some privacy, please?
Was someone trying
to rid him of demons?
- Is that how he died?
- No.
You really believe
he had a brain condition?
- You need to go now.
- Because if you sanctioned an exorcism
and he died, I can press to make you
an accessory to murder.
That is enough. Stop it.
Let's go.
I apologize for the intrusion.
- What happened?
- I think there may be a third victim.
Is that what you think?
I don't know.
We have ligature marks,
the Spain connection,
and scuff marks under the bed.
It's weird, definitely,
but there's no way
to physically connect dehydration,
a heart attack, and an aneurism.
- What's goin' on?
- We've had a complaint.
J.J.'s trying to smooth it over
with the D.C. police,
but we haven't been invited in
on the case.
That's how you have my back?
- Prentiss, I'm trying to protect you.
- I don't need protection.
Hotch said he got a complaint,
and he didn't come down on you.
You realize that?
You just dodged a bullet.
We have to approach this
like we do any other case.
Meaning what?
Grief can make us wanna believe there's
a reason for things when there's not.
That woman couldn't even use
Patrick's name.
She could only say, "my fiancé"?
Because she's convinced something else
died in that room that night.
As far as the police are concerned,
there is no open murder investigation.
We have no reason to be
investigating if they're not.
They're right.
All we have are three men who died
- in 3 very different natural deaths.
- So we just drop it?
Do you really believe we're dealing
with someone trying to exorcise demons?
It doesn't matter what I believe.
Possession, mental illness?
Exorcist, unsub?
Who cares what's true?
People are dying.
This isn't about religion.
It's about evil.
We attack it
with analysis and diligence.
For this unsub,
it's a fight to the death.
All hail the mistress
of information.
- You got somethin'?
- You know I do.
It's a posting from a web bulletin board
by Matthew Benton
to create a support group for people
who felt betrayed by their faith.
That helps explain
how these 3 men came together.
It gets better.
The week the 3 of them were in Spain,
the services
at Santiago de Compostela
were canceled
when the priest there died.
- Died how?
- Heart attack.
But if you listen to
the conspiracy chatter,
there is a strong belief
he was killed to interrupt services
- during the height of the pilgrimage.
- How?
Their best guess is some kind of gas,
Sarin or VX,
something that wouldn't show up
in an autopsy. But it could be anything
would induce stress,
cause a heart attack.
Then we have a motive.
And a potential M.O.,
an eye for an eye.
Without an invitation from the police,
I cannot authorize an investigation.
This has to be kept quiet.
- So the police are not investigating?
- Exorcism is a tough theory to sell.
The police don't think
the deaths are connected.
But you do.
You're gonna have
to give me some time here.
This is John Cooley.
He was also a friend of Matthew's.
I'm sorry. You saw him recently?
Is there anyone he associated
with out of the usual?
Anyone overtly religious?
Not that I'm aware of.
I've been doin' my best
to retrace his steps,
but I still haven't come up
with anything.
Buy you a cup of coffee?
I will call you if I hear anything.
There are nicer places
to take a girl for coffee.
Did you ever see The Exorcist?
The real case started right here.
The fire department actually...
burned down the house themselves.
The authorities referred
to the boy as Robbie Doe.
- He's still in the D.C. area today.
- Why did you bring me here?
Whole lot of effort went
into destroying the house of a kid,
who probably had onset
schizophrenia or Tourette's syndrome.
- I'm not following you.
- You're sure he was murdered.
So what's the story?
If you don't wanna explain,
that's fine,
but if you do, I'm all in.
Matthew knew
the bible inside and out,
- and he started to question everything.
- Why?
We moved around a lot
when I was a kid,
'cause of my mom's postings.
It was hard to get accepted,
and when you're 15,
that's all you want.
You'll do almost anything.
You got pregnant.
- Was Matthew the father?
- No.
I didn't know what to do.
I couldn't tell my mom.
Matthew suggested
I talk with our priest.
- And what did he say?
- He said
that if I had an abortion,
I wasn't welcome in his congregation.
- So what'd you do?
- Matthew found a doctor.
He took me there.
He stayed with me.
That Sunday
when we got back to Rome,
he held my hand
and walked me into the church.
Father Gamino actually
stopped his sermon,
but Matthew told me to hold my head up,
and we walked to the front pew.
What did the priest do?
He and Matthew just
stared at each other.
It was like
a battle of wills, and...
and then suddenly father Gamino
went back to his sermon.
Matthew saved my life.
He made me feel
like I was worthy of...
Love and...
friendship.
But that's when his anger
and questioning started.
He started doing drugs.
When that melded
with his religious questioning,
You could understand why his parents
were afraid he was possessed
by something evil.
It's my fault...
that Matthew's life unraveled.
Garcia uncovered some information.
It's possible Matthew and the others
killed someone in Spain.
- I don't believe that.
- I'm just saying
if we keep pushing, you have to be
prepared for what we might discover.
I need Matthew to rest in peace.
I owe him that.
Then let's go give a profile.
The police haven't invited us in.
The police aren't gonna do us
any good on this one, anyway.
As I was saying to the
agents, this is a topic
on which we usually agree
to silently disagree.
And we all respect that.
We are not here to examine your
beliefs in demonology or exorcism,
But we are operating
on the theory that...
the person responsible
for these deaths does believe.
We believe the inciting incident
was the death
of father Raul Del Toro
in Galicia, Spain, 4 months ago.
How so?
There's an element who believes
that the death was actually a murder.
You're not suggesting that
this is some kind of retribution?
Even a priest can have
a psychotic break.
He may be under the delusion
that he is working for God.
The man we're looking for would be
obsessed with the event in Galicia.
He believes he's fighting evil
and may very well have followed
these men here to Washington.
We believe that one
of the exorcisms took place
over enough days for the victim
to die of dehydration.
If I may, an exorcism
is like a prize fight.
It's completely draining,
both physically and spiritually. Now,
if this man truly performed
three rituals
within the last few weeks,
he would need medical care.
Is there somewhere
he would go to convalesce?
Anything less than a working hospital
would be too dangerous.
- Garcia, it's Reid.
- Speak, boy wonder.
I need you to run
catholic hospital records.
Look for any admissions
for exhaustion
immediately following
Patrick Cavanaugh's death.
- You got it?
- You know I do.
Now run the same search
for the days immediately
- following the first 2 deaths.
- I sense a cross-check
in my future.
Do you have anything?
One hit: father Paul Silvano.
Currently at St. Agatha's hospital
on 214.
We got him.
Are you father Paul Silvano?
Were you present at the deaths
of Thomas Valentine, Matthew Benton,
and Patrick Cavanaugh?
I've been expecting you.
He asked you a question.
Yes, I was present.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say...
What did he say?
He wants you to look in the drawer.
We're both fighting the same evil.
What is it?
It's diplomatic status.
He has immunity?
Explain to me why you were
the last person in the room
when three men died.
I'm a priest.
- I was there for them spiritually.
- They weren't on their deathbeds.
- Not physically.
- Did you kill them?
But you're not sorry
any of them are dead.
Physical death is always sad,
but now their souls are in heaven.
For that, their families have peace.
Up until 4 months ago,
his record's spotless.
No history of mental illness,
no censures.
He was even invited to say mass
at the Washington national cathedral.
What happened 4 months ago?
No details. Just says he took
a sabbatical for personal reasons.
4 months ago is just
after the death in Spain.
It looks like he lobbied the Vatican
for a diplomatic posting,
but they refused.
After that, he took the world hunger
mission from the Italian government.
Which brought him here
with immunity.
- Where's Hotch?
- On the phone with the department.
Gather the others.
I'll be there in a second.
Did you know...
The priest who died in Galicia?
Father Del Toro and I
were at seminary together.
Did you know that Matthew Benton
and the other men
were in Galicia the week he died?
- Do you believe they committed murder?
- I was contacted by a family member.
He was frightened.
He told me his real son never
returned home from that trip.
And you suggested
that he was possessed.
I said that I could help
rid his child of evil.
What did you tell
the other family members
after you watched their sons die,
that it was god's will?
I've never laid a hand on
anyone with malice in my life.
Then explain these deaths to me.
You know the power of evil.
You've been fighting it a long time.
Be strong.
The storm's almost over.
Yes, sir.
I completely understand.
As far as I know,
he's here voluntarily.
Right.
I understand it's a delicate situation.
What'd he say?
He claims he was
invited by the families.
And now he has them believing
their loved ones are in a better place.
And they're all devout.
The people they loved were troubled.
It's either believe they're in
a better place or live with the guilt.
It doesn't matter.
We can't arrest him.
- Can we deport him?
- Probably not.
It's crazy. Diplomatic immunity
wasn't intended to shield people
from murder charges.
So Hotch bypasses the state department,
goes straight to the Italian consulate.
And loses his career.
The state department won't
risk the potential embarrassment.
- They'll shut us all down.
- There's some real politic for you.
- So what do we do now?
- Did you check his papers with ice?
Yeah. His diplomatic status
runs till the end of the month.
- What?
- He told Emily,
"The storm's almost over".
- So...
- So forget priest. Think unsub.
He's a believer. He
deals in certainties.
In his mind, he has a job to do.
Which doesn't end until
the end of the month.
"The storm's almost over".
There's another victim on his list.
What caused their deaths?
- Medically?
- Yes. Please.
- I can't say.
- Were they under stress?
We all were.
- Did you sprinkle holy water on them?
- That's part of the exorcism ritual.
What was in the holy water?
Sarin? VX?
The smallest amount would
trigger respiratory failure.
- I'm not familiar with them.
- No? Really?
Because that's what a lot of people
think killed father Del Toro in Spain.
Father, you're free to go.
We're sorry if detaining you
has caused you any hardship.
I hope you find peace.
My office.
Are you actually accusing
the Italian government
of authorizing
this man's assassination list?
He admits he was present at every death.
The case is over.
- You said you'd give me leeway.
- And I did.
I understand your frustration.
There are some things
that we cannot control.
- Take some time off.
- What?
I don't wanna see you in the
office for the next few days.
You up for another drive?
- What are you doing here?
- Matthew died during an exorcism
by father Paul Silvano.
He's performed 3
in the last few weeks.
Each subject has died.
We believe he's planning another one.
- That's none of our business.
- Matthew's gone. You've accepted that.
At least let us warn the last family
so they know what kind of choice
they're facing.
This isn't about me.
This is about other families
and the people they love.
Father Paul didn't kill Matthew.
Why are you so willing to accept that?
I'm just trying to find the truth
about how your son died.
Then listen to me.
Father Paul never
laid a hand on Matthew.
How do you know that?
Dad!
And all your dark companions!
Don't look him in the eye!
Don't engage him!
- Dad, please.
- I cast you out...
Dad, please!
Don't look him in the eyes!
I was there.
You stood there and watched Matthew die?
He wasn't the person you knew.
Because father Paul said that?
Something horrible happened
on that trip to Spain.
You believe that because
father Paul said it.
- You can't think for yourself?
- Young lady, don't speak like that.
How could you allow him to
perform a ritual over Matthew?
- I loved my son.
- Then you knew how Matthew was.
- You knew how paranoid he could be.
- I was trying to save his life.
That priest must have done something.
His heart wouldn't have given out.
That thing killed Matthew!
It was inside him for years.
- I know you know that's true.
- No.
Matthew was a sweet boy.
He was just troubled.
He was never troubled until he met you.
Look, we need to know
about the demon
that possessed your son.
Father Paul explained
that Matthew was a conduit.
If you opened yourself, you were
putting yourself in danger
of being taken over.
Who else was Matthew with
while he was in Spain?
- I don't know.
- Who did he see once he was back?
- None.
- Please think.
If father Paul believes
Matthew was a conduit,
anyone he spent time with
could be a target.
He was not to see anyone
until he was better.
No, that's not true.
I know for a fact he saw
our friend John Cooley.
His parents worked with my mother
at the embassy in Rome.
You called him to tell
him Matthew had died.
I haven't spoken with John
Cooley in over 20 years,
not since you were kids in Italy.
- They're going to stop you.
- They have no authority.
My orders come from God.
I'm not part of your congregation.
You have no right to be here.
You don't frighten me... Belial.
We'll see about that.
Murderer!
- We need to talk.
- What's wrong?
- He's performing another exorcism.
- How do you know?
Prentiss and I went to see
Matthew Benton's parents.
- I gave her a direct order.
- This one is all on me.
That's fine, Dave, by the state
department's all over my ass.
- Where's Prentiss now?
- She and Morgan went to stop it.
- I can't protect them.
- I don't accept that.
Governments don't really appreciate
being accused of accessory to murder.
- Why not go straight to the Vatican?
- What are we supposed to say to them?
Say, "Talk to the Italian government.
"Help us stop this man from
perverting your beliefs."
This comes down on all of us.
I'm fine with that? You?
You're a murderer! You're a murderer!
I abjure you!
- I will cast you out like the...
- You're a murderer!Murderer!
I abjure you
in the name of the spotless...
- Step away from him!
- FBI!
- Tremble and flee...
- Step away from him!
- As we call on the name of the lord.
- Step away.
- You have no right!
- This is my friend's house.
- This is not your friend!
- Murderer!
- Step away.
- Stop!
- What is in that bottle?
Out!
Don't protect him. They didn't
protect you when you were a little boy.
Give praise to the lord jesus christ.
John. I wanna untie you,
but I need you to calm down.
Look at me. It's Emily. John.
All right, I'm gonna untie you.
Just stay calm, OK?
Emily, come on. I'm fine.
No. Look at you.
Stress can tear your body apart.
That's what happened to Matthew.
Emily, I'm sorry I wasn't there for you.
In italy.
OK, just let them do their job.
Good-bye.
I'll check on you later.
If you want my gun and
badge, I understand.
There's a plane ticket
in your name to Rome.
Agent Morgan and I will
drive you to the airport.
Any of your belongings
can be shipped to you.
- You have no right to deport me.
- The vatican intervened.
The Italian government has
rescinded your diplomatic status.
They'll do with you as they see fit
when you're back in their jurisdiction.
You've all just made the world
a much more dangerous place.
I saw that guy up there.
He was certain he was fighting
against evil.
- We all have to be certain.
- Don't tell me you believe in evil.
Don't tell me you do
this job and you don't.
I believe there are evil acts,
but those are choices,
brain chemistry.
What do you think, Hotch?
I think deep down, we're all
capable of unspeakable things.
Where it starts or what you call it,
I don't know.
Let's get him out of here.
Always.
What are you thinking?
It's like The end of the dead...
When Gretta remembers the boy
she loved when she was younger
and she says...
I think he died for me.
You know, James Joyce also said,
"There is no heresy or philosophy so
abhorrent to the church
"as a human being."
Where can I drop you?
I'm gonna walk for a while.
Almost seems unreal, doesn't it?