We appeal to him,
do not hurt any more people.
He killed those people
because of something I said.
That's part of the job.
Tell me now if you can do it or not.
Jordan?
He just killed his entire family.
Is this my fault?
No way.
I'm not sure I can do this job.
It's up there, on the right.
Come on, son, it's time.
I know you're awake.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
There's something on your mind.
Tell us what it is.
What if she doesn't like me?
Let her get to know you.
There's no rush.
Is that really
what you're worried about?
Do I have to meet her this way?
We've been talking about
this moment your whole life.
- I know.
- Baby, look at me.
You're almost 10.
You're becoming a man.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Come on.
- What was it?
- Excuse me.
This isn't good.
A request from Alabama.
I'll be there in 10 min.
A couple was murdered at their home
while they were sleeping.
- Their daughter went missing.
- I gotta call you back.
- When were they discovered?
- Less than an hour.
- Time of death?
- Approximately 1 A.M.
- 8 h.
- This isn't a serial.
You're right. Most abducted children
don't survive past the first 24 hours.
What's going on?
A missing little girl, home invasion.
Parents were killed in their sleep.
- Where's our clock?
- 8 h.
- I tell Morgan and Reid we move.
- Good. Wheels-up in 30.
You need your go bag.
Right. Right.
Please let me go. Let me go.
I won't tell. Please.
It's OK.
We talked about this.
- Are you... are you thirsty?
- Please don't hurt me.
It's only water.
Can I decide now?
It's up to you.
I'm gonna call you...
Elena.
Transcript : www.ydy.com
Synchro: mpm
- Criminal Minds -
Season 04 Episode 13 Bloodline
Winston Churchill said,
"There is no doubt that it is around
the family and the home
"that all the greatest virtues
of human society
"are created, strengthened,
and maintained."
We got the uplinks of
the crime scene photos.
This is Geoff and Nancy Hale.
Both their throats were cut.
- Any evidence of abuse?
- Nothing.
Slitting someone's throat
is quick and efficient.
That's because the real target
was down the hall.
- She has a name.
- What?
She's not "the target".
Her name's Cate.
She's 10 years old.
All right.
Amber alert in effect?
Since 7 A. M. this morning.
With the unsub's head start he could be
anywhere within a 400-mile radius.
Make sure that they're casting
a wide enough net.
- Who discovered the bodies?
- Jim Scheuren, Cate's father.
He had to take her for the weekend.
The police don't consider him a suspect.
We'll want to talk to him anyway.
We need a list of registered
sex offenders in a 20-mile radius.
- What's the makeup of the neighborhood?
- Mostly white and middle class.
We'll need aerial views.
If Madison county doesn't have them,
talk to Garcia.
Dave and Morgan, go to the crime scene.
We'll get up to speed at the precinct.
Bo Whitaker.
- David Rossi.
- I recognize you from the TV.
- Derek Morgan.
- Bo Whitaker. Pleased to meet you.
Point of entry's around back.
Now, the neighbors
didn't see or hear anything.
And the dogs lost the scent
almost immediately.
Not hard to target
a family out here.
Even in broad daylight.
Walk 5 feet off the track,
man could get lost for days.
So, he had plenty of privacy
to watch what he was really after.
I prefer cities.
You can see them coming.
Nothing very sophisticated.
Knocked off the pane
to unlock the door.
- Do you think the girl's dead?
- Depends on what he took her for.
The Hales' neighborhood is a series
of rural roads and one-block streets.
- How far to a main thoroughfare?
- A little over 3 miles.
So he didn't come upon
Cate by accident. Sheriff Bates.
- Is Cate's father here yet?
- He's on his way.
- Let me know the second he gets here.
- We already checked out his alibi.
- He's not good for this.
- I know, but he might know who is.
All right.
Is that the autopsy report?
- Listen, about the plane...
- That's already forgotten.
- Find anything in Cate's room?
- That's what's weird.
No sign of struggle. It didn't look like
she tried to get out of bed in a hurry.
Her parents' throats were cut.
If there was the element of surprise,
- they didn't have time to scream.
- Both of them?
- What are you looking for?
- The neck wounds...
Something's off.
I'm the unsub.
I kill Geoff Hale first.
He presents the biggest threat.
But how do I do that without waking
Nancy who's sleeping right next to him?
No ligature marks.
Neither one was tied down.
And no defensive wounds, either.
Geoff Hale, cause of death
was a single deep, smooth cut
- that severed the carotid artery.
- And Nancy?
Nancy Hale, death was caused
by a series of jagged,
shallow wounds that
punctured the carotid artery.
- There's more than one unsub.
- You're sure?
He was either able to restrain Nancy
while he killed Geoff,
or she woke up,
and she would have screamed.
At which point,
Cate would have woken up.
- We're looking at multiple unsubs.
- So things are worse than we thought.
Yes and no.
Cate's chances of survival
just got better.
- How do you figure?
- Two unsubs change the dynamics.
- What do you mean, dynamics?
- They spent more time with her.
Yeah, Prentiss has the same theory
based on the autopsy report.
We're about to speak to Cate's father.
Stay at the scene.
- I'll call you back.
- Dad's in there.
Sheriff, alert your men.
We may be looking at a team.
I'll get it on the wire.
- How's the father?
- Between you and me,
I've cleaned up bar fights smell
better than he does right now.
Mr. Scheuren. I'm Aaron hochner.
I'm with the FBI.
Can I get you anything? Coffee?
No, no. I can answer your questions.
Do you know if your ex-wife
and her husband have any enemies?
I mean, I don't know.
I don't... I don't know. I...
What about Cate? Has she talked
about anyone new in her life?
She's a normal kid, you know?
She... meets people all the time.
This would be an adult,
possibly a white male.
He might be an authority
figure to her.
The reason that I ask is that given
the location of your ex-wife's house,
we think someone has targeted
Cate specifically.
Sorry.
Is there anything that you
can think of that might be helpful?
We like to go to the movies.
There's a new multiplex at the mall.
How often do you see Cate?
- I have visitation every 2 weeks.
- Do you keep to that schedule?
The reason that I ask is that
right now time is of the essence.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- With all due respect, sir,
it means that if you can't add
to my knowledge of Cate,
my time is better
spent somewhere else.
I'll keep you posted
with any developments.
- Agent...
- Yes?
There's one thing...
Hold on a second.
I'm right here.
Hotch, I got it.
OK, bring it with you when you
come to the station. Thanks.
- What's going on?
- Cate Hale has epilepsy,
and whoever abducted her
didn't know to take the medicine.
And the primary cause
of seizures is stress.
- Remember what I said.
- I know, Dad.
Just concentrate. He shouldn't
even realize you're there.
I know.
Go ahead.
Chin up. This isn't
something you learn overnight.
I'm ready now.
You need to master it here first.
Now try it again.
- No, no! Don't touch her.
- What's wrong with her?
- Can you hear me?
- Don't go near her.
- She's sick.
- She's no good.
We have to do something.
You're right.
We don't kill young girls.
This is my family.
Then you kill her.
Help!
Help! Somebody!
Her father's with her. She's been in and
out of consciousness, but she's stable.
- Sexual assault?
- We haven't tested yet.
- We want to give her time to process.
- May we speak with her?
You should know, seizures often
come with retrograde amnesia.
She might have holes in her memory.
- Prentiss, you should do this alone.
- OK.
Thanks, sheriff.
Mr. Scheuren, hello.
I'm agent Emily Prentiss
from the FBI.
I would like permission
to speak with your daughter.
I'm sorry, I'd like to do it
alone if possible.
- Why?
- I need to ask her certain questions,
and sometimes it's easier for a girl
to answer those questions
- when there are no men present.
- I'm her father.
Please?
All right, baby.
I'll be right outside.
Thank you.
My name's Emily.
I'm so sorry about
your mom and your stepdad.
I'd like to ask you some questions
so we can find out
who did this, is that OK?
Yeah, it's OK.
The doctor told me that if they
hadn't been alerted to her epilepsy,
she might not have made it.
You helped save her life.
You seen this kind of thing before?
- Unfortunately.
- And kids come out of it OK?
It'll take time.
And patience.
She's going to need you.
Yesterday would have been the first
time I'd seen her in a month and a half.
A colleague of mine asked me
how my son was enjoying
the Christmas present he got for him,
and I had to make up an
answer because I didn't know.
I think I'll get
that cup of coffee now.
The police sent the blanket
and Cate's clothing to be processed.
Good.
- Garcia.
- Captain, my captain.
I need a list of crimes involving
partners within a 90-mile radius
of Harvest in the last 2 years.
- All crimes?
- Anything. Violent crimes,
break-ins, whatever's in the system.
I need to show Cate some mugshots.
You got it. One scumbag
yearbook coming up.
So you think they're local?
They dumped Cate 84 miles
from her home.
The sheriff who found her didn't
think that she'd been there long.
With the unsubs' head start,
they should have been long gone.
So we're zeroing in on them.
- Possibly.
- Then what's wrong?
I don't know why
they left her alive.
I'm going to do what's
called a cognitive interview.
It's as much about the things
you sensed as the things you saw.
I'm scared.
I know. That's OK.
I'm right here with you.
I'm here all the way.
Now, I need you to close your eyes.
What is the first thing
you remember?
It's cold.
You're outside?
Who's there?
A man. He told me to...
Keep quiet.
- What is he doing?
- He's holding my hand. It hurts.
He's waiting for something.
- What does he look like?
- I don't want to be here.
He can't hurt you,
I promise. I'm right here.
Tall. Dark hair. Old.
- Old? Old like me?
- Old like my dad.
Is anyone else there?
Someone's coming! Emily!
Emily, help me!
- Open the trunk!
- Help me!
OK, it's OK. I'm right here.
I promise you he cannot hurt you.
It's OK.
So he put you
in the trunk of the car?
Open the trunk!
- How long were you in there?
- I don't know. Not long.
10 minutes.
Was the ride bumpy or smooth?
It was smooth.
I wanted to scream,
- but no sound would come out.
- It's OK.
So the car stops,
and they open the trunk.
What do you hear?
Wind. Wind through the trees.
And what do you smell?
Cooking.
- Are you inside now?
- They've taken my shoes off.
That's so you won't run.
I want you to look down at your feet
and tell me what you're standing on.
Carpet.
I'm in a little room.
With clothes and tinfoil
all around me.
What else?
- I... I hear bells.
- What kind of bells?
Small. Like a fairy.
Every time they ring,
the man says something to the boy.
The boy?
He's standing right next to you.
How old is he?
I'm 9. Almost 10.
Puyule, come here.
- His parents want me to play with him.
- His parents?
Emily, I don't want to go.
I don't want to go. No!
Don't make me go!
Emily, no!
It's OK, I'm right here.
It's OK. It's OK.
Cate, open your eyes.
You did a really good job.
Mr. Scheuren, you have
an incredibly strong little girl.
- Did he touch her?
- No, no. Not in that way, no.
Thank God.
She was taken by a family.
A family?
Parents and a little boy
about her age.
They took her from her house
in a car and then into an RV.
A short ride on a road
and then into a wooded area.
Anything else?
She said the mother
called the boy puyule,
which I think is a Romanian term
of endearment.
I know I used to hear it
when my mom was posted overseas.
Get Rossi and Morgan
on the closest RV parks.
What are we looking at here?
I have no idea.
Most people pay in cash. We don't have
much in the way of records.
Ma'am, this was a family...
mother, father, small boy.
They would have kept to
themselves and left abruptly.
You just described
most of my business.
The son wouldn't have
mingled with other children.
He would have been tightly
guarded by his parents.
Sorry. I wish I could help.
The family we're talking
about is Eastern European.
They may have spoken some
foreign words to each other.
- They're in some kind of trouble?
- You remember them.
You can imagine I don't get a lot
of people speaking foreign around here.
What can you tell us about them?
Not much. The husband
was real businesslike.
Wife was nice, pretty.
Son was quiet.
A license or a credit card?
Left in the night and never came back.
I wouldn't have thought twice about it
it if I didn't have to clean up
the campsite from all the glass.
Glass?
All over the ground.
Almost like they did it on purpose.
Can you show us where they parked?
I told you, you're
not gonna find nothin'.
I cleaned it up.
Well, thank you.
Jordan was right,
you know, on the plane.
- What are you talking about?
- We hide behind language.
We don't talk about
the ugliness we see.
We talk about it every day.
No. We talk facts.
Signature, m.o, pathology.
What are you getting at?
We're working a case where a family
is grooming their son to kill.
They're not murdering people. They're
stealing children, poisoning minds.
Where's the horror?
We can't do this job
if we let it get to us.
Exactly.
Is it a match?
Which means the RV park owner was right.
They spread it on purpose.
So everything they do
is part of some ritual.
Have you ever seen
anything like this before?
A family that ritualizes
killing together? Definitely not.
You know, if the family speaks Romanian,
the spreading of the glass makes sense.
It's an eastern European
superstition for good luck.
- They're Romanian. We knew that.
- Not just Romanian.
We're talking about people that are
superstitious and obsessed with ritual.
Romany.
- Romany?
- Gypsies.
More accurately, someone who
has perverted Romany culture.
Call Garcia. They're tight-knit
and nomadic like our unsubs,
- but not usually prone to violence.
- Hiya, baby.
- Hey, baby girl, we need to talk.
- Pg or nc-17?
- You're on speaker phone.
- I charge extra for groups.
Run through crimes similar
to the Hale murders in the last 2 years.
- I already did that. Zip.
- Go back even further, Garcia.
Cross-reference against any small towns
that have had reports of petty theft
associated with waves of Romany
populations entering the area.
- Romany?
- Gypsies.
- As in "gypsies, tramps, and thieves"?
- Exactly.
Bless you all for turning
my life into a Cher song.
- You'll have it nearly immediately.
- You're the best.
You need to get your
men together right now.
Why?
'Cause whatever ritual these
people are trying to play out,
we know Cate Hale
didn't fit their needs.
Which means
they'll have to try again.
- It's too soon.
- He turns 10 in a week.
It's not safe.
You see one you like?
She's a fine choice.
The unsubs we're looking for
are a family.
A father, a mother, and a son,
approximately 10 years old.
We believe they're
of Romanian descent.
The family travels in an RV,
but they also have another vehicle
that they use to go back and
forth between campsites and cities.
We need you to call
every RV park in the area.
Alert the owners to be on the lookout
for a family that fits this description,
As well as a campsite that might
have broken glass scattered around.
The breaking of the glass
and the discarding of Cate Hale
because of her epilepsy
leads us to believe that they're
highly superstitious people
And that they are playing
out a very specific ritual.
The focus of this ritual
is the young girls.
- Do we know why?
- No.
But we do know from
the location of Cate Hale's house
that they don't come across
these girls by accident.
They study. They hunt.
Cate's father said that she liked to go
to the movies at their local multiplex.
- That's a good place to start.
- Also look at the parks, malls.
Concentrate on those that are an easy
drive from the RV parks you locate.
This family is out there and they're
looking for their next victim.
You guys need to see this right now.
Excuse us.
- What's going on?
- Garcia, you still there?
- Present.
- Explain what you got.
OK, I went ahead and went
further back looking for similar cases
- and I made the search national.
- All these are hits?
There's 30 of them.
They go as far back as 1909.
Rapid City, South Dakota,
Taos, New Mexico, Gary, Indiana.
My map is lit up
like a Christmas tree.
All these girls were abducted
and had their parents killed?
The time between the kills was long
enough and the regions so spread out
- that it never showed up as serial.
- What the hell is this?
I don't know, but it looks like
it's been going on for generations.
Reid and I will check inside.
Our highway patrol shifts're doubled and
we've got roadblocks at every line.
- Is there a picture on the wire?
- I pulled one out of her bedroom.
- They're bound to have hours on us.
- They didn't travel that far last time.
The past killings have been years apart.
We got lucky with Cate Hale.
Her epilepsy saved her life.
If this new girl fits
the unsub's need,
we might have lost our window
to catch them for years.
This is what I don't get.
In both this house
and the Hales' house
the girls' bedrooms
were closest to the exit.
The unsubs had to go out of their way
to kill the parents before abducting.
- I think it was a countermeasure.
- What do you mean?
They've been doing this for years
and they've never been caught.
- Why?
- They disappear in the dead of night,
they have a head start on the cops,
and they don't kill again for years.
Exactly.
When I was a cop, I would get 10 calls
a day from parents in child abductions.
Now, as sad as that is, if the families
didn't stay on you, at a certain point,
other cases would just
start taking priority.
So what are they doing
with these girls?
- What do you got, baby girl?
- Are you sitting down?
- You won't believe this.
- What's wrong?
I think I know what they
were doing with the girls.
Garcia got a hit on a hair fiber in the
blanket the unsubs used to wrap Cate.
So what's the problem?
- It belonged to Kathy Gray.
- Why does that name sound familiar?
She went missing in 1971
after her parents were murdered.
So this little girl
- is one of our unsubs?
- That's what it looks like.
Call Hotch. Tell him and Prentiss not to
come here and to meet us at the station.
You OK?
Yeah. I just need
to build a tacker skin.
You don't need to do anything
you don't want to. You understand?
So these little girls got abducted
and later kidnapped other girls
and killed their families?
I think that's why these unsubs
pick girls the same age as the boy.
What do you mean?
They're making wives.
It's OK.
I know what you're going through.
I understand. I really do.
Come here. I'm going to
take this off you now. OK?
Come here.
- I want my mommy.
- No, no, no, everything's OK.
You're a part of something now.
I was just like you.
A working theory from 1971 was
that a transient killed the family
and abducted Kathy Gray.
Then all the leads went cold.
How do you watch your family get murdered
and make a life with the murderers?
It's Stockholm syndrome.
You adapt or die.
And now she's training
her son to be a murderer.
At a certain point, once traditions are
handed down generation after generation,
there is no right or wrong. You simply
accept the way the world works.
The Romany are a closed society.
The unsub simply twisted and distorted
traditions to become entirely insular.
Abducting the children
keeps the bloodline pure,
and killing the parents ensures that
people eventually stop looking for them.
We got a report of an RV on fire
about 20 miles from here.
Dave, you, Reid, and Morgan
go check it out.
Garcia, I need you to digitally
alter Kathy Gray's photograph
to simulate what she would
look like today.
- Consider it simulated.
- Thanks.
It was started less than an hour ago,
so they can't be far.
It looks like
they left almost everything.
The got the girl they wanted.
They're starting over.
Look at the clothes. Most of them
still have the store sensors on them.
How'd they get them
past security scanners?
- Tinfoil.
- Excuse me?
Cate remembers being locked in a closet
surrounded by clothing and tinfoil.
Shoplifters use tinfoil to line
their bags and negate security alarms.
Makes sense. A lot of Romany make
their living as petty thieves.
It also explains
the bells she heard.
Cate says she remembers
hearing the sound of bells,
Followed directly by the father
talking to the son.
I think that's probably
what the mannequin's for.
School of the 7 bells.
You dress a mannequin,
you line a suit with 7 bells.
If you pick his pocket without a bell
ringing, you're ready to work a crowd.
- So we know how they make their money.
- That's not all we know.
These unsubs are guided
entirely by ritual.
They abducted Lynn Robillard
and killed her family in an area
that was surrounded
by police and the FBI.
They had to. They can't deviate.
We also know that they're starting over.
So they're gonna need some money.
- Where's the closest shopping mall?
- About 15 miles from here.
Hey, Hotch, we know
where they're going.
Focus on the high-end department
stores. They're bigger targets.
Mom.
Is this you?
Ma'am!
Hold it! Police!
Set those bags down, right now.
Kathy Gray! Take that woman!
- I said put the bags down.
- Cuff her.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
They've been stealing for years
and they never get caught.
This was too easy.
Kathy, I can't help you if you're
not going to be honest with me.
I already told you, I killed them.
- All by yourself.
- Yes.
- That's not true.
- It is.
How did you do it?
How did you abduct a child and control
two adults while you slit their throats?
You know she's not
responsible for this.
I know we have a string of bodies, and
she knows where her husband and son are.
- You are the victim here.
- No. She killed innocent people.
- Her family was murdered.
- And now she's killing other people's.
- Kathy, this is not your fault.
- My name isn't Kathy. It's Sylvia.
No, it isn't.
Your name is Kathy Gray.
And you were
a beautiful little girl.
Your mom and dad were murdered
and you were kidnapped.
Do you recognize yourself there?
- You see?
- I'm sick of this!
- Then leave us alone!
- Where are they?
Look at me. Don't listen to him.
They stole your life.
Let me help you get it back.
That little girl is better
off with my son
than any man she could
meet in your society.
I'm sure you raised him very well.
- Tell me about your own mother.
- I've already told you everything.
- I killed them, all by myself.
- How's it going so far?
They're trying to crack her by reminding
her of the girl she used to be.
I hope this good cop/bad cop
routine works.
If her family gets away,
we've lost that little girl forever.
You're lying.
- Kathy...
- My name isn't Kathy!
Yes, it is. Your name is Kathy Gray.
You're from Vienna, Virginia.
Tell me where your husband and son are
so I can help you get your life back.
- Want to see what you did?
- Don't show her.
If she killed them,
she can see it again.
Serial killers like to relive
their crimes. Did you know that?
This is Geoff Hale.
He died from a strong, decisive cut.
I think that was your husband.
Nancy Hale, her wound was more
tentative. This was your son, right?
I'm sure by the time he teaches his own
son how to kill, his hand'll be steady.
- This is the Robillard family.
- Kathy, you don't have to look at that.
Do you want to see some more?
- I don't know what that is.
- Then look closely!
You don't recognize
your own mother and father?
See? This is the tentative
cut your future husband made
while he slit your mother's throat.
Where are your husband and son?
Cate Hale is only alive because
of you, Kathy. Isn't that...
your... your husband wanted
to kill her, and you didn't.
How does that make you feel?
To know that he was willing
to kill that little girl?
That he would have been
willing to kill you, too?
They murdered your family, Kathy,
and they took you in,
but you were never really one of them.
- You were just a breeder.
- I won't betray my family.
Your little boy is only 10.
There is a chance
he could get
out of custody when he's 18,
but that's only if we get to him.
I love my family.
- She's ready.
- Then tell us where your son is
and we can all help him together.
- Scott woodland, Zander Blanchard...
- OK, come on, give her a second.
- Max Estep, Chip Jackson.
- I don't know who those people are.
It's a list of every
known fence in Huntsville.
And you're gonna tell us who
your husband took the goods to.
- Coles Rudzinski, Pete Shernit,
- Let her do the right thing.
- Matt Thorne, Brent Woodhouse...
- OK, I can't stop him, Kathy.
This is your last chance
to make things right.
Kevin Everson, Mike Fenner,
- Morris Collins...
- Stop!
- I won't tell you.
- You just did.
The boy's not with him.
Where are the children?
I'll only tell you
if you let me see my son.
FBI! Hands in the air!
Hands in the air!
Get on your knees!
Down on the ground! Now!
We got a long list of girls
to go through with you.
In history, warriors invaded towns,
killed the men, women, and boys,
but kept the girls for themselves.
You exist because your ancestors did
what was needed for you to survive.
- Get him out of here.
- You'll never find my boy!
We already have.
Come on, come on.
It's just you now.
You're going to be strong.
I love you, puyule.
Nu le spunelor despre furititai.
What did you tell him?
Sheriff, get that videotape.
We need to get it to a translator.
You got it.
The translation should be
here in a few minutes.
The little girl's aunt and uncle are
on their way here from Birmingham.
They'll be here in a few hours.
And also, I just spoke with J.J.
She'll be at her desk by the time
we get back to Quantico.
- She has 3 more weeks.
- I know, but she's getting to be back.
And, honestly, I'm...
Ready to get back to counter-terrorism.
It's where I'm needed.
They're lucky to have you.
- May I say something?
- Sure.
This team is like a family.
And families take on
the traits of their leaders.
- You don't show much emotion.
- Meaning what?
I've sat at J.J's desk and I've looked
at the worst things I've ever seen
just trying to do half her job.
I hope you don't
take her for granted.
I don't.
- We got the translation.
- What did she say?
"Don't tell them
about your brothers."
How many brothers do you have?
Mario Puzo wrote,
"The strength of a family,
"like the strength of an army,
is in its loyalty to each other".
You're almost 10.
You're becoming a man.
Are you ready?
I love you, puyule.
I love you, too.