Previously on
"criminal minds"...
The boston reaper?
the reaper.
If you stop hunting me,
I'll stop hunting them.
I don't make deals.
i'm the guy
Who hunts guys like you.
You'll regret this.
You should have
made a deal.
[gunshot]
Are you sure
that we're in danger?
Yes.
Tell them i'll protect them
like they're my own.
I'm not leaving
the team,
I'm just no longer
in charge.
Me?
you are.
George foyet
was the ninth victim
And the only one
who survived
the reaper.
He inflicted those
wounds on himself.
George foyet
is the reaper.
One of the inmates
has received 2 envelopes
I'll get this to the lab.
in the last 2 days.
He's torturing him.
It's great to see you
squirm, agent hotchner.
[prisoners shouting]
[sirens]
Get out of here.
Go see if they need
help downstairs.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Hotch:
"he who fights with monsters
"might take care lest
he thereby become a monster.
"and if you gaze
for long into an abyss,
The abyss gazes
also into you."
Friedrich nietzsche.
Please say your name and rank
for the record.
Supervisory special agent
jennifer jareau,
Communications liaison
for the behavioral
analysis unit
In quantico, virginia.
And how long have you
been a member of the bau?
6 years.
Could you speak up, please?
[clears throat]
sorry. 6 years.
And have you worked under
agent hotchner the entire time?
No, ma'am. i currently
Report to acting unit chief
derek morgan.
Who took over the unit
because agent hotchner's
Ability to lead the team
had become compromised.
I--i don't believe
that's the reason.
You have
a different opinion?
It's not just an opinion.
You have a different
understanding?
Ssa hotchner voluntarily
stepped down
So we could continue
to do our jobs unhindered.
How would you describe agent
hotchner's recent behavior?
Driven.
Driven. agent jareau,
your entire team is on the line
If i cannot reconcile
an adequate account
Of agent hotchner's
investigation into george foyet.
We were all investigating
the reaper.
Ssa hotchner
was not the only one,
Especially after he sent us
that calling card.
The newspaper articles
he mailed to karl arnold.
2 letters from
2 different locations.
They ramped us all
back up again.
I should just start
at the beginning.
Foyet had done a lot
of injury to himself
In the original
string of killings,
In an effort to paint
himself as a victim
And throw us off
the investigation.
As a result,
he became dependent upon
A large number of extremely
strong medications.
We'd been searching
the country for patients
With that exact
prescription combination,
But we hadn't had any luck.
The envelopes foyet mailed
to arnold are due back
from the lab.
They're flagged urgent.
Gina's here with them now.
They're processed. clean.
no prints, no dna.
She says they're clean.
Yeah, of course they are.
Anderson, listen to me.
I don't care
if you have to drive
To the postmaster general's
house.
I want to know where
those postmarks were applied
Before the team gets in.
Yes, ma'am. copy that.
Found it.
He's still not taking
his bottle.
Here. let me try.
Hey...
Can you take
your bottle, please?
Can you take--oh...
Thank you so much.
Oh, yeah. you are definitely
mama's little boy, huh?
Just like his ddy.
Pharmacist: next.
Hey, if you have to go,
go ahead.
I can take care of this.
I don't know what i would do
if i were in hotch's shoes.
If i ever had to say good-bye
to you and henry because--
We'rnot going anywhere.
We're not.
You're tracking
the prescriptions,
the postmarks.
Aside from another body
landing on your doorstep,
You're doing all you can.
I hope so,
For hotch's sake.
Next.
That's us.
Here we are.
Oh, actually, there should be
2 prescriptions.
We filled the antibiotics,
But we're out of
the antihistamine.
You know, crushing
half a claritin
Would do the job
just the same.
Save you a couple bucks,
too.
Wait--excuse me,
Are there a lot
Of over-the-counter
medications
That can be substituted
for prescriptions?
Too many to count.
Most of the time,
it's just a matter of dosage.
Foyet's meds--we have been
tracking the entire
combination.
What if he's been using
over-the-counter meds
For some of it
to mask his purchases?
Ok, narrow the search.
focus on the meds
He can't substitute.
good work.
[knock on door]
just got a call
From the postmaster general
inspector's office.
Already?
I'm not just a pretty face.
Is garcia in yet?
Are you sure?
Bacon doughnut.
you'll never be the same.
I can totally think of
more palatable ways
To up my adventure quotient,
thank you.
O...m...g.
It gets better
every time.
Kevin, you need to leave
right now.
Would you like some water?
No, thank you, ma'am.
Are you all right?
I--i'm just not, uh,
Comfortable
with any of this.
It's not ok.
What do you mean?
In my opinion,
Everyone is asking
the wrong questions.
Doesn't anybody care
About what the reaper
did to them,
How many people he hurt?
All anyone seems
to care about is...
This just isn't right.
Do you think that
agent hotchner was acting...
Agitated or unreasonable?
He...
No, no, he--
He was freaked out
about his family.
Which, considering
what happened,
I'd say was perfectly
reasonable.
The foyet letters came from
fredericksburg, virginia,
And westminster, maryland.
We can match
the prescription drugs
Foyet can't substitute
with a geographic profile
Of the 2 cities.
Can't substitute?
We need you to track
the drugs that can't be emulated
With over-the-counter drugs
and can only be dispensed
By a pharmacist, and you
need to do it quickly.
Foyet doesn't stay
in one place very long.
Then kevin needs to stay.
What?
sir, kevin is
an amazing analyst.
I can work almost
twice as fast
Fine.
with him running
part of my system.
Garcia, now long?
these are your screens.
I'll know once i get
into it.
We're gonna work
the geographic profile.
Call me when you have
something. and hurry.
Uh, ok...
I am gonna start
with the ultram--
No--you're gonna start
with the ultram and naproxen.
I'll work on the rest.
There's approximately
115 miles
Between fredericksburg
and westminster.
Why mail a letter from 2 cities?
Maybe it's purely
a forensic countermeasure.
He knows that mailing
letters close to home
would lead us right to him,
So he drives far away
to mail the letters
to throw us off his scent.
The unabomber did that.
so did the 2001 anthrax suspect.
He could have gone anywhere,
but he's trolling the d.c. area.
It makes sense
to stay close to hotch.
He stuck around boston
to watch shaunessy deteriorate.
Not that you're--
It's all right.
i know he's been watching me.
It's part of the reason
i stepped down,
So he'd think
i was falling apart.
Naproxen is available
in generic brands
over the counter.
Naproxen's properties
can be simulated by aleve.
Ultram can be substituted.
Ok, oxycontin.
Jeez, he's on that, too?
Yeah, and it's highladdictive
and therefore regulated,
So there's no substitute for it.
I know the dea
has a problem with it.
You can buy it
on the streets if
you know where to go.
Good point. ok, we're gonna
leave that off the list for now
'cause there's another way
to get it. next up...
Tapazole.
What's that?
Uh, it treats hyperthyroidism.
Hey, what's wrong
with this guy, anyway?
He stabbed himself--a lot.
Stabbed himself?
Yeah. so his body would have
permanent internal damage--
Work, honey--and he'd need
This prescription
to regulate his heart rate,
Keep down the palpitations
and the tremors.
And there is no substitute
for tapazole.
So if this is our missing
link, how do we find him?
Print out every person
who's on this prescription
Within a 60-mile of both cities.
the team will do the rest.
I'm gonna use your laptop.
Ok, so what are we gonna do
about the 2 cities?
Usually we need 3 different
points to get an accurate
geographic profile.
That's all we got right now.
Prentiss:
gaithersburg, rockville,
D.c., alexandria,
Bowie, annapolis.
Where the hell are you,
foyet?
Ok, me and the boy
found a thyroid medication
That has no substitute
over the counter.
You've gotta get it
from a pharmacist.
But a lot of people
are on it.
Find the midpoint
between the 2 cities
And isolate names
in a 25-mile radius.
153 names.
Well, he's not gonna use
his own name.
What kind of aliases
should we be looking for?
He could have easily
stolen someone's identity.
No, he's a narcissist
in love with
his own mythology.
He'd use a name
connected with the case.
A victim, maybe,
a cop.
Ok. let's check
the foyet files
For a list of names. and...
Nothing.
Wait a minute, guys.
foyet likes things
to have meaning to him.
The eye of providence,
The addresses in blood
he wrote on the bus
that led us back to him.
Maybe he's doing the same
thing with the alias.
Like an anagram
or something.
You see something, reid?
Not yet.
Reid, he named himself
the reaper.
Peter rhea.
There's a peter rhea
in arlington.
Rossi: we found him.
Once the team located
George foyet's
potential apartment,
Why didn't the bau
enter immediately?
Agent rossi?
Hmm?
I asked you a question.
Gold is still going up.
But knowing when to get out,
that's the trick.
[turns off recorder]
What are you doing?
What's the point
of all this, erin?
Why?
So this never happens again.
There is nothing
a bureaucrat can do
To make sure that
something like this
never happens again.
So we just wait
for the next bloodbath?
[turns on recorder]
Why did you wait so long
before going to foyet's
apartment?
We had to be sure
he was there.
If we went in
and he wasn't,
He would know
we found him.
Of course,
the longer we waited,
The more time he had to...
It was an impossible
decision.
So who made it?
Agent hotchner?
How much longer
do we wait?
I need to leave that call
to someone else.
Swat's getting antsy.
I'll tell them
when it's time to go.
Right now we sit tight.
let them know.
These guys are trained
to move, not just sit around.
I can't really
say that i blame them.
He may not even
be there anymore.
I know. the longer
we sit here,
the further away he gets.
You make the best call
you can, kid.
All right, this is what
we're gonna do.
Super.
There's a leak
in the apartment above you.
I need to check your ceiling.
Are you getting the signal?
Copy.
No warm bodies.
Looks like kitchen table,
chair.
Is that a laptop
on the table?
It could be useful.
Rossi: is that food?
get closer to that.
Wait, go back.
what's that on the floor?
Yeah.
it's his mail.
Go, go, go, go!
Hurry up!
let's go!
What happened?
He's not coming back here.
he left an untouched meal.
You drop your mail like this
when you're startled,
When you need to get out
of dodge quick.
Something tipped him off.
he knew we were coming here.
Suitcases are open,
some clothes are missing.
There's a safe with
a stash of guns in it.
He didn't even bother
to lock them up again.
If he's in a hurry,
he'll make a mistake.
Yeah, but when
foyet gets cornered,
He starts killing.
We're not gonna
let that happen.
We need to get garcia
on this.
He is creepy good.
How good?
He wiped his hard drive.
might have been
in a hurry to leave,
But whatever was on there,
he did not want us to see it.
Garcia, tell me that
you're hacked in and
that you can rebuild it.
Watch me work, darling.
Hello.
[beeping]
What have you got?
He had an internet alarm
on the name peter rhea.
It alerted him as soon as
we ran a check on it.
What else did he wipe?
Garcia, wait a minute.
freeze it right there.
Oh, my god,
isn't that--
That's the u.s. marshal
assigned to my family.
Foyet's been watching him
this whole time?
Voicemail:
kassmeyer. leave a message.
Sam, it's aaron.
we found foyet's location,
But he has surveillance
photos of you.
Call me for a meet location
or we're on our way to you.
We're gonna need to deploy
another swat unit.
That's gonna take
another half hour.
Hotch?
Go. go.
You left for marshal kassmeyer's
house immediately?
Yes, ma'am.
Wouldn't this be a job
for a tactical team?
We felt that it would
take too much time
To get authorization
for another operation.
We?
All of us.
Don't you mean agent hotchner
wanted that?
No, i mean all of us
wanted that.
I know what
you're thinking,
And i agree it would be
easy for us to blame him.
Easy?
Yeah. why not just
say it's his fault
And then we can all
just forget about it.
But, uh, the problem is,
I have an eidetic memory,
And that's not
what happened.
Sam.
This is agent rossi, fbi.
we need an ambulance.
We have a federal
officer down.
I wouldn't...i wouldn't...
We're getting an ambulance.
I tried.
hang on.
Just hang on.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
I...i tried.
Are jack and haley safe?
[breathing hard]
Sam, tell me
what happened.
I don't know how
he got in.
Aah!
Where are they?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Aah!
I'm gonna find out...
One way or another.
ohh!
Sam, i need to understand.
Does he know where
jack and haley are?
I didn't...
This little piggy...
Aah!
Look at that. he's not
going anywhere, is he?
What about her phone number?
what's her safe phone number?
I didn't...it won't matter.
Kill me. i'm not telling you
anything.
You're not gonna get off
that easy.
I need you alive
so you can tell
agent hotchner
That it's his fault
that his family's dead.
Aah!
I--i tried, hotch.
[breathing hard]
Gunshot wounds to each leg,
one foot,
He's missing several fingers,
and appears to be badly beaten.
Clear out of the way.
Get me a c-collar,
prep me a saline drip
While i grab a round of vitals.
Sam, are you allergic
to any medication?
Hotch.
Sam, i'm right here.
I tried.
Make sure they have
a trauma surgeon standing by.
Strauss: do you believe
it was marshal kassmeyer's fault
That agent hotchner's family
was compromised?
Absolutely not.
You answered that
very quickly.
When you're being tortured,
there's no end in sight,
Except giving them
what they want.
And kassmeyer didn't do that?
He withstood everything
that foyet had.
Then tell me
exactly what happened.
Is he conscious?
In and out.
Sam, it's aaron.
Can you hear me?
[siren]
I'm right here, sam.
aaron.
His pressure's dropping.
10cc morphine
going in.
Do not sedate me.
i need to talk.
Sam, does foyet know
where jack and haley are?
I wouldn't tell him.
it doesn't matter.
Let me guess.
The marshals service
Doesn't have anything
listed by name.
Case numbers only.
The thing is,
This relocation is
a bit of a special favor,
Which tells me that you might
bring your work home with you.
Who knows? maybe even
on emergency speed dial.
[clicks tongue]
Hello, haley?
I'm sorry. wrong number.
Hello, is haley there?
Uh, uh, no, ma'am.
i'm sorry.
It must have been
a wrong number.
Hello, is haley there?
Hello, haley?
Sam?
Haley.
Ohh--hal--
Uhh!
Sorry for using
your real name, ma'am.
My name is victor collins.
i'm with the marshals service.
Ma'am, we have a problem.
Marshal kassmeyer
has been killed,
And we're afraid your location
may have been compromised.
What?
Ma'am, i need you
to focus right now.
this is about saving your son.
We're trying to save jack.
do you understand me?
Yes.
I'm afraid there's more, ma'am.
I'm not quite sure
how to tell you this, but...
Your ex-husband
has been killed as well.
Oh, god.
We're gonna bring
you and your son in safe,
But i'm gonna need
your help for this, ok?
When we're through speaking,
i want you to hang up the phone.
Do not attempt to call
anybody else.
Do you understand me?
it could be intercepted.
Yes.
The next thing i need you to do
Is buy a disposable cell phone.
Get back in your car,
call me at this number.
Once i know your mobile,
i'll give you another number
Along with some instructions
on how to proceed.
Ok.
Now, ma'am,
i do not want you to worry.
We're gonna bring you and jack
in here safely.
Are you...
Are you sure aaron is...
Are you sure?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm terribly sorry.
[tosses cell phone on table]
See you later.
Ok.
[breathing hard]
She's going to him.
I'm so sorry, hotch.
[beeping]
[flatline tone]
They're ready for you.
Agent prentiss.
Ma'am.
We understand
that agent hotchner
Managed to separate himself
from the rest of the team.
He didn't "manage"
to do that.
When marshal kassmeyer
was in the ambulance--
Agent hotchner volunteered
to ride along.
To get answers before
he lost consciousness.
Why didn't you
go with him?
It didn't seem necessary.
Did you tell you that?
Is that what
you're looking for,
A way to blame this
on him?
What good could that
possibly do?
Agent hotchner was looking
for an opportunity
To separate himself
from the team
and he found one.
That isn't true.
He was desperate
and he didn't want someone
With a clear head
to stop him.
Is there a question
in there somewhere?
Tell me what happened
while agent hotchner
was in the ambulance.
We contacted
the u.s. marshals.
They said haley
was in the wind.
She had dumped
her cell phone,
So there was no way
to track her.
And how did agent hotchner
react to that news?
Foyet called haley
from kassmeyer's phone.
All right, we'll get
garcia to trace it. jj.
He told her she was
compromised and i was dead.
Well, have you called her?
No. he said to throw
her phone away
and to buy a disposable.
Hotch, we're gonna
come get you right now.
No, anderson's
bringing me a car.
You want to meet
back at the office?
I'm hoping that she's just gonna
call me, at least, to check.
Foyet posed as a marshal,
even called from a number
that haley recognized.
And then he did
what gets him off.
he scared her.
Prentiss: no, he paralyzed
her. he overwhelmed her.
And now she trusts him.
where do you think
he would take her?
Witness protection had her
living in new jersey.
He has a head start.
he could be there now.
Garcia's got a trace.
He's bouncing between
a few towers.
Where?
Fairfax county.
He's still local?
Send the coordinates
to my phone.
Done.
Why isn't he on his way
to new jersey?
Wait,
that phone's on?
Yes.
He hung up.
hotch?
Damn it.
[beeping]
What's that?
Hotch is calling foyet.
[ring]
Agent hotchner.
If you touch her...
Be gentle,
like i was with you?
What the hell
took you so long?
I was beginning to think
this phone was dead
or something.
Why so quiet?
You usually lash out
when you're frustrated.
I'm not frustrated.
you're more predictable
than you think.
Am i?
You didn't know
where haley was,
So you made her come to you.
You make me sound lazy.
Just another way
for you to show control.
Oh, that's terrible.
You're mother tried to protect
you from your father,
But she wasn't strong enough.
And you hated her
for that, didn't you?
You decided that
all women were weak.
Those are your words,
not mine.
What were you,
9 when you killed them?
It was a car accident.
That you couldn't
take credit for.
That had to be
hard for you.
But poor george
got another chance.
The little orphan
was saved
By the wealthy, sterile
eastside couple, the foyets.
And the story
should have ended there.
I don't believe
in fairy tales. do you?
That's the thing, george.
this isn't a fairy tale.
You don't have to write
this story.
You don't have to do
any of this.
I know you're exhausted.
Always looking
over your shoulder,
Always wondering when the
other shoe is gonna drop.
Haven't you gotten
what you wanted?
You've set yourself apart
from anybody we've ever
dealt with.
You're not just
a famous serial killer,
you're the reaper.
We're gonna study you
and your methods
for years and years.
You know what
i've been thinking?
Haley looks pretty good
with dark hair.
She's lost some weight.
Must be all the stress
you caused her.
Where's the little man?
Oh. there he is.
Does he like captain america
because of you?
[cell phone rings]
That's your wife.
Hold, please.
[ring]
Mrs. hotchner.
I'm here.
Open the gate
and i'll drive in.
Ok.
Aaron?
I really gotta go.
[beeping]
Strauss: and you still
didn't know where foyet was?
The phone belonged
to a u.s. marshal.
It was designed to
bounce between towers,
So we could not pinpoint
his location.
And agent hotchner
was driving around aimlessly.
No.
He wasn't.
We had foyet's profile,
And we knew
if we followed it,
We would know were
he took hotch's family.
All right, foyet
has to be in control.
He had haley
come to him.
Yeah, but where
would he take her?
He'd want hotch to find him,
to see where he was,
Which means he--
to see what he did.
He said something
on that call
That tells hotch
where to go.
Reid, what did he say,
exactly?
"haley's hair looks good dark.
she's lost some weight.
"it must be because of
all the stress you caused her.
"where's the little man?
oh, there he is now.
"do you think he likes
captain america because of you?
"that's your wife
on the other line. hold, please.
Hi. open the gate
and i'll drive in."
Open the gate?
It would be someplace
With the biggest
emotional impact for hotch.
And haley has access
to the gate.
Their house,
where they lived together.
Of course. foyet planned
this all the way to the end.
It's everything to him.
He wants to take over
hotch's home
To be in control
to prove his dominance.
Morgan.
[ring]
He's going to your house.
I know.
I'm sending out a full
tactical deployment, hotch.
Good.
We're on our way.
Foyet's calling hotch.
[beeping]
Garcia,
can you get us on?
[cell phone rings]
Foyet.
Aaron?
You're ok?
I'm fine.
But...
He said that...
Oh, aaron.
He can hear us, right?
Yes.
I am so sorry.
Haley, show him no weakness,
No fear.
I know.
Sam told me
all about him.
Is he, uh--
No, sam is fine.
Foyet: aaron, aaron, aaron.
Is that why
your marriage broke up,
Because you're a liar?
Don't listen to him, haley.
I have sam's service phone
right here.
They sent out a mass text
about his death.
You can take a look
if you want.
He's trying to scare you.
Did you even tell her
what this was about?
About the deal?
He's just trying
to make you angry.
Well, she should be.
she's gonna...
D-i-e
Because of your
inflated ego.
Ignore him, haley.
I'm sure you don't want her
to know this part either.
You know, all he had to do
was stop looking for me
And you wouldn't
be in this mess.
Don't react.
What is he talking about?
Tell jack i need him
working the case.
What?
Tell jack i need him
working the case.
[clears throat] jack.
Did you he that?
Hi, daddy.
Hi, buddy.
Is george a bad guy?
Yes, he is.
Jack, i need you
on this case with me.
Do you understand?
I need you to work the case
with me.
Ok, daddy.
Jack, hug your mom for me.
Mommy hug me too tight.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sad?
Oh, i just love you
so much.
Mommy, i gotta go.
i'm working the case.
Ok.
He's so cute.
He's like a little
junior g-man.
I'll be right up,
jackie boy!
Is he gone?
Yes.
You're so strong, haley.
you're stronger than i ever was.
You'll hurry, right?
I know you didn't sign on
for this.
Neither did you.
I'm sorry for everything.
Promise me that you will
tell him how we met
And how you used to
make me laugh.
Haley...
He needs to know
that you weren't always
so serious, aaron.
I want him
to believe in love,
Because it is the most
important thing.
But you need to show him.
Promise me.
I promise.
[3 gunshots]
And i don't know
what happened after that.
After i finish you...
I'm gonna find that little
bastard son of yours
And i'm gonna show him
both of his dead parents,
And i'm gonna tell him
that it was all your fault.
And them i'm gonna--aah!
Aah!
Ok. you got--you got me.
I surrender.
Uhh!
Hotch! hotch!
He's dead.
Hotch, stop.
come on, stop it.
It's over.
It's ok.
it's over, man.
[knocking]
[laugh
at are you doing?
I work the case
with you, dad.
Jack, i'm glad you're
working the case with me.
You know i can always
use your help.
I work the case daddy,
just like you said.
You did a great job, buddy.
What happened to you,
daddy?
I'm ok. i want you to go
outside with ms. jareau. ok?
Come here, sweetheart.
[sirens]
I'm so sorry, hotch.
Get out of here.
go see if they need
help downstairs.
[sobbing]
There was nothing
i could do for her.
She was already...
She died fairly quickly.
One of the wounds
severed her aorta,
And they don't think
that she...
she suffered much.
Agent hotchner, what do you
think would have happened
If george foyet had gotten up
from that floor?
If you didn't kill him?
I don't have to think.
i know he would have tried
to kill my son, too.
That's good enough for me.
Any questions?
Agent hotchner.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
And...
If you or your son
need anything...
Thank you.
Hotch: poet haniel long said,
"so much of what
is best in us
"is bound up
in our love of family
"that it remains
the measure of our stability
Because it measures
our sense of loyalty."
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com