Driver's license and
registration, please, sir.
Sorry, Officer. My wife...
....pregnant. Hm...
She's always calling
me when I'm driving.
And registration, sir.
Gun!
Sir, put your hands up on the dashboard!
But... my wife.
Hands on the dashboard!
I want to see your hands!
All right, nice and
slow, I want your hands
through the window opening
the door from the outside
and step out of the car.
Now!
- Charlie.
- I got it.
On the hood, sir, now.
Hands behind your back.
You just fired this gun, sir?
Damn.
You okay, sir?
Sir?
T
Te
Tea
Team
Team-
Team-N
Team-NC
Team-NCI
Team-NCIS
Team-NCIS.
Team-NCIS.c
Team-NCIS.co
Team-NCIS.com
Team-NCIS.com p
Team-NCIS.com pr
Team-NCIS.com pre
Team-NCIS.com pres
Team-NCIS.com prese
Team-NCIS.com presen
Team-NCIS.com present
Team-NCIS.com presents
Team-NCIS.com presents :
NCIS Season 4 Episode 4 :
Faking It.
Script : FRM
Synch : Orion for Team-NCIS.com
www.Team-NCIS.com
Men are such bad liars.
But if a good liar
was telling you a lie,
you would not know it was a lie.
Ha! I would.
How would you know?
Know what?
When an expert liar
is telling Ziva a lie.
And this started how?
Well, I told her that I
went to the gym this morning.
No great skill in guessing
you were fibbing there, probie.
You may have lost some
weight, and personally,
I'm very proud of you,
but "gym" is definitely
not your middle name.
Okay, well, Ziva ...
....thinks that all men are liars.
Really?
So if...
.... I were to lie to you,
you would be able to tell?
Particularly you.
You think?
Wouldn't go there, Tony.
Oh, watch and weep.
True or false:
I had eggs for breakfast this morning.
True.
Lucky guess.
Last night,
I had a date with a
very beautiful woman.
False.
She's good.
My first car was a
shiny new red Corvette.
False.
Strike three.
I win.
How did you do that?
When you said you had a red Corvette,
you looked down and to the left
a telltale sign when people lie.
And the date?
Gibbs.
Tony...
if you'd gone out with a
beautiful woman last night,
you'd have talked about it all day.
- I would?
- Oh, yeah.
Okay, but how could you possibly know
that I had eggs for
breakfast this morning?
Gear up.
Got a message from a dead guy.
Ready to roll, boss.
Dinozzo ...
Yeah, boss?
You got egg on your shirt.
Not just your shirt.
It's amazing what the
human body can endure.
This poor fellow probably
lasted longer than he should.
How much longer?
Several minutes.
Not much when you stack it against
a lifetime of minutes,
but minutes nonetheless.
He could've driven a couple of miles.
More like a couple city blocks.
Traffic sucks this time of day.
According to his military ID,
he's Chief Petty Officer Jack T. Vale.
You know him?
No.
Well, he knows you guys.
Jackpot.
Got to be 50 or 60 bucks there.
Yeah, there's more
in his trouser pocket.
What do you think, illegal slots?
Maybe he was on his
way to a video arcade.
Maybe he was doing laundry.
That's a lot of laundry.
Maybe he was a once-
a-month kind of man.
I do it once a week.
Laundry.
Who's the fare?
Oh, that's Robert John Stevens.
But the guy's got an accent as thick
as Polish sausage, so I ain't buying it.
Found a loaded .38 on
the seat, recently fired.
Got an exit wound?
Well, there doesn't
appear to be an exit wound.
So I dig out the bullet,
you match it to the weapon
and, hey, presto, justice prevails.
Open and shut case, boss.
No such thing, DiNozzo, only watertight.
Give me a call when you're finished.
You got it, Ducky.
Doesn't look like a fake ID.
Fake.
What are you talking about?
You barely got a look at it.
I can spot a fake a mile away.
I had the best fake ID in college.
Never got turned away from a bar.
Never?
Never.
Once.
Once?
- Or twice.
- A month?
A week. But, listen, we went out
every night, and it was a college town.
And they're very tough
there, eagle-eyed bouncers.
You really had to act
the part, too, you know?
You had to be mature,
worldly, kind of grown up.
So it wasn't really the ID, it was you.
Are you kidding me?
No, I was...
I was the master of fake.
Last call dialed was 911.
Cops will have it on tape.
Maybe this one will be easy.
Fake name...
fake plates.
Real weapon.
Real guy dead.
When he first saw you, he called 911.
When you realized he was
trailing you, you shot him.
Even the very, very good ones
slip up eventually.
And you...
Mister... Stevens?
You're not very good.
- Women want men to lie to them.
- Not true.
"Honey, does my butt look
big in these pants to you?"
"Actually, yes, sweetheart,
"your butt looks as big as Alabama.
"Didn't want to say anything, but
you got the 'Bama butt going on."
See ?
You want us to lie to you, so we do.
Especially if your
butt is as big as 'Bama.
Not that...
not that your butt is big.
- And not that I've even looked.
- Liar.
Okay,
I have looked, but, you know, I never...
Never what?
Oh, no.
I... I'm catching on to you.
And you're not going to
get me to say something
and then do your little
Mossad true-or-false trick.
I'm too smart for that.
Of course you are.
-Ziva...
- Gibbs.
How many languages do you speak?
Comment
vous-appelez-vous?
Ah, French.
Was wir nur wissen
wollen ist ihre naame.
Und German.
Mi dica il suo nome.
Italian. Of course.
Lee ma betellna essmak?
Greek?
Arabic.
Nice, boss.
Skah-zhee-teh,
kahk vahs zah-voot?
Ah. Got him. He's Russian.
Looked down and to the
left. Sure sign of a liar.
That's very good, DiNozzo.
Thanks, boss.
Ziva tell you that?
Tell me you found a match
on our suspect's prints, Ab.
Negative.
Still processing.
What we do have is $73.65.
That's what the victim was carrying.
And there's no pennies.
He probably threw them out.
A lot people do, you know.
I mean, I don't, but other people do.
Do you know how many pennies are
thrown out or put into jars every year?
Enlighten me.
Three and a half
billion. Billion, Gibbs.
That's, like, $35 million in pennies.
That's a lot of pennies in any language.
Including Russian.
No, Russians don't have
pennies, they have kopecks.
What's it have to do with Russia?
Run his prints through
Immigration and let's find out.
Oh, because he's a foreigner
and every visitor is printed
when they enter the U.S.
Clever, Gibbs.
Okay, I reviewed the 911 call.
Ready?
My name is Jack Vale.
This is really important, okay?
I've identified a
terrorist, a known terrorist.
I'm following him downtown right now.
Get someone over here. Call NC...
NCIS.
I'm guessing an overtaxed
relay tower in the downtown area
caused the line to drop
off before he finished.
But, Gibbs, this guy works
in the supply department.
What would he know about terrorists?
That's a good question.
I also isolated the background noise.
It's kind of a Pac-Man-
retro-meets-Vegas sort of thing.
Not really something you hear in a car.
He was on foot when he made the call.
We have a winner.
Nikolai Aleksandrovich Puchenko.
Russian.
And there's a Homeland Security alert.
You're not the only one
interested in Mr. Nikolai Puchenko.
I want lawyer.
Get a good one.
Tell him the charge
is going to be murder.
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
Normally matching the
bullet to the weapon
shouldn't present us with any great
difficulty, but this is far from normal.
How far?
I haven't seen anything like it
in 25 years of slicing and dicing.
The bullet entered below the rib cage,
traveling from left to right.
It nicked the pancreas,
missed the liver,
deflected off the fifth rib
and gouged its way through soft tissue
and perforated the stomach.
No exit wound.
And so that's where it
appears to have, um...
To have um, what, Dr. Mallard?
Vanished.
It's not in the bullet furrow
and it's not showing
up on any of the X rays.
I don't know where it's gone.
I'm afraid we don't have a bullet.
The 911 call was routed
through this tower here.
Anyone ever heard of Operation Sunburst?
That locates Vale somewhere in
this area when he made the call.
Anywhere outside of the
circle would have meant that
the call was routed through
a different cell tower.
Back in '91.
Come one, anyone, Operation Sunburst.
About three city blocks...
Less.
Abby said the signal dropped
out. That probably puts him
at the outside edge of the
reception area of that tower.
That's pretty clever, boss.
How'd you figure that out?
Too much time around you.
Boss...
Operation Sunburst,  you know it?
It was a sting.
One of our ops. Chief
Vale was part of it.
He was just a P.O. Three back then
detailed from the Supply Department
to NIS for five weeks.
Get that file from archives.
I can't.
I mean, it's not possible,
boss. I got the index reference,
but when I called the archive,
they said the file was missing.
Check the log. Who booked it out last?
CIA.
So I guess that's not a
"who," it's more of an "it."
Who was the NIS case agent?
What time is it in Mexico right now?
Cantina time.
Si.
Washington, senor.
Only one person in Washington DC
knows where to find me this time of day.
How you doing, probie?
Well, I'm surviving.
You?
Sun's hot,
ocean's warm,
beer's cold.
Got no complaints.
You change your mind?
Every day.
But then something stops me.
What's stopping you this time?
Operation Sunburst.
That was a long time ago.
Do you remember a petty
officer named Vale?
Right guy, right place, right time.
Went undercover for us.
Well, he was shot dead this morning.
And you think this has
something to do with Sunburst?
Well, you tell me.
We got a suspect.
Russian.
Arkady Kobach?
Nikolai...
....Puchenko.
Arkady Kobach is the man
you need to worry about.
Puchenko and he served together.
When the Soviet Union
started started falling apart,
they got into the arms trade.
Wanted to buy some of our Stingers
to sell to Chechen terrorists.
Tried to bribe Vale in
the Supply Department.
So you sent him undercover?
Someone tipped them off.
They hightailed it
back to Easter Europe.
A month later,
the CIA stuck its nose in and our
file conveniently went missing.
What happened to Vale?
He bumped into Puchenko in the street.
Recognized him, tried to follow him.
Puchenko shot him.
I hope you've got an ironclad case.
This piece of scum is way overdue.
Yeah.
Working on it, boss.
Good luck with the fishing down there.
Thanks for the tip.
Good luck.
We got a case yet, DiNozzo?
Like you said, working on it, boss.
We've narrowed down the
area where he was shot,
and we do have a suspect
in possession of a gun.
Which means murder one.
With a bullet.
If we can find one.
Hi, Ducky.
Penny for your thoughts.
Or three and a half billion pennies.
That was an in-joke.
So I have a pristine
bullet sample fired
from our suspect's .38.
All I need is the bullet
you pulled from him.
I'll make a match
and we'll send the bad guys wherever
the bad guys go when we catch 'em.
Where do the bad guys
go when we catch 'em?
The bullet's disappeared, Abby.
I thought there was no exit wound?
There is no exit wound.
Well, maybe it fell out, like
in his clothes or something.
I already checked.
Or an evidence bag.
- Checked.
- Or a body bag.
Ditto.
Well, bullets don't
just disappear, Ducky.
Unless it's an ice bullet.
I saw this really cool movie one
time where this guy carved a bullet...
- It's not an ice bullet.
- .. out of ice...
Do you really think you lost a bullet?
I didn't lose it.
At least, I don't think I did.
Oh, Ducky.
I'd be sick to my
stomach if I lost evidence
or screwed something up like
a DNA sample or a fingerprint.
Of course!
That's got to be it.
Nothing else makes any
sense. Abby, you are a genius.
Probie.
Yeah
What's this?
Number three?
Four.
Would have thought you'd have
been done practicing by now.
There's always something to learn, Mike.
Hard lessons.
Some harder than others.
Got any extra fine?
You didn't waste any time getting here.
You were expecting me?
Well, I would have been
disappointed if you didn't come.
Yeah, well, let's just say I...
don't like loose ends, probie.
Take more than loose ends to
get you off that beach in Baja.
These scumbags have been selling
weapons to tyrants and terrorists
ever since they gave us the slip.
Guns...
....and bombs...
.... and RPGs used to kill
American soldiers and marines
in every hellhole from
Mogadishu to Baghdad.
It's time it ended.
You know who tipped them?
Rumor was they'd agreed to supply
some new high-tech
Soviet missile to CIA.
Guess they figured they wouldn't get their
missile if their arms dealers were in prison.
Which is exactly where
I was going to send them.
You've got a chance here, probie.
Don't screw it up.
Same to you, Nikolai.
Who's that with him?
Marty Allen. His lawyer.
Hope he's not a good lawyer.
Enjoy your tour?
Yeah,
place is like a video arcade.
You've got more technology in one room
than we had in every office
across the whole damn country.
You know...
....if I needed to interrogate someone
when I worked at Camp Pendleton,
I'd take them into the broom closet
with a telephone directory.
No broom closet, no
telephone directory...
No smoking.
Another three reasons
why I left just in...
.... time.
Special Agent Gibbs,
may I have a moment?
Ooh-rah, Gunny.
You know that guy?
Yeah...
....Like a rat knows a snake.
Director Shepard...
Special Agent Gibbs,
this is Roy Carver, Homeland Security.
Agent Gibbs.
Mr. Carver is here in relation
to a suspect we're holding.
Nikolai Puchenko.
I'd like you to transfer him
into Mr. Carver's custody.
Why?
He's working for us.
He's providing valuable intel on the arms
trade among terrorist groups in Eastern Europe.
Was he working for you when
he killed a sailor yesterday?
I read the preliminary autopsy
report on that, Agent Gibbs.
Seems there's a lack of evidence
linking Puchenko to the crime.
He was carrying an illegal firearm.
Not connected to the shooting.
Yet.
Well..
Well, find evidence that he was involved in
any serious criminal activity and I promise,...
I'll hand him right back to you
Do we have anything yet, Agent Gibbs?
We will.
Until we do,
I'm releasing him to Homeland Security.
Ziva, get Puchenko.
Hello, this is Special Agent DiNozzo.
I have Ziva David coming down
to pick up Nikolai Puchenko.
If he walks out of here,
you won't see him again.
Any evidence you have
won't be worth spit.
We haven't got enough evidence
to even clear our throat.
We can't charge him with anything.
Mr. Carver, if you'll just sign
these custody transfer forms.
Director...
may I draw your attention to
an NIS case code name Sunburst.
Which dealt with serious allegations of
arms smuggling by this man Nikolai Puchenko.
I'm aware of the case, Mr. Franks.
As I recall, the file was lost, Mike.
I made a copy, Roy.
Jack Vale was the key witness.
He's dead.
You don't have anyone to testify.
I was the case agent.
I'll testify.
Serious enough charges
for you, Director Shepard?
Take him back into custody.
I'm sorry, Mr. Carver.
NCIS is not through with this man.
Homeland Security looks
forward to reviewing the file.
This is an outrage.
I strongly protest your
department's treatment of my client.
Come on.
What did he just say?
He said you're a dead man,
Mike.
We're taking Puchenko's threat
to kill Franks seriously,
so right now this is who
we have to worry about.
McGee?
Arkady Mikhailovich Kobach,
late 40s.
Served with Puchenko in the Spetsnaz
That's the Soviet Special Forces.
First Afghanistan then Chechnya.
In 1990, Arkady executed three
clerks in a payroll office
because they could not pay his men.
Then shot the colonel
who came to arrest him.
Been dealing arms ever since.
I want a 24-hour protection
detail. DiNozzo, you're team leader.
You're in safe hands, Mike.
I've seen your hands,
DiNozzo. They don't impress me.
I don't need babysitting,
Gunny. I can look after myself.
After spending four months in that
crap hole you call a home in Baja,
I find that highly debatable.
- Safe house, boss?
- Yep. Mine
Make yourself at home, Tony.
Won't touch a thing, boss.
McGee.
We'll be right down.
Boss, Ducky found the bullet.
It's fascinating where
bullets can end up.
I once found a .22 caliber
slug in a woman's knee
and she'd been shot in the chest.
See, the bullet entered her heart,
was pumped down through the aorta
into the iliac and on down
into the femoral artery.
Extraordinary.
So the missing bullet's in his knee?
No, no. Good heavens, no.
That's much to easy, and
anyway, it would have...
.... shown up on the X rays.
So where is it?
I have no idea.
None at all.
You said you found it.
Well, I have. I just don't know where.
I can, however, tell you how.
It was Abby who gave me the idea
when she said that she would be sick to
her stomach if she ever lost evidence.
"Sick," that's the key word.
So I had Abby run some tests of material
I took from his esophagus and we
found traces of protease pepsin
along with all sorts of
other things such as sulfides,
oleic acid, polyphenols.
But...
.... the smoking gun, so to speak,
was the presence of triticum durum.
Pasta?
Specifically spaghetti cooked
with garlic and olive oil.
Spaghetti aglio y
olio, as the Romans say.
Very nice with a glass of Sangiovese.
Anyway, anyway, when the bullet
became lodged in his stomach,
he became sick. What you might call...
....projectile vomit.
He puked up the bullet?
Yeah. Find the puke and
you'll find the projectile.
So you want us to look for
a pile of dried-up vomit.
Yes, and I'll need a generous sample
so I can positively match it
to what I found in the victim.
Oh, and of course,...
....the bullet.
Ziva, McGee, get onto it.
Well, uh, boss, we have narrowed
it down to a few city blocks.
Vale must have still been
on foot when he was shot
or he would have gotten sick in the car.
So maybe a parking garage or a
parking lot. That narrows it down.
Go, go. Don't come
back without the bullet.
Where is Mike?
I thought you were supposed
to be protecting him.
I was. I mean, I...
He was right here.
Couldn't have gone far, boss.
Don't count on it.
Franks?
Couldn't find a broom closet.
How do you know Carver?
Just another spook from the old
days that made my job difficult.
You never mentioned you made
a backup copy of that file.
It was a long time ago, probie.
Is it enough?
Should do the trick.
What's in it?
Where'd you learn to be
such a pain in the ass?
Working with you.
There's a lot of people who want
to see what's in that file, Mike.
Guess they're going to be disappointed.
There's nothing to see.
But there's plenty to listen to.
Vale was wearing a wire?
And I was on the other end
of it listening to every word.
Dubbed a copy.
I tell what I heard,
audiotape backs me up
and everybody's happy
except for Nikolai.
Where's the tape?
Safe.
How safe?
Safe enough that no one's
found it for 15 years.
This director,...
....she's okay, I guess, but...
.... I get the feeling that ...
....you've been working
under her a little too long.
The world's changing, Mike.
All the lines are
getting blurred, probie.
Hard for a man not to step over them.
And you can call off
this protection detail.
- I can take care of myself just fine.
- No, I can't do that, Mike.
All you have to be is half a
second slower and you're dead.
Or the other guy just has to be a
half-second faster just like it's always been.
I found him, boss!
Nice work, DiNozzo.
No Italian restaurants. Must have
eaten somewhere else and driven here.
It couldn't have been this public.
You don't shoot someone where
everyone can see you, do you?
I never do.
Unless, of course, it can't be helped.
Alleys, service lanes, parking lots.
You hear that?
What am I listening for?
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch.
That's Abby's mystery sound.
That explains all the coins.
Coin counter.
Vale must have been waiting
to use it when he saw Nikolai.
In the market?
Even arms dealers need groceries.
Okay, so he made the 911 call,
followed Nikolai...
....into the parking lot.
Ground zero.
I got puke.
That's a lot of regurgitation.
It doesn't look fresh.
It doesn't smell fresh.
Does it ever?
That could be blood.
Or the Colonel's special dipping sauce.
Ah!
Well, we could toss a coin.
Or not.
All right, give me some gloves.
You didn't pack the gloves.
I thought you packed the gloves.
I didn't pack the gloves.
Give me something.
Uh!
There's nothing here.
Hey!
Ugh!
Uh, you have a tissue or something?
We have got to buy some gloves.
This is going to be a long day.
Need-to-know
basis,
and this one you didn't need to know.
How well you know Carver?
- Um, been with Homeland Security since the startup.
- Before that?
NSA?
Try CIA.
In '91, he was trying to get a sneak
peek at top-secret Soviet hardware
which links him directly
to Puchenko and Kobach.
Sounds speculative.
And if I'm right?
If you're right, it probably was Carver
who tipped off Kobach and Puchenko when
we were going to arrest them in '91.
Hey, and look who pops up
to get Nikolai off the hook.
The CIA has a shopping
list, Carver is the buyer.
I want him taken out of the loop.
You don't seriously think that Carver's
leaking information to Kobach on Mike Franks.
He did it in '91.
No Mike, no case.
Puchenko walks, probably
right into a deal with Carver.
Jen.
Listen to me.
Take him off the
need-to-know list.
Too late. Carver's already been briefed.
You're supposed to be
inside the house, Mike.
Nice catch.
I must be getting sloppy.
Well, I smelled the cigarette smoke.
I can smoke inside if you want.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Nope.
- Hello.
- DiNozzo, it's Gibbs.
Oh, hey, boss, we were
just talking about you.
We got a security problem.
Time to go off script. Where's Franks?
He's right...
Mike?
Tony?
DiNozzo?
Tony !!!!
I lose any hair?
No.
- How is he?
- He'll live.
Well, I've been hit
harder, boss, by you.
How many were there?
I didn't see.
Came up real fast from behind.
The rest of our guys deployed from
the house in less than 30 seconds.
But they were already gone.
With Mike?
There must have been two teams. One to
take me down, and the other to snatch him.
Whoever did it, they were good.
Sorry, boss.
So...
....why grab him when all
they had to do was kill him?
He was holding evidence.
Where?
He wouldn't tell me.
Well, I guess you didn't hold a
blowtorch to his eyeballs to find out.
These guys will.
Yeah. Gibbs.
Tell her I'm on my way.
Jenny?
"Jenny?"
Just, uh..
.... how cozy did you two get
while I was away?
Well, that knock to the head must
have been harder than I thought,
'cause I'm saying crazy things
that I don't even understand.
You think she's single?
He's fine.
People should really
chew their food more.
And drink in moderation.
What's that look like?
Not puke.
Blood.
This Dumpster could have
just been moved here.
You didn't waste any time.
Bad news travels fast.
Especially in this town.
How's your agent?
Do you really give a damn?
- Any update on Mike Franks?
- No.
You expect to find him, Agent Gibbs?
He's a resourceful man.
No doubt.
In the meantime, I'd like Nikolai
Puchenko released into my custody.
I'm not finished with him.
But you are, Agent Gibbs.
Perhaps your time would be better
spent finding out who in your department
leaked the location of the safe house
where you were keeping your key witness.
Did you?
Gibbs.
No.
You did in '91.
If you would like to have this request
formalized, Director Shepard, that can be arranged.
I'm sure you didn't mean for that
to sound like a threat, Mr. Carver.
But in the meantime, Mr. Puchenko
will remain in our custody
pending our investigation into
the disappearance of Mike Franks.
I think you need to look closer to home.
Maybe there was no leak.
Maybe Franks just lost
his nerve and ran away.
Or Kobach met his asking price.
You don't know Mike Franks.
And you really think you do?
Director.
You've got about an hour and then
all hell is going to break loose.
Jethro...
I really hope you know Mike
Franks as well as you think you do.
Marty Allen, please.
Hello. Mr. Allen?
Mike Franks.
NCIS Mike Franks?
One in the same.
What can I do for you?
I have something that your
client's associate, Arkady Kobach,
might be interested in buying.
What might that be?
A one-off copy of the audio tape
that will send him and your
client to prison for 30 years.
If he's interested,
what would the price be?
$500,000.
You get the tape,
and I get to go back to Mexico and retire with
a sweet little waitress named Camila Charo.
I'll have to contact my client.
Can I get back to you?
Sure. You got a pen?
Hey,
-.. what kept him?
- Business.
God, I hate lawyers.
I demand you release
my client, Agent Gibbs.
You got no grounds to hold him. Your...
....key witness has disappeared.
You have no case.
Oh, you're right. I don't
have a case against your client
for arms dealing.
But I do have one for murder.
We deserve a medal.
That look...
.... is as close as you're
ever going to get, probie.
Nikolai, you have a choice.
You can spend the rest of your life
in prison, or you can cut a deal.
And you can tell me...
.... where to find your friend, Arkady.
Clear.
McGee.
Smoke's from a Russian cigarette.
Arkady hasn't been gone long.
Come on, double time.
Okay, we're on.
Ten calls made in the last day.
Three in the last hour and a half.
First was to a cell phone, Marty Allen.
Second call was to Merchant Bank.
The last call ...
....was to a hotel in the
port district El Ejecutivo.
Call was made to room seven.
Mexican hotel. Names and numbers,
McGee, starting with the hotel.
Are you sure?
That's what the manager said.
Room seven is booked in
the name of a Camila Charo,
but it was not a woman that paid cash
for the room. It was some old guy.
Franks's brand.
Beer's cold.
But they're all out of lime.
I sent the bar man to buy some.
I told him to take his time.
You've got what I want?
And I've got what you want.
Truth is, Arkady,...
....you've got nothing I want.
You think you are the
first to point a gun at me?
No.
No, but I will be the last.
I knew he was over there.
I figured I could take them both.
Arkady first,
then the big guy.
Maybe I am a half second slower.
There was no leak, was there?
DiNozzo okay?
Boss?
Clear!
Secure the room.
You set yourself up as bait.
The bigger the bait,
the bigger the fish you catch.
Arkady never would have got to
court, probie, and you know it.
Carver or whoever else is pulling the
strings would have made sure of that.
Another crappy deal.
More innocent people die.
If you think I'm not
going to sleep well tonight
because of what I just
did, then you're wrong.
I'm going to sleep like a baby,
because Arkady Kobach was a scary S.O.B.
who kept me awake nights
for the past 15 years.
Someone else will take his place.
That's your problem, probie.
I got my guy.
Hey.
You got that audio tape?
Beer's getting warm.
www.Team-NCIS.com