Covert intelligence involves
a lot of waiting around.
Know what it's like
being a spy?
Like sitting in your dentist's
reception area 24 hours a day.
You read magazines, sip coffee,
and every so often,
someone tries to kill you.
In.
You know,
mercedes makes an s.U.V. Now.
Big backseat.
It's great.
Surprisingly affordable, too.
Cia?
What do you say to that?
"No"?
Explain that a lot of spies
don't work directly
for the cia?
A lot of good that'll do.
Welcome.
Mr. Cia.
No, no, no, no.
I don't work
for anybody directly.
That's why I get to do stuff
like give you $750,000
to stop blowing up
oil refineries.
Hi, hi, everybody.
Whoa, easy, guys, easy.
Just getting the map.
You guarantee security
for the nembi oil field.
No fires, no explosions,
nobody falls into a swamp
and gets eaten by an alligator.
You mean "crocodile."
yes, that's...
I mean crocodile.
We agreed?
Da.
I'm now reaching into my jacket
for my phone
so I can get this man
his money. See?
Yes, I have
the wire-transfer information.
The aba number
is 0210010175...
Stop.
We got a burn notice on you.
You're blacklisted.
Excuse me?
I'm sorry.
Is there problem?
No, no problem.
Computer mix-up... Pc, mac.
Put your boss on the phone
right now.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
I have a wire-transfer number.
0210010...
You cia bastard!
You think you can steal from me?
Sometimes, the truth hurts.
In these situations,
I recommend lying.
I'm cia! I'm c...
I'm cia!
I've got the money!
Enough, enough!
Pick him up.
I've got the money.
It's not here.
I can take you to it, though.
I was gonna steal it
and blame it on you guys.
It's not personal, okay.
That's just what I was gonna do.
In 20 minutes, you'll have
your money... I promise.
Take him.
I need the bathroom.
I'm gonna be sick.
I'm gonna...
Wait, wait!
I'm gonna be sick!
I need the bathroom!
I'm gonna be sick in
the mercedes, you understand?
In the mercedes!
Blood... Everywhere!
In a fight,
you have to be careful
not to break the little bones
in your hand on someone's face.
That's why I like bathrooms.
Lots of hard surfaces.
Sorry.
I'll leave it at the airport.
Quick, quick!
Southern nigeria isn't
my favorite place in the world.
It's unstable, it's corrupt,
and the people there
eat a lot of terrible-smelling
preserved fish.
I will say this
for nigeria, though...
It's the gun-running capital
of africa,
and that makes it a bad place
to drive a passenger sedan
into a crowded market.
Right this way, sir.
If you're gonna collapse
on a plane,
I recommend business class.
The seats are bigger
if you start convulsing.
Although once you pass out...
You okay?
...It really doesn't matter.
You're a lucky man.
That many bruises, anyone would
think you fell under a truck.
Fiona, what are you doing here?
You've been out for a couple of days.
The maid got curious,
went through your stuff.
You still have me in your wallet
as your emergency contact.
You take that out when
you leave someone, you know.
I'm flattered you came.
Don't be.
I need to get out
of new york anyway.
Old associates
sniffing around.
And I wanted to try
someplace sunny.
And it sounded like
you might die.
I- I wanted to be there.
At the end.
To tell you
what a bastard you were.
Sunny...
Where am I?
Miami. Apparently you collapsed
on the flight out of nigeria.
Miami?
Why am I here?
Airline would only say they
were instructed to fly you here.
"Instructed"...
What does that mean?
It's home, in a manner
of speaking, isn't it?
Oh, I called your mom.
My mother?
Yeah, yeah,
we had a lovely chat.
She's thrilled
you're home for christmas.
Home... I'm not home.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna go.
Leaving?
yeah.
You're good at that.
Yeah, it's just better if my mother
and I aren't in the same hemisphere.
Fiona, someone put a burn notice
out on me.
I got to take care
of this now.
Or a few cracked ribs
will be the least of my worries.
Surveillance.
Two-man team, fbi.
Fi...
Why don't you go run
interference for me?
Please, fi, come on.
Make one of those scenes
of yours.
Bite one of them.
Set the other on fire.
Just do it in about 10 minutes.
I need to clean up.
You'll owe me dinner.
Fine.
Most people would be thrilled
to be dumped in miami.
Sadly, I am not most people.
Spend a few years
as a covert operative,
and a sunny beach
just looks like a vulnerable
tactical position...
No decent cover.
I've never found a good way to
hide a gun in a bathing suit.
Welcome to the chadwicke, sir.
I need a room
one, maybe two nights.
We've got a 10th-floor suite
with an ocean view.
I don't want a view.
Facing a wall, something
with no windows, if you have it.
Far from the elevators,
close to the exits...
If you have it.
Do you have another card?
This one was declined.
Declined?
I... I don't care
what the computer says.
I want my money
from my account.
I understand that, sir.
I...
Let me check
with the manager.
When a spy gets fired,
he doesn't get a call from the
lady in h.R. And a gold watch.
They cut him off.
They make sure
he can never work again.
They can't take away his skills
or what's in his head,
so they take away the resources
that allow him to function.
They burn him.
All I know
is the account is frozen.
The code
is government-related.
If you care to discuss this
with the police...
Hey. Hi.
Looks like
you could use a free hat.
Uh, pay phone?
Huh?
You put coins in,
and then...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
um...
Right over there.
I need to speak
with dan siebels.
I'm sorry. There's no one here
by that name.
He's my case officer.
I need to speak with him.
I know the protocol, I know
you're just doing your job,
but I don't have access
to a secure line.
I'm sorry, sir...
This is Michael Westen.
Just put dan on the phone.
He's my handler.
I've worked with him
for 15 goddamn years!
Sir, there is no one here
by that name.
Sorry, kid.
Please,
we trained together.
There's a lucite plaque on his
desk with a bullet hole in it.
He drinks sprite.
He's a friend.
Sir, I can't help.
No, no, don't hang up on me!
When you're being watched,
what you need is contrast...
A background that will make
the surveillance stand out.
An fbi field office
is full of guys in their 40s.
At most south beach
business hotels,
it would be tough to tell
which middle-aged white guy
was watching you.
So you stay in the place
where everyone is a jello shot
away from alcohol poisoning.
If you see someone
who can walk a straight line,
that's the fed.
In miami.
I need the address
for securacorp.
Brigalow south.
Thanks.
Sorry.
wrong room.
Come on.
No, wait.
He's kind of hot.
Kids, come here.
See that cop?
I'll give you guys 5 bucks each
if you go over and tell him
that a man in that car
over there
tried to make you sit
on his lap.
Can you do that?
Make it 10 bucks each.
$15, but you split it.
All right.
For $15, I want tears.
All right, dawg.
Hey, you,
come out of the car.
Come on.
Come on out.
Get out of the car.
Officer, uh, anderson.
I'll get some I.D. For you.
Hey, no, no.
Come on!
Whoa! Come on!
Come on.
Need to go someplace
you're not wanted?
Any uniform store will sell you
a messenger outfit,
and any messenger
can get past a security desk.
Show him in.
Janet,
can you give us a minute?
What an office.
Michael,
what are you doing here?
You cannot be here.
You heard, then?
Are you kidding?
You've been flagged
on every government list.
Why didn't you call me?
- Would you have seen me if I did?
- Of course not.
You were always good
at pissing people off.
It's a mistake. It has to be.
Just tell me what you've heard.
I don't know the details.
I just heard you were out.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
I'm just out?
What am I,
your complaint hotline?
Lucy, I'm broke.
Bottom line,
they trashed my credit,
they froze my bank accounts...
If I'm gonna figure this out,
I need to put some money together.
I don't have stacks of cash
laying around, and even if I did...
Lucy.
Michael.
Okay,
there may be something.
I'll call Sam.
Sam? Sam axe?
You still work with him?
Not when I can avoid it...
He's been drinking,
sponging off
of every rich divorc\e
in the greater miami area.
I throw him a job every now and then
when he's between sugar mommies.
What's the drama?
Guy's an operation manager
at an estate in miami beach.
Anyway, the place got robbed, and it
looks like he's in some kind of trouble.
What kind of trouble?
He didn't want
to get into it.
We talked price... Guy's
breaking open his piggy bank.
I told him the job
was a little small for us,
but he sounded desperate, so I
told him I'd keep my eyes open.
You're all heart.
Do you want the job or not?
I'll call Sam.
Thank you, Lucy.
Get yourself cleaned up.
New clothes.
You look terrible.
You look good.
Don't go away.
...Mama.
I assume you got word
of my situation?
You know spies.
Bunch of bitchy little girls.
Good news for you...
I'm a drunk and a washout already,
so I can talk to whoever I want,
burned or no.
You hear anything else?
Nobody tells me anything.
I'm not exactly
security-clearance material anymore.
Oh, Sam.
There she is!
keep 'em coming.
Look at the bright side... They
wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
Florida will do you some good.
I've been here a year,
and I've never been better.
Yeah, I understand
your main source of income
is an allowance
from a lawyer's wife.
Hey, don't knock it.
Free clothes,
ocean-view apartment,
and an endless supply
of little blue pills.
Speaking of apartments, you know
a safe place I can stay?
I been at a motel
with the girls gone wild.
I know a guy. I'll make a call.
How long you around?
Just long enough to put together some
cash and track down this burn notice.
Hey, so, this job tomorrow...
You want to do the meeting, or you need
me to come along and hold your hand?
Yeah, I'll be fine, Sam.
With this much money,
things get complicated.
Change a light bulb
in a place like this,
and a week later
you're on a speedboat
in the cayman islands
with someone shooting at you.
Mr. Westen.
I spoke to Lucy.
She told me
you do investigations.
I do a lot of things.
Last month,
there was a robbery.
$22 million
in odd jewelry and antiques.
It was very bad.
Looks like the police
are into it.
Says here they're talking
to persons of interest.
You're a person of interest.
The police asked me questions.
When this happened, I was
at home watching tv with my kid.
The security code they used for
the alarm is the master code.
My code.
Besides supervise the staff,
I set the shifts.
- It looks bad.
- Yeah, that looks pretty bad.
I told the police,
I worked there 15 years.
I would never do this.
Mr. Pyne talked to them,
said it wasn't me.
They took my passport,
told me not to travel.
If they arrest me,
my son, he's 8 years old.
I'm all he has.
"I'm desperate. Please
don't make my son an orphan."
just so we're clear...
You want me to figure out
who ran off
with $22 million in stuff,
catch the bad guys,
clear your name,
all for... What is it?
$4,500?
$4,600.
Oh, well,
that's much better.
I'm sorry.
I have nowhere else to turn.
Please.
All right,
I'm gonna see what I can do.
I need to talk to your boss.
Can I do that?
Yeah. Come on.
What are you, exactly,
mr. Westen?
A private detective?
Oh, no, I wish.
Nothing that official.
No, I'm just a friend
of a friend in town for a while.
I thought
I'd see if I can help.
Oh, thank you.
Javier's been with me
for a number of years.
It kills me
to see what he's going through.
What was stolen?
Some jewelry,
some artwork.
Insured, but the artwork
was irreplaceable.
Impressionists, mostly.
I had a sisley,
a clausen, and some other works.
Houses, landscapes.
I'm in real estate, so I've got
this thing for houses.
And you're confident Javier
had nothing to do with it?
Oh, this is miami.
Any incident, and the police
blame the nearest cuban.
Or haitian.
You should have seen the way
they were all over my gardeners.
What about
the security codes?
Oh, lord knows.
The police are looking into it.
You know, to be honest,
I'm just glad nobody was hurt.
Was there anyone
unknown to you around... Guests?
Any new business associates
that came to the house?
Not that I can think of. I went
over all this with the police.
You can talk to Vince
if you want to.
He takes care of my security.
I just have a few questions,
see if anyone missed anything.
I talked to the police.
I don't mean to bother you.
It would be a big help.
Does mr. Pyne
have any enemies?
Anybody worth $100 mil
has enemies.
Which is why
he hired a bodyguard,
I mean, a head of security.
I'm specifically talking
about enemies
that might rob his home, though.
We know who did this.
Mr. Pyne has a soft spot
for Javier.
I don't.
As far as I'm concerned,
the sooner he's arrested,
the better.
Well, you've been
a big help.
Place is upstairs in the back.
Rent is $200 a month, and...
If anyone finds out I'm there,
I say I broke in... Sam told me.
It's not so easy to live
in this place, you know.
All night,
club is boom-boom.
Fine, it's fine.
But I think guy next door
sells drugs to my customers.
Make fight with people.
Try to talk,
he puts a gun in my face.
Now, at home,
I can deal.
But here, with immigration,
liquor license,
it's a big risk for me, yeah?
I can handle that.
good.
The real Michael Westen,
yes?
Yeah.
Back home, your story russian
intelligence tells to scare.
They say you are one name
for many people.
Special operations team.
They think one person
cannot make so much problems.
Nope.
Just me.
Nice to meet you, Michael.
New world, yes?
Yes.
Mom?
My mom would have been a great
nsa communications operative.
How did you get this number?
That's how you greet
your mother?
I got it from your girlfriend...
Fiona.
Mom, what do you want?
Were you gonna come and see me?
I'm not gonna be in town
that long, so I can't.
Come now, then.
You can drive me to the doctor.
I don't even have a car,
so I...
Yeah. Well, you'll figure
something out.
Drop me in the middle
of the gobi desert.
Bury me in a goddamn cave
on the moon.
And somehow,
she'd find a way to call me
and ask me for a favor.
I don't like stealing cars,
but sometimes it's necessary.
I have rules, though...
I'll keep it clean.
If I take your car on a work day,
I'll have it back by 5:00.
Things have gone to hell since you left.
Thank god you're back.
I'm not back.
You're here for the holidays, though.
You're staying for christmas...
Mom, don't smoke in the car,
please. It's not mine.
Please.
Figuring out if a car
is tailing you
is mostly about driving
like you're an idiot.
You speed up, slow down,
signal one way, turn the other.
Of course, ideally, you're doing this
without your mother in the car.
Michael, where are you going?
The hospital is on 20th.
This is a shortcut. Mom,
please do not smoke in the car.
Donotsmoke in the car.
You know, you missed
your father's funeral.
By eight years.
Well, last time I talked to him,
he said, "I'll see you in hell, boy."
so I figured we had
something on the books.
Michael.
The two of you
were so much alike.
I don't know why
you had to antagonize him.
Mom, we werenothingalike.
Everything I did
antagonized him.
Being alive antagonized him.
Everything I did was a reason
for him to slap me around.
Michael, what are you doing?
Who's driving... You or me?
Actually, losing a tail
isn't about driving fast.
A high-speed pursuit
is just gonna land you on the 6:00 news.
So you just keep driving
like an idiot
until the other guy
makes a mistake.
Again, all of this is easier
without a passenger
yelling at you
for missing a decade's worth
of thanksgivings.
You were the one
that kept the family going.
After you left,
everything just fell apart.
I've been sending money.
What about nate?
Don't get me started.
Your brother is a mess.
You really should go see him,
Michael.
I don't think it's a good idea
for us to see each other.
I can't take care of him all by myself.
I am sick.
You know that I'm sick.
Well, what I know
is that you've been treated
for every disease
known to man.
I know this because
I'm paying all the bills.
Just because they can't find out
what's wrong with me
does not mean
I'm not sick.
Please!
You don't know, Michael.
I don't tell you
everything that goes on.
I don't need to know
everything.
What?
stop.
Mike...
Just...
Look, we're here.
Are you coming in?
No, I have to make
a phone call, mom.
I'm right behind you.
Fine, Michael.
Okay, mom.
Michael Westen for dan siebels.
I'm sorry...
Yeah, I know, I know,
he doesn't exist.
You tell him from me
if he doesn't call me back, I
will be in touch with him soon.
Sorry, I'm, uh...
I just... I'm not...
Yeah, he's with her.
Sleep through
an aerial bombing or two
and noise isn't an issue.
You just need some privacy
and a bed.
In a pinch,
you can lose the bed.
But the privacy is important
for projects like this one.
With everyone x-raying
and chemical-testing their mail
these days,
a box of wire and pipe
and batteries sprinkled
with chemical fertilizer
is a great attention-getter.
Hey. Thanks for coming.
Come on in.
You want some coffee?
No, no.
It's not a problem.
I made some just fresh.
I just wanted to
talk about...
This is my son, david.
David, say hi.
Hi.
Are you a soldier?
Uh... No.
Sort of.
My dad says
you're here to help us.
I might be. I just need to talk
to your dad about some money first.
Then are you gonna shoot
the people that robbed mr. Pyne?
No, no.
That shouldn't be necessary.
What if they shoot at you?
Well, in that case,
it would be necessary, so yeah.
Okay.
David, go play.
I can play here.
In your room.
Want to see my room?
David, go.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
So, will you help?
I'll need half the money
up front.
I don't know, $2,300.
Okay, wait. Wait.
I need you to know something.
I'll follow this
wherever it leads.
I finish what I start.
We do it my way... No questions.
Got it?
Thank you.
Working hard?
Tanning is an art
and a science, Mike.
You want something to drink?
They can bring you whatever you want.
No, I'm fine.
So, what have you found out
about Pyne's hired gun?
Well, he washed out of the
rangers after a couple years.
Then he went to work for some
private military outfit in iraq,
some kind of meathead
mercenary sort of thing.
Any progress with the job?
I checked the estate's
security logs... Nothing there.
So it's the hard way, then.
The best angle is the art.
I find the buyer,
I'll work my way back
to who pulled off the job.
Well, how you gonna do that?
I need you to set up a meeting
with me and Barry.
Can do.
Whether you're a coke dealer,
a thief, an arms dealer,
or a spy, you need someone
to clean your money.
Which makes a good money launderer
the closest thing you
can get to a yellow pages
for criminals.
Even better,
a money launderer will always
take your phone call,
burn notice or no burn notice.
Good to see you.
I've heard about your troubles.
Yeah, well, I'm working on it.
Thanks for coming, Barry.
I'm in the service industry.
That's what I do... I help.
So...
What you need?
An art dealer.
No, no, no, no.
Art's a bad place
to park money these days.
I.R.S. Is all over the place.
Plus, some schmuck in new york
says the wrong thing,
take a bath.
How about stamps?
Nice and portable.
Coins.
Got this guy who does coins.
All cash.
Has to be art...
I need someone to find me
a piece that's not
on the regular market.
Hot paintings.
I might know someone.
Nobody gets hurt?
Nobody you care about.
Just remember who still helped
you when you were down.
Me, Barry... That's who.
I gave you love.
You remember?
I'll remember.
Excuse me.
I'm just...
Sorry, man, we were waiting
on sugar and got carried away.
Sugar?
Yeah, I don't know
his real name,
but he usually hooks us up...
We wanted to score some "e."
are you the new guy?
leave.
Now.
Mom, what is it?
This isn't your mom.
Dan, hey, good to hear from you.
I thought you lost my number.
Just spent three hours
with the fbi,
discussing your little present.
They wondered why someone was sending me
a pipe bomb with no explosive in it.
Thought it'd get your attention.
So tell me what's going on.
I don't know.
Burn notice is eyes-only.
For what it's worth,
I think it's bull,
but I don't control
these things.
Tell me who to talk to
or I'm coming to d.C.
And raising some hell.
Don't do that, Michael.
You're on
all the fbi watch lists.
You go anywhere,
they're all over you.
What for?
All I know is that whoever
did this wants you on ice.
You leave miami,
you heat up fast.
We're talking manhunt,
police in every state.
Things may change,
but for now, be smart.
Lay low.
Can I at least see
the burn notice?
If I could see who issued it, then
maybe I can do something about this.
I risked enough just calling.
Look, some of us
are still on your side.
You pull another stunt like this,
though, and I won't be one of them.
What's up, bro?
You new around here?
Well, my name is sugar.
And I heard you messed with
some of my friends last night.
I asked a few of your customers
to get out of here, yeah.
What's your problem?
My problem right now
is a pretty-boy drug dealer
with a bad dye job
that's standing in my way.
Ohh!
whoa,
did I hurt you, bro?
Doesn't matter
how much traing you have...
A broken rib is a broken rib.
Don't start fights
you can't finish, bro!
I'll break it.
I don't want to,
but I will if I have to.
All right, all right!
All right, let go!
Let go! Let go!
You come highly recommended,
mr. Westen.
What are you
interested in...
Specifically?
British post-impressionists.
Sisley, steer.
That's nice.
We don't see much of that.
Most specialty stock
is out of the east these days.
Iraqi antiquities,
russian icons.
Although
that's mostly forged garbage.
I can get you
some french impressionists.
My collection is mostly focused
on the camden town group.
Oh. Very nice.
I wish I had something.
Several pieces were on
the market about six months ago.
There was a sisley
and several clausens.
Although, it didn't sell.
Really?
Do you rember who?
Oh, I don't remember the name.
One of these condo developers
that are everywhere these days.
But, during the impressionist
bubble in the '90s,
he went to all the major
dealers... Wanted to dump it.
It was all very discreet,
but...
People talk.
Really?
What happened?
Nobody was interested is what
happened... Not at his price.
I'm sorry I can't help, but...
No, no, no, you... You have been
very helpful. Thank you.
I do have some greco-roman
nude wrestling statues
you might like
to take a look at.
I never run around
in the bushes in a ski mask
when I'm breaking in someplace.
Somebody catches you,
what are you gonna say?
You want to look
like a legitimate visitor
until the very last minute.
If you can't look legit,
confused works almost as well.
Maybe get a soda
from the fridge or a yogurt.
If you're caught,
you just act confused
and apologize like crazy
for taking the yogurt.
Nothing could be more innocent.
Cracking an old-school safe
is pretty tough,
but modern high-tech security
makes it much easier.
Thing is, nobody wipes off
a fingerprint scanner
after they use it,
so what's left on the scanner
9 times out of 10
is a fingerprint.
Fighting for the little guy
is for suckers.
We all do it once in a while,
but the trick
is to get in and out quickly
without getting involved.
That's one trick
I never really mastered.
Javier? Javier?
You want some cereal?
no.
All I got is the one with
the little marshmallow guys.
Don't worry about that.
I just want to talk to you
before you go to work.
What is it?
Is it something wrong?
Basically,
your boss sold you out.
He robbed his own house,
probably had Vince do the job.
He collects the insurance,
and you're the fall guy.
Mr. Pyne?
No, he wouldn't...
He talked to the police for me.
That just makes it easier for
him to collect on the insurance.
You're a trusted employee.
He had no idea.
Take a look at this.
Half his real-estate projects
are just paper...
Empty lots he paid
a loan officer to sign off on.
He borrowed against those
to finance other deals,
but with the market cooling,
he's bleeding money,
and the art is all he has.
Without the insurance payout,
it all comes crashing down.
What do I do?
Well, you could go to jail...
10 years, give or take.
You could run.
Statute of limitations
is about 20 years.
Or you could fight back.
Pyne doesn't want any of this
to get out.
As long as we have this
information, we have leverage.
I'll handle the details.
But it could get dangerous.
People do bad things when
this much money is on the line.
Money...
Don't worry about the money.
You want to do this or not?
You're not going to work today
or ever again.
I'm gonna go talk to Pyne.
But be prepared...
This could get sketchy.
Hey.
You really want me
to shoot someone, don't you?
Hey.
So, mr. Westen,
what can I do for you?
I just wanted
to update you.
Fortunately, I think
we can be pretty sure
that Javier had nothing to do
with the robbery.
Have you spoken
to the police?
I'm not sure you want me
to do that.
Take a look at this.
I think this points
pretty clearly
to, um, some other suspects.
Where'd you get this?
I found it in
the course of my investigation.
Cops might find it, too,
if, say, Javier was arrested.
I'm guessing that's something
you'd want to avoid.
Well, you two
have a lot to talk about.
I know my way out.
Does that shirt
come in men's?
You're head of my security!
Well, it's your job,
damn it!
Powerful people
don't like being pushed around.
You can never quite predict
what they're going to do...
Or have
their washed-out special-forces
security guys do.
The point is, blackmail is a
little like owning a pit bull.
It might protect you,
or it might bite your hand off.
That's why it pays to make sure
you know what they're thinking,
and that means eavesdropping.
Hi, can I help you?
Yeah, I need two of these...
And your cheapest phone...
That one?
Oh, the "hello, sweetheart."
is it for your little girl?
No.
Oh, the "hello, sweetheart."
yeah, that's fine.
To build a listening device,
you need a crappy phone with a
Mike that picks up everything.
But you want the battery power
and circuits of a better phone.
It's a trick you learn
when the purchasing office
won't spring for a bug.
Hello, sweetheart.
So, Sam and I are gonna plant
the bug tomorrow
so we can listen in on Pyne.
Fi, I want to ask you,
um...
Yeah?
I need someone to track him,
provide a little
tactical support.
Sure.
It'll be just like the old days.
That sounds like fun.
I'm glad you think so.
I haven't worked so hard for so
little money since afghanistan.
Afghanistan.
But at least there,
my mother wasn't calling me
30 times a day.
Thank you
for giving her my number.
You're welcome.
Any thoughts as to why
you're so unpopular?
Why didn't they just kill you?
It might be a lesson,
a warning.
Maybe somebody
wants to offer me a job,
but they want me desperate
before they make the offer.
It could be a lot of things.
I don't know.
It'll be good for you to stay in
one place, resolve some issues.
Well, I travel
halfway across the world
to get away from those.
My point exactly.
Maybe if you stop running,
you can maintain
a normal relationship.
Listen, fi, there's a few things
I'm good at...
Tactical analysis, hand-to-hand
combat, and I'm a decent cook.
But relationships...
They're just not my thing.
They never were.
Well, now you're in miami.
Get yourself a 24-year-old
with big, fake tits.
They bore me.
If it makes you feel
any better...
You were the closest...
I ever got.
It... It just wasn't
close enough, I guess.
Things could have worked out
with us, Michael.
You were robbing banks
for the I.R.A.
A spy is just a criminal
with a government paycheck.
You're the one with two
fbi agents watching him eat.
Three.
One.
Two.
Behind me at the bar.
Bravo.
Shall we shoot them?
I've got enough problems.
Well, more sake, then?
When.
When, fi. When.
What? What?
I can't shag a man
who works in a bank.
The end.
He was rich, he's handsome,
and you broke up with him.
He had
no tactical awareness.
He didn't know how to shoot.
He didn't know how many exits
were in a building.
Oh, god!
You spoil me, Michael.
I thought it was
my winning smile.
Don't move.
Sugar wants you out.
She has nothing to do
with this.
Shut up.
He's right.
Michael, shut up.
I can handle myself.
You really ought to do something
about your neighbors.
I know, I know.
Fun.
yeah?
Shall we?
Yeah, well, fi, fi...
Violence is foreplay for you.
It's not for me.
I got to take care of this,
and then I got to go to bed.
Night.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Fi, you know, I could...
That went well.
You'll like this.
I found out Vince is calling
all his army buddies,
trying to figure out
who you are.
Yeah, good luck with that.
I don't even know.
I'll have them feed him
something, hold him off.
Well, stay on it.
I have a little home-improvement
project I have to do.
Once somebody sends
a guy with a gun after you,
things are only going
to get worse.
But like it or not,
you've got work to do.
For a job like getting rid
of the drug dealer next door,
I'll take a hardware store
over a gun any day.
Guns make you stupid.
Better to fight your wars
with duct tape.
Duct tape makes you smart.
Every decent punk
has a bulletproof door.
Who's there?
Hi. It's your neighbor.
But people forget
walls are just plaster.
Hopefully, you get him
with the first shot.
Or the second.
My knee!
Come on inside!
Now he's down
and waiting for you
to come through the front door.
So you don't come through
the front door.
Don't move.
Easy, vanilla ice.
Now, you got 20 minutes
to clear out.
Do you understand?
Yes! Yes!
The wound is not that bad.
Disinfect it, wrap it in this,
and you get to a hospital.
You won't walk with a limp...
You're still here in 20 minutes,
a limp will be
the least of your problems.
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
Look, point is,
you getting burned
wouldn't have happened back then.
I mean, in the '80s,
the rules were the rules.
They had their guys,
we had our guys...
Wasn't so goddamn complicated.
You could get your head
around it.
Now, today, it's all
about religion and oil.
It's no fun anymore.
I tell you,
I'm glad I got out when I did.
Good morning, bloody mary.
Hey, you want some?
No, I'm fine.
Hey, is that your mom
again?
Yep.
All right, there she is.
Pyne's coming out soon.
You sure this is a good idea,
you hooking up with her again?
I'm not hooking up with her.
That's not what's happening.
I need her for tactical support.
Is that what they're calling it
these days? Tactical support?
What about your cab driver?
Is he gonna let me down?
Pierre?
Don't worry about him.
I told him I'd give him 50 bucks
to punch me in the face.
That's all he had to hear.
Yeah, I'd do it for $20.
I don't want any excuses.
Now, you're my damn attorney.
I want to know what I can do
about this situation.
Hey, what the hell was that?!
You cut me off!
No, no, no, no, no!
There are two lanes!
You got a problem?
Yeah, I got a problem.
Hey, I'm not
through with you, man!
I'm calling...
I got your number!
The bastard breaks
into my house, into my safe.
You can't tell me
a damn thing about him?
Here you go, Mike.
Less than a week in miami,
you're already making friends.
It doesn't sound like he's
gonna roll over that easy.
Yeah, these rich guys bite
when you got them by the tail.
Call me
if he makes any moves.
We'll get about 24 hours
out of that battery.
It's voice-activated,
so you'll hear a beep.
Yeah, I know the drill, Mike.
You do your thing.
People with happy families
don't become spies.
A bad childhood is the perfect
background for covert ops.
You don't trust anyone,
you're used
to getting smacked around,
and you never get homesick.
I think I've got a parasite.
You don't have a parasite.
Pills don't work... As soon
as it reaches your liver...
The pills are for you not to
think you're sick all the time.
You and the doctor,
you think I'm crazy.
I think he's letting me
die of a parasite
'cause I can't pay his bill.
Oh, for now,
can we just try these pills?
I put up the tree.
I can see that.
Did you go see
your brother yet?
'Cause, um...
I thought we could all be, you
know, together for christmas.
But he's not returning
my calls.
The last time I saw him,
he threw a telephone book
at my head.
So what makes you think
ican make him come home?
Remember when you were 6
and daddy locked you
in your room and wouldn't let you see
the "star wars" movie?
Well, you just pulled up
the floor
and sneaked out
through the heating vent.
I mean, since when
was there ever anything
that you wanted to do
that you couldn't do?
Please, Michael.
For me.
30 years of karate...
Combat experience
on five continents...
A rating with every weapon
that shoots a bullet
or holds an edge...
Still haven't found any defense
against mom crying
into my shirt.
Mom, I-I can't,
'cause I'm gonna...
I'm sorry, hold on.
We got trouble, Mike.
Well, what is it?
Looks like Pyne is trying to get
some leverage of his own.
Vincent, you're gonna have
to go over and take the kid.
I don't know
what the hell else to do.
Maybe then we can talk
some sense into Javier.
Jesus, the kid.
Pyne got Javier
out of the house.
He had his lawyer call
with some legal thing.
Now the kid is home alone,
and your boy Vince
is on his way over there.
How long ago?
I called as soon as I heard,
brother.
Mom, where's your tool box?
You about to get ran over.
Move over.
Damn, please don't jack me!
This is not a carjacking.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I just need a big car
with no airbags.
You need a what?
Where the hell
are you taking me, man?
Just got to go to little havana
for a bit.
Little havana?! Just let me out.
I'll forget I ever seen you.
I don't have time
to drop you off right now.
Watch out for this car!
You got to get this fixed.
This is really annoying.
I just need to do something
real quick.
What do you need to do?
All right, man.
Slow down, slow down, all right?
It's almost over, okay?
What does "almost over" mean?
There's a lot of cops
around this area, dude.
Sean, hold on really tight.
Why do I
have to hold on tight?!
Because...
Of... This.
Look what you did to my car!
Damn, look at my car!
Air bags save a lot of lives.
But they also put you out
long enough
to get your hands cable-tied
to the steering wheel.
I just had this fixed!
Who's gonna pay for my car, man?
Sean, there's cash
in his wallet.
The rolex should take care
of the rest.
The cops will be here soon.
I'd be someplace else.
But how I'm-a get home?!
What's up?
Yeah, he's fine.
Do you have a place to stay?
Great.
You'll come get him?
Good.
David, your dad
will be here soon.
You two are gonna stay
with your aunt for a while.
You live here?
I usually stay
at four-star hotels.
I mean, I don't really have
a lot of...
Stuff.
If you're hungry, there's a
blueberry yogurt in the fridge.
That black eye...
How'd you get it?
Kids at school.
Yeah, why?
I don't know.
They don't need a reason,
mostly.
Last time,
they took my new shoes.
The time before,
it was just 'cause.
How many were there?
Is it a group
or an individual?
It matters...
Tactically.
It's a group.
They get up in my face, and
they start pounding me, okay?
Are you crying?
You're not crying?
Looks like you're crying.
Don't, okay?
All right, don't cry.
All right, stop, all right?
You have to lose some fights
so you can learn to win.
I mean, look at this.
I got the crap
beat out of me.
I have two black belts,
and they kicked my ass.
So you got nothing
to be ashamed of with me, okay?
I'm the champ
of getting beaten up.
But I'm also very good
at winning.
You want it to stop?
Yeah.
The key to fighting a group
is taking out its leader.
Take out its leader,
they'll all leave you alone.
It's bully psychology.
Works with third-world
military units, as well.
When I was in afghanistan...
Never mind that.
Um, who's the leader?
His name's jake.
Jake.
I'm gonna push you.
When I do that, you drop down
into a ball like you're scared.
Protect yourself.
Tight up like a ball.
Good.
Now, he's gonna move in
to make fun of you.
Keep those elbows tight.
He tries to kick you.
Protect that spleen, protect that liver.
I want you to stand up quick
and get your head right up
underneath my chin.
Go.
I'm a little dazed.
Make your fist.
One, two, three, four, five.
Very good.
Guys, it's like I told you.
There's nothing else.
We did the one job, and that's it.
How about the threatening package?
You may not take that seriously,
but the terror...
Oh, come on, guys.
He was just making a point.
We're not here
for our health, Sam.
Hi, guys.
Talking about me?
Can I get a coffee?
Sam.
Hey, Mike.
You don't want to introduce me
to your fbi buddies?
You got the wrong idea, pal.
Ford outside
has g-series plates.
Fast-draw holsters, off-the-rack
suits, and cheap loafers.
No, you guys are feds.
They're feds!
Michael, look, they came to me.
I was just trying to help.
It's not like I didn't know,
Sam.
I've got two known associates
in miami... You and Lucy...
And amazingly, you're
both willing to help me?
I know
how the game is played, Sam.
I was on the other side,
remember?
So. I'm Michael Westen.
You are...
Agent harris.
This is agent lane.
Do you even know
why you're following me?
Don't know, don't care.
Higher up the food chain.
Great. Let's call your boss.
Maybe he can tell me.
Those aren't our orders.
Our orders are to keep tabs on you.
Then you give him a message.
You tell him...
Sorry.
I do have a message for you, though.
Don't go thinking
you got nothing to lose.
You got friends.
You got family.
Is that a threat,
agent harris?
It's the truth.
Coffee's on me.
Mike, they got
my pension tied up.
Sam, Sam.
Look, they said
it would be better for you.
You can do anything you want, basically,
as long as you stay
where they can see you
and you don't cause any trouble.
Sam, don't sprinkle sugar on
this bull and call it candy.
I'm sorry, Mike.
I- I don't know what to say.
If I couldn't handle
my friends informing on me,
I wouldn't be in the business.
The way I see it,
better a friend
than someone I don't know.
The way I see it,
a friend would tell them
just enough to make them happy
but keep them
out of my business.
Hell, yeah, Mike,
absolutely.
Good. Good.
I got to go.
I got to go take care of Pyne.
You want me to come along?
It's the least I can do.
No, I can handle it.
Good luck, Mike.
When you work solo,
it's about prepping the ground.
Home-court advantage
counts for a lot.
You never know
what's going to happen.
You prepare for everything.
Most bad guys expect you
to just sit there
and wait for them
like those are the rules
or something.
Hello? Who's this?
He's there.
Hi, there.
Where is he?
Uh, Javier? He's not here.
Listen, we need to talk.
I'm not screwing around.
Where the hell is he?
He's not here.
Anything you need to say to him,
you can say to me.
I'm done talking, mr. Westen.
I don't know how in the hell
you got in my safe,
but I want to make it clear...
I will not be intimidated.
Well, neither will I.
By the way,
you're gonna have a hard time
blowing my brains out
with the safety on.
Whoa, hey, the safety was off!
What do you know... My mistake.
Vince, what the hell?
If you're going to put prints
on a gun,
sticking it into somebody's
hand isn't going to do it.
Any decent lawyer
can explain prints on a gun.
But try explaining
prints on the inside
of the trigger assembly.
Who...
Who was doing
all the shooting?
We have a special guest.
This bad boy!
.357 magnum loaded with blanks,
duct-taped to a flare.
Sounded like the real thing,
didn't it?
I need a hospital.
In a sec.
We're talking.
You shot your buddy here,
mr. Pyne.
And this...
This...
This here is
a crime lab's wet dream.
What do you want?
In a second. I'm not done
with my show-and-tell.
Vincent, you're gonna have
to go over and take the kid.
I don't know
what the hell else to do.
That is you
plotting a kidnapping.
That's hard time...
Federal time.
That's the rest
of your life.
Tell me what you want.
Vince here confesses
to the robbery,
Javier gets severance pay...
Five years,
with benefits and dental...
That's very important...
And never sees your mug again.
And you know what,
for christmas,
throw in a college fund for
david... How does that sound?
Well, let's get you out of here.
This will be a murder weapon
in 20 minutes
if Vince doesn't get
to the hospital.
And the documents...
The financial information?
We'll see
how good of a boy you are.
'Cause I'll be watching.
I cleaned up your place pretty well,
but you're gonna have
to replace the carpet.
But no one's gonna bother you
or your family again.
You can go home.
Thank you.
I don't... I don't know
how to say it, but...
Don't worry about it.
Yeah?
Can I borrow your binoculars?
No, I know you got some in
there, and you're not using them
because you need them to see me,
and I'm right here. So...
Please?
Fight! Fight!
As a spy, it doesn't matter
if you're helping rebel forces
fight off a dictator
or giving combat tips to a third-grader.
There's nothing like helping
the little guy kick some bully's ass.
There's nothing worse
for a spook
than knowing
you're being played...
Someone is pulling strings.
Who?
Not some intelligence-agency
bureaucrat in a cubicle.
This is someone
with more style.
Not fbi, either.
They're not this creative, and they
don't do surveillance on their own guys.
This is someone
who knows what he's doing,
someone who wants to send
a message.
"WELCOME TO MIAMI."
Subtitles: swsub.com