My name is Michael Westen.
I used to be a spy until...
We got a burn notice.
you're blacklisted.
When you're burned,
you've got nothing...
no cash, no credit,
no job history.
You're stuck in whatever city
they decide to dump you in.
- Where am I?
- Miami.
You do whatever work
comes your way.
You rely on anyone
who's still talking to you.
A trigger-happy
ex-girlfriend...
Should we shoot them?
... an old friend who's
informing on you to the FBI...
you know spies...
a bunch of bitchy little girls.
... family, too...
Is that your mom again?
... if you're desperate.
someone needs your help.
Bottom line... until
you figure out who burned you,
you're not going anywhere.
You must be getting used to this.
Isn't there a part of you that's
beginning to like Miami?
It's fine. "fine"?
There are people who come here
from all over the world.
They don't have water front
like this in afghanistan.
It doesn't rain as much,
either, there.
There are pleasant parts
of Afghanistan.
The mountains are nice.
Maybe we can
vacation there someday.
Oh, when you can travel again,
of course...
some special occasion.
Speaking of which,
it's my birthday in a few days.
Did you get me anything yet?
Yeah, I got you something.
You know, for someone who's worked
as professional liar
for most of his career,
you're not terribly good at it
when it counts.
What's he doing...
your mystery man?
Getting heatstroke, it looks like.
Well, Michael,
I'm pretending that I'm here
for more than just tactical backup.
we're supposed to be playing
boyfriend and girlfriend.
Do you want me to get you
a shaved ice, Fi?
I mean, I need someone, okay?
what's this guy's name again?
Perry Clark... that's the name
he gave me on the phone.
And he said he was here
to review your status?
That's desk-jockey jargon
for what, now?
He may be able to get me
off the blacklist,
revoke my burn notice.
And now you're about
to piss him off on purpose.
just a precaution, Fi.
I have learned to be careful.
work around spies for a while,
and you learn to be careful
when it looks like you're
getting what you want.
that's when you tend to let
your guard down, get careless.
look at him, Michael.
he's a cubicle monkey.
calling the cops on someone
can teach you a lot.
a foreign agent would run.
so might an armed assassin.
a bureaucrat's going to act
like a bureaucrat.
you can't look in that, sir!
I think he just passed
your little test.
well, aren't you gonna talk to him?
now might not be the best time.
Clark: I'm going to slowly reach
into my left inside pocket
with my right hand and give
you my I.D., very slowly.
everybody remain calm.
I work with css.
http://www.ragbear.com
I have been
more than patient, Mr. Westen.
I was willing to meet you
in a public park,
as you requested,
rather than my office.
I came down in the middle
of my workday.
I'm sorry.
I must have missed you.
yeah, I had a conversation
with the police
about a suspicious man
matching my description.
you're not the first field op
I've dealt with, Mr. Westen.
believe me, I've been vetted
every which way.
maybe we can set up
a new time.
I have had enough of new times
and places and tests.
I hope I don't have
to remind you
that my recommendation
carries weight
when it comes to removing you
from this blacklist.
bureaucrats live for respect.
east of the balkans,
that means a bribe.
in the west,
it's more about showing
you know they're in charge.
and I expect a little more
consideration for my time.
yeah, I apologize.
it won't happen again.
it's just I talked
with a man on the phone
who burned me recently.
he seemed unhappy.
this is not
about one nsa officer
who acted on information
in a file.
this is a departmental review
in which I...
let's set up a new time,
a new place to meet.
we'll review the file.
I'll check my schedule.
thank you.
you keep
pissing him off, Michael,
you'll be in Miami
forever.
at least I'll get an answer.
the government
sent him down here,
and he's not gonna go
back to d.c.
without getting
a verdict on me.
not at his pay grade,
anyway.
you think you could convince him
that you were set up?
I read the dossier.
it's pretty convincing.
yeah, Sam?
Mike,
I'm on my way over.
there's that thing I need you to
help me look into right away.
Sam,
I'm in the middle of --
new car.
yeah. it's a gift
from the lady friend.
I got it yesterday.
it's like
driving on a cloud.
what exactly do you do
for these women, Sam?
well --
never mind.
anyway,
thanks for coming.
I didn't have much choice.
yeah, well, you owe me
'cause I've been checking
into this guy from d.c.
what did you find out?
well,
I'm still working on it,
but he's a paper pusher.
he's a name and a cubicle.
that's all you got?
well, hey, you know,
with the crap you've been doing,
I'm not getting much love
in d.c.
keep digging, Sam.
keep digging.
I will, brother.
anyway, so this guy
we're gonna go see,
my lady friend
hooked me up with him.
he's got some kind of problem,
and he heard that she had
a boyfriend who could help.
"he heard that she had
a boyfriend that could help"?
I was vague.
I said I was
a freelance superhero/robin hood
kind of guy.
that's vague.
Mike...
a house like this, I mean,
it's probably some
expensive kitten up a tree...
a cakewalk.
you're Sam?
yeah, I'm Sam.
thanks for meeting me.
yeah, no problem.
this is Michael, the guy I told
you about over the phone.
yeah, your assistant.
what's up, bro?
uh, oh, no, no.
it's actually more like
a partner sort of thing.
so, veronica said
you want to talk?
yeah, dude.
I've got a serious problem.
come inside.
after you.
place like this,
you could have called
halliburton to help you out.
halliburton?
I don't know him.
I'm saying
you seem to be doing
pretty well
for yourself, Nick.
oh, no.
I don't own this.
I'm a house sitter.
I work three or four estates
on the island.
that's a job --
house sitter?
yeah, these people are only here
a few weeks out of the year.
okay, so, do you need
an application for that?
Sam.
tell me your problem,
Nick.
that's dawn.
she's my fiancéE.
she was kidnapped
the day before yesterday,
and the people that took her
want, like, $5 million.
and they think you have
that kind of money?
well, the thing
about this job
is that you drive these cars
and you stay in these houses,
and people kind of think
that you own them, you know?
and it gets harder to tell them
that you don't.
and your fiancéE thinks
that you own these things.
kind of...
I guess, yeah.
look, I didn't want to tell her
that I was lying to everyone.
I was afraid
I'd lose her, man.
I don't know
what to do, bro.
what you need to do
is call the police.
they said that
they would kill her if I did.
they said they'd know.
here, they sent me this.
they kidnapped that girl
last year,
and her family called the cops,
and now she's dead.
I got, like, an hour
before they're gonna call.
I told them
that I was trying
to get the money
together, but --
hour?
man, I got nowhere else
to turn.
look, you can have
anything you want.
I got about 15 grand.
I got a surfboard collection.
anything, you got it.
are you guys gonna help me
or not?
they're gonna kill her.
okay, okay.
Sam, why don't you go get Fi?
I think we're gonna need
a little help on this cakewalk.
I'm on it, Mike.
okay, Nick.
let's get you ready.
about 40% of kidnapping victims
are released safely.
these statistics are affected
by a number of factors,
including the nationality
of the kidnappers,
the age of the victim,
and whether a hostage
negotiator is employed.
I can't do this, man.
what's the point? they want,
like, 5 million bucks.
the odds go down sharply
if no one has any money
to pay the ransom.
keep it together, Nick.
you're doing fine.
just stick to the script.
do it like we practiced.
really?
it's gonna be okay?
let's just
get through this.
okay.
now, do they usually call
on time or...
that answers
that question.
just like we rehearsed.
pick it up.
Nick, pick up the phone.
Nick!
three, two, one.
hello?
You have the money?
I'm getting it. I just... I need
to know if she's alive first.
you talking to the police?
no, man. i...
I just need to know
that dawn's okay.
she's fine. but if you
don't pay, she won't be.
well, I'm not gonna pay
until I get to see her.
I need to know
you didn't hurt her.
you want 5 million bucks,
I want to see a video.
you're pushing it, carajo.
you're really pushing it.
now, hang on.
a kidnapping
is a business deal.
the bad guys have
negotiating power
since they're selling the life
of a loved one.
but, then again,
they have a market of one,
so they have to work with you.
go to the coconut grove mall --
two hours.
we'll call you.
jesus! oh, jesus.
I thought I was gonna puke, bro.
you did fine, Nick.
you did fine.
so you understand --
you pick up the package,
and you walk away.
you got it?
you don't look at us,
you don't talk to us.
you just walk out
with the video.
Fiona and i
will be watching
to see if the kidnappers
have someone there,
and Sam will follow in the car
if he sees anyone leave.
okay. so I walk to the car?
okay.
no, Nick. focus.
you just walk away.
walk away.
pick up the package,
and you leave...
like we're not even there.
but wait --
you will be there, right?
yes, we will be there.
okay, go ahead.
unlock it first.
okay.
working with untrained amateurs
introduces an element of risk.
it's a risk you have to live
with in a lot of operations,
although you often
find yourself wishing
everyone went through green
beret training in high school.
you buying me
a birthday card?
just window-shopping, Fi.
you got eyes on Nick?
yes...
all the way
from the escalators
to that charming little
they have a fabulous
little teddy in there.
it would make a great gift.
I've never seen you wear
anything but men's shirts
to bed.
fair enough.
there's a men's store
on the third floor.
nice selection.
the ones with the big buttons
are easier to undo.
focus, Fi.
can you see people
on my side of the mall?
'cause I can't look
at everybody.
yeah.
oh, Nick just got a call.
he's looking around.
there he goes.
anyone looking curious?
there's a decent candidate
at the caf?
gray shirt, on your 2.
ah, I see.
how's our ace operative performing?
looking good.
he's going to get the package now.
okay, Nick. walk away.
just walk away, Nick.
no, don't... don't.
he made me, Fi.
once a kidnapper
knows you're on to him,
he'll try to contact
his partners to have
the hostage killed.
at that point,
you have a choice.
you can start choosing wreaths
for the hostage's funeral...
aaaah!
...or take a hostage
of your own.
Thanks.
Nick! just pay them
what they want, please!
I want to go home.
they're gonna call you tonight.
Jesus.
oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
okay, stop saying that.
ohh, god.
I screwed
everything up, bro.
seriously, stop talking.
stop moaning now.
the moaning --
Nick, stop moaning!
listen, Nick.
I'm not saying I'm happy
with how things
went down today, either,
but this can still work out.
in some ways,
we're better off.
how? how are we
better off, dude?
you got some kidnapper
tied up someplace.
you got dawn --
oh, wait.
oh, I get it. you're gonna trade
dawn for the dude.
no.
he's just a hired hand.
if they find out
we've got their guy,
they'll kill her immediately,
probably leave town.
so, how are we
better off?!
they want $5 million
or they kill dawn, yes?
last time I checked, we don't
have $5 million, right?
so our only hope is
to find dawn
before they find out
we don't have $5 million.
we will convince this guy
to help us find dawn.
yeah, okay.
okay.
Michael: the art of turning
someone into a double agent
is delicate.
the target has to be put into
a fragile psychological state.
get this crazy bitch
away from me!
fortunately,
fragile psychological states
are a specialty of Fiona's.
I was just helping
our friend Lucio
into a more
cooperative mood.
where's Sam?
I had to get some air.
it was getting a little,
uh, loud in here.
so, what do we know
about our new friend?
well, his name
is Lucio velazquez,
columbian national.
he's got a rap sheet here
and at home.
he and his brother ran
an extortion racket in columbia.
his brother got caught,
Lucio ran.
good to meet you, Lucio.
go ahead
and taser me all you want.
I'm not gonna
tell you nothing.
taser? oh, no.
we have something
much better than a taser.
we've got an instant camera.
it's always easier
to turn someone
who works for a criminal gang
into a double agent.
the more secretive and ruthless
their side is, the better.
you work on their fear
that any hint of disloyalty
will get them killed
by their own people.
Lucio, you need to think about
your situation very carefully.
you have been caught
in the middle
of a delicate assignment.
say we let you go and give this
photo to your boss...
...along with a cooperating
witness statement
you're about to give
to the FBI?
no, no, no, no.
I never made no statement.
here's the form.
looks real, huh?
we'll fill it out,
sign it on your behalf.
Sam's pretty good
with a computer.
thanks, Mike.
it's just photoshop.
oh, look here.
you have a summons.
it means you're going to testify
in court against your boss.
so, anyway, we take the photo,
we put it in the file.
Sam here has ties to the FBI
and other government agencies
just in case your boss
does his homework.
I have to say, you guys
look pretty tight here.
my guess is he won't feel right
until you're dead.
what do you want, man?
you now work for us,
Lucio.
you tell us
what we want to know,
you do what we say, and that
is how you will stay alive.
where's dawn?
I don't know.
you don't know, Lucio?
no, no, no, no, no! I swear.
I swear. I don't know.
Reyes keeps
everything separate.
Reyes... your boss?
I find people in clubs,
in rich neighborhoods,
and Reyes, he does the job
with two other guys.
someone else
guards the hostages.
everything's separate.
nobody knows each other.
he does that for security.
let me be clear here.
the girl dies, you die.
if you're lying --
I'm not lying, all right?
now, I need to check in
with Reyes. I'm already late.
he's gonna know
that something is wrong.
fine. call him.
you broke your foot walking down
the stairs at the mall.
you forgot to call.
broke my foot?
I didn't break my foot.
aah! ugh.
there you go.
there are a lot of little
bones in your foot, so
you'll be able to walk.
you want to borrow
the mercedes, man?
Yeah.
just please try not
to scratch that car.
it's an s550 amg worth
like 120 grand.
and we need a house.
there's a penthouse downtown
that I watch.
what do you need it for?
we need to find
where dawn is being kept.
Lucio doesn't know.
his job is just finding targets
for Reyes,
so we're gonna have Lucio
bring him a new target...
a rich society wife...
enchant?
...and a disgruntled
bodyguard.
you bitch!
talk to Reyes,
tell him I'm willing
to help him pull the job,
but he's got to show me
where he keeps the hostages.
hopefully they'll bring Sam
to where dawn is,
and we can grab her,
but we got to move fast.
and we need a target
that will make him drool.
from karachI to bogot?
every kidnapper's favorite
resource is a corrupt employee.
her husband's worth
$200 million? good work, Lucio.
an employee
can handle alarms,police.
you can get financial
information,bank accounts.
you've even got a fall guy
if anything goes wrong.
to a professional kidnapper,
a good man on the inside
is worth a lot.
and a bad man on the inside
is worth even more.
Lucio.
okay,okay. I can't do this.
okay,man,I can't. Reyes is gonna
kill me if he finds out.
well,that's the point, Lucio.
you do your job well,
he won't find out,
and you'll stay alive.
did Reyes like our little
business opportunity?
the rich lady
and the bodyguard? yeah.
he loved it. okay,we've been
following them around all day.
he wants to meet
with your guy, talk terms.
what about dawn?
he's impatient.
the guy wants his money.
I held him off a little bit,
but I don't know if
I can do it much longer.
I'm supposed to be calling
you right now
and telling you
that you only got 12 hours
or the girl's dead.
tell him 12 hours isn't long enough.
tell him Nick's family
has hired a hostage negotiator
and that the guy wants
to talk to him in person.
with Reyes? no,no,come on.
you can't be serious.
you convince him it's the best
way for him to get his money.
we just need to buy enough
time to find dawn,
and then you're done,Lucio.
you'll do it?
do I got a choice? no,you don't.
you've got my number.
tell me where and when.
the thing
about doubling anyone
is that the more they do
for you,the deeper they get.
the deeper they get,the more
you can make them do...
great if you're running them,
but hard on the source.
the suicide rate is
above average.
I understand your
concerns,Mr. Westen.
I have worked with field
operatives before.
I may find your priorities
somewhat baroque and unnecessary,
but I suppose that's why
I work in an office
and you run around
the world with guns.
I suppose so,yes.
so,you've now had your opportunity
to screen me in public.
are you satisfied that
I'm not some shadow figure
sent to liquidate you?
can we do our business now? yes.
now,I have security concerns of my own.
as I'm sure you're aware,
your case has certain
issues pertaining to...
national security...
issues that require a private venue.
now,my office in fort lauderdale is...
I would not be able to make it up there
for at least a few days.
that's unfortunate.
maybe this isn't important
enough to you,Mr. Westen.
I have to get back to d.c.
you could come by my place
the night after tomorrow.
you hope to gain some sort
of home-court advantage?
no,it's just that
I need to be around here
for the next few
days for my day job.
if there were any
other way, believe me.
fine. call me with a time.
thank you.
yeah? You wanted to talk to me.
Andrew Chambers... hostage
negotiator for the family.
okay,you got a sniper trained
on you,Mr. Chambers.
tell me why I shouldn't kill you.
Nick's family's not gonna pay
if you shoot the negotiator.
you'd end up with nothing
for your trouble.
how do I know you're not a cop?
cops don't make themselves
available as potential hostages.
they don't get paid enough for that.
I don't know what the magnification
is on your sniper's scope,
but the label... the label's armani.
cops don't fit armani.
how do I look? I look good,right?
you gonna keep playing games?
'cause I got all day.
nice suit. get in.
I like doing my meetings this way.
I hope you don't mind.
No. fine by me.
you know I'm not wearing
a wire. That's smart.
plus,the massage music...
it's really nice...
and calming!
okay,all right.
look,let me get straight to the point.
I'm gonna have a hard time
getting Nick's family
to pay $5 million for dawn.
oh,is that so?
dawn's not part of the family.
the engagement really
isn't that official yet.
I don't want to talk out of school,
but I don't think the family
likes her very much.
well,I wonder how much they would pay
for a smart-ass hostage negotiator?
trust me. at my hourly rate,
you'd be doing them a favor.
sweetie,can you go a little
lower and to the left?
I have a trouble spot right
about... yeah,right there.
okay,so give me a number...
a counter offer.
I think I can close at a million.
$1 million?
that's 20% of my price.
mmm,you are good with numbers.
I take 20% of my price,
I'll give you 20% of the girl.
hostage negotiators hear that one a lot.
it's funny the first few times.
oh,you think I was joking?
it comes down to how much
we're willing to move on the price.
I gave you a number.
now it's your turn.
$3 million. that's as low as I go.
$3 million's gonna be a tough sell.
I'll bring it to the family,
but they'll need at least
72 hours to think it over.
48 hours! after that,the girl dies.
48 hours I can do.
now,could you have one of your
boys turn the heat up?
'cause it's a little chilly...
they paid you for
the whole hour,right?
man: 1 and 2...
is that a makarov? I don't know.
the... the guy who owns this
place is into guns and stuff.
well,that's a soviet-issue
sidearm from 1951,I think.
it's a beautiful piece.
I guess,yeah.
...in a row to begin
the evening for josh beckett.
and the last one
on the curve ball...
how big is that?
it's 60 inches,I think.
quality's nice.
now the curve ball.
is that satellite?
it's directv... HD.
that's why the...
the picture's bigger.
what the hell are we talking about?
look,I know that you asked me
to stop talking about it and
just stay here and watch tv,
but I can't watch any more.
are you gonna be able to save her?
please say yes.
foul off to the right.
we're working on it.
how did we do?
I bought us 48 hours.
yeah. I'm setting up
a meeting with Lucio tonight.
Lucio's gonna set up
a meeting with Sam,
and Sam will get them to tell us
where they keep the hostages.
and we're gonna finish this.
Lucio: Reyes wants to meet your
guy tomorrow to set up this job.
he wants to move on it quick.
did you get a time?
yeah... noon.
I think he's getting sick of waiting.
he wants to get rid of the girl.
hold him off,Lucio.
remember, if she dies...
yeah,I die,too.
we keep this up,though,man,
I'm dead anyway.
we on?
we're on.
GPS devices are becoming more
and more common these days.
mostly they're for nervous
parents tracking children.
but they're perfectly good
for other uses.
Is it working?
Yeah,like a charm,Mike.
you can follow me all over
Miami with that thing.
but wouldn't it be easier to grab her
when she takes her morning
jog along the beach
6:00 a.m. every single day,
nice and early?
I'll consider it.
you're the big boss man here, right?
that's what they tell me.
okay,well, the issue now...
I'm taking a pretty big risk here,
so I expect to be rewarded.
I mean,this is my employer
we're talking about
kidnapping here.
so as soon as this goes down,
I'm out of a job.
well,if what you tell me about
her husband is true,
you'll be very wealthy
when you finish.
I like the sound of that.
all right,now,look,
if this is gonna happen,
I got to know the vehicle
you're taking her in,
and I want to see where
you're gonna keep her,
'cause I hear stories of people
being shoved in dungeons,
and that ain't gonna fly,okay?
she can't get hurt.
she gets hurt,we get a lot
of extra heat here.
hey,we take care
of the operation,okay?
no,you hold it right there,
my columbian friend.
this is 20 million bucks
we're talking about,
and you've been on my ass
about every little detail
about how I deliver her.
as of right now, I'm on the hook
for life without
parole for kidnapping...
same as you,buddy.
so,you like it or not, we're a team.
fine,I'll show you. come on.
They're on the move.
got them.
this is the type of
car you use to grab them?
Reyes: yeah. we prepare
them like this.
we use it once, and then
we discard them.
shame to discard it.
when this job is over,
might get me one of these...
might get two.
it still has that new-car smell.
so,this is where you keep them,huh?
and you have security?
24 hours.
they're well taken care of here.
five years we do this,
only one  unintentional death.
not bad.
all righty,then.
let's do this.
Lucio, you should have called.
I wanted to talk to you face-to-face.
I've done all I can.
running a double agent
is a relationship.
there's a give-and-take...
mostly take,but sometimes
you have to give.
Lucio,you're doing a great job.
You're almost out.
you stay with it,
and you'll be rewarded.
we'll set up a bank
account for you.
Reyes wants to do the other job...
the one with your friend.
he wants to do it now.
he said it's better
to kill the girl so they can
start the other job.
he told me to call you
to finish this.
finish it how?
you have two hours
to get him the money,
or the girl dies.
Nick: you said we had two days,
now two hours...
they're gonna kill her.
not if we get to her first.
We know where they're keeping her.
maybe we should just call the cops.
you think the cops can put
together a rescue plan
in two hours?
the bad guys will be monitoring
the police scanners.
one whisper of this on the radio,
and she's dead.
so,what? I'm supposed
to just sit here?
no,you're going to get me
the yellow pages
and tell me where the nearest
pharmacy and gardening store is.
I need to pick up a few things.
yellow pages?
bro,I have a computer.
rescuing a hostage isn't
about battering rams and guns.
charge through a door
with a gun,
and chances are the person
you're trying to save
will be the first person
lying on the floor
dying of acute lead poisoning.
so you come up
with alternatives.
ingredients
from the local pharmacy
mixed with aluminum foil
powdered in a coffee grinder
will make a serviceable
flash grenade
that will stun anyone
for a good 20 feet.
thermite is another handy tool.
with a surface temperature
of 1,000 degrees,
it's used to weld together
railroad ties.
it will make pretty short work
of most locks,too.
go. you don't have much time.
I'm not excited about you
seeing Reyes by yourself.
someone needs to stall him
in case you guys need more time.
Mike, nobody's got your back.
this goes bad, Reyes
could get tipped off.
the only other option
for backup is Nick.
you guys like that idea?
call me when you got dawn.
Est? Limpio.
Nice view.
Where's my money?
Would you consider
being paid in bonds?
bonds? I said cash.
I know. but a bearer bond
is as good as cash.
it's issued without a named holder.
listen,I'm not saying it's right,
but the family has liquidity issues,
there are tax implications...
I don't care about the tax problems!
I want my money!
I understand,and I am trying
to get you that money.
no,no,no. you're trying my patience.
I said cash. I expect cash.
your time is up.
Go ahead,shoot.
Good luck hiding the body.
my guess is the cops show up first,
because that is a very
loud gun you're holding.
I am just trying to make this deal.
look at it from
the family's perspective.
they shell out $3 million
in cash,and then what?
it raises flags at the bank
with their investment advisors,
their employees.
people piece it together
that they paid you off.
that is not my concern!
but it concerns me because
if word gets out
that this family paid a ransom,
other guys like you will
come out of the woodwork.
I just need to make sure
that this never happens
to this family again.
they're gonna call me any second.
would you mind taking
that gun out of my face?
if you can't get through a door
without attracting attention,
the next best thing is
to attract a lot of attention.
once everyone's looking
at the door,
wondering what's going on,
you can pop in a flash grenade,
and they won't see anything
for a while.
drop the gun! get it down!
get it down.
attaboy. you're not
as dumb as you look.
you're safe.
we're going to untie you.
look at me. you're safe now.
unlike stocks,bonds
are financial instruments.
Now,that is the family.
May I take this?
tell them it's cash or she dies.
I got it.
yeah?
Hey,Mike. it's finished.
no,they won't do stocks nor bonds.
yeah,I explained the difference.
I understand.
that's it. they won't
pay the ransom in cash.
now,I hope you can reconsider.
killing a hostage... get out.
get out!
¿Qu?carajo est?pasando?
Leticia no le atendi?/i>
al teléFono.
mad...
drop the weapons now!
on the ground!
seriously,bro. I don't even
know how to thank you.
uh,those surfboards
right there...
yeah,I don't surf.
You're awesome,bro.
oh,sounds like they're here.
all set,Mike.
hospital checked her out. she's fine.
is Nick here?
he's inside.
you guys should talk.
cakewalk,huh?
oh... look,Mike.
you know,if you ever want
to borrow my caddy,it's yours.
thanks.
Nick!
hey,babe.
you lied to me!
baby,I love you.
another happy ending.
Mr. Clark.
I've never done a meeting
in a private home like
this before,Mr. Westen.
I'm not even sure it's allowed.
thanks for bending the rules.
yeah... again,
no guarantees,Mr. Westen.
we're gonna have to cut this short.
you tell me your side of the story,
I'll get back to you.
it shouldn't take long. oh,good.
my wife's expecting me to
actually make my flight tonight.
great.
you have any coffee?
coffee? yeah.
I think I have some instant.
that's fine.
the longer you've been
in the game,
the more you have to be careful
about underestimating
an opponent.
say you don't think much
of bureaucrats,
don't feel they're worth
your time or attention.
then a bureaucrat is
the perfect person
to send to kill you.
wow,you're pretty good.
let go.
it'll be less painful for you.
it'll look like you hanged yourself.
no surprise,really....
no work,no money.
this would have been easier
if you'd kept our appointment
in fort lauderdale.
I had some things arranged.
ah,well.
there's no way to anticipate
every danger.
you need a backup plan
for when things go wrong.
sorry to inconvenience you.
ugh! ughh!
that's why home-court advantage
is so important.
Mike,the cops found your
assassin in an alley this morning.
he bled to death.
no I.D. on him,and his
fingerprints didn't show up
in any government database,
so,officially, I guess
the guy never existed.
he must have been impersonating
the real Perry Clark.
do you think that the guy
who burned you sent him?
not a bad guess. Thanks,Sam.
you were right about him, you know?
you must feel a little
proud of yourself.
I wanted my burn notice resolved.
I talked myself into
denying my instincts.
that's nothing to be proud of.
I'm fine,Fi.
you almost died.
that's happened before.
so I'm not allowed
to be concerned,
to worry?
you can worry about me.
like Nick worried about dawn?
hopefully not exactly like that.
Oh,he was head over heels in love.
I talked to him about you...
about what I should get
you for your birthday.
a makarov.
he said you would like it.
ohh.
is it the same?
Nick convinced his boss to sell
it to me at a discount.
Thank you,Michael.
Happy birthday, Fi.
http://www.ragbear.com