Previously on "Ugly Betty"...
How bad is it between them?
It's like Cain and Abel.
Cut it out!
It's time for us
to get practical.
I will handle this.
Hey, whether you
like it or not,
he asked me to pick him
up from school today.
Last night,
a friend from home showed up...
My ex-girlfriend.
Wow.
Where do we stand?
Maybe it wouldn't kill us
to try and work together.
You do believe I'm innocent,
don't you?
I want to.
I know who killed Fey Sommers.
It was me.
Betty.
Betty, you're snoring.
Mrs. Meade?
I killed her, Betty.
I killed Fey Sommers,
and I'll kill you, too,
if you tell anyone,
especially Daniel.
Now... where do you
keep the Vermouth?
Hey, Betty.
Henry.
Cute headgear.
You met my girlfriend?
It's nice to meet you.
It's too bad it didn't
work out between us.
Claire Meade's gonna
kill you, anyway.
It's gonna be a long night.
Alexis, please.
You're my brother, Danny.
I'll call you whatever I want.
Fine.
Well, will you be at the
ad sales meeting at 10:00?
That might be awkward if we're
both sitting at the same table.
Daniel, we're both in charge.
It's only gonna be awkward if you
still shove grapes up your nose.
I did manage to get three up there once,
though, didn't I?
Hold on.
Your collar's going crazy.
Thank you.
Good morning, Betty.
Good morning.
Oh, right. Stella McCartney's
having that party tonight.
You know, I got plans with Becks.
You want my invite?
Um, yeah, sure, maybe.
Maybe?
Betty, last week I gave you
a calendar from my bank,
and you were all like, "shut up.
I can have this?"
This is Stella McCartney.
Daniel, I need to talk to you.
Okay.
Let me, um,
call Chloe from Prada first, okay?
Your mother killed Fey Sommers!
You don't need to
sign for this.
They were being so
nice to each other.
Maybe daddy told Daniel and
Alexis if they didn't play nice,
he'd take away their
private planes.
Oh, but they were smiling.
Stop fondling my limes
and do something!
And breathe in happy air.
Let me put out a gay-p.b.
among the assistants,
and I'll find out
what's going on.
You rang?
Do you want something hemmed?
You're not here to stitch.
You're here to snitch.
She needs information, bitch.
I thought we were rhyming.
What exactly do
you want from me?
Has  your friend Betty
told you exactly
what's going on between
Daniel and Alexis?
- How do you mean?
- Don't be a cluck.
The cold front between the
Meade boys has clearly thawed.
Who turned up the heat?
Okay. Here's the skinny.
Word is,
Alexis' calendar is empty.
Nobody's returning her calls.
No lunches, no nothing.
It looks like she's
reaching out to her brother
because she's friendless.
Really?
This might mean an in for me.
What are we thinking?
Okay, so I'm not
part of the "we,"
so unless you need
my sewing skills,
then I'm just going to leave.
Looks like that one's
gonna be trouble.
I want you to make sure that pasty
seamstress stays on our side.
Become her best friend.
Be her new Betty.
Oh, no. I guess
I have to start eating potatoes.
Betty, my mother tends to be a
bit delusional when she drinks.
She said she cut her brakes.
Yeah, and after a few cocktails,
she's also claimed
she's won the Boston marathon
and caused the tsunami.
She followed her in her Aston Martin
and watched her crash into a tree.
Call Rikers.
Tell them need to see my father.
Your mother did not kill Fey.
What are you listening
to that assistant for?
Why would mother confess
to something like that?
Here's a surprise, Daniel.
She's a drunk.
She may have her demons,
but she's not a murderer.
Why don't you try focusing on
something a little more important,
like  finding me a new lawyer?
I need someone better.
- I need "The Chin."
- The who?
The Chin. You wanna help me,
get me Grace Chin.
Grace Chin?
You dated that?
No, actually, I stood that up.
Good call.
Not enough beer in the world
to make that look good.
She was my T.A. sophomore year.
I promised her if she
helped me pass criminology,
that I'd take her to the
Sigma Phi New Year's kegger.
That's so man-whore of you.
Yeah, except that was the night
Cindy Howard showed up at my room
and decided being a virgin
wasn't cool anymore.
That's interesting, because she
decided that two weeks earlier
in my room.
Becks, Grace Chin will
never take my father's case,
not after what I did to her.
That was last century.
Look at this fatty.
She's probably got three,
four chins by now.
Give her a call.
She'll be happy to
hear from a man.
- What are you doing tonight?
- I've absolutely no idea,
but it involves a
buttload of alcohol.
Perfect. Daniel ge me his invitation
to the Stella McCartney party,
and you are gonna
be my plus one.
- It says "V.I.P."
- I know.
I've never even been
an I.P. before.
And look at the lettering.
It's so rich.
Oh, honey. You're feeling up a piece
of paper. You need to get out more.
I do. I really do.
I need to do something
to  get my mind off of Henry
and his slutty girlfriend.
You met her?
No, but you know she is.
Hello. Christina McKinney.
Yes, very good.
Who is this, really?
Really?
No--yes. Yeah. A-absolutely.
I'm on hold for
Sarah Jessica Parker.
- What do I do?
- You're doing it.
I can't.
You talk to celebrities
all the time.
I know, but not ones I like.
Hello. This is
Christina McKinney.
I'm Scottish,
not an australian hooker.
You saw my work at
the fashion week?
Of course I can create
an Oscar dress.
When do you need it?
Tomorrow! Crikey!
She'll do it! I'll do it.
Good day, mate.
No, Betty! What the whale?
I can't whip up a dress in a night!
It's gotta be done by tomorrow!
She's leaving for L.A.
You can do this!
You're one of the Top
Ten Designers to Watch.
No, no, but it's Sarah Jessica Parker!
It's the Oscars!
It's the chance of a lifetime.
Get psyched.
Oh, I can't. Yes, I can. I can.
Silk sheath...
low back...
And don't worry about tonight.
I will find another plus one.
Cut on the bias...
Good luck.
What? $14 for a
brownie and a sandwich?
They keep prices high
to discourage eating.
I'm--I'm sorry. I'm $2 short.
Uh, but what if I just
took part of the brownie?
Oh, no, no. Don't worry about it.
I got it. Here.
Oh, that's so sweet.
I've been in this city for two days,
and the kindest thing anybody's said is,
"hey, your ass could make
a nice chunk of change."
Well, that is just New York's
way of saying, "welcome.
You look good in your jeans."
Charlotte, by the way.
Everybody calls me Charlie.
You have an amazing aura.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
You haven't even studied
at beauty school yet.
Cosmetology institute, please.
And if I'm gonna get a leg up,
I have to practice, so...
Come on, papi. You said that
you would help me with this
if I gave you a beer.
Yeah, but you had two.
I was nervous.
Mom, emergency.
The weatherman said there's
gonna be a blizzard tonight.
Well, Justin, don't worry.
We will get you into the city
for "Hairspray," I promise.
Like you promised me the new Fergie CD,
which I still don't have?
Come on, mom.
Don't phunk with my heart.
Justin, your father's not even
gonna be here until 6:00.
It'll be okay.
Fine, but if I miss one
minute of the first act,
you think this is diva now?
Santos is going to "Hairspray"?
He knows that's not
a strip club, right?
I-I might not have told him that he's
going with us to a musical just yet.
Honey, what are you doing?
If Santos wants to spend
more time with his son,
then Santos should do
stuff that his son likes.
It's a good idea, right?
It is... it is... isn't it?
Ay, I need another beer.
So what kind of art do you do?
Mostly jewelry.
I love working with
found objects, but...
the only thing I've
found so far in New York
are hypodermic
needles and condoms.
You could sell that here.
No, really, it's New York.
Actually, I think this
city is a little scary.
Most people seem to
feel that way at first,
but it's really great once you get
past the crowds and the traffic
and that occasional mystery smell
you can't get out of your hair.
It's not so bad.
Hey, you know what?
Do you wanna come with me to the
Stella McCartney party tonight?
Come on. It would be really fun.
It's a V.I.P. invite.
V.I.P.? I've never
even been an I.P.
Me neither.
Feel this lettering.
- Oh. Oh, ooh.
- I know.
Charlie?
- Henry.
- Betty.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Wow, I guess you
two already met.
Betty, this is my
girlfriend Charlie.
Hey.
Transcript : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com
Yes?
Uh, am I interrupting?
No, no, no. I'm just...
What, no lunch date?
No, I've just been so busy.
Maybe not so busy.
Perfect.
I have two tickets to "The Flying
Dutchman" at the Met tonight.
I was thinking of maybe
a girls' night out.
We could start with drinks at the St.
Regis, and...
Oh, darling, what--what is it?
It's complicated...
coming back from the dead.
Please, Donna Karan does
it every three years.
I just didn't expect my
old friends to be so...
unforgiving.
Honey, you don't have to
apologize for who you are.
People cried at my funeral,
and now I'm back, and...
they want nothing
to do with me.
To hell with them.
One good friend
is all you need.
Thanks.
Shh.
Hey,  accountant man,
looking for Betty?
She's right down here.
What? I'm bored.
Oh, hey, Henry.
I just, um, I lost a contact.
Not mine.
Listen, I just wanted to thank you
for getting Charlie to go out tonight.
All we've done since she got here is
order in and watch movies in bed.
Sounds... rough.
Um, so just tell her that I'll meet
up with her at 7:00. Okay, bye.
Betty.
You--you sure this
isn't weird for you?
It's fine. It's totally fine.
Why would it be weird?
Well, you know, 'cause we--
there was that thing...
feeling... vibe... between us.
No. Uh, no,
there is no "us," so there was no...
vibe... feeling... thingy...
to be felt.
Really?
Okay, then.
Good.
Well, have fun tonight.
I'm still bored.
Watching nerd love
is so tedious.
There is no love. We don't have
any love. He has a girlfriend.
Yeah, who you invited
to a party. Pathetica.
Well, I don't want to,
but I'm stuck.
Oh, grow a set, Bambi.
You've been working
here long enough.
It is time to seize
your inner "Mode" girl.
My what?
"Mode" girls aren't
the other woman.
We are the only women.
Fight for your little dweeb.
Find this chick's
weakness and exploit it.
No, that's terrible.
I'm just gonna take her to the party.
- I said I would and I will.
- Doormat.
Or  maybe I'm just a
bigger person than you.
Don't. It's too obvious.
A musical?
Forget it. I'm not going.
Would you--oh, come here.
Justin is the one who
wants you to come with us.
He made me get three tickets because
he wants to share this with you.
He shouldn't even be going
to see this kind of stuff.
You ever think that maybe
that's why he is the way he is?
Okay, stop.
You're the one who wants to
spend more time with your son.
All right, look.
I got money on the
basketball game tonight.
No, listen. How about I ride with
you guys into the city on the train?
I'll catch the
game at some bar,
and when the show's over,
I'll come pick you up.
Wow, father-son
bonding on the e train.
That's some real quality time.
That's "The Chin"?
Yep.
Why would you stand her up?
Well, back in school
she was a mess.
She had braces and glasses
and this crazy hair...
which totally works
for some people.
Would you please stop looking at
me like that and just send her in?
Miss Chin.
Hi, Grace. How are you?
Let me take that for you.
Please, have a seat.
Well, this is, uh...
it's, uh...
- awkward, isn't it?
- Is it?
Look, let me just start with...
- I'm an idiot.
- Great, and I'm a pisces.
Now do you want to discuss
your father's case?
Uh, so there's nothing we
need to discuss first?
You do realize I charge by the hour,
Mr. Meade.
It's me. It's Daniel.
And I'm Grace. That was $40.
Wait a minute.
You don't remember?
Why should you?
'Cause we've never met.
Okay... so I've had
a look at the case,
and I'll be honest with you.
It is not an easy one.
But you've done the right
thing by calling me,
because I am the only
one who can win it.
- Great! So you'll take it?
- Not a chance in hell.
Whoa, wait. You just said you're
the only one who could win it.
And  you said you were gonna meet me
at the Sigma Phi New Year's party.
Oh, crap.
And by the way, Cindy Howard pulled
that virgin act with everyone.
So I've heard.
I was so excited about my
date with Daniel Meade.
Instead I ended up back at the dorm room
playing "Wolfenstein" on my computer
all night long.
"Wolfenstein, Wolfenstein,
Wolfenstein"!
Thanks to you,
1995 started off with a bang...
or should I say, without one?
Grace--
I bought a corsage for you.
I know that's weird,
but I was new to dating.
Look, I was a jerk, okay?
I probably still am.
Too little, too late.
I only came here to see the look
on your face when I rejected you.
Grace, I--listen.
I know you don't owe me anything,
but this isn't about me.
It's about my father.
He didn't stand you up.
Isn't there anything I can
do to make it up to you?
Every vendor in this city is
closed because of the snow.
Oh, right. You need fabric for
the Sarah Jessica Parker dress.
I see the gay-p.b.
is in full force.
Oh, please, it's Carrie Bradshaw.
We're on level pink.
Oh, are these the designs?
Taffeta?
Taffe-don't, and you're not thinking
of putting her in an autumn palette.
She's totally a spring.
Come on.
Do you know something?
You're the one gay I don't like.
Now will you piss off?
- You're confusing me.
- Confusing you?
Try saving your career.
Now let's start over.
Start over?
I don't even have any fabric.
Oh, shell-o.
Just repurpose something around here.
I can't.
This is Sarah Jessica Parker.
I can't just use something from
another designer. She'll know.
It'll burn her flesh.
And anyway,
she wants a McKinney original.
Okay, then we need to
think outside the box.
"We"?
Yeah. Sometimes it's good
to be on a team. Oh!
Are you sure the subway's
the safest way to go?
Yeah, I'm positive.
Look, all the cabs are off duty, anyway.
Besides, the subway's
perfectly safe.
What about all the mole
people down there?
Oh, they're nice,
just misunderstood.
Oh, god. Are you okay?
Are you--
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Oh, god. I don't know--
I don't know why Henry wants
to live in this city. I mean,
you know,
we need accountants in Tucson, too.
Well, maybe he has
bigger dreams than that.
Here, stay close.
Hey, like the music,
leave a dollar.
Thanks.
That was nice of you, but don't
you worry he'll spend it on crack?
Aw, Henry's girlfriend
thinks you're nice.
Hit her.
Amanda?
So what's your story?
Are you seeing anyone?
Um, nope, not anymore.
Oh, his loss.
I'm sure you're gonna
find someone great.
You did, and she took him.
She has got to go.
Just push Stevie Nicks
in front of the train.
God, this is crazy.
There's so many people.
Don't let go of my hand.
Here's your chance. Lose her.
She'll freak and be on
the next bus to Tucson.
- Ditch her.
- Ditch her.     - Ditch her.
Betty? Betty?
No, no, no, no! No, Betty!
I-I don't know what happened!
- Betty, Betty, Betty, Betty!
- Get off at the next stop!
Get on the opposite train and come back!
I'll wait for you here!
Bitch move, Betty.
Nice.
I can't get through.
There's no signal.
Well, here, try the pay phone.
Or not.
Ew, wet.
I don't understand.
How did this even happen?
Well, it was...
sort of--kind of an accident.
There were a lot of people,
and everyone was shoving,
and the doors just closed.
Great. Great.
She's on the subway by herself.
She's already
terrified of New York.
I know. I feel so bad, Henry.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Betty, it's not your fault.
Actually, it is--it is.
I think that I kind of...
lost Charlie... on purpose.
I am so sorry
about this, Alexis.
We will find a driver that
actually does have snow tires.
But don't worry,
I've never missed a curtain at the Met.
No big deal. You know,
I used to come to places like this...
before.
Why don't we sit and have
a drink while we wait?
- Peanut?
- No, thanks.
The band-aid in the bowl
puts me off a little.
Heads up!
That was you.
I threw that like
a girl, right?
I knew it--20 to 8:00.
I told you we should've left earlier.
I promise you,
we'll make the overture.
Mom, I appreciate the
whole effort thing,
but everyone knows that there's
no overture in "Hairspray."
Yeah, Hilda.
Everyone knows that.
Is there something you
wanna tell your son, Santos?
Yo, Justin, about tonight,
mijo, I don't--
No way. This is not happening.
Why, God, why?
Staples? Envelopes?
Coffee filters?
You were supposed to
be looking for fabric.
Yeah, there's none
in the building.
But we don't need it.
Think "Project Runway."
Those people made dresses
out of corn husks.
If I told you these were from Paris,
you'd pay 1,000 bucks for them.
I can't do this.
I'm gonna say "no."
No! You do not say no to
Sarah Jessica Parker.
She's the holy
grail of fashion.
I know!
This is your big chance,
and my big chance to meet her husband--
Ferris Bueller Parker.
Here, hold this. Spin.
Mm. You may not get a call
like this again, Christina.
You have to do this.
Make it work.
- She does have a quirky style.
- Quirky style.
No, no, no, you can't be closing.
It's just a little snow.
I-I don't need a waiter.
I don't need a cook.
I just need a table for two
with some candles and a few flowers.
That's it.
This is Daniel Meade.
Do you know that?
Hello? Hello--
That used to mean something.
- Should've used my name.
- Hey.
Thanks for meeting me here.
So what's the big surprise?
Actually, I was planning, um,
this amazing dinner at Babbo, but--
Let me guess--you're
blowing me off again.
No, no, no, no, it's not me.
It's the stupid blizzard.
Grace, I just wanted to give you
the New Year's Eve we never had.
Oh. Then maybe I should stand
out in the snow for three hours
and cry icicle tears.
Worked on that one for a while?
12 years.
Look, we can still do this.
Grace, we--we got party hats,
we got--we got noisemakers.
Look at this gift basket
Paul Smith sent over.
We can have a lot
of fun right here.
- Drink?
- I don't drink.
- Do you eat?
- Not often.
Listen, did you really think
it was gonna be that easy?
I would just come over here, and we'd
have a few laughs about that night?
I wasn't the only one you
hurt in college, Daniel.
Let's see.
Julie Dwyer--remember her?
- Not, uh...
- Exactly.
Julie now has a husband,
two kids and a dog.
Well, that's great.
In her mind.
She's in a mental institution.
Way to go, Daniel.
Does the name "Sarah
Hayden" ring a bell?
Sarah now has the largest "Indigo
Girls" fan site on the internet.
Are you gonna kill me?
No.
I am gonna make you apologize.
If you want me to even consider
taking your father's case,
you're gonna make it up to every
woman you ever hurt in college.
Oh, yeah.
The Chin's all about justice.
I swear the town car will
be there within 15 minutes.
- Ow! That's flesh.
- Well, don't move.
What's going on over there?
Christy and I are making a
dress for Sarah Jessica Parker.
I need a staple gun.
"Christy"? I take it
she's on our team?
Oh, we are so besties.
She taught me how to
do a butterfly stitch.
Perfect. I want the two of you
to be braiding each other's hair
before the night's over.
Whoo-hoo-hoo. Come on, WNBA.
The girl's on fire!
That's just lucky.
Actually, I'm the
one who's lucky.
No blizzard tonight,
and I'd be home on Staten Island,
and I wouldn't be
here with you.
I'm Joel, by the way.
- Alexis.
Can I buy you a cocktail?
Um, I won't be staying very long.
My friend has tickets to the opera.
- Oh, that sucks.
- Tell me about it.
How about one more
game before you leave?
All right.
Good news.
Marc found us a town car.
- Oh, great.
- You look familiar.
- Have we met?
- We're not even meeting now.
Let's wait outside. Come on.
Willy, any chance you wanna skip
the Met and stick around here?
What? Are you serious?
This was the plan.
We had girls' night out.
Well, isn't the point of girls'
night about meeting guys?
I mean, look, he's cute,
and he has friends.
Oh, dear god.
Come on, one shot.
What do you say? It's free!
Come on.
Yeah.
All right, here we go.
Nice release.
One minute until curtain.
This is the worst thing that's ever
happened, and I am not exaggerating.
Justin, honey,
you know the whole show inside and out.
If you miss some of it,
you know how it starts.
But dad doesn't!
And the curtain is up.
I am so sorry.
I think I'll be okay.
It's too bad.
I know you really wanted to see it.
Idea!
I'll catch you up.
Let me set the scene.
Baltimore, 1962--
the height of segregation and the
beginning of the teenybop revolution.
Our heroine's...
Tracy Turnblad--
chubby, but totally adorable.
She wakes and begins to sing.
Excuse me.
# Oh, oh, oh, woke up today #
# Feeling the way I always do #
# Good morning, Baltimore #
# Every day's like
an open door #
# Every night is a fantasy #
# Every sound's
like a symphony #
# Good morning, Baltimore #
Excuse me.
Ay, Justin, honey, don't dance near
the guy with his hand under his coat.
I don't understand. Did something
happen between you and Charlie?
No. Nothing.
Did she say something?
No.
Well, then I-I don't get it.
You just don't like her?
- No, I like her.
- Then what's the problem?
I like you, too!
There. I said it.
Why--why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me
you had a girlfriend?
- Because you have a boyfriend.
- Who I broke up with...
- What?
- For you.
I've thought a lot
about what I did to you.
I'm so sorry.
I never meant to hurt you.
Okay, so... thank you, nurse.
You'll make sure to give Julie that
message when she gets out of the quiet room?
Okay. Thanks. Bye.
Okay, so, um,
Debra Rossner is next.
You know,
you actually sound sincere.
You really would do anything
to help your father.
Come on. It's not like I don't regret
some of the things I've done in life.
You know, your sadness is...
kind of a turn-on.
The Chin likes remorse.
I am sad. I am so sad.
Shh. Don't talk.
You'll ruin it.
Hello? Hello?
Daniel, you there?
How many more of these calls
am I gonna have to take?
Okay, I'm hanging up.
Okay. I'm not hanging up.
Nice.
Alexis, our driver's here.
Oh, Willy,
would you hate me if I didn't go?
Opera's totally wasted on me.
- Yes!
- What'd I miss?
Sweet 3-pointer.
So much for our night.
What's this?
Hopefully your phone number.
Got it!
- What's going on?
- My boys back there bet me
I didn't have the stones
to get your phone number.
I don't live in a cave, dude.
I know exactly who you are,
and I don't hit on freaks
unless I know I'm
getting paid for it.
Pardon me. You know, Joel,
I was rude not to introduce
myself to you earlier.
That's what friends are for.
Come on.
Tracy totally ends up dancing
on "The Corny Collins Show."
It's way satisfying.
And then she has
this killer song--
Hey, kid.
Think maybe we've had enough?
Fairy.
Excuse me?
No, no, no, hold on.
Hey, you got
something to say, man?
Dígame, chico.
And now my son's gonna finish
telling me about the "Hairspray."
And when he's done,
you better clap.
All right?
Keep going, mijo.
I wanna know what happens to Tracy.
And you're right.
It's way satisfying.
Reprise...
Oh, let it go, sweetie.
Two weeks ago,
that idiot wasn't even walking upright.
I had all these ideas of how
it would be when I came back.
But people are kind of awful.
Well, don't forget, there are some
people that have been good to you.
You have...
and so has Daniel.
What?
I thought he'd reject
me like my father did,
but he didn't.
Uh, okay,
now you're making me nervous.
You are going to fire Daniel
and make me editor
in chief, right?
He's my brother, Willy.
He is the enemy.
See, that's the thing.
I've kind of realized he's not.
But think about
what you're saying.
We worked for months--
Look, you're the best creative
director in the business.
We can talk about salary.
- Stop the car.
- Willy...
You know,
you may be new at being a woman,
but you're an old
pro at being a bitch.
Betty, can we talk?
No. I'm getting some food,
and I'm going home.
Please tell Charlie
that I'm sorry.
At least let me pay
for your pretzel.
No, I don't want
anything from you.
Okay, a dollar.
- Thank you.
- You're... welcome.
Betty, here.
I know you like extra mustard--
Listen, Walter and
I--it wasn't about you.
I broke up with him because I
wasn't in love with him anymore,
and I don't know why I
blamed it on you.
Maybe it was easier.
Well...
if you didn't love him,
then you did the right thing.
Timing sucks.
Well, now you'll probably
meet someone new...
someone who'll see how
wonderful you are...
and caring...
and beautiful.
Is this a good idea?
No.
Henry!
Charlie?
- Charlie!
- Betty!
Oh, uh, are you okay?
Oh, that subway ride rocked!
People are so nice
in this city!
There was this one guy--he
kind of touched my butt,
but after I maced him,
he totally got me on the right train!
So you like New York?
Oh, I heart New York.
Honey, oh, honey, I'm staying.
I wanna try and
make it work here.
Oh, and, Betty--oh, oh,
Betty, it was like--
it was like fate that
got us separated.
Yeah. Yeah, fate's awesome.
So are we still gonna
go to that party?
Because we could just get on the
d train and change at Chambers.
I totally sound
like a New Yorker.
That was my shoe.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know what?
Um, I think I'm gonna go home.
You guys go to the party.
Henry should be your plus one.
- Betty...
- Yeah, yeah. Okay.
So, um, I'll see you tomorrow.
Hello, media!
It's amazing what you can
accomplish when you're sober.
Harsh words.
And Sarah Jessica's gonna love.
I know!
Listen up, people.
Our dear friend Alexis
has betrayed us.
She's keeping Daniel
as editor in chief.
What?
Don't worry. I'm not going
gently into this good night.
We need a new plan.
Excuse me.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm not one of your flying
monkeys, Wilhelmina.
Like hell you aren't.
I gave you your wings.
Sarah Jessica Parker
wouldn't even know your name
if I hadn't put you
in fashion week.
Don't cross me, sweetheart,
'cause you'll lose.
So, uh,
let's talk about your father's case.
Now? It's kind of
a buzz kill, no?
Ooh, not for me.
The law makes me hot.
My friend at the D.A.'s office told
me the case against your father
isn't as strong as they're
leading everyone to believe.
All right, quick,
before the blood leaves my brain--
How so?
Mostly circumstantial evidence, really.
Barely a motive.
Plus they can't even track down
their star witness. Person's a ghost.
What do you mean?
Mmm, a couple of other
witnesses claim they saw
a blue Aston Martin stopped on
the other side of the road.
Probably saw the
whole accident.
No luck tracking the
witness down, though.
Blue Aston Martin?
Why would you tell our son's
assistant that you killed Fey?
Our family is falling apart.
Don't get angry at me.
You were supposed to stay quiet
and let me handle everything.
And look where it got you.
You're here because of me,
because of what I did.
I'm turning myself in.
No! Claire?
Claire!
Claire.
Hello. Christina McKinney.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh. Right.
No, no, no, no, no. It's fine.
Of course,
I-I understand completely.
It's... just... okay.
Bye.
That was Sarah Jessica
Parker's people.
They're going with
another designer.
Wilhelmina works quickly,
doesn't she?
It gets easier.
Yes, Willy.
Oh, I'll get right on it.
Yes. I promise you,
the town car's on its way.
No, I...
Yes, of course.
Transcript : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com