Previously on "Ugly Betty"...
Bradford is into feet?
Bradford Meade won't be able
to keep his hands off you.
In six months you'll be
running Meade publications.
That's the idea.
What we have is... wonderful,
but I'm never gonna
divorce Claire.
Do you need a condom?
I've got one in my wallet.
You get her out of the country, and
you'll have everything you ever wanted.
She's already hooked.
You sleep with women to distract yourself
from what's going on in your life.
You're using them like a drug.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
They're sending me
back to Mexico.
$1,200 for a ticket
to Guadalajara?!
That's ridiculous!
What, are they kidding?
We cannot afford that!
Hilda, I got it.
No, I don't want a
package deal to Acapulco.
My father is being sent back to
Mexico to wait for his visa,
and then he'll--
Yes, I'll hold.
Suarez, are you still
working on those nails?
You do know the final
exam is timed, right?
Look, Valerie, I'm going through
problems with my family right now.
- Our fa--
- Oh, no. No.
I don't want your
excuses, Suarez.
I want your
commitment to beauty.
What does this look like?
Oh, my god,
is that an engagement ring?
Yeah. My ex and I
started dating again--
Lose it. And you cannot do a professional
manicure with claws like those.
Cut 'em before the exam tomorrow,
or I fail you.
She seems very helpful.
She's 130 pounds of bitch.
What did you say?
120.
Listen, why don't we take care
of this ticket thing tonight?
I'll cancel with Santos, and we can call
every travel agency in Jackson Heights.
I have this thing I have
to go to after work.
- Sorry.
It's the "Mode" party for
Administrative Professionals Day.
You mean Secretaries Day?
No. In 1998, they changed it to
Administrative Professionals Day.
Oh, that really
rolls off the tongue.
So where you guys gonna go?
You know that theme
restaurant in Times Square--
the Middle Ages?
You mean those snobby assistants from
"Mode" actually like that kind of place?
Oh, they love it. Every year they
pick a place where they can go
and make fun of "the
common people."
Last year it was that
roller disco in the Bronx.
"Wheels of Paradise"?
I love that place.
I know!
Anyway, I'm the
one who planned it,
so I have to be there
just to make sure
everything goes okay.
Well, you know,
it is Secretaries Day.
Maybe Daniel will
give you a big bonus,
and we can use it to
buy papi's ticket.
Happy Secretaries Day.
"World's best... notary"?
I, uh, got to the store
a little late.
Well, it's the thought
that counts, right?
But you do know that they changed it to
Administrative Professionals Day in 1998?
Right.
Uh, can you get me
Olivier Theyskens?
He promised us a
Nina Ricci spread.
And send over some
hot girls for that.
I'm in the mood for redheads.
Um, this is work-related?
Oh, we'll see.
What's that?
Yogurt.
My yogurt?
It didn't have a name on it.
No, but my name was on the
granola that was on top of it.
Don't you know the
refrigerator stacking system?
So does that mean that the
cherry pie was yours, too?
You ate my pie?
Well, not yet.
Game on, Suarez, game on.
God, I hate Secretaries Day.
You hide it so well.
Everyone gets a present
but the receptionist.
I might as well be invisible.
I mean,
who do they think forwards the calls?
Who fans the magazines?
Who signs for packages?
Tim, Sheila and Betty.
Well, who looks hot for
everyone when they come in?
I mean, these buttons don't
just pop open by themselves.
Where'd you get that vest?
This? It's Tavares'.
That cutie designer
made you another one?
What's with all the gifties?
It not like you're sleeping with him.
Of course not, 'cause he's gay,
and I'm a woman, and he's gay.
Oh, yeah!
Hey, what's fratty
so happy about?
What, did his sports team win
the beef bowl or something?
Close. Alexis signed him up
for a beer-of-the-month club
for secre--tariat's birthday.
He loves horseys.
Who knew?
I am now officially miserable.
Oh! Wait till we get to that
Middle Ages place tonight
and make fun of all the
nerds in shining armor.
It'll be the mocking
event of the season.
- I think I'm gonna pass.
- What?
You can't pass.
I'm not going stag, hag.
You'll have to buy
your own beer, queer.
- You can't just ditch, bi--
- Shut up!
Okay, tried it. Still hate it.
You are so white sometimes.
I'm white and I'm bored.
You know why you
don't like jazz?
Because it's about riffing
and being spontaneous.
You would love jazz
if you saw it live.
I am gonna take you to
the Blue Note tonight.
Oh, Willie,
can we hold off on that?
Why?
All we do is stay in.
It's just that with
Claire in prison,
this is the last thing
she needs to hear about.
Don't you think it's time
you move on with your life,
our lives?
You really care what
a murderer thinks?
She is not a murderer,
and I will not leave her
just because of one
moment of insanity.
It would never work.
Of course it would, so why wouldn't
you want to go to Brazil with me?
Uh, for one, I've got sideburns and
a moustache in my passport photo.
Come on, Rodrigo,
I can't do this right now.
My mother's in prison.
How can I just leave her?
I would think your mother
would want you to be happy.
So...
should I get used to this
whole mug shot look?
Oh, I was out late at the...
therapy meeting you
signed me up for.
Who's Kristin?
Uh, met her at the meeting.
"Soho Grand, room 709.
I'm going to..."
Not gonna finish reading that.
Okay, so maybe I didn't
go to a meeting.
Daniel, what are you doing?
You have a problem.
You slept with an underaged model.
Yeah, who turned out
not to be underage.
Why are you
so "glass-half-empty"?
No, no, no, no. The glass is crushed into
a million little pieces all over the floor,
and I'm just waiting
for you to step on it.
You got lucky.
Next time, you won't.
Do you think people will want the
royal feast or the jester's banquet?
I think people just
want to get drunk.
Look here. There.
This is a way you could make some money.
N.Y.U. is looking for
some research subjects.
- How much?
- $5,000!
Wait, all you have to do
is get injected with...
Can't quite read that...
Several syllables...
oh, and side effects.
Yeah, let's keep
that as a backup.
Aren't there any
part-time jobs?
- Got any welding experience?
- Oh, my god, yes!
- You weld?
- No, Christina, look!
I could get $1,000 for riding some
mechanical horse for just 15 seconds?
I could totally do that!
No, are you sure you wouldn't rather
just deal with the side effects?
Listen, when I was a little girl,
I hated getting my allergy shots,
so I used to grab onto
this tree outside my house
and wrap my legs around so tight,
no one could pull me off.
These are thighs of steel.
Betty, I think there is a big difference
between a giant robot horse and a tree.
I'm telling you,
I could do this.
If this is what it
takes to help my father,
then I will ride that
giant robot horse
all the way to Mexico!
Transcript: Raceman
Subtitles: Willow's Team
www.forom.com
I dare you not to
make fun of me.
Okay, seriously,
ye olde bowl cut.
- It's too easy.
- Exactly.
Imagine 30 guys
dressed like me,
serving tourists with
mullets and fanny packs.
Middle Ages is gonna
be duh-licious.
It's gonna be Britney shaving
her head all over again.
Oh, that was fun.
But then it got sad.
No, but then it got fun again.
What's your deal, anyway?
Why won't you come?
Okay, promise you won't
say anything to anyone?
I swear on the abs
of Marc Wahlberg.
Wow, you are serious.
Okay, remember how,
before I worked here,
I was an actress?
Shut the front door!
Your acting reel?
Bring it.
Hi, grandma.
- Hey, Betty.
- Henry.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I heard you were planning the
Administrative Professionals Day party,
and well, I was kind of
wondering if I could crash.
Really?
Yeah, bit of a Dungeons
and Dragons geek.
Big surprise, I know.
I-I guess I have sort of a soft spot
for castles and chivalry and...
princesses.
Okay, well, um, I'll just put you and
Charlie on the scroll at the door.
Oh, actually,
Charlie can't make it.
She's been waiting for Blanket
Space to open up on Astor Place
to sell her jewelry.
Anyway, yesterday one of the
guys got some bad chicken.
So long story short,
now she has a prime spot.
Well, that's great
for Charlie...
and for salmonella...
I guess.
Okay, well, I shall see thee
in the Middle Ages, milady.
You're such a dork.
You know you love it.
No one can ever
know of our love.
Nurse, get out! Stat!
That's your cue, honey. Go.
I'm a lonely kitten.
Call the chat line now.
I'm waiting to purr for you.
Greetings, lords and ladies,
and welcome to the Middle Ages,
a magical journey through time.
So partakest thou
of our humble fare,
and quenchest thine
thirst at ye olde bar.
Kids under 12 eat
free on sundays.
Okay, that was hi--wait
for it--larious!
For you, maybe.
They play this thing on
a loop by the front door.
All these losers
are gonna see it,
and they will never
let me live this down.
All those losers will be too
busy ordering jalapeño poppers
to watch some stupid
welcome video.
- I'm not going.
- Come on, Mandy-pants.
If you don't go, they'll just
laugh at you behind your back.
And besides, if you're there,
you'll know who to
punish tomorrow.
Well, I do like
punishing people.
Your 3:00 is here.
I don't have a 3:00.
You do now.
Daniel Meade, Tyler Blake.
Tyler works at the
magazine "Psychology Now,"
you know, on the 14th floor?
He's here to help you
with... your sex problems.
What is the matter with you?
You went down to the 14th floor,
grabbed the first guy you saw,
told him I'm a freak?
Actually, he's the
third guy I saw.
The first two thought
you were a lost cause.
Come on, Daniel, he specializes
in sexual compulsion issues.
Okay, well, I'm sure that that
has some therapeutic value?
I am not spilling my guts out
to some hack magazine writer.
If you're not gonna get the help,
then I'm going to bring the help to you.
Betty Suarez.
Oh, hi.
Thank you so much for calling me back.
What? No,
$1,100 is still too expensive.
Hold on. Where are you going?
To a model casting session.
I am not doing this, Betty.
No, Daniel, you're not going anywhere.
I've made this very easy for you.
No, I said he has to be in Mexico
by friday. I already told you that.
- Who?
- My father.
He's gonna be deported if we can't
get him to Mexico for his visa,
and we don't even have the
money to pay for his ticket.
Oh, and here you are--you
have everything,
and you won't even make the
effort to help yourself.
You know what? Forget about it.
Go with your models.
I give up!
Okay, jeez. Now you've ruined
the whole model thing for me.
Why didn't you tell
me about your father?
Because I didn't
want to bother you.
You have problems of
your own to deal with.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
You wanna help me, Daniel?
Then go in there
and talk to Tyler
and try and get better.
No! Don't do it!
Barbra didn't cut her nails to
play "Yentl." Why should you?
I have no choice.
If I don't cut them,
Valerie fails me.
Then she is a disgrace
to cosmetology.
You know what, mom?
She's your Mr. Weaver.
Your drama teacher?
What'd he do now?
He cast Joey Colano as
Tony in "West Side Story."
Well, what part do you play?
I'm his understudy.
Oh. I'm sorry.
But this isn't about me.
This is about you.
You're a grown-up, mom.
You can do whatever you want.
- Yeah.
Yeah, screw that place! I quit!
Now go get me my "Fiji Sunset."
Mommy needs a touch-up.
Oh, my god, is that a bruise?
Where did you get that?
- Yoga.
- Hey, no touching.
Come on, mom, you don't have to act
all tough for me. Are you okay in here?
Please, this is cake.
How many rehabs have I been through?
At least here you can score a
decent glass of toilet wine.
So what's bothering you?
Aside from the fact that my
mother's drinking toilet wine?
It's Rodrigo.
I think I'm falling for him.
He wants me to move to Rio.
And what do you want?
I don't know.
Honey, as hard as it's been with
your father and me over the years,
we've always stood
by each other.
And if you feel that you've
found that with somebody,
you follow him
wherever he goes.
Also, Brazilian men...
caliente.
Oh, mom.
Just... don't completely
disappear on me again.
I won't, mom.
I should go.
Try and be more careful with
the yoga next time, okay?
You're in my seat, fish.
Hello, Yoga.
You think the hat is
too much for prison?
Mm, it looked okay when you
wore it to visit Martha.
I was trying to detract from that
god awful sweater she knitted me.
Why are you going to visit that
gangly old boozehound Claire, anyway?
Because Bradford
refuses to divorce her,
and I refuse to accept it.
So I'm thinking
maybe I can convince
Claire to divorce him.
Oh... Wait.
Will you be back in time for that
luncheon for the homeless children?
Well, if I'm not, make sure they
get their free hair products.
Priorities, Marc.
Priorities.
I still have so much to learn.
You seek out sex so you won't
have to deal with your problems.
Come on, I think you're
reading too much into this.
I just really like having sex.
You gotta put your
brakes on, man.
- Face your life.
- Can I just face it tomorrow?
I have a really hot
date tonight. Look.
She's a model, plus,
she's allergic to pants.
Seriously, she
can't keep 'em on.
What's her name?
Marla.
Marla what?
Look, that's my point.
If you're serious about getting help, why
don't you and Marla go out on a sexless date?
You mean, like, talking?
Either you take a stand right now,
or it gets worse.
Greetings, lords and ladies.
'Tis mine honor to warmly
welcomest thou to the Middle Ages.
Squire Josh Weinstock
at thy service.
Here are your
complimentary crowns.
Enjoy yon merriment.
All right, Betty,
the sooner you tackle that horsey,
the sooner I tackle
something in a codpiece.
This is gonna be the easiest
1,000 bucks I've ever earned.
I think thou might be screwed.
Will you people stop
pushing Acapulco?
He needs to go to
Guadalajara for his visa.
Don't you have some
sort of a special fare?
Well, what if I put
him in a pet carrier?
Hey.
Well, thank you. You have been
absolutely no help, hijo de--
perra.
You know,
it's not worth all this.
Papi, stop it.
We gotta get the money for your ticket.
Hilda, I don't have to go.
I've been living here
for 30 years already.
- What if I just stayed?
- No, you have to go.
Look, "You must return to
your country of origin,
"and reenter this
country legally,"
or you're screwed.
Okay, well,
it doesn't say "screwed," but,
papi, you will be.
We don't have the money.
This is my problem,
not yours
and not Betty's.
I'm not going.
So much to make fun of,
I don't know where to begin.
This is so gay.
No, it's not.
Oh, my god. There it is.
Greetings, lords and ladies.
Welcome to the Middle Ages--
a magical journey through time.
- Hey, that's not you.
- I've been de-wenched.
That's good news, right?
Now you don't have to be embarrassed.
No. No,
they put in a younger girl.
Kids under 12 eat
free on sundays.
- So what, now I'm too old?
- I'm not following.
I'm going nowhere at "Mode,"
and now I'm apparently
too old to be a wench.
How long before I'm too
old to be a receptionist?
Sure, today I'm the eye candy,
but tomorrow I'll be old candy--
old, hard,
wrinkly candy covered in lint.
Are you having a stroke?
Maybe. I'm old enough.
I have to get out of here.
This was a big mistake.
Don't give up yet.
Maybe there's a drinking contest.
I've won those before.
Hello?
- Get home now.
- What's wrong?
I know you have your whole
Secretaries Day party--
- Administrative Pro--
- Shut up. I need you home now.
Papi? Flipping out.
- I'm totally calm.
- You're flipping out!
He is threatening not to go to Mexico.
He says, you know, we can't afford it,
so he's just--he's
just gonna give up.
You gotta come home. You just gotta
help me talk some sense into him.
Tell him I'm coming home,
and I'm bringing the
money for his ticket.
All right.
So let me make you a cup of coffee.
Get in here.
No, no, no, no, no.
No bedroom. Come on.
We're having fun.
We're talking.
I wanna get to know
the--the inner you.
Let me show it to you.
You don't, um, have to do that.
Why don't we play a game?
- Use our minds.
- Yeah!
Look, chess. Perfect.
And these are...
Condoms--I'm good at that game.
There's TV. How about that?
"The Notebook"--
I love that movie.
Oh, my god. That scene in the
rain makes me want to get naked.
Or, um, "Hotel Rwanda."
Daniel, what's the deal?
The last time we got together,
we didn't even make
it out of the cab.
I'm just trying to have a
different kind of night.
Look, can I ask you a question?
Seriously, do you think I'm addicted...
to sex?
Yeah!
- Hey, Betty.
- Hi.
Isn't this place great?
Usually mutton is so dry.
Oh, my god.
You're gonna tame the jousting steed?
Yeah. Yeah, it's no big deal.
I have thighs of...
Never mind.
Maybe we should just go play
darts instead. Much safer.
No, no, no, no, no.
- I have to do this.
- Why?
It's complicated.
She needs money to
help her father.
Ooh, look at that.
We're all out of drinks.
- You not doing this.
- Henry.
- I'll do it.
- What?
But I-can't let you do this.
Betty, my grandparents
had horses.
I never got near them
'cause I'm allergic,
but I used to watch them
out the window all the time.
Let me do this for you.
Um, okay.
Hello.
I told you I was gonna
be at the Middle Ages.
Well, yeah,
Betty's here. It's--
Charlie, we are not having
this conversation again.
Will you excuse
me for a second?
I'll be right back.
Charlie says hi.
I know I'm the last person
you wanna see, Claire.
It's just that it's
about Bradford.
He's just been so depressed.
His wife's in prison.
Wouldn't that make you just
the tiniest bit depressed?
- Of course it would.
- Why are you really here, Wilhelmina?
You're nothing but
a selfish bitch.
Oh, pardon my language.
Prison has hardened me.
Claire, I'm simply a
concerned observer.
Just because your life
has been put on hold,
doesn't mean Bradford
should have to be.
Oh, you poor, stupid woman.
Look at those toes.
You're sleeping with him,
aren't you?
Well, I certainly hope you
don't think it means anything.
It's hardly an exclusive club.
Well, if that were true,
dear, then why on earth
would you have to cut
the brakes in Fey's car?
Or were you threatened...
like now?
Listen to me,
you slut!
There's a hundred women in here I could have
slit your throat for a pack of menthols,
and I've got a whole
carton in my cell.
Stay away from my husband,
you degenerate piece of human filth,
or you're dead!
You hear me? Dead!
Willie?
What? Now?
- Hey, grandma.
- Hi.
Next up to ride the steed,
sir Henry Grubstick!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Henry!
Charlie, this is crazy.
Will you stop being so jealous?
- Henry!
- Last call for sir Grubstick!
I'm sir Grubstick.
Hello.
Look, I couldn't do it.
We had sex during
"Hotel Rwanda."
Okay, that--that is a first,
but I told you,
cold turkey is hard.
They don't make
a patch for this.
It will take every ounce
of willpower you have.
I don't think I can do this.
Daniel, I have a
confession to make.
Five years ago,
I was where you are right now.
I doubt that, Tyler.
Skipping work,
ignoring my friends.
I left my family on Christmas
Eve to go to a strip club.
What am I supposed to do?
Find something that helps
you focus on other things.
Like what, stamp collecting?
You wanna know
how I got through?
What is this?
Something I found overseas.
Next time, instead of sex,
this is your distraction.
Hear ye! Hear ye!
Behold--sir Grubstick!
Um, it's Betty... Suarez.
Okay, Betty, uh, good luck.
You're gonna break
the horse, Betty.
You get it? 'Cause she's fat, right?
Lock it up!
Ten seconds to go!
Ten, nine...
six, five,
four, three...
Oh, my god. Betty?
Are you okay? Betty?
I couldn't do it.
That's right.
You got a piece of the pep.
Drop a pound!
What's the matter with you?
She could've been hurt.
Whatever. Brace-face
jacked my yogurt.
My lords!
All quarrels in the Middle
Ages are settled one way--
on the log...
or we lose our liquor license.
Log! Log! Log! Log! Log! Log!
Oh, it's about to
get nerd-nasty.
Bradford thinks his wife
isn't really a monster.
So let's show him what
she's capable of.
I want you to hit me
as hard as you can.
Willie, isn't that a little extreme,
even for you?
Don't pretend you've
never wanted to do it.
Now's your chance.
- This isn't a trap?
- Go for it!
Hit me like a man, you pansy!
Wilhelmina Slater.
I need visible bruises,
damn it!
Who do you think made sure you didn't
get a raise the past two years?
Who do you think cut
your vacation time?
Who do you think broke
into your computer
and canceled your subscription
to Dudecruise.com?
Harder.
Henry, look,
I know you believe in all this chivalry
stuff, but you don't have to defend my honor.
Yes, I do.
Don't forget your crown.
Romantic little banger,
isn't he?
Let's have a nice, clean fight.
No punching, no kicking,
no hitting below thy belt.
Let's do this, beeyotch.
I am unmanned!
Oh, boo to the black knight!
Come on! Give him a right hook!
Come on, Henry!
Give him a big old--
He's done! I'm the winner! I'm the
winner! I'm the winner! Yeah! Yeah!
Stop it!
Henry!
Yeah! He's done!
Did I win?
Oh, my god. I'm so sorry.
I love you.
Henry. Henry.
Did you just say "I love you"?
Henry, wake up!
What did you say?!
- Ow.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
- Charlie?
- No, it's--it's Betty.
No, it's Charlie.
Oh. Um, hi.
How--how long have
you been here?
Long enough to wonder why my
boyfriend's getting hurt defending you.
No, no, you don't understand.
Um, it's not what
it looks like.
I'm not stupid, Betty, okay?
I've seen the way he looks at you.
Look, I swear,
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Maybe you didn't,
but there's a reason that fairy
tales don't have two princesses.
He's my boyfriend,
so back off, Betty.
You serious?
Yes. I'm coming to Brazil!
Oh, we need to celebrate.
Pour us some more champagne,
I'll light some candles
and run us a bath.
Cheesy, but it works.
Everything is going
according to plan.
You're sure she
agreed to leave?
I promise, Bradford.
She'll be gone.
She's coming to Brazil, and I don't
think she'll want to come back.
It is you. I can't believe it.
You're the old serving wench.
I'm the new serving wench.
I know who you are.
You replaced me.
Step off, skipper.
I-I didn't want to replace you.
I totally meant my performance
as a homage to yours.
Did Marc put you up to this?
Does Marc work at "Mode" with you?
Are you his boss?
- Kind of.
- You guys are so fancy.
You must get to meet
all the big stars.
Well, I...
did get a water for Brad Pitt once.
Still have the bottle.
I know you were on the
phone with my father.
Oh, amor, it is just business.
Like our relationship?
What are you talking about?
My father paid you to seduce me so
I'd go back to Brazil with you.
Alexis, wait.
I may be a woman...
but I still know how
to hit like a man.
Relax. Betty said
she'd get the money.
I told you, I'm not going.
Ay, papi, this is crazy.
Why wouldn't you want to go?
Lawyers make a lot of promises.
I don't know what's gonna
happen when I go down there.
I may not be able to get back.
Would you stop
talking like that?
You need to be prepared
to step up, mija.
What? I mean, Betty's--
No Betty.
You need to pull it together.
You're the oldest.
You have a son.
You're out of a job,
and you just quit beauty school.
Well, I didn't
wanna quit. Okay?
But they just--
they stopped appreciating all of this.
You're an adult, Hilda.
I'm not going anywhere until I know
you're able to take care of this family.
He said it, Christina.
I know he did.
How could he leave with her?
Maybe that twit Nick Pepper
scrambled his brains.
It doesn't really matter what
he said because he chose her.
Because she moved 3,000
miles to be with him.
He's just doing the honorable thing.
He's a good guy,
which is why you fell for
him in the first place.
I know.
What do you need a boyfriend for anyway?
Ah, they're overrated.
I don't need one.
It was just... it was nice,
you know,
having somebody rescue me for a change.
Especially him.
Do you want to know the truth?
You can take care of
yourself, princess.
Watch me pound this brew, bro!
Yes.
You want some pepper,
you're gonna get the spice.
Secretaries Day!
It's Administrative
Professionals Day.
What's up, yogurt thief?
Where's sir Dorko to defend your honor?
Sir Dorko--that was awesome.
Hey, Nick.
I can defend myself.
Thank you.
What are you doing
here, Suarez?
I'm finishing this course
so I can take care
of my family.
I was hoping I scared you off.
I'm not a kid.
I don't scare that easy.
Okay, people.
We're being timed on this starting now.
So brush it high
or say good-bye.
Okay, so your perm checks out,
which brings us to nails.
Suarez, is there some reason that your
model here doesn't have a manicure?
The test said I had
to do a manicure.
It just didn't say on who.
I wasn't gonna waste all that
hotness on somebody else.
Oh, you guys, it's no big deal.
I did all of these one-handed.
Pass.
Okay, people, back to work.
Show's over.
It's Claire again.
I can't believe she
had this done to you.
It was just so horrible.
Those three thugs...
pulled me into
that alley and...
they even tore my Chanel.
I guess I was wrong about her.
She's not the woman
I thought she was.
What does that mean?
Our marriage is over.
I'll talk to the
lawyer tomorrow.
There's still this ringing
in my ear from the trauma.
What did--what did you say?
I'm divorcing Claire.
Bradford.
You have no idea how
much this means to me.
Will you be a dear and
get me a glass of water?
I'm... I need to
take my pain pills.
Hello?
Is this Mr. Wolf?
I heard you might be able
to help me with a problem.
I need it eliminated.
- Good job, Betty.
- Yeah, good arm.
- Hey, good job.
- Thanks.
Way to go, Betty.
Betty, can I speak
with you for a second?
Good morning.
You look good today.
Therapy suits you.
Actually, I don't want to
talk about my problems.
I would like to talk
about yours, however.
I didn't know the
yogurt was his.
Not that.
Apparently, you've got
a very thoughtless boss
who didn't realize
until last night
that you deserve a lot
more than a crappy trophy.
- These are tickets.
- To Mexico.
For you and your father and
the rest of your family.
All they had was first class.
I hope you don't mind.
No. No, Daniel. It's too much.
Stop it.
You're always there
for everyone else.
Let me be there for you.
Happy Administrative
Professionals Day.
It's Administrative Profe--
No, wait. That's right.
Thank you.
I'm gonna go call my family.
Hilda, it's Betty.
Daniel got us
tickets to Mexico.
I know.
We're going to Mexico first class.
Transcript : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com