Previously on Ugly Betty...
I am your mother.
Then maybe you
should act like it.
Listen, I'm sorry.
I'm new here,
and I'm not really that
familiar with everyone yet.
- Of course, I'm--
- Daniel Meade,
"Mode" magazine--
the only one in this room
who was born into his job.
I never applied for a
green card or amnesty
because I was afraid
they'd send me back.
I killed Ramiro Vasquez.
Why are you dripping
on my bagel?
I was on the "M.Y.W." floor,
standing under sprinklers,
and there was a fire. Sorry.
And you were there because...
Oh! I was getting
Sofia's autograph.
You like her books?
It's terrific.
Seems like generic
chick lit to me.
No. No, Daniel.
Actually, it's--it's inspired.
Really?
"Girls like it on top"?
- It's a metaphor.
- Ah... yeah.
Anyway, she was signing my copy,
and there was a wastebasket by her
in the copy room, and the sprinklers
went off, and now I'm wet.
Betty, you have
mascara on your face.
Thanks.
Other side.
So... I have any messages?
Yes. Mike Day called, and he's turning
down the hotel review assignment.
He says he only does
serious journalism now.
Unbelievable. Five years ago,
he's writing for an airline magazine.
Now he's acting
like Katie Couric.
That's the third writer who's
turned down the assignment, right?
I'll put together a list of
other freelancers for you.
Everybody get in here.
We can't waste any more time.
- What the hell?
- Just keep all their stuff together,
- so it won't get mixed up.
- What are you doing?
Oh, my editors and I are working
here until our offices are cleaned.
No, wait a second.
You can't just come in here
and take over my
conference room.
Your daddy said I could.
Mr. Meade didn't
okay it with me.
Then you should take
it up with him.
Whoa, whoa! Be careful with those
mock-ups. You're getting 'em all wet.
Those have to go back
exactly as they were.
Well, of course, of course.
'Cause you might forget which
half-naked, emaciated woman
you want for your cover.
And your lead story?
Just great--"Ten ways to
lose thighs and get guys."
- So empowering.
- Really?
And what's your cover story,
"Ten ways to treat a guy like dirt
so you end up a lonely,
desperate cat lady"?
Well, the title's a little long,
but thanks for the story pitch. Bye.
This is outrageous.
Wilhelmina, be reasonable.
You're asking me to entertain Ted
Lebeau, the president of Beaumart--
a store which has the fashion
equivalent of canned ravioli.
We need their ad dollars.
Lebeau is only in town from
Texas for the weekend.
I need you to push him off the
fence and into our pockets.
Why aren't you assigning
this to Daniel?
We both know you're the
best person for the job.
You've landed almost
every account for "Mode."
And yet I'm still just
creative director.
Also, I think Ted might be more
receptive to a beautiful woman.
Well, I can't argue with that.
I'll charm the denim
chaps right off him.
Hey. You want a sandwich?
No, thanks.
Last time you were this quiet,
you were about to tell
me you were pregnant.
I think I know where we can
get the 5 grand for Leah.
You tell the lawyer anything
about why I had to emigrate?
No, I wouldn't tell
anybody that you...
Killed a man?
I can't imagine what you
and your sister think of me.
Hey, no.
Papi, you were defending mom.
We understand.
We don't judge you.
Thank you, mi amor.
So... where you
getting this money?
Santos.
Absolutely not.
I don't want a cent
from that degenerate.
We have no choice!
Oh, there you are.
Betty, I've got
something for you.
This one's nice and dry.
"To Betty... a girl like no other.
Love, Sofia."
Wow, that's so nice. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Listen, I need a little favor.
Of course. Anything, anything.
I want to get fresh eyes
on this piece I'm writing.
Yeah, okay. Um, I'll just call
the features editor,
- and they can help you.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I want your opinion.
You're my key
demographic for "M.Y.W."
I am hoping to appeal
to the regular girl,
not these hipster
fashionistas here.
Okay, cool. Um...
"sexaholics--spotting them
and stopping them."
Um... you know, I'm--
I'm not so sure that I'm qualified
to give an opinion
on the subject.
Betty Suarez,
you are more than qualified.
You understand my writing.
I mean, I have read every
single one of your books,
and, um, when I was at Queens college,
I wrote a report about you.
- What's going on?
- I'm honored.
Oh, I needed some
thoughts on this article,
and I'm taking advantage
of Betty's intelligence,
which I'm sure you
underuse on a daily basis.
All right. You know what?
I've had enough of you.
First, you take over
the conference room.
Now you're trying to
hijack my assistant.
Betty... come on.
I have a lot of things for you to do.
Sorry, Daniel. I didn't know
you were the jealous type.
Betty.
Sorry.
But maybe I can help you later.
I'm sure. Thank you.
She wants me.
Excuse me?
Well, you were there.
You saw it, right?
I didn't really pick up on it.
Oh, come on. Sexaholics?
That was clearly a jab at me.
She gave you the article
because she knew I'd see it.
Daniel, you think maybe you're reading
just a little bit too much into this?
No, no, no, no, no.
Trust me. I know women.
She's playing games.
But you know what? It's fine.
I'll just play
games right back.
Daniel, um, do you actually
have something for me to do?
Uh... yeah. I, uh, I need you
to pick up my dry cleaning.
I need you to buy me a new sliding
plastic thingy for under my chair.
That one's worn out.
"Slidy plastic thingy."
Coming right up.
Betty!
I'll tell you what. Uh...
I do have something
more important for you.
Um, you know I need a writer
for that hotel review.
Why don't you do it?
What? What,
I can write the review?
- Shut up. Really?
- Yeah, it'll be fun.
The hotel is 50 Prince in Soho.
You can just change the reservation
to your name, if you want.
Okay. Yeah. Great.
Um, when do you need it by?
Uh, monday.
Leave a little early today
and just spend the whole
weekend at the hotel.
Okay... wait! Um, this weekend?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Walter planned a romantic
weekend for us in Atlantic City,
and he's really
looking forward to it.
Oh, you can go to
Atlantic City anytime.
All you need to do is find
the nearest retirement home,
get on the first
bus that pulls up.
I don't want to disappoint him.
Well, invite Walter to go
to the hotel with you.
That way you still get to
spend the weekend together,
but just not surrounded by
seafood buffets and $10 hookers.
Yeah, but then he's gonna
distract me from my work.
Sounds to me like you've
already made your decision,
but you're feeling
bad about it.
Hey, braveheart,
Wilhelmina wants you to put together
a rack of Beaumart
clothes for the meeting.
Oh, check out the
Kelly Clarkson line.
All her skirts have a elastic waist-
bands, so they're really comfortable.
Thanks for the tip, love.
Of course.
So... I hear Daniel gave you
a big writing assignment.
Yeah, it's really exciting.
It's my first one.
A word of advice--
you may want to take
the Betty-wear
down just a notch.
The human piñata look may
be all the rage in Queens,
but in Soho, they'll arrest you
for crimes against humanity.
Have fun.
What about Atlantic City?
This hotel review is
really important.
If--if I do a good job, it could
lead to better things at "Mode."
I can't just pass up
this opportunity.
Oh, I was really looking
forward to this trip with you.
I got us tickets for the live
stage show of "The price is right."
- You did?
- Yes!
And you know I rule at plinko.
Well...
why don't you come and
stay with me at the hotel?
I don't wanna stay at some
lame Manhattan hotel.
I'm going to A.C.,
and I'm winning a dinette set.
That wasn't much
of an invitation.
Well, Atlantic City
isn't going anywhere.
No, honey,
but your boyfriend might.
Transcript : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com
I got it. I got it.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
It's just a hotel,
and I'm here to do my job.
Hi.
I have a reservation.
Betty Suarez.
Whoa. Nice orthodontia.
B right.
Thank you.
Um, do you need I.D.?
I have a business card
in here somewhere.
You're from "Mode"?
I am. Yes.
Do you need to see my card?
Ms. Suarez,
welcome to 50 Prince.
We're delighted to
have you as our guest.
We have a wonderful
suite waiting.
Please have a seat,
and the bellhop will
be right with you.
Okay. Thank you.
Um, those aren't real.
Right.
Thank you.
You know that's not
a pop-up book, right?
I hope not.
I'm doing research.
I'm writing an article on women
who tease their way to the top.
Can I get some quotes?
You think I tease
men to get power?
You don't know me at all.
Well, give me an hour.
Daniel Meade--
you are a
presumptuous, chauvinistic,
payaso, prepotente, insolente,
creído, presumido...
Shoot. I don't have
any cash, but...
I have three rides left on it.
Thank you.
I'm in heaven.
I'm in hell.
Imagine working at a sweatshop
and not even being proud
of what you're making.
Oh, now look at this.
This isn't too bad,
this little tartan number.
Well, then you wear it.
I'm sure you'll be a big hit at
the next bagpipe convention.
Oh, now I like this.
I think this is perfect for your
weekly meetings at the coven.
Here's what I've dug up on Mr.
Ted Lebeau.
Aside from being obscenely wealthy,
he has three kids,
four ex-wives and five
golden retrievers.
I think Davy Crockett
showed at Westminster.
How nouveau riche.
All right. Let's sprinkle a little
lone star state around my office.
Make him feel at home.
Oh, Mark.
Did, uh, Nico return my call?
Not yet.
Are you certain you sent the care
package to the boarding school?
I'm certain.
Can you call her again, please?
Yes.
Oh!
Soft and cozy.
No... uh, lavish refinement...
and downy opulence.
Spectacular view.
No... that's boring.
Deliciously divine view.
Ms. Suarez. How can I help you?
Oh. Hi.
I'd like to order a massage.
Very good.
You look like a bank manager.
I doubt any bank managers are
wearing La Perla undergarments.
I found an interview
in a whiskey magazine
where tex extols
the virtues of rye.
Yes?
Ah, yes. Marc will come and
escort him in. Thank you.
Oh! I wanted to
watch him mosey.
All right.
I'm gonna giddyap.
Ooh. Howdy.
Mr. Lebeau.
I'm Wilhelmina Slater.
Pleasure to meet you.
Call me Ted.
Ted it is.
That's our most popular line.
Affordable and stylish.
The career woman on a budget.
How you like it?
It's like nothing I own.
Well, it looks good on you.
So you a fan of college ball?
- Excuse me?
- Longhorns.
You went to U.T.-Austin?
Oh, no. Uh, Marc did.
Yes, I did.
It was so... southern.
Go Longhorns! Yay!
God bless America.
Is this your daughter?
Yes, it is.
So shall we talk, uh, business?
Well, my ad people tell me I
should be in your swanky magazine,
but I'm not sure
it's the right fit.
Why don't you convince me?
Oh, my gosh.
Hi, I'm Sven.
Ready for your massage?
You're not a girl.
No, all the women were
booked for the evening.
I'll set up the table,
and you can disrobe.
These are good, really good.
You can't even feel
the difference.
Definitely.
You know, I didn't get an
invite to the slumber party.
Did I miss the pillow fight?
Can I have the
water bra, please?
You know, if you want a man's
perspective-- natural and bigger.
Daniel, we're doing an article
on breast reconstruction
for recovering women.
Oh. Um...
um... I'm gonna go.
Are you sure you wanna
wear your glasses?
Yeah. Yeah, um,
I have to take notes.
So... um... would you say that
you are manipulating
my muscles right now?
I guess.
Hmm. Um...
is this Shih Tzu or...
or are you "Rolfing" me?
I'll get that.
You just, uh...
you just keep relaxing.
Yes?
What's going on here?
Santos.
Hilda. I haven't
seen you in a few.
You look good.
Um... can I talk to you
in private for a second?
I heard at junior's bodega
you hit big on a number.
Right to the point--
that's my favorite thing about you.
I can't say I have a
favorite thing about you.
Please.
I know what I got
that you like.
I need money, Santos.
For Ignacio.
Come on, in this neighborhood?
You heard I won money.
I heard you need money.
- How much?
- 5 grand for a lawyer.
Look, I've never
asked you for a penny,
but we're in a lot of
trouble right now.
I need your help.
You know how hard
this is for me.
You always carry that
kind of cash on you?
I didn't get a chance to deposit
it in my checking account.
I didn't know they had
checking accounts at O.T.B.
Look, I only got
half right now.
I'll give you the rest later.
But I want to see
Justin in return.
I want to see my son.
It's not what it seems.
It's just a massage.
I have to review all of
the hotel services.
I don't like strange, tall,
muscle guys touching you.
It was nothing.
- Excuse me.
- Thank you, Sven.
- You were wonderful.
- You're welcome.
Walter-- why are you here?
What happened to Atlantic City?
I got off the bus at Secaucus.
I couldn't go. I...
I just want to spend
time with you, Betty.
It's all about you and me.
It doesn't matter if it's
Atlantic City or a...
a really nice hotel room. Wow.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
This is freakin' sweet!
I'm really glad you're here.
But you know that I need
to focus on my work.
We can have fun,
but this weekend is
all about my review.
I'm not gonna get in your way.
Okay.
I need to get changed.
I made dinner reservations.
Okay. I'll watch TV
while you change.
Walter, you can't wear a
t-shirt to a 3-star restaurant.
Why not? Rock stars
wear t-shirts to award shows.
You're not a rock star.
You play the flute in a
Jethro Tull tribute band.
We're buying you a dress shirt.
You like it?
It's my prom dress.
Wow.
Our readership has climbed 10% in
the past year, which is impressive,
considering the internet's negative
effect on the magazine industry.
Yeah, but the people that shop
at Beaumart don't read "Mode,"
and the people that read "Mode"
are too uppity to shop at Beaumart.
What's the point of
spending money on ads?
Well, we do have regular
people that work here, Ted.
We're not out of touch
with real America.
I have an uncle who lives all
the way out in New Jersey.
Times are changing.
Couture designers are branching out.
Luella, Mizrahi,
McCartney are all doing lines
for discount-brand stores.
With my help,
I can convince a designer
to do a line for Beaumart.
That's interesting.
Why don't we chat about it over dinner?
Oh, wonderful.
I made reservations at Babbo.
You know,
I don't come to New York City often,
but when I do,
there's only one place I like to go to.
I love this place!
I think we're in Kansas, Toto.
But we're only 15 minutes late.
We gave up the table
after 10 minutes.
It's friday night,
and we're completely booked.
You're not getting in tonight.
Let's just go upstairs.
We'll order room service.
We'll snuggle.
It'll be romantic.
No! Walter, I have to eat here.
This is my job. Excuse me.
I'm here reviewing your
hotel for my magazine.
I'm from "Mode." "Mode."
My mistake. I have a lovely
table waiting for you.
Please follow me.
Give it back.
I don't want to be
indebted to that loser.
After everything he's
put you through? No.
Papi, drop it. It's done.
Santos is not a generous man.
What did you have to
do for the money?
He's coming to see
Justin tonight.
You're just asking
for trouble, mija.
I know that's not the picture
I chose, because the one I chose,
it wasn't focused,
unless I'm going blind--oh!
Very, very nice, girls.
Who ordered this?
- Hmm?
- Not me.
So you obviously made it
to the tenth chapter,
where I mention indian
food as an aphrodisiac.
Sorry about what I said before.
The whole breast thing.
Apology accepted.
So what do you think?
Oh, yeah, no.
I'm getting into it.
It's pretty funny. Interesting.
But you really think men are gonna
be obsolete in a thousand years?
Oh, absolutely. Maybe sooner.
That doesn't mean I
wouldn't miss you.
What else caught your eye?
Well, you're the first one in
your family to graduate college,
you speak five languages,
and you still have a bullet
in your hip from a...
hunting trip.
Oh, my god.
How can you eat this?
I'm mexican. This is nothing.
Oh, you look like you
could use some air.
Do you ride?
Ride what?
Red wine reduction.
Why would I want
my food reduced?
Maybe it has less calories?
I think we should get
the chef's tasting menu.
It's probably his
greatest hits.
So tell me--
would you say that the
ambience is romantic
or better suited for
business occasions?
I don't know.
It's kind of pretentious.
Walter, look.
I've never written
anything like this before,
so I don't know what I'm
supposed to be focusing on,
and I'd really
appreciate some help.
I don't know anything
about this stuff.
You know what?
Maybe if we go upstairs, right?
Order a couple of burgers,
watch a little cable...
I can help you review
the TV reception.
What?
Okay, here we go.
- Do you serve food?
- Of course, sweetie.
Anything non-dairy?
Ted, let's talk ad pages.
Just a second.
Let me see that menu, cutie.
Okay, we'll have an order of nachos,
extra chili,
and we want some hot wings,
and keep that beer coming, darlin'.
Do you like buffalo
wings, Willy?
Oh, they are my favorite snack.
Especially on super bowl sunday.
Marc!
You know, I think, it's...
- Marc, you can leave, darling.
- I love you.
Oh, come on!
Uh, it's a lucky shot.
No luck. I'm good.
Three out of five.
Do you really want to do that
to yourself? I play to win.
So do I. Let's, uh,
make it a little more interesting?
Keep that wallet out.
I'm gonna empty it.
Really?
Come on. Show me your rack.
Sweet corn foam with
black truffle jelly
and duck foie gras air.
Compliments of the chef.
Thank you.
Which one's foam,
and which one's air?
Well, that's obvious. It's...
whichever one's
lighter is the air.
Um, I think we're supposed to
dip the bread in the foam.
Go ahead. Dip.
Would you say that
that ravished your
inquisitive palate...
or induced an
orgasmic explosion
of scintillating flavors
on your taste buds?
It's like eating shaving cream.
- Did you call him?
- Four times.
It went straight to voice mail.
Mom, it's okay.
He's not coming.
Just forget about it.
He's right.
And it's better this way.
You don't need him around.
He's a speeding train
coming right at you.
Why do you think I'm a tease?
Why do you think
I'm a sexaholic?
You win.
Why did you just
throw the game?
Because your ego was
getting a little bruised.
Sofia, let's end the games.
You never answered my question.
Why do you think
I'm a sexaholic?
I never said that.
But you sent that
article over to Betty.
It was about me, right?
You're so narcissistic.
What makes you think
it was not about me?
That's it.
I am gonna grab that son of a
bitch by the back of his neck
and drag him down
Roosevelt boulevard.
Keep watching.
I might be on the 11:00 news.
Jellied terrine of brown crab
with lamb's brains
and courgette.
What's courgette?
Zucchini.
Why didn't you
just say zucchini?
Because they call it courgette.
I'm not eating this.
It's gross.
Walter, please.
I want real food, Betty!
Walter, will you please
keep your voice down?
Could I just get a
burger and fries?
I'll see what I can do, sir.
I can't believe that
you just did that.
What? What's the big deal?
It's a restaurant.
They have a stove.
They can make me a cheeseburger.
Oh, I should've
asked for cheese.
You know how important this review
is to me, and you're sabotaging it
because you've never liked
me working at "Mode."
No, what--I'm not
trying to sabotage you.
I just don't like this place,
and I-I don't like pretending
to be somebody that I'm not.
What? What,
you're saying that I'm pretending?
Yeah, and I don't get it.
We don't belong in
places like these.
No, Walter,
maybe you don't belong.
You're right. I don't.
I don't know Betty from "Mode."
I like Betty from Queens.
You know,
why don't you tell her
to give me a call
when she shows up?
Nestled in downtown gotham,
the hotbed of all that is super
chic and scrumptiously posh,
50 Prince is an absolutely
delectable dreamland.
Hate that. This isn't me.
It's not who I am.
Hi. It's Betty.
You're too late.
Justin's already asleep,
and I have been looking
all over for your ass.
So what? Tell me,
what is the excuse this time?
I can offer you an insert
in the june issue.
It's our bridal issue.
It is one of our top-selling.
One more round.
Oh, Ted.
Enough with the frat party.
You're not gonna advertise.
Just a minute.
Hey, Nico.
Did you get the, uh,
care package I sent you?
Oh, of--of course I knew
you're allergic to perfume.
That was for your roommate.
You don't have a roommate?
Well...
darling, I'm doing
the best I can.
Well, how-- how am I supposed to know
you're in jelly bean withdrawal?
E-mail me a list.
I'll have Marc go to the--
Nico.
Just... what happened?
The money I gave you--
I owed it to my bookie.
I was about to come
over to the house,
but a couple of large guys
paid me a little visit.
Well, at least they left
you with your teeth.
That was very
considerate of them.
Yeah, but I still had to
cancel my big photo shoot.
With this face?
You could do a public
service announcement
about the dangers of
illegal gambling.
I'm sorry you spent all
night looking for me.
I'm sorry about a lot
of other stuff, too.
Okay, don't-- don't start
getting all real and emotional.
It's not sexy.
I just-- I didn't want Justin
to see me like this, you know?
Hey, you know...
it's just a little
blood, and...
a couple of bruises.
You'll be brand new when he
sees you on Thanksgiving.
I'd like you to come.
Watch it.
That's what you get.
I have three teenage daughters.
When their hormones kick in,
one minute they love you,
the next, they're saying
and doing everything they
can to put the hurt on you.
Well, she has every
reason to be angry at me.
I didn't put together
her care package.
I had Marc do it.
She's like cat in a saw?
She's all upset?
I believe the exact words were,
"I hate you. You suck."
If you'd been a stay-at-home
mom and baked cookies,
she'd still hate you
and think you suck.
The truth of the matter is,
I could've tried to bake some cookies...
at least once.
When my girls were little,
I worked 15 hours a day.
Now I'm trying to
make up for it.
It's what you have to do.
It's what your daughter wants.
You know,
I'm glad I saw this side of you.
Wilhelmina Slater's a mom.
Trying to be a mom.
Well, someone who makes the
effort to be a good parent
is the kind of person
I want to work with.
You'll advertise with us?
Actually, I made that decision after
your sales pitch back at the office,
but I thought I'd have a
little fun at your expense.
So now I'd like some real food.
What do you say we
go over to Babbo?
I know Mario. He'll keep
his kitchen open for me.
Oh, thank you!
What's in the bag?
Your burger.
It's kinda cold, and I ate half of it,
but it's really good.
Thanks.
You came all the way back
here to bring me a burger?
No. I came back to apologize.
You know, when I said that you didn't
belong, I was talking about me.
I was just so nervous that I
couldn't do things the right way.
I don't get it.
Why--why do you put yourself through it?
Because...
it's--it's what I've
always dreamed of doing.
I'm scared of losing you.
You're not gonna lose me.
I'm here.
I just need you to support me.
I used the shampoo
you bought me.
It really gets the frizz out.
Oh, that's great.
- I gotta get going.
- Here.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
I think I did a good job.
I'm really proud of it.
That's what counts, mi amor.
- Have a good day.
- Thank you.
Justin, I need to talk
to you for a second.
Okay.
I better get ready for work.
I have a big surprise for you.
Guess who's coming to
Thanksgiving dinner?
Martha Stewart?
I won the contest!
Martha Stewart? No.
Your father.
I'll believe that
when I see it.
Look... papito, I know your
father messes up sometimes...
all the time,
but he means well,
and he loves you.
It's just something came
up the other night.
I've heard that excuse.
Look, your dad came through with
the money to help your grandpa,
so we have to open
our home to him.
I guess. It's just...
Martha would have been
a better surprise.
Good morning.
Our offices are
all cleaned up, so
we'll be getting
out of your way.
Out of my way? Sofia,
I haven't stopped thinking
about you all weekend.
Sent you a message--messages.
You get my e-mails?
Yeah, I was busy.
Busy doing what?
I had plans...
with my boyfriend.
Apologies galore
for friday night.
There's something about
drinking out of body parts
that makes me feel
kind of pukey.
I assume you landed
the account.
Among other things.
You must have had some weekend.
A straight man bought
you shoes--nice ones.
I peeked...
and maybe tried them on.
"A little high fashion and
a little down-home country
make a great match.
Love, Ted."
Wow, it's really good.
You did great.
I don't think I
can use it, though.
But you just said
it was really good.
No, it is.
I mean, it's--it's...
really you, Betty.
It's just... not really "Mode."
Right.
Okay, yeah.
I guess I understand that.
See, our readers--they're not interested
in a regular girl point of view.
They want something sleek and,
uh, and glamorous.
I will print a shorter
version, though--
the name of the hotel, the, uh,
the 3-star rating you gave it.
Okay.
Well, thank you for
the opportunity,
and I hope that if another
assignment comes up,
you'll let me try again.
Absolutely.
Okay.
Oh, there you are.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Why are you hiding
in the bathroom?
I'm not hiding.
I'm just...
I'm hiding.
Is it because of this?
I blew it.
He's not gonna run it.
Betty...
what do you care
what he thinks?
You cannot let other people's
opinions get you down,
especially in this business.
Now enough of the pity party.
Come on. Stand up straight.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Chin up.
Show me those braces.
Now repeat after me.
- I am an attractive...
- intelligent...
confident businesswoman.
- You did read my book.
- I did.
I thought your
article was terrific.
You liked it?
I loved it.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I'm running your article
in my magazine...
if it's all right with you.
Yes!