Peaches!
And then you wake up.
Yes
I mean ...
At least one was less violent.
I am a coward, Dr. McCrae.
You had two tours of service in Iraq
and anything that passes,
survivor guilt, pain,
loss, nightmares ...
- ... Make you less brave ..
- Valiente.
A brave man would have
sent these letters.
I write these letters
was more important than upload.
Remember that life had
out of the war.
And now you are free to live that life.
You have to try to move forward.
Yes
- What are you doing?
- I proceed.
You can not fire
symbolic here ..
Trevor, you've seen in dogs --
What are you doing?
Nothing. Reading.
I found these letters
written by ...
this soldier.
You crying?
No. I could have ... yawn.
In some tissue.
You know, some people
sneeze, Felix.
Yes, some people read letters
and cry about dogs
his apartment
and listen to soft rock 87.
Why a soldier you write letters?
Not for me.
Are for this girl he loves,
but do not know that love,
because they did not realize until
was in the midst of this war.
And the only thing that did remain
are your memories of your loved Peaches.
Do not worry, Joe.
Peaches bring you, my friend.
We bring you Peaches!
. :: WWw.Subs-Team.Tv::.
P r e s e n t
A translation of: angie.cortes,
Chuchi, cmillan, and Iriel Garper.
Corrections and adjustments:
Iriel.
Cupid - S01E05
Shipping Out
So this girl you are
trying to meet the soldier ...
"Peaches" is his name
of stripper?
It gives him the nickname Joe.
His name is Robin Peachtree.
Neighbors were in high school.
Playing basketball
in the way of entry.
Because I was crazy about her.
Joe donned value
asked Peaches
go to the dance of welcome.
And she said "yes"
and then he discovered
it was only a bet
made it popular with kids.
No. She said "yes"
and then the army's father Joe
was sent to New Jersey.
They left Baton Rouge two days later.
- Never been to the dance.
- No video image change.
No. They lost contact.
Later, Joe was sent to Iraq.
Suddenly, in the midst of war,
bullets pass at full speed.
Guess who they think.
Jane Russell.
Betty Grable.
- Robin Peachtree.
- Right.
This girl has not seen
not spoken in years.
When their lives hung by a thread,
That is what you thought.
He writes these letters never sent.
Instead ...
you gave yourself.
Yeah, well, something.
He was pulling
and I recycle.
I do 100 pairs.
This, my friend, it will be easy.
It is a federal offense to read
mail from another person ...
Friend.
As if that applied to me.
"If you drive through Baton Rouge,"
"Be sure to stop at Robin's Nest."
"Owner Robin Peachtree, 26 -"
Is the correct age.
Why need Cupid arrows
magical when you Google?
"Do not miss the donuts
crab stuffing. "
Robin's Nest - Cajun Cooking
and catering company.
Responsible for the meal.
All you need to
draw your attention ...
Lying ...
You have to be smart
romance your searches.
If you feel the need to conspire
to the attention of someone,
you are exceeding.
Exactly. Then there is this dance
where we of chaperones.
And I was thinking that my
bet
appointment was to take a sexy,
convince her that I demand.
I hear something?
I heard you.
I could not agree less.
You, however, Mr --
Like, friendly, countryman.
Trevor, you have a question?
Suggestion? Yes, I,
thanks for asking.
Perhaps more group celebrations
singles,
less charlitas self.
This he calls "charlita"
is what this group is, Trevor.
Currently, yes.
You listen to talk while
browsing room looking
someone to sleep.
People come here for advice,
console,
share stories.
In bed with someone who knew
in the group of singles.
That is not true.
People come here because
've gathered conveniently
a collection of available
premises within a group.
That is why they are here, right?
Correct. So I propose a party.
- I care?
- No. Go ahead.
All in favor of one party,
contribute some cash.
So if I'm reading
this correctly,
this is something that the group would enjoy?
You know what?
Maybe it's time
to bring our new
skills to the field.
Bring biscuits.
You are not allowed to plan.
You just have to go.
A little problem with the party.
- A little problem with my assistant. Josie?
- You may be in the bathroom.
So expect to be taken
a break to go to the bathroom
could enter and shoving here?
E interrupt your important
salad to go? Yes
Now about the party --
I thought you were supposed to not
I worry for the party.
You do not have to worry about.
You just have to donate ... a little
- To the supplier. We are short.
- How short?
- A plane ticket.
- What?
The provider lives in Baton Rouge,
but I found a cheap flight.
I think we ended up here.
What? No, come on. Mira, mira,
just listen to me, okay?
Look, even with the airfare,
it is still cheaper to use
a provider of Baton Rouge
- ... One of New York.
- I wanted to serve the cakes.
- The biscuits are not the issue.
- There is an issue now?
Of course there is an issue.
Josie, the next time Trevor is
here, there's no rest for the bathroom.
- Mardi Gras!
- Excuse me?
That is the issue. So clearly,
Cajun need a supplier,
and I know a great --
great girl, great smile
great donuts
crab stuffing.
You know this woman?
I know, and
great demand.
Look, it would be a feast of
Mardi Gras properly without it.
Okay. Cover the cost
to bring the supplier.
Excellent. This is unbelievable.
You will not regret.
- There are suppliers in New York.
- I know, but I believe this provider
may be the key to
actual identity of Trevor.
It is the first person
mention of her past
which is not a Greek deity.
- In two nights.
- That's right.
And I read about your buñuelos
crab stuffing
in the Dining Guide Map ".
I would love to help you with your party
Mardi Gras in New York, Mr. Pierce,
but I hired Brad Pitt
pelarle for a grape
on a rocket to
Mars that day.
J.T., I know you.
One question,
when one type of service
deliveries appear in your business
with a passenger ...
you will rise to that plane
I have been in the
City 20 minutes,
and you saw two types
holding hands
and the restaurant of "Seinfeld."
Well ... Yes, go to the matinee of
"My I", and have
your bingo board of
City of New York full.
What is this place?
This is where the party is.
I was hired to cook for a
party at a house in pornography.
What happens to you
those in blue states?
No, no, no. It was a pornographic film,
but it became a bar.
Here.
I took the liberty of
Sign in to your room.
I live in Louisiana ...
not in a cave.
I can see it
is an apartment.
For the rest of the world ...
but for you, this is a hotel
with all services.
See? Have your mentitas,
clean towels,
fresh flowers.
- This is Felix, the concierge.
- I'm not a janitor.
- Try to get your sex slave?
- Let's see where the day takes us.
Because all of my dress
Good kitchen knives,
- ... And my key ring is a whistle.
- I promise I'll be safe here.
Ago in New York
always so cold?
We have hot and muggy
if you stay a while.
Okay, who is
ready to cook?
I need a bowl
of jambalaya ...
- To carry.
- Sale in moments.
I do not know if that is okay
come here for lunch.
A person should eat
in an atmosphere of calm and familiar,
surrounded by beauty.
Is that ...
jambalaya?
Well, yes it is.
Like the jambalaya?
I lived in Louisiana
for a couple of years,
so, well ... yes.
God. That smells like
if true.
You have to try. In fact,
I think I have an extra spoon.
Man.
Damn.
That's good.
Have any idea how hard it is ...
find good food
Cajun in this city?
Sorry,
but today is the day
to steal a guy
a bowl of jambalaya.
You do not have to steal.
I know where you can get more.
You know what this is?
It is a hurricane with
your name on it.
- How much money was in that hat?
- Enough.
Cajun crab sandwiches?
Are excellent.
I am anxious to know
the cook, for which I paid.
- Where is the kitchen?
- Going through those doors.
So ... can cover
my turn on Friday?
I have tickets for Madonna.
- Perhaps, rabbit, maybe.
- I really want to see it, Trevor,
and I have already asked
all others.
Or you cover me, or an invention
Health code violation
and I closed the place.
I think perhaps we can
negotiate a deal.
Yes!
I am so happy that you have
snacks like crab.
That is, it's fun
cooking for people
who do not eat this kind of
food every day.
I am so happy that
Trevor has contacted me.
Yeah, about that --
When they met, and you Trevor?
This morning at the airport.
- No, no, I mean originally.
- This was the first time I saw him,
but it looks really nice.
You mean you do not know before?
Perhaps your family know
his family y. ..
Not that I know.
No, but it has been incredible.
Now, I'm sorry. I just --
I have to concentrate.
This shrimp etouffee
does not beat himself.
Trevor.
Why choose Robin
to cook --
Watch this.
What am I looking at?
The human condition.
Yes, of course,
the human condition --
There is, in all its glory.
Sabes? It is a fact
that the way you dance
is the way that you love.
Is that true?
Maybe you're a Jerry Lewis, you know?
As one of those guys who
move around.
Or maybe you're the dealer, you know?
Like when you're dealing,
spreading.
Sabes? Or maybe you're
Space Ghost.
And then there's the punishment.
- I do not dance, so ...
- My theory is confirmed.
- Quick Jump ... only.
- Why?
Because I am part of
percentage unfortunate
of the population seems
an idiot when dancing fast.
What makes you think
you can not dance?
I thought it was a
adequate dancer
until I saw the video
my first year dancing.
My first and last high school dance.
Wait a minute. Do not go
to a dance after that?
Girls are so sensitive to the fact
of being teased and ridiculed.
The key to dancing is getting caught.
Sabes? Out of your head.
That is what I have.
So tell me why
Robin knew that?
Dr. McCrae.
Joe ...
What are you doing here?
Trevor invited me.
Of course he did.
It turns out that we are both large
Fans of Cajun food.
Sorry. I knew it was not a party
group for singles.
Although I met Trevor
in his office,
so I guess that
That makes sense.
What is it?
Because I'm still confused.
Things should be clarified
at any time.
Someone wants lobster pie?
Peaches!
Joe.
This ... Peaches is.
Our cook is Peaches.
No, not anymore.
Joe was the only person
I called so.
We went to high school together.
We have not
seen in years.
It's like a strange coincidence.
Is that ... coincidence?
Well, I might be somewhat responsible.
I heard that Robin is a
great chef of Cajun food,
and I learned that Joe loves
Cajun food, you know what?
Who cares how it happened?
Is the destination.
Maybe I should use
discuss this in the alley.
If you and I are going to be fighting
you better remove the earrings.
I do not know how to fix this,
- But you're playing with fire.
- Love is fire, love is passion.
It's so game.
It's in the description of my work.
Well, the description of my work
is trying to help my patients,
and prevent it from hurting
themselves or others.
And you're bringing together Robin and Joe
to have a world of pain.
This relationship is doomed.
Are you sure you're not Greek?
Because you are too dramatic.
You are not a god.
You are not omniscient.
Joe stole the record or
spy my sessions with him.
Or something, and whatever you
did was something terrible,
because he is unable --
Not in a position to start
anything now.
And he and Robin and I will pay
to pick up the pieces.
Yes I did something terrible.
I can not do this.
I think now you get regodearte
You know what?
Robin, do not worry.
I will fix this.
- No.
- Let him go.
It is the opposite of a superhero.
Is rare.
In all my ...
fantasies of "See Joe Adams again."
The kiss was exactly true.
You really should go
to change my shirt.
I do not want to walk around the festival
appears that a baby
vomited on me.
Joe!
Where are you going?
Hey, come on!
This is your golden opportunity!
The girl for which he sighs,
the girl to write to him
when you were in Iraq.
Dr. McCrae spoke to you about that?
Because that is unprofessional.
Look, the truth is ...
was in the waiting room
dropped when the cards
and then, you know,
I took the loan.
Find Peaches
and organized this meeting,
so the two could be again.
I did.
Are you crazy?
Not at all.
I am colorful.
Get letters from the trash
half wet, half-burnt,
and read it.
That is not crazy?
Of eccentric, maybe.
Look, I loved those letters,
and I really think that Peaches
Also you will love.
Stop calling it "Peaches."
Not have given him the cards, or not?
No. Never ...
But ...
But what?
Did your other personality?
It could have been left in her bed.
Thinking that you and Peach --
I mean Robin could be on that
bed tonight.
And that might be the perfect ending,
perfect for a night.
Robin can not see those letters.
I think that a harasser crazy.
It is bad enough
The Hague kissed it!
Hey, no, look, I saw the kiss.
There was nothing wrong with him.
The problem was to go out shooting.
I wanted to stay.
Let's go back, okay?
We can tell Robin
to go out running
to put money in the parking meter.
I could sell it.
- What I say, your seat.
- I can go back to Peaches.
- Why not?
- It's complicated, okay?
Life is complicated.
Love is simple.
He had a plan, okay?
And this was not in the plan.
I want those cards!
Come on.
That's what crazy love.
Even where it is impractical,
even when it's drawbacks --
Not be assumed that saw these.
I am very happy to have.
Yes, yes, yes.
Coming.
Hello?
Trevor, you know where is Joe?
Claire Bear!
Good morning.
- Joe Adams. What are you?
- Happy to report that ...
Joe and Robin are
currently closed.
- Joe missed his meeting today.
- Anything that afflicts Joe,
I predict that the moment my plan
is fully implemented,
he will be cured.
You are greatly out of your element.
I can say that I
talk, please
I will. In fact, I'm desperate
by a change of underwear.
So anyway, I
venture there.
Promise me that this is the last time
I get a report
about your underwear.
Again.
Show me what you got, buddy.
Come to the left ...
Right y. .. No! Come on.
I did it again!
God! How was the whole day.
Come on.
Do it again, I want to see
you do it again.
want it? I want
Tell me what you want.
Tell me what you want
- Give it to me! Give it to me! Give it to me! Come on.
- Down here. Below.
What? Why not come
and try to do
Give me  Vamos! Give it to me
No, I will give you, if you want it
have to ganártelo.
- I want you to win it.
- Okay, cúbranse, guys.
I gotta go.
I need supplies.
Well, here I come.
Three, two, one.
I am opening the door.
I do not pay attention.
Remain in their field.
Trevor?
You can open your eyes.
They are dressed ...
And out of bed.
And slept on the floor.
You know, it was agreed that
I use my bed, maybe I was not clear.
- I slept in bed.
- Me on the floor.
You do not ...
We must refamiliarizarnos,
I mean, we have not had
yet a real quote.
Southerners.
Well, OK,
refamiliarícense you.
I have something in mind for the real event.
Do not forget  # #
'Cause you left a great impression #
In my heart  # #
I equivocaré  # #
I used to go here all the time.
This is my cousin
and this is my aunt,
- And this is, remember?
- Right, yes.
Singing this  # #
This  # # song for you now
# # You can not be close
Never forget  # #
# # I will never forget
Joe, what happens?
Peaches!
Yes, Joe?
Please can you check in my bag,
and see if I have an extra shirt?
Robin! Wait, I can explain.
No need to explain.
Book a flight
to Winnipeg tomorrow,
and had no thought
some reason ..
by which might be
mention it?
I thought this could be something.
I realized that not only
was your weekend. Taxi!
I could not tell, okay?
I did not want to think
he was a coward.
- Only ... I can not return.
- Go where?
Iraq.
Called me.
I was supposed to report tomorrow.
You are deserting?
This moment, now ...
That's why I could not tell you.
Could not bear to see your reaction.
You gonna cold.
This war has ruined me.
I close my eyes ...
And I'm back there.
Driving after a suicide bomb.
It blew itself to
a crowded market.
I am looking without aid
while a wounded colleague
calling his wife.
I can not do it again.
I can not go back --
Do not you owe me an explanation.
I read your letters.
Children?
I do not know how they do in Cajun country,
but here in the big city, we require
shoes and shirt.
What?
- is having lunch now.
- She does not care.
Why not tell me that Joe
was fleeing the country?
Because there is this thing called
Doctor-patient privilege.
- Sorry, Dr. McCrae.
- There was not much you could do.
Just give me a minute
with Trevor, please.
While we
the issue of disclosure.
Why does not mention that
I was flying ...
the high school girlfriend of Joe
well you could play God?
I am a God, okay?
If I ever know
I'm doing something divine,
never finish anything.
"Hi Claire, yes, I'm brushing
teeth. "
"Hi Claire, yes, I
making toast. "
"Claire: Yes, I am arranging a flight."
See what I mean?
I tried to make it perfectly clear
that the relationship was doomed.
You had to open the Pandora's box.
And please, do not tell me that
Pandora had a great rack.
I still have.
God! I was so close.
I was going to close the deal in
the couple tonight.
- I had planned this great event.
- I see.
You are the victim here.
No Joe, no Robin ... You.
I quit my room.
What was the big date?
Would welcome them with dancing
never had.
Look at you.
Mercenary, but sweet.
I think they need this appointment.
And frankly, it could
provide some closure
so they do not have to
spend another ten years
wondering, "what if?"
I do not get credit for closing.
Get it for love.
Well, maybe you just this once,
are not in your account.
Perhaps this is something nice
for two people whose relationship
never had a chance.
Think this is a good idea?
Yes, I think it will be very beneficial.
- This makes it easier.
- What's easier?
We need to borrow your car.
Yes, the flight tomorrow at 10:00 a.m.
to Baton Rouge,
leaving from Newark.
Thank you very much.
Well, at least I will see you soon
before I go to Canada.
Yes
I would like you to come with me.
You know, the party's annual sloshball
of Peachtree
is the next weekend.
We could use a bell.
Sloshball?
Softball, but ...
Uncle Ronnie puts barrels
at first base and third as well.
For the fourth entry,
Dad is a three layer
and cry about how the South
will rise again.
And Mom and Aunt Sue despise
the cake from the other.
Es .. only anarchy.
Okay.
Get hats, kids.
Let's experiment
a rite of passage.
Here is your bouquet.
Okay, Mommy, when we pick,
no pair in front, we are ashamed,
- Recógenos behind.
- I saw the dress?
I can not believe they finally come
Welcome to our dance.
Hi, I'm Tracy, I am with
welcoming committee.
I can see their IDs
student?
Perhaps in the left
your time machine.
Tracy, okay, okay.
These are my guests.
It's very generous of you, Carl.
Barely.
Thank you.
Sweet. Down.
Yes
You owe me one.
Is that one of the waitresses in the bar?
That would be Lita,
the sexy assistant.
And look. Here is our brand.
See how our fully evaluated
soft history teacher.
You're amazing.
You had to try
a couple tonight, no?
Just trying.
Notes, no hands.
You know, Carl has been coming
my group for years.
Incubated these confabulations
produced outside of bypassing,
because it can not simply walk
toward a woman and invite them to leave.
I will have to happen tonight.
Just preparing the bomb.
Man, maybe I should spend more
time in the secondary.
You see, you missed all these
secondary social
because you were concerned about the dance.
Could have been
kissing all the time.
You know how to do that, no?
Okay, bring the whole
the world to the dance floor .
Only  Scroll down a bit.
Here it is, is perfect.
Great smile, nice.
One more, one more.
- Maybe we should take a picture.
- No.
Come with me.
"Corazon intrepid?
It is a country song.
Yes it is.
We believe it is a public
who likes the country?
Daloa back.
I left excited  # #
Correct me.
It is the study of "Hee Haw."
We're going to love.
"Corazon intrepid"
Really?
Think is the best option?
That is not the relationship is doomed
because Joe is afraid of
return to Iraq?
So, I do not know.
If I choose a song,
perhaps choose something that
not emphasize the fact
that Joe is going to desert.
Joe told me he likes this song.
And indeed, received the Cross of
distinguished service, you know?
It is an incredibly brave man.
I sent him because he could not
leave behind what she had seen.
Is anguished, but not a coward.
And I sent it to me,
- And then do not listen to my recommendation.
- But still --
Well, there are all kinds of courage, Trevor.
With what Joe saw there, I think
to get up every morning
and face the day
is an act of courage.
And is this other guy, I think,
experienced a tragedy
in its past, and can not handle it.
Choose fend inventing
a fictional character.
and hide under a false reality.
What? You mean that pretends
be Captain America or --
Wait. I see.
- You speak to me.
- Nothing's wrong, right?
You know. It's funny.
Is calling me a chicken
woman who will not dance
because they laughed at it 15 years ago.
Listen. Yes!
Hello.
Guys, have seen Claire?
Is there.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
we're ready to start
boarding the flight ...
It is the first of many.
Not be open until
on the plane, okay?
Come here.
Wait.
No. Wait.
- Do not close the doors!
- Miss.
- Please do not close the door!
- Excuse me, lady!
Trevor.
Trevor, are you there?
You awake?
Joe will provide the service.
Will not go to Canada.
Will go to Iraq.
I can not stop doing that.
Not for me. If something comes to pass,
I could not forgive.
We have to find it.
Come on. Come on!
- Go to where?
- I do not know. But I have to talk to him.
Okay, let me think.
Perhaps there is something about where
Joe should report to your file.
We go to the office of Claire.
- Work on a Sunday?
- No, well we have luck.
May I ask what
are you doing here?
Thank you for coming so fast.
I called when I saw in this disaster.
So, it seems that someone in here
and reviewed all the files,
which makes me very badly,
because, you know,
I am a patient of Dr. McCrae.
So, I am enough
paranoid itself.
- I am going to shoot, right?
- I found the file!
Your file. Joe, here is your.
Thank you.
I was in the administration
and they called me --
Well, well, well.
This man claims to be his patient?
This man, in fact it is my patient,
and this is my wife ...
in charge of catering.
I got it from here.
Thank you.
- Can explain.
- I do not want to hear.
- Joe will return to Iraq.
- But is not ready.
So I stopped.
There is something here that
where reports say?
No, nothing, Trevor.
It's just saying that paper,
in my professional opinion,
Joe is ready to go to Iraq.
Something that his commander
you disagree.
So I know their commander.
I do not like, but I know him.
Get the
information on the road.
Joe Adams?
Meet Joe Adams? No?
Sorry.
Dude, Where's Joe?
- Joe Adams. Joe Adams.
- It's in your company?
- Joe Adams. Meet Joe Adams?
- No.
- Someone who is in charge?
- Know who Joe Adams?
Someone has seen Joe Adams?
Joe Adams.
It's in your company?
Have any idea where is Joe Adams?
Joe!
Peaches?
Are you supposed to be on the plane.
Are you supposed to be
en route to Winnipeg.
Okay, look, there's still time.
You can not do this.
Not for me. That is,
We had two nights together,
you can not do this type
decision based on that.
Look, I managed to hide all
my no attractive qualities.
That is, collect figurines of children.
Tejo costume for my dog.
I ...
I have seen "High School Musical"
as 30 times.
I plan to see it 30 more times.
I'm going to Iraq,
because if I do,
means that perhaps
can return some day
and learn more about the nightmare you are.
And if not I can never do that.
May need a
Southern restaurant in Winnipeg.
Come on. You hate the cold.
Perhaps I am accustomed.
This large family you love so much?
I could not ask that the leave,
and you did not want.
I want to do these 12 months.
And get off my head, and for the first time
feel that there is some
place to go home.
I want to go to church with your mom.
I sit in the
swing entry y. ..
and let the past go
and begin to live the present.
It appears your big closed the deal.
Going to war for me.
Going to war for love.
As I said.
# I can not promise that
this will work fine #
"But  kill me, dear,
if we had not tried #
# # I got a fearless heart
#  strong enough to
go through the part that frightens #
#  has been broken many times before #
# A fearless heart
just back for more #