- Last night was fun.
- Yeah yeah.
- Do it again tonight?
- Sure. I'll call you later.
I'll call you later.
How pathetic are you guys?
Pathetic, us?!
Who tells a
first date that they love her?
Oh yeah, right. I told
her that i loved her.
- Looked like you were gonna tell her you loved her.
- My point exactly.
- Whatever - Aw, e, thess
are just bitter
- 'Cause you're on a hot streak.
- Thanks, vince.
Guy's got more pussy the last
month than the previous 29 years,
I wouldn't call it a hot streak, i'd
call it entering the twilight zone.
That's what being a successful
manager does for you.
So you're saying it has
nothing to do with him,
- Just the business card?
- Yep!
Ah, now i get it.
So you've been banging
all these dates, e?
E don't bang them
that quickly.
E needs to be wined and
dined for at least a month.
Oh no no no! I think i
heard banging last night.
- Was there banging, e?
- Turtle: well?
Was there banging?
Can we talk about important stuff, please?
All right, what do you
have on your mind?
Are you nervous?
When you're prepared, there's no need to be nervous.
- It's just a driving test.
- I'm talking about leno.
I'm more nervous
about the driving test.
Don't take e's
aston martin then.
Those pricks give you points
off just for having a fancy car.
- Leno, vince. What are you gonna talk about?
- I'm open for suggestions.
I've never been invited on,
so i wouldn't have any.
Just tell the world how
sick the movie's gonna be.
No, the clip'll say that. He needs
something that'll make a statement.
Like when crispin glover
kicked letterman in the head?
- Not that kind of statement.
- Besides, i'm not that limber.
Tell him about how
you let those two girls
Believe that they convinced you
to have a threesome last week.
- I don't think that's gonna fly either, turtle.
- I'll save it for conan.
Who's that?
Oh, you have to be
kidding me. Who is that!?
- Get back here.
- Yeah, get back here!
- Hello?
- Hey, e, it's sloan.
Get back here,
you miniature stud!
Sorry about that.
Glad to see that fame and success
hasn't changed much over there.
- Yeah, nothing's changed.
- Good to hear.
- So what's up?
- It just so happens that a friend of mine
Desperately needs to sublet her
house to someone and i thought of you.
Is that what it takes to get a call from youhese days?
- Phone works both ways.
- I left you a message.
I didn't get a message.
E, i'm calling you now because i
thought of you when she brought this up.
- Why? I'm not even looking.
- I heard that you looked at a place
On crescent
a couple months back.
- Ah, keeping tabs on me, huh?
- For some reason
My friends think i'm still
interested in your whereabouts.
- But you're not?
- E, do you want to look at this house?
It's unbelievable.
Yeah, sure.
Morning, ari.
How are you?
My girl won her debate
on friday,
My boy scored a goal
in soccer on saturday
And my wife agreed to visit
her mother without me.
- I don't know how things could get much better.
- Ari.
- Give me something good, andrew.
- Greg garcia good?
You signed him? I thought
he was happy where he was?
Until i convinced him he'd be happier here.
You hear that, everybody?
"My name is earl" is now a
member of the miller gold family.
Mr. Andrew klein
is responsible for that.
Which means that
in this horrific economy
He has secured himself a future.
All of you can do that as well
If you go out there and sign someone
who can syndicate a goddamned show.
- Vinnie's doing leno. You want to come?
- Love to.
All right.
- What's all the yelling about?
- Oh, didn't you hear?
Andrew just signed another show runner.
Oh, i did. Very impressive.
So you either owe me an apology or a blowjob.
- Your choice.
- Oh, okay, ari.
I apologize. But i think
andrew should blow you.
You said he was a deadbeat.
The only one sucking is you.
All is well with
the miller gold agency!
- Well, not all.
- What's your problem?
I had dinner with
my parents last night
- And my father spent the entire
meal reaming me out.
You never told him
you liked dick?
- He knew that by the time i was nine.
- I'm not following you.
But the phone is ringing.
I need to talk to you
about my... career.
The career that you won't have
if you don't answer the phone?
Ari, i will handle the
phone. Please, i need to talk.
So talk.
I'm so glad you're in a good mood.
- Who says i'm in a good mood?
- You just did!
You just yelled "all is well
at the miller gold agency."
- That was an act to boost morale.
- Well, what's wrong?
- What's right? Have you seen my stock portfolio, lloyd?
- No.
And i shot
an 82 yesterday, lloyd.
An 82! I missed three putts
from inside eight feet.
Can you imagine missing
a hole from that close?
If i lose the club championship to
chervin i will sue butch harmon's ass.
- Ari!
- Yes, lloyd, yes?
I want a promotion!
- You do?
- I've been on your desk over three years.
- I've paid my dues.
- Is this about your father?
Did you know that my father
was very strict?
- No.
- Yeah. He berated me and he pushed me
And he insulted me
and it made me feel
very insecure and lost.
But i became a man-
My own man.
And now i berate
and i push.
- I have noticed.
- Make your own man, lloyd.
- I'm trying.
- Not trying hard enough! The goddamn phone is ringing.
But, ari, we haven't
even really talked.
I talked! And my hope
is that you listened.
Go!
No, cut it
- Cut it left. Left.
- Why aren't we using cones?
- Don't talk to him, drama!
- Let him concentrate.
- I got it, guys. I got it.
Now ease it in there.
- Sorry, e.
- That's okay.
I'll get you
a new one.
Don't worry about it.
Ahem.
All right,
you're almost there.
There you go.
Okay, i think
you're ready.
All right, everyone in!
Let's go!
Oh, st. Christopher,
please protect us.
- I'm gonna meet you guys over there.
- What? Really?
- What's the big deal?
- Vince: nothing, i guess.
What do you have to do that's more
important than watching me get my license?
I'm just gonna meet sloan
for a coffee.
- Was that sloan that called this morning?
- Yeah.
- You didn't tell us.
- I don't tell you everything.
Well, you tell me
everything.
Something's up.
- Definitely.
- Yeah, what's up, e?
Nothing's up.
It's a coffee.
20 years in this business, i don't
think i've had a sip in the office.
Well, when the king of karma sends
over a $1200 bottle of scotch, you should drink it.
This worked out better than i thought it would. Cheers.
- Amen.
- You're drinking in the middle of the day?
They do it on "mad men" all the
time and they're pretty successful.
That was in the '60s.
By the time they get to
season four in the '70s,
- They'll all have liver and heart disease.
- Not us.
- This tandem is unstoppable.
- This new team is thriving.
- Glad to see somebody is.
- What, are you sulking, lloyd?
No! I'm steaming. Steaming mad because
i tried to talk with you earlier
And you essentially
ignored me.
- Are we not in a meeting?
- I don't know what you're in,
- But you're acting like you're in a bar.
- I don't like your tone, lloyd.
- Do you have any plan to promote me?
- Hadn't even thought about it.
- Well, you need to.
- Lloyd!
Ari, promote me
or i'm leaving you!
Leaving me?
- Where would you go?
- To another agency.
Another agency? You'd have
to start all over again.
- You know that.
- Then i'll go work for my father.
- What, in a dry-Cleaner's? -
My father has a winery in napa.
I don't think sodomy
is legal in napa, lloyd.
Every time i have broached
this subject over the years
You have responded
with some wiseass comment.
The time has come. I want to
know if this is going to happen.
I want to know when
and i want to know today!
I will not be
strong-Armed, lloyd.
You just were,
ari gold.
Tough queer.
Wow, this is amazing.
- I told you.
- And why is it so cheap?
Because my girlfriend is
moving to vancouver for a year
And she just wanted someone
she trusts to take care of it.
- Oh yeah? She trusts me?
- Well, she trusts me
- And i told her she can trust you.
- This her?
- Uh-Huh.
- Ugly.
- So what do you think?
- I don't know.
I really haven't been
looking around much.
Just trying to get an idea
what's out there, you know?
This isn't out there. This
is a fluke opportunity.
- I appreciate that.
- Okay. I won't push.
I know what a big deal it is for you
to be out on your own without the boys.
It's not a big deal.
- And you hate change.
- I don't hate change.
E, you moved back
into your old house.
That was vince's idea.
- Does he even know you're here?
- He knows i'm with you.
He thinks
we're having coffee.
You know, look, vince is doing
amazing. The house is great.
He signed a two-Year lease thinking
we were all going to live in it, so.
Well, thanks to you
he can afford it.
I sunk so much money into my business,
do i really need my own place?
At your age,
you kinda do.
If i was in a relationship...
Oh, e, we've talked
about this.
You're not going to be in a relationship
so long as you're living in a frat house.
We always do pick up right
where we left off, don't we?
- So how is dating life?
- What?
Oh, let's not get
weird about this.
You're dating, i'm dating,
we can talk about it.
Wow, you really are
keeping tabs on me, huh?
I'm really not. But i was
forced to hear about you
Stumbling out of fox hill
with a pretty young girl.
And i was forced to hear
about you making out
With a pretty old dude
at dan tana's.
Oh, who's keeping tabs?
And you know me-
- I don't make out in public.
- I don't want to talk about this anymore.
I do. Who's the girl?
- Girls-Ss. - Oh,
multiple girls! Wow, e.
It's so unlike you.
Maybe you are maturing.
Would you stop?
- I gotta go.
- What should i tell my friend?
- Tell her i'll think about it.
- Okay.
- See you later.
- Ciao.
Make a right here.
- And i need you to make a left here.
- All right.
- Very nice.
- Thanks, i've been working on that one.
I'm excited about your new film.
"Gatsby" is one of my favorites.
Oh, i hope i don't
ruin it for you.
Oh no, the trailer
looked great.
Love scorsese. Let's do a
three-Point turn right here.
Okay.
He's awful.
- Don't hit that! Oh! Look at that.
- How's he doing?
- Bro's bumming.
- You were supposed to get him ready.
I did
- For the written. Even i couldn't get him roadworthy.
He's gonna show up on set, he's
not gonna know how to drive.
Hey've got stunt doubles for that.
Making him get his license
is for insurance purposes.
He's playing enzo ferrari. He
needs to know how to drive a car.
- Oh!
- Oh my goodness.
So?
I'm finally
an independent.
- You passed?
- No way! Really?
Yes!
Thanks so much, scott. See you at the premiere?
- Plus one, right?
- You know it.
Shall we?
He passed you for premiere tickets?
Why, cheryl walters
let me go in the back door
- For "young guns 3-D" tickets.
- Oh, you're disgusting.
- Vince: so how's sloan?
- What do you mean?
- I mean how is she?
- Oh, she's good.
Was that
a weird question?
- No.
- 'Cause you sure answered it kinda weird.
- Did i?
- Yeah. Didn't he?
- Turtle: yeah.
- Kinda weird.
- You're getting back together with sloan...
- No.
- ... After once cup of coffee?
- You're back in love with sloan?
- No.
- One cup of coffee's all it takes for this guy!
- Look, it was a friendly meeting.
- Ahh!
- Vince: a meeting?
- Turtle: a meeting which she called for.
It's all the girls he's been
getting. Pussy can smell other pussy
And then they have
to pounce on it.
That's why when you're on a hot streak,
you've got to press it like blackjack.
Are you pressing it
with sloan?
I'm done with this conversation.
I'll see you guys at leno.
- I'm riding with e.
- I'm gonna roll with you.
No no no, forget that.
Come with me.
- My car is here.
- We'll get it later.
Can we drive
with the airbags deployed?
Back in the day you waited
until your boss told you
You are ready for a promotion.
You didn't threaten him.
I was on terrence's desk 50 months
before he finally promoted me.
- And you ever threaten him?
- The man's a psychopath. Of course i didn't.
Lloyd thinks we're friends.
I'm too nice to him.
That's why you can never
be nice to an assistant.
- The fuck i am.
- You think lloyd would make a good agent?
I don't know.
He's smart, but he's...
- He's soft and he's weak.
- But you love him as an assistant?
The best ever. I had 14 in
the three years before him.
- But an agent- I don't!
Make sure you know.
I got a few i didn't promote
Make it big off of my desk,
they still won't return my calls.
- You think lloyd wouldn't return my calls?
- I don't know.
- Ungrateful prick.
- Nice of you to show, ari.
Nice of you to drop the baby weight.
What, do you have like nine kids now?
- Three, asshole.
- Really? Did you figure
out who the fathers are?
Don't take it out on me because you don't
have an excuse for those extra pounds.
I'm still at 6% body fat.
And still 94% full of shit.
Vinnie ready to make
this comeback complete?
Wait wait wait!
No no no.
No, that sounds
like a disaster.
- I probably hit three cones.
- But no people?
No, no people.
Just cones.
- So not a complete disaster?
- A little disaster.
- The guy still passed you?
- Uh... yeah, but...
Keep it between us
- I bribed him with a couple premiere tickets.
Oh, come on!
No no, that's a great
trade for you.
Don't you understand? You
don't know how to drive!
Yeah, in fact if you see me,
i'd be cautious.
Now see? See, that's amazing.
Being a movie star,
you get out of all this.
The rest of us, we tv people, we
have to learn how to parallel park.
- Here here.
- That's why i took up the motorcycle.
It's small,
it's maneuverable.
Plus i can try my jokes out in
biker bars. They're a great crowd.
No, they are.
They're a great crowd.
Tell me if i understand this. So
you didn't get your license till...
How old are you anyway?
My mom couldn't afford
to get me a car growing up.
- Leno: so you were poor?
- Milk it, honey, milk it.
- We were rich in love.
- Rich in love!
True dat!
Aw - He's doing great.
- He always does.
You can afford a driver.
Why even bother to learn?
I usually have my boy turtle drive
me around, but i'm doing a new movie.
- Leno: and what's that?
- You can still drive me around.
It's the story of the
race-Car inventor enzo ferrari.
That might be a good movie
to learn how to drive for.
- I think so.
- I don't know anything about it.
I'm just throwing it out there.
Let's talk about your current movie,
Which i saw last night-
Scorsese's "gatsby."
- Boy, i just thought it was brilliant.
- We have our great director
- To thank for that-
Martin scorsese.
Sloan? She's all
over you, huh?
Pussy.
Hey, i can't really
talk right now.
Okay okay, real quick. I swear
i'm not putting pressure on you.
I just thought you should know my
girlfriend has someone else interested.
Look, i haven't really thought
about it or spoken to vince.
Oh, come on, e
-I don't
want you to miss out on this.
-No pressure, huh?
Just a little.
- She wants to meet you.
- Sloan, i can't rush like this.
Look, just come and meet her
So she can approve of you in
case you decide you want it later.
- Can i call you back in
a little bit? - Tick-Tock.
- Bye, sloan.
- Bye.
- Vince, congratulations.
- Thank you.
Vincent chase, everybody.
Be right back with...
Vinnie!
Ari: vinnie killed it!
He did indeed!
How about
we stop off to celebrate?
- Naw, i gotta go see the kids.
- Family man ari gold, huh?
- Come on.
Yeah?
What's going on
with lloyd?
- What do you mean, baby?
- He called me.
- He called you?
- Yes, and he sounded very upset.
He wanted to say how much he enjoyed
knowing me. What's wrong with him?
- He- Lloyd is dying, baby.
- What?!
- What's wrong with him, daddy?
- Nothing, buddy.
Baby, tell me when
i'm on speakerphone.
- Did you fire lloyd, ari?
- No-
- Daddy, no!
We love lloyd, daddy.
Oooh, ruthless.
He's gonna make it-
With or without you.
Does that make the comeback
complete or what?
No, when he's got an oscar,
then it's complete.
I'd just be happy
to avoid a razzie.
There's nothing wrong
with a razzie, bro.
Drama's gonna go for the hat trick
if he ever gets another movie.
I only have
one razzie, asshole!
- All right, i'll talk to you later.
- Who was that?
- Would you leave me alone?
- Never.
- Turtle: ever.
- Was it sloan again?
- Another broad?
- None of your business.
I'm making it my business. So
you better tell whoever that was
To invite a friend or i'm banging pots
and pans outside your door all night.
You don't live here, drama. Which begs
the question, why are you always here?
Because isolation's overrated. Besides,
Baby bro likes
having me here.
I like having
you all around.
I'll stay up and bang
pots and pans.
Don't you have dinner
with jamie tonight?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna tell her you asked me to find a friend.
Pffft!
I didn't.
Don't!
Please don't.
All right, enough with the harassing e,
What are the boys without
relationships doing tonight?
- I got a night shoot, bro.
- Yeah, and that was sloan.
We're gonna meet for
a drink. No big deal.
Ari gold's office.
Be at my house
at 10:00 p.M.
- Your house?
- Sit on the stoop,
Don't ring the bell,
Don't make any noise,
wait for me.
Till when?
Hello?
- Hey, looking sharp!
- Oh, thanks.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm just gonna hang out for a bit.
- Maybe go for a spin.
- You're drinking!
It's one beer.
All right,
don't drive, please.
Okay, thanks, ma. You know
what? If you're so concerned,
Why don't you take a break from the
dating pool and come hang out with me?
- It's not a date.
- Oh no, that's right.
Have fun at your "meeting."
Actually, vince, i didn't
have coffee with sloan today.
- No?
- No. A friend of hers
Has a great house
that she wants to sublet.
Why? Sloan's got a
great house, doesn't she?
Yeah, well, it wouldn't be for
her. She thought i might want it.
Oh-Ho! That's why you've been
acting like a freak all day.
- I haven't been acting like a freak all day.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you have. If you
want to get your own house,
- Go ahead, get it.
- You don't have an opinion about that at all?
What opinion
would i have?
Oh, come on, vince! You know
you don't like to be alone.
- I don't like to be alone?
- No!
How would you know?
You've never seen me alone.
Because you're always with me
because you can't be alone.
- Have you ever lived by yourself?
- Have you?
And the guest house
doesn't count.
Exactly!
Besides, i got turtle.
Rarely. I mean, he's usually at jamie's.
Do you want to get
your own place or what?
Well, yeah, i'd kinda like
to have a little privacy,
Not have the peanut gallery
commenting on everything that i do.
Maybe you want to impress sloan a
little bit with your independence?
- It's not about sloan.
- Maybe a little.
Come on. Get your
place, e. I'll be fine.
- Don't worry about me.
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
- All right, i'll see you later.
- See ya.
- You know what, actually-
Sloan's friend is really hot
if you want to roll with.
Yeah?
- I could do that.
- Yeah.
We'll want to take
two cars just in case.
- In case what? In case you close?
- No, just in case you close.
To little league, growing up
and moving out on his own.
- Thank you. Finally!
- Sloan: cheers.
Oaso, vince, are you going to blame me
when you're feeling all sad and lonely?
Why doesn't anybody think he'll be sad?
I'm really much more fun to be around.
All right, you know what?
I'm usually not this pathetic,
But since you took e,
i'm gonna have to take amy.
- Interesting.
- Oh really? I am moving away for a year,
And i'm not that interested in having
a one-Night fling with a movie star.
Ouch!
Wow.
I'm just getting rejected
by everyone tonight, huh?
That's one thing i missed
about not having a license-
I don't think
i've ever fucked in a car.
I'm glad i could be
your first ride.
You're a cruel man,
ari gold.
You asked me for an answer by day's end. I
don't have an answer; i have a proposition.
And if you don't like it, you
can wander off into the cold harsh
- Unforgiving world without me.
- What is it?
100 days.
You survive,
you'll have your promotion.
What is this, a hazing? This
is why i didn't join a frat.
- What frat would have you?
- Ari-
Lloyd!
100 days, you do
everything that i say,
- Or you don't.
- Fine.
You drop 15 lbs.
- You want me to drop 15 lbs?
- I'm asking that for tom.
What i want will be much harder. Now go.
I'm gonna make it
through this, ari gold.
It'll be worse than when you had your anal
cherry popped, but, hey, you just might.
It's true.
Oh, that was fun.
Thank you.
- You're not gonna invite me in?
- No.
- E, you're dating.
- So are you!
- Exactly.
Look, i thought the whole reason you
were pushing me into this place-G.
Don't flatter yourself.
Invite me in!
E, you have girls-Ss.
- That was a joke.
- It was a good one.
Good night, eric.
Good night, sloan.
Hope i don't get too lonely
up in that house.
Never lived alone
before.
I mean, i lived with my mom up until
i lived with vince and the guys-
- Oh, get a dog!
- Oh, so cold.
Okay.
One drink.
Nothing more.
I'm serious.
You didn't want to be vince's driver forever anyway, right?
No, of course i didn't.
It's just that vince is blowing up so fast
again
- I kinda got lost in what i'm doing.
- Oh, what are you doing?
I got a couple of ideas.
Wh are they?
No, not till
they're ready, baby.
- Oh, okay. Tell me.
- No. Nice try.
You know what? Just for that,
i'm peeing right in the tub.
Hey, johnny,
we're running behind.
Gonna be here all night.
Sorry.
Don't be!
This is what i live for.
Oh yeah, a little higher.
Right there,
right there.
Hello?
Turtle!
Hello, anyone home?