Drama: How do I know that
girl Vince is talkin' to?
- Turtle: That's Sasha grey.
- The porn star?!
Former colleague Lizzie Grant is trying
to take clients. Who's she working for?
Vince isn't gonna be the face of some
Tequila company. He's not aunt Jemima.
- I read a script this morning.
I want to do it. - Okay.
- Stamos sent it to me.
- Jesus.
This is awkward. I happened to see
your search history on the computer.
Can we talk about this tonight?
I might be hiding
from you tonight.
I want Saget.
I wish I could've done more.
- What's up, Vince? - This Tequila's special.
I want to involved.
- This is Sasha. - This is the man,
the myth, the legend... Stan Lee.
- Oh, you look familiar.
- How'd the meeting go?
Not great. Vince brought Sasha
and apparently he was drunk.
- Good evening, Ari.
- Ari: Please don't tell me
you're the one who
picked up the stray Lizzie.
Anyone she wants,
I'm going after.
Well, she's going
after you too, Ari.
I'm going to make your life
miserable like you once made mine.
Good night, Ari.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
♪ oooh! ♪
♪ yeah yeah! ♪
♪ yeah yeah ♪
♪ yeah, my mind
had been enabled ♪
♪ in the memory
you overflow ♪
♪ I wanna be
your superhero ♪
♪ even if I
tumble, fall ♪
♪ I'm okay ♪
♪ but I need you
desperately ♪
♪ you know I need you
♪ I wanna be
your superhero ♪
♪ yeah, oh yeah ♪
♪ oh yeah. ♪
Turtle: Tell us, Vince,
what are we doing here?
We're having our own private launch
party for our new Tequila company.
Name, Vin.
Give 'em the name.
Uh, Tequila Avion.
- ( With accent ) Avion.
- Avion.
- Huh-uh, Avion.
- Avion!
And who is this?
This is my friend Sasha.
Aren't we more
than friends by now?
Oh no no, we are.
We're very good friends.
- And this is my friend.
- Alex.
Notice how she didn't say
we're more than friends?
You don't make a move soon,
Turtle, I'm gonna have to.
- What, am I not here?
- I'm just saying.
He's made moves.
We're just taking it slow.
Real slow.
Like the 405 at rush hour. Ow.
Well, Alex, all I know is I've
had a lot of sex in my life
and the best sex I've ever
had was while drinking this.
Can we quote international star
of stage and screen
Sasha grey on that?
I'm not shy. Drink this and you'll
have the best sex of your life.
Guys can fuck like me and girls
can fuck like a porn star.
- ( Laughs )
- Come on, Vince.
That was awesome.
Oh my God.
( Shrieks )
So what is the deal?
Are you two gonna bang or what?
Jesus, Drama.
I thought you were dead.
No, I'm just unemployed,
sad and lonely.
Don't worry, I'm saving a piece of
my piece of this company for you.
That makes me feel much better.
Say something on camera about it.
You're a pseudo-celeb.
I don't drink Tequila.
I drink Johnny blue
'cause I'm not
a pseudo-man like you.
- All right, you're out.
- I am out.
Doesn't drink Tequila.
Huh, what a loser.
What?
I was gonna kiss you.
- You've already kissed me.
- Fine, then I won't.
Why? Why do you like
teasing me so much?
I told you, I'm not that easy.
No, you're like breaking
into fort knox.
Then I guess you'd
better keep trying.
- ( Cheering )
- Yay, Turtle.
Okay, so what are we
looking at here?
Well, sexual harassment maybe.
Wrongful termination possibly.
I didn't terminate her.
She quit.
She felt that she was overlooked
for a promotion she deserved.
I would have given it to her.
Whose side are you on?
I didn't do anything wrong here.
Obviously Amanda Daniels
disagrees.
Why would she be willing to spend
her money supporting Lizzie?
- To get back at me.
- For what?
He stopped her from getting a job
she wanted once upon a time also.
There is no case here.
You say Lizzie's written
down things you've said?
- Yes, in a journal.
- Yeah, made-up words obviously.
- Obviously. - Look, it's her
word against mine, right?
They'll subpoena everyone in this office.
What might they say?
What do you think
they might say?
He told me I'd look good with a
ball gag in my mouth last week.
- Ari.
- Lloyd!
- Yes?
- What would you say
about my treatment of you
over the last five years?
- Treatment?
- This is Jim Lefkowitz, Lloyd.
- Our attorney.
- Attorney?
- What's going on?
- The lovely Lizzie Grant may sue me.
And you, Lloyd, and everyone
who works here may be asked
to describe how Ari treats his employees.
So what would you say?
Ari has always been gracious
and lovely, fair and reasonable.
This has been a dreamlike job
from minute one.
And would you say that
if you were under oath,
facing a perjury charge
and possible jail time?
Oh God, I can't do time, Ari.
I don't think anybody in my family could.
- I'm sorry.
- Go!
So do you think others
would speak better of him?
Worse is my guess.
What do you suggest?
Well, I mean, you're trying to bring an N.
F.L. team to Los Angeles.
- So? - So the N.F.L.
doesn't like controversy.
This goes to trial, win or lose, that's over.
You know that.
And your wife and kids
won't like it either.
I haven't done anything wrong.
- Jim, what do you suggest?
- I suggest you offer Ms. Grant
a generous amount of money
to not pursue legal action.
I already offered her
a generous severance package.
I'm offering her nothing else.
I'll call her new boss
and convince her
not to waste her time
or her money on this thing.
Just make sure she doesn't
write down everything you say.
- She's right.
- Jake!
Get Amanda Daniels
on the phone.
- Morning, E.
- Morning.
Late night?
You look tired.
I was up till 10:00
tasting wedding cakes.
I'm not tired, I'm nauseous.
- Any sign of an offer for Vince?
- Mm-hmm.
- How is it?
- Oh, I didn't look.
Okay, it's incredible.
- Wow. Scott!
- Oh, and a Billy Walsh called.
- Oh, come on.
- Yeah, why, who is he?
He was supposed to be a big director for a minute.
Never heard of him?
- Shall I call him back?
- No, but call Ari.
Tell him I want to talk to
him about this. Thank you.
Yes, Murray, I know.
Eric's here, he says hello.
- Hi, Murray.
- He says hi, yeah.
Okay, I love you. I really do.
Have a good trip.
- Have fun. Okay, bye. I hate myself.
- What's the problem?
- He wants me to babysit his house.
- He's got a nice house.
He also has two pugs that do
nothing but snore and shit.
- Don't worry about that.
Look at this. - What is it?
Vince's offer
for "air-walker."
- Back end?
- Huge, and 12 upfront.
- Holy shit!
- ( Laughs )
I have Billy Walsh again.
Tell him I'm out of town
or something like that.
- Did you call Ari?
- I left word with his assistant.
Call him back, tell him
we're heading down there.
- We are?
- Yes. You can be
my eyewitness that he had
absolutely nothing to do with this.
I can do that.
- ( Roaring )
- ( People screaming )
Johnny, you've got
to stop drinking.
- Why? - 'Cause you've been
going for 16 straight hours.
- So have you.
- Yeah, but I'm happy drinking.
I'm gonna keep doing it
until I get a job.
Maybe you should do a play.
I'd love to, bro,
but I can't afford it.
My mortgage rate's
ready to reset.
Whatever movie I do next I'm making
sure there's a role in it for you.
- Vince... - And I got your
mortgage until you find a job.
And that will be
pretty soon I'm sure.
How do you know, bro?
I was on a series six months ago.
I haven't had an offer since.
Correction...
dos equis asked me to be the least
interesting man in the world.
Johnny, this town is
up and down, up and down.
You know that.
I mean, look at me.
I was done, but I came back.
- And you will too.
- I hope so, bro.
But for now, let me
wallow in my misery.
Stop wallowing with my Tequila.
- I'm gonna run out of samples. - Boo.
What, are you in a bad mood too?
- No, why?
- You look sad.
I guess he couldn't close Alex.
It was looking
pretty good to me.
I closed.
- Great, so how was it?
- For me or for her?
We know it couldn't have been any good
for her, so let's hear about you.
But first, have a drink.
- It's 10:00 A.M.
- Suit yourself.
Top me off, bro.
So what happened?
I really don't want
to talk about this.
Lighten up, Turtle.
If it's any consolation,
this moonshine of yours
is starting to grow on me.
- Great.
- Come on, tell us what happened.
( Sighs ) I closed.
I did.
I just didn't close well.
What, did you pop off early?
It's been a long time for you.
Yeah, Turtle,
that's no big deal.
No, it wasn't that.
It just didn't start out so good
and then I couldn't
find my groove.
What, you didn't eat it right?
- Disaster.
- I'm sure you're just imagining it.
No, I'm not. And the truth is I've
been imagining it for a month.
She is so hot and then finally
I was all ready and I made
my way down there and...
- What?
- Nothing.
- Something.
- You guys are gonna laugh at me.
- No we won't.
- No no no.
Okay, I made my way down
there just as the sun came up.
The harsh light hit it directly
and it was completely
bald and I freaked.
- ( Laughing )
- Yeah, see?
I'm sorry.
Why did you freak?
Seriously, Turtle.
I love that.
It's like you peel back the curtains
to reveal the mystery of oz.
I don't have a problem with it.
It's just that close up
with the sun, it shocked me.
What, you saw
a shaved box before?
I have in porn.
Just not in 3d.
I've been with girls who were
nicely groomed... landing strip.
The landing strip went out
in the mid 90s, bro.
It's the truth.
Everyone goes smooth nowadays.
- Even you, I bet.
- Smooth balls for sure.
And I hope you do
yours as well.
- I don't groom my dick, no.
- Are you kidding?
It's 2010;
You'd better.
- Do people really do this, Vin?
- I only know about my own dick.
And, Turtle, you should
only worry about yours.
But listen, you haven't been
with many chicks since Jamie.
Many meaning zero.
And you were nervous.
So I'm sure you did fine.
No, I didn't.
I need another shot.
- Well, I am sure you will get one.
- I hope.
Well, if you do, you'd better do
a little courtesy manscaping.
Can't have your dick
looking like a chia pet, bro.
( Laughs )
Can I just get a little support?
At least tell me I'm not crazy.
No, you're not crazy.
Murray's hard on you.
People get into patterns
in work relationships.
Sometimes it's hard to get out of them.
You'll see with Ari and I.
- Why? How's that go?
- Well, he's a dick.
- Better not be a dick to me.
- Take it easy.
Would it be so bad if I gave Ari gold
a smack in front of all his peers?
Hey, Eric, and...
- Scott.
I told your office now is not a good time.
Ari is not in a great mood.
- Has that whore called me back yet?
- Told you.
No, not yet.
- I'm gonna cheer him up, Jake.
- No, Eric, wait.
- Uh, Ari...
- Hey, Ari.
What is this, the Big Brother
program of America?
- Except who's the Big Brother?
- This is Scott Lavin.
- So? - I called you last
week twice about Vince.
What are you two doing in my office when
you don't have a meeting on the books?
- Is he kidding?
- We're here for Vince.
Vince.
You remember Vince?
He doesn't play in the N.F.L.
but he still makes a good amount of money.
Who the fuck are you and why am I
wasting my time listening to you?
E, I got a lot on my plate.
Speak fast.
We got a big offer for Vince.
Could be worth $100 million
over three movies.
- Look, now he's paying attention.
- Scott.
- Randall Wallace?
- Scott: And Stan Lee.
- Why don't I know about this?
- 'Cause you don't call anybody back.
- I'll call Vince myself.
- Don't do that.
Truth is we got this done without you but
we obviously care about your opinion.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
The truth is I've been a little under it lately.
- E: N.F.L.?
- Personal stuff.
Oh wow.
Everything okay with the family?
- Yeah, thanks.
- Amanda Daniels.
- I've got to take this.
- She's on her way up.
- She's on her way up?
- Uh-huh.
- What are you doing with Amanda?
- Nothing.
You hitting that?
Look, you guys got to go.
This is really important.
I will call you as soon as I
go over this very thoroughly.
- He is hitting that.
- Listen, e, I'll call you in an hour.
Make sure that your dopplegang-banger
stays off the line. Go!
- Hello, Amanda.
- Hello, Eric.
- Get the fuck out. - Don't ever
touch me again, you fucking jerkoff.
What are you
doing here, Amanda?
You called and I thought you
might threaten me to my face.
- No one wants to threaten you, okay?
- Then what do you want?
I just simply want to know
if you really want to burn
every last dollar that you have
trying to slander my name.
- Slander?
- Mm-hmm.
No, I read Lizzie's journals.
There's some pretty horrific
stuff in there, even for you.
- Why are you doing this? - Because once
upon a time you walked into my office
and you took a job away from me that
I deserved simply because you could.
- So it's about payback?
- No no, this is like arms control.
See, you're like Iran and I need to take
away your weapons because you're reckless.
You're smart enough to know
it's only a matter of time
before I scoop up one of your
castoffs and sue you right back.
( Laughs ) Unlike you,
I had the foresight
to work Lizzie for a while.
So I have proof,
you'd only have hearsay.
Lizzie's little work-of-fiction
journal proves that I'm guilty
like Lindsay "blow-han" proves
that fame is fucking healthy.
( Laughs )
She has recordings of you too.
- Your voice.
- Bullshit.
Oh, it's true.
The tapes are so clear
it sounds like they were
professionally recorded.
- You heard them?
- I listened to them, yeah,
the last three nights and played
with myself while fantasizing
about fucking you in the ass.
Anything else you wanted to say?
I freed up my afternoon.
You follow through on this
and you're starting a war.
Then man up, Ari,
because I love to battle.
( Laughs )
It's funny, you know.
This was actually less
hostile than I expected.
So Vince has been tweeting
the shit out of the Tequila.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
- Said he started a new company.
- That's great.
I was thinking of
posting some of the videos.
- The cool ones, not the silly ones.
- Yeah.
Totally.
How's your sandwich?
Good.
Cool.
Better than last night.
- What?
- I'm kidding.
- No you weren't.
- Come on, it was awkward.
- You think? - I think maybe
we just did it too soon.
Or maybe we shouldn't
have done it at all.
No no no, of course
we should have done it.
It was my fault.
It was me.
- I take full responsibility.
- For what?
- For the awkwardness.
- What happened?
We were having a great time and then
the second the clothes came off
you turned into a clumsy mute.
I wasn't feeling great.
I don't know, Turtle.
Maybe we're just not meant to be like that.
I mean, Sasha said she had the best
sex of her life on our Tequila.
I thought it was the worst.
It wasn't the worst.
Okay, you've got to give
me another shot.
Maybe we're just meant
to be business partners.
No no no, come on.
I will wine you and dine you
and woo you and I will
blow your mind in bed.
You think?
Let me try.
Okay.
You can try.
Excuse me.
Can I have some ketchup, please?
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hi, I'm William Walsh.
I'm an old friend of Vince's.
I'm Sasha,
a new friend of Vince's.
Billy Walsh.
Oh my God.
Vince, how are you?
It's been awhile.
I'll say. Come here.
How are you?
- I'm okay.
- Hey, sash, this is Billy Walsh,
- an amazing filmmaker.
- That's kind of you to say.
I thought you looked
familiar, but different.
I've been through
a lot and back again.
- Can I come in?
- Of course, of course.
Hey, Johnny, look who's here.
Jeez, Billy Walsh.
It's like a mirage.
- How are you, Drama?
- Peachy, Billy.
I'm getting jerked off
by the network
'cause nobody can find
a idea for me.
You got one?
Not off the top of my head, no.
Superb.
You seem angry, Drama.
I've always been, Billy.
Only now I'm drunk too.
- I shot a movie with you.
- Yeah, uh...
You know, maybe this wasn't
the best place for me to come.
Porn stars, alcohol,
manic depressives...
I've avoided all temptation
for the last 24 months now.
So what are you
doing here, Billy?
I came to get back into
the business I left behind.
Vince isn't gonna make another stinker with
you, Billy, if that's what you're thinking.
- No, Vince isn't what I need at this point.
- So what do you need?
E.
Vince needs to get rid of Ari.
- Enough already.
- I'm being serious.
I mean, the guy is barely
even in the business anymore.
What do you think is gonna happen when
he's standing on an N.F.L. sideline
spending all his time
trying to bang cheerleaders?
Look, Ari's got a big mouth
but he's done a lot by us.
And he's obviously got
some serious stuff going on.
So does Vince and he needs someone
who's gonna be on the ball.
Are you telling me
you can't handle an offer?
You can't make sure he's paid?
Make sure he has a nice trailer?
Ari and Vince's attorneys
handle the little details.
We can take it to his attorney.
We can handle the details.
If Ari's so stressed out maybe he'd
appreciate you taking the reins on this one.
Come on, aren't you tired
of being a pushover?
- Who's a pushover?
- We both are.
We handled
this thing for Vince.
We're basically the ones
keeping this company afloat.
- So now you're back to Murray?
- Of course I'm back to Murray.
We do all the work.
I mean, the guy is literally never here.
- I wouldn't say never.
- You wouldn't say never?
Murray!
Hey, Murray!
- Anyone seen Murray, ever?
- Are you on drugs?
No, I'm fucking angry,
as you should be too.
- About what, Murray or Ari?
- About both of them.
They are checking out, okay?
We cannot.
This is our future, all right?
You saw how we handled
this deal with Vince.
You saw how we handled Ari.
We can run Vince and this company
without either one of them.
You do realize that I'm marrying
Murray's god-daughter, right?
- The one who got me this job.
- Family before business, I get it.
But you and Sloan are about to start
your own family so you need to start...
- shauna's on the phone and she's
freaking out. - Who isn't?
She says that Vince tweeted that
he started some Tequila company
and Turtle posted some
racy videos about it.
Awesome.
No, I did not know that Vince
was dating a porn star, shauna.
No, I didn't know he started
his own tequila company either.
I have to go.
Lizzie Grant.
I didn't know that you ate here.
Well, I know you don't eat here
'cause you don't like,
and I'm quoting,
"eating with all
the pussy-ass bitch agents."
You know what?
I have grown to love my own kind.
- Are you following me?
- You can't prove it.
You would be amazed
at what I could prove.
- I talked to your boss.
- I'm aware.
Yeah, she may use nicer words but
she's a much worse person than me.
Anyone in this town
could tell you that.
That is so funny
because she swears
you're the worst person
she's ever dealt with.
- Stealing clients...
- Have you ever seen me steal clients?
Ari, I have no interest
in talking to you.
Well, I have an interest
in you not sullying my name.
So tell me what you want.
- What I want?
- Yes.
How much money to settle
so we don't end up in court
where you will lose?
A writer's assistant on a sitcom
once sued for inappropriate talk.
It went to the supreme court.
You know what they told her?
They told her that the writers
can talk about gang-banging her
all day long as long
as they don't do it.
I know the case.
They're creative.
You're certainly not.
So you can talk about gang-banging all day,
but you're the only one
who's gonna get fucked.
- 100,000.
- No.
- 250.
- How about 10 million?
- Don't be absurd.
- You think I'm being absurd?
I think that you're
whoring yourself out
to a witch of a woman
who is trying to get you
- to slander a good family man's name.
- ( Laughs )
$1 million not to sue.
Ari, I cannot tell you
how good it makes me feel
to watch you squirm.
But you can rest easy, 'cause
I've already told Amanda
that I'm not gonna sue you.
So keep your money.
- You're not?
- No.
I will make my money because
I'm smart and I'm talented,
not because you're repugnant.
I think you're doing
the right thing,
because no one needs
to hear about our past.
No, that's where you're wrong.
Everyone needs to hear.
I want the women of the world
to know how you treat them.
What does that mean?
Check "deadline Hollywood."
I'm sure the story should
be posted sometime soon,
unless you can buy them off.
You sent tapes of me
to "deadline Hollywood"?
Is that even legal?
Sue me.
( Grunts )
I thought you wanted
to conserve your product.
- I want to relax.
- You freaking about tonight?
I'm not freaking,
I'm just on edge a little.
Let me tell you, shoving that poison
down your throat is not the remedy.
Poison?
This is 100% pure agave.
The only remedy for you is
storming the hairless beaches.
You're gonna be fine, Turtle.
I don't normally have
performance issues.
Yeah, you perform
as often as led zeppelin.
You should probably take a cab.
Or I can drive you.
You should take a cab.
I like you two as my parents.
- Hey, Vin, where's the can?
- To the left.
Yo, Turtle, you want a Cialis?
No.
Maybe.
Hi, I need a cab
for 3750 longo.
Johnny, why do you
carry around Cialis?
In case I really
got to bury one.
- You should use kaboom.
You get a bigger bang. - Good tip.
E, to what do we owe
this pleasure?
Turtle posted a video
of you and Sasha on Twitter.
I just got
reamed out by shauna.
That was unintentional.
I edited smaller parts.
- I just accidentally uploaded the whole thing.
- I thought it was cute.
A movie star telling guys
to fuck like him
and girls to fuck like
a porn star isn't cute, Vince.
- I said that?
- Yes.
- You did. - I'm sure the way
I said it was very charming.
Turtle, what happened? I thought the Tequila
company was gonna be on the down low.
No, it only went out
to my Twitter followers.
- You have a million and a
half followers. - I do?
Yeah, now t.M.Z.,
Perez Hilton
and just Jared all want to know
if Sasha's your girlfriend.
Well, tell them she is.
I thought we were
just really good friends.
Look, Vince, you just got the biggest
offer of your career today, all right?
- I just want to make sure you're focused.
- I'm focused.
- I'm focused. Aren't I focused?
- Seems focused to me.
You see? So how was the offer?
Was it good?
Yeah, it's great.
Ari's looking it over right now.
All right.
Well, things are happening.
No kidding. Check out this b.
B.M. I got today.
E, I've tried you several
times at the office.
I would love it if you could see yourself
giving me five minutes of your time.
- Technology is amazing.
- What's amazing
is that somebody gave this clown my b.
B.M. Address.
Hey, suit.
Long time.
( Growls )
Do you want Jerry Jones?
And you still haven't
called back Jeff Katzenberg
or Mike Meldman
or Tracy Morgan.
I don't want to talk to anybody.
Was I not clear?
Nobody! I don't care if
Justin Bieber calls
and wants me to negotiate
the rights to his virginity.
I don't want to talk to him.
Nobody!
Uh, your wife is here.
- Hello, Mrs. gold.
Ari doesn't wish to speak... - Hello.
- Get the fuck out of the way.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- You shouldn't talk to your assistants like that.
- I know, I'm sorry.
- What are you doing here?
- I told you I was coming by with the swatches
so that we could
redo your office.
- Oh.
- You forgot.
- No, I... - Okay, what do
you think of this one?
- Like it.
- You didn't even look.
No no, I glanced.
Baby, I got quick eyeballs.
U know that.
And I trust your taste.
You have amazing taste.
- And I love that.
- I'd like you to be involved.
- Why? - It would give us something
that we could do together.
Something we could do...
we do everything together.
- No, not anymore we don't.
- What do you mean?
- Since the merger.
- What since the merger?
- I don't feel good.
- Why?
Because you're never home.
Now with this N.F.L. thing...
- that may not happen.
- Why not?
- It may not happen.
- Why not? What's happening?
Nothing.
I feel like you've been keeping
a lot of secrets lately.
Honey, no. Listen,
let's go to an early dinner,
just the two of us.
We'll talk about everything. All right?
I'm sorry, Ari. Dana Gordon's on the line.
Says it's urgent about Vince.
I'll call you in an hour,
take you to Madeo.
- Just you and me, okay?
- Okay.
- Put her through.
- ( Phone rings )
Dana, is this really important?
If Vince is really gonna carry this
studio's next franchise, I'd say it is.
- ( Moans )
- Does that feel good?
Amazing.
- I told you I could do this.
- Yeah you can.
- You're incredible.
- Shh.
Sorry if I caused you
any stress.
It's okay.
I just thought
it was your first time.
First time what?
You know, having sex.
Are you serious?
- It's okay if it was.
- I'm 30.
I'm just saying.
You really think
I'm some ugly loser, huh?
- I didn't say that.
- No, but the first time I tried to kiss you
you looked at me like I was a
venereal disease. I'm cute.
You are, Turtle,
and I didn't see it at first.
- But I see it now.
- Good.
But something was up
last night.
- Just let it go.
- Was it me?
No no, are you crazy?
- Just tell me what it was.
- I'm immature.
What do you mean?
I've never been
with a girl before
who was totally shaved
down there.
- It freaked me out.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- You are immature.
I know. I had dreams all
night about playing pac-man.
- Pac-man?
- You know, pac-man.
Oh my God.
Is that why you shaved too?
Yeah, why?
You don't like it?
( Laughs ) No, I don't like it.
Guys are supposed to trim,
not go totally bald.
Thanks, Drama. So did I totally
just fuck this up again?
No, it'll grow back.
I really appreciate you taking
the time to meet with me.
I didn't have
much choice, Billy.
We all have choices
and I've made some bad ones.
Yeah. What can I do
for you, Billy?
I need you to help guide me out
of the toilet like you did Vince.
- Why would you want me? - Because, man,
you were the first guy to believe in me.
You found my first script,
you got me Vince,
you got us the money.
And as much as I was hard on you,
I always knew you were
the guy with the good eye.
- We can't work together, Billy.
- Why not?
Because there's too much
baggage and past.
- Pretend we've never met.
- How could I do that?
Well, essentially we haven't.
I don't drink anymore.
- I don't do drugs. I don't curse.
- You don't curse?
No, I've spent
the last three years
becoming an ordained
minister in Santa fe.
Got myself right
and I want to work.
You want Vince?
I want you to help me.
I'll do anything...
commercials, tv, anything.
I've changed.
Still got that Pablo Escobar
tattoo on your back?
No, I had it scraped off
with a bowie knife
in a ritual
smokehouse ceremony.
No, it's still there.
Some things haven't changed.
- But I've got a family now.
- Oh, you have a kid?
- I've got four.
- Four?
Set of Irish twins,
set of actual twins
and another one on the way.
I thought we could
live on love,
but tiny kids can't eat love.
( Sighs ) Look, Billy, I'm gonna
have to think about this.
You know, Drama was telling me about
this network deal that he's got.
Yeah, if you have any ideas, don't
be afraid to shoot them my way.
Actually, I was already thinking
like maybe he's not having any luck
because he's too ugly
to star in his own show.
- Yeah, you've changed, Billy.
- Come on, don't be mad. I'm serious.
Look, he doesn't have the face for
the screen but he's got the voice.
- So what, you think he should do radio?
- No, I was thinking a cartoon.
- Cartoon? - Yeah, like
"the simpsons" but angrier.
E, Ari's here
and he's being a douche.
You hear that voice?
How distinct and angry it is?
Were you talking about me?
- What's Ari want, Drama?
- He wants to talk to you.
- I got a lot of ideas.
- Sit tight, Billy.
Jesus, Billy, you're back and
apparently working at the gap.
- Hey, Ari.
- He needs representation, Ari.
- So does Vince. - Yes, he does.
Did you decide to start doing your job again?
I close my eyes for one minute
and he's dating porn stars
- and starting a Tequila company?
- Look, Ari...
you look. I need to talk to him.
My wife's in the car.
She's ready to shoot me
so I've got to talk fast.
- I already spoke to shauna.
- Well, I talked to Dana
and the director
and they're freaking out.
How could you let this guy show up drunk
and with a porn star to a meeting?
He took a Vicodin, Ari.
And I didn't let him.
- How is he doing now?
- He's fine.
The studio wants to sit down with
him to make sure that he is.
Jesus.
Look, is this thing real, the
relationship with the porn star?
- What? No.
- You sure?
Ari, Vince is fine.
- Where is he? I want to talk to him.
- He's out by the pool.
- Oh, hey, guys.
- Jesus.
Vince, wake up.
You have more visitors.
- Wake up.
- Yeah, he looks fine.
Vinnie.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
♪ we get ever so hot ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ whether we
like it or not ♪
♪ they say we can love
who we trust ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ but what is love
without lust? ♪