Previously on Swingtown
This works, you know--
you and me.
You're a really good teacher,
you know that?
Only for one more week.
Then what?
It's nice having
spontaneous nights like this.
I don't want to lose that.
Tom's starting
a new job.
Flyin to Tokyo
next week.
Are you worried?
You don't do well alone, Tom.
I'm not that guy anymore.
What do you think?
Who is that?
Harry Reems.
You're throwing a fund-raiser
for an actor in a porno film?
It's terrible what's
happening to this man.
You don't want to go to a party
like that without me.
I saw Deep Throat last night.
Why are you telling me this?
I didn't come to support pornography.
I just want to make that perfectly clear.
Harry Reems.
What is going on
with you, Susan?
Get your things.
We're going home.
No, I'm not.
I don't know what's going on
in the world.
It-It's not about you.
It... It's not about us.
It's... It's about me.
??? of Flight 274 from Bombay.
Flight 274 from Bombay.
I love our little airport game.
Okay, your turn.
Mm.
Standby passenger Ford Watkins
at Q Gate 34...
Yeah.
Redhead, 10:00.
Well...
I wouldn't kick
her out of bed,
but I always secretly preferred
Mary Ann to Ginger.
Hmm.
You got ten seconds.
- Nine, eight...
- Hold on.
seven...
Hello! Hitchcock blonde
in the white dress.
You got me.
So much for
Mary Ann.
Oh!
- You!
- For you.
- How nice.
- Mm-hmm.
Did you have
a good day at work?
- Yeah, the market rallied a bit.
- Mm.
Looks like we can keep
the house for another week.
Oh, good. See, it is gonna take
me at least that long
to choose a new wallpaper
for the living room.
What's the big deal?
Just pick one.
I don't want to
make some hideous mistake
we're gonna have to stare at
the rest of our lives.
So, I still got half an hour
to kill before my flight.
Double or nothing?
- You're on.
- Okay.
Start the clock.
How about climbing the stairway
to heaven with Robert Plant?
I'm way past my
hippie phase, dear.
And you are a stickler
for personal hygiene.
Ah, Silver Fox?
Oh, he's a dead ringer
for my Uncle Barry.
- Huh.
- Mm.
Tough room.
Five seconds.
Four, three...
Bingo.
Check him out.
Oh, my God.
Luke!?
Trina?
I can't believe it.
Hi.
Hi. Oh, my God.
Look at you...
Susan, I've been thinking about
what you said the other night,
about wanting to get more involved
in the world,expanding your horizons.
Yeah.
Don't look so surprised.
I think I have
just the thing.
The Children's Hospital
Ladies Auxiliary.
The what?
My boss's wife runs it--
Rita Pierce.
Pulled a few strings, got you
on the planning committee
for their annual benefit
this weekend.
Bruce, that's sweet...
kind of.
They meet tomorrow at the
Lake Crest Country Club.
Oh, I can't.
BJ's scout camp starts tomorrow,
and once we drop the boys
at the bus,
Janet and I have our traditional
lunch downtown at the Berghoff.
So bring Janet along.
Okay, here's the thing.
All the company wives'll
be there, pitching in.
All the wives?
Is this about expanding my horizons or
about making you look good to the boss?
- Two birds, one stone.
- Right.
You'll be doing me a big favor.
What do you say?
Please?
High school sweethearts.
- How about that?
- All four years.
On and off.
Not if it had
been up to me.
Back then, Trina wasn't
much of a one-man woman.
Guess that's
changed, though.
You're a lucky guy,
Tom.
That I am.
So, what brings you
to the Windy City?
Business.Running
my dad's company.
Can you believe it?
The same father who threatened to send
you to military school twice a week?
Same one.
Luke's family pretty much owns
the Manhattan skyline.
Maybe half.
Man, it is good
to see you.
You know, I'll be at the Drake
through the weekend.
You think you got time
to grab a bite?
How about tomorrow?
You can keep me company
while Tom's away.
We're cutting it
awful close, Captain.
About 15 minutes
to push back.
Thank you, Bobbi.
- You seeing your husband off, Trina?
- Mm-hmm.
You're so sweet.
Well, I better get going.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Take good care of my wife
while I'm gone.
Will do.
Safe trip.
- I'll miss you.
- You better.
I can't
believe...
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync:FRM@Dwight
Swingtown Season1
Episode04
Hello.
Hey, babe.
You're out of breath.
And dripping wet.
Oh. Really?
I just got out
of the pool, dear.
How was your flight?
We caught a headwind,
so we were a little late.
Just catching some shuteye
before we head back.
Well, hurry home.
I miss you.
Thought you had Luke there
to keep you company.
Not till tonight.
He's coming over later
for drinks.
- Why? You jealous?
- Should I be?
Please.
So...
tell me...
just how wet are you?
You all packed for camp?
Yup.
Can I go outside now?
Pens and stationery?
There's some in the kitchen.
Put them in your bag.
What for?
Two weeks is
a long time.
I expect you to write
to me this year.
It's camp,not school.
Don't argue with
your mother, BJ.
You know, means a lot to me,
you agreeing to do this today.
You didn't give me a
whole lot of choice.
But now that you are advising me
how to spend my days,
do you mind telling me what
I should wear to this thing?
I wouldn't want to clash with
the other company wives.
The pink definitely.
You know I've never been much
for group activities.
Didn't seem that way
at the Deckers.
The Harry Reems fund-raiser.
That is hardly the same thing.
You're right.Not all charity events
can benefit porn stars.
Somebody's got to help
the poor, sick children.
- Hello?
- Hi.
Hi, Janet.
Susan, did you rember
packing itch cream for BJ?
Ricky came home covered
in poison ivy last year.
I always say, "You can never
travel with too many ointments."
Right.
Janet,are you sure you don't mind
going with me to this thing today?
Susan, I told you
last night.
Berghoff's will
always be there.
A chance to work with Rita Pierce--
it's a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
I'll see you
in an hour.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
Once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity?
Susan got invited to the Children's
Hospital Ladies Auxiliary luncheon.
Guess who she's
bringing as her guest?
Charo?
Roger, this is a major
philanthropic organization.
It's very
exclusive.
These women are terribly proper.
Well, then
you should fit right in.
In this outfit?
I don't know.
Ricky, get down here.
We have less than an hour
to get you on that bus.
Tell you what?
Why don't you...
go buy yourself
something nice to wear?
Not that I think
you need it, of course.
Thank you
You have a
wonderful day.
Wonderful?
12 years of selling insurance,and I
haven't had a day full of wonder yet.
Ricky!
All summer, we've studied
the great thinkers.
Now it's time for you to think for
yourselves and speak for yourselves,
so no bluebooks
tomorrow.
Your final exam will be oral.
Be prepared to discuss the notions
of authenticity and self-expression...
drawing from all the philosophers we've
been studying,and most importantly,
from examples in your own lives.
Thank you.
Yes, Laurie?
Authenticity
and self-expression?
Uh-huh.
Using examples
from our own life.
That's the assignment.
In front of the entire class.
Right.
Interesting.
Mm, and don't forget:
each of you is expected to bring
at least two likely donors
to the benefit
tomorrow night.
That must be Bruce's
boss' wife.
Rita Pierce.
Her picture's always in
the Tribune party pages.
I'm sorry about
the Berghoff.
- I owe you lunch.
- Forget it.
But in the meantime, I want to
thank you ladies for your hard work
on behalf of all the sick
children who will benefit
from our efforts
tomorrow night.
Go ahead. Give yourselves
a little round of applause.
Oh.
Fabulous. Oh!
Brand-new suit,ruined.
Nobody touch
the jacket.
Give it to me.
Do I know you?
Janet Thompson.
I'm-I'm here with Susan Miller.
M- my husband works
for your husband.
Give me some Sweet 'N Lows,
much as you can find.
- Hurry!
- Yes, madam.
And once it's dry,
and the stain is absorbed,
you simply brush off
the whole mess, like so, and...
- ...voila!
- Oh!
Good as new.
Janet,you are a miracle worker.
Ladies, can
you stand it?
Janet, I insist-- you must come
to the benefit tomorrow night
as my guest.
It-It would
be my honor.
Rita, I was wondering
about the children.
When you volunteer
at the hospital,
what is it exactly
that you do?
Well,our efforts with
the Ladies Auxiliary
are mainly devoted
to fundraising.
So you don't work
with the children at all?
Oh, we're not
doctors, dear.
Although this one's a bit of
a mad scientist, isn't she?
Well, now, where's our waiter?
We need to order lunch
and get back to work.
Bruce.
I wanted to thank you.
Hey, Melinda. What for?
Learned a lot this morning.
What you did
with IBM-- brilliant.
How did you know to stay long
when everyone was selling short?
Uh, research,
uh, and instinct.
Your market's not
always gonna roll your way,
but if you keep an even head,
the odds are with you.
Think I'll write that down.
Whiskey on the rocks, right?
Oh, no, no,
let-let me get it.
Bruce, you're a gentleman,
but this one's on me.
Hey
Hey, guys. Would you excuse
me for a minute? Thanks.
All right! All right, O'Hara,
got you down for 50 on Miller.
You got business
I should know about, Mareno?
Strictly
extracurricular.
Office pool on who'll be the first
to bag the hot new runner.
Melinda?
Right now, you're the odds-on
favorite, two to one.
Are you kidding me with this?
Just making a market, Bruce.
What we do for a living.
You want in?
I don't know what I want.
What do you think?
Depends.
What do you want the wallpaper
to say about you?
That I have good taste
in wallpaper?
Come on, Mom.
Try and get in touch
with your authentic self.
- My authentic self?
- Yeah.
According to the existentialists,
we're always encountering
all these outside pressures from society,
and the only way to remain authentic
is to remain true to our own desires,
despite those pressures.
So it really doesn't matter
which wallpaper I like.
It matters which one you like.
I knew I was having
a decorating crisis.
I didn't know
I was having an existential one.
Sorry.
Philosophy final tomorrow.
- And it's an oral exam.
- You'll be fine.
You obviously know
what you're talking about.
Here maybe, when it's just you
and me and the wallpaper,
but in front
of my entire class?
In front of... my teacher?
Unfortunately, life isn't always
about doing what we like.
I like this one.
The wedding silver?
What's up?
I am. I am
up, up, up.
I had the most
incredible day.
Turns out there's more to Susan's
new world than just the Deckers.
These ladies
I met today...
These are the kind of people
we should be friends with,Roger.
I'm looking forward
to meeting them.
Good,because you're going to
tomorrow night
at the Children's Hospital
Ladies Auxiliary Benefit Gala.
Sounds fancy.
They all belong to Lake Crest
Country Club where we had lunch,
and I was thinking,maybe if we make
a good impression tomorrow night,
one of them will sponsor us
to join.
Janet, you know
we can't afford a country club.
Well, not right now,
maybe, but...
Remember this morning,how you said
you've been selling insurance for 12 years?
Don't remind me.
Maybe you need to be reminded,you are
the best salesman that company's got.
Maybe you need to remind
your boss of that, too.
Mr. Stone has to realize
how valuable you are.
I think it's high time you stood up
and asked for a raise.
You certainly deserve it.
We deserve it.
My God, that bathing suit?
Might as well have
been a nun's habit.
Not to me.
That was the summer my mom caught
you sneaking out of my room.
You got me grounded
for a month.
The one and only time that she dragged
her ass out of bed before noon.
What were the chances?
Thought I told you to go out
the window like everyone else.
Shimmy down the drain pipe?
No,I was gonna walk out the door
of your bedroom like a man.
Please. You weren't a man
until I made you one.
Oh, no.
Actually, being forbidden to see
you was probably the best thing
that could have
happened to us.
How is that?
I always want
what I can't have.
Hello?
Hey, babe.
Tom,you're missing
quite a show here.
We dug out
my old slides.
- "We"?
- Luke's here.
- Where are you?
- Uh, San Francisco.
We hit that same weather system over
the Pacific,had to fly around it.
Forced us to stop
and refuel.
I... I should be home
by morning.
As long as
you're safe.
Miss you.
Yeah, I miss you, too.
Bye-bye.
Looks like I'm free for dinner.
So where do you want to take me?
Actually, I could stay here
looking at these slides all night.
Let's order in.
How about a drink,
Captain?
Sure.
Why not?
Susan.
Come on in.
To what do I owe
the pleasure?
Well, I-I know
it's last minute, but...
uh, Bruce's boss's wife
is hosting a benefit tonight
for the Children's Hospital,
and I'm on the committee suddenly.
Anyway, we're supposed to invite
people like you and Tom.
Say no more.
- Count us in.
- Really?
God, that felt great.
What a way to start the day.
Hi.
Susan,this is Luke,
my boyfriend.
From high school.
Oh.
Luke, this is my neighbor,
Susan Miller.
- Hello.
- Pleasure to meet you.
You're not busy
tonight, are you?
Whatever I've got,
I can cancel.
Susan,if you're looking for donations,
invite Luke to the benefit.
He's filthy rich.
Filthy.
Who's filthy?
Honey...
welcome home.
Thank you. Susan.
- Luke.
- Hey there, Tom.
Hey, Trine,
I've got a meeting downtown.
Can I grab
a shower?
Sure. Right
through there.
Luke and I had a late night
reminiscing.
Think he had one too many.
Well, I'm gonna...
See you tonight.
Predominant cultural norms are inauthentic,
according to Kierkegaard and Heidegger,
because they require peopleto behave
in ways that obscure their own desires.
So,concluding from that,
authentic self-expression
is possible only when
it is unfettered by the confines
of societal conventions.
Thank you.
Is that it, Laurie?
That's it.
The assignment was to draw
from philosophers we've studied,
and from experiences
in your own life.
I know, but...
Guys,
the subject of this exam
is authentic self-expression,
so,when you're up here,I want you
to really express yourselves.
Laurie,why don't you
take another stab at it?
Sorry, Mr. Stephens,
that's all I got.
And I've also exceed sales in
each of the past six quarters.
Sir, what I'm
saying is this.
Based on my track record,
on my experience,
I believe I'm ready to step into
a stronger management position,
one with a stronger
compensation package.
Mr. Field, you're wanted
in the conference room.
Well, I believe you're right.
Thank you.
Unfortunately, Rog,
that just can't happen here.
Not in this economy.
Heck, corporate is forcing me to
make cutbacks at every level.
We can't afford to compensate someone of
your experience anymore,not fairly,anyway.
And you know
I am nothing if not fair.
- Mr. Stone...
- The truth is,
I've kept you as long as I could,
under the circumstances.
I wish you luck,
wherever you end up,
and I thank you for
your years of service.
Hi, Mr. Thompson.
You're home early.
Didn't want to be late
to the party.
You better hurry up
and get changed.
I'll-I'll call
the Thompsons.
See if they can be ready
a little earlier.
The Thompsons are coming?
To my boss's
wife's benefit?
Rita Pierce loved Janet.
Then I bet she really loved you.
She loved that I brought Janet.
- Tom and Trina are coming,too.
- Good.
Far as I'm concerned,
the Deckers and the Thompsons
cancel each other out.
Haven't you chosen
a pattern yet?
I'm trying to decide which one
expresses my authentic self.
What do you think?
Your "authentic self?"
Uh, honey, I have no idea
what that is.
Roger!
Janet, wow.
I was just in town having my hair
fixed for the benefit.
Thought I'd swing by
and pick you up.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Oh!
And look.
A tuxedo.
It's a rental
from Fells.
I was hoping we'd have a little
something extra to celebrate tonight.
Well, don't keep me
in suspense.
How did it go
with Mr. Stone?
Did he agree
you deserved a raise?
He did.
Oh, I knew it!
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
Things are about
to change for us, Roger.
I can feel it.
Can't you?
Yes.
I can.
I'm excited.
Are you excited?
I'm not sure I fit in
with these women.
Not... not
like you do.
Susan, you just got
to keep an open mind.
Give them a chance.
You know,like you're always
telling me to do with Trina.
- Bruce-ky!
- Hey, Mareno.
- You know my wife, Susan.
- Yeah.
I think you met
Janet and Roger at our housewarming.
Yeah, right, right.
Hey, remind me what it is
you do again, Rog.
Roger's the sales manager
at Mutual of Omaha.
Janet!
There you are.
I want you with me,
setting up the auction.
I love auctions.
The excitement, the paddles.
Mr. Mareno,
I can't thank you enough for
volunteering to be our auctioneer
again this year.
It's my pleasure.
Anything for the kids.
Susan, I'd like you to collect
the checks at the end of the night.
Uh, Rita, I'm-I'm
Bruce, uh, Miller.
I just want to say how fantastic
it is to work for your husband,
and-and also what a- a great thing,uh,
this is you ladies are doing tonight.
I'll be sure to pass that on
to Mr. Pierce.
Ladies, follow me.
Auctioneer?
Hey, man, you want to get
in good with the boss,
you gotta get in good
with the boss's wife.
I mean, you've got Susan
playing for Team Miller,
though with a woman handling the checks,
no wonder it's a non-profit.
And speaking of women
and profit...
Melinda?
I think I'm having
a flashback.
Good one or bad one?
My mother used to parade me
around at these things.
Feel like I'm 16 again.
With your high school boyfriend here
to complete the trip.
Hi, Tom.
Trina.
Lovely as the day
I first saw you.
Minus the braces
and ponytail.
God, I think the last time
I saw you in a tux was...
Your cotillion.
You still remember
the dance?
With your permission,
of course.
Go for it.
Janet,Susan,
the girls and I have agreed:
we would like to
formally invite you both
to join the Children's Hospital
Ladies Auxiliary.
Wow, that's...
Such an honor just to be included,
um, in-in-in all your good work.
For the children.
- Susan, isn't it an honor?
- It is.
Roger,Susan and I have been asked
to join the Ladies Auxiliary.
Wow.
- That's terrific, honey.
- I know...
but, you know,with my schedule
and the kids, I'm not sure
- I'm gonna have time...
- Yeah, ladies, uh,
would you excuse us
just for one moment?
By all means.
What are you doing, Susan?
This is a big opportunity
for you.
I think you mean
For us.
It's not right for me, Bruce.
I am nothing
like those women.
You've barely given
them a chance.
Oh, please,
I- I don't think Rita Pierce
could find the Children's
Hospital on a map.
And-and what happened
to being open to new things,
all options on the table?
- This is different.
- Why?
Because it's
something I want?
You're not being fair.
Maybe we should go
over the rules one more time.
Bruce...
I'll go start damage control.
I was passing by
and saw the light on.
Yeah, I'm just packing up.
About today...
you asked me to express myself
in a true and authentic way,
but the truth is
that you're all I think about,
and all I want to do is scream it
out to anyone who will listen,
and I knew that anything I said in class
today besides that would come across
as complete bull which, unless
I misunderstood the assignment,
was the exact opposite
of what you wanted.
- Laurie...
- But I couldn't exactly say that, could I?
Not in front of the class-your class-
because you're my teacher.
I'm not your teacher anymore.
- Huh?
- Summer session's over.
So then, we can...
Say whatever we want.
I think I'm done talking.
Which one's yours?
Sorry?
Which trader are
you married to?
Uh, Bruce Miller.
He's one of
the good ones.
- You work for Lehman Pierce?
- Uh-huh.
I didn't... I didn't know
they had any, uh...
Women? Not many.
Job's not for everyone.
No, I've seen
the trading floor.
All that pushing
and shoving.
How do you
stand it?
It's what I've always
wanted to do.
And a padded blazer
doesn't hurt.
A padded blazer?
Some guys grope.
I figure:
why not fake it,
let them think they're getting
what they want?
Fake it?
Sure.
I laugh, by an eye.
Makes the guys easier
to manage.
- That doesn't make you feel...
- Cheap?
No, I-I was...
going to say inauthentic.
They make it hard for me
to do my job,
I do what I can
to make it easier.
Sure, I lie a little
every now and then,
but I'm still being true
to myself.
I know exactly who I am.
Man, Jan, you
look dynamite.
Thank you.
Isn't this the most
fabulous party?
Uh, been to a lot
of parties in my day.
Well, not me.
I had no idea Trina
was such a lovely dancer.
Yeah, she's a woman
of many surprises.
- Janet?
- Hmm?
Would you like to dance?
- It was really nice to talk to you.
- And you.
Good luck
with everything.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- Yeah, okay.
- Oh, hey.
- Oh, hello.
Excuse me.
Interesting priorities, Susan.
What do you mean?
You insult the boss's wife,but
you be friend the lowly runner?
You just asked me
to give these people a chance.
I didn't mean her.
I like Melinda.
And she's not lowly.
Unlike most of the women here,
she's actually doing something
with her life.
Well,you know all the guys
are taking bets
on who'll be the first
to sleep with her.
That says something.
That says more about the guys
than it does about her.
Did you try to stop the bet?
Or tell her about it?
Interesting priorities, Bruce.
Next item up for bid
is dinner for two
at the beautiful
Lake Crest Country Club.
Start the bidding
at $25, 25...
$25 right there.
Do I hear $50?
Fifty.
$50, do I hear 75...
Janet, I need
to talk to you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
$75...
I don't think the Ladies
Auxiliary is right for me.
I hope you're not offended.
Why would I be offended?
Well, a little disappointed
maybe, but not offended.
$75, $75 to the gentleman.
How about $100?
For a hundred dollars, folks.
Of course I'd rather we join together,
but as it happens,they want me
whether you're part
of the package or not.
And we both know
that's not always the case.
...$75 going once.
So you're okay
if I don't join.
As long as you're okay
if I do.
$75 going twice.
$100!
$100 going once...
twice...
sold!
Oh! Oh!
So why do you think it is
that we didn't end up together?
Must've been
some reason.
Ever wish that
we could go back?
I like to live
in the here and now.
Right here is good.
Right now.
Easy, tiger.
Tom doesn't have to know.
Yes, he does.
Tom and I have
an open marriage.
We don't cheat.
So, you mean...
My wife and I are
a package deal, Luke.
- Uh, Melinda...
- Excuse me.
Bruce.
Fun night, huh?
Mareno really hammed
it up out there.
Yeah. Look, uh,there's something
I-I need you to know about Mareno,
and-and all
the Lehman Pierce guys.
They've-they've got this bet.
About you.
I know.
Mareno just won.
What?
You and Mareno?
What, here?
For the smartest
guy on the floor,
you don't know much about
women, do you, Bruce?
No, I, well,
I guess not.
I agreed to say
I slept with Mareno;
and he agreed to split
the pot with me.
Look, how much
did you lose?
- I'll give you your money...
- No, uh, no.
I- I didn't bet.
You didn't?
I knew you were one
of the good ones.
There you are.
Susan, I overheard
them saying
that you are in charge of getting
the checks from the auction.
And I'm going need to get
Janet's check back.
Why?
I got fired today.
Oh, Roger...
I'm so sorry.
I'm not.
You know what selling
insurance is?
It's selling safety.
And you know the best way
to sell safety to someone?
- How?
- Scare them.
I was miserable at that job.
I was just too scared
to admit it.
Roger, I...
Janet didn't...
Oh, Janet doesn't know.
I didn't want to ruin
her big night.
Still, you-you shouldn't have
to keep this from her.
It's not about me.
I can pretend for one night.
I'll see what I can do
about that check.
Thanks.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Thanks.
- I really...
- Forget it.
Here.
What's this?
The certificate for dinner
at the country club.
I bought it for Janet.
She'll never know
the difference.
Susan, I can't accept this.
I owe her lunch anyway.
You ready to go?
Good night.
Bye, Susan!
I'll see you next week
at the hospital!
Bye, Rita.
See you then.
The hospital?
Yeah, I volunteered.
I thought the Ladies Auxiliary
wasn't right for you.
Maybe I can make it right.
And until then,
I can fake it.
You coming back in?
Oh, I think
I'll sit this one out.
You go ahead though.
Babe, what's going on?
You and Luke...I don't know...
It just feels different.
Maybe it's 'cause he gets parts
of you that I'm never gonna get.
What do you mean?
Your childhood
and your family.
You're my family.
Do you ever wish
you'd married him instead of me?
I'm gonna tell him to go.
Don't.
Come on.
Coming to bed?
In a sec.
That's the one.
You sure?
I'm sure.
welcome to www.1000fr.com