The house has no roof.
Noticed that.
All the other houses have a roof.
Maybe someone stole it.
Who would steal a roof?
Hmm... maybe kids stole it.
Kids will steal anything that
isn't nailed down, anything.
I know I did when I was a kid.
Ah... body's upstairs.
Ladies first.
Traffic chopper flying over saw
it this morning. Called it in.
With this housing market,
That chopper doesn't see him, he
could've been up there for months.
Why is he up here at all?
Sand on floor...
Birds nests
This roof's been off awhile.
Don't they usually take the old roof off
one day and put the new one the next?
Got a 73 Al Camino up front.
Registered to a Roy McCullough.
"JHY Construction".
Hmmm... construction.
No tools.
No roof either.
Maybe someone stole it.
Aah... got bruises on the face.
Neck and arms.
One gunshot wound to the chest.
Very nice
Beaten and shot.
Ah... better shacked than sorry I guess.
Pockets are empty.
This guys mouth full of twenties
Not a robbery come back.
Oh, there's got to be...
There's got to be a couple
hundreds in here at least
Oh, it looks like it's
jammed all the way down there.
Not jammed.
Shoved.
As in "I'm gonna shove that money
all the way down your throat".
I don't think kids did this.
Relec/Resynchro: Lafeelicita,
Grischka, PerkosDhed Marc-Anthony
SeriesSub.com
- Chicken and ribs.
- Ribs?
Chicken?
Eh, why choose when you can have both?
Here you go.
Lemonade?
Uh, this is JHY Construction?
It is.
And you do roofs?
Yeah, but let's not talk business yet.
How long have you two been together?
What do you say,
Sasha, about two years?
Looks like two years, yeah.
It has actually been about two years.
How do you know that?
Over three years, you stand
further apart. Much further.
And newlyweds hold hands,
but still you two seem like...
we're not married. We're partners.
She has commitment issues.
Who needs a piece of paper
as long as you got a
roof over your head?
A roof over our heads, now
you're talking business.
- Isn't that why you're here?
- No.
We're detectives.
Did a Roy McCullough work here?
Roy and I, we lived together.
The house Roy was found in
had its roof taken off.
That's something your company does.
We usually put them back on too.
This would have been off for a while.
Any reason why you'd take a roof off
and not put it back on?
We'll need to see your records.
Make sure it wasn't one of your jobs.
Yeah, of course. I'll get them.
And we need to know where
you two were last night.
Right here, both of us.
It's the end of our tax year.
We were hunkered down working the books.
Roy was supposed to help,
but he didn't show up.
Either of you own a gun?
You know anyone who'd want to hurt Roy?
Roy had... other interests.
This business wasn't enough for him.
What business was enough for him?
Do you think after a few years
we'll stand further apart?
That'd be sad.
Crews, we're not a couple.
Oh, yeah.
Still, it'd be sad.
Time driving a wedge between us.
Oh, "roof raisers".
"Wenderson's roofing".
"Schienbloom and sons".
He's got a lot of signs here
but no roofing supplies.
Yeah, there were no roofing supplies
in the attic either,
'cause there was never
gonna be a new roof.
All these companies, you know,
I'll bet none of this is legit.
Looks like our Roy was working a scam.
Most likely these companies
didn't do anything.
Well, let's go find out
who these companies
didn't do anything to.
"Who these companies
didn't do anything to"?
- Do you have to talk like that?
- Like what?
I don't think I talk differently
than anyone else talks.
Maybe sometimes I don't not say things
that other people don't not say,
but most other people don't not say
the same things I don't.
You know what I'm saying?
Red Pesca?
Yeah, I see you staring.
My hair was Red when I was a kid.
Then I got the nickname,
then I grew up and it changed.
I kept the name 'cause
"salt and pepper Pesca... "
sounds like a pasta dish?
Actually I was staring
at the whole winter wonderland thing.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I dress like this 24/7.
Ever since I hired
"Murrigan and sons" roofers.
I got the flu.
The whole family's got it
since we sleep in a house with no roof.
You can't get the flu from being cold.
The flu's a virus.
Well, then we all got colds.
Well, the cold is a virus too.
Then we all got whatever
you get from being cold.
Well, you get cold.
But not a cold.
Mr. Pesca we saw the better
business bureau complaint.
Right, they were real reliable
at taking the old roof off.
But then that Roy guy,
he wanted to charge
triple what we'd agreed
to put the new one on.
So I said, "no, I'd sue".
And he said, "go right ahead.
I'll just declare bankruptcy
and open a new company".
Not a bad little game.
That woulda made me mad.
Does that make you mad, Red?
No, I just laugh things off.
My doctor says you live longer that way.
We hired rain go away roofing
to put a new roof on
our mid-century modern.
He took the old one off
and then disappeared
with our deposit check.
We called but the number
he gave us was disconnected.
But everything worked out okay.
- How's that?
- We decided to do the work ourselves,
and it strengthened our bond.
You can watch us on the web.
WWW dot andy and rory put
on their own roof dot com.
- Would you like to be on our show?
- What would I have to do?
Can you work a router?
Mrs. Ford, it says here
you wrote a lot of checks
to a company called "a
roof of our own" limited.
Yes.
Most everything I had.
A by "a roof of our own",
you mean Roy McCullough?
Nice young man.
Polite.
I have nothing bad to say about him.
Except that he stole most of your money.
He was so polite.
I baked him cookies.
Why so many checks, Mrs. Ford?
Well, he kept saying
he'd lost the one I'd given him,
so I'd write another.
- Then he'd lose that one.
- And you trusted him with your money?
Well, why wouldn't I?
He was so polite.
Yes.
He was.
But I guess he was just a
thieving prick in the end.
Home, Finn.
Oh, detective Crews.
Where's Finn?
I suppose that is Finn.
Why won't you just call?
I guess you've got a
big question to ask me.
Why did you want me to
go after Roman Nevikov?
Were you always so
serious even as a child?
Look, your driver's in the trunk.
Your security guard is cuffed to
a pipe back at the garage.
Maybe you want to tell me what you know.
You gotta laugh, Charlie,
or you're never getting out of here.
Okay, detective sourpuss,
I'll tell you what you wanna know.
But there's something
I need to show you.
It's gonna take me a
little while to get.
So why don't you come back
and see me then?
How many complaints on this guy?
About 60.
He underestimated someone,
ripped them off, they whacked him.
That was Reese's theory.
It's a good theory.
Doesn't explain the money
shoved down the throat.
He was sending a message.
Who to?
Who'd see a guy in the
attic of a vacant house?
Well, that's what the taxpayers of LA
Are paying you to find out.
Is that a new suit?
Nice. Where'd you get it?
At the, uh, suit store.
Which one?
I don't remember.
Didn't buy it yourself?
It was a gift.
Is this where I say "unfreeze"?
Guess who owned the house
our victim was found in
before the bank foreclosed.
Red Pesca.
Two houses, no roofs,
salt and pepper hair, and a cold.
Just stay where you are, Red.
And put your hands...
put your gloves
where we can see 'em.
Truth doesn't seem to
be your strong suit, Red.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- I think what detective Reese means
is that you lied to us
when you said the ex-Roy McCullough
was found dead in your ex-house.
You gotta believe me.
I didn't kill anybody.
Remember the part where you lie?
So... everybody and their aunt Marie
is making money flipping.
You take the equity
out of your house
and you use that to buy
a second house.
You double your money.
But not Red Pesca.
No, the minute I try it,
the whole housing market
just dries up like that, poof.
And Roy McCullough?
He offered me two roofs
for the price of one.
And you got no roofs?
Right, so I can't sell the house
I'm flipping with no roof, and
I got no money left to put one on.
And so the bank forecloses.
Yes!
Wow, that's some cold you got there.
You want to take those off
for us, Red?
I sure don't.
Okay, well, we can get a warrant.
- For my gloves?
- For what's under them.
All right.
Let's see those hands, Red.
Hey, sit back down now, Red.
He's punching...
the wall.
I guess laughter doesn't
work after all.
We should probably stop him.
Feel better?
Much.
Hi, Ann.
Hi.
Oh, I almost fell over
when you called.
Not really fell over,
that's an expression.
But you know that.
Does your mom know that you called?
No.
You've grown so much.
Okay.
You're... a beautiful young woman.
Sure.
Ann, you can call me
"dad" if you want to.
I don't.
Are you gonna let me in?
Yes.
Ann, who the hell are they?
Oh, they're my crew.
Punch a wall?
Let off steam?
That's right.
- Doctor says...
- you'll live longer.
Looks like you got
some scabs already.
I guess I punched a wall last week.
Or you punched something else.
You punched that wall
to let off steam?
Or to cover up what was
already on your hands?
Where'd you get those scabs, Red?
What else u been punching?
Lunched a wall last week.
My partner has ESP
Did you know that?
No, I sure didn't.
Well, he's gonna look
into your future now,
no charge.
We're gonna test your DNA.
Then we're gonna
check out the ad guy.
And the results are gonna show
your DNA all over the dead guy.
Is he right?
I'm gonna look further
into your future, Red.
I see a house.
This one's got a roof on it.
It's a big house
with bars and walls.
There are guards on the
walls. It's always noisy.
There's yelling and
crying, and a weird laugh
that sounds like a cry.
And there isn't any fruit, ever.
How does that future sound?
Hang on.
Okay, yeah, I went to
the guy's office
to get my money back.
And, you know, he laughed at me,
and,
before I knew what I was doing,
I was all over him, but
I didn't kill anybody.
Red, I think you're a smart guy.
- Really?
And I gotta ask...
why'd you go for the
"two-roofs-for-one" deal
in the first place?
Because that woman who worked there.
Sasha?
Sasha.
Yeah, one smile from
her and I whipped out...
the checkbook.
Checkbook.
I really don't believe
in the future.
I know.
There is no future.
There's just now.
I know, Crews. I'm...
yes.
Got it.
All right, thanks.
ME's office.
Roy was beaten several
hours before he was shot.
So Red beats him then shoots him?
Or he's telling us the truth and...
he only beats him.
When you've got cash
flow problems like Red,
found money goes into your wallet,
not down a dead guy's throat.
60 complaints to the
better business bureau.
Only one complaint
withdrawn, a Mary Ford.
Why do you file a complaint,
and then withdraw it?
So one of us should go
talk to old Mary Ford,
- and the other one...
- Should go talk to Sasha.
All right, just keep your
checkbook in your pants.
I don't really know the Pescas.
Roy just asked me
to deliver some papers there
a couple times.
Well, we call that being
an accessory.
To what?
Conspiracy, fraud,
grand theft.
The DA's office will add some later.
They're good at that.
Believe me, really good at that.
I don't even know
anything about this.
Oh, come on, Sasha.
Roy may have kept the
business names separate,
but you were all in this together.
No, I just delivered some papers.
Detective, this business is legal.
Well, I got 60 people on
record disagreeing with you.
They don't read the fine print,
it's not our problem.
Kids, you stole people's roofs.
It's what makes a house a home...
a roof over your head.
People like their roof.
It makes 'em feel safe.
People don't feel safe, they do
stupid things, violent things.
I don't know what Roy
was doing, I don't.
But we run a legitimate business.
So please, just stop.
Detective Crews' job
is to talk to anybody
who might be involved.
He's just talking to
the wrong people,
that's all.
Well, guess I'm not getting ribs.
What a beautiful home, Mrs. Ford.
It's William's.
Everything here is William's.
I can't live in my house.
It's got no roof.
And William is?
My son.
Actually, he's more like
the daughter I never had.
He takes me antiquing.
We exchange recipes.
I tell him he should find
a nice girl and settle down,
but he says the only girl
he's interested in is me.
Well, he sounds very sweet.
And a little off, if you ask me.
Mrs. Ford, I do want to ask you
about withdrawing your complaint
against Roy McCullough.
The prick.
William asked me to.
There's no eating the store.
It's just an...
an apple. I know, I can ell it.
And you're not eating
it in this store.
You'll get down to the core,
and then you won't know
where to put it,
and then you'll stick it in a vase
like that was of gum
I found over there.
What if I eat the core?
What, seeds and all?
Can't see you if you're
nodding your head.
Seeds and all.
That a girl you got there with you?
He can smell your...
essence.
Girlie, you better make
sure eats the seeds.
You might want to call her
"detective girlie". She gets touchy.
Detective.
You cops
Are you William Ford?
Do I look like Willie Ford?
I'm William Ford.
Mom called and said you were coming.
- Nice lady, your mom.
- The best of the best.
She didn't deserve to
get ripped off like that.
You asked her to withdraw
her complaint.
Well, we prayed on it, and it just
seemed like the right thing to do.
- Turn the other cheek.
- Yes.
Enough hate in this world.
William Ford, aka "Sweet William".
Aggravated assault,
aggravated assault,
aggravated assault.
- He's easily aggravated.
- Rode with the vandals out San Berdoo.
This guy dropped a dime on William.
Ended up with his tongue
being cut out.
Case unsolved.
This guy leaned on his bike.
Somehow had all his fingers broken.
Assailant unknown.
This guy stole biker gang drugs.
Found him at the beach,
a large bore hypodermic
needle jammed in his heart.
That pour schmuck Roy
didn't scam the wrong guy.
He scammed the wrong guy's mother.
Mr. Apple and detective girlie.
And you brought friends.
Anything you have to say,
you probably want to speak up.
Yeah, why do you say that?
It's about to get really
loud in here.
Hands up.
Slowly.
Very slowly.
Don't worry...
it's not loaded.
You got yourself a boat?
No.
You should get yourself a boat.
I used to bring women on here.
So many women.
No more.
The treatment's kinda put
a stop to that.
You said you wanted
to show me something.
It's more peaceful though
without that constant need.
It's like I can finally think.
I can clear my head.
- I'm gonna go now.
- Okay, okay, it's under there.
It's under there.
What the hell is that?
It's a scorpion.
Deep fried.
I raised it myself.
What do you want me do with it?
I want you to eat it.
Why would you want me to eat that?
Because I want you to.
Because you need to.
Because you got all that money
and you don't have a boat.
Because you're so angry.
And because if you eat it,
I will tell you everything
you want to know.
Everything.
I took the stinger out.
I eat the scorpion and he dies.
Got ya!
I looked good, didn't I?
Like I really croaked?
- I practiced that.
- I am going to go now.
Bank of Los Angeles.
A deal is a deal.
Yeah, we took that money.
And that was just the start.
We took a lot more
over the next few years.
That was the plan...
steal everything we
could get our hands on,
and then get out.
And Jack Reese?
His crisis of faith came early.
Jack never kept a dime.
Stayed a cop.
Gave his cash to charity.
And Roman Nevikov?
- Why'd you want to have him put away?
- All that money we took,
we invested it.
Roman Nevikov
was one of our investments.
But Roman Nevikov is a bad man.
Cops put bad men away,
and we are cops.
You're dying, and you want to polish
your tombstone before you go.
No,
I'm dying, and I know
I'm going to hell when I do.
But there is some justice
I need to get done first.
Sweet William is long gone.
- I'm just William now.
- You paid your debt, huh?
I'm still paying it,
every single day.
And not because I have
to, because I want to.
It makes me feel good to do good.
So why the 180?
My mom straightened me out.
She say you keep cutting
out people tongues,
she'll send you to bed
with no supper?
No, she told me to make myself right
in the eyes of my maker.
So I want straight.
- Everybody lives happily ever after.
- Yeah, except for Roy McCullough,
in that he's not actually
living at all.
Just because some guy
rips off my mom,
does that mean I kill him?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Sweet William would have killed him.
- William Ford...
- turned the other cheek.
Yeah. You read that book?
- I saw the movie.
- William,
either of your cheeks have
an alibi for when he was killed?
Detectives.
They all say the same thing.
They rode with William up to Oxnard
on the day before the killing,
camped that night,
rode back the next day.
To review,
Ian, Roy, and Sasha
see the old lady.
She's an easy mark.
They bleed her dry.
Mom file a complaint, but then...
- Sweet William finds out about it.
- Mom un-file it, because in his world,
they have their own way
of filing complaints.
William find Roy.
He wants his mother's money back.
Roy resists for two seconds too long,
gets himself dead, then...
then they all work out the
story and alibi each other.
What?
No, you two are doing...
you'doing great.
- But?
- But, you know, if Sweet William
shot Roy and then shoved
that money down his throat,
why are Ian and Sasha
still working the roofing scam?
Look over this list and just initial
by all the changes that we made
and make sure
that you're okay with it.
And the total is
gonna be right here.
Sasha.
Detective.
Excuse me.
Did you,
- did you find who did that to Roy?
- Actually, I'm not here on business.
Well, I'm not here on my business, cop
business. I'm here on your business,
roof business.
I'd like to hire you.
- Hire us?
- See, I like a lot light.
A lot of light. And,
you know, I've just been thinking my...
my roof kindagets in the way of that,
the light.
So I was thinking if
I didn't have a roof,
I could have more light.
And I thought of you.
You're still in the business
of taking people's roofs, right?
Listen, I have to get back to work.
We're pretty sure
William Ford killed Roy.
Then you should arrest him.
If you think that he murdered Roy,
then you should arrest him.
Why are you still working the scam?
It's a legitimate business.
After what William did to Roy,
he took over your business,
didn't he?
I have to get back to work.
After Roy was found dead,
William moved in on
you and Ian, didn't he?
Ian and I own this business.
Sasha,
these men work for William Ford.
Come with me right now.
I can take care of myself.
Ann,
I understand
how hurt you must be. And
if you need your
crew here to talk to me,
I understand that too.
You can ask me anything you want
to know, anything at all.
I am wide open.
I don't wanna know
anything about you.
I don't understand.
The purpose of this is an oral history
about my ancestors.
So you don't wanna
know anything about me,
what I've been doing?
No.
Well, that's just...
silly.
My husband and I
designed this project...
your husband? Your husband?!
When did you get married?
Four years ago.
Where is he?
Interviewing his mother.
And where is that?
In Ulaan Baatar.
- Ulaan ba... what?
- Mongolia.
My husband and I designed
this oral history project
to start one generation back.
One generation...
so you don't wanna know about me?
No.
Okay, I understand that.
I understand that.
Can I ask where you
met your husband?
No.
Can I ask if you have children?
"No" I can't ask or
"no" you don't have them?
So you're not gonna ask
anything about me,
and I can't ask anything about you?
Ann...
well, I-I...
I guess we're done here.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess we are.
Do not slam that door!
If Ian and Sasha are
afraid of William,
they're not gonna talk.
And William's biker buddies and
his mother aren't gonna turn him in.
So how do we break William's alibi?
Reese?
How do we break William's alibi?
Tidwell looks good in that suit.
Oh, I'm just saying, you know,
it's a nice suit.
He looks good in it.
Detective Crews.
That's right.
Can we speak privately?
And you are?
Someone who'd like to
speak privately with you.
Shall we?
Amanda Puryer.
Puryer security services.
- Didn't think you were a cop.
- Can't see why you would.
You're not recruiting, are you?
I'm pretty happy at my job.
No, I'm not recruiting.
I'm here about one of my clients,
Mickey Rayborn.
My company provides his security
package, protection, driving,
intelligence
around the clock.
Is this about the driver
that I put in that trunk?
No.
About the bodyguard I
left cuffed in the garage?
No.
You can't smoke in here.
Why not?
It's against the law.
I don't believe that's true.
I'm here
about this.
Coast guard found the boat
adrift about a mile out.
No body.
But as you can see...
plenty of blood.
Your police lab is
typing the blood now.
I'm sure they'll be
in touch with you soon.
And I'm sure they'll
have their own questions.
You were on that boat this morning.
You're not I. a. P.
d. Why are you here?
Because if that blood is
Rayborn's, if he's dead,
my company owes his
estate $15 million.
Because if that blood's Rayborn's,
someone killed my client.
And I think it was you.
You can't smoke in here.
Was she smoking in here?
Now that's a woman...
who needs to take better
care of her health,
much better care.
Crews,
your head in there or in there?
- There.
- All right,
here's what we know
about William Ford.
He makes it a habit of taking over
people's businesses.
He also makes it a habit of leaving
his mark on his victims.
One has his tongue cut out.
One has his fingers broken.
And one of them was blinded.
- No one on this board was blinded.
- No, no one on that board.
William Ford takes over
people's businesses.
How do you think
he got into antiques?
Detective girlie.
And Mr. Apple.
Wayne Hall.
How'd you know my name?
I never told you my name.
We know a lot of
things about you, Wayne.
We know you did time for
possession and dealing.
We know you walk around
that antique store
like you used to own the place,
- like it was yours.
- I just work there.
That shop belongs to William Ford.
Yeah, you know, we saw
that in the title records.
You signed it over.
We know something
else about you, Wayne.
You were not born blind.
What happened, you
piss off William Ford?
He take your store?
Then took your sight?
What'd you do, you steal money?
You steal drugs?
You stole drugs.
That was your store, wasn't it?
That was a long time ago.
- Do you want it back?
- How's that gonna happen?
Well, we don't think William took
your store because he likes antiques.
He could care less about them.
So what's he really selling there?
Hey, whatever you tell us,
we were never here.
I never saw you?
China
clock.
How may I help you?
- China clock.
- We'll take that one.
- That one there.
- It's not for sale.
It's a personal favorite.
You strike me, you'll
only be striking yourself.
What, some kind of karmic payback?
If only.
No, my partner will just
shoot you in the head.
Reese,
you ever seen a clock made of china?
You have to be
really careful with china.
Fragile.
Oh, and there was china in it too.
Oh, that dope also
a personal favorite?
Say good-bye to the world, William.
Record like yours and dope
like that, that's 15 to 20 easy.
If you can pin that dope to me.
Everything in here came
from somewhere else.
I don't know where
that clock has been.
Maybe you can handle
another stretch.
What about your mom?
Can she?
My mom?
She gave away her life
savings with you outside.
How safe is she gonna
be with you inside?
Okay,
let's do some business then.
I got something you want.
Yeah, what's that?
The murder weapon from that killing.
The gun in the McCullough shooting?
With Ian Ryker's prints on it.
Insurance policy?
Yeah, it's my insurance.
One little thing.
- Yeah, what?
- This is a. 45.
Roy was killed with a. 38.
Now
what exactly did you mean
by "insurance"?
You know what this is?
This is the gun that you gave to us,
but that is not the murder weapon.
That was a. 38. This is a. 45.
There are fingerprints on this gun,
and those prints are Ian's.
- So do you know what this is?
- You already asked him that.
Right.
This is not the gun that killed Roy.
William,
why did you think Ian killed Roy
with a gun that didn't kill Roy?
And why would Ian touch the
gun that didn't kill Roy?
And here's the big one...
why do you have the gun
that Ian touched
that didn't kill Roy?
William,
Ian gave you that gun.
He tried to give me barbequed ribs.
They looked kinda moist too.
Not too saucy.
It's what Ian does.
He wants to sell you something,
he gives something away. So
if he gave you that gun,
what did he sell to you?
Okay.
Those kids take
everything your mom has.
You get mad. You get your hand
around Ian's throat.
- So what does Ian do?
- He sells you something?
Don't be ashamed.
He's good at his job.
You wanted one of them dead
for what they did to your mom.
Ian saw that.
That's why he's good at his job.
- He knows what people want.
- Ian gave you what you wanted.
Did he tell you that if you'd let
him go, he'd take care of Roy?
And then he gave you that gun.
Told me to dust it for his prints.
For insurance?
Yeah. There's still
the problem with that
one little thing.
That is not the gun that killed Roy.
So...
then I didn't do anything wrong?
Except for felony possession
and aggravated extortion.
Oh, yeah.
So where's the gun that killed Roy?
Sasha said she knew how
to take care of herself.
Offer me some chicken.
What?
- You want some chicken?
- No.
Now offer me some ribs.
- You want me to offer you...
- some ribs.
Come on, you can do it.
Ribs first, then business.
- Do you want some ribs?
- No.
I thought you wanted me to offer...
- now offer me a gun.
- A what?
- Offer him a gun.
- I told you, I don't have a gun.
Okay, well,
just offer him one anyway.
What did you mean when you said
you could take care of yourself?
Did Ian give you something
so you could take care of yourself?
Did Ian give you a gun so you
could take care of yourself?
After William killed Roy, after
those men took over,
Ian gave me a gun,
for my protection.
I have no idea what
she's talking about.
It's okay. You did it to protect me.
No, no, no, don't...
don't touch that.
I'm not gonna do anything.
Except get your prints on it.
A.38.
Just like the gun that
put that bullet into Roy.
I never knew she had that gun.
Yes, you did. You gave it to me.
No, I didn't. And I never touched it.
You won't find my prints on it.
Oh, just Sasha's?
Well, you really are
good at your job.
After you talked William
out of killing you...
and then you set William up by shoving
that money down Roy's throat.
Is that the gun that killed Roy?
You gave me
the gun that killed Roy?
I don't know what you're
talking about, Sasha.
I want to arrange for her a lawyer
so she doesn't get one of those
appointed ones.
Who do I talk to about that?
You ever kill anyone
before you killed Roy?
- I never killed Roy.
- Take a life.
You think you're ready
for it but you're not.
- I didn't kill anyone.
- It makes your whole world go away.
Makes you forget who you are,
who you want to be.
Makes you forget
where you came from,
and where you're going.
Makes you forget a lot of things.
You only used one bullet.
You remember to wipe down the gun.
Did you remember to
wipe the bullets?
We gonna find your prints on those?
I told you kids stole that roof.