Ugh, look at all these bills.
Water and power.
Oh, and my perennial
favorite, the rent.
What am I missing?
- Not a thing that I can see.
- Doyle, try to pay attention.
I am paying attention, princess.
We just need the income
to pay for the outgo.
This is a business.
We need to start running it like one.
We should be charging.
Angel works day and night...
...to help people
fight personal demons...
...but I need a raise.
You've worked for him for 20 minutes.
A month. And I have needs.
- Needs.
- A person needs certain...
...designer...
...things.
I don't think you need much clothes.
But you are right,
Angel needs to start charging.
He just hates bringing up
finances with clients.
He likes playing the hero...
...walking off into the dark,
his long coat flowing behind him...
...in that mysterious
and attractive way.
- Is this a private moment?
- No, I'm not saying I'm attracted.
He just projects
a certain kind of image.
Asking for money isn't part of it.
He's sensitive about that.
Here he comes.
We're gonna stand up to him.
We're standing up.
Just as soon as he's had his coffee.
Right.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- What is this?
- Last week's coffee.
- Think of it as espresso.
- I think my esophagus is melting.
Sure been making us proud
fighting the evil and all.
You've been fantastic,
saving people left and right--
- I'm not comfortable asking for money.
- Then get over it!
I mean that in a sensitive way.
It's not your favorite thing,
but you gotta do what's right.
It's right to ask people
in trouble for money?
No.
- So we agree?
- No.
- We don't agree?
- Make up your mind, will you? Doyle!
Uh-oh. Vision fit approaching.
Pen. Paper.
- A single malt Scotch.
- Here.
What'd you see?
Melissa Burns,
at Pardell Paper Products.
- How'd she look?
- Melissa Burns.
Better than me.
This ain't single malt. It's...
...polymalt.
Okay, Pardell Paper Products,
200 Wilshire Boulevard.
Guess I'm going to work.
Maybe I'm a little attracted.
I clearly said Penny!
I spelled it with letters.
It's okay, I'll fix it.
Here, you do these.
Aha! Perfect.
- Okay, light them.
- Okay, I'm lighting.
Great.
- What about the "J"?
- What's going on?
Happy birthday!
Oh, this is so sweet.
You've only been here a month...
...and already you know
four of the letters of my name.
Well, it's just we thought
you should be Penjy from now on.
We think it suits you better.
- Make a wish already.
- Okay, all right, wait.
Yeah!
I painted the pot myself,
so feel free to break it by accident.
Don't be silly. Thanks.
Check it out. My little
philodendron just got upstaged.
I don't know anybody
with taste that good.
Oh, right you are.
They're for Melissa.
- Who they from?
- I don't know.
Delivery guy from Ned's Flowers.
Something wrong?
No.
No one ever sends me flowers.
- Would you watch my phones?
- Oh, sure, honey.
Melissa.
I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to startle you.
- I thought you were someone else.
- You all right?
Yes.
- I'm Angel. I'm in private security.
- Excuse me?
It's what I do.
It's my job.
You walk around garages
telling people this?
I think you may need my services.
- I can't afford private security.
- It's not about money. I help people.
- Sometimes when the police can't.
- Out of goodness?
- I'm not explaining this very well.
- No, but thanks.
If you need anything,
call that number.
I scared her,
Seems like she was already scared.
Hey, am I intimidating?
I mean, do I put people off?
As vampires go, you're pretty cuddly.
You might think about mixing up
the black-on-black look.
Maybe she'd feel safer talking to you.
When she hires us, I'll get involved.
Cordelia's right.
I don't think so. I got a feeling
we should get involved now.
- This shouldn't be about money.
- It isn't.
Yeah, you should listen to--
It isn't?
It's about doing what's best
for those you've helped.
People get attached
to a mysterious savior...
...and can you blame them?
But as long as you're a man
who's doing a job and getting paid...
...they'll feel like they've paid their
debt and move on, independent-like.
You're a lot smarter than you look.
Of course, you look like a retard.
It won't work.
I changed your pin number.
I mean, your birthday? That's
the first thing a thief would try.
What are you doing here?
I changed it to 3-5-99.
The day we met.
- You have to stop doing this.
- Stop looking after you? Why?
What do you want?
I just want you to be
happy and healthy, silly.
Speaking of, are you losing weight?
I think it's the tranquilizers.
How many did you take
in the bathroom at work, three?
- How do you know--?
- To be honest...
...they don't help with the anxiety.
Now, I prescribed
a calcium selenium supplement.
Did you take it?
No, you threw it in the drawer
the minute you got home.
These are for your own good.
Why can't you just leave me alone?
How can people in love
leave each other alone?
In love?
Ronald, we had one date.
Honey, honey, don't get upset.
I take commitment pretty seriously,
and I know you do too.
Did you have a rough day
at work, is that it?
Surgery. I have to run.
Oh, don't forget
your money, sweetheart.
I'll see you tonight.
Angel Investigations.
We help the hopeless.
I'd say right away.
She's coming in.
I gotta change my shirt.
It's been going on about seven months.
It wasn't so bad at first.
What's his name?
Dr. Ronald Meltzer.
He's a neurosurgeon.
I had an infected nerve
behind my right eye.
He operated and saved my sight.
Afterwards, he asked me out.
I didn't really want to, but....
He helped you, you felt obligated.
Plus, a doctor.
So we had one drink, one time...
...and he started calling me, a lot.
Then he started showing up
at my work, my apartment...
...saying we had something special,
that we should marry.
I said I wasn't interested.
Then it got worse?
I know it sounds stupid...
...but I can feel him
watching me all the time.
Today, he knew I took my Xanitab...
...when I was alone in the bathroom.
He's just everywhere.
I don't think I can take
much more of this.
Well, we're gonna help you.
Bigtime. And for a reasonable fee.
- Doyle will see you home safely.
- Thanks. You've been really kind...
...listening to me...
...and it's terrible.
- We're gonna take care of that.
- No, I mean the coffee.
Angel...
...how did you know I needed help?
I have a friend
at the police department.
I'll check in with you later.
Can you imagine? A doctor.
They examine your body.
They know every inch of you.
How's he doing it?
How does he see her
when she's alone, in private?
Is he invisible?
Or some kind of ghost?
Maybe he can astral project.
Maybe he has an accomplice
or a hidden camera.
Not everything has to be creepy.
No, but Doyle had a vision.
Which last time led to a sex-changing,
tear-out-your-innards demon. Right.
I guess they don't call you
for the everyday cases.
He sees her when he's nowhere around.
How?
Okay, flesh, anytime you want
to stop crawling is okay with me.
Hello, Kate.
Angel.
Hi. It's good to see you.
You too.
Judging by your discomfort,
I'd say...
...you're about to ask me out
on a date or you need a favor.
And I'm gonna go with favor.
So ask, and I'll see if I can do.
A girl. A client.
She's being stalked.
I think it could get ugly.
She's being stalked, then ugly
it already is. What's her name?
You don't have to stay
with me all day.
I'm here to protect and serve.
If I'm not in the way.
I like it.
As long as you're not bored.
No, I'm good.
Got the word jumble right here.
Should keep me occupied,
sadly, for most of the day.
I feel better now. I guess Angel's
handled a lot of cases like this?
Dozens. Hundreds.
Dozens of hundreds.
It happens that often?
Well, exactly like yours?
Not quite so many.
But protecting women such as yourself?
Oh, yeah, there's been four,
and three of them are very much alive.
Is that you?
Yeah, bungee jumping.
I always meant to do that,
but I intensely don't want to.
- So I haven't gotten around to it yet.
- It's fun. It's scary.
You don't seem like
the thrill-seeker type.
Well, I used--
I used to do a lot
of things, you know, before....
Don't worry. When Angel's
done with this case...
...I guarantee you'll be wanting
to jump off a bridge again.
Your girl did file
a report two months ago.
The doctor responded
and denied everything.
A lot of noise from his lawyers.
What?
His lawyers. Wolfram and Hart.
- You know the name?
- I've heard it.
They're the law firm Johnnie Cochran
is too ethical to join.
They actually filed
a restraining order against her.
Very cute. There's still no record
of violence from the doctor.
Yet.
- You think he's gonna blow?
- I do.
I'll put a uniform on her.
I probably can't spare one
for more than a day or two.
- Thanks. That'll help.
- And your client? She's holding up?
She's scared.
He's put her on the ropes.
Help her get mad. That's the only
way she'll be able to fight him.
I'll fight him.
That's why she hired me.
That's not what I mean.
He could go to jail tomorrow...
...and still kill her
in her dreams every night.
I've put these creeps away.
It's hard to know he's still winning.
She's still afraid.
He took this girl's power away.
Nobody can get it back
for her but her.
- You're a miracle worker.
- Oh, thank you.
If you'll step right over here.
What are you doing in my office?
Name's Jensen. I must talk to you.
- Then make an appointment.
- I don't have time.
- I heard you do things nobody else can.
- I'm calling security.
My wife has a malignant tumor
pressing on her ocular cavity.
She'll die unless someone
has the nerve to operate.
You're talking about a
difficult and dangerous procedure.
I could lose my license.
I understand your situation,
but I can't help you.
- What does she mean to you?
- What?
Is she your wife? Your girlfriend?
- She's my fiancée.
- Nice. You set a date?
- We're working that out.
- Did you know right away?
That she was the one?
- I don't see how this has--
- I'll tell you how.
Know what it is to be so close...
...you don't know where
they end and you begin?
Would you die for her?
Yes.
Then you understand I won't
make any compromises.
I won't watch her suffer and die
while the law catches up with science.
What I will do is pay you
whatever it takes.
Think about it. Please.
Another article about Meltzer?
Well, our readers at...
... The Journal of Diagnostic
Orthopae-- Et cetera...
...seem endlessly fascinated by him.
He is fascinating. Before he
became an ocular surgeon...
...he specialized in orthopedics.
He developed nerve and blood vessel
accelerants that helped many.
- How?
- Well, when you sever a limb...
...you only have so much time
before it atrophies.
- Yuck.
- What?
Nothing. Please go on.
Meltzer's work extended
that period of time significantly.
He's one of the best
at reattaching nerves.
So he's good at the cutting
and the sewing.
He ever strike you
as a dangerous creep?
What? What kind of article
are you writing?
I've gotta be honest.
It may not be a very nice one.
I don't like the way he treats women.
I'll keep your name out of it...
...but just between us,
what is the real dish on this guy?
He's not very generous.
He doesn't share his techniques
with the medical community...
...and a lot of what he claims
to have done is pretty radical.
Like what?
Reattachment of eyes, for one thing.
He can do anything with a knife.
Oh, you so don't want
this guy fixated on you.
What is stalking now, the third
most popular sport among men?
Fourth, after luge.
I don't get it. He has a lot to lose.
What about Melissa
has got him going all O.J.?
Nothing. It's not about her.
It's about rage.
He's too messed up
to deal with a real woman...
...so he creates a fantasy
about a girl he barely knows.
She'll fail him,
and he has to hurt her...
...because when he looks at her,
all he sees is how useless he is--
What a fun date you must have been
back in your bad vamp days.
But, it should give you some insight
into the jerks of the world.
I know how he thinks.
I don't know how he does it.
Being everywhere at once?
Natpudan says we're everywhere at once
since we're made of the same molecules.
I remember that guy, made a big noise
a few years back on public television.
- Then had a big case of Joe Recluse.
- He had a nervous breakdown...
...not long after he had a retreat...
...for a group of famous
yogis and doctors.
I'm guessing Dr. Stalker
was at that retreat?
- What are you doing?
- Sending Joe Recluse an e-mail.
I need to talk to him.
"I hope you have the nerve to believe
I need help with Ronald Meltzer."
"Thanks for having the nerve to--"
Did you steal this book?
- Yeah.
- Good.
You said in your e-mail...
...that Dr. Meltzer
might hurt an innocent woman.
What do you think I can do about that?
Help me understand him better.
I don't think he's like other people.
No, he's not. Of course,
no two people are alike.
God, in His infinite variety and
wisdom, likes to keep it interesting.
- How'd you meet him?
- He came to one of my lectures.
My operating thesis at the time
was that the mind...
...is the single most powerful
force in the universe.
In any average human,
it regulates billions of cells.
And that's with 80 percent
of the brain still untapped.
What are the possibilities if a
person could master all that power?
I introduced Dr. Meltzer
to psychic surgeons.
Yogis who are able to shut down...
...their somatic systems
for days at a time.
But he eclipsed us all.
Until Dr. Meltzer, my studies had
been based on hearsay and theories.
But he exploded all that.
That's when I stopped teaching.
Because you stopped believing?
No.
Because I began to believe.
Completely.
All right, pal.
Why don't you just turn around?
Nice and easy.
Put your hands up.
I was just out for a walk.
Hands. Now.
I'm sorry.
We got a report of someone--
Not you.
That's quite all right, officer.
Just doing your job. I understand.
- What's wrong? Did someone break in?
- He's--
I can't help if you don't tell me.
Did someone break in
or you had a bad dream?
In there.
Okay.
Everything's okay now.
Look, there's no one in your bedroom.
There's no one in your bathroom.
Now, start from the beginning.
Just tell me--
It's me. It's me.
He's in there. He's--
His-- His hands.
I know what he can do.
He killed a-- Please don't leave
me alone. Please don't leave me.
It's all right.
I'm not gonna let him near you.
Here, drink up, love. It's over now.
- She's not making much sense.
- She's been living in terror.
- You think it's the doctor.
- I know it.
How could he do it?
She has bars on the windows.
The security cameras in the hallway
show officers going in...
...and nobody suspicious all day.
- I mean, who is this guy? Houdini?
- Something like that.
I've pulled prints.
If they match his, he's going down.
Detective, can you sign
the coroner's release?
- How's she doing?
- Numb. They get any prints?
- Yeah.
- Good, so we put him behind bars...
...for about 90 seconds
until he skitters through them.
Not many things make me shudder...
...but this guy,
crawling around under the covers?
At least it was just
his hands down there.
- I wish I hadn't even thought that.
- He's coming undone.
- I'll say.
- I mean, he's out of control.
He's killing now.
Anybody that stands
between him and his obsession.
You okay?
We stand between
him and his obsession.
Not putting too cowardly
a point on it...
...but if this guy can't be contained
or killed, what are we gonna do?
His body parts go too long without
blood and oxygen, they deteriorate.
He can't put himself back together.
Not even with psychic surgery.
So we break him down and box him up?
Of course, it's just a theory.
What do we do in the meantime?
Protect her.
It's not good for the ventilation,
but he's not getting in here.
I was just trying to fix your collar.
What say we leave it crooked
until this is resolved?
I don't see how this can--
I mean, this can't be happening.
What I saw. You must think I'm crazy.
No, I believe you.
But, it's not possible.
He can really--?
Yes.
Remember I told you I handle
things the police can't?
Now, this is one of those things.
I'll take care of him.
Doyle and Cordelia will stay with you.
Try to get some rest.
- Here.
- Thanks, but I'm not gonna cry anymore.
I'm tired of crying and being afraid.
- Don't be afraid.
- You're duct-taping for fun?
You survived a living hell
these last months...
...while he's coming unhinged
at not controlling you.
- He's weak. You're strong.
- He knows what he's talking about.
He has stalked plenty of--
Books on the subject.
Could I see you upstairs for a moment?
Melissa stays here with us,
that makes sense.
The part about you
taking care of the doctor?
This guy is really dangerous.
What are you doing?
Seeing where I can get
steel boxes at this hour.
Steel boxes? Why would you want--?
Oh, for packing up people parts.
This job-- Don't get me wrong,
I'm grateful to have it.
God knows it's educational
and all, but sometimes--
Who's calling at this--?
It's the special line.
- Answer it.
- Right, right. Okay.
Are we Johnson International Holdings?
- Jensen.
- Jensen. Good, got it.
Jensen. Now, does that sound
like an international--?
Cordelia.
Jensen International Holdings.
May I help you?
- Mr, Jensen,
- Please hold.
It's him.
- Brian Jensen.
- You're working late,
Downside of being global.
If you still want,
I'll operate on your wife.
I do, thank you,
We have to do it out of the country.
I'll need $100,000 to get started.
Are you in your office?
I'll bring it to you tonight.
You're going there?
What if he comes apart on you?
If he comes apart on me,
he's gonna stay that way.
That's a big box.
You didn't have to
bring it in small bills.
- Actually, I didn't bring--
- Any money at all?
No, I didn't think you would.
Although the safety deposit box
was a nice touch.
Your name's not really Jensen.
You don't have a wife.
What a tangled web, eh?
I developed this injector for animals.
They don't like having
their limbs cut off.
They can hurt you
if you get too close.
You'll feel a slight
sinking sensation.
That's your heart slowing
as the paralytic takes effect.
Eventually, it'll stop altogether.
I just can't get over the audacity.
To think you could take her from me?
I saw you holding her.
Nobody can break the bond
between us. Nobody.
Clearly, even she can't accept that.
I've tried so hard to show her
in so many ways.
I've taken care of her,
been there for her...
...even when she didn't know it.
If that's not devotion....
What do I get for my trouble?
She lies. She cheats.
But no more.
I won't be made a fool of.
She would've made a beautiful bride.
I got everything, I think.
She's resting.
What did you put in her tea?
Enough whiskey to drop my Aunt Judy.
That woman had some girth.
- What's the point?
- It tastes good and it relaxes you.
No, I mean of ever
going out with anyone.
Well, people need people.
And people who need people...
...I mean, are the luckiest peo--
If you like them, they don't like you.
Or you can't stand them, which
guarantees they'll hover around...
...and never go away.
I hate guys like that. It's-- Yeah.
I'm gonna check on her.
It's just so unfair.
This poor girl hooks up with a doctor.
That should be a good thing.
You should be able to call and say,
"Mom, guess what? I met a doctor."
Not "Guess what?
I met a psycho stalker.
By the way, his hands and feet come
off, and he's not even in the circus!"
Not every relationship
leads to disaster.
- What if Angel doesn't come back?
- He'll be back.
- What if Dr. Chop Salad shows up?
- I got this place sewn up now--
What was that?
Just the wind.
Want to play some cards
or watch the tube?
Sure. How about some gin?
A penny a point?
Yeah, you'll owe me money.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
Cordelia.
Whoa.
Hi.
Getting some rest?
What are you?
I'm more than meets the eye. But you
never bothered to find out, did you?
You just took advantage
of my kindness.
Led me on until you could find
yourself a vacuous L.A. pretty boy.
You disappoint me, Melissa.
I know. I didn't mean--
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Stop, now. You're babbling!
I think--
I think you disappoint yourself.
You gave up on being loved
a long time ago.
Now you're another creep
who gets off on pain.
- Don't use childish--
- I'd be crazy to want to touch you...
...to wake up next to little pieces
of whatever you are.
- Shut up!
- You turned yourself into a freak.
A vile, repulsive freak.
I'm done being afraid of you.
You can cut me, and you can kill me.
It still won't change what you are.
Angel was right, you're weak.
I'm weak? Then how is it
that I killed him?
Inefficiently.
You can't be alive. You're not human.
You should talk.
We could have been so happy.
Ronald!
You all right?
Oh, goody. Recycled coffee.
My personal favorite.
He'll never put himself
back together, right?
He's in 12 steel boxes buried
in 20 feet of concrete...
...in L.A.'s newest subway stop.
That ought to bring in the tourists.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Hey. How's it going?
I brought this for you guys.
Oh, hope it doesn't need light.
It'll be fine in here.
- Can I offer you some coffee?
- Coffee? Oh, no.
I can only stay a minute.
Places to go. People to see.
Thanks to you.
- There's....
- What?
There's a bill....
Bill who?
The bill. For my services.
Oh. Of course.
That's the other reason I came.
- Here.
- I'll take that, thanks.
I mean, I didn't do it
for the money.
Oh, please. You earned it.
Well...
...I hope I never see you again.
Me too. Good luck.
Thanks.
That didn't go so badly.
You can save the girl and make money.
Is this a great country or what?
Let's march down to the bank right now
and deposit this beauty.
You guys go. I think I'll stay here
and not burst into flames.
Oh, right, you're pretty much
a night deposit guy.
Well, still. Cause to celebrate.
You think everything's
a cause to celebrate.
- We need more of these.
- We'll have more soon enough.
- Now. Have a vision.
- I can't perform on demand.
- We need clients.
- Money's corrupted you.
If I hit your head,
will you have a vision?
Get away from me. You're insane.