Anna.
Master Liam?
Anna, come closer.
Master Liam, your father....
He'll be at church repenting his sins.
And he should. Closer, Anna.
Why are you in the shadows?
Are you sick?
The light.
It bothers my eyes just now.
And I know the reason why.
Out again all night, is it?
Drinking and whoring!
I smell the stink of it!
- And a good morning to you, Father.
- You're a disgrace.
- If you say so, Father.
- Oh, I do. I do say so.
Have you had enough for one night?
Must you corrupt the servants too?
Servant, Father.
We have one servant.
Anyway, everyone gets corrupted.
But I find some forms
of corruption more pleasant--
I'm ashamed to call you my son.
A layabout and a scoundrel.
You'll never
amount to anything more.
Crazy homeless guy got
out the subway.
Tore up the car,
threatened some passengers.
They pulled the emergency brake.
They're all shaken up.
- What about the suspect?
- Gone.
- The call said a hostage situation.
- It was.
The suspect escaped?
We're still getting
the story, it's unclear.
You have 24 witnesses.
- They all have the same story.
- Which is?
Suspect went out the top vent
while the train was moving.
- He climbed out of a train?
- He was pulled out.
Pulled out by what?
Get statements.
Guess I can forget
about reading him his rights.
It's...
...not a person, is it?
No. Demon.
- And is it--?
- Dead? Yeah, it's dead.
So they die, then.
Yeah.
I'm still having trouble with...
- ...this otherworldly stuff.
- Right.
Demons aren't otherworldly.
In fact, they were here...
...first.
Who should I call?
- Don't call anyone. I'll handle it.
- What do I put in my report?
- Do what you always do.
- This isn't a normal case.
It's L.A., you've seen this a lot.
You didn't have a name for it.
No. I think I'd remember.
People can see what they need to.
Nothing about him stood out.
Except maybe the smell.
Just an average homeless guy.
This is what we got.
Average height, weight and build.
This is your best?
You pulled the emergency brake?
Guy came right at me.
- Why?
- He didn't say.
Why did you pull the brake?
It was an emergency.
Let's get this circulated.
- We want this guy, right?
- We'll do our best.
- Can I go?
- Yeah, you can go.
Why's your father here?
- Daddy, why are you here?
- In the neighborhood.
You've been listening
to that police scanner again.
Nothing on cable, anyway.
You had a hostage situation.
I missed the action.
In 35 years, haven't you seen enough?
Do you know I'm lead officer on scene?
You're doing okay, get back to it.
- What's he up to?
- He's checking up on me.
You sound surprised.
No, you don't get to do that.
- What?
- Kill a demon in front of me...
...then act like we'll have coffee
together. That doesn't work.
- How does it work?
- I'm not sure it does.
No offense. I think you're probably
a pretty decent guy for what you are.
This is business, not personal.
I'm not your girlfriend.
Who is he?
Who, that one?
Yes.
He's magnificent.
Oh, yeah. God's gift, all right.
Really? I've never
known God to be so generous.
His lies sound pretty
when stars are out.
He forgets his promises at sunrise.
That's not a problem for me, actually.
Pay attention!
We just have to decide
what the code will be.
- Code?
- For the security system we got.
- What have we been talking about?
- I don't....
It should be something
easy to remember.
Like my birthday.
- I don't know your birthday.
- I'm aware of that.
After 11 months of punching it in,
you won't have any excuses.
- Did you identify it?
- I believe so.
Would that be the demon you
encountered this morning?
Yeah, that's him.
Her. It's a Kwaini.
They're all female.
How do we dispose of them?
Should be standard. Burial in virgin
soil, simple Latinate incantation.
- However....
- What?
Well, it's curious.
According to the books...
...a Kwaini is a peaceful demon.
- Nonviolent.
- Nonviolent?
No. This thing was a fighter.
Not if it's a Kwaini.
Not a fighter by nature.
They're articulate, gentle creatures.
Not capable of
the strength you described.
Maybe it was just having a bad day.
- Something set it off.
- Clearly.
Forget whether it should've
fought well as it did.
What would make a peaceful demon
attack a train full of commuters?
Something on the train?
Or someone.
- Angel.
- Hi. Can we talk?
- What's up?
- It's about that demon.
If you must discuss this, could
you please not use that word?
It makes me, I don't
know, just uncomfortable.
Just say "evil thing," okay?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
I thought you'd handle it.
I am. It's just that the
evil thing wasn't evil.
The evil thing wasn't evil?
Well, it was an evil thing.
It wasn't an evil-evil thing.
There are not evil-evil things?
Well, yeah.
All right. Sorry.
How did you get in here?
It's daylight.
- Sewer system.
- Right. I remember.
- I need the names of the passengers.
- Why?
I think the demon--
- The train was targeted for a reason.
- The "evil thing" needs a reason?
- It was after something, someone.
- Nothing was there.
- Passengers.
- Checked out.
Look into them. We'll start with
the guy who pulled the brake.
- He said--
- It's still dead, right?
- Yeah.
- Good. I'd like to forget about it.
- I think--
- There's nothing here.
Your not evil "evil thing" was just evil.
Can't we leave it at that?
I guess you can't blame
her for being skittish,
I don't know. Since she tried
to kill me, it's been different.
She'll come round.
Most people require time to adjust...
...after seeing the dark
forces around us,
- Women, in particular...
- Found it!
...struggle with it.
If she struggles with...
...the bigger picture,
she'll miss the details.
- Details?
- Yeah.
Like why a guy who drives a van
would be on a train during work.
Good question,
Anyway, we've located
the Kwaini's body.
- Okay, you'll run the tests?
- Yes,
See you at the office.
- Mr. Lockley?
- Yeah.
I'm Angel. We met at your party.
- I'm Katie's friend.
- Did something--?
She's fine.
- She with you?
- No. She doesn't know I'm here.
I bet she'd like to know
who else was visiting you.
She thought you were there
because you were worried?
- What do you want?
- What was in that package?
What do you mean?
You took something from the crime
scene that the police didn't find.
Who do you work for?
I don't work for anyone.
I'm retired.
I'll find out. I'm telling you
out of respect for Kate.
Are you threatening me?
No. I want to protect your daughter.
Protect my daughter?
From what?
Finding out you weren't there
today because you care.
- You got any kids, Angel?
- No.
Don't think you
know how a father feels...
...or why he does what he does.
Liam! You'll do as I say!
Sweet Kathy. No tears.
- We'll meet again.
- Not if you defy me.
Not as long as I live.
Move away from the door.
Go, but don't expect to come back.
As you wish.
Always just as you wish.
It was a son I wished for! A man!
Instead, God gave me you.
A disappointment!
You couldn't have asked for better.
You told me in word, in glance,
what it is you've required of me.
And I've met your goals, haven't I?
That's madness!
The madness is, I couldn't fail enough.
We'll fix that now.
I fear for you, lad.
And is that all you can find
in your heart for me now, Father?
Who'll take you in? No one!
I'll find a place to sleep,
I tell you that. Out of my way.
I was never in your way, boy.
If you go courting trouble,
you're sure to find it!
You know what to do...
...darling boy,
I could show you
things you've never seen,
Why the urge for lunch?
Lunch time, ain't it?
So you drive here for a hot dog?
One of Manny's. Best there is.
I'll let you and Manny speak.
I thought I'd spend time with
my daughter.
So....
- You been good?
- Yeah. Yeah, good.
And how's Angel?
Pardon me?
Tall guy you brought
to my retirement party.
Yeah, I know who you mean.
That ain't a Mexican name,
is it? Angel?
I don't think so.
You two seeing each other?
We were never
seeing each other, Daddy.
- What's wrong with him?
- Nothing.
Must be something. He married?
- No.
- West Hollywood?
Daddy, no.
Angel's just not my type.
Or I'm not his type.
There's a type and it's the wrong one.
He got a job?
Yeah. He's a P.I.
Private investigator. He any good?
Yeah, he's good. Very good.
- He likes working nights.
- That's good.
That's good he's good.
You came here to talk about...
...a guy you saw me with once?
Well, he made an impression.
- You like him?
- No. Not really.
Then what's this all about?
Nothing. Just....
It's not good to be alone.
Well, vivisection confirms it.
This certainly is a Kwaini.
So they become violent?
No. My tests
detected something else.
- What is it?
- Think of it as the adrenal gland.
- It should be a lot smaller.
- What happened?
The inflammation was
caused by this substance.
I found traces of it in
the Kwaini's system.
Know what it is?
Difficult to say
under these conditions.
But what I can tell you is,
it's synthetic...
...and it seems to contain properties
not unlike PCP.
Though more metaphysical in nature.
I found "eye of newt"
as an ingredient...
...added chiefly for
taste rather than kick.
- It was on drugs.
- Yes.
The delivery guy was carrying.
I think it would be fair
to assume it...
...was jonesing to get well, yes.
Not only did this turn it violent,
it enhanced its strength.
Times 20, I would say.
What would happen if
a battle demon took this?
I shudder to think.
Hey, guys?
Why have a security system
if you never turn it on?
I could have been anyone
or anything.
Move your entrails.
So you're back.
Good, Mr. "I-Can't-Follow-Suspects-
In-Daylight-Because-I'll-Burn."
- What'd you find?
- I hate following detail.
The voyeuristic side is unseemly.
How about traffic?
And parking? Or the lack of it?
- Not like the movies, is it?
- No. Fortunately, I am.
So it turns out he
really is a delivery guy.
It's not the package
he got from Kate's dad.
He had lunch here
and was in there forever.
Don't know what they served,
but he had leftovers.
That's it. That's the source.
That's where it's all coming from.
Guy's name is Angel.
He's an investigator. A good one.
Why is he looking at our operation?
I don't know.
He's got his reasons.
- What was in the package?
- We agreed--
We agreed that I'd use
my connections...
...to help you move illegal parts.
We didn't agree that I'd remove
crime evidence...
...or use my daughter
for information.
We understand what you've done for us.
We're appreciative.
My advice to you:
Whatever you're moving in
your packages...
...dial it down for a while.
Sound advice, Mr. Lockley.
Thank you.
How should we deal with Angel, sir?
- Kill him.
- Is that wise?
Lockley doesn't like
our arrangement.
Angel's death could turn him.
Kill Lockley too.
Must I think of everything?
Someone get me an adrenal gland.
A man of just 26 years.
Liam was loved
by everyone he met....
We pray that you take his
eternal soul into your care.
Welcome to my world.
It hurts, I know. But not for long.
Birth is always painful.
I could feel them above me...
...as I slept in the earth.
Their heartbeats...
- ...blood coursing in their veins.
- Yes.
- Was it a dream?
- A dream for you.
Soon, their nightmare.
You there!
What have you done?
Grave robbers!
You know what to do.
Our Father, who art in heaven...
...hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done.
Give us this day--
It all makes sense
now, doesn't it?
Perfect sense.
You can do anything.
Have anyone in the village.
Who will it be?
Anyone?
I thought I'd take the village.
O-5-2-2.
There. See?
Right. Now we're protected by
home and workplace security...
...designed to compliment
any room, home or office.
No minions of hell get in
without us knowing first.
Sun'll be down soon. I'm going out.
- You'll want backup.
- No. Not this time.
I need to know what we're facing.
Right. A cautious approach is best.
- "Fools rush in."
- No, he wants you to stay here.
- Hi.
- Give me that.
- Am I interrupting?
- No, come in.
Here.
What's this?
The list of names you asked for.
Passengers on the train.
Right.
Thank you.
Why'd you change your mind?
- Something my father said.
- Your father?
He asked if you were good.
"Good"?
At what you do. I said you were.
Thanks.
No matter how uncomfortable I am
with certain circumstances...
...I can't ignore your instincts.
If you think there's more
going on, there probably is.
- I appreciate that.
- And I'd like to be involved.
What?
In the case. You find something,
you bring me in, okay?
Are you sure about that?
- Gotta face those demons sometime.
- Right.
Isn't this above and beyond
the call of duty?
Let's try, Wesley.
I understand you
want to protect her...
...from learning about her father.
You've already warned him once,
and that's too much.
I warned him about me, but he
needs to know who he's working for.
- If he doesn't already know.
- He can't.
Perhaps. Still, he must realize
he's in league with someone...
...who, if not criminal,
is unethical.
- It's his choice.
- I understand.
Sometimes the price for a bad choice
isn't equivalent with the offense.
- Go set him straight.
- Thank you.
- Hope he knows what he's doing.
- Have faith, Wesley.
Door is open,
Yeah, thanks.
Bathroom window is ajar,
Bet you'd like some of this?
Hopheads.
Window is open,
I'm unplugging it.
All right. Talk.
Kate, pick up. Get your father
out of his house. He's in danger.
- Mr. Lockley, may we come in?
- What do you want?
Let us inside.
It concerns your daughter.
He doesn't know, he won't understand.
I'm on way there now.
You're like the rest of them, Father.
Cowering in their houses.
Boarding up the windows.
Smearing garlic in their doorways.
You'd think something evil, vile...
...and monstrous was
terrorizing this village...
...and everyone in it.
Be gone, unclean thing.
A demon cannot enter
where he is not welcome.
He must be invited!
That's true. But I was invited.
She thought I'd
returned to her, an angel.
Murderer!
Strange.
Somehow you seemed
taller when I was alive.
Lord, bind this demon now.
To think I ever let
a tiny, trembling thing...
...make me feel like you did.
Deliver me unto
thy protection, Father.
You said I wasn't a man.
You told me I was nothing,
and I believed you.
You said I'd never amount
to anything.
You were wrong.
You see, Father...
...I have made something
of myself, after all.
- You boys like a drink?
- We'll wait.
So you said this was about Katie.
Yes. Just a question.
You haven't mentioned
our association, have you?
She doesn't know a thing. Why?
We thought that had you
confided in her...
...she might not share
your pragmatism.
Given her position and youth.
You're afraid
she's not crooked like me.
She'll never be, I've seen to it.
Providing for her future.
I'm glad we could help.
Yeah.
I'll thank you when I get my Father
of the Year award. Anything else?
Just one more thing.
- I need you to invite me in.
- What? Get out of here.
- Invite me in. Do it now.
- You need to go.
Invite me in!
You're not welcome here.
If he dies, I'll come in
and kill you both.
Oh, Daddy! No, Dad!
Kate.
Kate, he invited them in.
- But you knew.
- I wanted to save him...
...he wouldn't let me.
He didn't understand what
he was involved in.
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Get out. Please get out.
Please get out.
What happened to
"investigating before rushing in"?
- That was plan A. We're on B.
- Plan B is?
Do I have to explain it to you?
No.
Unlike my father,
I know what you are.
- Do you?
- Oh, yeah.
I see.
I know it won't kill you,
but this will.
Told you I knew.
What do you know?
Do you know what walks this city?
You have no comprehension
of what stands before you!
A demon who thinks
he's scarier than he is?
Yeah, she knows.
We go, you won't lose your head.
Let's go.
- You're dead.
- I'm already dead.
Welcome to the club.
You okay?
Never trust an evil-evil thing.
Kate, I know that
what happened with your father....
My father was human.
You don't know anything about that.
This contest is ended, is it?
- Now I've won.
- Are you sure?
Of course.
- I proved who had the power here.
- You think?
What?
Your victory over
him took but moments.
Yes.
His defeat
of you will last lifetimes.
What are you talking about?
He can't defeat me now.
Nor can he approve of you...
...in this world or any other.
What we once were informs
all that we become.
The same love infects our hearts...
...even if they no longer beat.
Simple death won't change that.
Love?
Is this the work of love?
Darling boy. So young.
Still so very young.