The Cylons were created by man
They evolved
They Rebelled
There are many copies
And they have a plan
Previously on Battlestar Galactica.
This Planet is Kobol
The birthplace of mankind.
Organise a ground survey team.
Three Raptors.
Put it down!
Get down!
She just jumped away
go back to Caprica
and bring me the arrow...
I will show us the way to Earth
Starbuck?
I'm terminating your presidency
as of this moment.
I'm placing you under arrest.
This is mutiny. You know that.
Come.
See the face
of the shape of things to come.
Isn't she beautiful, Gaius?
I'm not a Cylon.
This isn't happening.
You can't fight destiny, Sharon.
It catches up with you.
No matter what you do.
Where are the medics? Where's Doc Cottle?
Off ship, on rounds in the fleet, sir. Stand clear!
Sgt. Fisher reporting, sir.
It's gonna be okay. Okay.
I'm your new shipmate. Bill Adama.
Saul Tigh.
H-he's gonna be okay.
Okay, we've got tension pneumo.
- I'm gonna stick him and release the pressure.
- He's gonna be okay.
What's going o要? What happened?
Sergeant of the guard, secure that thing in the brig.
Aye, sir. Hollis, Wenzler, let's go. Let's go!
Ah! No! Wait!
Okay, he's breathing!
Let's get him down to sickbay, RFN.
What the hell?
Valerii's shot the old man.
What?
Three, one, two
She must be a Cylon,
Colonel's in command. You are second.
Make a hole!
As you were, Captain.
Like hell!
Put him in the brig.
Colonel! Colonel Tigh!
He's my father! Colonel!
Colonel. Could this be
a prelude to a Cylon attack?
How would they know where we are?
Valerii could've told them, sir.
What? How?
When we aboard the base star,
she left the raptor for
a few minutes
and came back without her helmet.
She might've told the Cylons
everything. Our position, defenses
Colonel, the toasters
have knocked out our CO.
This has gotta be part of a bigger plan.
I recommend we execute jump
to urgency standby coordinates.
Colonel, I've located Doc Cottle.
He's aboard the rising star.
Dradis!
Signal of contact, Cylon base
star bearing 4-8-7 carom 0-1-5.
Sir, we can't stay here.
Sir.
So what's your plan here?
Personally, I tend  to go with what you know.
'Til something better turns up.
Sir!
Dee, alert the fleet.
We are making an immediate
jump to the emergency coordinates.
Sir, Doc Cottle is still 15 minutes away.
He'll have to rejoin us
on the other side of the jump.
Sir! What about our people
on the surface of Kobol?
If they're still alive, they'll have to wait.
FTL?
Go!
Nav-con?
Galactica to all vessels.
Prepare to make immediate FTL
jump to escape coordinates alpha.
I say again, escape coordinates alpha.
Clock will start on my mark.
Mark.
Captain, what have they done to you?
What's going on?
My father's been shot.
What?
Someone get this frakkin'
thing off me, please?
I'm not authorized to do that.
I'm behind the frakkin' bars!
Captain.
How bad is your father?
Bad.
Two bullets in the chest.
Is Dr. Cottle with him?
No, Doc Cottle's not on board.
Attention, Galactica. Fleet is away.
Stand by to jump in five,
four, three, two, one
Jump.
Jump completed.
Report.
Report!
Dradis is empty, no contacts.
No contacts?
Where is the fleet?
Dee!
Checking all channels.
No colonial signals.
They're gone, sir.
Isn't she beautiful, Gaius?
I don't think I have ever been
touched so deeply in my entire life.
You're going to make a wonderful father.
Speaking metaphorically, of course.
And literally.
She's our child, gaius.
Our little girl.
What?
Do you want to hold her?
Yes. Yes, of course I do.
But she's not real.
Any more than, uh
any of this is. Real.
She's real.
She is?
She may not be with
you yet, but she will be. Soon.
I'm having a little difficulty...
I'm trying to understand,
I want to understand. I...
You are the mother.
And you're the father.
Am I the father?
Excuse me?
Dream,
I'm been clearly having a dream
We're moving out, sir. Get up.
And if you wouldn't mind carrying
something this time, that'd be great.
This is serisone, it should help
you breathe a little easier.
Here, just take it easy.
You'll be feeling
better in a few minutes.
Excuse me, sir.
We've got to get you up.
- It hurt.
- I know.
If you don't mind my asking,
where are we going, Crashdown?
Tree line. We can hide,
still see the crash site in case
Galactica sends a rescue party.
Galactica will be
sending a rescue party.
Everybody down!
what was that?
That Cylons?
Maybe. Seelix, grab the ammo.
Staggered formation, I'll take point.
Chief, you're bringing up the rear.
Be ready to tell the private, people.
Lt? I think we should double-check
the supplies before we bug out.
Sorry, Chief, we don't
have the time.
If that's an aircraft turbine, they're
gonna be o要 us any moment.
Lt, we gotta make
sure we have everything!
We don't have the time, Chief!
Damn it.
Gods Damn it!
What's going on, saul?
here's the fleet?
We don't know, they
jumped to another location.
You've got blood on your pants.
Why would they do that?
Every watch we update our emergency
jump calculations with new star
fixes to compensate for inertial
drift, and then we transmit
them to the rest of the fleet.
This time ours were updated,
but theirs weren't.
Gaeta was supposed to transmit
them to the rest of the fleet.
So it's Gaeta's fault.
Oh, the kid was overwhelmed.
He had his hands full.
If you say so. It sounds like a
pretty big screw-up to me
I should have checked before
I gave the order to jump!
This doesn't sound like you, Saul.
You don't let people slide.
You bust their ass.
Now, if Bill doesn't make it...
- He'll make it.
- If he doesn't,
this will be your ship,
your command.
All I'm saying is you need...
This is Bill Adama's ship.
This is his command.
His orders are still the word
of the gods on this ship.
Just so we're clear.
This will be Adama's command
until the day he dies.
And we are not going to
let him die.
So say we all.
As you were.
So how do we find the fleet?
If we jump back to our
original coordinates,
our nav computers can use those star
fixes to generate a best fit solution,
given the fleet's current position.
The Cylons are waiting for us back there.
How long will that take to
calculate once we get back there?
If we shut down all
our functions, 12 hours.
There's no way we can hold off
a Cylon base star for 12 hours.
We have got to jump back.
We can't stay here.
Lt Thrace won't be able to find us once
she retrieves the arrow from caprica.
If she retrieves the arrow.
She'll retrieve the arrow.
Captain, you've got to get reinstated.
You've got to get back to CIC.
Gotta denounce me, disavow me,
do whatever you need to do.
Colonel Tigh cannot relocate this
fleet on his own without your father.
Tigh's not letting me out of here.
I put a gun to his head.
He won't forget that anytime soon.
I am so sorry that
I got you into this, Captain.
No, don't apologize.
I knew what I was doing.
But I didn't do it for you.
I did it for
well, actually, I did it
for nothing, turns out.
That's not true.
You took a stand.
And now look at us.
Watch your foot.
Everyone take five.
Give me the med kit.
Where's the med kit?
How you doing?
Hey, how you doing, buddy?
Good.
Just listening to the birds.
I'll be damned. I don't remember
the last time I heard birds.
Take it easy, okay?
Damn it.
We're out of serisone.
It's all right,
I'll get the other med kit.
What other med kit?
Oh, don't frakkin' tell me.
We pulled two med kits from the ship.
I told you to keep an
eye on both of them.
I only saw the o要e, sir.
There were two.
I'm sorry, sir, but
I don't remember you telling me
Well, I did!
Sir, his lungs are
filling up with fluid.
If he doesn't get more serisone soon,
he's not gonna make it.
Okay, Tarn.
You forgot the med kit, so you're
gonna have to go back and get it.
Take a rifle, three clips
of ammo, and a canteen.
What?
Move.
Cally, come here.
Watch the rear.
Lt. You can't send him alone.
You questioning my orders, Chief?
No, I'm just pointing out
flaw in your plan.
Doesn't need to be
ny bigger than that.
Cally and I can go with him.
All right, fine, but
would you look out for Cally?
Cally, give me the rifle.
We three go. Leave that,
leave your backpack.
Sidearms out.
Tarn, you're bringing
up the rear in the middle,
shh. Eyes and ears.
Her consciousness is being downloaded
into another body right now.
And when she wakes up, she'll
tell them exactly where we are.
She's right, we can't stay here.
She's right, huh?
Sharon the Cylon is right.
It's all just,
"listen to Sharon the Cylon."
"Do whatever she says."
Cause that's a good idea.
Hey, Kara, she
helped me get this far.
Okay, I get it. I get it, Helo.
You and I go way back, so I get it.
All right, I remember how you felt about
her, but that is not the real Sharon.
That is some cheap knock-off copy.
I'm not a copy.
I'm Sharon.
I remember the first day
I met you, Starbuck.
You were puking your guts out in the
head because you'd eaten bad oysters on
Don't do that.
Hey!
I don't like it and I don't like you.
So the best thing you can do is
just keep your damn mouth shut.
Starbuck.
Put it down, for gods' sakes.
What do you want from me, Helo?
She's a Cylon.
You've been had.
We've been had.
So what, I'm just supposed
to be nice to her?
Because she says
she's pregnant?
Get out of the way.
No.
Carl, do not think that I will not...
I'm not gonna let you kill her!
Okay? She's carrying my child.
My gods, men are so
painfully stupid sometimes!
How do you know that?
I know, all right?
She is not lying.
They lie about everything, Helo.
Their entire existence is a lie.
They're not human, Helo.
They're machines.
You can't have a baby with a machine.
I don't know what to tell you. Okay?
But I believe her.
I-it's hard to describe.
We've been together a long time.
I mean, I know what she is,
but she is not like the others.
She is not.
No, no, no, no, no!
Bitch took my ride.
How's he doing?
Well, the bullet's tore up his spleen.
His blood pressure is way down.
Somebody needs to get in there and
stop the bleeding, or we'll lose him.
So what's your plan?
Don't really have one.
I'm getting back into the cockpit.
I'm getting back into my fleet.
And I want you to come with me, Saul.
You really believe that we
can get back in the fleet?
Yeah, I do. Yeah, I do.
How long 'til Doc Cotter's aboard?
I don't know.
It's gonna be a while.
He doesn't have  much time, sir.
You're gonna have to go in yourself.
Me? I'm just a medic.
Today you're a doctor.
Colonel.
Open cell.
How's the Commander?
You've bungled the job.
If that's what you're asking.
Then he's alive.
Thank the gods.
How many of our pilots were Cylons?
I don't know.
Who gave the order
to shoot the old man?
No one.
Just get it over with,
you frakkin' coward.
Give me your firearm.
Give me your gun!
Yes, sir.
Just shoot me.
Get it over with.
Okay, Tarn. Go up, take a look.
If it's not there, it's at the raptor.
And we'll have to move up more.
I got it, Chief.
All right, let's get
the hell out of here.
Tarn on point.
Let's go. Go, go, go, go, go.
This makes no sense.
Why am I carrying the med
kit when you forgot it?
First of all that's Lt's kit.
Secondly, I'm o要 point.
Whatever.
All right, children, that's enough.
I'll tell you what, Cally.
If it makes you feel any better,
I'll put him on hangar deck
mop-up duty with you for next week.
Now you're talkin'.
For what?
If anybody should have
mop duty, it's Lt.
Go! Go! Get down!
Top of the ridge!
Cally, take the rifle and cover me!
Suppressive fire.
Okay, okay, wait for me.
Wait for me, all right?
Go, go, go, go, go.
Don't move! I'm coming
for you, don't move.
Jeez! 'm coming. Give me fire! Cally, go, go!
They're dug in, Chief. I can't see them.
Cover me! Come on. Come on.
Come on Chief
You'll be okay, you're okay.
You're okay, you're okay. It's okay.
Get on my back. Get on my back.
Get on me, get on me.
Chief, they're not
following us anymore.
Cally, there. There.
I know you're hit, buddy.
It's okay, I'm gonna check you right
now. I'm gonna put him here, Cal
Here, stay down.
Be with me right here.
Okay, I'm gonna check you right now.
It's not that bad, it's not that bad.
It's not that bad. Cally, check the ridge.
I wanna go home, Chief.
I know, I know. We're going home.
We're going home, okay? Okay.
Sh, sh, sh, sh. It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay. Stay with me.
Hey, hey. Look at me. Look at me.
Stay with me, stay with me.
Be with me, be with me.Come on,
come on. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Chief.
Chief, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
Chief.
That's it. That's it,
you stupid, frakked-up crap!
Chief, Socinus needs
us now. Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
Not your fault, Lieutenant.
Not from where I was standing.
I was the O.O.D.
It was crazy in there, sir.
Can't blame yourself.
So we jump back to
the last coordinates.
But we network the FTL computer with
a nav, dc, and fire control computers.
Once they're linked, we'll only need
ten minutes to complete the calculations.
You can't be serious.
The old man would never
do this, Colonel.
- No computer networks on his ship.
- I acknowledge that, sir.
But I can devise a software
firewall that will buy us more time.
Really, you're gonna out-think
the Cylons at computer software?
Sir, if we don't do this,
we're never gonna find the fleet.
Certainly not
before the commander dies.
This is still
the old man's command.
We can't do
something he'd oppose,
especially when it puts
the entire ship at risk.
This is the XO.
Begin jump prep.
Those are  my orders.
The kid is back in the fleet.
So, let's have the truth.
How did you do it? How'd you
get off this frakkin' freighter?
Connections.
Anne's father has a friend
on the defense subcommittee.
So the new wife comes through.
Wish I had in-laws with pull.
Gimme a couple of years.
I'll have some pull.
You watch me.
I'll have my own battlestar one day.
Open up, please.
All right.
You have my parole.
When I'm on duty, I'll make no attempt to
free her or sow insurrection among the crew.
And when I'm not o要 duty,
I'll report directly back to this cell.
Pre-flight brief is
underway in the ready room.
Right.
Good hunting, Captain.
Thank you, Madam President!
Colonel, once you find the fleet,
I'd like to have a word with you.
There's nothing to talk about. You went
up against the old man and you lost.
We jump in, we hold off the Cylons.
We crunch the numbers.
Then we jump out.
That's it. Simple plan.
Not so simple to do.
Computers have been networked.
My board is green, sir.
All stations report ready to jump.
That software firewall ready?
Best I can make it, sir.
Wish Dr. Baltar was here.
To hell with that. Take your work over
that shifty son of a bitch any day.
Stand by. In five, four,
three, two, jump.
Jump completed.
Report?
Multiple dradis contacts.
Cylon base star and multiple
Cylon raiders bearing  4-8-7 carom 2-2-1.
Lieutenant.
Computations underway.
We'll be able to plot the
fleet's position in seven minutes.
Whoohoo! Ha ha ha! Let's get these psychos!
Hey flyboy, you know we got
a pool going, right?
See who gets the most
kills now that Starbuck's awol.
Well, we know i'm gonna clean up.
Flyboys, shut up and focus.
This is not a simulation.
Roger that.
His heart stopped!
Defib, now!
Power's unstable,the battery
units are at the aid stations.
Well, then, get me a knife.
Weapons free.
And open racks.
And engage!
Here they come.
Cylons are hacking our network.
Attempting to access our gateway.
Now it's a race.
First firewall penetrated.
Sierra Alpha, we got a new bogey.
What is that thing?
I don't know, but whatever it is,
it's bearing on Galactica.
We gotta take it out.
Apollo, Hotdog offensive.
Three right, five at two.
Tally, Hotdog.  Count on me.
Roger that. I'm with you, leader.
Will you pray with me?
Help us, Lords of Kobol.
Help your prophet Laura guide
us to the path of righteousness.
That we might...
that we might destroy our enemies.
Let us walk the path of righteousness
and lift our faces unto your goodness.
Help us turn away from
the calls of the wicked
and show us the knowledge
of your certain salvation.
We offer this prayer.
Calculations at 56%.
Second firewall's been breached.
Frak they're fast!
Third firewall down!
Approaching Galactica's  flak barrier.
Cylon target within gun range.
Winged it!
Apollo! We're straying into
Galactica's engagement zone!
I'm almost there, I'm almost there.
I'm almost there, come on!
Back! Back, back!
Damn it!
I had it!
Apollo reports impact
on the starboard flight pod.
You got a decompression
in the flight pod.
No explosion. No fire.
Repeat, no fire.
No fire.
Calculations at 80%. Almost there.
They're through the fourth firewall.
One left until they've
accessed our mainframe.
Frakker.
Whoo! That was mine, that was mine!
Come on, come on.
We have a solution
for the fleet's position.
Break the network.
Network is broken!
Computers restored to local control.
Tell the vipers to get back aboard.
We're getting awful lucky today.
Prepare to jump.
Vipers aboard, sir.
Stand by.
In five, four, three, two, jump.
Jump completed.
Report?
Multiple contacts 'round the board.
Colonial transponder, sir. We found 'em!
Captain Kelly.
- Lieutenant Gaeta.
- Sir.
Dee.
Contact the Rising Star.
Tell Cottle to get his
ass over here A.S.A.P.
Hell of a job.
From now on, no more
heart massages for me.
I'm sticking to
pills and enemas.
Sir.
Let's hear it.
Well, I managed to stop the bleeding.
Um, but  he's still critical.
Doc's on his way.
Can you hear me, Bill?
Go away.
Captain Tigh, It's the shore patrol.
Sergeant Watkins, sir.
Open up, please.
Major Adama's compliments.
He wishes me to inform you you've
been reinstated in the colonial fleet.
With the rank of Captain.
Major Adama.
Welcome back to the fleet, sir.
I'll be right with you, Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
You never should have
brought me back in the service.
If you'd just let me be, I'd have
died back there in Caprica along with
everyone else, and
been happier for it.
I don't want to command.
I never did
Don't you dare die on me now
-= Legendas & Sync: Fr0g =-