The Cylons were created by man.
They evolved.
They rebelled.
There are many copies.
And they have a plan.
Previously on Battlestar Galactica:
This will be Adama's command
until the day he dies.
And we are not going to
let him die.
Sir! What about our people
on the surface of Kobol?
If they're still alive,
they'll have to wait.
Lt? I think we should double-check
the supplies before we bug out.
We don't have the time.
I could give you a shot,
but you wouldn't like the side effects.
Just do it.
The time is going to come when you won't
be able to hide what you're going through.
Sir, his lungs are
filling up with fluid.
If he doesn't get more serisone soon,
he's not gonna make it.
Tarn, you forgot the med kit, so you're
gonna have to go back and get it.
Take a rifle, three clips
of ammo, and a canteen.
Too late.
He's not gonna make it.
I'm sorry, Chief.
Lords of Kobol,
take these brave men into your arms.
Take upon...
in your arms the spirits
of our fallen friends,
so that they may share in
the everlasting life
that awaits us all beyond the vale of tears.
So say we all.
Nothing awaits them.
No eternal life, no damnation.
Only oblivion.
Because they haven't seen
the face of God, I take it.
Because they died here.
On Kobol.
- I see.
- Doc...
Let's go.
We're moving out.
Doc, you hear me?
- We're moving out.
- I did hear you, Chief.
I just don't respond to the title "Doc."
A "dock" is a platform for
loading and unloading material.
My title is "Doctor," or
"Mr. Vice President," if you don't mind.
You are loading, are you not?
El-tee?
Crash!
Hmm? Oh, yeah, Chief,
I'll be right there.
- No Cylons.
- You sure?
Uh-oh. Wait a minute.
Tree-line, two o'clock.
- Got 'em.
- What are they doing?
- Looks like they're dismantling the ship.
- Why?
Why not just use it to fly
the hell out of here?
I don't know.
I can't tell.
They're... dragging it into the tree-line.
It's, uh... oh, wait oh minute.
They're building something.
- Chief, is that a...
- A missile.
They're building a missile battery.
Well, at least we know
why they're not chasing us.
Why?
- Why aren't they chasing us?
- Because they don't have to.
They can just sit back,
launch a missile barrage
that'll wipe out every
living thing in this valley.
Next time I say I'm in a hurry,
cycle the damn air lock faster.
Is this your first day?
Doctor, thank the Gods, you're here.
The President needs your help.
- Move.
- Doctor...
Doctor!
Okay... let's have some vitals.
Like now.
Two bullets, 9 mm.
This one lacerated the spleen,
the other one nicked the aorta.
Now, we've removed the spleen,
and we thought we repaired the aorta, but--
Over the past few hours,
his BP'S dropped down again.
It's only 80 over 40.
And his heart rate's creeping
into the 130s.
Well, you missed something.
He's still hemorrhaging somewhere.
We're gonna lose him unless
we can stop that bleeding.
Get me an ABG, CBC and coags,
and get set up for a rapid
sequence intubation.
- Is he gonna make it?
- How should I know?
I'm not a psychic.
Now get the hell out of here.
Fragged
EN Subtitles by Laddin
bsg.ic.cz
fixed by Mersault
47,862 Survivors
In search of a home
Called Earth
Earth
It is a mess in here.
Looks like the mesenteric
artery may have been damaged.
3.7 mac.
God damn it, Kim, learn the instruments.
I said a 3.7 mac!
Sorry.
Clamp. Clamp!
Dr. Cottle, his pressure's dropping.
It's 60 on 30.
Heart rate's starting to fall.
I don't think he can last much longer.
Just stay focused.
Get some more suction in here
so I can see what I'm doing.
Ahem. Colonel...
how's the Commander?
What?
- Uh, ahem, how's the Commander?
- He's still in surgery.
What's on your mind?
Uh, I need some medication
for the President.
She's not the President anymore.
Cottle's a little busy right now.
Sir, she's very ill...
Why aren't you in the brig?
Um... because...
no one put me in there?
What the hell's all this?
Why aren't you in the brig?
I'm on duty, Sir.
Planning the search and rescue mission.
Search and rescue?
For who?
We lose a plane, and nobody tells me?!
For our Raptor crew down
on the surface of Kobol, Sir?
Simes is senior pilot now.
He can plan the SAR.
You asked me to command the
air group when I'm on duty.
So am I in command... or not?
What's the status of
the SAR, Captain?
Well, we don't know in what
area Raptor 3 went down.
So the only realistic chance
we have of finding her is to hope
that her transponder disaster
beacon is still functioning.
I intend to take two Raptors,
one with medical personnel,
and make five low level
orbits of the planet.
What about the Cylon base ship
that Lieutenant Valerii supposedly destroyed?
What if she was lying?
Racetrack confirmed the
destruction of the base ship,
and I checked the gun camera
footage from the Raptors,
which verifies it.
Lieutenant Gaeta,
why are you hovering about?
- Uh, it's the press.
- The press?
They're demanding to know
how much longer we plan on holding them,
and when they can
contact their home ships.
They demand? They're in no
position to demand anything.
You tell them to shut their yaps.
We'll get to them in due time.
Excuse me, Colonel.
Shuttle from the Zephyr has just requested
permission to enter the landing pattern.
- The Zephyr?
- Yes, Sir.
Evidently the Quorum of Twelve is aboard.
They're demanding to see you.
They demand?
Demanding job,
commanding a Battlestar.
Clear them to land.
Put them in the ward room
and hold them there until
I have time to see them.
Madam President.
What's wrong with her?
I don't know, but she's clearly sick.
You can see that, can't you?
Well, there's nothing I can do.
- Madam President...
- Yes?
Can I get you anything
while you're in the brig?
Really?
No, thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm finding it... hard to think.
It's withdrawal.
- The chamalla?
- Yes.
I'm trying to get you more.
Go fast.
I count... six missiles being
carried into the forest site so far.
It's all so pointless.
We kill them.
And they kill us.
So we kill more of them.
They kill more of us.
What's the point anymore?
You and your...
race invented murder.
Invented killing for sport, greed, envy.
It's man's one true art form.
You've done some killing
of your own, I think.
Yes, well, we're your children.
You taught us well.
Why does God want to bring
a child into this kind of world anyway?
Because, despite everything,
despite all of it,
he still wants to offer you salvation.
Our child will bring
that salvation, but only if you
accept your role as her father.
And her guardian.
I'm not ready for that.
All right?
I'm not a father.
I'm not a guardian.
I'm not a moral leader
capable of leading anyone.
Let alone a baby.
Be a man, Gaius.
What?
Be a man.
Whatever else
you are, you are that.
The time is coming when
you'll have to act like one.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
El-tee, check this out.
What do you got, Chief?
45 degrees east of the launcher.
You see that tree stump?
- What the hell is that?
- It looks like a dradis dish.
At least, the Cylon version of a dradis dish.
It's probably salvaged from
the nose cone of the ship.
They're building an anti-aircraft battery.
Anti-aircraft? For what?
There are no other aircraft around here.
The Galactica's gonna send
a search and rescue team.
When they do, that's at least two
Raptors doing a low pass over the crash site.
When those Raptors come looking for us,
risking their lives to rescue us...
Cylons will shoot 'em down.
Seven birds down for repairs.
Three out on picket duty with the cap.
Uh, con traffic, Sir.
Priority messages are on top.
Cut to the chase, Captain!
How long before you launch the SAR?
Come on, Dee,
these are all marked "priority."
Sorry, Sir, that's how they came in.
I'm cannibalizing 305 for parts.
Should be up in the air in,
I don't know, 90 minutes.
90 minutes?!
We got men down on that frakking planet!
Get your head in the game.
You do your job, or go back to the brig.
Are on the members of
the Quorum in the ward room?
All 12, Sir.
Don't suppose you wanna do this for me?
Never was much for public speaking, Sir.
So why are we here under guard?
That's what I want to know.
Laura Roslin suborned mutiny
and sedition aboard this ship.
She caused a key military
asset to be lost at a critical moment!
The Commander felt he had no choice
but to remove her from power.
- You've said that, several times.
- Well, ...
You don't seem to be listening, Colonel.
It does not matter what Adama felt.
- He had absolutely no authority...
- Adama knew exactly what he was doing.
He was paving the way to declare martial
law and usher in a military dictatorship.
- Isn't that right, Colonel?
- I can't speak for the Commander.
He's still in surgery.
Well, you seem to be giving
the orders around here.
So what exactly are you planning to do?
- Are you declaring martial law?
- Absolutely not.
I know for a fact that the old man
hated the very idea of martial law.
He believed in freedom and
democracy and all that good stuff.
Well, since this is still a...
democracy, and all that good stuff,
I move that the Quorum demand
immediate access to President Roslin.
Excellent. I second it.
All those in favor.
Aye.
Motion carries. Colonel,
we demand immediate
access to the President.
I will take your "demand"
under advisement.
Madam President.
- I have to consider...
- Laura. Laura.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Are you all right?
I, uh, just came down to see if
there was anything I could do for you.
Anything I can get you?
I would like to have a conversation
with my attorney.
Could you arrange that?
Yeah. Yeah, sure, right.
Laura, do you know where you are?
I'm in jail.
- What's my name?
- Have we met?
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
There's just...
a ringing.
Excuse me.
Ringing?
Right.
Okay, then.
Take care.
Oh, my Gods.
Ellen Tigh.
Ellen?
Lords of Kobol...
The launcher looks like a simple
point-and-shoot. No built-in guidance.
Ordnance appear to be standard
ship-to-ship missiles.
They're modifying them for
atmospheric flight.
one Cylon Centurion walks the perimeter,
stopping at regular intervals.
The dradis dish that controls
the missiles is on the 4.5 kg wavelength,
judging by the diameter.
It's guarded by two
Centurions, I think.
I'm sorry, Doc, did you say it
was guarded by two Centurions?
Yes, I did.
Okay, is the dradis guarded
continuously of intermittently?
I saw two Centurions
through the field glasses...
continuously, for five minutes.
In that time, they didn't leave their post.
So there's three toasters near the launcher.
Two more out by the dish.
That's a lot of Cylons.
You ever handle a weapon?
Who, me?
No.
I'm not a soldier, Crashdown.
I'll try to give you the most simple
assignment, but I'm gonna need every man.
You're not suggesting
we attack the Cylons?
We owe it to Socinus and Tarn
to tack the frakkers
out before they kill anyone else.
We have equal numbers.
We have the element of surprise.
Therefore, we have the initiative.
We can attack at the time
and place of our choosing.
El-tee, a word... in private.
He's crazy.
I'm not trained for this kind of thing.
I've never fired a gun in my life.
I haven't fired one since basic.
You?
I just joined to pay for dental school.
Basic ground assault was
a long time ago. For all of us.
Those aren't training officers out there.
They're programmed killing machines.
We don't have any choice.
Galactica will definitely be sending
a search and rescue party,
It's just a matter of time.
And if we don't take out that launcher...
we can't go up against an armed
and defended position like that.
- They'll wipe us out in the first
two minutes. - That's enough!
Chief, look, under the circumstances,
it's important that you keep your cool.
- I don't believe I've lost my cool.
- I disagree.
Look, I don't want to attack
the launcher either, but it's our duty.
We owe it to the rescue party,
and we owe it to Socinus and Tarn.
I fail to see what this has
to do with Socinus and Tarn.
Maybe that's why I'm an officer,
and you're not.
Dismissed.
This briefing will outline
a plan of attack in five graphs.
Graph one: Situation.
Our situation is that we are stranded on
Kobol with a group of five Cylons
who plan to use an AAU
to destroy any SAR craft sent to find us.
There are no friendly forces present.
What's all this graph business?
- Graph two...
- It's a five-paragraph order.
It's a basic command tool.
It's taught at officer candidate school.
It's just not usually used this...
literally in the field.
Graph four: Execution.
We will assault the Cylon launch
site from the northwest, using...
Oh, come on.
This is absurd.
What, we're talking on
the Cylon army, are we?
Us?
Look at us.
What, with two rifles and a canteen?
- Have you lost your mind?
- That's enough, Doctor.
Is it? Look, no disrespect,
but why are we always going uphill?
Does anybody else think
that this plan is frakking nuts?
I'll tell you what's fair. This is fair.
We'll have a show of hands...
No!
Absolutely not!
This is not a democracy!
The El-Tee's in charge!
The El-Tee's in charge.
No ifs, no ands, no buts.
He say we go, we go.
There's no questions...
We've already lost two men, Chief!
How many more people are we gonna lose?
You need to sit down.
And shut up right now.
Nobody tells me to shut up.
I'm the Vice President...
You need to sit down
and shut up right now.
Your briefing, El-Tee.
Thank you, Chief.
Graph four.
We'll approach the Cylon launch
site from the northwest,
using natural ground
cover to mask our approach.
Our objective is the command and control
console. once we reach this position,
Cally, you're gonna flank out to the left,
making a feint on the Cylon position.
Hopefully drawing their
fire long enough for me and Seelix
to flank out to the right and
get a shot at the console.
Tyrol, you and the Vice President
will stay at position one,
and provide covering fire for
both flanking maneuvers.
I have been given the opportunity to
perceive the scriptures more clearly.
Anything that impedes that,
I have to view as contrary to
the survival of the human species.
This is ridiculous.
Look, she obviously needs her medication.
I keep trying to tell anyone that'll listen.
Sounds like she's talking about
the scrolls of the Prophet Pythia.
I suppose.
Pythia foretold the rise of a leader.
A leader who would lead all
humanity to salvation.
So say the Gods.
Impedes that action...
You seem to know a lot
about the scriptures.
I'm from Gemenon. We believe in
the literal truth of the scriptures.
Contrary to the survival of the human...
Corporal Venner?
There's a, uh, a drug that
priests sometimes use.
It's called chamalla extract.
- Guess it's happy hour.
- What's happy about it?
The old man is still in surgery.
And I got a boatload of politicians
and press demanding to see Laura Roslin.
- Let 'em.
- Yeah, right.
- She's crazy.
- I know.
No, no. Really, Saul.
She's lost it. I just went
down to the brig to see her.
- You did?
- She's...
completely nuts.
She doesn't even know
where she is anymore.
- You're kidding.
- You should let 'em see her.
The press, the Quorum.
All of 'em.
I mean, the little schoolteacher's
mind has gone bye-bye.
And the Vice President is
either missing or dead.
That leaves you in unchallenged
command of this ship.
- And this fleet. - Just until the
old man gets back on his feet.
Well, of course.
Galactica, Apollo. We are
preparing to jump to Kobol.
Roger that, Apollo.
You are clear to jump.
And good hunting.
Thank you, Galactica.
Let's go find our people.
Okay, cock the rifle,
click the safety, open the scope.
One of you will turn against the others.
- During the mission?
- Yes.
- One of us will betray the others?
- During the attack?
- Yes.
But if the attack fails?
You'll die.
Not me.
I am God's instrument.
God turned his back on Kobol.
Turned his back on man and
the false Gods he worshiped.
What happens on Kobol is not his will.
Saddle up.
It's time to junk some toasters.
XO.
Combat.
Dualla here, Sir.
The Quorum is demanding to
see the former President.
They're being pretty adamant and
they're giving the sentries a hard time.
Uh, maybe we should tell them to
shove their demand
up their collective asses,
how about that?
Yes, Sir. I need
instructions for the sentries.
- They're asking how to respond.
- Tell them that they are going to get to see
what has become of their precious
President. You tell them that.
I got a transponder signal.
Definitely Colonial.
Trying to establish a lock.
Got it.
Northern hemisphere.
Looks like mountainous terrain.
There's a valley.
Take us out of orbit.
Signal Raptor Two to form up on us.
There they are.
All three of 'em, right where
they're supposed to be.
All right, people, this is it.
We're going in.
Cally, move up the tree-line
to point alpha.
El-tee, there's five Cylons
at the launch site.
What?
Something's wrong, isn't it?
Something's wrong with the plan...
Quiet down, There's nothing wrong.
There's just a couple Cylons that
we didn't account for.
That makes for seven Cylons.
Five here, and
two up at the dish.
Are you absolutely certain about
the two guards at the dish?
I know what I saw.
Maybe there are only five Cylons.
They just changed their deployment.
They brought the two that
were guarding the dish down here.
Now the dish is unprotected.
Gods, Chief, that dish is,
like, almost a click away.
So what?
It's unprotected. We can go take it out.
We don't have to take on
the whole Cylon army.
- What the hell was that?
- Sonic booms.
Spacecraft entering
the upper atmosphere.
It's the SAR mission. They're here.
They are right up there, Chief.
We gotta go.
There's no time for discussion.
All right, everyone, move out.
It's game time. We're taking these toasters
out before they kill any more of us.
- Cally, I said move.
- I can't.
What?
That's an order.
She doesn't have to.
We can just go take out the dish.
Cally, you have to move.
Cally, this is not a joke.
Go. This is not a game, Cally.
Go. We have people counting on us.
They're up there, Cally.
Move!
Listen to me. We still have time to
double back and take out the dish.
Shut up for a second. Cally, Cally.
Specialist. You have your orders.
I need you to go out there and
create a distraction now!
Move!
- Move!
- Lt.
There were only supposed to be
three Cylons and now there are five.
How are we supposed to
take on five Cylons?
Frak orders, frak court marshal.
Our people are up there.
We have to save them.
We don't have any time.
Move!
- I can't do it.
- I said move!
No!
Chief!
Put it down.
You're going out there, Cally.
You're going out there or
I'm gonna blow your brains out.
Right here, right now.
Put it down.
- Hey, El-Lee. Easy.
- Take it easy.
I'm gonna count to three.
This is crazy.
This is crazy!
One.
Put it down right now.
Oh, my Gods.
Listen to me!
Drop your weapon.
Two.
Three.
Fall back! Fall back!
Go! Go! Go!
Doc, Let's go!
Now you're a man.
- ETA?
- Five minutes!
Oh, Cally!
Doc! Gimme the launcher!
Gimme the launcher, Doc!
Come on!
Missiles!
There's a battery down there!
Evasive!
Break, break, break!
No lock. No lock!
They're not locking on us.
Chief.
Stay there!
Chief!
You're welcome.
- Viewing time at the zoo.
- Glad to see you hold the President...
- ...in such high esteem.
- Your day's gonna come, laughing boy.
Let's go.
I don't know, what to do.
All right, the show is over.
Let's give her some privacy.
Everybody out.
Let's go back to the ward room
and we'll, uh,
talk about the business of
how we proceed from here.
Thank you all for coming.
I have a statement I'd like to make.
The attempted military coup
against the lawful government of
the colonies is illegal, ill-advised and
clearly doomed to failure.
I have not resigned the Presidency and
I will fight this action with
everything at my command.
She's crazy, she's nuts. She thinks
she a prophet or some such nonsense.
Just hold on Colonel let her speak.
Just ask her, ask her, she'll tell you.
Just listen to her.
What was it, the uhh,
the Arrow of Apollo will open the uhh, the
Tomb of Artemis. Or some such nonsense.
Everything I've done is
consistent and logical.
We have found Kobol,
we have found the city of the Gods
and when we retrieve the arrow
we will open the tomb of Athena
and we find the road to Earth.
Madam President, have you
read the Scrolls of Pythia?
Many times, and I humbly
believe I am fulfilling the role
of the leader.
Okay, enough of this
nonsense, everyone out.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Sarah. You represent Gemenon,
you know more about the scrolls and
the scriptures than anyone else here,
why don't you speak up?
The scrolls tell us that a dying
leader will lead us to salvation.
She's not dying.
She's crazy.
I am dying.
I have terminal breast cancer.
Dr. Cottle will verify the diagnosis.
I have a few months to live.
And in that time, I will lead
the people to salvation.
It is my sole purpose.
Praise be to the Gods.
Here is our salvation.
- Sergeant of the guard,
- Yes, Sir.
Remove these people from the brig and
escort them back to their shuttle.
Yes, Sir.
Thank you, Corporal.
Thank the Gods.
It's a hell of a butchers Bill, Chief.
How did Crashdown die?
Leading the charge.
He gave his life in the...
in the finest tradition of the service.
Yeah. He was a hero.
To the end.
I'm so proud of you Gaius.
Why?
- 'Cause I've taken a life?
- It's what makes you human.
Is it?
Not conscious thought?
Not poetry or art or music, literature?
Murder.
Murder is my heritage.
Is that the lesson I'm supposed to
pass on to our child?
Shh. It'll be all right, Gaius.
Okay, Doctor, let's go!
Doctor, come on!
We gotta go.
I'll be your conscience.
Come on, Doctor!
We gotta get outta here!
He'll live.
When will he wake up?
Knowing him, when he damn well
wants to, probably.
I really frakked things up for you, Bill.
The events which took place aboard
Colonial one are unfortunate.
Laura Roslin's actions in
suborning mutiny and
sedition among the military
could not be tolerated.
Therefore Commander Adama was left with no
choice other than to remove her from office.
Miss Roslin is now resting comfortably
aboard this ship,
where she will remain until such time
as the Commander deems otherwise.
As it appears obvious that
the government cannot function
under the current circumstances,
I have decided to dissolve
the Quorum of Twelve.
And as of this moment,
I have declared martial law.
- Get those people the hell off my ship.
- Yes, Sir.