Previously
on Battlestar Galactica...
Hi, um...
we're-we're kinda lost again.
We're trying to get
to the CIC. Could you-
alking,
no talking, please.
No cheating.
Hold it up a little higher.
Eight.
Sneaky.
Nine.
Uh... start again.
You lost track.
Zero.
I've asked you here
to find out
why the Cylons
hate us so much.
It's what you said
at the ceremony.
That humanity
was a flawed creation.
And that people still
kill one another
for petty jealousy
and greed.
HmYosaid that humanity
never asked itself
why it deserved to survive.
Maybe you don't.
Sleeper... agents...
within the Fleet.
Takeover by brute force...
Cylon impregnation...
and reproduction...
Multiple models...
suicide bombings...
assault on natural resources.
Eyewitnesses claim to have seen
one of the known Cylon models
moving in and out
of Galactica's brig.
Admiral Adama
has made no comment
on this situation.
We will continue to-
How the hell did this
get out to the press?
I'm surpri
it didn't happen sooner.
m told you've been meeting
with her regularly,
allowing her to interact
with members of your crew.
She's a military asset,
providing us with vital
strategic intelligence.
While we pray
that she's not somehow...
colluding
with other Cylons.
If I felt for one second
that she posed some kind
of a threat to this fleet,
I'd pull the trigger
on her myself.
I think the fleet
may need to hear that,
Admiral.
Even more,
they need ve it.
Someone took theto vitamins
this morning.
Yeah, I don't know
what got into me.
No, you're right.
Keeping Sharon Valerii alive,
allowing her pregnancy
to continue-
There is no road map
for any of this.
Somebody,
somebody has got to keep
asking the hard questions.
I agree. I wanna stay ahead of this.
Acknowledge the Cylons'
existence, and then make...
some kind of case for her
to stay aboard Galactica.
I don't think
that's gonna work.
What?
Why?
I think you need
to trust the people.
Use the press,
tell them the truth.
I mean, we barely know
anything about the Cylons.
And until we learn more,
we're not gonna destroy
the only source of information
that we have, period.
Period.
That simple, huh?
Uh... well...
Um, could I-
could I have a minute?
Sure.
Important? Mm-hmm.
You were saying
about the hard questions...
I know it's just my
debate team ring,
but it's the best I could do.
This... this really isn't
how I planned it.
Anyway, um...
Billy...
I love you.
I've loved you since-
since the first day I met you.
I mean, you were half naked,
granted...
I know that I kind of
blindsided you with this.
Okay? I mean, it doesn't have
to be tomorrow.
We can take our time.
Billy, I can't marry you.
I don't know how else
to say it.
I'm sorry.
He pulled out that ring...
and it was like
an electric shock.
I could barely say anything.
Well, maybe you're regretting
that you didn't say yes.
No.
I don't know what to make
of me and Billy, but...
I know I can't marry him.
Then again, I don't know what
to make of you and me either.
'Scuse me.
Hey, two more.
Coming right up.
Ellen.
It's, uh...
it's... good to see you.
It's good to see you,
Captain.
Dee.
Billy.
I didn't know
you were coming down here.
I, um... I grabbed
a two-day rotation.
I thought I'd grab
some R & R.
I'm on business,
as usual.
Captain Adama.
Oh...
I really am an idiot,
aren't I?
No, Billy-
Don't.
Don't bother. Can you give us a minute?
No, you know what?
Have a seat, Captain.
Be my guest.
Billy, I'm sorry.
I thought if anything,
we were honest
with each other.
But you knew you were gonna
be here with him today,
and you let me propose
to you. I didn't-
I know that giving you
that ring was stupid.
That's fine.
And maybe this wasn't
gonna work out between us.
But this...
You should've told me
about this.
Well, it's hard, you know?
To choose the people
we fall in love with.
To love only one person
at a time.
People like us...
are more complicated.
Us?
I'm sorry.
I'm here with friends.
Ellen, you're a regular
here, right?
You ever see
that woman before?
In the corner?
Oh... only when I came in
and wondered
when they were gonna start
enforcing a dress code.
Ellen, the bathroom's
over here.
Are you serious?
Let's go.
Lee Adama,
you amaze me.
Shh.
This is it now.
You ready?
Yes.
We're with you.
Do it.
Everybody by the bar!
Now! Move!
You, you-t up against the bar
Oh, my gods.
Three men, one wan,
all armed.
Is it true
the Fleet knows
I'm on Galactica?
I'm interested
in navigational weaknesses.
Worm holes, dark matter
blind spots.
Likely ambushes.
I would avoid
these pulsar pointers
because of dradis
interference.
If I was gonna plan
an ambush, I'd do it there.
It depends, Admiral.
They adapt to your every move.
Every move
triggers a counter-move.
Adapt.
That's what
you're good at, right?
Why won't you
answer my question?
Does the Fleet know
I'm on Galactica?
Mm.
It's the baby.
She's kicking.
The Fleet knows.
That'll be all
for today.
Guards.
You know, if people knew
how much you've relied
on that thing's
so-called intelligence,
they'd be scared
out of their wits.
What about you, Saul?
Are you afraid of her?
You know,
the truth is...
I don't like the way
it gotten under your skin.
What are you doing?
The pressure hatch can withstand
explosive decompression.
The only way help's getting in
is with a raft
of high explosives.
Or we could just let
these clowns
open the pressure door for us.
There's bound to be a security
force on its way soon.
Open the door for us?
Why would they do that?
Gimme your drink.
Let me talk to them.
The ice-
I need the dry ice.
Okay, stay calm.
Ellen!
Please don't shoot.
Who are you?
Ellen Tigh.
Get over here. Now.
Move.
We are not criminals.
We are members of the Fleet,
just like you.
My husband's XO of Galactica.
You've just made the worst
mistakes of your life.
Colonel Tigh, Admiral-
you need to hear this.
Saul-
Ellen? What's wrong?
They're holding us hostage.
They're threatening
to kill us!
My name is Sesha Abinell.
I have seized control
of the Cloud Nine lounge...
and held the people in it
hostage.
What do you want?
What I want...
This is not about...
what I want.
The Colonial Fleet
has become
a Cylon-occupied territory.
You are working in collusion
with a Cylon agent-
The very same model
of a Cylon
who tried to murder you,
Admiral Adama,
on your own ship.
We want Sharon Valerii.
You have two hours.
Get me everything you can
on Sesha Abinell.
Yes, sir.
Sesha Abinell...
Fleet records indicate
she's the widow
of a Ray Abinell.
He was a casualty aboard
the Greenleaf freighter
when the Cylons hit it
about ten weeks ago.
Widow.
Who do we have
aboard Cloud Nine?
Uh, rotation schedule shows...
Captain Adama,
half a Marine squad,
and Starbuck's already there
on R & R.
Get me Starbuck
right away.
Yes, sir.
Hell, one of you beauties has
got to be an O-2 sensor.
And I'm guessing it's you.
Take a sip
of carbon dioxide.
There was another guy
at the bar.
Check the back.
We don't want any more mistakes.
Kern, ere's anawful lot
of military types here.
And that's why we're here.
To get Galactica's
attention, remember?
Page.
You go.
No problem.
Good to see ya, Gunny.
I'm gonna need
some of those gorillas
you call Marines.
Most of my gorillas
are already here, sir.
Just trying to cop
a little R & R.
Tell me about it.
All right,
here's what we know.
We got an unknown number
of shooters
at least 20 hostages.
And about a 90-minute window
before they start
throwing out bodies.
You got a plan, sir?
Lock and load.
Let's figure out the rest
as we go along.
Put your weapon down.
Tell them.
He says he's Captain Adama
from the Galactica.
He just wants to talk.
Talk, that's it.
Just talk.
They're together.
Put it down.
Or she dies.
Hey, she dies, he dies,
you get it?
Difference is,
you won't do it.
He will.
Okay?
We all have someone
we care about.
It's his son.
He's not gonna choose the Cylon
over his son.
Get in line with the others.
CO-2 is through the roof.
They're trying
to suffocate us.
What is this, a trap?
There's a reason
you don't just start shooting
on a spaceship.
You probably nicked a line.
Why don't you let me
talk to the Admiral,
see if we can't
find a way out of this?
I've got
two strike teams
inbound to you.
ETA ten minutes.
We'll have plenty of fire power,
so that's good.
But I'm concerned
with limited accesedints.
Admiral.
It's Abinell.
Keep Starbuck
on the line with us.
Adama.
We're losing oxygen.
If it's not restored,
the hostages die.
Then you'll all die.
Because this is over.
Not until the Cylon's dead.
I'm willing to die
to see this through.
You willing to risk
your son's life?
Son of a bitch.
Suddenly you're listening.
Gods damn it,
give her what she wants!
Give her the Cylon!
You're all alone
on this, Admiral.
I'm not gonna sacrifice
a military asset
on your altar of revenge.
What are you talking about?
This isn't a-
You said this was about us
being played by the Cylons.
But it isn't.
It's about the loss of your
husband, and I understand that.
It's about you wanting
to strike back,
and I understand that too.
But we've all lost people
that we care about.
An learn to live with it.
I am sure
you are aware, Admiral,
of the concrete evidence...
that Caprica's defenses
were compromised
by a Cylon agent
who infiltrated
the Ministry of Defense
on the eve of the attacks.
People look
for complicated answers
when something terrible
happens.
Maybe we were just
caught by surprise
and were beaten.
And maybe we have to learn
to live with that.
And maybe you are
just missing the point.
You were infiltrated.
You.
The military.
And you are being infiltrated
again right now.
You can sit there and pretend
you know what you're doing,
but you do not.
You are being played.
And the rest of us do not want
to go down with your ship.
I want this air system
restored right now.
One person comes in alone,
fixes it, leaves.
Anything goes wrong,
somebody gets hurt,
it's on your head.
Keep a direct line open
to Cloud Nine.
What do we do?
We repair the air system.
Saul, we can't
give her Sharon.
I hope you
know that, right?
I know that.
We can't start dealing
with the terrorists.
We start now,
it'll open the floodgates,
and it'll never stop.
But by the way,
it's not "Sharon".
It's a frakkin' Cylon.
You don't think I know that?
I think there's part of you that
looks into that thing's eyes
and still sees that yo trl
that reported aboard two years
ago as a rook pilot.
Well, it's not.
It never was.
Bill, it's a machine.
Admiral?
It's Captain Thrace.
Sitrep.
I had one
of the Cloud Nine techs
double-check the oxygen feed
in there.
There's nothing wrong
with the air.
Could be a glitch.
Or maybe someone screwed
with one of the CO-2 censors
inrs bar.
Lee.
Why?
Maybe he's giving us
an opening.
If I can get someone inside,
get a clear idea
of what we're dealing with-
Kara, this is a recon mission.
Get someone to volunteer.
Then you assess the situation.
And then get the hell out of
there. Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
I'm here to repair
the O-2 line.
Captain, what
are you doing?
Volunteering.
Let me see that.
Close the hatch.
Search her.
You might not want
to do that.
You're running out
of air in here.
Looks clean.
Do your job.
Cover her.
Wait a minute.
Turn around slowly.
Check the box again.
We're hot.
Let's go.
Get down!
We gotta get out!
Now!
Come on!
Billy.
I need shirts, towels-
anything I can use as a bandage.
Billy!
Nobody said you could move.
You still want the Cylon?
Do you?
Because if
the admiral's son dies,
you're not gonna get a deal,
you get that?
If he dies, you're not
gonna get what you want.
He's right.
Let him go.
Sir, it's Starbuck.
We got a report of gunshots.
What's happening?
My cover was blown.
I had to move.
I'm sorry.
Any casualties?
Two marines.
Probably KIA...
At least one of the gunmen...
And Lee.
It was crazy in there,
confused.
He got hit.
How bad?
I don't know.
Stand by.
Hold your position.
Make no move unless
you hear from me.
It was friendly fire.
Lee got hit
by friendly fire.
I think it was me.
I gotta stop
the bleeding.
I can't tell
if it hit an artery,
or...
Lee?
Don't leave me.
Lee, Lee.
Don't leave me, okay?
Please.
Hey.
He's gonna be okay.
Just hang in there, come on.
Stay with me.
Please, stay with me.
Are you playing with us?
Are you playing with me?
I've saved the ship.
Saved you.
How many times now?
Five? Six?
You just can't believe
I'm not plotting against you.
You know that there are Cylons
within this Fleet.
You know what they look like.
You know where
to find them.
If I were to ask you,
would you tell me
who they are?
No.
That I believe.
He'll be all right.
Thanks for the concern.
She loses a husband,
and suddenly the world
owes her an explanation.
He was a good man.
And he wasn't just her husband.
He was my brother.
My brother died on Picon.
He was a good man too.
They're all good men.
The Abinell woman sent over
a manifesto to the press
before they took over
the bar.
It's mostly a collection
of rumor and conspiracy theories
about Cylons in the military
and the government.
Bunch of crap.
It's getting
a lot of attention.
We gotta get our people
out of there.
You have Marines
on Cloud Nine.
Pressure door
to the room has been resealed.
If we try blowing it open,
we'll need so much G-4,
we'd risk killing
everyone inside.
There are no options
left except for one.
No.
We don't strike deals with
terrorists. We can't.
We give them Sharon Valerii,
we're inviting terrorism
and we weaken our position
permanently, you know that.
Gentlemen, everyone in that
room is someone's son,
someone's wife,
someone's mother.
Billy is the closest thing
that I have to family
left in this world.
And if you don't think
that that...
confuses things emotionally
for me-
Let's not be naive.
What if they're right?
What if Sharon
has been playing us all,
plotting our destruction
with every passing day?
What if the terrorists
are right?
This isn't about Sharon.
It's about something
much bigger than that.
It's about the long-term
survival, it's about the way
we conduct ourselves
in all of this.
Sir?
It's Abinell on the line.
How's my son?
Alive.
But my friend is dead.
So are two of your soldiers.
And your son's dying.
You know, I thought
a long time about this.
About what I'd do...
about how far I'd go...
And I honestly did not know
until this moment...
Chu.
What?
Get on your feet.
What are you gonna do?
Saul, give them
what they want!
It's just a machine!
They're gonna kill her.
Hold your fire.
I'm giving you the Cylon.
But you won't be alive.
What does that mean?
That is not the deal.
It means
that you've convinced me
that wy
have been played.
And if that be the case,
and she's been playing with me,
then I can't take
any more chances.
So you make up your mind.
If you wanShon Valerii,
you can have her.
But on my terms.
I give you the body,
you give me the hostages.
Done.
Cut the wire.
Admiral.
Let me help.
Please.
Let me take it
from here.
Let's go.
Stop looking at him, Billy.
I can see you watching him.
I know you think
you can get that gun.
I'm only thinking in case
something happens. No.
You're not a soldier.
You're not trained for that.
You've got nothing
to prove.
I know.
They're right outside.
We open up,
they'll give us the body.
Okay.
We're opening the door.
But if anything goes wrong...
we start killing
hostages.
Do it.
It's over.
Wait-
This isn't right.
This one's been dead
for weeks.
Their Cylon is still alive.
Kill the girlfriend.
Down, report.
All clear.
I need help over here!
Medic!
Lee.
Lee, can you hear me?
Lee!
Can you hear me, Lee?
Come on, son.
Come on, hurry up.
That's good.
Billy.
No.
Is this what you gave 'em?
It was a calculated risk.
It wasn't worth it.
Oh, dear.
Well, that's better.
That's better.
He was so young.
Hey.
Hey...
What is it?
Nothing.
When you're feeling better,
we can talk.
This was a hell
of a vacation.
Yeah.
Lee?
Lee, you can't leave.
You have to stay.
You have to really stay.
You understand?
It's okay.
I'll be here when you wake up.
I'll be right here.