The Cylons Were
Created by Man
They Evolved
They Rebelled
There Are Many Copies
And They Have A Plan
Previously on
Battlestar Galactica...
The raiders are going to send a
signal to activate the virus.
On my mark,
initiate the computer wipe.
I'm connecting through the network now
Congratulations, commander
I'm leaving Galactica...
not you.
I'm coming back.
I said it,...
I meant it.
I understand what is like...
to lose someone that
you care about deeply
They're not lost,...
not yet.
We have to go back to Caprica.
Given the current situation,...
I'm afraid that I have no alternative...
but to announce
that I am, as of now,...
a candidate for the presidency.
I'm going to lose.
Yes, come in, please.
One minute, Madam President.
Thank you, Tory.
No one should be under any illusions
about what we're going to face here.
Our final jump will take us
intra-atmospher...
less than two klicks
above the surface.
We're also expecting
to take heavy fire.
Simulations indicate losses
of up to 20% can be expected.
That's why this mission
has been designated...
as 2-alpha by the command authority.
It's volunteer only.
You want out,...
now's the time.
I know it's hard to believe
right now, but if you have faith,...
everything will
turn out exactly as it should.
I don't like to lose.
Have faith.
I am about to face
public humiliation.
And you are singing
the same old song.
I'm a little tired of the melody.
Sorry about the mess. It's, um...
bit of a ritual...superstition, really.
I used to do this before
testifying at committee hearings.
This is what I do.
I take one,...
memorize a talking
point, then...
tear the card,...
and let the pieces fall
as they may. It helps.
Yeah, my father used to break
pencils before he went into court,...
then borrow one from the clerk.
Break preconceptions,
work with what you have.
You know, I like that.
Let me see.
I like it.
It's good.
Feel better?
Yeah.
But what happens if the, uh,...
moderator doesn't
have a pencil?
Then you're pretty screwed.
Oh, no.
I used to...
get the giggles before
debating in high school.
Oh, yes.
It's time, Madam President.
Thank you, Tory.
What many of you don't know is
that the captured cylon heavy raider
is capable of much longer
jumps than our raptors.
In fact, we realized early on...
that if we could install a
heavy raider navigational system...
aboard one of our raptors,...
a strike team could make the
entire trip back to Caprica...
in less than ten jumps.
Now, the limiting factor up until
now has been our inability...
in install the cylon computer
with our computer.
That obstacle has
now been overcome.
She's here to help us.
She's gonna lay out
our navigational markers...
and update our jump coordinates. Does
anyone have a problem with that?
You've been chosen to
lead these people...
by almighty god.
It will happen.
Like the baby happened?
The one I was
destined to protect?
Don't let your anger drive
you into blasphemy, Gaius.
The election's still
two weeks away.
Get your act together.
You ready?
Yeah, I was just
taking a little nap.
Chief.
This is our mission.
It's our duty to the
people we left behind.
And if we need to use a cylon to
get them back, then so be it.
This is about trying to get as many
survivors off Caprica as we can.
Even so, it's still 2-alpha.
Anyone want to eject?
Commander on deck.
Don't worry.
I won't be long.
I want to hear it too.
You just have to really try to think
about something serious.
That always helps.
- Right?
- Like what?
Well, like, uh...
Great.
No one has ever attempted...
a rescue mission
from this distance,...
much less behind enemy lines.
You'll be making history
just by making the attempt.
But bring these people
back from Caprica...
and you'll be making
part of the future.
Questions.
If you guys find Earth
before we get back,...
will you save us a few seats?
Earth? Hell, if we find any rock
with food and water,...
I'll build you guys a bar.
All right.
See, I told you
I wouldn't be long.
Mr. Gaeta, turn on the wireless.
Let's give these people a
chance to hear what kind of fun...
they'll be missing
for the next five days.
We are just minutes
from the start of the first...
presidential debate
between President...
- You okay?
- Laura Roslin and her oppenent...
Vice President Gaius Baltar...
Can I go now?
Coporal Masters
submitted by members of
the civilian fleet...
covering a wide range of topics.
So please stay tuned as we
get set for the first of two...
presidential debates.
The atmosphere in the
auditorium is tense...
as we await the arival of the
two candidates and their aides.
The real pressure will be on
vice-president Baltar tonight.
Chief.
Here comes Vice President...
Gaius Baltar into the room,...
uh, as we, uh, we
await Madam President.
Laura Roslin is very much
ahead in the polls at this point.
We believe that, uh...
she's entering the room shortly,...
but still...still,
of course, waiting for her.
blindsighted her by announcing
his candidacy a month ago.
Dr. Baltar of course is
one of the most admired...
and brilliant scientistific
minds of our generation...
and played a critical
role in saving the human race...
from the cylon threat.
Yes, here comes
the President now.
Laura Roslin, the President,
has entered the room.
I'm going to wipe the floor
with you, Gaius.
You must be losing
your mind again.
If that's the best you
can come up with,...
you're in a lot of trouble.
Good luck.
How you doing?
You okay?
Sharon.
Don't shut me out.
Not now.
Something dark
is coming, Helo.
I can feel it.
I can feel it
lurking out there,...
waiting.
What do you mean?
Back on Caprica?
No.
Not on the mission.
Not any specific thing.
It's more like a dark time.
Chief.
Chief...
Help!
49.579 survivors
in search of a home
Called Earth
Chief Tyrol,...
I am Brother Cavill.
I understand you've
asked for religious counseling.
I never really believed
in psych therapy.
My father was a priest.
I see.
You thought you'd have an easier
time with a priest than a real doctor.
Okay.
I pray to gods...
every night.
But I don't think
they listen to me.
Do you know how
useless prayer is?
Chanting and singing and...
mucking about with old
half-remembered lines of bad poetry.
And you know
what it gets you?
Exactly nothing.
Are you sure you're a priest?
I've been preaching longer than
you've been sucking down oxygen.
And in that time, I've learned
enough to know that the gods...
don't answer prayers.
We're here on our own.
That's the way they set things up.
We have to find our own answers,
our own way out of the wilderness...
without a nice
little sunny path...
all laid out in front
of us in advance.
That's what I'm trying to do.
I'm trying to find my way.
Well, it's not going to get better
until you see what the problem is.
And the problem is,...
you're screwed up,...
heart and mind.
You. Not the...not the gods or
fate or the universe.
You.
Thanks for the pep talk.
- Hey.
Um...
I just wanted to say, um...
well...
good hunting.
Thank you, sir.
Yeah, it's a good plan.
It's a good plan.
Sharon should be able to jump you...
into the atmosphere a couple of...
klicks above the surface.
Down below the...
cylon dradis. I know the
plan, Lee. I wrote it.
I-I gotta go.
I hope you find him, Kara.
I really do.
So do I.
From the Colonial Dispatch.
"Last night's debate only
solidified the perception..."
- I'll do that later.
- "That doctor baltar, for all his charm,..."
"is essentially an empty suit..."
"when it comes to matters of
substantial policy."
It's nice to see the press is
getting it right for a change.
Don't forget, the radical religious
charge is dangerous.
It may be a low blow
from a desperate man, but...
it's the only issue he's
managed to get any traction on.
He will keep exploiting it.
He's gotta come up with something
much, much bigger than that.
If he wants to make it the central
issue of his campaign,...
it's not going to work.
You gotta keep hitting her on
the religious thing.
Every time we go there,...
you score points and we
move the polls in our direction.
I'm not sure if
you're aware, Tom,...
but the mob isn't usually in
the habit of electing...
ungodly apostates who
denigrate people of faith.
Things are going to turn around.
You'll see.
He's right.
Listen to him.
Of course.
Of course, how blind i'm being.
Thank you. Yes.
Things are going to turn around,
you'll see. What is that, advice?
Well, thank you.
Thank for your keen insight,...
your astounding political acumen.
You know, I'm so
assured right now, Tom,...
I'm just going to sit right back
and wait for the hand of god...
to reach down and change
my political fortunes.
How about that?
Galactica, Starbuck.
SAR squadron
confirms readiness check.
And we are spun up out here and
ready for the first jump.
You are go for the jump, Starbuck.
Roger that.
Jump in ten minutes. Mark.
Galactica,
I'd like to speak with actual.
Sir.
Actual. Go.
Did I ever say "thank you"?
No.
Then again, that would be
a first, wouldn't it?
Thank you.
Just come back
in one piece.
That'll be thank you enough.
Good hunting.
Actual out.
SAR team, Starbuck. Set navcon
inputs to coordinate recheck.
Standby for bounce
back and stabilization routines.
Let's do a final check, people.
I still can't believe you
talked me into this.
It's important.
And I'll be with
you there and back.
It's you and me from
now on, no matter what.
Just like we agreed.
I know. I know.
I really appreciate it,
Helo, I really do.
I just can't get her
out of my head.
Our little girl.
Is there a problem?
Racetrack, check.
Callon Chedk.
Wireless check complete.
Board is green and we are set.
Sharon, you're on.
Ready.
SAR team, Starbuck.
Standby to jump on my mark.
Five...
Here we go.
Four, three, two, one.
Commence the first jump.
This doesn't look right.
No other contacts on dradis.
What?
Oh, man. We're at the wrong
jump coordinates.
Frak.
Helo, we've lost
someone already.
It's Racetrack.
So do we go back?
Mission rules say we keep going
unless we lose three.
So we keep going.
Racetrack will just
have to find her way back to base.
It's a hell of a way to start, though.
Let's, uh, let's talk
about what happened.
I can't really believe it.
Cally.
I-I-I don't understand how I
could do that to Cally.
It's like it's a nightmare.
She said you were asleep
when she found you.
Were you having a nightmare
when she woke you up?
I don't remember.
Oh.
Been having any recurring
dreams lately?
No.
Okay.
That's what we in the pray
trade call a lie.
And lies aren't going to
get you anywhere, my friend.
So skip over the
denials and the deceptions...
and let's get right
down to it, shall we?
You're having dreams.
What are they?
Tell me about
your dream, Chief.
Every night...every night,
it's the same.
For how long?
Couple weeks.
And you were having the same dream
when Cally woke you up, weren't you?
I don't know.
I don't remember. Maybe.
It doesn't matter, does it?
All I remember is Cally on
the ground and the blood.
She stopped you.
By waking you up,
she prevented you from carrying out
your secret desire to kill yourself.
I don't have a secret
desire to kill myself.
Well, actually, you're right.
It's not a secret.
You obviously want to kill yourself.
Question is why.
I think there was some kind of
glitch in the navcon firmware.
Hey bottom line, we're to hell and gone...
from where we're
supposed to be, skipper.
Okay, um, any chance that we
can still catch up with them?
Not a chance.
Mission rules say we head back.
Frak me! It was the first jump!
Hey, look, you gave me
these coordinates.
Back to the barn.
Hey.
I am picking up a large
planetary body.
It's frakkin' close.
Where'd that come from?
Hell if I know.
So much dradis interference here,
it didn't even register.
Hey, check this out.
Atmosphere is nitrogen/oxygen.
Organic molecular spectra.
Fresh water?
Hey, you know what this is?
It's habitable.
We may have just found a world
that can support human life.
Maybe we're not just a bunch
of frak-ups after all.
Climate readings overall are within
human norms.
There's some extremes at the
poles that we couldn't withstand...
but that's not unusual.
Well done.
Thank you, sir.
We got a mottled area here at
the river mouth.
So it's probably a delta.
And the chances are, we've got
significant plant and animal life.
So I want a lot of nice,
low passes across here.
Heard the Pegasus survey
mission found wildlife.
Fruit trees.
Rivers of milk and honey.
Yeah. You forgot the lakes of ambrosia.
Most of the planet's
actually pretty barren.
Plant and animal
life located in a...
temperate belt around the equator.
But the best part is...
with all the dradis
interference from the nebula...
the cylons will
probably never find it.
Who cares about
this stupid planet anyway?
Song and dance over nothing.
Less than 20% of that place actually
supports human life so...
You're not seeing the big picture.
This is your new home.
The place where you will
lead a new life.
This is the future, Gaius.
Now there's a
difference in thought.
What's that?
Oh, nothing, Tom.
Just, uh...
can you imagine if we actually had
to live on that thing.
You...
are a genius.
And?
Pay attention.
You're about to win the election.
I'm sorry.
What were you saying, Tom?
We needed an issue.
Something to set us
apart from Roslin.
Something to put her clearly on
the wrong side of a major issue...
that people care
passionately about.
This is it.
Permanent settlement on this planet.
Permanent settlement here.
Have you lost your marbles?
It may look dreary,
it may be dreary,...
but it's solid ground under your
feet and a real sky over your head.
You'd be surprised what a
powerful idea that is to...
people cooped up in metal
boxes for nine months.
You should listen to him, Gaius.
He's a smart, sexy
man, just like you.
Oh, give up.
What?
Give up on Earth.
Yes.
So we'd settle here.
You know, it's starting to look like a
lovely little planet after all.
This is a rest stop.
A place to load up
on food and water.
We're not settling
here, obviously.
You've heard the
captain's reports.
Every ship in the fleet has
people begging, pleading,...
demanding they get time
down on the surface.
Even if it's only for a few hours.
Well, a few hours is one thing.
But permanent settlement's
quite another.
Suddenly Baltar's holding out
hope for breathing real air,...
growing real food, sleeping in
a bed instead of a bunk.
Living in a house
instead of a ship.
It's a fantasy.
Look at the mission reports.
All the data indicate that
life on this planet would be hard.
It would be a struggle to even eke a
living out for a few years.
Today's polls show that he's...
also making headway
with the idea that...
because the planet is
hidden in a nebula,...
it will provide a refuge
from the cylons.
What, are we
now assuming that...
cylon technology is not sufficient
enough to find this planet?
We just found it.
Madam President, in my opinion,
people vote their hopes,...
not their fears.
Baltar is offering them what
they want to hear,...
and you're offering
them a bitter reality.
I'm offering them the truth.
They don't want to hear the truth.
They're tried, exhausted.
The idea of stopping,...
laying down their burdens,...
and starting a new
life right now...
is what is resonating
with the voters.
How well is it resonating?
It could turn the entire
election around.
Why are you running?
I'm not.
How long are you
going to do this?
How long are you going to
refuse to see what's...
right in front of your face?
Forget it.
I'm done.
What, you're... you're leaving?
That's right. I'm done.
I'm done dancing
around the truth with you.
You know what's going on.
But you can't or
you won't face it,...
so...
I'm not a therapist.
I'm not going to hold your
hand and help you along.
I'm just trying to get you right
with yourself and with your gods,...
but you're not willing to do it.
I don't even know what
you're talking about.
Oh for gods' sake, chief!
Come on!
You think you're a Cylon.
I am not a Cylon.
Well, of course you're not.
But that's what you're
afraid of, isn't it?
That you might be a cylon
and not even know it just...
just like Boomer, right?
Right?
That's the thought
that's torturing your dreams...
and crippling your soul.
I'm a cylon,...
just like Sharon,
and I deserve to die.
Sharon didn't know...
what she was.
She just kept...
thinking... feeling...
that she was going to
do this terrible thing.
But she knew that she had to
stop herself before she did.
And you think that's what you're
going to do. Some terrible thing.
Well, the truth is, you might.
But not because you're a Cylon.
Because you're a human being,...
and human beings do terrible
things all the time.
But how do you
know I'm human?
Oh, well, maybe because
I'm a Cylon,...
and I've never seen you at
any of the meetings.
There's not much more
I can do for you.
You're going to have
to go back to work...
and try and leave all
of this behind you.
No. I...
I can't.
I can't go back and face
the deck people again.
And Cally?
Well, you'd better.
That's the only family you've got.
Just know that that's your
family and that they love you.
Even Cally.
Especially Cally.
If you doubt your humanity...
and your essential nature
as a human being,...
all you need to do
is look to them...
for the salvation you've been
seeking from the gods.
The gods lift up those...
who lift each other, Chief.
SAR team, Starbuck.
We are set here.
Stand by for final jump to Caprica.
Remember, we are going
very low to the surface.
Be prepared for wind shear,
rain, storms...
anything.
Roger that, Starbuck.
Ready.
Here we go.
Jump.
SAR team, Starbuck.
Form up on me.
Roger that skipper.
Any cylons, Helo?
Nothing on dradis.
Wait a minute.
Missing a raptor.
I'm only reading 17 out there.
We're missing raptor 6-12.
That's toughguy and carousel.
What, they jumped to
the wrong coordinates?
No.
No, no. I'm picking up their
transponder, so they made it.
Bearing 827, carom 443.
About half a klick from here.
That would put them...
oh, my gods.
Where, Helo?
Talk to me.
They jumped
inside the mountain.
Damn.
SAR team, Starbuck.
We've lost raptor 6-12.
We are proceeding without them.
Follow me.
Roger that Starbuck.
I would think that my position...
and the position of my
campaign is abundantly clear.
Madam President,
you have 30 seconds to respond.
Well, my initial response is
there he goes again.
Once again, ladies and gentlemen,...
Doctor Baltar is distorting
the real issues before us.
The issue here,
the real question, is...
not allowing the scriptures to
dictate the policy of this government.
The question is...
do the scriptures
contain real world relevance?
Do they contain the
information necessary...
to guide us to a safer home than
some completely unknown planet...
that we've just now discovered?
Obviously, my answer to that
question is yes.
I have always and will
continue to feel...
the scriptures hold
real world relevance.
Mr. Vice President,
the next question is for you.
Uh, how do you
respond to the charges...
that you seized the idea of...
permanent settlement
on this planet...
as an opportunistic
gamble, um,...
some would say as...
to be construed as a desperate
move from a campaign,...
uh, that was falling
behind on every poll?
Well, you know that is, um,...
that is an excellent question,
in fact, Jim. Thank you.
And I'm only too glad to
have the opportunity to respond to it.
You see, I have long been a
proponent in the search for Earth.
The promise of perhaps
finding not only a new home,...
but also the prospect of
discovering our long lost...
brothers and sisters of the 13th
colony is a powerful one...
and one I have believed
in heart and soul.
But the trouble is,...
the cylons continue
to follow us...
as they have done
every step of the way...
since the destruction
of the colonies.
And if we have a chance
to change this dynamic,...
to stop this deadly chase,...
should we take it?
My answer is yes.
Thank you.
Madam President, 30 seconds.
There's no assurance...
none whatsoever...
that the cylons don't already
know about this planet,...
that they don't make regular
stops here looking for us,...
and that in fact...
they aren't simply waiting for
us to settle on the surface...
- so they can...
- I have to respond to that.
I simply have to
respond to that.
I'll give you 15 seconds.
What you've seen right now,
ladies and gentlemen,...
is another example of
the President using fear...
to drive her campaign.
Fear.
Fear of the gods.
Fear of the cylon.
Fear of fear itself.
Is it not time to
stop being afraid?
I'm asking all of us...
to stop running
from our lives...
and start living them.
Thank you.
That is all we have time for today.
I'd like to thank, uh,...
both the candidates for
their frankness today.
Very exciting debate.
This concludes the cycle of
the debates for the presidency.
The polls will be
open in three days.
Please vote.
Thank you and good night.
Not your night, I guess.
Why don't you go frak yourself.
With me now is campaign
manager for Doctor Baltar,...
Mr. Tom Zarek.
Tom, welcome. Uh,
you were in there with us today.
What was your impression?
Well, I...
thought Doctor
Baltar did exceptionally well.
Laid out his vision of the future...
and offered the people a way
to end the suffering and terror...
that defines so many
of their lives.
On the other hand,
I found myself wondering how...
Roslin's arguments against
settlement could possibly win.
CYLON OCCUPIED CAPRICA
Let's go.
- right there.
- Go it.
Let's figure out
where we are, Karl.
Resistance base camp.
We're still...
another klick ahead.
Movement. Eleven o'clock
Friendlies?
You got a Samuel T. Anders there?
Is there a Kara Thrace there?
If there is,...
you tell her she took her
good, sweet time getting here.
Friendlies.
What took you so long?
We have marines in raptors.
We're gonna get you and your
people out of here, okay?
As good as your word, huh?
Yeah, good as my frakkin' word.
What, did you think I
was going to leave you here?
Now you feel like a big frakkin'
idiot, don't you?
All right, just shut up
and save us already, okay?
People, this is nice,
but we have toasters on our ass.
Where are the rest
of your people?
This is it.
Toasters hit our base
camp this morning.
I lost half my crew.
Incoming!
Back to the raptors!
No!
Shell trajectories are coming
between us and the raptors.
We're cut off!
to be continued
-= Grupo Legendas Galactica =-
br.groups.yahoo.com/group/leg_galactica