Previously on Jericho
Some of them were on planes
that landed in the middle of nowhere.
They've been walking for weeks.
They must have gone through hell.
Oh, my God.
At the current levels of consumption,
we will be completely
out of gas and diesel in two weeks.
There's a woman in that
group of refugees that
Bill is processing.
I think you should talk to her.
Hello, Rob.
Someone on my team sold us all out.
You're smart enough to know
that they would say anything
to get you to talk, Sarah.
Get the package.
We're the United States Marines,
and we're here to help.
... and those are to restore lights,
power and infrastructure
to Kansas, one town at a time.
Something's wrong about all this,
all right? Trust me.
They've got somebody on the edge of town
pretending to be their headquarters.
Is any of this real?
- The gun's real.
- Hands up. Get them up!
What the hell do we do with them?
You will leave your weapons on the tank,
and you will move out!
- What do we do with that?
- Stanley,
got room in your barn?
- Seriously?
- Why not?
Never know when you might need a tank.
You're making too much noise.
Sorry.
Where did it go?
There it is.
- It's locked.
- We shouldn't go in.
Go in here.
- Why do I have to?
- So we can eat.
You see it?
Katie?
Come on, Jake,
there's a line here.
Did you hear about the tank?
Those Marines coming or what?
Everybody, just calm down!
You'll get your share.
You'll get your rations!
People, please, back up!
How is Gray handling this?
You better get in there.
I think we really screwed
ourselves this time.
You said everyone in the shelter gets
half-rations until the Marines come.
Well, the Marines aren't coming,
and you've known all along.
We did the best that we could.
People had to believe
that help was on the way.
And you know what?
Half-rations is a lot more than
those refugees had before they got here.
Did you know about this?
The Marines...
That they were con artists?
Yeah, but we didn't give them
any of our supplies.
And Gray is right. The last thing
this town needs is to lose hope.
Hope won't keep
my friends from starving.
I've got one woman too weak to walk.
It's a mathematical problem.
We've got your friends,
plus another 50 who migrated here.
That's too many people,
and not enough food.
We'll just have to figure out
how to make what we have last.
I say the first thing we do,
is stop giving it away to strangers.
What if we cut
the food rations in half,
again?
It's more than the food.
What about medicine?
Those refugees came here sick.
They've been burning through
our meds for a month.
Can we make it to spring, Harry?
Some of us can. Not all.
Crime's been going up
since they got here.
since the bombs.
It's got to be done.
The numbers speak for themselves.
Just look at 'em.
I don't need to look at 'em.
I see them in my sleep.
What are you going to do?
Folks?
Folks, listen up!
I am sorry to say that
the town no longer has the resources
to take care of you.
What?
Where are we supposed to go?
So if you could please
gather up your belongings,
you will be escorted
to a FEMA camp out
- near I-70.
- We've been to those FEMA camps.
We barely made it out
alive the first time.
FEMA has medicine and supplies,
and we don't.
You heard the mayor.
You need to start packing up.
What are you going to do,
put us in jail?
Great.
If I didn't have to do this,
- I wouldn't.
- We've been working!
Okay? We've been chopping wood!
Jessica's been helping you
with your medical center.
I'm sorry.
But if you put us out on the...
This isn't a debate.
You're right.
'Cause we're staying.
Season 1 - Episode 16
" One Man's Terrorist "
[ Transcript ]
swsub.com
[ Synchro ]
Benj! / Loky / aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
Anything?
Static.
No news.
I guess now the secret
about the tank is out,
there's no need to hide the radio.
Yeah. I'll take it down
to Bailey's later.
We can all be annoyed together.
Emily.
Gray's trying to kick out the refugees.
They barricaded themselves
inside the church.
Was anybody hurt?
Is there another door?
No. They blocked that one, too.
Look, Roger, I'm sorry, but...
You lie about the Marines,
you get caught, you need someone
to blame, so you pick them.
We have taken in almost
a hundred people since the bombs.
Roger, you brought over 50 yourself.
We've done our part.
It's time for somebody else
to share the burden.
- Now, these FEMA camps...
- Those FEMA camps are jungles.
Putting anybody out on those streets
is a death sentence.
You've been out there.
You know that.
Look, it comes down to ressources.
All right? And people of Jericho
have to come first.
It's 100 of them or 100 of us.
Let me work on Gray.
You and Emily try and talk
some sense into the refugees.
Don't give Gray
a reason to make this worse.
All right? Gray can't send
these people away like this.
It's his call.
Well, isn't there
something we can do?
Give them warm clothing for the trip.
We've given away
everything we can spare.
Well, there's...
What?
April's things?
Kyle, what are you doing?
We're not leaving here without a fight.
- This is a bad idea.
- What should we do?
We take down the barricade.
We go out unarmed.
We look them in the eye,
and we ask them to stay
till the end of winter.
Look them in the eye.
That's your plan?
- You don't know this town.
- Apparently, that makes two of us.
Where did you get the food from?
You stole it.
You broke into people's houses?
It's not like you didn't do the same
thing when we were out there.
Yeah, well, this is different.
This town took care of us!
We took care of us!
Because we knew,
one day, this town wouldn't.
What do you see?
Looks like Simmons has got
his nephew guarding the shed.
I don't think I can get in.
You have to.
You traded them for that gas,
and they're holding out on you.
You can't let these farmers
get away with it anymore.
It's easy for you to say.
I'll go this time.
Very funny.
What? You think you're
the only badass here?
- Uh... yeah.
- You want to bet?
Forget it, Skylar. Simmons is not
a pushover like Frederickson.
Neither am I.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You could get hurt.
You're worried about me?
That's so sweet.
Now, watch and learn.
Found them!
Tear gas?
Gray, those things been
sitting around for years.
You can't do this, Gray.
I've given these people sanctuary.
Reverend, this is a police matter now.
You have no right
to assault these people.
They've committed no crimes.
- They'll be my responsibility.
- What, are you going to feed them?
What, you got a little hospital
down there, Reverend?
No, I didn't think so.
What's that sound?
They're boarding up the windows.
There were half a dozen other places
we could have stopped,
but you kept talking like Jericho
was the end of the freakin' rainbow.
So we kept walking...
losing people... for this.
Out of my way, Johnston!
I know what I'm doing.
You know why we never used those?
A little thing called Waco happened.
The FBI used tear gas,
and they swear it didn't start
that fire, but it could have.
- You ready to live with that?
- Dad!
We can't hold off a town.
- It's too big a gamble.
- It's not a gamble for you!
You get to go home
to a warm bed every night.
I told you... I'm with you.
What happens when
we get kicked out of this town?
Come on!
What are you doing?
Get out of the way!
She's got no pulse.
Hank! Hank!
- Skylar!
- Thank God. There are men on the road!
- Men? What men?
- They're with Ravenwood.
Is your uncle here?
- No, it's just me.
- We have to hide!
Okay, yeah. Come on!
How many were there?
I don't know. Five, maybe six.
I can't see them.
You know what?
I bet you have
a better view from the hayloft.
- I'm right behind you.
- Okay.
Skylar!
Stop!
It's okay. I'll wait.
One of the refugees is still out there.
You have the rangers search the barns.
Use dogs if it'll help.
And the rest of them?
Take them to the med center,
get them fixed up, Harry.
Then send them away.
What about the extra food
you promised them?
Give it to them.
- After what they did to us?
- Will you just do it,
before somebody else gets hurt?!
It's not too late.
Just let them stay until spring.
You think I haven't tried
to make that work?
The numbers don't add up.
- They're good people, Gray. Just...
- And?!
Good people are dying every day!
Someone finally has to tell the truth.
It's musical chairs out there.
The music has stopped!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, get away from me!
Get away from me!
A hundred counts of murder, Gray.
That's what they should charge you with
if you send them away.
We have been feeding them
and we have been heating the shelter.
We've been taking
from my friends
to give to strangers,
so don't you dare lecture me!
Whatever happens to them is on you!
Let me go, please!
- I don't want to hurt you!
- Just let me go, please!
You're not leaving
until this is resolved!
This is resolved!
Get out of my way!
- They're not going anywhere.
- You want to bet?
Just take whatever you want!
Just get out!
And go where?!
I got the entire police force
guarding the refugees,
and one way or another,
they're going.
Hey, stop it!
All right, stop it!
What's going on?
What happened?
Gray pulled a gun.
It was an accident.
Like hell! He shot me!
There's so much blood.
He needs a doctor.
- Get-get Kenchy.
- No, get Jessica.
Shut up!
You're not running things!
Get Jessica, please, all right?
I trust her.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What are you looking for?
Superglue.
The sole on my boot came apart
after a couple hundred miles.
My son's shoes might fit you.
I'd rather fix these.
Why?
They're all I have left that are mine.
Where are you going to go?
I don't know really.
My family was in Chicago.
I wish there was more
that we could do.
Ma'am,
there are empty houses
all over Jericho,
and we sleep in a shelter.
Those are our neighbors' homes.
They were gone
when the bombs went off.
They're coming back.
Well, wherever your neighbors are,
I hope nobody's kicking them
out of town in the middle of winter.
What the hell happened in there?
- Gray's bleeding badly.
- I'm busy.
- I need your help!
- Get Kenchy.
Look, you're the only
one Roger trusts.
You want me to save
Gray Anderson?
If Gray dies, so does Roger.
People aren't just going
to let it go. Please?
We can all get out of this.
I was just trying to help them.
Now... there's no way the
town lets them stay.
It was an accident.
I saw it.
Gray...
just until spring.
That's all I ask.
Come on!
You were right.
This is on me.
I brought them here.
I did it...
I did it for my own reasons.
But don't punish them,
I'm begging you.
Just till spring.
Go to hell.
I've got Jessica. Let us in.
You need to let me look at him.
You give them a chance...
...I'll give you a chance.
I was going to give you
food, an escort.
We wouldn't survive out there...
you know that.
We have to stay here.
Why would you die over this?!
He's our only leverage.
Roger, this isn't you.
I survived out there
for three months.
You have no idea what
I can do if I have to.
- Any sign of her?
- No.
Check the buildings.
She's got to be around
here somewhere.
Hold up.
She changed the location again.
Meet you back at the road.
Bill, don't!
You think I want to?
Roger's a friend of mine, but I can't
let the mayor bleed to death.
What if you miss?
What if you hit Emily?
Get off me.
If I get the shot, Jake...
I'm taking it.
Damn it.
We have to get him help.
He didn't want to do this.
It doesn't matter what
we want, does it?
It matters what we do.
I tried to get us all back here.
I promised them if we
just stuck together.
- And you did.
- Yeah.
Emily, most of us made it back.
19 of us didn't.
What's going on?
And I remember...
every one of their faces.
- Get away from the window!
- Jake, what are you doing?!
- I told you to stay out!
- Get away from the window!
Get away from the window!
Roger, get away from
the window!
If you want your friends to live...
you better back the hell off
right now and listen to me!
Roger, he's here to help.
I'm listening.
What if we give you
transportation?
And food and fuel?
So we can die out there?
- Guy is that what you think about?
- No!
You can make it to
the migration trail.
Head south and beat the winter.
It's not your decision to make.
Won't be yours either if you're dead.
You can't keep us in here forever.
This will end.
And when it does,
you can forget about staying.
They will kick you out
with nothing.
I'm going to need guns.
I can't give you guns.
I can't protect a hundred
people with what I have.
But you let Jessica take Gray
to the medical center.
He's not leaving.
Roger, if that bullet is still in him,
I'm going to have to open him up.
Is it a deal?
You make sure everything's ready.
I'll let him go.
Hey, Allie.
Dad, you can't be around here.
Mom will freak out.
I won't stay long.
Come on.
So...
I just wanted to know
how you were doing.
Settling in okay at
Jimmy's place?
- Yeah, he just never stops talking.
- No...
He doesn't.
ow's Sam?
You know, he gets scared.
And you?
I'm fine.
Look...
that thing you had
to do to Sarah...
I know how that can
change people.
Dad...
don't worry about me.
I'm not Sam, and
I'm not Mom.
So...
you're not going to live with
us anymore... are you ?
I don't think it's a good
idea right now.
Then don't worry.
I'll take care of them.
Come here.
You are not me.
Thank you for helping me.
Just try to keep still.
It's my job, you know.
I didn't want to do it.
I had to.
We all have our jobs to do,
whether we want to do them or not.
Just hang on.
The bus is here.
When do you think you'll come back?
After this...
he's never going to
let me come back.
Maybe I shouldn't have
brought them here.
There were other places...
camps...
towns we heard about.
But I had to see you.
A refugee broke into the house.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'll get the guys.
Listen to me.
We can't let this happen.
We're ready.
Get up.
Wait, you can't take him.
Once my friends and I...
are safely out of town...
I'll let him go.
He'll be dead by then.
You can't let them go out there.
A woman died on Main Street today.
I didn't even know her name.
Did you?
If you need a hostage,
take me.
Think of our neighbors who
haven't made it back yet.
That's who they are.
Now my family can feed two people.
Who else here is willing
to share their rations?
They're coming out!
All right, move back!
Move back!
Come on, people, we can do this.
I know we can, please.
Thank you, Bob. Yeah.
Right. Good.
Who else?
Come on, who else? Please.
Please.
Everybody, get back!
Get back!
Keep your guns down.
Keep them down.
Move back!
- Move back!
- My God.
Roger...
it's over.
They can stay.
We found them homes.
Just put the gun down, Roger.
You won.
Come on, put it down.
How's the mayor?
Jessica did a great job.
He's, um...
he's lost a lot of blood,
but he's stable.
We talked him into letting
the others stay.
But, um...
Not me.
Well...
I'd say I'd call you, but...
I'm coming with you.
No, you're not.
Roger, I-I am, so...
I did this
so the people I love
can be safe here.
I'm not taking the person I love
the most out on those roads.
I can handle it.
I can't.
So... what do you think?
Well, it's no Saks Fifth Avenue,
but...
it's pretty great.
Thanks to all the deals we made,
we have a real trading post now.
Hi, Mr. Simmons.
Hank.
- What?!
You think this is a joke?
I could've shot you.
Talk to your uncle, Hank.
He's the one that broke the deal.
You're just a real big man,
aren't you?
Just give me my horse
and the gas, and I'll be on my way.
The horse is tied up in the alley,
but the gas is mine.
I'm through playing
games with you.
Hank, get the gas.
Meet my new employees.
This is, um,
Jim and Judy Moore's house.
They were visiting their grandchildren
just outside of Philadelphia.
Rations are on Tuesday.
We'll be by to share them with you.
Mrs. Green.
Thank you.
We got together
some canned food and water.
I wish I had more.
Nothing I say is going to...
is going to sound right, so...
Are you really sad to see me go?
It's not about that.
Here.
Take Cedar Run first, it's clear,
and then head to New Bern.
Heather, Stanley, my brother,
they can help you
once you're there.
I know my way around.
Bodies were found
along Route 400 near Cimarron.
We've also received reports
that the bombers gained the trust
of local officials which allowed...
Wait, I've heard that voice before.
Oh, yeah, that's the guy that does
the farm report. It's real news.
... to research laboratories.
In New York,
the terrorists who were apprehended,
were all carrying nearly
perfect fake FBI badges.
Their identities have not been released.
Authorities have increased
security at all critical sites.
Jimmy?
Jimmy, what is it?
All citizens
are encouraged to be vigilant.
As we receive more information,
we will bring it to you.
Until then, all news is now local.
Take care of each other, Kansas.
[ www.seriessub.com ]