Previously on Jericho
Oh, my God, Ted.
- Jake, this is... Ted Lewis.
- Hey, how you doing?
We grew up together over in New Bern.
This is Russell and Mike.
- Hey.
- Yeah, we met.
With a dozen full-size windmills,
you could power the whole town.
I'm gonna help turn the lights on
for everyone back home.
- You're just going to leave?
- Won't be for very long.
Johnston, you SOB.
How the hell did you lose an election?
No, the question is: how did you get
to be in charge in New Bern?
- They get tired of you being sheriff?
- No, I'm still sheriff.
Just got a little more authority.
Does this thing work?
Can we get power from it?
Probably sometime tomorrow.
Let's get it up as fast as we can.
Can we buy some more of these things?
You got one of the only salt
mines around for 400 miles.
- We're going to need food.
- Won't see another crop till spring.
Spring crop is what I'm talking about.
Ten wind turbines for, let's say...
ten percent of your spring crop.
No, we can't put ourselves
in that position.
Starve next fall or freeze this winter.
Okay, look,
we'll give you the food.
We can have the wind turbines
to you in a couple weeks.
We're going to need ten Jericho
men to help us build them.
Is this about manpower
for wind turbines?
Or is it more about making sure
you get our crops come spring?
I am not going to build
these things on credit.
You want them now?
You're going to help make them.
What you are about to do...
means this town's survival.
All right, let's move out.
If anything happens
to any of them...
you're the first one I come for.
I know.
Hey, Jeff, they're back.
I didn't expect to see
you till spring, Russell.
I thought you might
be needing these.
Your windmills.
It's good to see our guys back, but...
it's going to take some time for me
to find the guys to replace them.
You don't need to replace them.
Well, now, wait...
our agreement was that
we got ten windmills
for ten percent of the crops.
You'll get your windmills,
but we don't need your men.
Constantino called it
an act of good faith.
I didn't think Constantino
knew that term.
But...
I'll take it.
Stanley!
- Welcome home.
- Thanks.
Where's Eric?
He didn't come back, Mary.
He said he wasn't ready.
But...
I'm sure he'll be back soon.
Okay.
Thanks.
I didn't know you guys
were coming back today.
- None of us did.
- How are you? You okay?
Where's Eric?
Come here.
He didn't come back with us.
Why not?
When I talked to him, he was still
pretty messed up about April's death.
He said he was thinking about
staying in New Bern for a while
to get his head together.
- When was this?
Three days ago.
Then, he didn't show up for work,
and I haven't seen him since.
I don't know what's
going on in New Bern.
When I asked about Eric,
they couldn't tell me anything.
Then, the cops started escorting
us wherever we went.
Then today, out of nowhere,
Russell says,
"Pack it up, we're going home",
like...
like it wasn't safe for us
there anymore.
Where's my brother?
- I don't know.
- What?
I know he hasn't been
seen for a few days.
Did you even try to find him?
- I asked Constantino.
- And?
And he told me that
they were looking for him.
And then this morning, he told me
to bring the rest of your guys home.
What the hell's going on
over there, Russell?
Should I be worried about him?
Answer me.
Should I be worried?
I would be.
- I'm going with you.
- No...
you've been gone for weeks.
Go home.
You need someone who knows
their way around New Bern.
I'll try to find Heather
as soon as I get there.
She knows it better than any of us.
Look, it's not safe out there.
You can't go by yourself.
I'm not.
I need your help.
Season 1 - Episode 19
" Casus Belli "
[ Transcript ]
swsub.com
[ Synchro ]
Hutch / aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
You can't just ride into New Bern
and start breaking china, Jake.
I got to try and find him.
I can't just...
There's something going on in that town.
I can feel it.
Stanley starts asking questions,
and they just send them home?
Okay, but you understand why
I can't just up and leave, right?
- He's my brother.
- And you said he was upset,
so maybe he just...
- If you're saying no, just say no.
Come on, Jake, I'm not saying no.
I'm saying we got to
understand the situation.
The situation is...
he's been missing for three days,
and I came to you...
for help.
Okay.
But if we do this,
we do it my way.
Oh, my God.
I'm so glad you're home.
I missed you guys so much.
You're totally back.
Mrs. Green.
I'm really sorry to bother
you like this, but...
I thought you should know.
Know what?
The men came back from New Bern,
and Eric wasn't with them.
Why not?
He decided to stay a little longer.
Decided to or Constantino insisted?
Stanley talked to him.
He said...
he said he wasn't ready
to come home.
- How'd you hurt your hand?
- Oh, I just...
was trying to fix the copper
tubing on my still.
It just popped off and cut me.
Is alcohol really a priority right now?
Actually, it's not to drink.
I was trying to make antiseptic
for the med center.
I should go.
- You got any sand over there
at the bar?  - Sand?
Yeah, I think I can show you a way
around that copper tubing.
I'll just give you a hand.
See you in a bit.
Guys... yo, listen.
Stop unloading that.
Put that back.
What the hell is this?
- Salt.  - Who gave you permission
to take it from the mine?
51% of the mine belongs to me.
I just took it from my half.
You don't have a half...
of anything. Your parents do.
Look, I know you still think
of me as a child...
and I can't help it if that's
where you're stuck,
but the fact is I have
a right to what I own.
You are a minor and
you don't own anything
as long as your parents
are still alive.
Or do you have some information
that I don't have?
Look, just... just take
the salt back to the mine
and don't make me have to
send my guys to do it.
Proof of residence?
We're not from here.
Sorry, you're going to need
to turn this car around
and proceed back
the way you came.
I'm here to see my brother.
His name is Eric Green.
You're not hearing me, sir.
No one's allowed...
No, you're not hearing me.
I have to see him.
He came here as part of the deal
you made with Jericho. Now...
Hey, Jake...
I want to talk to Phil Constantino.
- Get out of the car.
- Hell, no.
Put your hands on the dashboard.
I want to see your hands.
That's Johnston Green's son.
Let him through.
I'll escort him in
to see Sheriff Constantino.
Go ahead, let him through.
Mister, Mister.
Do you have any food?
I'm sorry, I don't...
I'm sorry, I don't have any.
All right, ma'am, come on.
Get those kids out of there.
Hey, come on.
Come on, please.
I thought we had it bad.
What the hell happened here?
Ravenwood.
My brother is missing.
I know. I've got patrols
out looking for him.
- And no leads?
- No.
Sorry, I wish there's
more I could do.
You're the sheriff and the mayor.
You can do more.
I'm trying, Jake.
You sure Eric even
wants to be found?
What's that supposed to mean?
We all knew April.
We know what happened.
Last I heard that Eric was
having a tough time.
He'll be fine as soon as
we get him home.
You know what?
Let's face the facts.
He might have been attacked.
Could be lying in a
ditch somewhere.
- Why would you say...
- Take it easy!
The fact is some folks around here
aren't too fond of Jericho these days.
That's why I sent the workers home
today. When your brother went missing,
I got worried for their safety.
Why?
There's been a lot of rumors
flying around about your town.
What are people saying?
They're mad that Jericho didn't
warn us about Ravenwood.
They think you're going to renege
on your part of the food deal.
We've had it rough here, okay?
They're just looking for
somebody to blame.
- Where was Eric last seen?
- The factory.
End of his shift.
Look, we're just trying to help.
What is it that you want
that we're not giving?
I want to talk to Heather Lisinski.
Take care of each other, Kansas.
Anything new from Mr. Hewitt?
No, it's just the same bulletin about
the riots in Chicago Camp West.
Hey, thanks for taking on a shift.
Jimmy, it's the least I can do
to make myself useful.
I feel like such a freeloader
sitting around your house all day.
You kidding me?
You're like the best houseguest ever.
You cook, you do the dishes, you
never get bored playing Boggle.
And we're dreading the day you
and your husband work things out.
That sounded a lot less
insensitive in my head.
- I'm sorry.
- No, I understand, thank you.
Listen...
can I talk you about something?
Yeah, what is it?
Last night Sam and Woody were
drawing pictures.
That's one of Sam's.
I didn't want to bring it up at
the house with everyone around,
I thought it might be upsetting.
No, I'm glad you showed
this to me.
I'm not a psychiatrist,
but that really looks like a kid
dealing with some kind of trauma.
I'm-I'm not surprised.
I mean....
30 million people died a few months ago.
I'll bet there's kids all over the
country still trying to process that.
Maybe, but it's so specific.
The bodies, the house.
He's coming by after school.
I'll talk to him then.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Sand keeps the copper from buckling.
How'd you learn this?
Well...
like... most things that
are fun and illegal...
from my dad.
So the stories Eric tells are true.
Afraid so.
You remember that book...
something about...
women are from Venus,
and men are wrong.
Not that I read the book, mind you,
but I did,  you know...
flip through Gail's copy of it.
Lot of stuff in there about
men needing to...
go off and hold up in
a cave sometime.
Now, I don't know if this was
actually in the book, but...
if men can't find a cave,
they'll make one.
Out of...
whatever circumstances happen
to be lying around.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I'm sure that's all it is.
This isn't your fault, Mary.
It wasn't anybody's fault.
I think Eric's figuring that out.
This place is the only reason New Bern
made it through the Depression.
The factory whistle's like
a heartbeat to this town.
Put the wind turbines binds
together just down here.
Sheriff!
Who's that?
It's a friend of Heather's.
We met him at Black Jack.
Good news.
- This guy knows where your brother is.
- Really? Where?
Eric went home.
He and Heather both.
They... left this morning.
- Home? To Jericho?
- Why would they do that?
Why didn't they go
with the convoy?
Well, Heather had to talk
him into going. So...
by then, the other guys had left.
So, I lent them my car
and my rifle.
They didn't seem worried at all.
Probably back in Jericho by now.
Right.
- Hope they're okay.
- Thank you.
- We got to clear the building.
- All right.
What happened?
We had to retrofit all the
machines after the EMP,
and one of them overheated.
Caught part of the building on fire.
You got what you need?
Yeah, mystery solved, I guess.
Good. Glad to hear it.
If there's nothing else, Deputy Perkins
will escort you out of town.
No. We don't need
to be escorted.
It's policy.
You're big on policy.
We almost lost everything when
Ravenwood came through here.
I'm big on anything that
keeps us alive.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Move the truck.
Let them through.
- You buying any of that story?
- Nope.
Neither was Ted.
Slipped me this when
he shook my hand.
- It's an address and...
- "Come Alone"
So, we done here?
Back it up.
Let them through.
How long have I been gone?
No, before you answer that,
how long has he been here?
- It's very recent really.
He hasn't been here that long.
I asked you to do one
thing for me, Mimi.
One thing!
You know, you listen
to me, Stanley.
Your sister is not a child anymore.
You can't just throw this fit
and kick Sean's ass
and think that's going
to be the end of it
I hope you're going to
explain why I can't.
Because if you do,
she's just going to latch
on that much tighter.
Unless they really get angry,
in which case, the age-old teenage
remedy is to run away,
which used to mean that they'd
hear from them in a couple of days
when they ran out of bus money.
Nowadays, chances are much better
that you'll find their bodies
on the side of a road.
Look...
right now it is under our roof.
And it's a pain in the ass, I know,
but it's a safe and manageable
pain in the ass,
and I suggest you let it stay here
before it turns into anything
more than that.
That's Perkins' truck.
What's he doing staking
out Ted's trailer?
Let's ask him.
Hand your gun to my friend,
and let's pay Ted a little visit.
Come on.
Where's my brother?
I don't know, ask him.
He threatened to throw me in jail this
morning if I didn't feed you that lie.
- So you haven't seen Eric?
- No. Not for days.
- What about Heather?
- She left for work this morning.
Next thing I know, they tell
me she's gone missing, too.
Two people disappear,
nobody knows anything?
Oh, somebody does.
Right?
Where is he?
Screw you.
Hey, come on, Jake,
we got to be smarter than that.
We need answers.
Getting answers...
is easy.
It's getting the truth...
that takes work.
When did you last see Eric Green?
Look...
this is not my thing.
I didn't ask you that, did I?
Why do you act like
we did something wrong?
We were attacked.
How do you figure that?
The those machines didn't overheat
this morning at the factory.
It was his brother...
and that girl.
They sabotaged it.
They would never do that?
We need that factory
just as much as you do.
- I saw them.
- If you saw them, then where are they?
They ran away.
Hold his knees, please.
Look,
why would I be staking out
a trailer park if we had them? Huh?
Constantino put us on alert.
He gave a SOS.
- SOS?
- Shoot on sight.
Look at me.
What is in that factory?
I don't know.
No, I'm a cop. I'm a cop.
Ask Constantino.
He knows?
Look at me.
- We go to the factory.
- But Eric...
I don't know about Eric.
But we cannot search this whole town.
So we should go and see what it was
that he was risking his life for.
All right.
You got some place safe you can go?
Yeah, my grandfather has
an old hunting cabin.
You take what's important because
you are not coming back here.
Get up.
On your knees.
What is he doing?
- Down on your knees.
- What?
What are you doing?
Hawkins!
Is that doing it your way?
You asked me to come along.
- What were you going to do?
- You want the truth?
Less than you would have.
You see, I've done...
I've done enough, Jake,
to know better.
It's the fear of torture
that gets results.
Actual torture only works
in the movies.
And this one guy, he was
so skinny, you could
count his ribs through his shirt.
I tried to give him food when I could,
but none of us had much so...
And then one day, I could just...
see it in his eyes.
He'd, uh...
he'd given up.
I never thought I'd be so
thankful to live on a farm.
From now on, I promise
I'll only complain intermittently.
Well, we don't have much, but, uh...
we'll always have enough, so...
Dude, all they need to do
is get the Internet back up.
After that, it's a piece of cake.
Why is that?
Well, you could do anything.
I mean, you could run for president.
Make a virtual White House.
Fly a plane into that.
I mean, virtual cities and towns...
nothing to nuke.
- Yeah, but...
where would we get...
stuff?
What stuff?
I don't know.
Food, clothes, blankets, fuel.
Not a problem.
After the Internet is back up,
you just order all that stuff.
You know, Stanley,
you would not believe
how helpful Sean has been
around here with the livestock,
and the house,
and... just everything.
It's true.
Yeah, it's weird, Stanley, 'cause
I am much more of a vibe guy.
What the hell is a vibe guy?
You know...
I mean, I've never been into, like,
physical labor.
I'm more the guy that people
have around for my vibe.
My house, my rules, my vibe.
And you sleep there.
So anyhow, it's, like, 3:00 a. m.,
I've got this flashlight in my face.
Gail's over on her side of
the bed trying to find the phone
to call the cops and finally,
I located the light switch.
It's Eric,
who's standing there and he says,
"I can't go to sleep until
I confess I'm drunk. "
I said, "You're what?"
He said, "I'm drunk."
"It won't ever happen again.
I don't know what I was thinking."
Well, meantime,
he looks perfectly normal,
his speech isn't slurred or anything.
Gail starts grilling him. Turns out
he has had a beer and a half.
I said to him,
"Son, do you have any idea
how much beer it takes to get drunk?"
He said, "No, I don't. "
I said, "Well, get out of here and
don't wake me up again until you do."
He left, Gail and
I just could not stop laughing.
She doesn't laugh too much anymore.
Here I am rambling on. We probably ought
to go take a look at that still.
Good idea.
Hey, buddy.
Your mom just ran to the little
girls' room. Why don't you grab a seat?
Could you give us a minute?
Sure.
Say, you know what?
Why don't we go sit in my office,
maybe we can talk.
About what?
About your artwork.
This is Russell.
He saved our butts out
at the Black Jack.
Hi. It's nice to meet you. I'm Skylar.
Stevens, right?
Something we can help you with?
Well, I was thinking
we could help each other.
You've got a salt mine
with no real distributor.
I've got men, trucks, guns,
but no supplies.
- If we become partners...
- Partners?
I'm asking for half
your share of the mine.
We're doing okay now.
Okay, but the people in Jericho,
they only need so much salt.
I've been out there.
I know the trade routes,
where to find the highest bidders
and how to make it
back here in one piece.
What's in it for us?
Bigger profits.
Where I'm going, I can get you
five times what you can make here.
And...
I'll deal with Gray Anderson for you.
When do you need an answer?
Before I leave in the morning.
Believe me,
this is good for everyone.
It's a full inventory of Jericho.
It's our mine.
And our town.
They sliced it up like they own it.
What do they know that we don't?
Come on.
Hey, sweetie.
What's going on?
We were talking about my drawings.
Look, do you mind waiting
in the lobby a minute?
I just need to talk to
Mr. Taylor alone. Okay?
What are you doing?
Darcy, something going on,
and it's not just about the bombs.
My son has enough to deal with,
you know, without
being poked and prodded.
If there's a problem with him,
I'll take care of it myself.
Right.
Thank you.
For what?
Letting Sean stay.
You're welcome.
And for not calling him an idiot
even when he is done.
Okay, if you know that...
Sorry. Just a little frog
in my throat.
Don't let me interrupt your nice
sibling-bonding moment.
That's what it is, right?
Sean can be an idiot,
but he can also be really great.
All guys are like that,
you have to put up with the
"idiot" stuff...
to get to the "great" stuff.
Yeah? And where did you come
by that litlle pearl of wisdom?
What did she say about me?
When did he learn how to sign?
He's sleeping with a deaf girl.
That's my sister.
I guess if Sean Henthorn is
my biggest problem, then
I'm a pretty lucky guy.
Want to get luckier?
What are you doing?
It's binding.
The lawyer said it makes me
an emancipated minor.
By declaring your parents dead?
This is wrong
in every way that
something can be wrong.
- Let's just forget about this.
- You can't do that.
- It's legal.
- So,
what, are you gonna pedal your little
bike to Topeka and file this, Dale?
Forget that I'm the mayor.
Okay, I'm speaking to you as
your parents' friend.
My parents would want me to have
my share of the salt mine
Your parents are coming back.
And if it turns out that
that is not true,
then I will help you learn the business.
And who decides when that happens?
You?
I mean my decision, are you saying
laws don't apply any more?
You didn't make a decision.
You signed a piece of paper.
Do you really want your parents
to be dead that badly?
- Okay, stop it.
- No.
You're advising her, Dale.
Did you also tell her
how her parents died?
Because New York survived,
so I guess you probably had
to get pretty creative, right?
Were they killed there?
Or were they murdered
on their way back
to the child who meant
everything to them?
It's just a piece of paper.
Come on.
They're making mortar rounds.
They're running a munitions factory.
Hurry up.
Constantino wants those tonight.
We'll have them ready.
They're getting ready for war.
We need to get back to town.
No, we need to try and stop them.
Cover me.
Hey, there he goes.
Down there.
Hold it!
Hand it over.
Sorry. I guess I'm late for dinner.
Or lunch.
Take your pick.
I was helping Mary.
It took longer than I expected.
You told Eric we'd take care of her.
What I meant was that
we'd help keep her alive.
What I didn't mean was that
we'd run over there
and spend the entire day
every time she needed
somebody to do
a little heavy lifting.
Wait.
You don't think
I'm the reason Eric left?
Do you?
Is that what you think?
I think Eric left for
a lot of reasons...
...but Mary may be why he comes back.
I don't want to have to come back
to this house again.
Did you get all the toys you want?
So,
what did you and Mr. Taylor
talk about today?
Nothing.
Now, Sam, you know we don't keep
secrets in this family.
Yeah, I know, baby.
What's he doing here?
I think we should talk.
Hey, Sam, honey,
why don't you go upstairs
to your room and
get that last box, okay?
Hey, buddy.
Look, I-I understand, you know,
you being curious about my family.
We haven't made a lot of friends here.
We just kind of keep to ourselves, but
if you want to ask any questions,
just talk to me, okay?
Leave my children out of it.
But I think Sam's trying to say
something with that drawing.
Something he can't put into words.
What do you mean?
He's drawing a little boy
that's afraid...
...because his dad's not
around to protect him
or his family.
I told him he's not alone.
I know what it's like to have
parents who have split up.
I told him
I'd been through it, and...
I think I turned out okay, so...
I think you turned out better
than okay, Jimmy.
I appreciate that.
So, I guess I'll head back
to the house then.
See you there.
Thank you, Jimmy.
Sure.
- How did it go?
- Good.
Turbines all went up without a hitch.
Thank...
Thank you.
You were as good as your word.
Even better.
I'm glad you see it that way,
because I have another
proposition for you.
We need salt.
Well, it's no problem.
I'll have my guys load up your truck.
Well, actually,
I mean to help you sell it.
We were thinking
a quarter stake in the mine.
Would we be Constantino?
Is that what all of
this good will was about?
No. Hear me out.
This will work for both of us.
For both of our towns.
If you agree to let me sell salt
from the mine.
I'm sorry.
I guess you and the, uh, Olsen twins
think this is kind of cute.
Well, for whatever it's worth,
we did conduct a legal transaction.
- Not for sale.
- Your people on New Bern
who think it should be.
- I don't care what they think.
You need to.
When I saw that
map of Jericho,
I asked Heather about it.
She didn't think
New Bern could do that to us.
Then she snuck in, and, uh...
she saw the mortars and...
their plans.
Look, you're going back to whatever
rock you crawled out from under.
Dan, get in here!
Mr. Mayor, there's a lot more
going on here than you realize.
- Is that so?
- I'm trying to help you.
Look, New Bern barely
survived the winter.
And the people there, they know
the food is coming from you.
And they also know that it's not going
to be enough to feed everyone,
and so, some of them, they're thinking,
what can we do about that
right now?
I want you to find every deputy you can
and get them up to the salt mine.
I want it under heavy guard
until further notice.
Gray, I've already got men up there.
Gray, listen to me.
This deal is a good thing.
I know you don't see it that way
right now, but please,
you do not want the alternative.
These rumors about Jericho,
about the food hoarding,
about how they sicced Ravenwood on us...
maybe they're not just rumors.
We restored their power supply,
and now that Jericho has what it needs,
it has no intention of making good
on its half of the deal.
Why didn't you just leave town?
'Cause we wanted to break the machine,
stop the factory.
Then they caught us.
They brought me here.
So, where is she?
Where is Heather?
She's dead, Jake.
But it's not enough for them
to keep their food
and leave us to starve.
You, up. You, too.
They want to see us destroyed.
I looked their mayor in the eye,
I told him how desperate
our situation was.
But on the day
that we made good
on our end of the deal,
what did they do?
They tried to destroy the factory
that keeps this town alive.
Here's your proof.
These are the sons of Johnston Green,
sent from Jericho to wreak
havoc on this town.
Now we know,
if these people had their way,
New Bern would cease to exist.
With your help
and sacrifice,
I will make sure that
that never happens.
[ www.seriessub.com ]