Previously on Jericho...
Jake Green.
How you doing, man?
- Wait a minute, where the hell you been?
- Around.
Jake, no one's been around for five years.
Seriously...
where have you been?
Hey, brother.
- What you put this family through...
- Johnston, for God's sake...
- Now, he could've been...
- You could spend a week talking
about what I could've been, all right?
- Stay one more day.
- I gotta get back to San Diego by tomorrow.
All right, looks like the explosion
came from the west, maybe Denver.
- Are we under attack?
- This could've be a test,
could've been an accident.
Hi, Dale.
Sorry I didn't call sooner, Angel, but we...
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
I am so sorry.
- I didn't know your mother was in Denver.
- She was in Atlanta.
Oh, my God!
- My mom died yesterday.
- I think my mom died yesterday, too.
Get April.
We'll meet you at the medical center.
There's an empty prison bus out there.
Look, I know you're telling people
it was an accident,
but if it was an attack, Sheriff...
...there's chaos out there,
you might not want the wrong people knowing
that Jericho was still here.
Riley!
Is there anybody on this channel?
There are men here with guns.
I think they might have killed the sheriff.
Won't the rain clear
the radiation out of the air?
- Yes, and bring it straight down
on Jericho. - How do you know
about radiation, Mr. Hawkins?
Because I was a cop in St. Louis
and after 9-11, we got up to speed.
How long before the radiation gets here?
How long does it normally take a storm to
get here from Denver?
Less than two hours.
Everyone over here can go
to the town hall shelter.
All those on the north side
will go to the clinic.
Our shelter's no good.
I'm bringing these people to town hall.
They can't come in here, Jake.
- What do you mean they can't come in here?
- We're packed.
The salt mine, how many people will it hold?
We have to seal the entrance.
There's no door, Jake.
Well, we can't just let the rain
pour down the shaft.
These people won't be safe.
We're all clear.
- What's happening out there?
- I don't know.
You always know something.
You know, don't ask me questions.
She's still not talking.
I get that.
I mean, I'm a cop.
I've never killed anybody.
She'a schoolteacher.
Where's Stanley?
Jake, my brother doesn't know
about the radiation.
When the rain stops,
he'll be back, don't worry.
Bonnie, I know Stanley.
He'll be fine.
Jake, I got your brother.
- He's with your dad.
- Finally.
- Eric, how's Dad?
- He's good.
The town hall shelter is secure.
Listen, Jake, where are you?
I'm at the Richmond's.
As soon as the rain stops,
get every digging tool you can
find and get to the mine
I had to blow the entrance
to keep the rain out.
These people have been sealed
up way too long.
And I'm more worried the explosion
might have put some debris
into the ventilator.
Enough to slow it down?
Enough to shut it down.
We got to get them out.
We can't reach anyone at the mine.
We have no radio contact with anyone there.
Here, honey, take a little sip.
Okay, just a little. Pass it on.
Good, you guys, good.
Good, good, good.
One second.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me.
Hey.
- How you holding up?
- Oh, Heather.
I think our students
are taking it better than I am.
They just know there's
nothing to be afraid of.
For them, it's just like a bad field trip.
I'll be fine.
- Just having a hard time breathing.
- It's all right.
Here, take a little water.
Yeah.
Good.
I have to get outside.
Soon.
- Is Mr. Rennie okay?
- He's gonna be fine.
We just need to give him
a little bit of room, okay?
Go on back.
I can't do this!
- Got to get outside!
- It's okay.
Deep breath, deep breath.
You doing all right?
Stupid question?
Right.
How do you know the rain's radioactive?
Denver's pretty far away.
Well, we don't know how many bombs
there were, we don't know...
What is it?
Someone's up in the house.
Not more prisoners?
- Stanley!
- Bonnie, thank God.
No! Hey, hey!
No! Uh-uh.
Stanley, don't touch her.
The rain may be radioactive.
April, Stanley seems to be okay.
I'd say he was in it for about 20 minutes.
Yeah, I was out at my cousin's
helping him put the livestock up
and got caught in it.
Is he vomiting?
No, he's not.
Okay, do you have any iodine there?
Bonnie, iodine?
Hey, what's with all the tanks?
What tanks?
On my way home, I passed a line of tanks.
They were hauling ass towards Denver.
Stanley, how many tanks did you see?
- Five, maybe.
- Where?
They were over the ridge.
I couldn't tell you
exactly where they were.
But I was on Pharr's Mill Road near I-70.
April, we have iodine.
He's going to need to take
a couple of tablespoons.
But it tastes vile,
so do you have any bread,
something that he could take with it?
We're in a cellar-- all we've got
is canned peaches and pickles.
Not the pickles.
Maybe the peaches.
Jake, just give me the iodine.
The second that the rain breaks,
rush him to the clinic.
And, Jake...
if he throws up in the next couple of hours
get Bonnie out of that room.
Why?
Because her brother's going to die.
- Just concentrate on breathing, please
- I can't.
Got to get out of here.
- I know. Soon.
- I got to get out of here!
Mr. Rennie, please, just concentrate
on your breathing.
Look at me.
Controlled.
Very...
- I got to get out of here.
- I know, Mr...
I got to get out of here!
I don't want to die down here!
Get me out of here!
- I don't want to be here!
- Look, everybody just calm down.
There's nothing to worry about.
- You're scaring the children, Scott.
- I can't breathe.
- He's claustrophobic.
- We got to get him out of here.
- Look, it's me.
- I'm sorry.
It's Shep. Try to focus, man
- try to focus.
- I got to get out of here!
- We got to get him away from these people.
I can't breathe!
- I don't want to die down here!
- Please be careful!
Please!
Stay back.
I don't want to die down here!
I don't...
Get me out of here!
- Jake wants to talk to you.
- His cough's getting much worse.
- I want you to make it brief.
- Okay, okay.
Yeah, son, what is it?
Dad, Stanley saw a line of tanks near I-70.
Well, you know,
there's a National Guard unit
to the southwest of there in Goodland.
Maybe they've got a relief effort going.
We need to get out there and see.
That could be a dangerous thing to do, son.
Can't just sit around and wait
to find out what's happening.
I'll go to Goodland.
Someone should check out Topeka.
Okay, son.
I'm going with you.
What?
I have to find Roger,
- and Goodland's on the way to Wichita.
- You're in no condition to...
I'm going.
With you or I'm going by myself.
For the last time,
you can't smoke here.
- waters for everyone.
- Thank you, honey.
- Johnston, I need to take
your temperature again.
- Oh, you just took it five minutes ago.
- Shh...
- Hasn't changed in five minutes.
- The mighty Johnston Green
felled by the flu. - Here it comes.
I don't know if I told you this
but my father is impervious to mere germs.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, I believe that was the quote.
- First inauguration-- have it all on video.
- It was a joke.
I was trying to...
April, don't ever make a mistake.
This family will never let you forget it.
Okay, I'll remember that.
- Oh, come on.
- But still...
- Shh, Johnston.
I don't like him.
Me neither.
Here.
They're really stale.
You know, I keep thinking about
when we were kids
and how they used to make us practice
hiding under our desks
in case of an atomic bomb.
Yeah, duck and cover.
That's the first thing I thought of
when I saw that mushroom cloud.
Did they have enough time
to hide under their desks?
That's pretty stupid, huh?
No.
Eric?
I'm just a little confused.
Your wife isn't really acting like someone
- who knows the marriage has
been dead a long time.
- Mary...
Or did I get the wrong impression?
Mary, let's just get through this, okay?
Well, the next thing you're gonna tell me
is that she actually does understand you.
I'm sorry.
Jake, don't let Bonnie see your lips.
Listen, man.
If this thing doesn't turn out so good--
- the thing is,
Bonnie's still just a kid, so... - Stanley.
Don't even, all right?
- You're gonna be fine.
- I don't know.
My head is pounding and I feel like
I'm gonna throw up.
Eric, the rain has stopped.
What's this black stuff?
That used to be Denver.
- Bill, Emily, get Stanley
to the medical clinic now. - Okay.
Find April, she'll know what to do.
- Jimmy, you're coming with me to ne,
all right? - Jake.
- I meant what I said, all right?
- I know.
Look, I know, I know.
I will help you find Roger.
- I promise, okay?
Go, I'll meet you at the medical clinic.
Eric, we're coming to the mine now.
We have to dig those people out.
What was that?!
I think somebody's on the other side.
Get these people out of here.
All right, everyone,
you're gonna be okay.
All right, we have food and water.
And there are vehicles waiting for you guys
to take you to the clinic, all right?
Nice and slow.
File out, these guys'll help you.
Listen, you're okay.
Women and children first.
Please. Watch your step,
everyone, be careful.
It's gonna be okay.
- Are you okay?
- I think so.
Gray, what happened?
He's dead.
What?
Hey.
- Hey, how's Stanley?
- We're still watching him.
Where is he?
- We had to isolate him.
- Where? Where is he?
What the hell?
Do you like it?
It's where they make
the contagious kids wait
so they don't give everybody chicken pox.
- Did you throw up?
- Yeah, a couple times.
Apparently, that's what happens
when you drink a bottle of iodine.
I need to get back to the house.
I need to check on the livestock.
I need to check on the corn.
I need to get out of here.
- There's really nothing you
can do right now. - He's right.
- You need to stay.
- Yeah...
I'm really sick of being poked with
needles every ten minutes.
They'll be sorry when my
spider powers kick in.
Well, you're still an idiot,
so that's a good sign.
Yeah.
How bad is it?
Well, you're sleep deprived
like everyone else.
Bring the bandages to 102.
No, I mean the radiation.
Am I dying?
- Have you vomited?
- No. Should I?
- You just need some rest; go home.
- I'd like to.
When's the next flight to D.C?
Dr. Green?
Oh, there are a lot of people waiting.
- If you could just... - I just want
to know what happened to my friend.
Scott Rennie.
It looks like he had a heart attack.
I'm sorry.
But...
So what if I have three queens,
but I only have two jacks?
- I'm out.
- I so bluffed you.
- Skylar, are you still alive in there?
- Hey, what's up?
Sky, are you home?
- Hello?!
- Hey...
- Dude, I'm starving.
- What's up?
- Oh, my God.
- What's he doing here?
This is not how it looks.
It sure looks how it looks.
Skylar, wait.
That guy's a weirdo.
I can't just sit around here all day.
We've got to find the sheriff and his men,
- we've got to get the power back on.
- Okay, now you're going to
stay here as long as it takes.
Now, don't make me take your pants with me.
- I can run this town without my pants.
- It wouldn't be the first time.
- Huh.
- All right.
That's a story I never want to hear.
Sweetheart.
How are you feeling, honey?
My leg's a little sore, but...
how's everything here?
- Your father has the flu.
- It's nothing.
Did you hear Mr. Rennie died?
It's terrible.
I've been thinking,
more than anything,
this town needs information.
We could organize a group of people.
Send them out in every direction.
- I don't think anyone should be
leaving Jericho. - We have to.
We can't just sit here in the dark.
He's right.
Makes us too vulnerable.
Abrams, you and Crossfield are taking
the northern route
up through Nebraska to the state police
barracks in Broken Bow.
Well, I can go east to Topeka
and connect with the state government.
Ridley can head west to Denver.
Well, what's left of it.
You'll probably run into a ring
of FEMA and EMS people
before you even get
within sight of the city.
See what they know.
What about you?
He's going to Wichita with me.
That's right, Emily and I are taking the
southern route to Wichita.
Well, let's try to radio
back as much information
as possible along the way.
That's the plan.
Hitting the major cities in each direction
north, south, east and west.
- The four horsemen of the apocalypse.
- Let's hope not.
Nope, we've still got static.
Try pointing it east.
We've got nothing,
keep moving it.
Nope, just static.
Just keep trying.
Mary.
Excuse me.
Man.
Busy place.
Yeah, although the service
isn't what it used to be.
What'll you have?
Oh, my God.
We've got something!
- Where'd it go?
- Come on, bring it back!
We're losing the feed!
- Bring it back!
- Go back. We had something.
Was that Korean?
- Does anybody know?
- I think it was Chinese.
It was Mandarin.
The question is, were they just reporting it
or were they behind it?
Did Stanley say if there were any markings
- on the side of the tank?
- No.
- I mean, maybe we're being invaded.
- Abrams and Crossfield are out.
- They won't drive into a war zone.
- Yeah, well, I don't blame them.
Look, why don't we put this plan
on hold right now?
We saw one image;
we'll probably see another one.
Going out is more important
than ever, all right?
If this country is at war,
we need to know it.
Okay, we have Los Angeles,
Seattle and Philadelphia.
- What else did you see on the TV?
- I think Seattle's wrong.
- Okay. Uh, could it have been Portland?
- I don't think so.
Hey.
- I understand you lost some of your men?
- Yeah.
Need a volunteer, I'm available.
- Thanks, Mister...
- Hawkins.
Mr. Hawkins.
- Do you have a family?
- Two kids.
I think it's best if we stick to people
who don't have families.
Hey. Em?
Um, excuse me? Mr. Cale?
Something's been bothering me.
It's about Mr. Rennie's death.
The mine was full of people from the clinic.
How come nobody called for a doctor?
I don't want to talk about it.
I know you're upset.
But he was my friend, too.
I... I worked with him for three years.
Hey, Shep?
We're heading out for supplies.
Why don't you give us a hand?
You know, this whole thing
has been pretty hard on Shep.
He lost a good friend today.
We all did.
Emily?
Talk to me.
Was it the broadcast?
- Because we don't know
what any of it means.
- They got Wichita.
Roger is dead.
- We don't know that.
- I saw it on the map.
- Your fiancé might have made it.
- How?
What if his flight
got diverted to Des Moines?
Des Moines' gone.
Emily, what if it was Omaha, huh? Or Tulsa.
What if they set down in the middle of
a cornfield in Nebraska?
He could be anywhere.
Plane went down trying
to find a place to land.
- What if it exploded?
- Emily.
- What if he's dead?
- He's gone, and I'm here with you.
- Emily.
You were supposed to be the one
that was dead... not him.
Just leave me alone, Jake.
Go without me.
They took everything.
Oh, Dale.
Thank God.
I looked everywhere for you.
Are you all right?
I was so worried.
- I was safe.
- Good.
Gracie?
Oh, what now?
We're closed, Gail.
- I'm out of everything.
- That's why I'm here.
Some of the folks at the shelter brought
some stuff back,
and I thought you could use it.
It's one box.
I'm out of business.
My train shipment was supposed
to come through on Tuesday.
Without a delivery,
these shelves are gonna stay
as empty as they are right now.
I don't have a freezer anymore.
- Most of this stuff is going
to go bad any minute now.
- I know. Food's going bad all over town.
I need my shipment.
But we don't know if we'll ever
get the power back on.
Maybe we should cook it.
- What?
- Yeah. Everything, all of it.
As long as it's still good enough to eat.
Are you okay?
If you call radiation poisoning okay.
Were you out in the rain, too?
Oh, heavens, no.
I touched a building
when we came out of the shelter.
Oh.
Look, you can stop pretending.
What do you mean?
I audited your farm.
Why do you care?
Maybe I'm a nicer person than you.
Right.
Were you in the rain?
Yeah, for about 20 minutes.
- Well, you look pretty good.
- Thanks.
Try to work out.
Look, um... you know I think
I got the worst of it.
So as long as I'm okay,
you should be fine.
You're really sweet.
- And you still owe the IRS $180,000.
- Yeah, I know.
Every radio needs to be fully charged.
We'll stay in contact as long as we can.
Gray, the long-range ones are all charged.
- They're in the storage unit.
- All right, thanks.
Ridley, why don't you go
pack up the Geiger counters and the flares?
I'll meet you out there.
Gray, I just wanted to tell you
how much I appreciate what you're doing.
It's a gutsy move, and, uh,
- the whole town thanks you.
- Yeah, thanks.
What the hell happened out there?
I've known Scott Rennie his whole life.
He's strong as an ox.
I just...
I can't believe he's dead.
He was a good man.
- Heart attack at his age.
- Yeah, well, it wasn't a heart
attack that killed him.
- What do you mean?
- It was poor planning.
What are you talking about?
What I'm saying is that none of this
would have happened
if that clinic shelter had been maintained.
- You have a lot of people to answer to.
- All right, that's enough.
No, that's not nearly enough.
I get back here,
there's gonna be an investigation.
Hundreds of people could have died
'cause you dropped the ball.
- Why don't we talk about this in my office?
- You dropped the ball,
and it killed Scott Rennie.
In my office. Now.
Right now these people need our leadership.
I will not have you tearing this town apart.
And when all this is over,
if you and I are still alive,
you investigate your ass off.
In the meantime, if I hear any more
talk like that out of you,
you and I are gonna have a problem.
Do we understand each other?
- Where's Emily?
- She's not going.
Good.
- You're not going alone, are you?
- Yeah.
Don't give me that look.
- What look?
- You know what look. That look.
Hey, I told you 7,500 times
I have watched you drive away
not knowing if you were coming home.
I've earned a look.
I'm coming back.
Let's go!
Ridley?
Come on.
Shep?
Taking Ridley's place.
Going to Denver.
You don't have to do this.
What about your family?
I got to get out of here.
Shep, you'll get past this.
Yeah?
- Hey, Heather.
- Oh.
- Shep left this for you.
- Thanks.
"Dear Heather,
"I want you to know the truth
about Scott Rennie.
"It was my fault.
"Gray wanted me to keep him quiet,
"and his heart went out.
"I should have called
for a doctor, but I was scared.
"I let him die.
"I'll never forgive myself.
"You were a good friend to Scott.
"A better friend than I ever was.
Shep."
Well, they should be about
50 miles out by now.
Jake, are you still reading me? Jake?
I lost him.
Shep, are you there? Shep?
Eric, do me a favor.
I missed that last one, Shep.
Can you say it again?
Tell him I'm sorry.
Tell the family I'm sorry.
You're breaking up, Shep.
Hey, Gray, did you catch that?
No.
No, I didn't.
- I don't know, that would make
about 45 miles. - Right, so,
in about an hour...
- Jake, what are you doing back?
- You should be in Wichita by now.
- Smoky Hill Bridge is blocked.
- What is that?
It's a flight data recorder.
- I thought they were supposed to be black.
- Well, where'd you get it?
A couple of pilots used the highway
as a landing strip with mixed results.
- This is the only one I could get.
- Were there any survivors?
It was a commuter plane that didn't make it,
a 757 that was empty.
Well, where are they?
Where'd they go?
How do we listen to this?
- Do you have that old reel-to-reel
laying around? - Yeah.
Your father needs to hear this.
I'm going to go get him.
- You okay?
- Yeah. I'm a little freaked.
Dad's here.
I've gone through most of this recording
from the plane that crashed.
This is the last 30 seconds or so.
A lot of background noise. You can hear...
pilots from planes in the area
talking to each other.
Wait.
The kids.
Oh, yeah. Come on, girls. Let's go.
Is anyone on this frequency?
There's no reply from ATCC!
Please advise. Ray-27 in emergency descend,
need coordinates for approach.
Give me full flaps; it's about to get bumpy.
This is Chinook 116 heavy.
Missed our handoff to Kansas City ATCC.
Does anyone read us? Over.
Chinook 116, this is Glen 5-6, reading you.
We're bingo fuel,
lost all VFR heading out of Chicago.
Tried all frequencies;
there's no one out there.
What does that mean?
They're out of gas and blind.
Guys, this is Primary 221.
I've got a mushroom cloud 16 kilometers
in height somewhere northwest over Denver.
I've got a visual on two separate plumes--
one over in Kansas City and one
south somewhere in Texas.
- Does anyone read ATC? - Negative.
There is no ATCC anymore, Chinook.
He's saying there's no traffic control.
There's 10,000 planes with no place to land.
That's about a million people in the air.
Whoa! Are those F-16s?
Right. Do you have a visual?
Affirm. Prime Missouri Guard.
131st out of Landburg.
These guys are hauling ass somewhere.
Chinook 116, this is Glen 5-6.
We found a stretch of highway long enough.
Follow us in. Setting down
On final approach, stand by.
Here we go.
Flaps, I need more flaps.
Losing it.
I can't hold it.
We're sliding here.
- Pull up! Pull up!
- I can't...!
Chinook 116, this is Glen 5-6.
We found a stretch of highway long enough.
We found a...
- Chinook 116, this is Glen 5-6.
- Trans Shore...
We found a stretch of highway long...
Emily, come here.
- Roger was on Trans Shore 724, right?
- Yes.
Listen.
- This is primary...
- Jake, what is this?
- Just listen.
My co-pilot's blind. Background chatter.
- Chinook 116, this is Glen 5-6.
- This is Trans Shore 724.
We've set down in a field,
GPS malfunctioned.
I think we're north of Kansas.
Minor injuries.
He's alive. He's alive.
Robert?
There's, uh, music outside.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, the party.
Sounded like Sam Cooke from here, but, uh
there's a chance it could be Kenny Rogers.
Oh, Lord.
Robert, the kids would like to go.
- To the party?
- Yes.
We're not ready.
- Robert.
- No.
No.
Well, I'm glad there was
enough food for everyone.
I just wish someone would've said thank you.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Thanks.
She looks so much better.
You really made her happy.
- I owed her.
- Well, I'd say this makes you even.
Not even close.
You haven't said two words all night.
Just taking it all in.
It might be a long time before
we see Jericho like this again.
I got to go.
What time is it?
It's a little past midnight.
Do you really have to go?
Yeah, I should probably go.