Previously on Jericho
Bring them inside.
Some of them were on planes
that landed in
the middle of nowhere.
They've been walking
for weeks.
They must have gone
through hell.
Oh, my God... Roger.
You have moderate frostbite
on your toes and fingers.
You need to keep
them clean and warm.
Do you know anyone
in Jericho?
Actually... I do.
Hello, Rob.
We're using the generator
to power the town hall
for three hours a day,
the Med Center for six.
With 53 new people, at current
levels of consumption...
we will be completely out
of gas and diesel in two weeks.
- Mrs. Green?
- What?
Eric told me that
April's pregnant.
It's the Old Man.
He's coming for us
using us against each other.
We go see him and if,
if he is behind this,
We take him out.
We leave first thing
in the morning.
Any luck out there?
Sorry, ma'am.
Nothing?
Not even rabbits?
Never seen anything
like it before.
Nothing moving out there.
Think it was the fallout? Maybe it was
the radiation that killed the deer.
There'd still be dead animals,
carcasses, something.
I mean, it was weird.
Like all the game had vanished.
How far out
did you go?
15 miles out by Mill Pond
along the creek there.
Guess we're going to have
to drive, huh, Jake?
Yeah, but we have to be careful
about burning the gas rations
in the middle of winter.
We need everything we can
to run the generator.
We can live without
power for now.
Make fires to stay warm.
But we won't see Spring
if we don't eat.
Stanley and I will have to use
whatever gas we can spare.
and go out west,
Go out as far as it takes.
The rest of the hunting parties
will have to scrounge around locally.
Yeah, and Mimi's coming
with us.
What?
Well, in case something happens to me,
I want to make sure she knows...
how to trap and shoot, okay?
Look, the further you get
the hairier the roads are.
With food being
as scarce as it is,
there's bound to be
some trouble out there.
That sleeping bag's
rated to 40 below
and here's a wind-proof lighter for you.
You're going to need them both.
Good hunting.
I'm guessing the good folks
of Jericho don't know
about all this stuff down here.
- They don't know about a lot of things.
That'll be enough to get us
to the Old Man's place?
He is only about
two hours away.
I didn't realize
he was so close.
He chose the rally point.
Wanted it in his backyard.
How long as he been
watching you?
My guess...
since I stopped communications
a few days ago.
You worried about what we're
going to find out there?
- You're not.
- We can handle him.
It's you and me.
Let's get to work.
My grandmother
went fast than this
and she didn't
even have a car.
We have to take it easy,
we only have half a tank.
Well, hopefully we'll make it
to Flint Springs. It's got...
Hopefully? What do you
mean "hopefully"?
It's got a river.
It's prime white-tailed terrain.
I know, but...
This is crazy.
I told you that
I can't hunt.
Now you want me to kill Bambi.
You're gonna have to
learn, all right?
Everyone's doing their part.
Bonnie's been out twice.
Well, good for
frickin' Bonnie.
Bonnie grew up on farm.
The closest I ever got
to the outdoors
was the is the Ralph Lauren
section of Neiman Marcus.
There you go,
bargain hunting.
Same thing, but with a gun.
Bargains? At Neimans?
Sometimes I forget
that the biggest designer
in your closet is Wrangler.
What are you
laughing at?
I've never seen you in a
domestic squabble before.
Knock it off.
This isn't squabbling.
Oh, my God.
These dogs have tags.
Look at all this.
Wall Drugs.
Wall, South Dakota.
Do you think that's where all
these people were coming from?
Think about it.
South Dakota without heat,
electricity, or...
food being trucked in.
It's got to be even worse
in North Dakota,
Montana.
Oh, my God.
I read about this
at Blackjack.
Mass migration, hundreds...
maybe thousands of people
heading south.
Trying to outrun winter.
Should we be doing
that, too?
Season 1 - Episode 14
" Heart Of Winter "
[ Transcript ]
swsub.com
[ Synchro ]
mOOchie / Loky / aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
How far is it?
...60.
It's about 60 yards.
So 60 yard with almost
1.5 people per yard.
That's 90.
That's almost 100 people
just across.
The way the ground
is trampled,
you got to figure five
or tens times that amount
of people came through here.
Almost a thousand people?
Where are they going?
South Texas, Mexico.
Anyplace warmer.
It'd take weeks
to get there by foot.
God know how many thousand
people have the same idea.
Mexico's borders
could be closed.
We don't even know if
there still is a Mexico.
Maybe we should try
to catch on with them.
We can barely feed ourselves,
let alone... hundreds more.
We got to keep going.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
I'll be right back.
Hey. Glad you came down.
Thank you.
- What time did you, uh...
- Early...
late, I guess.
I didn't want to wake you,
you looked so peaceful.
Peaceful? Really?
Did you have another one of those
bad dreams? Keep on there.
I guess neither one of
us got much sleep.
All I could do was think about
all these people down here, you know.
And then I remembered about the
clothes we had in the attic.
I thought that sweater
looked familiar.
Yeah, that woman was on
layover in Kansas City
when the bombs went off,
Her husband and two kids
were waiting for her at home.
Where?
Denver.
I lead these people here.
For better or worse
this is their home now.
It's on me to make sure
they're taken care of.
Yeah, of course.
What can I do to help, huh?
Talk to them,
follow your instincts.
The truth is...
I'm winging this myself.
I'll be outside.
Here.
Should be back
before dark.
And if you're not?
Just tell me when I
should start to worry.
This is the last time,
okay?
After today
I'm here...
for good, huh?
Okay.
I'll hold you to that.
Hi, honey.
How'd it go this morning?
The whole thing
was a bust.
I'm sorry, hon.
Jake's out there now.
Hopefully he and Stanley
will have better luck
than I did.
Is April here?
No, she's at
the clinic.
She promised me
she'd take a nap.
I hope it is warmer in that
clinic than it is in this house.
I think this house has
dropped ten degrees
in the last hour.
Feels like a storm's
coming in.
We'd better seal up these
windows the best was we can.
Been going around collecting
old sheets and linens.
We'll shove them
underneath the doors.
Look what I found...
hidden in Jake's closet.
Lord knows how long
that's been there.
Well, at least he was
drinking the good stuff.
I used to hide the most awful
rotgut in the world
behind my mother's
china cabinet.
What do you think?
On an empty stomach?
I'll get the glasses.
Why would anyone destroy all this.
If they'd wanted it out of commission,
they could have just taken it.
Be worth a fortune after the E.M.P.
Maybe there wasn't time,
or maybe they didn't
care about this stuff.
- How long?
- A couple of days...
Give or take.
But we just heard
from him yesterday.
We heard from someone.
Remote uplink.
Somebody else using
his access codes.
Who could have done this?
Wager for the first kill.
I'm in for a dozen eggs.
Two hours chopping wood.
Tax return consultation.
Oh, how about
foot massages for a week?
For me, not for him.
We'll talk.
Stanley, stop.
- What are they doing?
- They're blocking the whole road.
More like staking it out.
All right, turn around.
And... and go where?
I don't know. Just do it, all right?
Turn around. We'll find another road.
I see it. Damn it.
Why are they following us?
Stanley, gun it!
This should get us
back to the highway.
Then what?
We try to make it back home,
find the patrol.
Maybe they'll give up by then
or run out of gas.
Yeah, if we don't first.
Stanley...
Stanley, hold on!
Doesn't look like
he put up much of a fight.
He was probably out
before he knew what hit him.
He must have trusted whoever did it.
The thing is, whoever it was,
they knew what
they were doing there,
not over here.
I mean, look at this.
It's a mess.
But the drives...
They look like they're still intact.
The old man had information
on the entire team...
Contact information,
backgrounds...
Last known whereabouts.
Let's find out where everybody is.
We can't outrun them.
- How far till Jericho?
- Too far.
Oh, God!
Stay down.
Give me that drive you got there.
Must feel good to be back
in the saddle, huh?
I wish we didn't have
to come out here in the first place.
What, are you getting soft on me?
Too much domestic bliss?
Not quite bliss.
There.
There it is. We're in.
Thank you.
Karaoke bullfighter, right?
Excuse me?
At that bar in Barcelona.
You decked a bullfighter who tried
to get you to stop singing that song...
"Stairway to Heaven"?
Did Roger tell you that?
He also mentioned you like Oreo,
ice cream and white daisies.
Don't be mad at him.
He was trying to keep us entertained.
He kept talking and,
somehow, we kept moving.
Hey. How you doing?
I'm a little tired.
I'm going to head home
and get cleaned up.
Think I'll stay here for a
little longer if you don't mind.
Yeah. Of course.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Looks like you owe
these folks a rematch.
So, um...
I will see you when I see you.
- To Jake.
Who would have thought,
six months ago, you'd be toasting him?
Well, God knows Eric wouldn't
have hidden the bottle.
You and Jake have always
had much more in common
than you wanted to admit.
You going hunting
all those weekends...
Why that kid got sit
in a deer stand for hours?
We wouldn't say a word
to each other. Just...
be in the woods together.
I was always afraid that Jake
would forget about that.
You know, that he'd grow up only
remembering the bad times. That we were
That he wouldn't remember
that we had been close.
That we were... buddies once.
He remembers...
deep down.
That's why you mean
so much to him.
Boy, that wind sounds awful.
I hope Stanley and Jake
are okay out there.
What happened?
Jake, Stanley's not moving.
- What?
- Stanley's not moving.
Oh, my God. Go hide.
- Go hide.
- No
- Go on.
- No, No. Stanley...
You'll be fine.
Go! Go hide!
Come on.
Help me with Stanley.
I can't move.
Ritts, Woodworth, Pierce.
That's half the team.
We're being hunted.
It's worse than that.
It's Woodworth and his wife.
They were in Richmond.
That's his daughter.
Anyone close to us
is in danger, too.
No loose ends.
Don't worry about your family.
We're not going to let
anything happen to them.
It's just us, Chavez
and Cheung left.
We'll get back out on the field,
stay in the weeds
until we can connect
with the chief.
Here. Look at this.
What is that?
If we are being hunted,
there... is the hunter.
Stanley, are you okay?
Can you get up?
Your leg?
I think I busted my ankle.
I'm okay.
I'm just stuck.
- Let me try to get this off.
- Stanley, don't.
We can't do this ourselves.
You might make it worse.
Maybe you could dig me out.
All right.
Help me get the shovels. They're in
the bed of the truck.
It's gone.
All right, get the jack.
The jack's back there.
They took everything.
How was your bath?
Lukewarm, then luke-cold,
then pretty much icy.
- Look. Remember this?
- Oh, yeah.
Times Square,
New Year's Eve, 2005.
Wasted.
That hangover was epic.
Do you remember the last thing I said to
you the night before you left Jericho ?
That I was selfish
and I didn't listen?
Something like that?
You have no idea how that ate
at me while you were gone.
- I just kept thinking that was
the last  - You were right.
You know, today,
seeing you with those people...
It was like you had found yourself.
I'm still just trying to figure
it out, you know?
We're not these people anymore.
But I'll tell you the one thing
that hasn't changed.
The one constant.
I love you.
And it's going
to take a whole lot more
than the end of the world
to change that.
- How are your legs?
- I don't know I can't feel anything.
The ground's
frozen solid.
It's sucking the heat
right out of you.
Why can't we build a fire?
You smell the fumes?
You have to get back to town.
All right. I'm going
to try and go.
No. You can't on that ankle.
- I'll go.
- No. Those guys are still out there.
They went the other way.
Jericho has a patrol
five miles out of town.
We can't have come
more than ten.
Jake, it's too dangerous.
What are our options?
With no bags, no fire?
All right, one of you goes
or we all die here.
All right, fine, fine.
I threw a flashlight over there
somewhere. You might need it.
Listen...
stay on the shoulder
the whole time, okay?
If you see any headlights
or you hear any engines,
get low and hide,
all right?
Now, you're gonna
want to head
southeast.
Stanley, that doesn't mean
anything to me.
Stay on this road.
Stay on this road
and then you make...
make your first left
Okay?
And you're gonna go about a mile
and then you're gonna make
your second right,
and you're gonna make another right
and then another left.
And then once you get to the crossroads
of the highway, you're home free...
You'll see a big sign pointing
to the way to Jericho, okay?
Got it?
Left, second right.
Right, left,
Right.
Mimi, I...
Don't worry.
I'll be careful.
Here's what we're gonna do:
I know a place that's safe.
We take Darcy and the kids
out of Jericho
and stash them before you and I
get back on the move.
I am not leaving them alone.
- I don't think you have a choice.
- No...
See, because I've got leverage.
If they kill me, they will
never find the package.
It's not you
they're gonna kill.
It'll be Sam
or Darcy or me;
anything they can use
to get to you.
Anything they can
use to get to me.
The body.
These... These, uh...
...these half-smashed drives,
...this whole...
this whole setup--
If someone had wanted
to destroy all this,
why leave the house
standing, huh?
Why not just burn it all down?
Someone wanted us
to see all this.
We're being played.
Why would anyone go through
all that trouble?
I don't know,
but this is all too big now.
There's too many angles
to cover.
Too many unknowns.
I need to get home.
- Robert, wait.
- What?
Let's think about this.
What's the plan?
What are you going to do?
You know, maybe the plan all
along was to get us out here.
I gotta protect
my family, Sarah.
And what about the package?
It'll need to be moved.
This isn't so bad, right?
Hey, we've been
through worse.
Remember the time we got stuck on
the roof of the...
town hall in the middle
of a lightning storm, huh?
We were so afraid the lightning
was going to...
blow up the fireworks.
You squealed like a little girl
wanting to jump off that roof.
That was you.
Your voice hadn't changed yet.
Please, I had you beat by,
like, six months.
Drink some water.
It's frozen right through.
What?
I saw an abandoned cabin about
a quarter mile up the road.
You need to get inside.
It'll hurt, but you can make it.
- Jake, I'm staying.
- Listen to me!
There's no point in both of us
freezing to death out there.
- She's coming back.
- When?
She's been gone for, like,
an hour.
It'll take her a little while to
reach the patrol,
but when she does,
she'll find someone.
I know she'll find someone.
Unless somebody finds her first.
Look,
it's gonna get dark soon,
you need to go.
You wouldn't leave me
any more than I'm leaving you.
Mimi's strong.
She'll find her way.
Wait...
he said keep going east.
No... southeast.
And... look for a sign.
Oh, God, I hate this place!
Come on, man.
You can't fall asleep.
You got to stay up;
come on.
You stopped shivering.
Come on.
You got to talk to me--
come on, come on, buddy.
You gotta talk to me.
Talk to me, buddy.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
About what?
Five years ago.
Sorry I left the way I did.
Iit's okay. It doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter.
I was gonna call.
I know. Listen, I want you
to forget about it, okay?
We never got to go backpacking
in Costa Rica.
You know what?
We're still gonna get to go
backpacking in Costa Rica, okay?
We're gonna...
we're gonna learn how to surf.
We're gonna sleep
on the beach.
As soon as the planes
are up and running again,
it's gonna be you and me.
Hell, you can fly us
there yourself, huh?
Come on. Come on.
Tell me something good, man.
I haven't talked to you in five years.
You've been gone for five years.
Tell me... Hey, tell me
about San Diego.
How was it?
- Warm.
- Warm, right.
Beaches, blondes, huh?
What were you doing there?
Flying, flying planes.
Really?
That's cool, man.
Your grandfather
would've been psyched, huh?
Did you have a girl there?
I know you had a girl.
She's dead.
What do you mean?
You don't know that.
I mean, it all depends on where she was
when the bombs went off, right?
I mean, she could
have made it, right?
- Tell me what her name was.
- She's dead....
It was my fault.
- It's not your fault.
- Let me lay down.
- Jake, no.
It wasn't your fault.
Come on... Come on...
Come on, stay with me.
You gotta stay with me.
Come on, Jake.
Stay with me, Jake.
Come on, man.
Stay with me.
Come on!
Okay, gotta keep moving.
Gotta keep moving.
Please don't hurt me...
please don't hurt me.
Please don't hurt me!
Please don't hurt me...
Mimi?
- It's Gail and Johnston Green, honey.
You're safe.  - Oh, thanks God!
Come on, baby,
let's get out of here.
Come on.
Those are hideous.
Are those the sheets
from your old apartment?
Because you can't expect
anyone to sleep on those.
If anyone asks, we'll pretend
someone else donated them.
Your dress.
Guess I shouldn't be seeing this, huh?
The day's sort of come and gone, so...
It'll come again.
You think?
I do.
I tell you what, I've got
a pack of Ramen noodles
with your name on it,
what do you say?
Great. I'll deliver this to the shelter
and come back and wash up.
Roger, wait.
I'll come with you.
It's Mom and Dad, honey!
Stanley, you all right, sweetheart?
You need to go get in the truck
and get warm, pal.
- Where's Mimi?
- I'm right here.
Stanley, I'm right here.
Wake up. Wake up!
Wake up, Jake.
Wake up.
Wake up. Oh, thank God.
We're gonna help you, honey.
We saw the storm coming
and we started to worry
when you hadn't come back.
Sweetheart...
Honey,
we're not gonna be able
to get this truck off of him.
I need you to take
these guys back to town
and get me some help out here.
You signal when you're coming back
so I know it's you, all right?
- I'll flash the lights.
- All right, go, go, go!
Jake, look at me, son.
Lookie here.
You're gonna make it, son...
I know you.
I know what you're made of.
You're gonna be all right.
You're gonna make it.
Stay with me now.
Robert, please,
the kids are sleeping.
- I'm sorry.
- What on earth are you doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Jake, you'll be home real soon,
but you got to stay
with me now. Come on.
Leave me here.
Leave me alone.
Now, I'm not going anywhere.
But you got to hang on.
Now, they'll be here soon, son.
Dad...
I'm sorry.
Oh, son, you got nothing
to be sorry about.
Open your eyes, Jake.
Come on, now.
Look at me.
Look at me, Jake.
I can see her.
See who?
The girl.
What... girl?
Jake, I think you're hallucinating, son.
No, listen to me.
When I was in Iraq...
... there was a girl.
She couldn't have been more than...
10 or 12...
Don't talk now, son.
You save your energy.
We'll talk when we get... home.
I killed her, Dad.
I killed a little girl.
Hurry up!
Open your eyes, Jake.
Open your eyes.
All right, everyone on three...
One,
two, three!
All right, he's free.
Let's get the board in here.
One, two, three.
You were right.
I need to get my family
as far away from me as possible.
I've been thinking, and...
There's no other choice.
You're doing the right thing.
Listen.
After they're safe,
you and me need
to get back in the field.
That's half our team gone, Sarah,
and whoever did that
did it for a reason.
How are you gonna tell Darcy?
I'll tell her after I've moved them.
She'll never agree if she knows
I won't be staying with them.
He's better off here
than the med center.
We're still on emergency power,
and it's... it's warmer here.
Here, honey.
What about his injuries?
Well, the cut on his head
isn't very deep,
and neither one
of his legs are broken.
He's very lucky.
I'm freezing.
I'm gonna go get you
some more blankets.
You're still hypothermic.
It's just gonna take a few hours
for your body to stabilize.
- Can we have a minute?
- Oh, sure.
Dad...
What I told you out there...
please forget it.
Please.
Afraid I can't do that.
I've seen a lot of things
in my time, Jake.
I've been to war.
I know what war can do.
I know what men can do... Terrible...
... terrible things.
I know what I did.
You can talk to me.
When you're ready, son.
When you're ready.
You okay?
How's the sprain?
I think it'd be better with painkillers,
but I'm not gonna complain.
You know, for a while there, I didn't
think I'd ever feel anything again.
When I was out there,
just for a moment,
I didn't think
I was gonna make it.
And I stopped... to rest.
And then I just didn't
even want to move.
But you did.
You did make it.
And I knew you would.
Your lips are still cold.
Maybe you can warm them.
That's the worst line
I've ever heard.
I know. I've got others.
- Shut up.
- Okay.
Tomorrow morning...
we're leaving.
We're leaving?
For... for where?
I don't know yet.
You don't know?
Darcy, when I came
to get you in DC...
I told you it wasn't safe,
but I couldn't tell you why.
I'm going for a walk.
I have something
in my possession.
And there's people
out there that want it,
that will stop at nothing to get it.
And that puts you,
me and the kids
in danger here.
Okay, so th... then we go.
I trust you.
Robert, do y...
Do you trust me?
- You're late.
- You're impatient.
Then listen to me.
Okay, Sarah is not on our side.
Now... whatever's...
gone on between the two of you,
I'm telling you, Robert,
she's not here to help us.
Have you located the package?
Soon.
Hawkins is starting to put
the pieces together.
- He needs to be eliminated.
- I know.
We've already eliminated the other
three targets without incident.
Why are you stalling on this one?
Because this one is different.
[ www.seriessub.com ]