Previously on Jericho
Oh, my God... Ted !
We grew up together over in New Bern.
- You just going to leave?
- It won't be for very long.
Johnston, you SOB.
How the hell did you lose an election?
No. The question is, how did you get
to be in charge in New Bern?
They get tired of you being sheriff?
Can we buy some more of these things?
Ten wind turbines for, let's say...
ten percent of your spring crop.
Okay, we'll give you the food.
We're going to need ten Jericho men
to help us build them.
It wasn't safe for us there anymore.
You can't just ride into New Bern
and start breaking china.
It's a full inventory of Jericho.
They slid it up like they own it.
They're making mortar rounds.
They're getting ready for war.
Hold it!
We wanted to break the machine.
Stop the factory.
Where's Heather?
She's dead, Jake.
Everybody go!
Jericho is about to be invaded.
We'll do this day and night
for as long as it takes.
Most of you have no idea of
what's coming.
This isn't a fight about land.
This is a fight for our very existence.
I know this has great artistic merit,
but...
i'm taking these shoes off
in ten minutes.
So, if you don't want
to have to hide my toes...
Oh, Gail, make yourself comfortable.
We can't really do this
without the best man anyway.
Where is Jake?
I don't see him.
Grandpa seems to be missing, too.
Take a wild guess where they are.
Right.
Oh, Beth.
It's so nice to see you, dear.
I need your help.
We need to go over
to the medical center.
- Is everyone in there?
- Yeah. We're just waiting for you.
How is it going out there?
They took Talbot's farm.
How many men?
I'd say 60... 70.
That's probably just
an advance team.
I would imagine they got more than that
up the road in reserve.
Constantino has us outnumbered
and outgunned.
If we split our force, and try
to defend each one of these farms,
he's goino toverwhelm us.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying we don't split up.
We choose a place to stand together,
deliver a good, hard counterpunch.
Let them know that,
if they intend to take from us,
it's going to cost them dearly.
How?
Well, right here.
Stanley Richmond's farm.
It's the last place
before this road divides,
and they start taking ground
faster than we can keep up.
Plus which it's the highest point
in the whole area.
There's where we make our stand.
Deputy Perkins just radioed back.
He told the farm is secured.
Let's go get the rest of them.
Let's go!
This one's alive.
Season 1 - Episode 22
" Why We Fight "
[ Transcript ]
swsub.com
[ Synchro ]
aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
6 YEARS AGO
- Grandpa, you're drunk.
- Yeah!
Thank you, darling
Keep 'em coming.
Gail's going to get so mad at you
for getting her boy drunk.
I've got Gail wrapped
around my little finger.
Says the guy who taught me
to fly his crop duster when I was 13,
then told Mom I was lying
when I mentioned it.
I was so jealous.
My mom knew that you let him fly,
and she wouldn't let me go
anywhere near you.
You see, Jake would...
Jake would come over and tell me
all the stories you told him.
I loved...
I loved the one about the peanuts.
What the hell are you talking about?
The peanuts in World War II.
He means the "Nuts" story, Grandpa.
Not peanuts.
There were no peanuts involved.
So what's the story?
Tell me the story, somebody.
What? It's his story.
All right.
World War II.
The winter of 1944.
The Nazis penetrated the Allied lines,
and surrounded...
a division of Americans
in a little town called Bastogne,
freezing, starving and running out
of ammunition, but they knew...
that they had to hold that ground.
Just before Christmas,
the Nazis sent a note
to the American commander
telling him that he could
surrender and save the rt of his men,
or they could stay and fight.
The American commander
sent a one-word reply
to the Wehrmacht commander,
and it said...
- ... "Nuts."
Why did he say, "Nuts"?
It means, "Go to hell!"
Why didn't he just say, "Go to hell"?
Because he said, "Nuts. "
Gail, my sweetheart,
you look beautiful.
Save it, Dal.
Was it your idea
to get my son drunk tonight?
Right. Okay.
Everybody back to the reception.
- Come on.
- But I'm hammered.
And I want to talk to you.
Have a cup of coffee, Stanley.
Here.
Well, what's this?
As your brother's best man,
you are required to give a toast,
so I wrote down a few thoughts,
some things that
you might want to say.
You think I was going to wing it?
Let's go take some pictures, okay?
What's going on?
Mr. Green, I have access
to a keyhole military satellite
that I can use to track New Bern's
movements in the field today.
- Beg pardon?
- It's real.
The one restriction...
is that no one can know
where you're getting this information.
Tell them I'm... scouting in the field,
tell them what you want...
but the satellite must remain a secret.
Sounds good.
- That's it?
- What do you want me to say?
I get it. Man has a satellite.
Doesn't want anyone to know.
- But...
- I am about to go to war,
with New Bern, Kansas,
the home of the nearest Costco.
Today is already just about
as weird as I can handle.
I'm not asking any more questions.
Mom, Dad,
there's a chance we may have
to leave here today,
and we might not be able
to make it back, so...
I just wanted to...
We just...
wanted to pay our respects.
Remember I told you about that witch,
from the IRS?
The one that wanted
to take everything
you've ever worked for?
Mom, Dad...
this is Mimi.
Hello.
It's nice to finally meet you.
I really love your son.
And, of course,
Bonnie is...
she's just wonderful.
And I've really enjoyed
living with them and...
- Oh, great.
- What?
I didn't say we were living together.
We're not married.
I'm so sorry.
I certainly... I...
Is everything a joke to you?
I figure one day we're going
to be buried here ourselves,
and I...
think it would be nice if...
our kids came and,
and joked around with us.
I hope that's not
for a really long time.
How we doing?
We've got about 200 men.
That includes Dale's crew.
We got more coming, right?
They're trickling in. It's taking
a lot longer than we thought.
Saying good-bye to their families.
Get on down to the pass.
Get everybody organized.
We don't have a whole lot of time
before their advance unit hits.
- Not you.
- Why not?
Because these people
elected you their leader.
We protect you at all costs.
And, besides, in a few minutes,
I'm going to need your help.
Help with what?
Arming our tank.
Our daughter is out there carrying
a rifle and... I'm in here.
Sam needs you here.
You know, Allie's safe.
She's been assigned to Town Hall,
and the fighting is miles from there.
Right now, there really isn't
anything else you can be doing.
Here we go.
Jake, you are about
to have company.
Already?
New Bern is on its way.
There are...
70, maybe... 80 men.
Is that tank there yet?
They're trying to load it
with that mortar round right now.
I think you're gonna need it.
All right, let's get ready!
They're coming!
Get some ammo down here!
What is it?
I'm being tracked.
Tracked?
What do you mean?
Someone is trying to trace my location
through the satellite.
- Well, can they?
- If they have time, yes.
Do you know who it is?
My guess is, it's... Valente.
What him?
From... Homeland Security?
I don't know who he's working for now,
but he told Sarah
to get the bomb any way she could
and to eliminate all witnesses.
All the witnesses.
- Shut it down.
- No, I can't.
We just have to make sure we disconnect
the feed before he finishes the trace.
I don't get it.
- Why are they just standing there?
- I don't know.
Do we fire the first shot?
New Bern's here.
Get into position.
We're gonna need that tank.
Having a good time?
By the way, I think I saw April
making out with Shep Cale.
All right, all right.
You need to stop drinking.
Listen.
Read this.
It's a speech.
Figure you should have something ready,
so you don't embarrass yourself.
You mean so I don't embarrass you,
because you don't have to worry.
Is that how you spell
"venereal disease"?
This day is important to me, okay?
Just because your life's a big joke
doesn't mean you have
to treat mine that way.
Why is my life a joke?
- Just read the speech.
- No, seriously, Eric,
why is my life a joke?
- I'm not getting into this right now.
All right.
You think people don't wonder
what you've been doing?
You spend all that time
in flight school getting your license.
Instead of using it,
you come back here,
hanging out like it's the summer
after high school.
Hauling stuff for Emily's dad.
If I'm such a joke,
then why'd you want me as your best man?
You didn't want me, did you?
No, not really.
Where's that tank?
We're not going to last long
against those trucks.
We have to hold out.
Damn it!
- Got to keep drawing their fire,
all right?  - Got It.
Give me another mag.
Where are you going?
We'll never get a clean shot from here.
I need to get up that hill...
and shot on the gunner.
- I got your back.
- All right.
Cover him!
Why eliminate witnesses?
I mean, whoever's tracking you,
they either...
want to use the bomb
for themselves or...
they want to keep you
from using it, but...
either way,
what difference do witnesses make?
The bombs have fingerprints,
don't they? Something that...
make them traceable.
I remember reading that.
It's the uranium.
It has...
It has a specific signature.
It places the origin of the device
where it was made.
So there were dozens of these things
used in the attacks, right?
And now you have the last one.
I don't think these people are looking
at this thing as a weapon.
It's more than that.
It's...
Evidence.
It's the smoking gun
behind the greatest crime
in the history of the world.
The bomb...
it could expose the people...
who were responsible for the attacks.
That's why they need it back.
Did u see what I just did?
Holy crap.
That was...
Holy crap!
All right, that bought us some time.
But they'll be back,
and there'll be more of them.
And it won't be near as easy
next time.
Easy?
You thought that was easy?
Dad?
What's wrong?
Clear the table!
Clear it!
- Clear it!
- I'm gonna go get Kenchy.
- Get my mom!
- We'll need towels.
And some antiseptic,
and some alcohol.
- We need alcohol.
- Get a towel!
Get me some alcohol!
Here we go.
Give me that, come on!
Okay, all right.
Keep the pressure on.
What?
Keep it on! Keep the pressure.
Jake, come in.
Nice work out there.
Tell your father that
they're coming back around.
He's been shot.
I'm sorry.
You know what to do, right?
Keep pressure on the wound,
and there should be some morphine
syrettes in the... supplies I gave you.
Yeah, we've got it.
Listen, Jake.
People are gonna be
looking to you now.
You know what I mean?
Okay, the guys will be back.
They retreated to Talbot's farm.
My guess is,
they're waiting for reinforcements,
so you should have a little time
to regroup out there.
Just keep the radio close,
and I'll update you.
Out.
Please, I need to talk
whoever's in charge.
Right over there.
Excuse me, sir?
Colonel Hoffman.
You don't have to call me sir,
unless you plan to enlist.
There's a city called New Bern.
It has a munitions factory.
It's planning to overrun the town
of Jericho. People are gonna get killed.
They tried to kill me,
but I got away.
- You've got to help these people.
- Where is this?
Kansas, not far from
the Colorado border.
I wish I could help. My orders are
to secure the roads in this area.
- But, sir...
- I don't get to make these decisions.
I'm just a government employee.
Which government?
United States.
Are you all right, ma'am?
We heard there were six different people
claiming the presidency.
There were. In fact, there are still
a couple of holdouts...
Texas, a bloc in the East.
The new federal government's
been restored in Cheyenne, Wyoming.
Colonel, this is an emergency.
You have to go to Jericho. The fighting
could be happening right now.
I am very sorry, ma'am.
Casper, you see she gets back
to the medical unit.
Come on, ma'am.
Get 'em out.
Clear everyone out.
You listen...
This place,
is where you survive.
You make a stand here,
you hear?
We will.
I'm sorry you have to see this.
You've been through enough.
Dad...
Dad, stop.
You're stronger than you think
you are, though.
Always have been.
I love you, son.
I guess I zigged when I should've
zagged out there, huh?
I sure wish your mother was here.
She's coming.
She'll be here.
Tell your mother I love her.
I was... hard on you.
I pushed you... away.
I'm glad you... came... home.
I'm proud of you.
The big toast.
Before I start,
is there anyone who...
hasn't written me a speech?
It really makes me wonder
how screwed up you think I am
that I can't be trusted
to say a few things...
about my brother.
The thing is...
these are all pretty lame.
Not one of them mentions
my brother's musical theater phase
when we all thought he was gay.
Seriously.
You have not heard disturbing
until you've heard him singing
"One Hand, One Heart"
in the shower every morning.
I tease my brother a lot,
but...
the truth is...
the truth is I'm very proud of him.
I'm...
I'm proud of how kind he is...
I'm proud of how giving he is,
and...
he's a very lucky man.
Really.
My father's dead.
We'll get through.
Get Gray back to town.
What?
Wait a minute...
Come tomorrow,
what's left of us will need a leader.
I think we've lost enough
in that department for one day.
We're gonna need
every set of hands we can get.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- You're too important now, Gray.
It's not negotiable.
Get him an escort.
And start getting everyone
into position.
Who knows when
they're gonna come back again?
Go ahead.
So they got their reinforcements.
It's a couple hundred men.
And another six of those
deuce and a halfs.
They're mobilizing now,
so I say you got about 15,
maybe 20 minutes
before they're on you.
You get back here as soon as you can.
All right?
Say, what do you know about
a set of train tracks
running alongside the river?
Why?
What do you see?
Hawkins, what's on the tracks?
I don't know. I can't see.
- Hang on.
- Robert, disconnect it.
Jake, you got a very large train
coming from New Bern,
and they've got three cargo cars.
What's in them?
I think it's men,
and there's hundreds of them.
It's a whole set of reinforcement...
Hawkins, what's going on?
Talk to me.
I'm on my way.
I've got to go.
Wait.
Look, they only had a few seconds.
It wasn't enough time
to get an exact location.
- We're fine for a little while.
- Where are you going?
I have to stop a train.
I-80 is secured
from Cheyenne to Grand Island.
We now control the area
between Kearney and Hastings.
I-70 is turning out to be a challenge.
There are organized road gangs
controlling much of the interstate.
I've also been told by a patient
in our medical unit
to expect a significant skirmish
between two towns
in northwest Kansas:
New Bern and Jericho.
What is the location of those towns?
CZ-12, Quadrant Four.
We've tracked the terror suspect
to within 200 miles of that area.
Capture of this suspect
is a top priority
for President Tomarchio
and the administration.
Do you understand?
- Should I re-prioritize, sir?
- Immediately.
Go to Jericho and crush the skirmish.
Once the area's clear,
we will begin our search
for the terrorist.
I'm gonna ask Mimi to marry me.
Yeah?
Yeah. She can't cook,
she's never seen nine innings
of baseball in her life,
she hates my clothes...
but I love her.
And I'm happy.
Jake, I don't want to die today.
You're gonna make it out of here.
That I promise.
Constantino and those trucks
are right on your doorstep.
You don't have much time.
What about that train?
20 minutes, give or take.
Tell me you have a plan,
a really good one.
I need to borrow your tank.
It won't fire.
I told you that, right?
There's not a single
round of ammo in it.
I'm not planning on shooting anything.
The throttle's there on your left.
And to steer, you're just gonna...
Hey. This is not my first time.
Good luck out there.
You, too.
Any minute now, huh?
I'm...
You know, he's here...
watching.
You know that, right?
They still doing
the bunny hop in there?
I think it's the Macarena.
The what?
Yeah, they're still doing the bunny hop.
Quite a speech you made in there.
I had no idea you were
such a sentimental fool.
Mom wrote it.
You think?
Listen, I know that you and Eric
aren't close and...
maybe you didn't feel like standing up
in front of a bunch of people and...
acting like you were.
Sometimes doing what you feel like doing
and doing what needs to be done
are two different things.
You don't have to worry about me, Dad.
I'm fine.
I somehow get the feeling
my worrying days are far from over.
But they will be one day.
One day, I know you're gonna become
the man I know you can be,
the man you were born to be.
My God, that day's gonna be
something to see.
Come on, Johnston.
This scotch ain't gonna drink itself.
Me and the old man are gonna
head down to the lake
and share some 30-year-old single malt.
You want to come?
Yeah. I'm just gonna...
wait for Emily, say good night.
I'll...
meet you there.
I'll save you a place.
- Where's he going?
- Waiting for Emily, say good night.
That's the last we'll see
of him tonight.
Dad...
If I had a girl that looked like that,
I wouldn't keep her waiting.
You hear that, boy?
I'm gonna take that girl
away from you.
You talk a good game.
You better watch out
for yourself, too.
Your wife is crazy about me.
Oh, my wife wants to take a hickory
switch to you three times a day.
It's Constantino.
I'm here.
My scouts just informed me.
I am sorry about your father.
You're outmanned,
and you're outgunned.
There's too many of us and
we are too desperate to give up.
You cannot win this.
I'm giving you one last chance.
Walk away,
put your guns down...
and return to town,
and no one else will be harmed.
Jake, I need an answer.
What's it gonna be?
Nuts.
Sorry, I didn't get that.
You can go straight to hell.
About my father...
you're the one I'm coming for.
I want to go home.
Our orders are to take people
out of the conflict zone.
You'll be safer in Cheyenne.
Colonel Hoffman?
What is all this?
- Sir, wheels up in five minutes.
- Roger that.
- Jericho's been moved up to priority #1
on the list.  - Thank you.
Oh, God, thank you.
This is all thanks to you.
Don't worry. We're gonna get things
back to normal again.
All right, saddle up.
My father expected us
to make a stand here.
To defend our home.
That's what we're gonna do.
Smoke bombs!
Get in position!
Don't waste your rounds!
Wait for a clean shot!
Wait...
Now!
[ www.seriessub.com ]