My bird is missing.
It's "I lost my canary."
And try telling it to the woman in the cafe upstairs.
I, uh...
I've lost my canary.
You should have clipped its wings.
It's weird.
Are you cold?
I'm kind of cold.
It's probably nerves. It's not like I've ever sto--
Now, can I see my money?
As soon as you show me the weapon.
Yeah, um... funny thing about that.
The weapon...
might take a little while.
Only way I could smuggle it out.
I swallowed it.
Uh, we have company.
Single white male downstairs at the back.
What? What's wrong?
You didn't follow our safety protocols, did you?
What? Of course I did. Why wouldn't I?
You were followed.
I've got second white male.
I see another two.
Strike that. Three more.
Going to plan "B."
- What's plan "B"?
- Come on!
Come on, come on.
I can't make it.
You don't have a choice.
Anybody got a twenty on the last guy?
Come on.
Hey.
God, you look awful.
Thank you.
Good morning.
You all right?
Yeah. You know.
It's not every day you see a guy shattered into a million pieces.
Yeah.
Two weeks ago, the CIA was contacted by an american ex-patriot named Derek Modell.
Mr. Modell, for reasons more pecuniary than patriotic,
stole a sample of a new biological agent from an arms dealer in Montenegro.
He called it Ice 5, and offered it to the agency for $10,000.
As you know,
mr. Modell failed to comply with any number of safety protocols we'd outlined,
and he was flowed and killed before the exchange could be completed.
Killed? He exploded like a frozen pinata.
We believe his death was caused by this biological agent he was transporting.
Are you saying this stuff turned Modell into a human popsicle?
Uh...
if I may, I might be able to -- if you're all curious -- elucidate.
Well, we know that this guy Modell,
he swallowed the sample to smuggle it out, kind of like a drug mule.
Based on some tests,
we found the sample in this medical container.
It was found in the van amongst the, uh...
Chunks.
Yeah. Chunks.
This was not meant to be swallowed.
It probably started leaking as soon as it got into his stomach.
And then when he was tackled, bam!
Complete rupture. Instant O.D.
When you say "instant O.D." You mean it instantly froze him?
Well, not exactly. It didn't really freeze him as much as freeze-dry him.
It crystallized him in seconds.
So the mission was a bust.
So to speak.
Now this man Derek Modell
spent the last nine months as a relief worker at the hospital Sava in Montenegro.
We believe that ice 5 is being covertly developed there
by a man named Fintan Keene.
I haven't heard that name in a while.
That's because mr. Keene claims to have gone legitimate.
Seems to be all the rage among evil geniuses.
Fintan Keene is wanted by just about everybody.
But he's protected.
He runs his arms and drug op out of Montenegro,
taking advantage of its political instability.
You want us to take down Keene.
The director simply wants us to obtain a viable sample of Ice 5.
So, Sydney, we're sending youinto Montenegro
as a relief worker forthe U.K. branch of OMNIFAM.
I want you to understand this is not a tactical mission.
We go in, obtain the Ice 5, and come out.
I don't want anybody else getting this before we do. That's all. Good luck.
Is something on your mind, agent Vaughn?
No. Not really.
I'm not sleeping very well.
It's Lauren, isn't it?
I think I see her sometimes. Or...
I thought I saw her in the market in Algeria.
That ever happen with you?
Do I have visions of Lauren?
I don't know that many people who killed the woman they were married to.
I was just wondering if that's what happens.
It  did.
Now it doesn't.
I'm taking the last of the toothpaste.
It's okay. I'm going to the store later.
Do you know how excited I am that I'm not the only one going to the store?
Do you need anything?
No, I'm good, thanks.
You mind if I...
No,  go ahead.
Are these our mother?
There was a fire.
I lost all the pictures I had of her.
So I asked my dad if he had any, and he found those.
The only one she hadn't thrown out.
Is this you?
I don't know who the baby is.
I've never seen pictures of her like this.
Just the official stuff.
I haven't seen much.
It's Vaughn.
Be safe.
You too.
I hope you're not squeamish.
From time to time, they send me a squeamish one. It never ends well.
I'm not squeamish,
though most of my relief work with OMNIFAM has been administrative.
We'll fix that. Have you patching folks up in no time.
You're a doctor?
Nurse by training, doctor, janitor,and babysitter by default.
Sounds overwhelming.
Nothing a bit of bushmills and a few "hail marys" can't cure.
Phoenix is in play.
Copy that.
I know it's too risky, but I wish she was wearing a transmitter.
She will once they trust her.
Besides, it'll give you a chance to brush up on some of your old-school tricks.
Hey, a little respect for your elders.
No, I'm not happy.
You promised we'd have the test tube kits two days ago, and we're still waiting.
Tell you what.
Our cafeteria lucked into about 20 crates of fresh strawberries.
You have my kits here by dawn tomorrow,
and I'll cut you in for half the fruit.
Yeah, fresh as in...
not old or frozen.
You're amazing.
Thank you.
Okay then.
There's more work than we can do, so you need to pace yourself.
Be quick, but don't hurry.
I've gone through nine relief workers in the past six weeks.
I'd hate to lose another.
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
That, madame, is what they all say. Let's find out.
Poor old guy suffers from psoriatic arthropathy.
He needs to be greased from head to toe.
Welcome aboard.
There's no way I'd eat this. No way.
My kid would. Mitchell? He would eat anything.
He's already been to the emergency room twice.
He swallowed a quarter and a car.
But not a real car,'cause, you know, I mean -- well, huge.
- He's beautiful.
- Yeah, thanks.
I got a million of these pictures. I probably should update them.
You like that one? There's a funny story behind that, actually.
I gotta warn you right now, Nadia's immune to your cute baby story charm.
I'm not so sure.
Do you have any weaponizing scenarios for Ice 5?
The three obvious forms are liquid, powder, and gas,
but it really depends on a few things.
Difficulty of manufacturing, stability, intended use.
Right. I mean, is it designed for an evil empire
that wants to dump it in the water supply and freeze-dry an entire city,
or, you know, maybe for just one crazy assassin guy?
Put a couple drops on a hollow-tip bullet --
Either, it's a hot ticket.
We should target major players -- governments, large terrorist cells.
Then offer it for sale ourselves.
See who might be shopping for designer bioweapons.
Right. I'll put a list together.
You're married.
What  are you doing in here?
We're almost out of syringes.
I was searching for a purchase order.
What can I do?
Prayers never hurt.
What happened to him?
I don't know.
What did he say?
Car accident.
- We can handle it from here.
- I don't mind helping.
If you want to last here, you'll do as I say.
Get back to that supply room and finish what you were doing.
This area's off limits.
You can eliminate both the KTL
and the african global party from your list of potential Ice 5 buyers.
It's out of their league.
Everyone else seems good.
Thanks.
Jack?
I was wondering if you knew who this baby is.
Where did you get this?
Oh, it's Sydney's.
She gave this to you?
I found it.
I was hoping you might be able to tell me --
There's nothing to tell.
Sorry to, uh, interrupt. We got the uplink from Montenegro.
A soldier came in presenting the same frozen symptoms we saw in Algeria.
He was taken to a secure wing of the hospital by a nurse named Kiera MacLaine.
That's  M-a-c capital L-a-i-n-e.
She said she was from Glasgow.
- Is MacLaine imbedded with Keene?
- We don't know yet,
but Sydney said MacLaine definitely recognized the effects of Ice 5.
She's still at the hospital trying to learn more.
There's a strong military presence at the hospital,
but it seems to be in support of the staff. Nothing we can't handle.
Okay, MacLaine seems to be clean. Registered nurse, no criminal record.
For the last nine years, she's worked for relief agencies around the world.
We know Keene gives cash to the hospital.
Maybe she takes care of his men in exchange.
What do you know about this secure wing?
We think it's the research lab.
Blueprints indicate several interconnected rooms in the large ward.
The entrance is protected by a swipe card and a keypad.
We already have the access code,
but we need that card, which we'll get off MacLaine.
Come on, man, it's got to look real. Do it again.
Vaughn, I hit you.
Yeah, like a girl. Just hit me again. Come on.
One more time.
You can do better than that. Come on. One more time.
Damn it! Watch it!
What are you doing?
- Sorry, father.
- Just trying to help.
Let me take a look at that.
Maybe I should watch, see how you do it.
I was going to sew it shut right there --
- Ah! Stop that.
- Sorry.
Go! I'll look after him.
Sorry. She's new. A bit eager.
I can't help but notice the fine cologne you're wearing, father.
Glenlivet, if I'm not mistaken.
- Is it that bad?
- Not at all.
Come here. I'll finish you up in the office.
It's a pretty nasty cut. Mind telling me how you got it?
Someone didn't like my last sermon.
Well, I've known a priest or two.
That sounds rather ominous.
But none that get into bar fights.
Well, I see my reputation precedes me.
I'm father Michael Lacott.
I'm new here at st. Cyrus.
Kiera MacLaine. Good to know you. I think.
I should also mention I
hear confession every week day from 4:00 to 6:00 at tavern Nikolai.
Why does that not surprise me?
When's the last time you went to confession, Kiera MacLaine?
I'm not sure how I'm supposed to feel.
About what?
A flirty priest.
I assure you my intentions are honorable.
Mostly.
You're not what I expected.
Is that your way of saying
"what's a nice catholic girl doing in a hellhole like this?"
Same as you.
- I was sent here for my sins.
- It's not that bad.
Fintan. What are you doing here?
Well, it's nice to see you, too.
She's not real happy with me of late, father.
I see.
You two are married?
No. Your good book would frown up on that, wouldn't it?
- We had an agreement.
- We do.
But one of my men had a wee accident today.
I thought I'd spin by, pay my respects.
You treated him, right? So how's he doing?
I think you know.
You should be nicer to your big brother.
Isn't  that what the Bible says?
What, do I look like some kind of an expert?
Don't worry, Kiera. I'll be out of your way soon enough.
Your brother seems like a nice enough guy. What's he do?
You must be new here.
Not only has Keene developed Ice 5, he's testing it on humans.
I saw a roomful of test subjects.
I'm more concerned by the pressurized cannisters.
It means Keene's found a way to make it airborne.
Here are the photos Sydney took.
I thought the tanks were full of propane or liquid nitrogen.
Then I saw the cyrillic stencil.
Ice 5 released into a city-- the damage could be in the tens of thousands.
How many tanks in the lab?
I'd say 14.
We found a buyer in Damascus. That's what they're expecting.
And they want it fast. Less than 48 hours.
We have to shut Keene down.
I don't disagree, but you lack the manpower.
You aren't a tactical squad.
We can do it without a fight. We can use Kiera MacLaine.
After  we learned she was Keene's sister, we re-ran her info.
Her real name is Meghan Keene.
She's former IRA, as is her brother.
They were involved in several bombings in the early '90s,
including one that killed a father and two boys.
But MacLaine's conflicted. Has issues with her brother.
We think we can turn her.
She's the one person who could get Keene alone,
away from his men.
It could give us a chance to grab him without a fight, shut down the lab.
Have you determined how to approach MacLaine?
Yeah. In confession.
Thank you.
I'll have another one of these for my parishioner.
I don't know what I'm doing here.
I'm glad you came.
- Cheers.
- Is it that bad?
- Is what that bad?
I don't know. You tell me.
I supposed I'm feeling a bit... trapped.
At the hospital?
Yeah.
Trapped by your brother?
I do this for a living. Not the drinking.
And it doesn't take a priest to notice
how angry you were when you saw him yesterday.
It's complicated. "Love the sinner, hate the sin."
Isn't that what they say?
Something like that.
A long time ago, he saved me.
I owe him.
But he scares you.
You don't know Fintan.
He's done some awful things.
We both have, I suppose.
You could always leave.
Like I said, you don't know my brother.
He can do it.
He can turn her.
I know what it's like to feel trapped,
to have a past you despise, that you can't escape.
We all have secrets, Kiera.
I was married -- for a short time.
That being your secret?
That being a part of it.
Now, obviously it was before I had the collar.
The woman I was married to betrayed me.
She betrayed a lot of people.
And when I found out what she'd done,
I let my hate for her consume me.
And I began to wish the woman I loved was dead.
I woke up every day imagining how I'd do it.
What was the best way.
What was the most efficient way.
I mean, it's all I wanted.
That woman was evil, and deserved to be punished,
so I killed her.
And although that woman was the worst kind of evil,
I also know that killing her was wrong.
I don't sleep much. I --
I mean, I can't close my eyes
without seeing it.
That -- that moment.
That look on her face.
She won't leave me.
She won't.
Forgiveness is a tricky thing, isn't it?
Even God can't do it if you won't let him.
I've never been able to say no to him -- to my brother.
I'm not alone in that, but...
it's my shame.
It's the one thing I can't forgive myself for.
I understand what it feels like to wish someone was...
I just wish there was a way out.
There are other ways
to keep him from having power over you, to make him go away.
You underestimate my brother.
Or maybe you underestimate me.
I know it doesn't feel like it, but you can leave.
- What are you --
- You deserve another chance.
I can't even think about doing something like that.
Why not?
When?
Tonight.
- Here.
- Just --
Freight manifests from our contact in Damascus.
Thank you. And that?
I thought you might know something about the picture.
Who the baby was.
Yeah. Well...
Your mother was a very private person, Nadia.
And as you know, my relationship with her was...
brief.
That's okay.
I just thought maybe you'd seen it before.
Thanks.
What are you?
S.A.S.?
MI-5?
I meant what I said. I can make your brother go away.
Well, whoever you are, you're sweet.
Kiera, I need you to listen.
Whatever your brother's done in the past
pales to what he's doing now.
I wouldn't know --
Yes, you do. You've seen it.
You know he's been testing it on your own patients.
I have nothing to do with that.
You're a party to it. That's enough.
There's nothing I can do about that.
Thousands of people will die if you don't say no to him now.
Do you want that on your conscience? Could you ever forgive yourself?
Who do you work for?
You've been afraid of your brother for too long.
Help me, and I swear I will protect you.
I can't wait to hear the details.
Did you really think my sister would betray me
for you after everything she and I have been through?
Nothing really surprises me anymore.
You'll discover that isn't true.
You know, the trouble with Ice 5 in its liquid form
is it's too unstable.
It's too hard to mass-produce.
I've made people drink it, breathe it.
I've applied it topically. I've mixed it into food.
The one thing I've never tried, though,
is to inject it directly into the brain.
Mainly because it's not cost-effective.
I think you should do it.
It's your fault he's here.
You hate him. You hate what he does.
Shut up.
I could have helped you.
I would have.
My sister may look like an angel,
but her heart is as black as yours and mine.
I don't believe that.
I know you want out.
Everything I told you was true. I can still help you.
You know it. You can feel it.
Show this fool he's wrong.
Inject it into his eye.
I want you to be the last thing he sees.
I don't know how you got in here, little girl, but it was a big mistake.
For...give --
- Forgive...
- Kiera...
You know I'm not really a priest. I can't do that.
No.
I --
I forgive --
I forgive you.
Fintan Keene's in custody and the Ice 5 has been acquired.
Sydney's safe. Our whole team made it.
Good. Thank you.
May I see that photograph?
Irina told me years ago that this is a picture of her holding her niece.
She told me that holding this baby filled her with a longing and
a hope to have children of her own.
The next day, I asked Irina to marry me.
I wanted my child to be loved like the baby in this photograph.
Of course her story could have been a total fabrication.
Another one of her countless lies designed to draw me in.
But I choose to believe it was the truth.
When we had Sydney, Irina held her in this exact same way.
And I can only imagine that she did the same with you.
So, for me,
I choose to believe.
Well, then I suppose each of us needs to find our own sense of closure.
Listening to you talk to that woman...
I know.
I just wanted you to know you can talk to me whenever you want.
Thanks.
When we get back, maybe you should spend the night.
Vaughn?
Traduction: Alucardo
SYnchro/transcript: Travis/RaceMan
www.forom.com