What's taking so long?
You're an impatient bastard, aren't you?
Time is money.
The hydrosect will be here soon,
at which point we'll move on to the next stage.
Which is?
Dispersal.
For now we relax and enjoy ourselves.
Cheers.
Outrigger's armed.
He's in V.I.P. with Kradic and two others.
Expect delivery of hydrosect any minute.
Good work, Phoenix.
Once delivery is confirmed,
we need to take every precaution to ensure the hydrosect remains stable.
Have we confirmed the method of transport?
It was Jack's responsibility.
He hasn't checked in yet this morning, has he?
No.
Now, it'll most likely arrive in a large metal biometric case --
you know, the kind that are usually named after large multinational corporations.
Shotgun, what's your status?
No sign of Kradic's men yet.
Yeah?
Good.
The hydrosect's here?
- Out front.
- About time.
Got a visual on the hydrosect.
Vaughn, take cover!
Phoenix, what's happening?
Drop the gun or lose your arm.
Don't move!
I'm on him!
Phoenix, what's going on?
Third party tried to intercept the hydrosect.
I'm in pursuit.
Put the guns down!
Or this goes into the drinking water!
I said put them down!
Send in the biohazard team. We need to contain the hydrosect.
On their way.
So the CIA has the hydrosect?
They got lucky. If I can find out where they took it, I can get it back.
Leave that to me. Come to Los Angeles.
Contact me when you get here.
Everything all right?
Oh, yes.
Just making a hotel reservation.
Sophia, you just got here.
Didn't I used to say that to you?
Stay. I insist. We want you to be here.
Please.
All right.
But you must tell me the minute I become a burden.
I promise.
- Hey.
Have you seen my father?
Nothing yet, huh?
I'm worried. I left him like a dozen messages.
He was supposed to report in two days ago.
So what do you want to do about it?
So this is where your dad lives, huh?
Yeah, what did you expect?
I don't know, a bunker or something.
So you've really never been here?
- No.
- That's very strange.
As opposed to everything else about my relationship with my father.
301. Here it is.
Dad?
- Not much for clutter,is he?
- No.
Sydney, come here. Look at this.
Body temperature, blood pressure, blood cell counts.
He's monitoring his vitals.
Marshall.
Oh, hey, did you hear the news?
I get to run an initial analysis on hydrosect this afternoon.
I love level 4 biohazard toxins.
My father asked me to give you
this artist's sketch based on descriptions from Sydney and Vaughn.
- He wants to know if you can --
- Run a biometric match.
Yeah, but off a sketch it's a bit tricky.
Can you do it?
Flinkman doesn't know the meaning of failure.
One ugly puss, huh? Muy feo.
Now they have a picture of you.
They have a cartoon drawing.
They'll never get a positive I.D. off of that.
You underestimated them in Vienna,
and we lost the hydrosect.
Lucky break.
Nadia  has a laptop with A.P.O. access.
She brings it home every night.
We may be able to use it to find the hydrosect.
How long would it take you to hack into it?
I'm afraid our options are limited, Jack.
The white blood cells anomalies are not what we'd hoped for.
Limited, not exhausted.
Science is full of happy accidents.
Alexander Fleming spent years trying to figure out
how to treat bacterial infection.
He  needed a vacation so bad,
he forgot to wash his petri dishes before leaving the lab.
So he comes back a week later, well rested, tanned, and what's he faced with?
A stack of moldy dishes.
But he looks a little closer, and son of a gun.
Not an iota of bacteria growing anywhere near the mold.
Penicillin.
Just a happy accident.
Fascinating anecdote,
although its relevance to my condition isn't exactly --
I have spent most of my career researching genetic mutations.
Mostly in rats.
I like rats.
Much smarter than they're given credit for.
These little buggers were exposed to the mother lode of radiation.
I was distracted one day -- problems with the wife --
and I accidentally gave them a lethal dose of an alkylating agent.
But lo and behold, a few of my rats survived.
Milo lived to the ripe old age of 4.
That's something.
Yes, but 84% of my rats were dead within a week.
And given what they went through, death was a blessing.
We both know the prognosis for my condition.
I don't see that I have a choice.
This alkylating agent was discontinued decades ago.
It was considered too lethal, even in controlled environments.
I have contacts. I'm sure I can procure the necessary chemicals.
Here's what we need.
Jack, as one friend to another, these drugs are nasty.
If they don't cure you --
I'll turn out like one of your rats.
I'll be in touch.
Come up with anything on that assailant?
Not yet.
But I am writing an algorithm into the program to speed things up, so...
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Hello?
I hate to bother you at work, but I was hoping that
I could make dinner for you and Sydney and your boyfriends tomorrow night.
Sophia, you don't have to.
It would mean so much to me after all you've done.
Are we free for dinner tomorrow?
Dinner? Food? Are you kidding me? Yes.
It's fine with us, but I have to check with Sydney and Vaughn.
Great.
Jack.
Were you able to get what I requested?
Yeah, sure.
Cute.
Listen, I need you to promise me
there's no way this is gonna get traced back to me.
I'm familiar with your concerns.
Look, Jack...
I don't mean to be presumptuous, tell you how to handle your business,
but the human body is not designed to handle this stuff.
Whoever this poor guy is you're gonna be torturing --
Curious morality coming from a guy who kills monkeys for a living.
What I'm saying -- be conservative.
A few ccs at a time, or you're gonna be out of fun before it begins.
Thanks for the advice.
So, this -- this pays off my debt to you, right?
Be seeing you, Anthony.
I need a favor.
Sure. What can I do for you?
Pull up everything you've got an alkylating agents
and cross-reference it with radiation sickness.
Okay. Kind of an odd combination. What exactly are you looking for?
Something's going on with my dad. I have to get to the bottom of it.
Coming right up. Just, uh...
Marshall, what's wrong with my father?
Hmm?
You know, don't you?
It was after your mission to Yakutsk.
Yeah?
God, he pulled the fuel right out of the core reactor.
He told me not to tell you.
He actually made me swear on Mitchell's life,
but seeing that you came in here to me,
I guess I didn't really violate --
I thought you shut down the reactor from here.
So did I, at first.
But then you got trapped in the experimental chamber,
and he thought it would be best if he went inside, and --
Marshall, whatever information you have on his treatment, I need it now.
Syd...
there is no treatment.
I mean, I have been all over the medical journals,
harassing researchers that I know -- some that I don't know.
If there was a treatment,
I would have found it by now.
Sydney,  what is it?
We have to find my father.
Jack Bristow is in need of immediate medical attention.
Currently he's off the grid.
We've tried all usual avenues of communication.
We have contacted every hospital and private practice in Los Angeles county.
No one has record of treating him.
Maybe he checked in using an alias.
Well, we considered that,
but the genetic mutation he experienced
would require any doctor to make special note,
and nothing matching your father's criteria has been reported.
The truth is, whatever my father has,
it isn't treatable.
If he's as sick as we think he is,
it's likely that his mental faculties are impaired.
Which means someone might be preying on Jack
using the false promise of a cure.
We must act quickly. If someone is actively trying to harm Jack,
he may be in no position to defend himself.
How did it go?
All right. I'll prepare this, and we'll be ready to go.
Connie will take care of your personal belongings.
How are you feeling today, Mr. Bristow?
Hopeful.
We got a hit. Jack just used a drive-thru ATM on 9th
about 20 minutes ago down near Staples center.
Great. I'll log onto the traffic surveillance network,
see if I can spot his car leaving the bank.
Fantastic.
Come on, dad, pick up your phone.
Please leave your name and number with a brief message --
- Damn it.
- Syd, we'll find him.
Okay, I got it!
- Yeah, Marshall?
- We found his car.
It's parked outside a building on Pierpont.
- Do you know where Pierpont is?
- Yeah, five minutes out.
Oh, thank you, Marshall. Remind me to kiss you.
Okay.
What? What'd she say?
Uh, nothing.
Everything's set.
The whole procedure should take about four hours.
What are these restraints for?
Uh, some patients go into convulsions when they're unconscious.
I didn't want you to hurt yourself.
Jack, have you thought about talking to Sydney?
I do keep too many secrets.
When this is behind me, that's gonna change.
Sydney deserves more.
She deserves to know that she's the most important thing in my life.
She and Laura, of course.
I'm proud of you, Jack.
We found his car.
What would my father be doing here?
I don't know.
That's my father's jacket.
Where is the man you took these from?
Hey! Where is he?
Come on.
If for some reason this doesn't work,
tell my girls I love them --
Sydney and Laura.
You're gonna pull through this, Jack.
I'll see you on the other side.
I'd like you to count backwards from 10.
10...
9...
8...
7...
Dad.
It's okay. Everything's...
Oh, my god, dad.
Marshall, we need medical attention now.
Sydney's with Jack. They've taken him to the infirmary.
So he injected himself with poison?
Well, apparently he thought it was a cure.
Now they got it out of his system, but this illness --
they say within 72 hours,
his condition will advance to the point where it's irreversible.
Did he wake up in the ambulance?
Briefly. He kept wanting to see his doctor -- Dr. Liddell.
Apparently he's been suffering from hallucinations for weeks.
- Dr. Liddell?
- Yeah.
Dr. Atticus Liddell.
He exists?
He did.
25 years ago, Atticus Liddell developed a radical thesis
regarding the treatment of genetic mutations.
In 1981, he left the U.S. to pursue his theories.
He was working with patients devastated
by an undisclosed nuclear accident in the soviet union.
Unfortunately, it was the cold war.
Shortly after he arrived,
the soviets became convinced that in addition to being a physician,
Liddell was also a spy.
Which he was.
- Did they kill him?
- No.
One of Jack's handlers informed us of the russians' suspicions,
and Jack was able to extract him before they could act.
He  changed his name, gave him a new identity.
Then there must be a record of where Liddell was relocated.
No. In those times, Jack and his handler had a strict policy --
anything that sensitive, they kept no documentation.
So we have to contact my dad's handler.
Jack's handler is dead.
He died eight years ago.
But supposing Jack knows where Liddell is,
why didn't he make contact when he first developed symptoms?
He thought he did.
Wow. Mr. Bristow hallucinated the one man who can actually save his life.
Even his delusions are lucid.
A man like Liddell can't just disappear.
Yes, he could,
if he was hidden by my father.
Hey.
Is there anything I can do?
We're doing everything to find a doctor who might be able to help.
- I'm so sorry, Syd.
- Thank you.
I'm gonna sit with him for a while.
You want company? I'll cancel dinner with Sophia.
You should keep it. There's nothing you can do here anyway.
Okay. But if you need anything...
- Hi.
Mmm. Something smells good.
- You must be Eric.
- Yes.
- I'm Sophia.
- Oh, hi. Eric Weiss. Oh, wow.
How are you? I love her already.
I'm so sorry Sydney couldn't make it. How sick is her father?
It's hard to say. They're running some tests now.
- Yeah.
- That's awful.
It's very hard. When it's a parent, it's always so difficult.
Give me those. I want you two to relax. You had a rough day.
I'll take care of everything.
- Uh, Eric?
- Yeah?
You have no ideahow excited I am to meet you.
Nadia says the most beautiful things about you.
Really?
She asked me if you were tall, dark, and handsome.
I told her you were tall.
Dad?
Dad, can you hear me?
Oh...
Hello.
Hi.
What are you doing -- why am --
I need to ask you something, dad.
Oh, no.
It was my turn to pick up Sydney after dance class. I'm sorry.
Can -- can you take care of that?
I'll cover next time, Laura, I promise.
Laura?
I don't -- I don't know why I'm so tired, sweetheart.
I'm so tired.
What are these, the emperanas? These are inc-- they're so good.
Empanadas.
Whatever. They're delicious.
I taught Nadia how to make them when she was very little.
Well, I've been seriously deprived.
Please.
Have you ever made these for me?
Excuse me.
Can't you let it go?
I really have to get this. I'm sorry.
Nadia.
Do you want some more wine?
- Sure.
- Red? White?
- Red.
I know there's -- you know, there's seafood in here, but what --
what is this? Is this artichoke hearts?
- What is this?
- Many things.
And the rice. What is the spice in the rice? I can't -- is it, um...
- Saffron.
- Ah. Saffron.
I was going for cumin. Saffron -- your secret ingredient. Of course.
- It was Vaughn.
- How's Jack?
He's too far gone, Sydney.
In his present mental state, he will never tells where he hid Liddell.
Not to mention that it's possible your father doesn't even remember.
My father doesn't forget things.
We can hypnotize him.
Yeah, I considered that myself, but given his situation,
his condition, these hallucinations...
He called me Laura. He thought I was my mother.
He called you Laura? Not Irina? You said he called you Laura.
Suppose we convince your father that he's still living in 1981,
specifically the day that he extracted Liddell out of Russia.
My dad's hallucinating.
That's distinctly different from what you're suggesting.
No, no, I'm not sure it is. Calling you Laura, imagining Dr. Liddell.
What if we could recreate his surroundings?
Perhaps we could guide his delusions, get him to reveal
exactly where he relocated Liddell.
You want me to be my mother?
That's right.
Found a girl.
Six years old. She's got your eyes.
Her mom wants to know if she can use this for her acting reel.
You okay?
I get it. Not okay.
I don't know how I'm gonna do this.
Well, you know, it's not too late.
We can always have Weiss dress up as Irina.
I'm sure he'd make a great housewife.
I don't remember my parents back when they were together.
Well, you were a little girl.
I remember the time. I don't remember them.
My dad... was my dad.
He was never around when I was a kid. He was always away on business.
My mom...
I don't know what my dad was like around my mother,
or what she was like around him. I don't know how to do this.
Syd, it's just a job.
It's another alias like all of the others.
Just trust your training. Follow your dad's cues.
Follow his lead.
Besides, I've got snipers everywhere if he starts to get inappropriate.
They're ready.
Hey, listen to me.
You can do this.
Oh, my god.
It's unsettling, isn't it?
This is my old house.
It should be sufficient as long as Jack doesn't examine the details too closely, hmm?
That bowl is in the wrong place.
Hmm. It's murano glass.
Emily and I gave this to your parents --
or at least the original version --
as a housewarming gift.
It belongs on the coffee table.
That's right.
We'll give you a few minutes after Jack wakes up to sell the illusion.
When the phone rings, give him his privacy.
Medical will move in as soon as we get Liddell's location.
We'll get this --
we'll get this over with as quickly as possible, Sydney.
You ready?
Your mother used to call your father "sweetheart."
It was a pet name for him.
Good luck.
He should be conscious in 30 seconds.
Turn on the television.
Okay. TV... on.
Sydney, go ahead.
Jack?
Oh, good. You're home.
Sydney?
She's upstairs, isn't she?
Would you give me a hand with these?
Sweetheart, is something wrong?
- It's not working.
- Just give her a moment, please.
Arvin called. He and Emily want to have dinner next Saturday.
I told him we'd love to.
You could have just said we're busy.
I know you put up with Arvin for my sake.
Sweetheart, he's your best friend. I'm your wife. I can tolerate him.
How can you do that?
Do what?
How can you be so perfect?
Loving mother...
beautiful wife, just --
just by standing there.
Vaughn.
Would you get that?
Hello.
Control number 80709. Is this line secure?
Yes, it is.
I'm calling from agent Grady's office.
We've moved up the timetable to get Liddell out of Minsk.
We have to get him out of there now.
Yes, I understand.
I can expedite your movements from here.
What travel arrangements do you need set up?
Jack, where do you want Liddell moved?
His mind's rejecting this,
possibly because Vaughn's voice doesn't sound like his handler's.
We should send in the girl.
Do it, Marshall.
Sending in...the girl.
Hi, dad.
Is it okay if I practice the piano?
Of course.
- Are you still there?
- Yes, of course.
- I have company.
- I understand.
About the doctor, I've been feeling a bit under the weather,
but I'm much better now.
It's code. Do you recognize it?
No, must be something Jack had with his handler.
Go ahead.
Despite that, I think I'd be wise to have a checkup.
It's been a year since my last stress test.
Can you schedule that for me?
You got it.
Thank you.
Sydney, Marshall should be able to decode the message.
Keep trying to get Liddell's location.
Sorry, honey.I have bad news.
Oh?
That was Grady. Who else would it be this early on a Sunday?
He has a mission for me. I'm afraid I have to leave town.
He told her. She knew he was a spy.
It would seem so.
What's the mission?
There's a doctor whose research has put his life in danger.
I need to make him disappear.
New name, new identity, new life.
Low risk. I promise.
- Where will you take him?
- Finland.
Marshall, run a biometric of Dr. Liddell
against the databases of finnish passport offices and medical licensing board.
Already on it.
Sydney, we got it. Good work.
What concerns me -- I won't be back until next week.
I'll miss Sydney's birthday again.
That's okay.
You'll explain it to her. She'll understand.
She's a child. She shouldn't need to understand her father
isn't home to celebrate her birthday.
Laura, the only memories I have of my father are of him leaving.
I don't want it to be that way for her.
She deserves better.
The work you do is important.
Not as important as her.
Or you.
When I get back from Europe, I'm going to talk to my supervisors.
What about?
I'm giving notice.
Sorry.
I should have discussed this with you before I made any decisions.
No.
That means more to me than you'll ever know.
We'll send in the med techs to sedate your father.
That's good. Can I join you?
- Uh-huh.
- Okay.
Laur-- ahh!
Dr. Liddell.
Jack Bristow needs your help.
Guys! Weiss, Nadia, hold on.
I was about to run some more carbide tests on the hydrosect --
case carbide tests, and I went to get it out of cold storage,
and it wasn't there, but of course you knew that.
How would we know that?
Well, it was moved at your request
by your unit to a low-security facility off-site.
I'm just wondering why, 'cause that's some dangerous stuff.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm terribly sorry, but I'm lost.
Could you please tell me where Division street is, please?
Sure. Actually Division street is the one-way street heading north.
What's going on?
Just some lady asking directions.
No one in our unit authorized anything.
Well, the request was authenticated. It came over our secure network.
The security system's offline. I'm calling it in.
You're saying that way is a one-way street, goes --
Right -- aah!
Hey, hey, hey, how did you get in --
Nothing. I'm getting nothing. No answer.
Let's go.
It's double-folded titanium.
Take a look at this.
You can cut through that.
Done.
The hydrosect's gone.
Oh, god.
It's the guy from Vienna.
The one Sydney and Vaughn --
What the hell happened here?
Atticus. So good of you to come.
After what Jack did for me...
Sydney will show you the infirmary. If there's anything you need --
- I'd like to see my patient.
- Right this way.
Dad?
A friend is here to see you.
Hello, Jack.
Am I cured?
Not yet.
But I'm going to make you better.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com