Douglas Adams once wrote:
He felt that his whole life was some kind of dream…
and he sometimes wondered whose it was…
and whether they were enjoying it.
Breakfast of champions, Dad?
You were out late.
You have fun?
Ah… you know, I was… out with the guys.
I thought maybe we could work out after school;
do some weights.
Yeah, whatever.
We should be offering organic entrees in all our locations.
We'll talk about this when I get in. Yeah, I'll see ya in ten.
Good morning, honey.
Morning, wife.
You're outta here early.
Meetings all day.
Good morning, Lucas.
Will you be home for dinner?
I'll call ya.
I better go.
Got my eye set on a new location.
How many café's can one person own?
Even dozen should do it.
Late night for you too, huh dad?
Oh, man, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you.
Finally taking the court – ladies and gentlemen – is the Rivercourt's own Nathan Lee,
star player and recent applicant to the prestigious High Flyers basketball camp.
Oh, you forgot, uh… ladies usual.
Had to stop by the post office.
High Flyers, baby. What's the word?
I dunno; I haven't opened it yet.
Dude, what is wrong with you?
That's a felony.
Yeah, whatever, turn us in. Come on, what-what's it say?
Say's he's a finalist.
Nathan, that's awesome.
Alright, I'm just a finalist.
It's not the same thing as me actually getting into the camp.
Uh-huh, act like you don't want it.
What I don't want is to get my hopes up.
There's no way they're gonna pick some guy that's never played organised basketball.
They'll pick a guy who played like you did on my videotape.
Nate, uh, I'm your best friend, right?
So I feel like I can tell you this; uh…
stop being so damn modest and come out here so we can keep you humble.
Shoot for teams, huh?
Exactly.
Oh, okay, okay.
So, you wanna hang with the guys tonight?
Oh, gee, there's a unique idea.
Come on, Peyt, what, I can't bond with the team?
What about bonding with your girlfriend?
I was listening to that.
Fine!
You don't wanna hang out with us?!
Why don't you just sit in your room; listen to your loser rock…
and do live sex shows on your webcam for all I care!
Lucas, look out!
Daddy teach you how to drive?
Yeah, he sends his love.
Now get outta my way, loser.
'I'm sorry'.
Why do you have to treat him like that?
Could've easily been you, you know?
If your dad had married his mom instead of yours.
Yeah, like that was ever gonna happen.
You see, it's this… retro style and the, uh, leather interior package;
makes this one-one powerful sexy machine.
And when you factor in the Keith Scott service guarantee and that elusive thing
that we call the, uh, the cool factor;
this car is definitely gonna get you laid.
Uh, do me a favour; have a seat in my office and think about that leather interior, huh?
Oh, let me guess:
Doug ate your work ethic.
Nah, I had to go by the uniform place; sign off the new Ravens logo.
Yeah. Like Whitey's actually gonna let you make a decision.
Come one, Keith, it's early, don't start.
I'm the boss here.
Maybe you shoulda married Deb;
you mighta gotten her parent's money, things'd be different.
Can we just leave the past in the past?
Yeah, that's what you're best at, isn't it?
See that lady out there eyeing the convertible?
She's ready to deal.
Try not to screw it up, huh?
I'm on it, Keith.
Oh, hey, I gotta cut out early for basketball practice, okay?
Just about the time the bars open up, right boozy?
Huh?
How bout I buy you a cold beer, Miss. Lee.
Otis, you've been offering for ten years; you know I don't drink.
Doesn't hurt to try, does it?
Hey, sweetie.
What's up, mom. I got the mail; some bills,
a letter from uncle Cooper and, uh…
this.
Thinking about taking some classes?
If they offer a course in making ends meet.
You ever regret it?
Your folks cutting you off.
Not for one second, Nate.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have you.
Besides, money buys you nothing but misery.
I mean… look at Dan and Karen and Lucas.
Well, you know, you could up the traffic in here by hiring some… hot girls to dance in the bar.
There you go. Yeah.
Just saying.
Speaking of hot girls... sorry I'm late.
School bus driver ran out of gas.
Where were you today?
I told you, Mr. Hirshfield took us to the planetarium.
If you ever listen to me, maybe you'd know that.
Okay, alright. I just can't believe you went out in public with that hat.
Remind me why I'm friends with you again.
Nathan, this is from that basketball camp.
Yeah, I'm a finalist.
It's no big deal.
Well, it's a huge deal, honey, I'm really really proud of you.
Yeah, me too!
Congratulations. Well, we'll have to celebrate later.
Right now, dirty dishes are beckoning.
You rock, don't let it go to your head.
You know, you two are gonna end up married some day.
Stop it. We've known each other forever; we're just friends.
Good place to start.
Keep dreaming.
Nah, for real, man, I'm serous, dule here really got bigger.
Skills.
Nah, I'm serious.
You guys must be lost.
Well, Whitey closed up the gym.
We gotta have somewhere to run.
Well, you ain't bout to do it up here.
- Oh contraire...
- Tim, just say 'yes we are'.
See, I'm in training for High Flyers.
You wouldn't know anything about that now, would you?
Street trash.
You wanna bet?
Nate's a finalist, too.
Guys.
It's true.
Pipe dream, much?
Coz they only take one player from each high school.
Now who d'ya think they're gonna pick, huh?
Star shooting guard…
of the undefeated Ravens…
or the Rivercourt bastard.
So I guess the rumours are true;
Mr. Size 14.
Wh-a. Uh… I think… you're in the wrong locker room.
Well… the… sign says 'Boys'… doesn't it?
Okay. Whoa.
Oops.
I'm Brooke; but I bet you already knew that.
Yeah, I-I gotta go.
Hi, Coach Scott.
Ah-ah, I got you. Come on. Push!
God, I had it, dad.
Right. What're you slinging?
Bout 160.
Wow, didn't know I had a daughter. Let's kick it up.
We're gonna have to start 200 a day if we're gonna impress the High Flyers scout.
Why, coz you couldn't, back in the day?
I'm trying to help you. I don't want you to make the same mistakes that I did.
What do you know about your other son applying for High Flyers?
Don't call him that. Don't worry, he'll never make it.
Well, he made finalist.
Which means Whitey must have signed off on his application.
You're not seriously considering Deb's son for High Flyers spot.
Well he's your son too, Danny.
And good morning to you.
That kid's just trying to sabotage Lucas' shot.
That 'kid' sent in a tape that impressed the scouts so much that they made him a finalist.
All I did was sign the papers.
I'm an equal opportunity instigator.
You did this just to get me.
Danny.
Maybe it didn't make the nightly news but this is not about you.
Nathan's never played for a real team. He's a street-ball player, Whitey.
And apparently, a pretty damn good one!
Least he got something from you.
What're you up to?
Just fairness.
I wouldn't expect you to understand that.
But if Lucas is the better player,
he's got nothing to worry about.
Till then, let the best man win.
Oh, and, uh, be sure and let the door hit you in the ass on the way out.
She was totally naked?
As the day she was born.
Only a lot more… curvy.
Well what happened then?
I got the hell outta there.
You and Brooke Davis.
Captain of the 'CheerSluts'.
That is hard to picture.
Yeah, I'd say 'hard' is the right word.
Eeew.
Okay, what's this?
Oh, score, a bracelet.
Last time I got some fake tattoo with a random number.
Well, here. It matches that, uh, thing you call a shirt.
My mother made this for me, and shut up.
- You shut up.
Don't say I never gave you anything.
I think you have the wrong son's house.
I need to talk to you about your game.
I didn't know you were that good a player till I saw that tape.
You're a little rough round the edges but you got the makings.
If this is about me joining the team, you can forget it.
Son, I'm a lot smarter than you give me credit for.
Asking you to play alongside Lucas, when that, uh,
ass-crack of a father of yours is my assistant coach;
I wouldn't wish that on my worst enemy.
Tell me, why did you apply to the High Flyers?
Coz I love the game.
Coz all the messed up… history in this town has kept me from being able to play.
This camp might give me a shot at playing college;
where I don't have to… live in anybody else's shadow.
I know I'm good, I just wanna prove that I'm good enough.
Nathan, I'm gonna level with you:
you getting into that camp is a long shot.
I can only pick one athlete from this school…
normally, Lucas'd be a shoe-in…
but I was impressed by your tape.
Then… pick me.
It's not that easy.
I have to be sure you can hold your own with a real team:
passing, defence… running picks.
Well, I can't play in that gym, Coach.
Well, then play at the Rivercourt.
You want me to play against Lucas?
Technically, I want you to beat him.
That's up to you.
Want me to cue Springsteen's glory days?
Take the picture?
So, I'm nostalgic.
That's one word for it.
Sweet dreams, dad.
Hey, cut me some slack, son.
I look at you and I see… I see myself twenty years ago.
It reminds me of all that promise.
If I ride you,
it's because I wanna see you feel all the triumph that I never had.
But I'm telling you, this 'kid' is a risk to all that.
Oh, you mean you other son?
Only biologically. He means nothing to me, and you mean everything.
I saw his tape today,
and I was wrong when I said that he's no threat to you.
So you're gonna have to do whatever it takes to beat him.
Don't sweat it, dad.
I'll protect what's left of your good name.
You got bigger problems anyway.
Come visit us in ten years and… I bet you can meet the kids
and get a tour of our big house… and see how happy we are.
What time is it?
God, I gotta go.
Oh, no.
Oh, I've already worked late a lot these past few weeks.
Dan is not gonna be suspicious, trust me.
Why don't you stay the night?
You know I can't do that.
Well, you could if you leave him.
Who would protect Lucas?
From what? Becoming a jack-hole like his father?
I think it's a little late for that.
Keith.
Okay, I'm sorry.
You know, I would raise Lucas like he was my own.
Sometimes I think he is.
Lucas, you're up late.
Makes two of us.
Meetings, you know.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, wait.
I thought I'd make some coco. We could sit and talk like we used to.
You want a late night chat, mom?
Why don't you just try calling Uncle Keith?
I'm sure he'll come running.
As you see, class, galaxies come in three main-
Of course you're gonna do it, you've gotta play this game.
Haley, it's Lucas.
So, you can't let him stop you from chasing after your dream.
That's easy for you to say.
Dude, nothing is ever gonna happen for you if you don't put yourself out there.
You gotta shoot for the stars.
What about you? What're your dreams?
Chocolate.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, chocolate.
Um…
well, I never told anybody this…
but, I kinda wanna be a singer.
A singer?
Yeah, you know, like, tour the country and play concerts
and wear really cool clothes and then release an album.
Oh, you think that's funny?
No… I just…
Haley, I've heard you sing.
Shut up.
Just because I'm tone-deaf doesn't mean I can't dream, okay?
No, yeah, you're right. You're right, I guess it doesn't.
I got it.
Seduce the tutor girl.
You know, like, get inside her head and… steal her away from him.
Then dump her; crush her heart.
Tim, that's the dumbest idea ever.
What're you talking about? It's genius.
You wanna hear genius?
Tonight's the game.
He can't win if he doesn't show up.
You're gonna kill him?.
You got mad things, yo.
Tim, just say it's a good plan.
Um… you're a tutor, right?
You're a jackasses girlfriend, right?
Guess we're both right.
Uh… look, I'm Peyton… and… I know you're friends with Lucas' brother.
Half-brother, his name's Nathan.
He's, like, you're boyfriend or-
He's, like, my friend.
Why do you people always assume that? God.
Look, let me just save you some time, okay, Goldilocks, he's really not into cheerleaders.
Okay, first: retract the claws.
Second: Lucas is planning on doing something to Nathan tonight.
Before the game.
What's he gonna do?
I don't have any specifics…
but, he will do anything to get to that stupid basketball camp.
So you might wanna warn Nathan.
Just thought you'd like to know.
I thought it was time to break the ice.
After seventeen years?
Nice try.
That's my DNA, you know?
If that's what you need to believe.
Let's get right to it.
I'll give you five-hundred bucks to withdraw your application.
Well, I'd give you this weeks allowance…
You really think you've got a chance to win this thing?
You're kidding yourself.
Just like your mother was kidding herself when she moved to Tree Hill.
You know what?
I wasn't even sure if I was gonna go through with this game…
but now I am gonna play.
And I'm gonna win.
I guess you are my son after all.
Okay, it's eight bucks for the beers, ooo, twenty dollar tip.
Hey, the twenty's on the Rivercourt team.
Ah, good man.
Hey, honey.
What's going on?
We're starting the victory party a little early.
What, bad idea?
No, it's just…
Dan came to visit me.
He offered me cash to drop out.
Oh, honey.
Shut him out. You're good.
I don't know if I tell you this enough, but I… am so proud of you.
Even more so when you kick that kid's butt tonight.
Yeah. That's the plan.
Good luck, Nathan.
Thank god. Where have you been and why aren't you answering your phone?
Right here and I'm… recharging the batteries. Why, what's going on?
Because Lucas is gonna try something tonight, okay?
Let him. I'm not scared of him.
Will you just be careful, please?
I'm gonna be fine, alright? I promise.
Yo, Nate!
What the-! Get off of me!
Oh, come on.
Oops.
I warned you.
It seems you and me have something in common.
We don't quit.
You and I, moron.
What?
Look,
I have been working towards this camp since junior high…
and nobody's gonna screw it up for me.
Especially not you.
So I'm gonna be nice
and let you walk away from this game.
We should take his clothes.
Tim, what is wrong with you?
You pitch that every time we kidnap a guy.
I mean, it'll make it harder for him to get home.
And so will this.
Getting your jollies?
You tell anybody about this…
and you're dead.
Let's go.
You ready?
Nope. I'm not going.
Oh, come on, Peyt, I thought we were gonna work on… you know, getting back to normal.
Okay, trust me when I say that normal is the last thing I want with us
because – in case you haven't noticed – normal sucks with us, Lucas.
And I hate it when you call me 'Peyt'.
Is this about Nathan?
No. It's about you.
I'm starting to see who you really are and I may be late to that party but…
better late than never.
You did something to Nathan, didn't you?
What, your stupid kidnapping thing?
I thought you said this wasn't about him. Hm?
You know, I'll just come back when you're not so… PMS.
Don't bother.
- Peyton-
- Luke, I mean it.
We're done.
Your loss.
Peyt.
Hey, where's Nate, man?
Maybe he chickened out.
Maybe you're a dick.
What?
Where's Nathan?
That's what we're trying to find out.
Hey, how'd you get that shiner on your eye, dawg?
What, you and your boyfriend here like it kinda rough?
Hey!
Break it up, break it up.
Come on, what're you trying to do? Get thrown outta the game before it starts?
Get over there.
My son better be alright.
Where are you, Nathan?
Get in.
How'd you find me?
You think you're the first guy he's done this to?
I can see why you stay with the guy.
Actually, I broke up with him tonight.
So you're helping me just to piss him off?
That, and you seem like a decent guy.
Plus, I think everybody deserves a shot.
If you really want something bad enough no one has the right to stand in your way.
What?
Nothing, I just…
I got that weird… déjà vu thing.
I don't believe in past lives.
I think we've got one life, one chance and what we do with it is up to us.
So get it. I'm your only hope of making it to the stupid game on time.
Well, ladies and gentlemen, the game's looking like a forfeit, with Nathan Lee a no-show-
Not so fast, Mouth.
What'd you do?
What, it's not my fault your boyfriend finally grew a brain.
Sweetie.
Peyton said that you were gonna try something...
- Are you alright?
- Yeah.
Am I too late?
Almost.
Get this game started.
Four on four. Let's hustle.
No.
Me against him.
It's the way it's always been, right?
Why should tonight be any different?
Your funeral.
Game to eleven by one.
Let's go!
Shoot for ball.
Fine by me.
So, rank my last two girlfriends and you'll have the score folks; it's ten-nine, Nathan Lee.
Oh, and that's a foul by Scott.
That's gotta hurt.
No foul…
the basket counts.
And Lee calls it good. It's ten-ten, game point. Next basket wins.
You know, he's never mentioned you once;
not in all these years.
And you really think things would have been different if he'd married my mom?
If you do, you're a fool.
You're the fool…
and after you miss this basket, a loser too.
Whatever.
This is for my mom.
Looks like Nathan's going to High Flyers after all.
It's just a game, Dan.
Good game.
You deserve to go to that camp.
Thanks.
You're gonna be okay. Just…
come back to us soon.
What's that-?
They haven't invented words for how much I love you.
Doesn't look like I'll be needed this anymore.
Don't say I never gave you anything.
Haley?!
Haley?
Hey, Nate?
Nate.
Hey, it's me.
Don't worry.
It's okay, it's me.
Hey…
welcome back little brother.
How're you feeling?
Like I hit a brick wall.
Well, the doc says you're gonna be fine.
You know, what was this anyway, huh?
Some sort of messed up… anything Lucas can do, I can do better?
No… you wanna hear something really messed up though?
I thought I died, went to heaven.
No kidding.
Yeah.
Only… heaven was a place where…
Dan chose your mom…
over mine.
Then Haley was tone-deaf.
But that was only a dream.
I did kick your ass on one-on-one, though.
Well, I guess it was a dream then, huh?
I know you… you asked me not to, but…
I called Haley.
She's your wife, Nate.
And she loves you.
She needed to know.
Nate?
I have to ask you something.
When you hit the wall…
there was no brake marks on the track.
You're asking me if I did this on purpose?
Nathan.
Oh, thank god.
I'll let you two, uh…
Nathan, I-
I love you, mom.
I mean that. And I know I've been a jerk lately; to you,
to everybody else.
I'm sorry.
You've been hurting.
It doesn't matter.
I know you're just trying to be a good mother.
I haven't been a good mother, Nathan.
But that's going to change now.
What're you talking about?
I need to be stronger for you…
and for myself.
So, while you're healing from this…
I'll be healing too.
I promise you.
Whatever it is…
I got your back.
Do you ever… wonder what life would be like…
if Dan had married Karen…
and just stayed out of our lives?
All the time.
Why?
Glad to see you're awake, son.
A receipt for a car?
Were you able to get in touch with Keith?
His voicemail is full.
He… needs to know what's happened to Nathan.
But I… can't even leave him a message.
Where is he, Whitey?
I wish I knew.
It's okay, Deb.
I'll be here when you get out.
'BRIARWOOD RECOVERY CENTER: PRIVATE'
Sorry guys, visiting hours are over.
You need anything?
No, I'm cool, man.
I know you both want me.
Yeah. In your dreams.
Hello?
It's me, Nathan.
Thank god.
What happened?
I'm gonna be okay.
Well, I'm glad.
I'm coming home tomorrow, okay?
Actually, no,
it's not okay.
Don't come home, Haley.
Nathan, I have to come home.
No, you don't.
You have to go after your dream; just like I have to go after mine.
Coz if we don't, then…
we're just gonna end up regretting it…
then we're gonna end up resenting each other.
- Nathan, I wouldn't-
- Yeah, but we don't know that.
Nobody knows what's gonna happen.
Whatever choice you make today…
is gonna affect the rest of your life.
So…
don't come home, Haley.
Nathan, listen…
Coz I don't want you to.
Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net