Previously on One Tree Hill.
I’ve got a way for you to leave but you’ve gotta go in the morning.
- Hey.
- What’s wrong?
You know how much I care about you… Anna.
But there’s somebody else.
Is this what you’re after?
Jake!
I lied to you.
I slept with Keith.
Hey, Jules, it’s Keith.
I just realised something and I had to say it.
I love you.
Nice work, Jules. Just like we planned.
Haley, you owe it to your music! You owe it to yourself!
Your dreams are a bus ride away.
I know it’s scary… but just tell me if you can show me your heart.
If you do, I’ll guard it with my life.
Tennessee Williams once wrote…
When so many are lonely…
as seem to be lonely, it would be inexcusably selfish…
to be lonely alone.
- I don’t even have a toothbrush!
- I think they have those in New York.
I can’t believe I’m doing this.
You did good married girl.
I can’t do this.
I’m sorry.
Yeah, I figured.
You’re not ready.
I’m sorry, Karen.
- I should have told you about Keith, I...
- I think you should go.
Haley?
Whoa! Haley didn’t mess around.
- You’re Nathan, right?
- Yeah, yeah, do I… do I know you?
Well you should; I’m your sister-in-law.
Oh, uh… Vivian?
Don’t make me smack you!
- Quinn?
- Taylor!
Haley never mentioned me to you?
Can I come in?
- You wanna grab that?
- Wha-excuse me?!
- My suitcase.
- Oh! Yeah.
So, uh, Haley never said you were coming.
Ah, she didn’t know. So, where is little sis?
Out.
Well that’s vague.
Guess we’ll have to get acquainted till she gets home.
Yeah, sure… just make yourself at home.
Careful what you wish for, little brother-in-law.
- Who the hell are you?
Rick, never mind, I made a mistake.
High school girls!
You were dreaming.
Think you’re okay now.
Are you back for good?
Where’s Jenny?
I didn’t bring her.
I’m only here a couple days to check on you.
So what’s got Lucas so worried he’s gonna call my cousins in Savannah, huh?
Nothing, now…
So… you never answered any of my emails.
Yeah, I’m sorry.
I didn’t wanna give Nikki any chance of tracking me down and…
I just-I didn’t wanna get you caught up in this even more, just in case, you know.
Have you heard from her?
But she’s out there.
She might still be in Seattle.
That’s where Brooke and I told her you went.
Um… what are you gonna see Lucas while you’re here?
I don’t know. I’m gonna see my folks but…
other than that, I just kinda wanna keep a low profile.
Our secret, okay?
Okay.
Here, you go back to bed. We’ll talk about this in the morning.
- I’ll crash on the floor.
- Jake! Don’t be stupid.
Sounds like it finally stopped raining.
Maybe it finally did.
Where the hell have you been?
I just… I needed to clear my head, Nathan.
Little sis! Look at you!
Tay, what’re you doing here?
I’m on break. And I wanted to see the house before the new people moved in,
and I haven’t seen you in forever!
And mom told me that you got married so here I am.
Nathan said I could stay for a couple of days.
- Actually, I...
- You won’t even know that I’m here.
Yeah, okay, um… can you give us a second, please?
You said she could stay? Do you think… maybe that was worth a conversation?
I told her she could make herself comfortable because you weren’t here!
You were with Chris again, weren’t you?
- Yes, but I...
- Great! Great!
Will you just listen to me, please?
It’s over, okay? He… left town… he wanted me to go with him.
- What?!
- I said no because I-my life is here!
He didn’t mean anything to me, okay?
Besides, we’re gonna have to stick together if we’re gonna… survive ‘Hurricane Taylor’.
Anna!
How are ya?
Well, I was confused, I mean, after you showed up at my door talking about other girls.
Anna...
But, once I remembered you have a reputation for being a total ass-hat,
it pretty much cleared things up!
- Nice necklace.
- Thanks, Felix gave it to me.
I thought you guys were done.
That was before we currented up to full-on dating. Thus, the loot.
Are you sure about this?
Look, Lucas, I know you don’t like him but you don’t really know him.
Look, Brooke… I just want you to be happy.
Well, if I’m dating Felix and you’re dating Anna, does that mean we’re somehow related?
- Well, actually, Anna and I...
- Hey Brooke! You forgot something.
- What?
- This.
See you after?
Lucas, I’m happy. I hope you are too.
- Hello?
- Oh…
Uh, I was looking for Andy Hargrove. Um… I must have dialled… the wrong number.
Actually, I grabbed his phone by mistake. He bought us both the same kind.
Is he there?
He’s in the shower. Who’s this?
Um… A student. I’ll call back.
Karen? Are we ever going to talk?
- What is there to say?
- That I made a mistake.
Maybe what you did with Keith was a mistake…
but lying to me about it was a choice!
One that I can’t accept from a business partner; or my friend.
So, since your mom hired me to work here,
Keith helped me do a crash refresher course on bartending last night.
Ask me anything.
Okay, what’s in a… Long Island ice tea?
Wouldn’t you rather have a Screwdriver?
Can you toss me that?
Lucas, Hey! It’s early.
Yeah, I know, uh, can I talk to you?
Sure, I was just meeting Keith for breakfast and…
as usual, I’m late, but other than that… let me grab my shoes.
- Yeah.
- Everything okay?
Well, uh… that’s what I’m here to ask you.
Is this about your mom? Coz Keith told me the whole story and I feel like I’m horning in.
How do you know Dan?
Do I know a Dan?
Dan Scott – Keith’s brother?
He called you on your cell yesterday at the club.
Oh, that Dan.
Why’d he call you?
I bought a car from him.
And Dan had some questions about my credit references.
What’s going on?
I’m just, you know… looking out for Keith.
- Keith’s all grown up Lucas.
- Right.
Can we just… forget this?
Forget what?
Thanks.
Whoa! Peyton, this place is amazing!
Thanks. It can be, it’s just… it’s harder than I thought.
Well when did you ever give up, huh?
Um… anyway, the uh, the big news is: Nathan and Haley got married!
Married?
- For real?
- Yeah.
And it turns out Haley is, like, this mega talented musician and she’s going for it.
What’s the face?
Well, when I got off the bus, I saw Haley kissing some guy.
He was… kinda scrawny; had a guitar case; sort of… hell-t hair.
- Who’s he?
- Someone she shouldn’t be kissing.
Hey! Open up top!
Huh… see, I don’t know CPR and even if I did, I wouldn’t give you mouth-to-mouth so…
try not to drop when I’m the only person around.
I’m getting the stupid test, give me the damn ball.
Forget it.
Nice air-ball.
How bout Playstation? Nobody ever croaked from that.
That would involve me going home.
- You and Haley still fighting?
- Her sister’s here for a few days.
Which one?
Taylor.
Taylor?
Dude, she’s crazy.
Perfect! Dude, the thing is… when I saw her, I got that… déjà vu thing.
Like uh… like I’d seen her before.
Well, when we were freshman she was a senior so you probably saw her around school.
Yeah, I’m pretty sure I’ve seen more of her than that.
Two years ago, when they put me on varsity from the freshmen team…
the seniors threw this, kinda, out-there party at my parent’s beach house…
Taylor was there.
This is ugly.
Yeah, I was… I was pretty wasted… and… she was…
she was kinda the first girl I ever had sex with.
Great! Great. Laugh it up.
You know what; the only good news about this is that I don’t think she really even remembers me.
Oh, wow, you rocked her world, huh?
- This is not funny!
- You’re right, it’s hilarious!
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey, heart patient, remember?!
How bad is it?
Well, let’s see – my mom threw our last piece of water fern at my dad last night…
and it shattered where the hopper used to hang and now he’s sleeping in the pool house…
while we still have one. So…
They talking about moving? Say no.
Not so much talking as yelling, constantly.
It’s kinda gotten to the point where I just don’t wanna go home, you know?
Then we won’t.
Come on, I’ll buy you a nice dinner.
No. No, no, no, no! Felix, we can’t go in there, are you crazy?!
Why not?
Because this is the place that you made me do… do the dine-and-dash thing on Dare Night!
- What is so funny?
- You.
Do you honestly think I’d do that to you?
I paid the matredee on the way out when I left you.
- I’m full of surprises.
- You’re full of something.
You’re home. Sorry bout the mess. I needed a major, hot, soak after my ten mile run.
You run?
Well how do you think I got this great ass?
Are you blushing?
Adorable!
Run with me tomorrow. If… you can keep up.
If you can keep up.
I… bought some beer; you want one?
Uh… yeah… sure.
Look at you – such a jock!
So, come talk to me.
How bad is it?
How bad is what?
This thing between you and Haley.
Dinner chucked in the garbage; little sis coming home in the middle of the night;
hushed arguments behind closed doors.
Though that and… she told me all about it.
And she told you that Chris is out of the picture, right?
Chris… right.
You’re pretty threatened by him, huh?
Only because Haley was buying his crap.
For a smart girl, Haley sure can be stupid.
What’s… your issue with Haley?
I think she blames me for all the pressure she puts on herself.
How so?
I dunno, she didn’t wanna disappoint our parents like I did, I guess.
I tend to screw up, a lot.
Yeah, uh, I know how that is.
Really?
Mind if I get another beer?
- No, I insist.
- Yeah, okay.
You know, I still can’t believe little sis snagged such a hottie. I mean, usually, I get them first.
You want anything else; after-dinner drink, dessert, new shoes?
You don’t have to buy me things.
- Debit card ok?
- Of course.
- Felix!
- It’s okay, Brooke. You’re with me now.
I’m gonna take care of you.
- Looks like you were hungry.
- Yeah, I had a friend over.
You just missed him.
Him?
Oh it’s… not like that.
Um… I was gonna call you, it’s just…
um, last time I saw you it was… pile-on-Peyton day. You know? So, um, sorry.
Well, you had a right to be pissed at me.
You needed a friend… and… I wasn’t there for you.
Anyway, can I, um… still take you up on that ‘we can talk anytime’ offer?
Yeah! Come on, what’s up?
Lucas, kinda… broke up with me.
I mean… I’m not sure if we were even dating but, now there’s not even a chance.
I’m sorry, Anna.
I don’t know what I’m doing, Peyton.
None of us do.
Do you think there’s something wrong with me?
What?! No!
I think maybe there’s something wrong with Lucas; coz you are great.
Come here.
- On my god!
- Anna, that not really my thing.
I’m sorry.
- I’m-I gotta go.
- But, it’s cool, Anna!
Hey, I hope this is okay.
Look… I don’t know what came over me.
I was just… pretty upset and… you know, I wasn’t really thinking straight.
You know what I mean?
Anna! It’s cool… Okay?
I mean, now a lot of stuff makes sense like: how you acted at the Formal and…
how you blew me off after the whole locker thing.
Can we please just forget the whole thing?
Absolutely not!
Don’t be afraid to be who you are.
We can still be friends, right?
I don’t know if I can do that.
- Mine!
- Beat the girl! Such a gentleman!
Sorry. Good run.
Yeah. If I don’t run everyday, I got nuts.
Started when I left home; been running ever since.
I know the feeling.
Now I am all about the future.
Speaking for which – we haven’t had our mollocarian bathing ritual yet.
A what?
The mollocars, are a tribe in the South Pacific who celebrate weddings with a family bath.
- They must have a big tub.
- In the ocean dumbass.
Ah, what!
It symbolises the washing away of past sins and the rebirth of the family’s soul.
You have any idea how cold that water is?
Yeah, but I’m gonna appeal to you competitive side, sissy!
Alright! On three.
- One, two...
- Three!
What-get back here!
Oh! It’s cold!
Got you! Mollocai’s is a bar in Durham!
What?
I warned you, man.
You know, this is really getting old.
Heh, not as old as you hurting my sister. She’s at home, crying, coz of you.
I’m sorry man, but I don’t see how any of this is your business.
Coz I make it my business.
You hurt her, I hurt you.
You don’t wanna do that.
You’re right, what I wanna be doing is this.
Forget it!
Yeah, one more thing.
Damn, boy! Why aren’t we living here?
It’s my dad’s. Got the keys though.
Tell you what – I’ll turn on the fireplace if you grab the towels.
- They’re just...
- I know where they are.
Varsity basketball.
Yeah. Um…
- I was pretty wasted that night.
- Oh, what, you don’t remember me?
No, of course I remember you, I just…
I didn’t think you would come back to bite me in the ass.
Well this time I’ll only nibble.
Why didn’t you say anything?
I was having too much fun watching you squirm.
Does that make me bad?
Here.
So are you gonna tell me why you’re really in town?
I… screwed up at school.
I got caught cheating on an exam…
and then my professor and I got caught cheating on his wife!
He was paying my rent; expenses.
Yeah, until she found out and then that was that.
So, I… got kicked out.
And, next thing, I’m… knocking on your door.
So how bout we make a deal?
You keep my secret… and I’ll keep yours.
That sounds like a good plan.
Speaking of Haley – uh, we should get back.
I guess we could do that. This time.
You know… how you find a song and you just listen to it, like, over and over and over again,
until it becomes this, like, soundtrack, until you find… a new one?
Or, till you wanna forget the things that it reminds you of.
How’s you life, Jake?
It’s been hard.
You know, I’m not in school and… I’m working all these crummy jobs
and the whole time I just keep looking over my shoulder
thinking that Nikki’s gonna swoop down and snatch Jenny away.
You know I have to go back, Peyton.
I know.
I’d stay if I could.
I want you to know that.
So, when are you leaving?
Tomorrow.
I promised my folks - I’d have dinner with them tonight.
But… I’ll stop by – in the morning, before I head out.
Jake...
can you stay here again, tonight? Just to sleep.
I’ll come back after dinner.
I thought that since you wouldn’t answer my calls, maybe you’d been abducted or something.
I assume your mother has an accent?
Ah… not to me but yeah.
And you said you don’t have a sister.
Just one loser brother. What’s this about?
I called you in New York; and a woman answered and said you were in the shower.
Now this may not be fair to you but with everyone lying to me lately,
who is she?
Look, Karen, um…
this is something that I’m not really proud of but...
Tell you what – from now on; I’m the student, you’re the professor…
and I’ll see you in class!
Oh, nice, you guys finally decided to come home.
I left you a note. We went for a jog.
To where – Atlanta?
I’m… gonna… go take a shower.
We are supposed to be working on our marriage.
At least you knew where I was.
This has to stop, Nathan.
I don’t wanna lose you and it’s obvious that we still have issues; only now it just feels like you’re avoiding me.
I’m not avoiding you!
Then why are you spending so much time with Taylor?
Wha-are you threatened by her?
I don’t trust her.
Whoa girl, you look happy.
I can’t keep this.
Why not?
Because my mom married my dad for his money and you see how well that worked out.
- You think that’s all this is?
- I don’t wanna be like her.
And you’re giving me nice gifts and buying me expensive meals and I don’t wanna do it anymore.
- You’re breaking up with me?
- No! Just with your money.
I need to start feeling good about myself so I can start feeling good about us. Okay?
Okay.
I really don’t wanna go home.
- Spend the night with me.
- I’m not in the mood.
So? Spend the night anyway.
You really are full of surprises, aren’t you?
Trouble sleeping?
Just listening to you breathe.
Been thinking about stuff.
Alright Peyton, I gotta ask you – the other night, when I found you…
that was a drug deal. Am I right?
- I mean, Lucas called me for a reason...
- I…
I did coke with that guy… but it was… it was one time and… it was stupid. I know.
You’ve got so much going on, why would you need a crush like that?
I was weak.
- You don’t have to worry about me, Jake.
- I know.
But what if I want to?
Hey, Jules.
- Lucas, people are gonna start talking if you keep...
- You lied to me about how you know Dan.
I checked you out at the dealership.
Come inside, okay?
So, I know you paid cash for the car; which means, there was no credit check.
Bout two years ago, I was engaged to this guy.
I was crazy about him; even after he hit me a few times.
I thought it wasn’t gonna happen again… until he put me in the hospital for two weeks.
He disappeared after that and…
my welcome home present was finding out that I was over a hundred and fifty thousand dollars in debt;
with no way to pay the medical bills.
I was beyond desperate, Lucas.
So I posted an add on this website;
saying I’d do anything, legal, for money.
And Dan answered.
Said he’d help me out. He started paying my medical bills.
So, what did he ask you to do?
Make Keith fall in love with me.
Then break his heart.
I tried to tell Dan that I wasn’t gonna go through with it but its too late.
I never though I was gonna fall in love with Keith.
But I did, Lucas.
You have to believe me;
I love him!
Thought I was having a… bad dream only to wake up and find out its real.
But, I know that you have to go.
Last night, you said you were feeling weak.
Well here, let me show you something I use when I’m feeling weak.
‘If my hopes could bring you home, you and Jenny would be with me now’.
It’s the first email I sent you?
It’s like, I’d be working one of those jobs or…
feeling like I was gonna be on the run forever and I would-I’d read those words and…
it’s like this sudden calm… would wash over me.
You’re so strong, Peyton.
You don’t even know it.
I mean, you got me through some pretty dark days.
And… I’ve been thinking that, if I can get all that… from some words on a piece of paper…
just imagine what it would be like to have the real thing every day.
I’m just-I’m tired of running, Peyton;
come with me, let’s bring Jenny back home.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- I’m helping you pack!
- Am I packing?
- That’s where I’m sending you; packing.
Wait a minute, Haley.
You know what; complain window is close, okay? It’s time for you to go back to school.
- I’m… done with school.
- Well, I’m sorry.
I need to be here, working on saving my marriage and you’re getting in the way!
- I need a few days to figure things out.
- A few days is gonna turn into a few weeks.
I know you, Taylor. By then, it might be too late for Nathan and me.
We have to let her stay, Haley.
She’s family.
Just until you figure out what you’re gonna do, alright?
Sure. Thanks, Nathan.
Today, we’re gonna pick up with managerial ethics; where we left off just before my trip.
Actually, no, change of plan, forget that.
Who can tell me the word that I wrote on the board on the first day?
Karen?
- Greed.
- That’s right.
It’s a motivating factor in business, religion, politics.
I mean, I know it sure as hell motivated me.
Or it used to.
Three years ago, I was barrelling along in my SUV,
on my way to yet another meeting with yet another financial group.
At that point in time, my liquid assets totalled around thirty-one million.
On my cell I had a broker…
who could have, uh, pushed my net-worth up by another quarter of a million.
And I was so on my game this day. I mean, I was saying all the right things;
I was turning all the right screws… when, um…
I didn’t even see her –
until I got out of the car.
By that time, she was lying in a-in a pretty impossible angle and there was…
so much blood that I was sure that I’d killed her.
But she survived. Her name is Miriam…
and, uh, she’s gonna carry that accident around with her forever.
As will I.
Since then, I’ve tried to do right by her and… twice a year,
I visit her and her son.
To make sure they’re okay.
And some people say that I do that out of guilt; that may be but…
there’s another reason that I do it; I do it to remind myself that in this life,
there’s a point when enough’s enough.
Now if you’re haggling over money that you don’t even need;
enough’s enough.
Just… believe me on that.
So, if you’ll still have me, um… managerial ethics.
- Tunes for the road?
- Yep, right here!
- You got your bag?
- In the trunk!
Beef jerky? Oh, come on, you can’t have a road trip without beef jerky. You’re buying.
Okay, how bout, I got my debit card; we’ll just stop at the first truck stop!
Now we’re talking.
Top up or top down?
Down.
I don’t think it’s gonna rain today.
I know you have no reason to believe anything I say, but, I feel awful about this, Karen.
Our friendship has gotten me through some pretty dark days.
I never meant to betray that.
But… I can have my lawyer drop off the papers to dissolve our partnership, if that’s what you want.
It isn’t, Deb.
Just… please don’t lie to me again.
Felix told me what happened.
I’ll live.
I kind of owe you the biggest apology in the world, Lucas.
Me?
Yeah.
Coz, um…
I’ve been blaming a lot of stuff on you that isn’t your fault.
The last place we lived, the all-girls school I went to,
there were these… rumours that got started and…
my family found out and… I made a big deal out of it all… and we moved.
Felix was pissed at me because of that.
But the thing is, Lucas, those rumours, weren’t just rumours.
They were true.
What were the rumours?
That I like girls.
You’re the first person I have ever said those words to out loud.
Okay.
I mean, I’m into guys too so its a-it’s kind of confusing and…
I guess I put all my hopes on you; which wasn’t fair.
I thought since… you liked me and I liked you, maybe… that would make it go away.
Until you broke things off and then… there I was – right back where I started.
I’m not proud of it but that’s why I was mad at you.
Only I guess I was really mad at myself.
Wow, huh, this is a new one.
I’m not ready for people to know; especially Felix!
I won’t say anything.
Thanks.
And, I won’t say anything about you and Brooke.
What about me and Brooke?
She’s the girl you like, right?
I mean, it’s kind of obvious.
I thought I was cooler than that.
Well, apparently not!
Come here.
- I want you to have this.
- Felix...
It’s a gift. It’s not a payment.
And I didn’t buy it for you as much as I bought it for me.
Coz seeing you wear it makes me happy.
Sandwiches?
You like crow? Coz I’ve been craving it lately.
Don’t worry about it.
It’s about time I owned up to my mistakes.
Me too.
This isn’t really crow, I hope.
Turkey with Swiss.
Apologies on the side.
- Hey!
- Keith, uh, can I talk to you?
Sure. Come on in.
You know, um,
did I happen to leave my… MP3 player here?
Uh, no, haven’t seen it.
Right, um…
Oh, what, you wanna come in and hang out?
No, I’m okay.
See ya.
Feeling left out?
A little.
Well, you wanna be left out together?
Hey, uh, do you need some help?
Yeah, sure.
Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.fr -
www.tvsubtitles.net