Previously on One Tree Hill.
I’m glad you came son.
I wanna do something I shoulda done a long time ago.
Went to go see Dan.
What did he say this time?
That he was sorry.
Before the proposal we were friends Keith,
I mean can’t we at least try to go back to the way we were then?
I don’t think so.
My doctor’s put me through some cardiovascular rehab; I thought you might like to join me.
So you wanna be workout buddies?
Give us a chance to spend some time together. Get to know you.
You had my whole life to do that.
I thought the divorce went through.
Well technically no, Dan had the heart attack before signing the papers.
While signing the papers actually.
Look, would you do me a favour
and put a copy of this in the lockbox in my bottom desk drawer?
You are the one that I want.
Yeah, me too.
Excuse me!
Hello?!
Hola?
Hola.
Okay.
Look, I don’t know what my mom told you,
but here’s the drill, pool boys don’t get swimming privileges.
Right I… ciento you too.
Um… get aye outay.
What? You lose your suit?
Okay, I ditched Spanish the day they covered the naked verbs.
You no swim here.
Okay?
Okay.
Every night I watch you sleep,
Peace in dreams I hope you’ll keep.
Until your death,
With your last bre- Breat-brea.
Are you writing a song or are you planning on killing me?
Uh, officially I’m writing a new song, unofficially; I’d watch your back.
By the way, I found a new car on the internet.
- It’s great.
- Define great.
Five-hundred bucks great, which is actually thirty-six bucks less than we’ve got in the wish dish
so we could probably spring for a full tank of gas.
Well you know; my wish was more along the lines of TeeVO… surround sound.
Well a car will get you off the bus before Keith fires you for being late.
Will you just take a look at it? If it’s a piece of junk we’ll keep looking.
- Deal?
- Deal.
And um… make sure the trunk’s big enough to fit your body.
Just in case.
Dan?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I’m gonna order some lawn gnomes.
Front yard looks a little bare.
It’s a nice day. You wanna try a walk?
Maybe later.
- Hey Peyton.
- Hey.
- You looking for Lucas?
- Um… actually I was looking for you.
I just wanted to say I’m sorry things didn’t work out between you and my dad.
I was really enjoying getting to know you.
Yeah, I liked that too.
So I was hoping maybe we could keep in touch. Unless that’s weird.
No. That wouldn’t be weird at all.
Okay. Great.
Can I ask you for some advice?
You’re just the only woman I know that runs a business and I’ve got this crazy idea.
Well I like crazy ideas. What is it?
Okay. It is impossible to see good live music in this town without a fake ID
so I went to THUD and I suggested they sponsor an ‘all-ages’ night.
You know, not like here at the café but… like a club night.
- That sounds great.
- Yeah, I thought so too but no takers so far.
The club managers find out I’m in high school and it kinda ends there.
It only takes one person to say yes Peyton.
If you believe in it, see it through.
Eventually someone else will see it too.
Hey dad! How’s it going? Oh, pretty good son. You know I’m proud of you.
How’s Haley?
Well at least the cardboard one’s polite.
You know, Nathan, you’re not gonna be detailing cars forever.
I’m gonna find you something, you know, better.
No, you know, it’s cool. Whatever I have to do.
I mean just… treat me like any other employee who has no skills and whose last name isn’t Scott.
Okay, I will.
Oh yeah, Keith? Uh… I have a favour to ask.
Oh see now you are like any other employee.
Well… me and Haley have been saving up for a used car and…
well she found one she likes but I don’t know anything about cars.
So I was wondering if you could, check one out for me tomorrow?
I’d be happy to. Long as you don’t spread that ‘I don’t know anything about cars’ around the dealership.
Look I know this isn’t exactly glamorous… but you’re doing a good job.
I’m glad you’re here. It’s... it’s nice to be around family.
Alright, I’m gonna take off.
Oh Nathan.
Sorry. Force of habit. Lucas.
It’s okay.
Actually that reminds me. I left my history book in the kitchen.
I’m gonna be late for school. First day.
You’re gonna do great.
You sure you’re gonna be okay here? I mean if Dan needs you, I can get Lucas in after school.
Oh no, it’s fine. I don’t think I’m what Dan needs anyway.
- What do you mean?
- Oh he’s withdrawn, he’s depressed.
Well the doctor did say mood swings were pretty common after a heart attack right?
Oh well, it’s more than that. He just… he sits around watching TV.
He won’t do his rehab. I can’t reach him.
And, without Nathan around,  I don’t know who can.
- I’ll see ya.
- Okay, bye.
Lucas.
Um… door was open.
Wanna have a seat?
Actually, I was wondering if you wanted to go out.
Um… not thanks. I’m not really up for it today.
Listen, you said you wanted to rehab together; here I am.
Well maybe later.
Today only. Take it or leave it.
You think you can make it to the corner?
Of course.
You been shooting around at all?
Some. You know, this isn’t a race. You know, we can slow down if you want.
Easy for you to say.
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing. It’s just…
it’s hard to be less than what you once were. You might not understand that.
Yeah, I do.
You know, I’m not sure I’ll ever play basketball the same level ever again.
Think about it every day.
- Nathan doing okay?
- You really wanna know?
Yeah, I do. After all that’s happened, he’s still my son.
He’s good, you know. He and Haley are happy. He… really likes it at the dealership.
My dealership?
Yeah, uh, Keith took him on. I thought you knew.
We’re done here.
Hey come on. It’s not that far to the corner.
I said I’m done. My health, my call.
Okay. Well let me at least take you back to the house.
Lucas, go to school.
So, Business 101 huh? You a business major?
I’m not sure yet. It’s uh, my first college class.
Are you taking it with Hargrove? This guy’s tough.
Really?
How tough?
I heard he shot a guy, it ‘B’ school, just to watch him die.
- You’re kidding?
- Yes.
Well about him shooting someone. Not about him being tough though.
Good luck.
Morning folks. My name is Andy Hargrove, welcome to my class.
When I was twenty-one I made my first million with a B2B search engine.
The next year, I tripled it and then I tripled that.
Did an IPO, got really rich, cashed out and wound up here.
Well there’s a couple of hangovers in this side trip to Nepal between there and here
but that’s not important right now.
Okay.
Let’s talk about…
greed. Can’t run a business without it.
Anyone disagree with me?
There’s one in every class. Okay.
So, what’s your name?
Karen, and granted, I run a small café
but I’ve found that if your treat people well, they come back.
If you price things fairly, if you make a… quality product;
you don’t have to be ruthless to be successful.
Does… does anyone agree with her?
Well that’s too bad coz she’s right.
Guy co-look, I know that this class is titled Business 101,
but I like to think of it as Zen Business.
Who here wants to do well?
Everybody.
Who here wants to do good?
Coz there’s absolutely no reason why you can’t do both.
And since I’m the teacher, let’s just presume I’m right about that for now, okay?
Alright so everybody flunks today’s lesson, except for Karen.
Are you okay?
Yeah, unless we’re both dead.
Hey buddy! That’s my spot!
What are you doing here? You’re the pool boy.
You no park here.
Do you know this guy?
No. I’ve just seen him naked!
Pool boy! Wait up!
Running and gunning baby. You gotta keep up with me.
You speak English!
Figured we wouldn’t get very far if you kept trying to speak Spanish.
Who the hell are you anyway?
Hey! Buddy these are two hundred dollar shoes don’t make me speed walk!
I’m your new neighbour which makes you, the girl next door.
And in the movie, she was a porn star.
Ha, well I don’t believe you coz if you were my neighbour, you’d know that house has its own pool.
I like yours better.
Look, this thing between us, it’s inevitable.
What thing? There is no thing.
Come on! We fight, we flirt.
Maybe even slap me but eventually, we end up in the sack together
so how bout we skip the anger and cut right to the sex?
How bout we cut right to the slap?
Okay. It’s part of the sex.
Hey Brooke. Who’s your friend?
He’s no friend of mine.
Girl I love it when you’re sassy!
Oh how you doing man? I’m Felix; the new guy.
I’m Mouth; the been-here-forever guy.
Right, so tell me something man; how’s the talent around here?
Sports?
Keeps up with me Mouth; women. The girls.
How’s the stock? Are they all like your friend Brooke?
Oh um… I don’t really…
Oh you don’t know. That’s okay.
I need someone to show me around. You up for that?
Sure, guess so.
Great. Look here’s the thing; we gonna act strong now.
We’re not gonna hurt anyone but we’re gonna break a few hearts, it happens.
They live, you learn.
Occupational hazard. Alright, who do you like that’s available?
Who do I like?
For me Mouth. Okay? Don’t be selfish.
How about her?
Nah, too young. You wanna hit it, not baby-sit it.
Look, onto of that, I’m the new guy.
I mean my game is strong anyway, but new guy status is hardcore.
Peyton, Haley. This is Felix.
- Hi.
- How you doing?
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Girl, you are totally fine.
Dude, I’m totally married.
Really? Who’s the father?
Little close aren’t you?
Oh, guess it’s you.
She’s not pregnant but they are married.
Yeah yeah, I saw the ring. Guess she likes poor guys.
This should be interesting.
Yeah!
So I showed him around and he seems pretty cool.
His family, they move like almost every year.
Witness protection?
Uh-uh, doctors without borders. They’ve been all over the world.
His parents are opening up a private practise over here.
Who we talking about?
- Felix, the new guy.
- You met him?
Sort of, he was hitting on Haley.
I thought you weren’t supposed to be playing.
Hey look, a little pick-up every now and then aint gonna kill me.
Wanna run?
I was on my way home.
Got a tonne of studying to do and I gotta work tomorrow. One shot.
Yes!
How’s work anyway huh? Boss not riding you too hard?
No man, Keith’s cool;
a lot cooler than my dad ever was.
It’s kind of weird how… my closest contact with him now is a cardboard cut-out.
Oh yeah, listen, I may have screwed things up… for you, with Dan.
He asked about you… and I kinda… mentioned the dealership gig.
But you talked to him?
Yeah.
Look, your mom’s having trouble getting him to rehab.
So I figured maybe I’d… give it a shot. If that’s cool with you.
Honestly; after everything you know about the guy are you sure you wanna let him in?
You know, when Dan had his heart attack,
I figured; well that’s it. You know, we’re never gonna know each other.
But… he didn’t die.
So it kinda makes me wonder if I don’t take a chance now,
will I regret it someday?
You do what you need to do man.
You should know who he is.
I want you to fire Nathan. Name over the front door still says ‘Dan Scott Motors’.
As long as I’m running things, I’m gonna make hiring decisions as I see fit.
You know, word is you actually got a heart in your chest Dan;
why don’t you try thinking of Nathan.
You know Keith, if Nathan can support a wife, he’ll never realise what a colossal mistake this marriage is.
He’s emancipated Dan!
That’s his mistake to make and if you want him fired,
then you’re gonna have to look him in the eye and do it yourself when you come back to work.
Until then… he stays.
It’s all attitude Mouth. It’s gotta work with the vibe you got.
Geeky and shy are not a vibe.
Packaging my man; you’re not geeky, you’re sensitive.
You’re not shy, you’re mysterious.
Girls love that.
Anybody special you looking to impress?
Nah, nah, I’m just um… you know, I’m playing the field.
Sup Mouth?
Hey Luke.
- Run anybody over today?
- I feel you man.
It’s hard when the big dog comes to town. Not sure where you stand anymore.
I get that. Hang tough bro. It gets easier.
Still mad?
Still here?
So what happened between you and Brooke?
Or was it Peyton?
Tell me it was both at the same time.
Dude, I never said a word. I swear. He’s got like… psychic super powers.
Nah… I just been in eighty schools in the past ten years.
You learn how to read people.
So; Brooke? Peyton?
We’re all just friends.
If that’s your story.
Um… see you later.
How much do you love me?
Do we get the car?!
Close you eyes.
- It’s a car in our apartment?
- Haley, come on.
Come on... alright alright, I’m closing my eyes.
Alright, come here. Wait a second.
Alright. Open!
You love it?
What did you do?
Now you have something to compose on.
But you were going with Keith to look for a car.
Yeah we did but Keith said it was no good so…
Nathan… you have to take this back.
You don’t like it.
Of course I like it. It’s beautiful.
But we need a car.
Haley, we can get a car anytime.
With what?! Magic beans?
I mean... Look, I know. I know you’ve never had to deal with money before
but things are different now. You can’t just go out and...
and buy a… keyboard because you feel like it! We agreed on a car!
Haley! You are a really good musician! Okay?
I have a feeling about your music. It’s gonna take you places.
It means a lot to me Nathan. It does but what is gonna take you to work?
Alright, you know what; I was just trying to do something nice for you. Okay?
Fine. You wanna do something nice for me? Get us a car like we talked about.
It’s a beautiful gift but… we worked so hard to save that money.
Hales, boys are clueless. I swear to you, I’m thirty years away from giving them up for good.
Okay, so, what about this? Does this say… ‘let me promote and all-ages club night’?
No. Not enough skin. Try… this.
Oh god. That much for two doilies and a piece of wire?
You’re not gonna try it on?
Not today.
Not today? Brooke Davis, this is a shopping day you will never ever get back again.
Hey listen, if you’re still waiting on your ATM card, I can front you the cash.
Nah, it’s cool.
My dad just… spaced a deposit to my account.
Okay!
Ah, now we’re talking. If this band manager is a guy, you are golden!
You know, speaking of guys, can we just do five minutes on this Felix person?
Yes! He is hot and totally vibing on you married girl.
No wonder Nathan’s jealous.
It’s kinda weird, I’ve never had anything like that happen before.
Okay, but guys, how can he make Nathan jealous? This boy is repellent!
I mean he’s been here what, five seconds and he’s already butting in everybody else’s business,
bossing people around and acting like he owns the place, come on!
What!?
Earth to Brooke, he’s you… in pants.
He in not!
Kinda is.
Argh! Argh I hate you both!
Any verdict on college yet?
Well my teacher’s a little unorthodox. And younger than I expected.
Ahh, so you’re one of these ah, maturity… likers.
Sorry, I suck at grammar.
So, why did you pick me out of the class?
I mean you always find somebody to torment?
I like to find the student who can give me a run for my money.
Ah, which is a lot of money of my google search is correct.
Yeah, it is.
What kind of guy cashes in on a fifty million dollar business?
A guy who wasn’t happy.
Oh no look I mean I started with a small business you know? Like your café and…
I got bored, I took some risks, business picked up
and when I hit fifty million, obviously I realised I could just… coast on that forever.
What’s the point you know? No getting challenged.
And teaching is that challenge for you?
Yeah. Yeah, scares me to death.
I just know that one of those weasels in the front row is gonna ask me a question that I can’t answer.
So what about you? You ever thought about growing your business?
Oh sure.
I even drew up expansion plans but it was never the right time.
Never is you know. Just gotta figure it out ask you go along.
But if you ask me, the object of the game is to make a difference.
Okay, all I’m saying is that a lotta kids would support live music if they had a night of their own.
Now you manage more than one band. Okay, so if you would just work with me on this,
I know we could get a club owner to agree to try it out.
Look. My band doesn’t play to kids.
We play to shot and beer crowds, not high school proms.
Okay but what I’m saying is that an all-ages club could work in this town.
Sorry, no dice. I’m just not interested.
Swear to god, this is the last time I hire a singer off a flier at Kinko’s.
You know nothing, absolutely nothing about music man.
I went to Berkley ass-face; studied a little something called composition.
You might want to look into it.
Yeah I will, the next time I look in the audience and they’re ignoring us.
Plant and Page.
Have we met?
Who’s this?
I was in the crowd the night that you guys played together the first time.
Go on.
There were what, like twenty people in the crown that night?
But your energy was… I mean it was so real!
You know, you guys looked like you were gonna explode up there on stage
but that’s what made it work.
That’s the tension that made Led Zeplin work and it’s the same tension that sets your music apart.
The Key Club.
That was a good night.
Well… yeah, they could all be good nights if you guys would just quit your bitching
and… focus on what matters.
But then again, what do I know you know I’m just a kid.
But if I were you guys I’d put my energy into the music otherwise…
you’ll be lucky to play at the high school prom.
Hey, thanks for coming back.
Sorry about the crappy mood the other day. Shouldn’t have taken it out on you.
It’s cool but if it starts to become a habit; find yourself another trainer.
New car?
Dealership.
I like to drive all the new models so I can tell the customers what they’re getting.
Problem is, the doctors won’t let me drive yet.
You mind?
Mind what?
Taking it for a spin. Tell me how she handles.
Any kind of feedback would help.
We can stop somewhere along the way and do some rehab.
You game?
Lucas, I can barely take a walk without gasping for air right now.
At least I have my work.
You’d really be helping me out.
The job doesn’t end getting the band you know? You gotta take care of them.
You gotta be part cheerleader, part babysitter, part therapist.
It’s no problem, I can handle that.
What I’m saying is… you gotta look after all their needs; food, drink, drugs.
Um, drugs?
Oh don’t worry, I’ll set you up with the guys I buy from.
They’re reliable.
I mean, they’re drug dealers, you don’t wanna mouse it or anything…
but… they won’t burn you.
I got a good sense about people.
You’re young but you… might be worth the risk.
No thanks.
Here’s your shot kid.
What do you say?
Brooke?
What’s wrong?
I just keep screwing up this toe.
Brooke.
You know how I told you that my credit card got declined because the bill got paid late?
It’s a load of crap.
Well what happened?
We're broke.
My dad’s company went under and…
doing this stupid bankruptcy thing and my mum’s telling me we might have to sell the house.
God Brooke. I’m so sorry.
Yeah me too.
I love being rich, I’m good at it.
So is that why Felix is getting under your skin? Coz he’s… the rich guy next door.
I dunno, maybe.
Brooke, its just money. You know. There is so much more to you than that.
Yeah but that’s my favourite part.
I don’t wanna talk about it anymore. How was your meeting?
It’s not gonna work out.
Really?
I’m sorry.
Yeah… me too.
Guns and Roses, Whitesnake, Metallica, Aerosmith.
Please tell me you’re kidding. You didn’t actually listen to metal?
Even had my own spandex.
Man that is not a vision I wanted to have in my head.
Lucas right?
Yeah.
Nice wheels.
Thanks. You know you’re on the wrong side of the road, right?
Yeah I know. Wanna air it out?
Maybe some other time!
Come on. Race your for that girlfriend. What’s her name? Brooke?
Ex girlfriend.
Which was inevitable once I got to town.
Don’t hate the player; hate the game.
Hey, tell me you’re gonna wipe the smirk off that punks face.
Come on, my T-Bird coulda taken him.
Go go go go go go! Woah!
What the hell are you doing?!
Come on chicken!
You did the right thing.
Yeah.
Don’t sweat it. Chicken’s not for everyone.
Who you got riding shotgun?
Uh… this is… Uh, this is my...
Dan Scott. Scott Motors.
When you’re ready to trade up, come on down to the dealership.
We probably should get going.
Hey.
Hi, the printer dropped off the proofs for the new menu,
I wasn’t sure if you were coming by the café today so…
- These are great.
- Yeah.
What’s this?
Café expansion plans from million years ago.
I was gonna add a bar.
Why didn’t you go through with it?
Ah, you know, the timing was never right.
I was… busy all day at the café and I didn’t wanna give up my nights with Lucas too.
Are you reconsidering?
I’m writing a business plan for class. A start-up for a new venture.
The more I play around with these fake companies,
the more I’m thinking… maybe it shouldn’t be just an exercise.
I'd always hoped to branch out some day.
- Is that nuts?
- No, not at all.
In fact, I’ll be one of your investors.
You don’t even know what I’m proposing.
But I know you and I know how hard you’ll work.
Ah besides, what’s life without a few risks.
Excuse me!
I need to check your bag.
Okay.
Sure.
- What’s this?
- It’s a birthday present, for me.
She’s shy about buying stuff like this. But hey, I guess that’s part of the turn-on right?
I would have come in to check it out sweetie.
I was just… gonna take it outside to show him.
Blue’s perfect, that’s your colour. We’ll take it.
I gotta admit… it’s a great car.
You want it?
You can’t buy me.
Come on Lucas, it’s not like that.
This is what I do for people I care about.
What, you care about me now?! You don’t even know me!
I want to. More than you know.
We both know I owe it to you.
You almost had me, you know that?
Shame on me, right?
I mean I actually enjoyed the day with you. Till now.
Some town you’ve got here.
I mean, all the relationships are inbred.
One of the hottest girls get married, if that’s even legal
and the rich girl shoplifts for kicks.
What were you doing in there?
I needed the new catalogue.
Besides, you meet the trashiest girls in lingerie shops.
Look, I don’t…
I mean I’ve never done anything like that before.
Well clearly. You suck at it.
- Have fun?
- No!
It’s just...
It was a mistake and I’d like it to stay between us.
I can keep a secret.
Promise?
You’ll just have to trust me.
I don’t know you well enough to trust you.
You will.
You might as well have it. I’m planning on seeing you in it soon.
Not a chance in hell!
You’re welcome, Winona.
You weren’t even gonna come inside and say hello?
I’m working. We got a call to pick up the car.
Oh sure, you’re working.
You’re emancipated now right? Course your old man still sets the table.
I gotta get back.
Hey, I had a heart attack. I coulda died.
Dad, we both know that’s never gonna happen.
You can’t jerk anybody’s chains if you die.
Okay, just wait.
- Let’s just talk.
- About what?
I dunno. How’s your wife?
Lot happier than yours.
Hey Nate, come here, I wanna show you a couple of the basics.
Alright, you see this battery clamp?
Well, if it gets corroded, then the current can’t get through to the starter
and then you get that ah, that noise when you crank it.
Yeah, the noise.
And everybody thinks it’s a big deal but it’s not.
You just, uh, you just clean it, with a wire brush and… you’re good to go.
That’s so cool! My dad never taught me this stuff. He didn’t want me to be...
He didn’t want you to get grease under your fingernails like me.
Look, that’s my dad, Keith. That’s not me.
So how did it go at the house?
Uh… pretty much what you’d expect.
As a matter of fact, I think I had so much fun, I’m gonna go back tonight
and I’m gonna disappoint Haley some more.
Haley didn’t like the keyboard?
Oh no, she liked it, she just wanted it to have four wheels and a trunk.
I think I might be able to save your marriage.
What do you think of this?
I think it was probably a pretty sweet ride back when dinosaurs ruled the Earth.
Yeah, I was gonna sell it for parts but, you know, we could work on it together.
Fix it up and… then you can have it.
So it’s like a family project?
Yeah, you bet.
We’ll fix that.
If I’da known you couldn’t play any better than that, I wouldn’t have bought it home.
I wanna apologise. Alright?
- That was your money too.
- Oh it’s not that Nathan. I totally overreacted.
Partly because I love this gift
and I love you for getting it for me.
But partly because we just can’t be as careless as we used to be.
Not if we wanna make this marriage work.
I know, you’re right and… I don’t know the first thing about managing money,
it was just always around.
Yeah well… at least you don’t have that problem anymore.
Hales. I want you to keep this keyboard. Okay?
You have a talent, you need to use it.
- Nathan I...
- We’re keeping it.
Besides, there’s an old car that Keith said I could fix up.
He’s gonna help you?!
Yeah.
Oh! I really wanted to keep it! Thank you.
He didn’t wanna see me.
He didn’t wanna see either of us.
Remember when he was little?
I used to take him to work with me on Saturdays.
He’d have to get up early but he didn’t mind.
He wanted to hang out with his dad.
Now I’m thinking it was all a lie.
What if I spent my life chasing the wrong things Deb?
Success, money, respect.
What if it turns out none of it matters because I lost my family along the way?
Can I get it back?
Is it too late?
I don’t know!
Hey Karen, what’s up?
You know it was such a good… space for Nathan and Haley’s party?
And I think, it would make a great club.
The only thing is, I’m gonna need someone who can run… my all-ages night.
You had a great idea Peyton and I know you’d be worth the risk.
What do you think?
I’ll give you a thousand dollars…
for a decent cup of coffee.
You’re right.
My pool is better.
Synchro : Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net