Previously on One Tree Hill.
No one else needs... to know.
You mean Karen.
You know, I was thinking about this whole ‘Friends with Benefits’.
Felix with Brooke… FWB.
How many other songs have you written?
I dunno, a few.
- Alright, well you’re gonna open.
- No, I’m not.
I get… major stage fright.
You’re gonna have to get out for this one.
You gonna tell me what it was?
Maybe.
You’re great.
Yeah, I know. When do I play?
You’re okay, but… we had a lot of really good people show up today, so…
we’ll call you.
Hey, look, I know it’s kinda short notice so…
bring Lucas along if you can’t find a sitter. Love to meet the little guy.
My brother owns the dealership. I’m just helping out.
I’m actually a mechanic.
I like mechanics.
I got a good sense about people.
You’re young, but you… might be worth the risk.
Here’s your shot kid.
Oliver Wendell Holmes once said;
Many people die with their music still in them.
Too often it is because they are always getting ready to live…
Before they know it… time runs out.
You’re still here.
I thought we had an understanding; once the hooking-up is over, you go home.
Damn.
You can make a guy feel used.
Oh I’m sorry.
Well you could just cancel our little arrangement and save your pride.
Nah. Being used is fine.
Yeah, that’s what I thought. So why don’t you get your used butt up outta my bed, ‘Pool Boy’.
I have a big day ahead of me and you’re in my way.
Hi.
I think you got the wrong store.
‘Forever 21’s just down the street there.
That’s Jeff Buckley. You heard of him?
Who hasn’t heard of Jeff Buckley?
That man’s the reason I became a musician. You know why?
Because he never sold out.
Why stop there? Didn’t he also drown in a river?
Listen, if you want me to play your show, you’re gonna have to ask nicely.
- I don’t need this.
- Sure you do.
Why else would you be here at eight a.m. on a school day?
Okay, here’s the deal; the turn-out for auditions was kind low so… if you want...
Read my Writer.
- What is this?
- It’s like… a list of artist’s demands.
I know what a Writer is.
Camomile tea… one small vegetarian pizza…
Oh! One box Magnum, extra large sized condoms. Are you kidding!
The regular ones cut off the circulation. We got a deal here or what?
You go on at nine.
Have fun at school.
Come on, pony up people! There’s kids in this world a lot more miserable than you!
Thank you. God bless.
Look at this; one over-ripe cantaloupe,
two number three pencils, what kinda Writer is this?
God bless you.
Change for the needy?
Brooke, I had no idea you were so… charitable. What’s the cause?
Just… needy people. God bless you.
Brooke. I recognise the photo.
It’s from an add for cramp medicine.
Wow. Homeless and PMSing… poor girl.
Brooke!
Alright. The money’s for me.
I’m the needy one as in I need some things for your club opening.
Do you realise how wrong that is?
Sort of, but… you know, what am I supposed to do for money?
- Try getting a job.
- Right, doing what?
Anything, a number of things. What are your skills?
I dunno. I’m good with guys. Dates, dating.
Yeah, and?
Sex but…
That would make you a hooker.
Thank you.
I’ll take you shopping on a budget.
- Hey Felix.
- Mighty Mouth.
You going to the club opening tomorrow?
- That’s the plan.
- You taking Brooke?
Nah, I like to alternate my cheerleaders. This week - Theresa.
But I thought you and Brooke were together.
It doesn’t really work like that.
So… she’s not gonna be there with anybody?
Not that I know of.
Hey you.
You know, I had a great time the other night.
Me too. Listen, can we talk?
That doesn’t sound good.
It’s not like that. It’s just…
I love spending time with you. You know that… but…
being dropped in a new place is hard enough without jumping into a new relationship too.
You must really hate me.
Stop it! I’m just saying, let’s not rush things. Let’s hang out, see where it goes.
Did Felix say something?
No, it’s not that. Promise.
Okay, friends.
With potential.
- Hi.
- Ready for your big debut rock star?
- Please don’t remind me.
- She’s ready.
You know, didn’t you once tell me that there was such a thing as over preparation?
Yeah, for a math midterm. This is like… avoiding public humiliation.
Hales, you’re gonna do great.
Hey.
Saturday night, three bands. Bring your friends.
Adrian Tomine fan?
You know his stuff?
Yeah. Oh, I love Optic Nerve.
Really?! Wow, a fellow comic book geek.
Well, closeted.
- I’m Anna.
- I’m Peyton.
You’re Felix’s sister right?
On the days that I claim him, yeah.
Oh. So how’s… Tree Hill treating you?
Okay.
But I think someone for not giving me the secret password.
Yeah, people in this town tend to stick to their own crowd.
At least the guys are cute.
Okay.
Tree Hill rule number one;
people in this town tend to have really complicated histories.
Dan! How’re you feeling?
Good.
Good, Deb’s not in till four.
I came to see you.
Okay.
To apologise.
I was hoping you’d forgive me for the things I’ve done to hurt you.
Can I be honest with you Dan?
You’re creeping everybody out.
This Phoenix bird thing, this sensitive thing that you’re pulling; no one’s buying it.
I’m sorry you feel that way.
But I understand.
Oh, by the way, Deb says Keith hasn’t been hanging around here lately.
I hope it’s not because of what happened.
You should know that I’ve chosen to forgive him.
For what?
For sleeping with Deb.
Oh, I’m sorry Karen…
I really thought that you knew.
Speak!
Hey. It’s uh… it’s Keith.
Sorry, I know a lotta Keith’s. Could you be more specific?
The Keith you kissed the other night?
Nah, you gotta give me more than that.
Uh… in a convertible.
On a car ramp at Scott motors.
Okay, that… that narrows it down to about a half-a-dozen or so.
You’re funny.
Uh… hey look, I know its last minute but...
there’s a club opening tonight. You wanna go?
Wow, I dunno. I think I already have a date.
Besides, don’t you know about the Wednesday rule?
The Wednesday rule?
A girl can’t accept a weekend date if the offer comes after Wednesday.
It’s a rule.
Yeah, well you know who follows those rules?
Girls who sit at home on the weekends.
Well you may be in luck.
I’ve never been a big fan of rules. Eight o’clock?
Does this look overly ripe to you?
Sorry, that’s not my area of expertise.
So what’s going on with you and Felix now?
I don’t know.
I mean the whole point of ‘Friends with Benefits’ is that there’s no strings attached, right?
Right.
Well lately he’s been getting really stringy on me.
And why are we looking for… overly ripe fruit again?
Chris’ Writer.
Basically, I have to give him everything on this list or he won’t perform.
So wait a second, he makes a list and you have to do everything on it to get what you want?
Exactly.
Interesting.
Just in time.
Just let me finish here and then we can go upstairs.
You can go upstairs and… finish yourself. I just came by to give you this.
It’s a Writer. List of artist’s demands. Peyton told me about it.
What’s it for?
Well, yesterday you seemed a little sketchy on the terms of our agreement
so I figured I’d clear it up for you.
With a bunch of rules?
And you better follow them if you ever want me to… perform at your venue again.
No sleeping over. No sleeping late.
No non-sexual bathing, is this necessary?
You’ve been getting a little needy.
Needy?
Please, I have a date tonight.
You are okay with that?
Item 12.
No asking if it’s okay to date other people.
So we’re clear?
Crystal.
That’s an odd sight.
What, you thought I’d be blind?
No, I just didn’t think you could read.
Five hundred things a person should see before they die.
I’ve seen twelve of them.
You gonna do something about that?
Well that’s the plan.
At least until practice starts.
I always wanted to die with the matarays in Tobago.
So... Coach…
I turned down ‘High Flyers’.
Is there a reason you turned them down or… should I even ask?
Well it’s just… Haley’s pursuing this whole music thing.
She’s done a lot for me, Coach. It’s her turn now.
And me going to camp is just standing in the way of that.
Sometimes… marriage is about sacrifice.
Maybe you’re not taking a step forward as a basketball player…
but you’re taking two steps forward as a man.
Thanks Coach.
Hey.
Oh hi.
Hi. I just dropped by to… wish you good luck tonight.
Thanks. You’re still coming right?
Of course, yeah.
Oh, good.
Um… I also wanted to talk to you about something else.
Okay.
Um… I know that you and I were never… an item
but I thought you should know…
I’d like to…
bring a date to the club tonight.
Anyone I know?
Uh… her name’s Jules. I… I met her at the dealership.
Is… that it?
Yeah.
Good! I look forward to meeting her.
Okay.
Beware of strangers bearing gifts.
- What is that Andy?
- Well look, every… cool club needs its own t-shirt right?
- So… here you go.
- There are sweet.
Oh, Lucas. That reminds me. Uh, I got him one too.
Oh, um… Keith, this is Andy.
My professor.
- Nice to meet you, Keith.
- Yeah. Yeah you too.
- But I want it so bad!
- No. It’s not in the budget.
Besides, if you get the purse, then you can’t afford the outfit for the opening.
Screw the opening. I’ll stay at home with the purse.
What’s going on, you alright?
- Yeah, I just feel a little light headed.
- Why?
- I… sold some stuff.
- What stuff?
Some… blood.
Blood!? You sold blood? Brooke, you really think that’s a good idea?
You actually don’t look very well. Kinda… pasty.
I’m discount shopping. I’m gonna have to get used to looking like crap.
And besides, I needed some extra money for the dress.
Which is only thirty-six bucks.
Shoes.
- Eighteen dollars.
- Eyeliner to go with the shoes.
Seven fifty, which is what? Sixty-one fifty with tax. I mean please, you have plenty left over for...
Alcohol! We’ll stop by the liquor store on the way home.
I really don’t think you should be drinking after you just gave blood.
No! The woman told me to re-hydrate myself and besides,
if I’m gonna be seen in these shoes, I’m gonna need a drink or two.
Okay, we’ll have a DJ downstairs.
The bar is stocked. Wristbands?
Uh… they are down front with Junk right now.
That’s it !
It’s out of our hands.
Oh no, you forgot something.
What!?
To take a deep breath.
Just for a second. Look around, I…
you guys did this. And it’s great.
Yeah.
Oh god, but what if I didn’t make better flyers, what if I didn’t put up enough
- and then what if nobody shows up outside and...
- Come here.
I don’t think that that’s gonna be a problem.
Okay, my thighs are itching…
and not so much in a good way, I think I’m allergic to polyester.
But it’s fine; I’ve had a few drinks.
I should have a few drinks because… do you see all these people?
You’re gonna be fine.
Hey, Miss Roe. Club looks great.
Uh… let’s see the wrist, Brooke.
No alcohol! Are we clear?
Yes.
Good. Now go have some fun.
This is definitely the first time I’ve felt like the oldest person in the bar.
Second oldest.
Oh, Andy, this is Peyton. Peyton, this is… my friend, Andy.
Hi.
Hi. Um… well I’ll try to keep out of your hair.
You didn’t happen to bring little Lucas tonight did you?
Oh, well. Yeah… he’s wondering around here somewhere.
Great, great. I can’t wait to meet him.
- Little Lucas?
- His words, not mine.
So, what’s the story with you and your… friend.
You know, I’m not sure how to describe it.
Put it this way; are you two getting…?
Peyton!
Cos if you were, I’d… I’d describe it as pretty lucky.
He’s a fox.
So, how was your other date before the cancellation?
Why? You wanna ask him out?
No, just didn’t know you were seeing other people.
If you’re one of them, I’d shut up.
Okay, you know, that’s a good point.
So how’s it going Junk?
All good. Here you are, Mr Scott plus one.
VIP - over twenty-one wristbands.
- I didn’t know you were so hip, Keith.
- Yeah, well neither did I.
Karen never said anything about drinking outside of her club.
Hey Brooke. I like your dress.
So… I was wondering if maybe you wanted to do something some time.
Hey, you wanna catch a movie some time?
Sup Mouth?
- Hmm… hey Theresa! Nice dress.
- Um… thanks.
Why does it look so familiar? Oh I remember, cos it used to be mine.
Brooke, I asked you before I bought it. You said it was okay.
Yeah, well that’s before I knew how your ass would look in it.
Theresa, why don’t you go up, I’ll be right there.
I’d have to check the list but I’m pretty sure acting like a jealous girlfriend is against the rules.
I’m not jealous!
I just figured you’d have gone for someone with a little more class.
Why? I went for you, didn’t I?
- Hey.
- Hey!
I can’t do it.
- What?
- I can’t do it.
Do what?
Play. At all. I have to back out.
And you’re telling me this now?!
I’m sorry! It’s just all these people and... I told you this might happen, okay?
So please just… don’t hate me. I’m sorry.
Haley, you can’t do this okay? You’re name’s already on the poster,
there are people here expecting you to play.
Well so what? I mean, who’s gonna know the difference, right?
You’ve already got two acts and a DJ, right?
I’ll figure it out.
Okay.
But you’re gonna have to get on that floor sometime.
Hey Karen! This crowd; you must be thrilled.
Oh, try crazy. Seems like every teenager in the town showed up.
So Andy made it.
Yeah, I’m still trying to figure out how to introduce him to Lucas.
Uh-uh well… think fast.
So ‘Kings of Convenience’? I just got their album last week. It’s great.
Oh, you should see them live.
Oh god, I bet.
So how’d you find out about the club?
I’m actually kind of... dating the woman who’s responsible for all this.
Really? You dating Peyton?
- She’s got the curly hair right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, the cops’ll love that. No, no, no, no, her name’s… Karen.
Andy.
Mom?
Oh boy.
Lucas, this is Andy. Andy… this is my son, Lucas.
Um… little Lucas?
I… I thought you were six. Not… six one.
Oh hey, there’s... someone I want you to meet. Deb!
Oh Keith, I was hoping you’d make it.
Uh… Jules, this is… my sister-in-law, Deb. Deb, this is Jules, my…
Girlfriend. Nice to meet you.
This is my girlfriend, Jules.
Nice to meet you too.
Thank you. I’ll uh, get us some drinks?
Okay. I’ll just take a water.
Two tequilas it is.
- She seems fun.
- Yeah, she’s really great.
It’s nice to see good things happen to you Keith.
You deserve it.
Previously on ‘Saved By the Bell’.
Hey, Chris, this is my husband Nathan.
Married in high school. Yeah, that’ll work.
Peyton told me you bailed on the gig.
Guess I was wrong about you.
Appropriate response. So, ready for our first dance?
I don’t know. Are friends supposed to have a first dance?
They are when the have potential.
Yo! You wanna explain this? My sister’s topless.
You wanna get that outta my face?
Lucas, just walk away. Please.
Outside! Now!
- Are you out of your mind?!
- Are you out of yours?
It’s because of crap like this, we had to move again…
and you know what? I liked my last life.
- Oh, great! This again. You...
- You want people to talk?
Keep it up, oh cos they will. Just like the last time.
Just because people say something, doesn’t make true Felix. Those were rumours!
Yeah? Well how do you think rumours get started?
Hey, what’s going on Tree Hill?!
Uh… I’d like to welcome you guys to the opening night of TRIC.
It’s a night we like to call… House of Freaks. You guys ready?!
Yeah? Okay, great!
Well then please help me in welcoming, to the stage, Chris Keller.
- Hey P. Sawyer.
- Hey!
It’s your big night. I’m sorry I didn’t get you anything un...
- Okay, sush, sush. It’s okay.
- Boy’s a fox.
- Hey, show us your te...!!
- Hey!
Alright, here we go now.
Hey!
You guys aren’t ready for this!
What!
Ah, what’re you gonna do, right?
Hey, wait a second. What about Peyton?
Tough break. Least it beat being screwed over by a friend, right?
Sorry, sorry everybody. Uh… we just had a little…
I’m not… whatever that was.
Uh, but while we’re sorting it out, the DJ’s gonna play and…
how bout a… a free round on the house?
No! All-ages!
Oh juice! Of juice! Of juice. A free round of juice.
Hey! What are you doing?!
- Not playing.
- Why?!
Because playing to a bunch of mallrats who hate anything they can’t PoGo
to aint what Chris Keller’s about.
Really? That would have been really nice for you to tell me before I put you up on stage!
Also it would have been nice to know you talk about yourself in third person!
Okay, I get it; Curly’s pissed but look at it this way,
if I hadn’t done what I did, would she be up there right now?
Don’t think. Just play.
So… you’re saying you went through all this
just to get Haley up there to play?
Who knows? Chris Keller aint telling.
You did a really good thing for her Nate.
No, she did it all by herself.
Hi Brooke, I like your dress. Is it new?
Unfortunately, it’s discount.
Well it’s hard to believe. Cos you look…
beautiful.
Why can’t guys be more like you, Mouth?
I mean, you’re loyal… sweet…
and you bought my dollhouse back for me.
- It wasn’t that big a deal.
- Yes it was.
You know what you are? You are like…
a really great…
little brother.
- She’s really good.
- Yeah! She’s really great
I gotta bring my other boyfriends back to see her next time.
Alright!
Alright Haley!
Thank you.
Hey.
I’m sorry. I had no idea that was gonna happen.
And you don’t deserve any of it.
It’s cool. Don’t worry about it.
Are you sure?
What?
I just… wouldn’t mind seeing that picture again.
What they hell are you doing to Brooke?
One second.
Is there a problem?
- Brooke is back there, wasted and alone.
- So?
So why aren’t you doing something about it?
And don’t say you don’t care because you do.
Otherwise, why did you pay for the dollhouse?
Look, I don’t need you to understand any of it Mouth.
And the dollhouse is our secret.
Now if you don’t mind, I’m having a crummy night. Theresa’s about to change that.
Stop it Mouth!
Hey! You got a problem with my friend?
Maybe I got a problem with you.
Yeah, I think you do.
You’re lucky…
I’m not gonna do this in here.
That’s too bad.
Coz I am.
Felix! Stop it!
Stop it! Felix!
Get you damn hands off me!
Not until I get you outside.
Oh right, everyone here’s related. I get tossed cos you’re the guy’s uncle.
No, you get tossed because you’re an ass.
So did you have fun tonight, mom?
Sure, if you… don’t count the part where my son started punching people.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to ruin your night.
Yeah, well I didn’t mean to screw up your week.
Then again, without the use of your cell phone, MP3 player and the car…
it could suck for you.
Trade!
One week. Two, if you complain.
How’re you doing?
You should see the other guy.
Well I’ve got my mom’s car so… I’m gonna take off.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
But… thanks for punching Felix!
I’ve wanted to do that for years.
Anytime!
Call me tomorrow?
You tell me.
Call me tomorrow.
Alright, well I’m gonna go home mom.
And don’t worry, I’m going straight home.
Alright, no street fighting.
Right.
- Uhh… nice to meet you Andy.
- Yeah, yeah, you too.
So I guess that t-shirt I bought him is gonna fit a little snug.
Ohh, right, that.
Why didn’t you just tell me, Karen?
I mean you’re… you’re son’s a teenager. Why do you think that would matter?
Because it matters to me.
Andy, I like you…
but tonight, seeing you sitting there with Lucas, it just seemed so normal.
Like friends.
So?
Well… so that makes sense to me.
Look at us!
I mean, does this picture look right to you?
Yes. To me it does.
But I think the… the more important question is…
does it feel right?
- That feels good.
- Yeah. Yeah it does.
The rest doesn’t matter.
Good night.
- Good job!
- Thank you.
- You were great.
- We loved you.
Oh, thanks so much!
Predictable sappy ballad. How’s it feel?
Uh… great till ya just… dissed me!
No, look, you’ve got a good sound.
And watching you tonight, I can definitely see us doing something together.
Really?
Yeah, I never joke about music. Here’s my number. I got some studio time coming up.
Oh… wow okay.
Oh! I just remembered THUD Magazine wanted me to do a… interview with them.
- It’s probably gonna take a little while and...
- Nah, it’s cool.
- Okay.
- This is your night.
- Go, enjoy and I’ll see you at home.
- Are you sure?
Yeah, I gotta work early tomorrow anyway.
Okay. I love you. Thanks.
You have any idea how many guys in the room wanna nail your wife right now?
Good night, Brooke.
I love you.
Hey.
I was just checking on her.
She’s fine.
You like her, huh?
Yeah.
But guys like me don’t get girls like her and…
guys like you don’t care.
That’s not true.
Look man… I owe you an apology.
Friends?
Just treat her right.
Felix?
Hey girl.
You’re a mess.
You took care of me?
Yeah…
Sometimes you gotta break the rules.
So! How’d we do?
Well… it’s a little early for exact numbers but…
a few thousand nights like this and I think we can retire.
Ah, works for me!
Ah… Deb, I need to ask you a question.
Of course.
I mean, it’s stupid and considering the source, I shouldn’t even ask.
I mean, I probably don’t even have the right ask but...
Karen, we’re friends.
Right.
Yesterday, Dan told me that you slept with Keith.
Is it true?
No! Of course not!
Well… that date had everything.
Good conversation, dancing… fisticuffs.
Yeah, I’m sorry about that part.
So… I was thinking.
You called me your girlfriend tonight.
Yeah.
Well… if we were exclusive,
just you and me… would you be okay with that?
I’d be great with that.
Good. Me too.
So what do you say, boyfriend? Wanna sleep over?
Boy!
- So… hell of a night huh?
- Yes, I’m still shaking!
Thank you so much for everything! And I’m sorry about earlier.
No, dude, you totally redeemed yourself after indie-boy flaked on me!
- Ha! You wanna get outta here?
- Yes but, I gotta clear out some stragglers.
Hey! Relax, they’re cool.
In fact, Peyton and I did a couple lines the other night.
Aint that right Peyton?
What do you want, Felix?
You like my sister?
You know I do.
Too bad. Stay the hell away from her.
Is that an order?
No… it’s a warning!
Synchro : Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net