What’s up man?
Brooke?
It’s called ‘Dare Night’.
One night, two teams, multiple dares.
Each envelope contains a two-part dare.
Part one is on the front; part two is on the back.
Each dare is worth a certain number of points.
This cell phone has picture and video.
Oh sweet!
You do the dare; you send proof of it to the other team.
At midnight, time’s up.
We meet back here and declare the winner.
And what do we win?
You Mouth, win an excuse to be out till midnight.
The rest of you, get a night to remember.
And you get to humiliate us.
Why would we do that?
Look guys, there’s nothing in these envelopes that’s harmful to you or anyone else.
It’s all about having fun, testing your limits.
Every once in a while, you gotta wake yourself up.
You wanna do it Nate?
All anybody does in this town is brood and… pout, get married.
I’ll play.
Yeah, what the hell. I’m up for something daring.
Who else is in?
Come on! I wanna play. I didn’t get invited.
Tell you what; you can play if… Brooke and Lucas play.
- Pick the stupid teams.
- Alright.
Boys against the girls. You six guys against the three girls… plus me.
I count as three anyway.
Yeah, three girls!
Sweet. Teams are set.
- What’s this?
- That my friend…
is your first dare.
Return these clothes to stores in the mall.
What’s so hard about that?
While wearing them.
- Hello?
- You guys ready to forfeit yet?
You talk a big game little booty, but we about to light your ass; up.
Game on.
Alright. Nate you got your picture phone?
- Yeah.
- Beautiful. Skills.
I got one.
Alright boys, that game is to divide and conquer. Alright, I’ll catch up with you guys later.
If not, we meet at the café at midnight.
You really gonna do this dare?
Yeah.
You know why? Coz he doesn’t think I will.
Strong.
- Tim, you’re coming with me.
- I’m in it to win it.
Just say yes, Tim.
- Damn, he is good.
- But I’m better.
Catch you guys later.
Let’s do this.
Okay, hate to break up Charlie’s Angels but…
you guys take the Cingular phone and do these.
There’s nothing too crazy on there.
Why do I have to go with you?
Because this is your first dare.
Please! I could do that in my sleep.
Great! Prove it.
A little to the left.
You like ‘The Constantines’?
Sure.
I mean as much as anyone can like a band they’ve never heard of.
So… how’s it going? Um… is everything okay?
You’ve stopped in for coffee every morning this week and well I enjoy seeing you
it’s just, well I’m not sure it’s appropriate.
Well you know, in some cultures ah, you can buy coffee
without actually having to have sex with the café owner.
Um, you know, those cultures aren’t nearly as much fun for me but what you gonna do?
I have... I’ve jumped to conclusions.
I’m sorry.
Um… forget that I came by.
- Absolutely. Won’t mention it again.
- Thank you.
As long as you have dinner with me.
I’d like to return this shirt.
Oh, I happen to have the receipt. Here it is, yeah.
Can I ask you why you’d like to return it?
Um… wrong size?
Can’t we get you another size?
No, thanks, no I’m good.
I’m good.
Oh um… excuse me?
Would you mind taking a picture?
Thank you.
Smile!
Hi, can we have five pickled eggs please?
So I had an idea, why don’t we just get a picture of you eating one egg
and then tell them you ate five.
Haley James-Scott, we don’t cheat.
Well you did with Lucas.
Don’t make me smack you!
Here!
Thank you.
- Alright, are we doing this now?
- Here we go!
Do it, do it. Go go go.
Four and a half more to go!
Oh, make the five.
Mmmm. Not cheating tastes good.
Get that away from me you crazy...
Well this is it. Massage and Spa.
What’s the back say?
Ask for the special.
It’s the Happy Ending.
Okay, so all I have to do is get a table?
With no waiting. It’s the hottest restaurant in town.
If you insist on wasting my time, at least come up with better dares.
- Hi, I was wondering...
- Name?
- Brooke Davis.
- No.
You didn’t even check your list.
Perhaps there’s another name.
- Angelina Jolie.
- No.
- The Queen of Sheeba.
- The Queen of Hearts.
- No.
- How about Queen Latifah?
- I’m afraid not.
Table for two. Right this way sir.
How did you do that?
I made a reservation for two last week.
Come on team mate.
Can I… help you?
Forty-one thousand four hundred and sixty seven dollars.
Okay…
I know exactly what the dealer invoice on this car is.
MSRP, tax, freight. I don’t wanna haggle over scotch or… floor mats or anything.
Take it or leave it.
- And you’re sure you want this car?
- Absolutely.
Hmm. Well maybe you wanna test-drive it before you over-pay me.
Cameras, are you seeing this?
It says we have to get a hit on the fastest pitching machine.
Oh man, this all good, back up.
Using your head.
Well come on man, get in there. We aint got all day. Let’s go.
So what, you can’t get a date. Move to new towns and trick people into eating with you?
Wow, you totally exposed me.
Seriously, I mean mostly naked here.
How bout you? What’s your story?
Bored and ignored.
Bored maybe… but you never been ignored by a guy in your life.
I meant at home, genius.
Guys are easy. They usually fall for me over the first… pathetic… little… dinner.
Yeah?
What do they fall for first? The shoplifting or the eating disorder?
Excuse me!
Hi. Just curious; what’s your most expensive entrée?
Well, we have...
Sounds great. I’ll take two. I’m really hungry.
Nicely played. I’ll be right back.
Okay! Full body treatment.
The special. We want the special.
What exactly is the special?
Oh the special is very nice.
- Who’s first?
- Me.
Okay. I’ll just peel back your sheet.
Oh yeah!
So this is legitimate right? This is… like a massage?
Dude, shut up!
I am concentrating.
Yeah, you know what, I really don’t think I need to be here for this.
Oh… it won’t take long.
Yeah, I’ll bet.
Okay, one special! Full… body… wax!
I’m out!
Come on Mouth, toughen up dawg!
- It’s gonna hurt!
- So what? Be a warrior.
- Yeah, take one for the team Mouth.
- But what about you guys?
- Man, I’m takin the pictures.
- I’m helpin him.
Dang! Man I missed that one. You gonna have to do it again.
Come on, back on the plate.
Uh… I need to return some pants.
Okay... do you have them?
Hello?
You know, you shouldn’t be answering my phone.
Where the hell are you?
I’m at the café.
What?
Flip the dare card over, and read it.
You did not just leave me here!
Look, I don’t have the money to pay for this and I am not walking out on the cheque!
Why not? I’ve seen you steal before.
Besides, I dare ya.
Okay. Just stay put son.
Follow me! Hurry up!
Excuse me Miss! Your bill!
My car’s outside!
Trust me.
Ha, mission accomplished.
You want the locker key back?
No thanks! Look, I’m sorry about all of this.
I… just… dare night thing.
Just didn’t wanna back down.
Oh yeah. I saw you earlier and I figured it was something like that.
I didn’t want you to get busted for just having a little fun.
Thank you.
- So what’s your name?
- Anna.
I’m Lucas. You from Tree Hill?
Yeah, but… we… wouldn’t have met.
Why not?
Oh, I tend not to roll with guys in bras and leather pants.
You’re funny.
Oh sorry. Anyway, I owe you one.
Well… how bout you pay me back by letting me play too.
Okay.
So? What’s next?
Um… I don’t know. Lets find out.
Sell a box of cookies.
Great. I get my crack waxed and you get… cookies.
Felix left this for you.
You know, I really don’t like this Felix kid.
Good evening Mr and Mrs Tree Hill resident.
We’re selling these delicious cookies to raise money for ‘Lady Leprechauns’.
An organisation that empowers us girls to be strong, beautiful, independent women of tomorrow.
Screw this dare night crap! Can’t believe I’m wearing a skirt!
Yeah, in public.
When we get back to the café, I’m gonna beat on that kid. Felix!
I think he’s kinda cool.
You would.
I’m just saying. One week it’s Lucas, now it’s Felix.
Just tell me who we’re hatin on next week
Nate coz… I’m kinda having trouble keeping up.
Yeah well you wouldn’t have that problem if you got a life of your own and quit living mine.
Whatever!
Tim, I didn’t mean that. Wait up man.
Come on!
So, um… where was I?
You’re trying to force me to get the CD changer!
I wasn’t forcing you. It’s just an option I thought you might like.
There’s um… also the leather interior, the… optional touring package…
and option to pause at stop signs!
Okay, that wasn’t my fault. The thing just jumped out at me.
- The stop sign?
- It practically pounced!
Okay! Um… I think maybe I should drive us back.
No, I’ll be fine.
I just get a little nervous.
I only have so much money and this is a big decision for me.
Besides, car sales men are always such jerks.
Why are you smiling at me?
My brother owns the dealership, I’m just helping out. I’m actually a mechanic.
Oh. I like mechanics.
Oh, you are such a jerk!
Come on, it was just a dare.
You got us big points for that one. Lock it up!
You should be locked up!
Brooke, I’m sorry! Don’t go.
It was just part of the game. I promise.
I didn’t know you’d be so upset. Okay?
How bout you read the next one?
Go to the cemetery. Hm!
And take a photo in an open grave! That’s perfect.
Since I plane on killing you, anyway!
I think we get bonus points for that.
Great!
- Hey yo, Fergie, what’s the next dare?
- Karaoke.
- Mouth!
- I like big butts and I can not lie,
You other brothers can’t deny,
When a girls walks in with an itty bitty waist
And a round thing in your face
You get sprung!
Wanna pull up front
Cuz you notice that butt was stuffed
Okay, I got three dollars and… eighty cents!
Alright, we need five dollars.
Oh, a quarter!
Fellas
Has your girlfriend got the butt?
Well shake it,
Shake it,
Shake that healthy butt
Baby got back
Okay, hold on a second.
Oh, oh my gosh! Are you okay? It look... Oh! Ooh.
So ladies
Ladies
If you wanna role in my Mercedes
Then turn around
Stick it out
Even white boys got to shout
Baby got back!
Baby got back.
So this is dinner.
I want you to have anything you want. I’m rich you know.
Well I’m getting chilli on mine!
Thank you.
So… I know that my class is obviously the highlight of your week but what else do you like to do?
Mostly school and the café and my son.
You have a son? Nice.
Yeah.
Well he’s got a tough mom.
I think it’s so great that you went back to school in your late twenties you know.
Early thirties?
My god, how old are you?
Old enough to have never heard of that band, ‘The Constantines’.
Ah, but you see, now you’re one of the hip kids.
Hardly.
So I was thinking about what you said last week; about challenging yourself, moving forward.
Well I had a plan that I would open another business here in Tree Hill
and I discussed it with my business partner and… we decided to take the plunge.
Can I invest?
No!
But what would you say to some ice-cream?
Oh it’s fine but I’m not really made of money, Karen.
My treat.
Well I love ice-cream but… if you bought me ice-cream, you know, does this mean that…
You know, there are some cultures where you can actually have ice-cream-
- Yeah, I get it.
- Yeah.
How much do I owe you for the pizza?
Nothing.
I took a little extra from the fountain.
This is… weird. Isn’t it?
Oh I mean, people don’t just meet and hang out like this.
Unless it’s a hook-up.
- And it’s not?
- I didn’t think it was.
Besides, not doing that anymore.
Anymore?
Long story. Trust me.
Do you think two people can get to know each other…
without ever going into their long stories?
Sure.
But isn’t who you were a part of who you are?
Maybe,
but I guess I’m saying that; I don’t really need to know the person that you used to be.
As much… as the person that you’re trying to be.
Yeah…
me too.
- You ready for our next dare?
- Oh, yeah.
Do the honours.
Take a photo, with a stranger… in a photo booth.
Come on.
So. I have a confession to make.
The card doesn’t say take a photo with a stranger in a photo booth.
No?
No. It says… make out with a stranger in a photo booth.
Ah, here’s the thing...
Look, it’s just a dare, right? I mean… it’s no big deal.
There’s a part two right?
Ah; bonus points.
You’re gonna have to get out for this one.
Mm, enjoy.
Okay! What’s next?
You gonna tell what it was?
Maybe!
Okay, so I’m kinda thinking that… maybe we don’t really need these points so much.
- Come on! I’ll protect you.
- Yeah, that’s exactly what I’m counting on.
Well maybe you prefer Lucas.
What did Mouth tell you?!
Nothing. We move around a lot, school cliques are easy to read;
who rolls with who, that kinda thing.
You and Lucas obviously had something.
Yeah we had something.
We had something fake and painful that I’m not gonna discuss
with you and a bunch of dead people.
What about you anyway? I can’t imagine anyone would actually date you.
The question is; why would I date them? When I could just hook up with them instead.
You know, friends with benefits.
No strings attached.
I don’t think that works. Somebody always ends up getting hurt.
Not if you’re upfront about it.
Think about it; you had sex this year, and so did I...
but I didn’t end up in a cemetery talking about how painful it was.
Oh perfect!
This one will do.
In you go.
Oh no! You haven’t done anything tonight. Why do I have to go?
I gotta work the camera phone.
Besides, you wouldn’t be able to pull me out.
I really don’t like you.
Okay.
Be careful.
Okay. See you later.
Felix, don't you dare leave me here!
I’m just playing.
Hold on. Let me get a picture.
What’re you doing!?
Stop it!
Yo man, this dare is totally screwed up, dawg.
Borrow a wild animal for the zoo?
It’s like that movie where they try to steal the cougar but…
- But what?
- Cougar ate their ass didn’t it?
Sort of.
Mouth man, I said a bird man. We in a damn snake house!
Man, I’m not stealin no snake, dawg.
Nothing with teeth, fangs or claws. Man forget it!
I guess we could try for a fish.
Uh-uh. Too slimy.
Look, I got a problem with animals okay? I’ve never had a pet.
I bet you Felix knows that too. I mean that dude is psychotic.
- Psychic.
- Yeah, dat too.
Okay, I think they’re gone. Gimme a boost.
Are you kidding? Your shoes are muddy.
It’s either you give me a boost or be buried alive girly girl.
Fine!
Okay. Get me out.
Stupid dare night. Where did you come up with this ridiculousness anyway?
I mean, what is the point!?
The point is simple;
see how far you’ll go. You face your fears.
And sometimes you’ll do things you wanna do because calling it a dare makes it okay for a night.
Things like what?
Like spending time with me.
So we never really talked about the wedding. Like… how you got there.
I told you; I got dressed, I… threw up at my parent’s house,
brushed, flossed and… went to the beach.
Okay, hard image to forget. But, I meant more like...
I don’t know; how your heart got there. Marriage is big.
I don’t know how you trust somebody for your whole life.
I can’t even… date somebody with that escape hatch.
I don’t know if it was so much about trusting Nathan - which I do - it was…
more about trusting myself.
Yeah, my old friend; self doubt.
I dunno, sometimes everything seem… really simple
- and then...
- It’s not?
Yeah.
Alright, so what does this card say again?
We’re supposed to… go to the confessional and read whatever’s on the card
except you’re not supposed to read it until we get in there.
Right, right, right. So… okay, so here’s the deal;
I’m actually trying to avoid eternal damnation…
so… I’m gonna pass.
Alright. Give it.
Bless me father for I have sinned.
You see, lately I’ve been having impure thoughts about…
Um… actually, I haven’t been doing very well lately.
This is… the first time I’ve been in a church since my mom died.
I think about her every day!
I just… I wonder what she would say to me right now if she could see me
and see how I’ve been living.
And I wonder if she knows
and most days, I fall short of being the person that she wanted me to be.
Or…
I wonder if she saw me do that line of coke last week!
And the thing is… I don’t even know why I did it.
You know, my life is pretty good, it is.
But… I was just searching for something to make it great.
Something to make it matter so…
I don’t know, I guess last week when I had the chance to change that
and it was… it was right there in front of me,
I guess I was just scared to let that go.
But I know it was wrong.
And I want my mom to know that and…
I want her to know that I am not that person.
And I’m not going to be.
I’m sure she knows.
Tim, wait up!
I said I was sorry. I didn’t mean to tear you down!
Then why did you?
Because I was pissed at Felix alright? And you were defending him.
- I just don’t like him flirting with Haley.
- It’s always about Haley.
No it’s not always about her. Tim, what do you want me to say? She’s my wife now.
You know, we used to be tight! It was always you and me.
Now you’re constantly with Haley or Lucas,
and there’s never any time for us to hang out.
Don’t you miss your ‘Tim Time’?
Do I miss hanging out with you? Yes.
Do I miss you saying things like ‘Tim Time’? No.
Look, Tim, I know a lot of things have changed but us being friends isn’t one of them.
We’ve been boys a long time now. I wouldn’t trade that for anything.
Especially now that everything’s so crazy. Alright?
- Can we at least finish ‘Dare Night’?
- Yeah absolutely.
Good. Coz this next one’s great.
Well I’d, uh, point out the safety features but I think that fact that...
you know, we got back in one piece speaks for itself.
Look Jules; you picked a good car.
But… the price you offered me was a grand too high and I couldn’t take a penny more.
- Is this some new car selling trick?
- How would I know? I’m just a mechanic.
How bout if I think about it?
Was my counter offer too low?
No, I just figured that if I wait a few days, then you’ll have to call me.
You have my number.
Eternal damnation for you?
I think jury’s still out on that one.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thanks for hanging out with me tonight Haley.
You’re a good friend.
Thanks.
This was fun.
I’m glad we did this. I needed a night like ‘Dare Night’.
Yeah, me too.
Steal the Tiki God from the second hole right?
Here, check out part two.
Get it? Dude, the hole’s number two!
There is something wrong with you. You know that right?
What? I didn’t write the dare card.
Dude, hand me the camera and give me some leaves alright?
Thanks for hanging out tonight.
Well thank you.
Well… I better get going.
I’ve got a business class in the morning and my teacher is a tyrant.
Yeah, I heard about that guy.
Karen,
I think you’re doing a great thing; going after you new club.
It’s a ‘Loosen up your collar’, ‘Run like a river’, ‘Glow like a beacon fire’.
- Constantines?
- Oh, see how cool you are?
Um Andy, what I said earlier…
I did misread the café visit, right?
Absolutely not.
I’ll see you in class, Miss Roe.
So, it’s almost midnight. The dares are done, we should head back.
Actually, I can’t.
I need to take off.
You know, I had this… weird history of meeting girls
and them… disappearing at the end of the night.
You sure you can’t meet my friends?
Not tonight.
But how about… you give me your number?
Can I have yours too?
Luke, it was just ‘Dare Night’, right?
No bonus points for you.
Anna?
I dare you to call me.
The guys trail by a hundred and fifty points.
Yes!
We’re here.
What is that?
We had to capture a wild animal from the zoo.
Yeah, you might wanna back up. This thing is kinda ferocious.
Go ahead and laugh, but you shoulda seen this thing before we tamed it.
I’m telling you, it was vicious. I mean it was snapping and…
Oh man!
Well, well. With your other dares, it appears to be a tie.
Oh no, no. Wait, don’t forget this.
Dude! What the hell are you doing?!
It says it right here on the dare card.
Man, that’s a typo. It’s supposed to say take a shot on the second hole.
Tim!
Gross!
No dice. It’s still a tie and I just happen to have a tie breaker.
Kiss a team mate on the mouth.
Well I guess you guys win.
Damn it!
Convenient!
Okay.
Sorry!
Okay! Alright.
Unless any of you guys… kissed a stranger in a photo booth…
that’s the only dare you didn’t do.
Anybody?
Sorry guys. Guess they win.
You know Skills, you could always keep him. He could be your first pet.
Man, I’m not bout to keep some creepy looking turtle, dawg.
Besides, caged up aint living. He need to be free.
There you go.
You realise that was a saltwater turtle, right?
- Hey, did you have fun tonight?
- Eventually, missed you though.
I guess I’ll see you later then.
Tim. How about a game of NBA Live?
Alright.
You see, the ‘Tim’ is on the house and you better recognise...
Just say you’re gonna beat me, Tim.
Admit it; you had a good time tonight.
By a good time, you mean wasting an entire evening of my life that I can never get back?
Then sure.
I have a question for you.
You said you read people and that’s how you knew to invite all of us tonight.
So how’d you read me?
I don’t know about you yet.
Gonna have to watch you a little more.
So I guess this night makes us friends! Right?
Maybe.
Friends with benefits?
I’ll think about it.
How was the mall?
You don’t know?
How would I?
Fine. So, what’d you do tonight?
Not much. Just explored really.
Trying to figure this place out.
I think we’re gonna like it here, Felix.
Yeah.
Me too.
Okay. Goodnight, little sister.
Hey. How was your night?
Was good!
Yours?
It was good.
Hey, do you have a CD by The Constantines?
Yeah. Uhh…
Here we go.
It’s very hip, mom.
Thanks. I thought I’d try something daring.
Synchro : Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net