=:= Bite My Shiny Metal Ass Team =:=
And now...
The transcredible exploits
of Zapp Brannigan
brought to you
by Bartley's Rocket Wax.
I wax my rocket every day.
No one can save you now, Leela.
What about Zapp Brannigan?
Well, obviously, Zapp Brannigan
could save you, but...
So, Emperor Chopchop,
once again, we meet at last.
Drop that space gun
or I'll shoot... like so.
Tie me back up and ravish me.
I'd like to, Leela, so I will.
Shake it, baby.
Shake it like...
I surrender
and volunteer for treason.
Emergency summons
from the president, Captain.
Oh, it's you.
Just let me freshen up.
Computer, captain's musk.
The long, dramatic corridor.
That's never a good sign.
Glove recognized.
Proceed, Mrs. Eisenhower.
Mr. President.
What the hell?
At ease, Brannigan.
What you're about to see
is highly classified.
Reptilicus, hit the thingy.
At oh-zero-hundred hours,
Planet X-3 was attacked
by a mysterious Death-Sphere.
Magnify that Death-Sphere.
- Why is it still blurry?
- That's all the resolution we have.
Making it bigger
doesn't make it clearer.
It does on CSI: Miami.
They fought back
with advanced military hardware,
but it was like shooting
BBs at Bebe Rebozo.
That poor, brave hardware.
The Sphere then fired
some kind of hellish blackout ray.
Erased that planet
like 18 minutes of incriminating tape.
I just wish I understood why.
Why I should care.
Because the Death-Sphere
is now on course for Earth.
My God, we're defenseless,
like fish in a barrel.
- Options?
- My instinct is to hide in this barrel
like the wily fish.
Then we're down to our last hope:
a radical new weapon
built by a visionary scientist
I once dismissed as crazy.
Let's see how crazy I am now, Nixon.
The correct answer is "very."
All right, Professor,
sock it to me.
Top secret news, everyone.
I've developed a tiny,
one-man stealth fighter
that's virtually undetectable.
How undetectable?
It's in front of you.
I find that...
to believe.
But how exactly is this Happy Meal toy
going to destroy a giant Death-Sphere?
From within.
This ship should be able
to sneak, undetected,
through the Sphere's
one vulnerable opening.
What vulnerable opening?
All Death-Spheres
have one vulnerable opening.
Well, sure, but who's brave
enough to fly into something
we all keep calling a Death-Sphere?
- I say Brannigan.
- I say no.
- I say me.
- I say Leela.
- I say yes.
- I say no.
I say Leela, too.
I say yes again.
I say I shall join her.
But it's only a one-man craft.
I say.
There'll only be one man... me.
How would you feel if I rode rear
as your personal tail gunner?
Creeped out.
Then it's decided.
I have to sit in your lap?
It'll help us achieve
maximum thrust.
I made you some trail mix
for the flight.
Also, this picture, to remember me.
You hold onto it.
I'll be back soon.
Activating stealth shielding.
- Liftoff!
- I'll roger that.
Does anybody else feel aroused
and jealous and worried?
I haven't felt much of anything
since my guinea pig died.
Death-Sphere in range.
Engaging holographic targeting.
Activating the Force.
Feel the entrance, Leela.
Destination on your left
in 0.3 miles.
Zapp to Leela.
Look at all that surveillance equipment.
We better whisper.
Switching to pillow talk mode.
Look! What are those huge letters?
V- GINY?
Doesn't ring a bell.
I don't like
the looks of this V-GINY.
Does anyone recognize
those call letters?
Nope.
It's not in the Janeway's Guide.
Deciphering that I.D. code
is critical.
I'll be
in the Chamber of Understanding.
This is it... the moment
we should have trained for.
Holy cr...
Incoming yucky.
Firing pocket-rocket!
Don't panic, Leela.
Go, go.
I hope this is the control stick.
Captain's log. We've lost control.
Addendum...
And now back to...
The transcredible exploits
of Zapp Brannigan
Chapter Two: "The Heat Thickens".
Leela, wake up.
I can't face
this mysterious planet alone
without you or someone like you.
Zapp, wake up.
- Where are we?
- We crashed on an uncharted planet.
When I woke up,
I was pinned under this tree.
Help me!
If anyone can move it, I can.
No one can move it.
Are you hurt?
No, but I'm so thirsty.
This space suit is making me
sweat like a sow.
Me, too.
We'd better strip them off
and continue surving au naturel.
I suppose so.
Here, we can cover ourselves
with these sticky, sap-covered leaves.
I'll try to avert my eyes
from your nudery.
You will?
What's the point?
You'll have to look sooner or later.
Well, I promise
not to abuse the privilege.
For now I'd better scout around
for food and water and help.
What a thoughtful
and considerate thing to say.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not quite sure.
Perhaps it's the fresh air
or a severe head injury.
In any case, I'm off.
If you see any steaks,
that'd be good!
Why isn't Leela back yet?
- Do you think she's okay?
- How should I know?
And how come you never ask
if I'm okay?
I'm feeling a little neglected here.
- Are you okay, Bender?
- Shut up.
What difference does it make?
When that Death- Sphere gets here,
we'll all be blown to Manwich meat.
Well, I guess it's time to indulge
in some end-of-the-world debauchery.
Who's up for an orgy?
Maybe a Parcheesi tournament.
Belay that Parcheesi tournament.
I've identified the Death-Sphere.
We may yet have
a faint hope of survival.
Still, a Parcheesi tournament.
This is a top secret
military satellite
launched by the air force in 1998.
And this is a top
secret FCC satellite
launched that same year
to censor indecent TV programs.
Like The Pimpsons and Ass-o-rama?
Precisely.
However, the satellites collided
shortly after launch
and were never heard from again.
I found the board!
Now I've simulated that collision
using Shrapnel-vision.
Granted, all that makes
perfect sense.
But why is this Death-Sphere
destroying planets?
That makes the most sense of all.
Look at the planets
it's destroyed so far.
First came X-3
the nude beach planet,
then Poopiter,
and finally that world
that can't be mentioned
in polite company.
You mean...
How dare you.
So the Death-Sphere
is "censoring" indecent planets?
Indeed, and we're next,
if we can't keep it
in our collective pants.
Our sole hope
is to persuade the people of Earth
to abandon their smutty ways.
So the orgy's off?
So thirsty.
Why couldn't a water fountain
have fallen on me?
I couldn't find any water, but
the moisture in these fruit-nut-berries
should sustain you.
I climbed perilously high
into the trees to pick them,
yet I saw no sign
of intelligent life.
Bummer.
Moreover, the crash
totally destroyed our ship.
So we're stuck here
until someone finds us?
Alas, that may never happen.
Stealth technology
makes the ship impossible to locate,
yet easy to stub your crotch on.
Well, there's worse places
to be marooned.
Plenty of food, mild climate.
It's a veritable Garden of Eden.
It is?
Did that snake say hello?
No. We're both delirious
from dehydration.
Just like Adam and Eve.
We can still save Earth.
People are sure
to clean up their act
when presented with cold, hard facts
by rational folks like us.
The end is near!
Repent thy sins!
I'll thinks it overs
while I engages
this five-dollar hooker.
Don't do it!
It's not worth it!
Okay, make it three dollars.
I don't wants
no three-dollar hooker.
I'm going backs
to the adults bookstore.
Adult bookstore?
I thought this was the public library.
Pubic library.
Where are you?
God, I'm actually
starting to miss him.
Maybe you two belong together.
We do not.
And you can't talk.
Come on.
It must be an awful temptation.
Guess who just killed a
woodchuck with his bare feet?
I thought I'd whip
us up some shelter.
Make this a little more like home.
I do miss the Earth terribly.
I wonder if it's even still there?
Let's find out together.
I'll brave
the ship's wreckage to
fetch you the telescope.
That's so sweet.
I'm just sayin', is all.
I know my new plan is a long shot,
but it's the only hope left.
Well, now I've heard everything.
On my iPod.
So, do you have a new plan, Professor?
And is there any hope left?
Indeed. We're here on
Earth's last unspoiled acre
to show the Death-Sphere
there's still purity in the world.
Begin transmitting.
Commence purity chant.
I'm proud of you, Bender...
avoiding sin for almost a full minute.
Yeah, baby, you're quite a dish.
Quiet your riot.
What's the worst that could happen?
Earth is gone!
We're the only two humans
left in the universe!
Oh, God, I'm sorry, Leela.
Maybe this was meant to be.
Maybe you and I were meant
to build a new world here.
We can avoid humanity's mistakes.
Like the tuba.
We'll be like Adam and Eve.
Only without the tuba.
And we'll beget little Zapp Junior.
And Leela Junior.
And they'll have kids of their own.
Yuck! Is that really
what happened in the Bible?
It's a sick and twisted book
of holiness, all right.
Then we'll write our own bible.
With less Sodom and more Gomorrah.
Let's do it.
I shall become
the mother of a new world,
trapped here, under this tree.
The Tree of Knowledge.
Look, it even has apples!
Come here, Adam.
Partake of my forbidden fruit.
Thee will be done.
Wait. One more bite
before we begin the begetting.
Juicy.
Those nut-berries
you found were so salty,
I couldn't think straight.
I mean, not to belabor it,
but they were as salty
as that bag of trail mix
Fry gave me.
Exactly as salty.
Wait a second!
I have a terrible
confession to make.
You see, when I first went foraging,
what I actually found was the smoldering
wreckage of the ship.
Ignoring all danger, I charged
inside to liberate our provisions.
So thisisthe trail mix Fry gave me!
I exaggerated when I said
I picked it from the treetops.
I just wanted you to think...
a little better of me.
Your motives were good.
And we were both loopy
from dehydration.
Wait.
You've been doing
an awful lot of urinating.
There's plenty of water.
You see, after I selflessly
rescued the trail mix,
I braved the flames once more,
in search of fluids.
Why didn't you give me any?
I thought it might help you forget
your intense hatred for me if
you were a teensy bit delirious.
So you let me dehydrate
while you washed down the trail mix
with imported mineral water?
Not exactly.
You see, besides the trail mix,
the minibar also contained
Doritos, beef jerky,
and an assortment
of fine chocolates.
I wanted to offer you
the chocolates.
I truly did... but I was
concerned about your waistline.
Very concerned.
It's because
I haven't been exercising.
If only this tree
hadn't fallen on me by chance.
Oh, dear God!
It was just after we crashed.
I awoke first, to find you trapped.
Wake up.
You could've moved
this grub-infested log
any time you wanted?
Well, sure...
but then I wouldn't have been able
to provide the loving care
you wouldn't have needed.
I'd leave you to rot
in this paradise,
if only the ship weren't destroyed.
The ship's fully functional,
isn't it?
You see, after re-trapping you
and before feigning unconsciousness,
I paused to enjoy a cigar.
Though mellow and satisfying,
it did parch me a bit,
so I went in search of brandy.
That's when my keen senses
detected the still-invisible ship.
So we can go back to Earth?
But there is no Earth anymore!
Everyone I know is dead!
This seems like a good place
to take a dump.
You're alive!
But how did you find this planet?
Well?
We're actually on Earth.
The ship's homing device
brought us back.
But I saw Earth explode.
I'm actually
kind of proud of this one.
You see, what you saw
was merely a simulation I rigged up,
using the ship's holographic
targeting projector.
The alleged "telescope"
was a toilet paper tube.
You said there wasn't
any toilet paper!
And that humanity was annihilated!
My motives were pure.
I just wanted to you to think
we had to save humanity
so you'd be willing to have sex.
Please say you believe me.
Yes, I believe you.
There must be something
to steal on this island.
It's Leela.
Let's go home, everybody.
At least the world wasn't destroyed.
Yet.
People of Earth!
Hear the righteous word
of the mighty V-GINY!
The mighty V-GINY!
Seeing you frolic
in this unspoiled garden
gives hope that this world
may yet be redeemed.
Huzzah!
The purity chant worked!
Unacceptable wardrobe malfunction!
I was referring to Adam and Eve!
We're not Adam and Eve.
You see, due to a series of...
Consummate your union,
or I shall destroy Earth.
If it's to save Earth...
I guess I could take one
for the team.
What? Right now?!
But I need a romance first.
Maybe a vanilla candle or something?
Commence intercourse!
Those giant guns
are making me feel sort of inadequate.
- I'm not sure if I can...
- Move it.
I gotta get home and do laundry.
For God's sake, censor it!
Censor it!
Approved for all audiences!
And now, the spicy finale of...
The transcredible exploits
of Zapp Brannigan
That was a close call,
but we saved Earth.
Was it as good for you
as it was for the human race?
Let's save another planet right now!