In November 2009,
Uncle Marshall and Aunt Lily
hosted the first Thanksgiving.
Marshall had found
the perfect turkey.
Baby, it is beautiful.
It's 22 pounds.
It's organic.
Remember my bald Uncle Heinrek?
It looks exactly like his head.
My turkey...
So, when we showed up for the big day,
Marshall was pretty bummed out.
Well, we got the turkey.
You didn't.
You got the pathetic replacement turkey.
Damn it, why didn't I listen
to the precorded voice
of former mayor Ed Koch
reminding me to take my belongings?
- You don't understand.
- We went to the port authority,
and there,
sitting in their fridge...
Is this your turkey?
That's my turkey!
Come here,
you handsome little bastard!
I'm gonna go put this in the oven.
You are the best friends ever!
It was totally a team effort.
I don't know what to say.
It's Thanksgiving,
but thanks doesn't seem like enough.
You would've done
the same thing for us.
I would, and you know why?
Because I love you.
I'm going to show you just how much.
I bequeath unto you
the fourth slap.
What?
Kids, you remember
Barney and Marshall's "slap bet".
When Barney lost, Marshall won the right
to slap Barney five times
as hard as he could.
So far, he'd used three slaps.
With the third being doled out
exactly two years earlier
on Thanksgiving day 2007.
A day that history came to know
as "Slapsgiving".
- Are you saying...
- What we think you're saying?
Probably not.
Unless you think I'm saying
"Slapsgiving two:
revenge of the slap",
in which case, yes,
that's exactly what I'm saying!
No way!
- Slaps aren't transferable.
- Lily is the slap bet commissioner.
Slaps are transferable.
You realize you'll only have
one left after this.
Are you sure
you want to spend this slap today?
Life is short.
I figured, Slap-e Diem.
Rule number one:
the slap must occur before sundown,
so as not to interfere
with Lily's meal.
Two, you have to decide
who gets to do it.
Three...
We're going to tie barney to this chair,
which shall henceforth be referred
to as the slapping throne.
Sound fair?
- Totally.
- Absolutely not!
It was all set to be
the best Thanksgiving ever.
Until...
Are we expecting somebody else?
It was someone Lily hadn't seen
or spoken to in three years.
Dad.
Synchro : -Titou-
.:: La Fabrique ::.
Now, Lily and her dad, Mickey,
had always had a tough relationship.
Mickey's dream was to invent
the next great American board game.
But his ideas were a little off.
Daddy?
You missed my ballet recital.
Yes, but, look!
I just put the finishing touches
on my new, hit board game,
"Tijuana Slumlord".
You missed my gymnastics meet.
But this is the one!
"Car Battery:
"how long can you hold on?"
Grab these.
I had a nightmare.
Here, come play daddy's new game:
"There's a clown demon
under the bed!"
Her whole life,
Mickey disappointed Lily.
And she put up with it,
until one day in 2006
when Lily went to visit
her grandparents.
So, Rita, are you excited
about the big move to Florida?
Actually, slight change of plans.
We're staying here
for the time being.
We had a slight financial hiccup.
The straw to my juice box broke!
- What a pleasant surprise.
- What happened to your apartment?
I had a little falling out
with my roommate.
- What happened?
- He wanted me to pay rent.
Got kind of ugly.
You should be paying rent,
not living in your parents' basement.
It's not my first choice.
Having the old farts right upstairs
is crimpin' my style a bit.
Clearly, they're not getting
the whole "sock on the doorknob" thing.
- They caught you with a girl?
- In a way.
I'm off to work.
- You're retired.
- Now I have an extra mouth to feed,
I had to go back to the steel mill.
Where's my truss?
So, not only did you stop them
from moving to Florida,
but now you forced Grandpa
to go back to work?
Just until I get Aldrin Games
unlimited off the ground
with my new sensation:
"Dog Fight Promoter".
Lily gave her dad a look that Marshall
had only seen a few times before.
A look we all prayed never to be
on the receiving end of:
her "you're dead to me" look.
Which brings us
back to Thanksgiving of 2009.
I brought "Diseases"!
- Why is he here?
- Dunno.
But we should let him in
and find out.
No, I don't want to see him!
Get rid of him!
Just hang tight, okay?
We'll, we'll work this out.
Take your time, amigo.
I'm okay as long as I have "diseases"!
The fun's infectious.
- God, I hope Lily's okay.
- Me, too.
She doesn't talk about it much,
but this thing causes her a lot of pain.
Just tell me which one of you
is gonna slap me!
- What?
- I'm dying over here!
Ted reaches for a chip, I flinch!
Robin fixes her hair, I flinch!
I'm doing so much flinching.
It's bad for my skin.
I'm getting crow's feet.
Crow's feet!
Lily, it's been three years, okay?
That's long enough.
Having him in my life
causes me nothing but stress.
It's just easier for him
to be dead to me.
I supported you when our neighbor,
Mr. Ossias, was "dead to you".
- That's our newspaper.
- You'll get it back in 15 minutes.
Make it 20.
I had a steak last night.
And I was fine when your bridesmaid,
Whitney, was "dead to you".
You look so amazing!
That dress is gorgeous!
Thanks, guys.
I'm just not a fan of strapless.
I even understood when Mr. Park
was "dead to you."
One coffee, please.
But only if you have decaf.
I don't want to be up all night.
Dollar fifty.
- Coffee, regular.
- Dollar fifty.
Excuse me.
Are you sure mine was decaf?
You just used the same pot.
I lie to him. Okay?
You son of a bitch.
That was not decaf!
I supported you
with all of those random people,
but this is your father.
Can't we at least
just give him some turkey?
Come on.
Please, I can't ask the guy
to leave on Thanksgiving.
You don't have to ask.
Just tell him that it's really important
that he be here.
And before you know it,
he'll be at a game convention in Toledo,
giving your braces money to some guy
claiming to be Milton Bradley.
He was just out
trying to provide for the family.
No, that's what my mom did
by working two jobs.
That man broke my heart
every single day for 20 years.
Well, then we'll just give him
some dark meat.
No, seriously, Robin,
you should get the slap.
You're a great slapper.
In fact, I want to study slapping
under your tutelage.
I want to be your slap-prentice.
Don't sell yourself short there.
You're a slapping rock star.
Your name should be Eric Slapton.
This is torture.
Just put me in the chair...
- Slapping throne.
- And get it over with!
- He's all yours.
- It's you, I insist.
- Okay, I'll do it.
- Wait, what?
I'll slap him.
What, so that's just, like,
the end of the discussion?
You said I could slap him.
I was just being nice.
If anyone's gonna slap him,
it's gonna be me.
No, it's not.
This is interesting.
Lily, he's family, okay?
And I'm sorry,
but you just don't cut off family.
That's easy for you to say
when you come from the most
ridiculously close family in the world.
We are not ridiculously close.
Really?
What about the Eriksen family dinner
every single sunday?
Everything looks delicious,
Mother Eriksen.
Thank you, Papa Oear.
Would you say grace?
Well, I would be happy to, mother.
Everyone, please join hands.
Dear Lord...
I'm sorry, but that's weird.
A family should be that close.
I want our future family to be close.
And that includes your dad.
I can't believe
you're taking his side.
Let me be clear on this.
That man will never cross
the threshold into this home, ever!
It's just gonna be,
like, five more minutes.
Hopefully soon, amigo.
I'm fighting a losing battle
with hemorrhoids here.
That's one of the diseases?
Ted, there is an hour
before the sun sets,
at which point,
neither one gets to slap Barney.
So just let me have it.
I had the idea to call
the port authority lost and found.
That's a good point.
Rebuttal?
- I'm the one who slipped the guy a 20!
- Philosophical conundrum.
Idea versus execution.
Please discuss at length.
I carried that huge turkey
all the way up here.
I paid for cab fare.
You slept
with one of my best friends!
What?
- You said you were okay with that.
- I'm not!
Why didn't you say
something at the time?
Because I'm still in love with you!
Do you really want
to slap Barney so bad
you would lie
about being in love with me?
I really want to slap him!
Your dad has made
some mistakes in the past,
but he's a different person now.
He's out of your grandparents' house.
He's got a job.
He's paying off his IRS debts.
How do you know all that?
Body language.
We met for a drink last week.
I miss her a ton.
Little princess.
She ever talk about me?
Like, all the time.
She tells
this one really sweet story about...
- So never?
- Not a word.
But...
It doesn't have to be that way.
We can fix this, right?
You know, I always thought
it'd get fixed at the wedding.
I even wrote a toast.
But then, no invite.
Hell, I haven't even seen
a wedding photo.
And then, right before my eyes,
your father broke down crying.
That's it!
You're coming to Thanksgiving!
You invited him?
The guy was, like, blubbering.
What was I going to do?
Then, some jerk at the next table
called him a sissy
which I thought
was totally uncalled-for.
I can't believe you.
What gives you the right to do that?
You and I are married.
And that means he's my family, too.
Ted, you better roll quickly.
Your gall bladder's about to burst.
Mickey, it's been half an hour.
I think we should go look for Lily.
She just needs some time to cool down.
Let's finish the game.
Play another round.
Best of seven!
Damn it, Robin!
I've known Barney the longest.
I get to slap him.
That slap is mine, Mosby.
I've never slapped Barney...
above the waist.
I've wanted to slap Barney
since the moment I met him!
You don't think
that I want to slap Barney?
Wait a minute!
This slap was supposed to be
a wonderful thing, a gift,
and...
it's turned us against each other.
My God, you're right.
This once pure fruit has turned
into a poison slapple.
You know what?
Seriously, you take it.
Are you sure?
Slapsolutely.
I really think
that we should go look for Lily.
Gall bladder about to pop.
It's decided. Barney, come on.
Get in the throne.
Are you...
Come on.
Well, I guess that is the...
best decision, Robin.
I mean...
Men are stronger than women.
Don't listen to him.
It's been decided.
And that's what
you've always wanted, isn't it?
A strong man to take care of you?
I mean, sure.
Growing up, you were a scrapper.
Playing hockey with the boys,
skinning your knees on the ice.
But what you couldn't tell
your teammates...
What you couldn't
even tell yourself...
was that all you really wanted...
was that pretty white dress...
in that pretty white chapel.
And at the end of that center aisle,
strewn with pretty white flowers,
a man to do
all your slapping for you.
Let me at him!
- What just happened?
- Sorry, Ted.
Gallbladder burst.
You move back three spaces.
You come in here,
and you watch your daughter leave,
and you don't even care.
And now
you've destroyed Thanksgiving dinner!
Lily worked all day on this!
Relax. It's not real bile.
It's just lead-based paint
from China.
And horse bile.
And at that moment,
Marshall gave Mickey a look
none of us had ever seen him
give anyone.
- What's this? What's he doing?
- Did you swallow some of that paint?
This is my "you're dead to me" look.
Lily's is so much better...
Get out of my house!
Mr. Park's? This is the last place
I expected to find you.
I'm sorry.
But just hear me out.
I used to think
that family was a right.
But it's not. It's a privilege,
and it has to be earned.
I kicked your dad out.
And I promise, baby,
I will never make you see him again.
What?
Baby, what happened?
Marshall,
I came in here because it was cold
and this was the only place
that was open.
I wasn't even gonna look Mr. Park
in the eye.
And then I found out...
Mr. Park died.
He really is dead to me!
And if I feel this bad
about never making up with Mr. Park,
a guy who meant
literally nothing to me...
We got to go get my dad.
So that's how on Thanksgiving 2009,
your aunt Lily performed a miracle.
She brought a man
back from the dead.
Everyone.
Before we get started, Barney,
we're going to need you
on the slapping throne.
Slap bet commissioner, surely tying me
to a chair is a breach...
Less yappin', more slappin'.
Ted, Robin.
It's two minutes until sundown.
Have you decided which one of you
is going to get
to slap Barney right in his face?
It's gonna be Ted.
What? Why me?
Last year,
you got left at the altar.
You lost your job.
But you've come
such a long way since then.
I'm so proud of you, Ted.
You deserve
to slap someone in his face,
as hard as you can.
Thanks.
This is the worst.
Mama!
You went through
your breakup, and...
While I know you and Barney
left it on good terms, isn't there...
some part of you, deep down,
that wants to slap him
right in his face?
There is.
I know there is.
This is basically hell on earth.
All right.
It hurts!
I can't do it.
I can't take this from you, Ted.
No or I, you.
Thank God.
So, I'd like to make a gesture.
No way!
I'm glad you and Lily
are trying to work things out.
So, to welcome you
to our little family...
I'd like to offer you this slap.
Really?
Well, I feel a little weird.
I just met barney,
and I don't have anything
against the guy, but...
how often do you get a chance
to slap someone right in his face?
Soft!
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Thank God.
Lily...
I haven't been much
of a father to you.
You are kidding me.
So for all the ballet recitals
I missed,
for all the art shows
that I should've been at...
for the wedding gift
I never got a chance to give to you...
Princess...
I give this slap...
to you.
She is the slap bet commissioner.
She's supposed to remain impartial!
Slap bet commissioner says
it's okay.
This is not good.
Please.
Let me...
Just close your eyes.
It'll be over soon.
Running through a meadow.
I can't do it.
Why can't I do it?
Because...
this slap has done
exactly what I hoped.
It's brought us all closer together.
And it's caused us to recognize
both the frailty and the greatness
in ourselves
and each other.
Give me a break.
And that is why...
There will be no slap today.
This is the best Thanksgiving...
That's four!
So, turkey?
From Aldrin games unlimited, it's...
Slap Bet!
The slap-happy game
that's a real hit.
You just got slapped,
across the face, my friend...
For kids of all ages.
You just got slapped,
that really just happened...
Everybody saw it,
everybody laughed and clapped,
- 'cause it was awesome...
- I win!
The way that you just got slapped.
Slap yourself silly with Slap Bet,
the happy hitting game from Aldrin.