It was the Fall of 2009
and I was a professor now.
So I decided to change
my look a little bit.
And people were noticing.
Tweed.
Textile of the eunuch.
I've always wondered why those
tweed jackets have elbow patches.
Because the people who wear them
are constantly going,
"Geez. Why can I get laid?"
You are wrong.
The ladies dig the professor look.
There is something to that.
I remember thinking my tenth grade
math teacher was very sexy.
I wonder if Harold's still in jail.
What?
Tax evasion.
Among other things.
So guys, Marshall and I wanted
to invite you to our place
for a little couples' night.
Sure. Why not?
For years, Marshall and Lily
had been the only married couple
in a group full of single people.
It got lonely.
So they were always searching
for another couple to double-date.
There was only one problem.
- Welcome.
- Gouda?
They sucked at it.
This is great. We're having fun.
You're having fun, right?
So, should we just go ahead
and lock the four of us in
for new year's?
It's april.
Right. Sorry.
We're getting ahead of ourselves.
Let's talk Thanksgiving.
Our parents really want to meet you!
Well, we should probably be going.
Wait. But, wait, if you leave now,
Colonel Mustard just gets away with it.
It's getting pretty late.
We're going to go.
There's still pie.
Tonight was fantastic.
We should do it again.
I'm sorry, Marshall
but Falguni and I
are just not that into you.
And you.
But just when Lily and Marshall
were about to give up,
two of their best friends
in the world got together.
And hope returned to their hearts.
So when Lily said...
Marshall and I wanted to invite you to
our place for a little couples' night.
Sure, why not?
Barney and Robin had no idea
what they were about to walk into.
Okay. Game time.
Let's review the flow of the room.
Barney and Robin enter here,
stop here for margaritas.
That's a great conversation starter.
We can tell them about
our trip to Cabo.
Great, cause I got that story
about Sammy Hagar
and the Belgian waffle
locked and loaded.
Then we'll move on to the
hot apps station. And,
depending on how things are going,
some lively pre-dinner charades.
Right, but...
we'll play that one by...
Sounds like?
Okay, you can be Robin's partner.
Baby, we can do this.
- Welcome.
- Gouda?
Meanwhile, my half-baked theory
that ladies dig the professor look
was actually proving to be true.
So is it hard to grade papers?
You've just got to make it fun.
For example...
every time I spot a grammatical error,
I do a shot.
I'm trashed right now
and I blame our public school system.
Sometimes things just seem
to magically fall into place.
So, you said
you live right upstairs?
Whether it's in the dating world...
Take care.
... or the double-dating world.
- Nailed it!
- Best night ever!
Worst night ever.
Synchro: Mickeyte
Traduction: Dark_Chii,
Eomyn, Litéo, Lino72 & MiniBen314
Relecture: MiniBen314
How I Met Your Mother
5x04 - The Sexless Innkeeper
par la "Have You Met Team"
pour www.forom.com
How was the big couples'
night with Marshall and Lily?
- Brutal.
- Really? How?
It was like we were
on a date with a sad,
chubby girl our mom made us call.
And they were so nervous,
that they weren't even
making sense half of the time.
Come on in.
Would you like a margarita?
In Cabo, I saw Sammy Hagar
eating a Belgian waffle!
And they kept shoving platters
of food in our faces.
Let me guess, did Marshall get, like,
super intense about the cheese?
- Yeah, how'd you know?
- Poor Marshall.
Lily's this gourmet cook,
and all she lets Marshall do is
pick out one sad block of cheese.
That's prosciutto-wrapped melon.
You guys are going to want
to get in on this gouda.
That's seared scallops
with a mango chutney.
Seriously, don't sleep on the gouda.
And that's lobster ravioli
in a black truffle oil.
Tick-tock goes the gouda clock.
We didn't realize
there was gonna be dinner.
We sucked down
a couple tacos outside the subway.
PS, not sitting great.
And if anything didn't go according
to plan, they would freak out.
What do you mean,
the egg timer is broken?
What are we going to use
for charades, sweetie?
I'm working on it, darling.
Okay? Just stall them.
Now, Robin...
You work in television.
We're experiencing some
technical difficulties.
You get that?
We're still laughing.
Right? Laugh, Marshall.
Come on, they just got excited.
They've been looking for couple
best friends forever.
Plus, I'm sure
they weren't that bad.
Show him.
This is a web site Marshall
already made about last night.
It's called:
itwasthebestnightever.com.
It was the best night ever
Laughter raining down
like April showers
We talked for hours...
- Best night ever
- That's not good.
Then we played charades
Lily made some creme brulee...
And now that we're
best couple friends
There's only one thing
Left to say...
Are you free?...
Are you free next Saturday?
- That's the 17th.
- Are you free?
Friday or Sunday would also work.
Or basically any other day.
Needless to say, we've both
changed our e-mail addresses.
I don't understand.
If last night went so horribly,
why do Lily and Marshall
think it was such a hit?
We knew we were gonna have fun tonight
but we had no idea how much.
Tough luck, every Saturday night
I've ever had,
cause this one just
blew you out of the water.
- Let's do it again, soon.
- Yeah, we'll call you.
They're your friends! Why would you
just blatantly lie to them like that?
That's what you say
at the end of a crappy date.
Great time last night.
Let's do it again, soon.
I'll call you.
Right?
- Who was that?
- I don't want to brag, but
it seems chicks are really digging
the whole professor thing.
Last night,
she picked me up at the bar.
And then...
She actually wound up falling asleep
on the couch. But, hey,
that happens.
- No, it doesn't.
- Sure, it does.
You know, she was just exhausted
from being turned on.
But you heard her.
She wants to do it again, soon.
Ted, let me ask you a question.
Where does this girl live, exactly?
Westchester. Why?
- You're the Sexless Innkeeper.
- Oh, my God! You're right!
He's totally the Sexless Innkeeper!
What the hell is
"the Sexless Innkeeper"?
Many a man...
nay, many a soul...
has their own tale of
the Sexless Innkeeper.
Why, I had run-in
with one just last year.
I even composed a poem about it.
- Would you care to hear it?
- Not really.
"It was the night before new year's
and the weather grew mean.
It was 3:00 in the morning
and I was stranded in queens."
"The tavern grew empty,
the gas lights grew dim."
"The horse-drawn carriages
were all but snowed in..."
Wait. If this was last year,
why are you acting like
it was Oliver Twist?
It's a poem.
"Last call was approaching
and my fortunes looked bleak."
"Then I turned to my left
and stifled a shriek."
"She had a peach fuzz beard
and weighed 16 stone."
"She gobbled up hot wings
and swallowed the bones."
"I muffled a scream
and threw up in my mouth."
I asked, "Where do you live?"
And she said, "One block south."
"I swallowed my pride
and six shots of whiskey."
"And prayed to the gods
that she wasn't too frisky."
"Back in her cave,
she prepared us a snack."
"Neath her mighty hooves,
the floorboards did crack."
"But when she returned,
she found a sound sleeper."
"And thus she became
the Sexless Innkeeper."
And so are you
Wait, you're saying that girl
just used me for a place to crash?
Ted, you mentioned that
you live right upstairs.
She saw the tweed jacket
which basically says
you're not interested in, nor probably
even capable of, having sex.
And she thought,
"Hey, free lodging."
No way.
I'm not the Sexless Innkeeper.
That girl had no intention
of ever hooking up with you.
Which is funny, because usually
it's the Innkeeper
who offers turndown service.
Hey, guys. Good news.
First of all, you can ignore all the
e-mails and texts we've sent you.
We have. Go on.
Because we went ahead and booked
that couples weekend
for all of us in Vermont!
Wait, you guys were
serious about that?
We never joke about B&B's, especially
at the height of syrup season.
Saturday we've got apple-picking,
antiquing, then
a hanted hay ride.
And then on Sunday, we're up
at 6:00 a.m. for the fall foliage hike.
Now, you better pack your long Johns,
cause it is cold up there.
I'm sorry that we have been
dodging your calls
but we respect you guys
too much as friends
to give you some song and dance.
You deserve the truth.
The US Navy has found
intelligent alien life
at the bottom of the ocean.
For reasons I can't explain,
Robin and I have been tapped
to lead the expedition.
That kind of sounds like
the stuff you say to girls
when you're too much
of a coward to dump them.
You know, that's exactly
what it sounds like.
But if that's true, that's awesome.
What's going on?
Look, all the couple-y stuff,
it's just not us.
Barney and I are barely equipped
to date each other, let alone you guys.
Plus, the alien thing.
- Come on, Marshall. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- No... Lily...
- You know what?
I hope those underwater aliens
are cold-blooded.
Cause then you guys will
get along just fine.
I think they bought it.
I can't believe they
broke up with us.
We're so lovable.
No, we're not.
We're ugly and gross.
- I thought we did everything right.
- I know!
I know. We had the gouda.
We had my waffle story. I even sent
them a awesome photo montage.
Nothing.
Oh, dear God.
Marshall, we've been
over and over this.
You have to stop
sending those to people.
It was true.
Marshall had become addicted
to creating songs
and photo montage is documenting
various mundane events.
So for months,
all of Marshall's friends and
professional colleagues
were getting e-mails like this...
Ordered Chinese food today
Some moo shu pork sauce got away
Flipped the cushion
Now everything's okay.
Cat-sitting for Lily's mom
It's gonna be fun
It's gonna bring us all
closer together.
Cat funeral...
It was an accident
And not entirely my fault
Cat funeral...
We'll miss you, Whiskers.
I can't believe you sent them
one of those.
They think we're insane now.
If I recall, they didn't dump us until
you brought up that Vermont trip.
It was way too early.
First, a boat ride around the city,
then a trip to Vermont. It's a rookie
mistake, and you're better than that.
What about you forgetting to check
the egg timer for charades?
I gave you one thing to do,
Marshall. One thing.
One thing?
Really?
I guess that gouda
just walked itself
right through the door...
sliced itself up,
and arranged itself
in a perfect semi-circle
around not three,
not four...
but five
different kinds of sturdy,
cheese-bearing crackers?
You're a sturdy,
cheese-bearing cracker!
Lily and Marshall haven't been
to the bar all week.
They're taking this really hard.
I could listen to this
guilt trip all day,
but don't you have to
get back up to the inn?
Who's working the front desk?
Seriously, they're your friends.
You got to go apologize.
To your point, Ted,
as an Innkeeper,
do you do that cheapy thing
where you only change
the linens upon request?
How much water
is that actually saving?
Robin, you know I'm right. Ignoring
a problem doesn't make it go away.
Usually, it just makes it bigger.
- You're right.
- Thank you.
All that sexlessness
has made you wise.
For God's sake!
Mint on the pillow!
And don't charge for wi-fi.
It seems greedy!
But eventually,
even Barney and Robin had to admit
they owed Lily and Marshall
an apology.
We wanted to say we're sorry.
I wish you had called.
I swear, he was right there
just eating a Belgian waffle!
He can't have enjoyed it as much
as I'm enjoying this gouda!
Listen...
Now's not a good time.
We'll call you.
Wait, we just want...
Long time no see.
Have a seat.
We can't.
We're here with Py and Shea.
It's just... we haven't seen
you guys all week.
Maybe all six of us could hang out.
It might be weird.
We're kind of on a double date.
Wouldn't want you to feel
like a fifth and sixth wheel.
Who the hell are these people?
They just moved here from Hawaii.
Py is a total foodie
and Shea, well...
She's...
Shea... Shea is just...
Anyhoo, we can't stay long.
We're just gonna grab a quick beer
and then take these kooks
for a boat ride around the city.
It sounds like this is
getting pretty serious.
We don't want to jinx it, but...
we kind of think
they might be the two.
- Who needs 'em?
- Not us.
Livin alone
We think of all the friends
we've known
But when we dial the telephone
Nobody's home
Two for dinner.
Just the two of you?
All by ourselves
Don't want to be
Anymore
All by ourselves...
Why don't we call that
weird couple down the hall
from you? You know, with the ferrets?
Maybe they want to come over
and play taboo.
After midnight? No way.
We can't Tabooty-call them,
it's pathetic.
Are you wearing sweat pants?
Maybe. But they're Armani.
Okay, guys, I've got
some bad news for you.
So I'm just going
to come out and say it.
You're a couple.
And no matter how hard you try to
fight it, couples need other couples.
That's why you miss
Marshall and Lily.
And can't you just admit that?
- That was amazing, Lily!
- I know!
When I got that left-hand-yellow,
I was like, "What?!"
- You guys are the best.
- Right back at you!
For charades.
How do we know you two
won't hurt us again?
You don't.
You know what? We have two...
very nice people
up in that apartment
who are perfect for us.
Then what are you doing,
standing out in the rain with us?
Damn it.
Why is there something
so attractive about a bad boy...
and girl?
I think we can change them.
Come here, you two.
We'll never sleep
on the gouda again.
All by ourselves...
I got a little poem for you.
You want to hear it?
- Not really.
- "It was the night before this one,
I had hours to kill.
I sat in the tavern,
grading parchments with quill."
With quill?
Barney. It's a poem.
A busty, young lassie
flashed me a grin.
Her garb said "classy",
but her eyes whispered "sin".
She said, "You're a teacher?"
I said, "Yes, indeed".
"I must have you", she moaned.
"I'm turned on by tweed".
With haste we did scamper
to my chamber anon.
We fell to the couch,
and, bro, it was on.
I unlaced her bodice.
Our passions grew deeper.
And thus ends the tale
of the Sexless Innkeeper."
No way.
You made that up.
Are you coming back to bed,
professor?
God, I love being single.
You ready for brunch
with Lily and Marshall?
What have I done?