Kids, in many of my stories,
I'm a starry-eyed romantic
on a noble search for true love.
In this one, I'm just a jerk.
Well, guys, tonight is the night.
I'm inviting Tiffany up to my place
to see my antique camera collection.
- It's Ted's bait.
- "Bait"?
A true gentleman invents a pretense
to lure an honorable lady
into his apartment.
Some item of interest
or beauty you can both
pretend to admire for five minutes
before she hops on your disco stick.
Like she's coming up to "borrow a book"
or "check out an album on vinyl. "
Or to see your new rap poster.
"Rap poster"?
Who would that work on?
It was the first week of college.
I was really into Wu-Tang Clan.
Yeah, bait is tricky.
It has to be something interesting
enough to get the girl upstairs,
but not so interesting
that it overpowers the night.
I found that a slot machine
was too fun.
And a trampoline...
turned out to be too dangerous.
But then I found the perfect bait:
a teacup pig.
"A teacup pig"?
Who's that working on?
- You have a teacup pig?! I
- Didn't know you had a teacup pig!
- Can I borrow your teacup pig?
- Yes, you can.
You have a teacup pig?! My gosh!
I can't believe you have a teacup pig!
You're just so cute!
Yes, you are the cutest piggy ever!
What?
Were you always this pretty?
Or are you going to give me that whole,
"In high school I was
really shy and awkward" line?
I was shy and awkward.
I was, like, a hundred pounds heavier
and I had these crazy buck teeth.
- Seriously?
- No, I've always been hot.
What are you going to do?
Do you know who else
would love this teacup pig?
My boyfriend.
Synchro: ShalimarFox, -Titou-
..: www.sous-titres.eu :..
- You have a boyfriend?
- I know.
So annoying, right?
I mean, he's
not really my boyfriend.
- Good.
- I mean, technically, he kind of is.
Is he or isn't he?
Some of both,
but definitely not either.
Are you getting any of this?
Look, I really like you.
I just need you to be patient.
I don't want to lose you,
Big Brown Eyes.
Somebody doesn't want to lose
She's got you on the hook.
What? What?
I'm not on the hook.
You are totally on the hook.
She's stringing you along.
She's not committing to you,
but she's keeping you
around just in case,
like an old can of chili
in the pantry.
Who's buying canned chili
and not eating it immediately?
Amen, sister.
Don't feel bad. We've all been there.
I've been on both sides of it.
I've been a hookey and a hooker.
Move past it, guys.
I've been a little bit loose,
but money never changed hands.
I've been on the hook.
Lisa Walker.
Picture it:
1994, St. Cloud, Minnesota.
So I was, like, thinking, Lisa...
do you maybe want to,
like, go out with me?
That sounds great.
But I'm sort of seeing this guy.
He's got a LeBaron convertible
and an "in" at the roller rink,
so I'd hate to burn that bridge.
I understand.
But how about this?
You can be my secret boyfriend
who does all my homework for me.
A'ight.
You want to see my rap poster?
Poster whore.
Anyway...
Lisa Walker strung me
along for months until one night,
I went to go tell her
how much I loved her.
In song.
She wasn't home yet, so I waited.
And waited.
I woke up four hours later,
covered in snow.
And that's when I saw it.
Lisa's footsteps.
She had walked right over me
and into the house.
It was the best thing that could've
happened. It got me off her hook.
Okay, that is definitely not
what's going on with me and Tiffany.
Listen to this.
I'm really into you.
I just can't be with you right now.
Ted, "right no" is the classic
on-the-hook catchphrase.
"Right now" paints a picture of
some sort of magical future time
when everything will work out, but
the truth is, that will never happen.
It's like this.
"I can't be with you. "
"Right now. "
I think my high school boyfriend,
is still sort of on the hook for me.
Sort of?
He totally is.
The poor guy showed up at our
wedding hoping to win you back.
It's sometimes weird
when I see him at work.
Wait. What?
Scooter works in the school cafeteria.
We've talked about this.
Lily. Nice dress.
Tater-tots?
We most certainly have
not talked about this!
Yes, we have.
I've mentioned it tons of times.
"Lunch Lady Scooter. "
I thought that you were referring
to some sort of long overdue
device that carries around
those poor,
underappreciated lunch ladies!
This explains a lot.
Lunch Lady Scooter
was there again today.
Did you jump on that thing?
Give it a ride?
Really? If it were me,
I'd be riding that scooter
all day long until I broke
that thang in half.
So those poor women still
have to walk everywhere?
Wait. Scooter is working
at your school?!
Are you jealous?
No, I just feel bad for Scooter.
'Cause the reason he took that job
is he thinks he has a shot with you.
You have to make it clear
that he doesn't,
so that he can move on
and a real lunch lady
can get her job back. Damn!
I've tried.
I saw you had seventh period free.
So do I.
You want to run away together?
Let me be clear, Scooter.
There is no way you and I
can ever be together.
Right now.
I'll see you tomorrow, Lily.
It's Tijuana Tuesday.
"Right now"?
You right-now'd Scooter?
You need to let him
off the hook once and for all.
You're right. Day after tomorrow,
that's exactly what I'm going to do.
Why not tomorrow?
Baby, I can't ruin Tijuana Tuesday.
Really?
You're really going to sit here
all night watching the door
because Tiffany said
she'll "try to stop by"?
Barney, I'm not going
to just give up on her.
I should have given up on her.
This girl is special.
She was the devil.
Things are going
to work out with her.
No, they're not, dumbass.
Ted, let me be clear:
this girl is a poison
and you need to cut her
out of your life forever.
There she is.
She brought some of her coworkers.
Hang on to this girl.
Hang on to her and never let go!
These are some of the
hottest girls I've ever seen.
And they all work with Tiffany?
There could only be
one explanation for this.
Is Tiffany a ph...
pharmaceutical sales rep?
- Yeah, how did you know that?
- And you never thought to mention that?
What? It's just a job.
Just a j... just a jo...
Ted, throughout time
there has always been one
cutting-edge profession
to which hot girls,
like Tiffany, have flocked.
- Shall I walk you through the history?
- I'm gonna explicitly say no.
It all started
2.5 million years ago.
Man was a hunter.
So, the hottest
profession of the day?
Gatherer.
Homo erectus indeed.
As man mastered technology,
the hottest profession
of the day evolved.
I'm pretty sure it's a hernia.
Can you check again?
And then, man took to the skies.
And so, hot women put on high heels
and became stewardesses
I am in the upright
and locked position.
And then man said, "Life is hard.
I should start taking
lots of prescription drugs. "
And so, hot girls
rolled into doctors' offices,
looking sexy enough to render
the very erection pills
they peddled ironically redundant.
So now, pharma girls are today's
hottest profession.
Big Brown Eyes.
How you doing?
I'm good.
By the way, you, you ditch
that loser boyfriend yet?
No, sir.
Touched my nose.
Dude, ditch Tiffany
and join the Barnacle
in a pharma girl free-for-all.
Side effects may include
loss of clothing, rug burn,
shortness of breath and sore
abdominals the next morning.
What in the world is up?!
I know that you've been having trouble
letting Scooter off the hook.
I decided what you need is practice.
Now, you say
the problem is his cute, sad eyes?
Well...
All right, shut it, woman.
Now,
I want you to look at this teacup pig
and tell him that there's no way
that you could ever be with him.
Teacup Pig,
there is no way
I can ever be with you.
Right now.
Come on!
Grow a pair!
I'm sorry, but...
he's just so freakin' cute.
I just want to cuddle him
all day long.
- Yes, I do.
- You know, that's funny.
I remember when you used to say
things like that about me.
I still do.
Not as much, Lily.
Not as much.
Ain't no party
like a pharma girl party.
'Cause a pharma girl party
don't stop!
Dude, I have already hooked up
with three of them.
Fantasmo.
Plus, my cholesterol is down.
My restless legs syndrome is cured.
I've never felt more alive.
Guys, great news.
Tiffany broke up with her boyfriend.
- Proof that I am not on the hook.
- You're still on the hook.
Listen to how we spent last night.
First, we cuddled.
Then,
we shared chocolate cake.
Then, well, I don't usually
join in on locker room talk,
but I gave her
a pretty sensual foot rub.
And let me guess,
it didn't go any further than that.
No, but...
And tell me, did you by any chance
make that chocolate cake?
- It was a mix.
- Dude.
There's no shame in admitting it,
Ted.
We've all been on people's hooks
and we've all kept someone on the hook.
I most certainly have not.
- What?
- Are you joking?
What about that girl
from the university library?
Henrietta?
Henrietta and I are just friends.
She is so on your hook.
Absolutely not.
She totally was.
I mean...
we cuddled.
We shared chocolate cake.
She gave me foot rubs... long ones.
I'm not proud, kids.
You like having Henrietta around
for the reason
that Tiffany likes having you around,
it's a nice little ego boost.
No wonder you're such an expert
about keeping people on the hook.
What about that poor camera guy
you work with?
- Mike and I are just friends.
- Come on.
That's the stuff.
Robin, have you ever thought about
taking us to the next level?
If you're talking about
doing my laundry, I'm on board.
You got yourself a deal.
What?!
I am not keeping Mike on the hook.
You are Captain Hook.
Dude, I'm a girl.
Our girl parts are like a spiderweb.
Sometimes you'll catch
stuff you don't want.
That doesn't make it okay.
And Henrietta is in, in no way
wasting her time with you, right?
Henrietta knows
that we're just friends.
In fact, I'm gonna call her up
and hang out with her tonight,
as friends.
I love you. What?
Do you want a foot massage?
'Cause I've been practicing
on myself.
I'm good.
I didn't know if you were hungry,
so I threw together some...
it's not a big deal.
Kids, looking back,
I don't know how I didn't see
that Henrietta was in love with me.
I'm going out of town this weekend
for my friend's wedding.
Want to be my date?
I would love to.
What are you doing right now?
God, no.
Awesome.
I'll see you in, like, ten minutes?
Great.
Sorry, Henrietta, something came up.
Take a rain check, pal?
It's no problem.
You're strong.
What a jerk.
Henrietta, I...
Wait. Where did Ted go?
I thought we'll meet him.
Something came up, okay, Mom?
I told you there was no Ted.
I heard that.
So there I was,
at one of the surest signs of taking
a relationship to the next level,
an out-of-town wedding.
It was finally happening.
Champagne?
Ted, my gosh, I forgot to call you.
Whatever it's you wanted to talk about,
we can do it now.
This is Jack.
He's the best man at the wedding.
We just got back together.
Now that I think about it,
a phone call would have been nice.
You're Ted?
I hear you make
a mean chocolate cake.
Isn't he great?
And he's in a band.
Thanks.
Come on.
You have to get Scooter off the hook.
Now, try again.
Teacup Pig...
I don't want to be with you.
- Right now.
- Man up!
Teacup Pig...
I don't want to be with you.
Ever.
Finish him!
We will never be together
in any sort of sexual way
ever again.
Nice.
- A weird thing to say to a pig.
- It felt really wrong.
Anyway, I just don't think
you and I are going to work.
Right now.
And that's when it hit me.
I was on the hook.
I also realized...
I missed this so much, baby.
... Tiffany was on this guy's hook.
It was a vicious cycle.
Henrietta was on my hook.
And years later, I found out
this bastard was on Henrietta's hook.
You know what?
We're not going to work ever.
I'm done.
And it's better for the circulation
if you knead the arches with thumbs.
Now, I'm done.
Marshall, I can do this by myself.
Then prove it.
Grab me a pudding.
Listen up, Scooter.
There is no way
you and I will ever be together.
Right now!
I'm sorry, but he's adorable.
Listen.
- I don't want to be with you.
- Right now.
Hang in there, Scoots!
I'm not going to live forever.
Last night I was
with this pharma girl who was so hot,
you should call a doctor
if you don't have an erection
for more than four hours.
Am I right, people?
There's no people...
just the girl you most recently dated.
I want you to meet
the newest pharma girl.
Gladys Reynolds.
Nice to make your acquaintance.
I represent statins
and other cholesterol-lowering drugs.
Come on.
Let's go get our drink on.
It's over.
What's over?
Pharma girls are
no longer exclusively hot chicks.
It's the end of an era.
You're being a little dramatic.
Am I?
It starts out with a Gladys.
Next thing, a few not-so-fabulous
gay guys enter the ranks.
And before you know it,
pharma girls look
like the crew on a Southwest flight
from Albuquerque to Little Rock.
It's over!
So that night,
I went straight to Henrietta's...
all set to let her off the hook.
This is Jack.
He's the best man at the wedding.
I'm done.
The answer is yes!
It gets worse.
It's perfect!
Mom, Dad!
Ted proposed!
I knew this day would come!
Son!
There's been a...
What did you do?
I seriously considered
just marrying her
out of sheer awkwardness.
But I did what I had to do.
I did what anyone
keeping someone on the hook should do.
I broke her heart.
Henrietta, I'm sorry if this is blunt,
but I think I owe you this.
I don't want to be with you.
Right now?
Ever.
But we're still getting married,
right?
It was... brutal.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Honesty is tough, but in the end,
it is the far kinder alternative.
Hey, sweetie.
Hey, Mike.
I have to tell you something.
Did you finish my delicates?
- Got one more load.
- It can wait.
How's it going?
Still in mourning
over the end of the pharma girl era?
I realized
that their reign had to end
for some new hot girl profession.
Maybe it'll be...
intergalactic communications officer
on a rocket ship
to some distant solar system
we can't possibly imagine.
Maybe it'll be... meter maids.
We just don't know.
But one thing is sure.
The future glows
like a giant sun
shooting amber rays of light
into our hearts and minds.
What changed your mind?
The realization
that hope springs eternal, Robin.
That
and this little bottle of purple pills
I found in my couch cushion.
I don't know what they are,
but they are amazing.