- I heard this great joke at work.
- Dude, come on.
She's not gonna like it.
It's boy-funny. It's not girl-funny.
That is sexist!
Funny is funny, Ted.
Lily's cool.
She'll appreciate this.
- You're on your own, man.
- Just tell me the joke.
Okay. Ready?
Lily, what's the difference
between peanut butter and jam?
- See? It's funny.
- It's boy-funny.
- She's not gonna like it.
- Why don't you let me decide?
What's the difference
between peanut butter and jam?
And then Barney said the punch line.
To this day,
it's still the dirtiest joke
I've ever heard in my life.
And no, I'm not gonna say it.
Yeah, I can't hang out
with you anymore.
Oh, come on.
That's a funny joke. That...
Told you.
She'll be back.
And we didn't see Lily
for four weeks.
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Arrow
Kids, after getting laid off,
I was finally pursuing
my lifelong dream:
starting my own architecture firm.
All I needed was some clients.
I think it's so great that
you're striking out on your own, Ted.
- I admire that.
- Thanks.
And thanks for being so cool
with me using the apartment.
Yeah, of course.
Anything you need.
Small thing, do you mind not watching
television during business hours?
- This isn't working!
- I'm sorry. It's just, I....
I can't concentrate
while Wheel of Fortune is...
A penny saved
is a Penny Marshall! Yes!
Ted, I know you're nervous,
but you've got to stop procrastinating.
You've spent the last two days choosing
the official pen of Mosbius Designs.
I've made some progress!
I've eliminated felt-tip.
Who am I kidding?
Felt's back in the ballgame.
Hey. You hear there's gonna be
more layoffs?
I know. I'm freaking out.
- Are you worried?
- Are you kidding?
The things I know about this company.
I won't ever be fired.
There's a pretty good chance one day
I'll wash up on shore
with no fingerprints or teeth,
but I won't be fired.
I wish I had your confidence.
Look, you just need a way to make
yourself absolutely essential.
Well, I work harder
than anyone in my division.
Yeah. Keeping your job has
nothing to do with hard work.
- You need a thing.
- What do you mean, a thing?
You know, something
that makes you fun
and well-liked, like Marcus Denisco.
Marcus Denisco worked
in account services
and was perhaps the most expendable
employee at the company.
I brought some donuts.
They're probably stupid.
But eventually,
he came to be known as...
Food Guy!
Who wants some pulled pork?
Of course you do! Come on!
I love Food Guy.
They could never lay him off.
You know what I love about Food Guy?
- He always has food.
See? That's what you need.
You need that thing
that makes you a guy.
I have that thing
that makes me a guy.
Maybe even a guy and a half.
Not that thing.
You know, a thing. Like Toy Guy.
Guys, bad news.
As your HR rep,
I got to review the new overtime
scheduling policy with you.
The good news is we're gonna do it
while wearing Wolverine claws!
Section 5A:
Overtime will no longer be paid
at time and a half.
This is awesome!
Claw five!
I love Toy Guy.
See? You need a thing.
Like YouTube Clip Guy.
You're right.
I do need a thing.
But choose wisely.
You don't want
to be Creepy Back Rub Guy.
Don't fill up. Food Guy's
got panna cotta in his office.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, Douglas.
You're so tight.
I was relaxed about two seconds ago.
You're next.
Hi. Welcome to Mosbius Designs.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm PJ, Mr. Mosby's assistant.
- What the hell is going on?
- I'm sorry. We do not interrupt
Mr. Mosby during
his brainstorming hour.
It's okay, PJ. That's Robin.
She lives here.
I'm sorry for the disturbance, sir.
Do you need anything else?
- I wouldn't say no to a cup of coffee.
- You're right there!
So now, Ted has an assistant
to help him not do anything.
PJ's been a huge help to me,
setting up the office,
designing the Web site.
And in return, I'm mentoring
a bright young mind.
Yes, the mentoring.
I want you to go outside
today and simply...
put your hands on buildings.
All right? Feel
the concrete pulse.
Listen... Listen to the stories
the stones are telling you.
And pick up my dry cleaning.
I will.
- Thank you so much, Mr. Mosby.
- All right.
This table just told me
you're a douche.
This whole mentoring thing
is just another way to procrastinate
- from actually calling clients.
- I'm not procrastinating.
I just... I want everything
to be perfect, okay?
I only get one shot at this.
Fine, but PJ is not helping.
If Ted says that PJ
is important to the company,
then PJ is not going anywhere.
See? He's very valuable.
PJ's a guy?
PJ's not some hot chick
you're banging?
No, I'm mentoring him.
Mentoring.
I mentored a young fellow once.
Even made him my wingman.
Then, one day, he hired an assistant
to work ten feet
from his bedroom who...
get this... isn't a hot chick,
proving he never listened
to a word I said.
And do you know
that young man's name?
Maybe. I don't remember.
Because he is dead to me!
PJ's gonna be getting
a very confusing card in the mail,
along with a garment
that he should by no means wear
for three days
and then mail back to me.
I thought of a "thing"
to make me more essential here.
I'm Eco Guy, 'cause everybody loves
a guy who recycles, right?
Fired. What else you got?
I thought of a few others:
Wacky Tie Guy.
- Fired.
- Daily Fun Fact Guy?
Did you know that you're fired?
I Know a Good Stretch for That Guy?
Downward-facing fired.
Monty Python Guy?
We are the knights who say...
You're fired.
Wait! Wait!
I did used to run
a fantasy baseball league
back in law school.
That's not bad.
You might be on to something.
Awesome. Awesome!
I'll be Fantasy Guy!
We'll have to make you Sports Guy.
We already have a Fantasy Guy.
- What's up, bros?
- Hey, Frank.
Hello?
Where are you?
You're never late.
You're on top
of the Empire State Building?
Listen to the old gal.
She's got some stories to tell.
Take all the time you need.
Wait a second.
"Ted Mosby Home".
Oh my God, the call is coming
from inside the house.
That's not
the Empire State Building.
Robin, you cannot sleep
with my assistant.
I'm trying to run a business here.
How did this even happen?
Well, at lunch, when you go
on your wisdom walks,
it gives me and PJ
some time alone together.
Inspiration... do your thing.
It always does, sir.
It always does.
Hey, PJ, I actually have
an architectural question for you.
How does Ted's ass taste?
I wouldn't know, but I assume
it tastes like genius.
Why is the bathroom locked?
Visitors need to sign in
for the bathroom key.
Listen, Peej, and I want you to think
this over real good
before you answer.
Are you telling me that I can't
go to the bathroom in my apartment?
I am telling you that you need
to ask permission
to use the bathroom in my office.
Why is that so hot?
There are billions
of guys in the world.
Why do you have to sleep with him?
Ted, when I get off work,
it's 5:30 in the morning.
Do you have any idea
what kind of guys I'm meeting?
I deliver newspapers. It's a dirty job,
but somebody's got to do it.
Don't worry. I'll wash them
before I handle your business.
I live with my mom.
At night, we watch TV in her bed.
We call it "Cuddle Club".
So, you, get up really early to trade
on the European stock exchanges?
What's that like?
Look, is this going
to happen or not?
Okay, first of all,
I've hung out with Fantasy Guy.
You could do a lot worse.
Secondly,
this has to stop.
Distracting PJ is going
to kill our productivity.
What productivity? You haven't
even called a single client.
Once I get the Web site up,
the brochures printed,
and figure out what trusts games
we're going to play at the corporate
retreat, I am making those calls.
Corporate retreat?
Mr. Mosby and I are going camping
on the roof.
Hey, Sports Guy. I hear people
are raving about your league.
It's a lot harder
than I thought it would be.
Between entry fees
and transaction fees
and penalty fees, I'm actually...
I'm holding on to a lot of money.
Great work, Sports Guy.
That's for last week.
60,
80, a hundred.
This is $18,000 cash.
It's not a big deal.
I'll just take it home
and put it somewhere safe.
Okay, just walking down the street
with some money in my pocket.
Don't touch the money.
That's so obvious.
Just be cool.
The baby's on to me.
Babies can smell money.
Everyone knows that!
I'm carrying a lot of money!
Seriously, dude,
I'm not sure how much longer
I can keep doing this.
Marshall, last week you were trash
that no one wanted to look at.
Now, you're Sports Guy.
- I was trash?
- Last week!
There's Ted Mosby
of Mosbius Designs.
How's the home office coming, buddy?
It was going great till Robin started
banging my assistant.
It's our apartment, okay? You leave
a big chocolate cake on the counter,
Mama's gonna cut her off a slice.
I told you.
Hire a cute assistant
that you can sleep with,
but instead you hire a cute assistant
that Robin can sleep with.
And of course he's gonna sleep with her.
She's the greatest woman on the planet!
I'm getting off topic!
You're an idiot!
That's my message!
One person storming off isn't enough!
Marshall, storm off with me!
Dude, why are this upset
about Ted not having sex
with the people he hires?
Because it hurts!
- It hurts you how?
- It hurts because I love...
Ted.
Having sex with women.
I'm a very dedicated wingman!
Look, Lily's the only person
that I can talk to about this stuff.
Just get her to talk to me.
I'll try, but there's no guarantees.
She's still really outraged
about that joke.
That joke.
Torn our little group apart,
pitted people I love
against each other.
Seriously, I wish...
I wish that joke had never come
into our lives.
- It's kinda of funny though, right?
- It's so funny, man.
Hey, good news, PJ.
The brochures you designed just came in.
Really interesting choice for the cover.
I like how instead of one
of my designs,
you chose this.
You know what?
I must've sent in the wrong photo.
You think?
Look, PJ,
the Web site's still not done.
You didn't even show up
to the corporate retreat...
by the way, I saw a shooting star...
... and you're late every day.
I'm sorry, PJ. I gotta get focused.
- You're fired.
- You can't fire...
PJ, you're fired.
Fine!
Hey, baby.
I just got fired.
Yeah, I'll wait for you
at your place.
Wheel of Fortune.
I love having all this free time
to spend with you.
I'm going to kiss you here...
And here.
And here and here.
And...
- One more.
- Please stop.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
I'll miss you.
I'll miss you, too.
- You're already sick of him.
- He's driving me crazy.
When PJ had a job, he was sexy.
He was guardian of the bathroom key.
A hot guy telling you
when you can and can't pee?
That's the dream.
"That's the dream"?
The dream?
Like what Martin Luther King
was talking about?
I have to end it, don't I?
I'm terrible at breakups.
I still have to go a little bit, but
I couldn't be away from you 1 s longer.
Listen...
Dude, I don't know.
- What?
- Yeah, it's just...
It's not really...
ix-nay, you know?
Ix-nay on what?
Not feeling it.
Not feeling what?
But friends and stuff.
My God, this is
the worst breakup ever.
You're breaking up with me?
If that's what you want,
I totally understand.
You still haven't activated that
shortstop the Mariners just brought up.
Got to have it.
See, Sports Guy!
People love you.
I can't be Sports Guy anymore, okay?
It's killing me!
I keep getting
these constant texts and e-mails
and phone calls
in the middle of the night.
Sometimes I even think
that I'm being followed.
Hey, buddy.
I need you to push that trade through,
so I can set my new lineup.
You really carry it
in your shoulders, don't you?
Seriously, it's over.
Do you want me to stop?
With Robin and PJ broken up,
I was free to make
some staffing changes in the office.
Welcome to Mosbius Designs.
You got to be kidding me?
And now that PJ was back at work...
So, apparently Robin and PJ
are an item again.
You got to be kidding me!
Are you all right?
Since Lily's not talking to me,
there's something I have to tell you.
And this isn't easy to say, all right?
I'm... wait for it...
in... wait for it...
love... wait for it...
with... wait for it...
a... wait for it...
- certain... wait for it...
- I know that you're in love with Robin.
- What?
- Lily told me.
She told you?
Great.
I bet you guys have been laughing at me
behind my back the whole time.
Actually, in a weird way,
we both think you're kind
of perfect for each other.
You do?
Matter of fact,
we even try to sit on the same side
of the booth so you two
will have to sit together.
Really? That's so sweet.
But let's be clear.
I don't love her. Okay?
I just...
miss her when she's not around.
I think about her all the time,
and I imagine us one day running towards
each other in slow motion,
and I'm wearing a brown suede vest.
Are you ever gonna tell her
how you feel?
Maybe. Never. I don't know. Look...
I just need to get
that PJ idiot away from her.
If Lily were here, she'd know exactly
how to get rid of him.
- Maybe I can help.
- Marshall, you're no Lily.
Lily is a diabolical puppet master,
subtly manipulating
every situation to get
exactly what she wants.
She's pure evil, Marshall.
You got a good one there.
Hang on to her.
Meanwhile, my bizarre tug of war
with Robin over PJ continued.
I was about to go on my wisdom walk.
Want to join me?
I took the bathroom key
without asking.
What are you gonna do about it?
Look...
you guys are both great.
But the truth is I'm taking another job.
These are for you.
Robin, I hope this letter
offers some closure.
I'm really going to miss you.
You can't trade Manny Ramirez
for two middle relievers!
If you veto that trade,
I am out of the league!
I'll figure it out.
Hire the kid to be a "paralegal".
He gets to do all the work,
and you still get to be Sports Guy.
Pure evil, Eriksen.
Pure evil.
You okay?
What if I don't think of the books?
Excuse me?
There's this famous architecture story
about an architect
who designed this library.
It was perfect.
But every year,
the whole thing would sink
a couple inches into the ground.
Eventually, the building
was condemned.
He forgot to account
for the weight of the books.
This company... it's just me.
What if I don't think of the books?
First of all, nobody goes to libraries
anymore, so who cares about that guy?
Secondly, you need to get
on the phone and start calling clients.
The longer I put off
starting my own firm,
the longer it can remain a dream
and not something I screwed up at.
It's like I'm giving up
before I even started.
You want to talk about giving up?
I used to describe my ideal guy as
"funny, smart,
"passionate, challenging".
And now, apparently,
I will settle for...
"in my apartment".
Didn't you think you'd have it
all more figured out by now?
Are you kidding? By 30,
I was gonna be annoyingly successful,
married to the perfect woman,
maybe a kid on the way.
Instead, I'm just some guy
sitting in his apartment,
having a staring contest
with his phone.
And losing.
You can take that thing.
Hi, this is Ted Mosby
of Mosbius Designs.
I'm calling to inquire about any design
needs you may have now or in the future.
- That sounds great.
- Really? I sound confident?
- Now call an actual client.
- Great.
Hey, Food Guy!
Hey, Toy Guy!
Who's that guy?
He doesn't work here.
I think we should leave the building.
- Really?
- This has happened before.