[Booth]
Florida? Today?
- Is that work?
- Yeah.
Hot, fun, Miami, Florida...
or sticky, you know,
swampy Florida?
- [Man] Really.
- You're welcome. God.
- What's going on in Florida?
- Wait a sec. What flight?
- # [Calliope]
- Hold on for a second. I can't hear you.
Enough with the song already,
all right?
I'm doing business here.
Deal with it!
Hold on for a second.
Now my pen's out of ink.
- Here.
- Oh, hold on. I can't hear anything!
- The kids love the music.
- Well, I don't see any kids.
The music attracts them!
Did you say the Everglades? Look, I can't
hear anything because of this insane music!
- [Gunshots]
- # [Stops]
- [People Screaming]
- You shot my clown!
Great. Flight number?
- [Man] Move out of the way!
- Hey! He shot my clown!
- [Electricity Crackles]
- [Booth] Okay. Thanks.
- Okay. We're all set.
- That was not good.
I thought you said you'd be down
on the next flight.
- [Booth On Phone]
Well, I haven't met with the shrink yet.
- What shrink?
Well, the department psychiatrist has to
sign a piece of paper saying, you know...
that I'm not nuts
before I get my gun back.
So, I got
an appointment tomorrow.
Great. Now I have to break in
this... Agent Sullivan?
Wait. Sully's a great guy.
Okay?
- And for your information, you never broke me in.
- Oh, I think that's him.
- Okay, I'll talk to you later.
- [Police Radio Chatter]
[Sighs]
Dr. Brennan?
- Agent Sullivan?
- Uh-huh.
- Name's Eugene.
- Okay, Eugene.
No, not me. I'm Sully.
Short for Sullivan.
- Well, then, who's Eugene?
- [Man] Right here.
Eugene's been king of this swamp
for as long as I can remember.
Broke my heart to
have to shoot him.
Is there an actual human victim?
- Inside Eugene.
- He ate somebody?
Damn spring breakers
think it's a real kick...
to come here
and drink beer with the big fella.
I just chased off a bunch of'em.
And there was Eugene in the middle
of the swamp gulping down somebody's arm.
Someone from the group of kids
you chased off?
No. No, gators
don't eat fresh kills.
They drown their prey.
They stuff it down underwater to tenderize
for a few weeks before they can eat 'em.
Okay. Why don't you drag the rest
of the swamp for any additional remains?
I'll check Fort Lauderdale missing persons.
You start cutting.
No.
Wh... Isn't that what you do?
Any potential remains
are far too sensitive to be retrieved here.
[Sighs]
Okay. Well, where... where do you suggest?
- My lab at theJeffersonian.
- The whole gator?
I'll handle transport.
- You're gonna need a big crate.
- [Scoffs] And a lot of ice.
Okeydoke. Well, if you're doing this...
then there's a boat for sale
that I'd like to check out.
A boat? Booth helps.
- 'Cause Booth can't relax.
- There's something metal in here.
[Grunts]
Uh-huh.
- [Police Radio Chatter]
- Don't you have a boat to buy?
I knew it was a gator.
Brennan told me it was a gator.
- And yet... wow.
- Definitely confirms one thing.
- We have the coolest jobs ever.
- Look at all these teeth.
Step away, please.
There are 80 in total.
Note the conical shape.
"Step away, please?"
Just because you have a doctorate now...
does not mean I won't
use you as a swizzle stick.
Animal foot.
Possibly a rabbit.
Not so lucky
for either of them.
- Frog.
- Yummy.
- Do I hear music?
- # [Latin, Muffled]
# [Continues]
- # [Stops]
- Hey. I liked that song.
What do you think, Zack?
Definitely a human foot.
Lovely.
Dr. Wyatt.
Ah, Agent Booth, is it?
Yes. Gordon. Gordon Wyatt.
- Right. You're the shrink?
- Uh, shrink, yes, meaning psychiatrist.
That's great, Doc. How's about
you just sign my piece of paper here...
- and I'll get back to work.
- Uh, certainly. No, no. I have a pen.
- Okay.
- Do you mind if I ask what
exactly it was that you did?
- Yeah, I shot a truck.
- Ah.
Full of terrorists, no doubt,
or plutonium or fleeing felons, was it?
- No. It was an ice cream truck.
- Do you have a good reason for firing on it?
- Yeah. The music, it was bothering me.
- Ah.
Yeah. There was a speaker
in the clown's mouth.
- Oh.
- Yeah, I just pulled out my gun, you know, and...
[Imitates Gunshots]
It was gone.
So the F.B.I. sent you to me
because you shot a clown?
Not a real clown.
I suggest you cogitate on the underlying reasons
you shot that clown while I make us some tea.
What? Cogitate?
Tea?
The depth of these bite marks...
very impressive.
One torn pair of jeans.
One red linen blouse, size two.
And one platform wedge.
Made it all the way
to the lower intestine.
Florida F.B.I. just beamed over
names of recent missing persons.
We'll need dental records.
- Sully!
- Cam!
Look at you, in charge of
Moon Base Alpha here.
And you're still a G-man.
What happened to that restaurant you were
gonna open? Or was it a petting zoo?
Well, I am keeping myself open
for the perfect opportunity.
- I tried out a beautiful boat.
- But he made it back to shore.
[Hodgins]
Victim is female, in her late teens...
eliminating three of
your missing persons right here.
- So cause of death?
- For the gator?
We have these.45-caliber slugs.
As for the girl's, so far we've got the gator.
Okeydoke. Well, um,
I am gonna go grab a slice.
So give me a call
when you got an I.D.
Her name's Judy Dowd.
Shouldn't you at least look at the X-rays
before deciding that?
It says right here she had surgery
to repair a cleft palate at age two.
The bone graft is here.
She was a freshman
at Virginia State.
Reported missing three weeks ago.
An alligator?
Oh, my God.
When did you last
see your daughter, Mr. Dowd?
The day she left with her friend
for spring break.
Her friend, uh, Abigail Sims?
Abby. A good kid.
[Voice Breaking]
I never should've let her go.
We found this among the remains.
This was her mother's.
Lanie died when Judes was 11.
It's just been
the two of us ever since.
Did you get any calls from her
while she was there?
Every day.
Any sign that she was in trouble?
No. She...
[Sighs]
She sounded happy.
So happy.
[Sniffles]
You are really English.
Oh, I don't know.
I think I've assimilated quite well.
Typical American house, right down to
the white picket fence, a truck that's the, uh...
What is it? "The heartbeat of America?"
But tea?
Tea is, uh, sacrosanct,
thank you very much.
Me? I'm a coffee drinker.
Hey, listen, pal.
You know, in an effort to
understand your culture better...
I've been trying to embrace this very American
practice of preparing meat in the garden.
- Barbecue.
- Mmm, it's a delightful word, isn't it? Barbecue.
I think it's from the Caribbean, barabicu...
which means
a sort of sacred fire pit.
Did you know that the Latin for hearth,
though, is "focus?" Isn't that revealing?
It's quite literally
the focal point of every household.
The hearth, the heart.
Hmm? Interesting.
I told the ice cream guy
I was sorry, all right?
l-l-I even bought him a new clown head.
So just sign the paper.
[Sighs]
I must apologize.
But I've got to go off and get
some ingredients for my mortar.
- Um, why don't we reschedule?
- We can't reschedule, all right?
I gotta get back to work.
Oh. Well, in that case...
um, why not finish off
preparing this area here?
Could you do that?
All the specifications are on the plans.
You are fit for physical labor,
aren't you?
I mean, the, uh, the clown
didn't return fire, did it?
Oh, what if I said that
the plastic clown did fire back, huh?
Brilliant.
[Chuckles]
Now while I'm gone, what I want you to do
is to consider what you were really aiming at...
when you drew a bead
on that unfortunate clown.
Hey, buddy, when I aim at something,
I hit it.
Precisely.
Anyway, I shan't be long, Agent.
It's all on the plans here.
I'll be back before long, Agent.
See you then.
Do help yourself to more tea
by the way.
Like I told the police, me and Judy were
just doing the usual spring break stuff.
The whole night was
kind of a blur...
until I woke up the next morning
at the hotel, and Judy wasn't there.
- She hadn't come back with you?
- I can't remember.
So why didn't you report it to someone
till later that night?
- I thought maybe she'd hooked up.
- Hooked up?
Hooked up.
Uh, with anyone in particular?
We met so many guys.
You know how it is.
I'm guessing that she doesn't.
Do you have any pictures
from that night, Abby?
No. The police
took most of them.
Wait. Most of them?
There's a couple
on my personal Web page.
I didn't want them
showing poor Mr. Dowd.
Judy would never want him
seeing her like that.
Like what?
Here's the spectrophotometric evaluation
on Judy Dowd. Any results on her tox screen?
No drugs, but her blood-alcohol
was sky high.
Point 11. And...
- Oh, dear.
- [Angela] What?
S.P.M. reveals hidden hematomas
in decomp tissue.
See this shaded area here?
It indicates bruising
to her vaginal wall.
Meaning Judy was raped.
Or at the very least, subjected to
some extremely unpleasant college sex.
With one of these fine lads?
[Saroyan] Without D.N.A.,
it's the proverbial needle in a haystack.
Wait. Our victim was an H.S. B?
- Excuse me?
- HottyStudentBody. com.
It's this Web site that
gets drunk college girls...
from all over the East Coast
to take their clothes off.
I clicked on a pop-up,
got caught in a "pornado."
What?
Oh, splendid. So it was your father
who taught you to read plans, was it?
Wrong tree, Doc, okay?
Dad and I were tight.
Only, it's just that earlier you said that
you weren't used to drinking tea with men...
which suggests to me that you're usually
pretty rigid in your assignment of gender roles.
What? No, no.
My-My partner's a woman, okay?
A woman who needs my help.
Hmm. But are you
currently involved with anyone?
I just broke up with someone, okay?
Me. And I ended it.
And how long had you been
involved with her? O-Or him?
Her. Let's get that straight, okay?
Her.
- Couple months this time.
- This time?
We'd gone out...
We'd gone out before a-a f-few years ago.
And you know, we, uh...
I broke it up when, uh, you know,
my ex wanted to give it another go.
[Winces]
Complicated.
Ah! That's it!
I shot the clown because
I can't let go of the women in my life.
Ha! Thanks, Doc. All right.
Now, I can go back to work.
And you can sign the paper!
Excellent theory,
but quite wrong.
And we're out of time.
Tomorrow all right for you?
Just right. Yes.
[Sighs]
- We found a stab wound.
- Let's see it.
It's more of a puncture, really.
Hidden here among the bite marks
just below her scapula.
Angela doesn't like me
being her superior.
- Because you're acting superior.
- Which is what a superior is.
Don't be a horse's ass. She's your friend.
That's all that matters.
These ridge marks inside the wound
look like the threads of a screw.
We're trying to I.D. the weapon.
At the least, it proves Judy didn't stumble
into the swamp and feed herself to Eugene.
- That was my conclusion as well.
- Okay.
And the hits keep coming.
It seems Judy Dowd was raped and murdered.
No more rough college sex?
Now that we know it's a murder,
I'm feeling a lot less charitable.
- [Laughing]
- # [Hip-Hop]
- [Brennan] What is all this?
- Have a look.
[Together]
Hotties by the pool!
It was shot in Fort Lauderdale
the same nightJudy disappeared.
- [Brennan] Who is that?
- His name's Monte Gold.
Internet kingpin
and aspiring Hugh Hefner.
Monte has made millions
off of this site.
He also paid out a million in fines
last year for filming underage girls.
[Brennan] I wonder ifhe knows you can't
just pay a fine if you murder someone.
# [Background: Dance]
Dude, she's all over you.
What are you doing?
Whoo! Look at this, baby!
- Monte Gold?
- Uh-oh. Grown-ups with badges.
- Lloyd?
- Hi, um, I'm Monte's producer, Lloyd.
We've got shooting permits
and signed waivers.
- You know this girl?
- [Brennan] She's on your Web site.
And a thousand more. Might as well ask
a Chinese guy to remember a grain of rice.
- She's not a grain of rice, sport.
- She's dead.
Eddie, off!
Cameras off!
- Go away, babies. Shoo. Let's go.
- [Girls] Aw.
- What do you mean dead?
- Her name's Judy Dowd.
We found her in Florida raped,
murdered, and fed to an alligator.
And she's posted on my Web site?
Lloyd, do you know about this?
- How would I know?
- Get her off. Now, Lloyd.
- Now! Go!
- All right, all right.
You say an alligator?
[Lloyd]
We never would've posted her if we knew.
- Monte is insanely careful.
- Not always, from what I hear.
But he learns from his mistakes.
Now every I.D. triple-checked for 18
before any girl signs the waiver.
- Idiot! You let her on my bus?
- I didn't want to be rude.
Off the bus.
Your boyfriend has no warrant.
You know, anthropologically speaking,
you follow a very ancient tradition.
Okay. Entrepreneur?
- Pimp.
- Class is over. Off the bus.
Here you go.
Follow his path. Learn his word.
You, too.
Uh-oh. There it is! Another misguided waif
tumbles from the devil's sin-mobile!
- Excuse me?
- Uh, no. She's with me.
Why are you winking?
I'm not with... He's with me.
This is Isaac. Isaac's with The Church of
the High Calling from way down in Eldon, Kansas.
Yeah. But let me tell you something.
There is no distance too great...
to dissuade these lost young women from
the grips of Monte Gold's carnal temptation.
[Brennan] Looks like you plan on
saving a lot of souls.
- [Sully] Women like this?
- Oh. Uh-oh.
Who is she? Huh?
What did Monte do to her?
- [Monte] Give it a rest, Isaac.
- Monte? Hey.
Hey, remember me? I'm Alan.
I sent you, uh, my résumé.
- Not now, man.
- Hey, hey, look. I'm a great webmaster.
- Another sinner about to throw
hisself into Satan's hellfire.
- Shut up, freak!
[Grunts]
You come back, I call the cops.
Get him out of here.
- You'll never work for me, pal.
- [Girl] What's that about?
God even fed you today, Isaac?
Okay, let's get you a sandwich.
- Eddie, make the preacher some food, will ya?
- Yeah.
What? The wing nuts
come with the territory.
All right. Let's quit playing games.
What is it you want to know?
- Fort Lauderdale.
- Lauderdale was Lauderdale.
Partied that night. Gave some
willing girls their 15 minutes of fame...
and, uh, headed out to Daytona
for the next day's gig.
- Any girls ride with you?
- As much as I hate to disappoint you...
uh, fact is, I'm not entertaining
like I used to.
Ah. Getting too old to exploit
little drunk girls?
You seen the videos?
They exploit themselves.
- Ready to roll when you are, Monte.
- [Clicks Tongue] Yeah.
Now they all want to be
a Hotty Body.
Walk into a place and the shirts fly off,
making what used to be a rush kinda...
I don't know, mundane.
Because you objectify them.
You never see what makes them human.
[Scoffs]
Man, you have to spend all day with her?
Yeah. An actual woman.
You oughta try it sometime.
Video's off the site.
There's a copy of the girl's waiver.
You know, I think I, uh...
I think I remember this girl.
- You do?
- Yeah. You remember, Lloyd.
We were leaving
the Lauderdale gig...
and you made a joke about
the bouncer swapping spit with that girl?
- That was this girl?
- Pretty sure.
Oh, she was hot.
Passed the two of them
playing tonsil hockey in the doorway.
That bouncer was a big dude too.
- And it's me you're harassing?
- [Lloyd] Let's go, Eddie.
This waiver is a joke.
I mean, look atJudy's signature.
She could barely hold a pen.
Well, Florida Bureau's gonna
scoop up this bouncer and call me back.
- We need to get back in that bus.
- Well, we need cause for a warrant.
You tell Mario
that he is still an artist.
- Sure thing.
- What is that?
Mmm!
Only the finest
sausage and peppers on earth.
Someday, I'm gonna turn it
into a franchise. You want a bite?
I thought you were buying a boat.
I am. Well, maybe
I'll start a charter service.
I can serve these to the passengers,
you know? In Jamaica.
- Good.
- Mmm, the word is great.
Or maybe I'll manage a band, you know?
They could play on the boat too.
So you don't...
You don't like being an F.B.I. agent?
Oh, sure. l-I do. I just don't want it
to be the only thing I ever was.
[Chuckles]
You're telling me you're just gonna be
a bone lady your whole life?
I spent years
studying anthropology.
Well, I got a degree.
But I'm not gonna let it ruin my life.
- I'm going back to the lab.
- Mmm, here!
Take one of these with you
back to that spaceship.
I'll call you when
we get our bouncer.
Mmm, mmm.
Mmm, Jamaica.
I can dig it, man.
- Oh.
- Hi.
Um, do we have a schedule?
Uh, listen.
I really need to get back to work.
So why don't you give me one of those clown
restraining orders and just sign my paper?
- Have you had an insight then as
to why you shot at that clown?
- Yeah.
- You know what?
I have some insight. It's right here.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
That's my Bones calling, huh?
My partner. Right? Yeah. Bones.
So when are you
coming back again?
What? Aren't you
playing nice with Sully?
- I'm not sure how serious he is about his job.
- Look.
He's one of the best.
He just likes to keep his options open.
- I've noticed.
- Listen, Bones.
Sully, he, uh, lost his partner
about, uh, a year ago. All right?
Something like that happens,
you just...
You hear that clock on the inside
ticking just a little bit louder.
So, uh, you know what?
You're in good hands.
Here he comes.
So I gotta go. Gotta go.
Hey. All right, so maybe
I am a little irritable.
Why do you think
that might be?
Come on. Look, don't they give you,
like, papers and files and reports and...
All right. Um...
[Exhales]
Me and my partner caught up to this serial killer
by the name of Howard Epps, and he died.
And whose fault was that?
Yours or your partner's?
Oh, no. He jumped over that balcony
because of her.
[Chuckles] Sometimes
I think he had the right idea.
And where were you when Mr. Epps fell?
Holding his arm.
- No, that was before he fell, surely.
- What?
Well, Mr. Epps was dangling
from your arm before he fell.
At which point, he was
no longer dangling, but falling.
Attached to you, he was alive.
No longer attached, dead.
Well, I don't feel guilty about that.
I mean, Epps is a serial killer.
He tried to kill my partner,
and he threatened my son.
I was glad
when he hit that pavement.
Do you think about suicide
often?
Suicide? Me?
No, no. Never.
And yet, you sometimes feel that Howard Epps
had the right idea about jumping off that balcony?
It was a joke. Okay?
It was a joke.
Yes. You do that a lot,
don't you?
Makes me feel such a bully
for prying.
Well, we'll pick up on this
next time.
[Scoffs]
Increase magnification,
please, if you're ready.
- I don't mean to appear dictatorial...
- I get it, Zack.
- Hey.
- So what are we looking at?
Bits of gold foil embedded deep within
bite marks along the T11 and T12 vertebrae.
Jewelry?
More likely scenario has the gator's teeth
piercing Judy's stomach.
Embedding whatever
she last ingested into her bone.
How would someone eat gold?
Not eat. Drink.
- Goldenrod.
- Goldenrod?
It's this hundred-proof cinnamon schnapps
that we drank in college.
It's infused with real gold flakes,
purely for decadence' sake.
How did it taste?
Oh. It's way worse coming up,
I can tell you that.
She could've wandered into
bars we don't know about.
If we can find every place
that carries that stuff...
I don't think we'll need to, Doc.
We've got our bouncer.
Of course, he denies all.
But his alibi just about buries him.
- Buries him how?
- He left work early that night
to get to his other job...
giving midnight
swamp tours on his boat.
Sounds like a good job actually.
So, he's admitted to knowing the Everglades
like the back of his hand.
Which would not be smart
ifhe were, in fact, the killer.
Most of the killers I know
aren't all that smart.
The gold flakes are definitely from
the liquor we found in her system.
- And I remembered something.
- Monte and his harem. So what?
Check out the caption.
"All the girls love Monte's gold!"
Now, granted, there are plenty of bars
that carry this stuff. But...
But this could be the probable cause
we need to search Monte's bus.
- I'll get the warrant.
- [Phone Beeps]
Bouncer's alibi checked out.
So Monte's minions were likely
just trying to throw us off.
Unbelievable, you people.
What is it now?
Hey, hey, cool your jets, Hef.
We just want to search your bus.
- This is you, isn't it?
- Please don't point your finger at me.
I knew the first time I saw you...
here comes another feminist crusader
out to spoil some good, all-American fun.
Ow. Get off! Get off.
- It was self-defense. He assaulted me.
- Yes, he did.
Crazy bitch.
I'm calling my lawyer.
Here. You can read him this.
Now I just hope we find something.
[Laughing On Television]
- There.
- Well, it's not exactly a smoking gun.
- Can you prove she drank it here?
- I can try.
Okay. You can only admit evidence
that's in plain view.
Although on this bus, that could be
D.N.A. on virtually any surface.
That's an image.
Keep your eyes open
for a metal screw-threaded thingy.
- A what now?
- Judy's stab wound was probably
from a bolt of some kind...
right through... here.
Oh, just inside her scapula.
Yes. But most laymen
refer to it as a shoulder blade.
Well, I told you I went to college.
I minored in kinesiology, although this is
the first time I've used it to impress a lady.
[Both Chuckle]
- What was your major?
- Art history.
I also got a master's certificate in sailing...
a pilot's license, and I'm a certified E.M.T.
There's more,
but I don't want to brag.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
- Hold on.
- Hi, Hodgins.
- Judy Dowd wasn't killed at
the swamp where she was found.
Cryptosporidium on her clothes
came from saw grass...
a plant that doesn't even
grow in Eugene's swamp.
- Where does it grow?
- Well, pretty much everywhere
else in the Everglades.
But in terms of gator distance,
there's a saw grass marsh two miles south...
where Alligator Alley
meets State Road 29.
All that from cryptosporidium?
Did I not mention
the fresh asphalt in Judy's shoe?
That intersection was just repaved
about a month ago.
[Brennan]
Very interesting.
- Thanks, Hodgins.
- Hmm? What's interesting?
Miss Montenegro?
I'm Bill Dowd, Judy's father.
Oh. Hi.
Um, I'm sorry.
How do you know me?
The F.B.I. told me that theJeffersonian
was investigating Judy's murder.
I read your team's biographies online,
saw your picture.
- And you followed me here?
- I'm sorry. I know how that must look.
But I just... need answers.
I need to know
who killed my daughter.
I'm sorry, Mr. Dowd.
There's nothing I can tell you.
I already know about the Web site...
and this Monte Gold son of a bitch.
The F.B.I. told you about that?
A buddy from my job
found the video.
He thought I'd be embarrassed,
but all I care about is what happened next.
Did this guy kill her?
I really can't discuss the case.
The way he's pawing at my girl
on that video, he's gotta be a suspect.
At-At this point, Mr. Dowd,
there are a lot of suspects.
But not many like him.
I mean, do you trust him?
Do you think he's a good man?
No. Of course not.
I find him repulsive.
Please. I just gotta know.
Was it him?
I'm very sorry about
your daughter, Mr. Dowd.
There's nothing I can say.
I understand.
I shouldn't have put you on the spot.
I'm sorry.
You lied about the bouncer, Eddie.
- What?
- The bouncer in Lauderdale.
You never saw him kissing Judy Dowd
the night she went missing.
Really? I was sure it was them.
- Uh, you drive the bus, too, don't you?
- Yeah, so?
So you drove out of Lauderdale,
straight up the 95 to Daytona?
Is that what Monte said?
- Yeah, straight up 95.
- You sure about that?
Oh. No, uh, that's right.
There was, uh, construction.
We got detoured
cross state on 75.
- Right, 75. Isn't that Alligator Alley?
- Mmm.
Come on, Eddie.
A girl is dead.
- We didn't kill her.
- But she was on your bus.
She had a few drinks.
You have sex with her?
No. No way.
I... was driving.
- While Monte had sex with her?
- I guess.
You guess?
Was-Was it consensual?
All I know is she was drunk,
all right? Really drunk.
And when Monte got done with her,
she came up by me wanting to get off the bus.
- Eddie, don't say anything!
- Where were you in all this?
- Lloyd drives in front of us.
It was me and Monte on the bus.
- Shut up, Eddie.
Monte's lawyer says that we don't have to
talk to anybody until he gets here.
He has nothing to worry about.
No one's under arrest.
Why'd you let her off the bus?
I didn't want to. It was really dark.
She could barely stand up.
- Then Monte wanted her off?
- He was pissed off. She was crying.
- Eddie!
- He was gonna fire me if I didn't.
We owe Monte a lot, okay?
The guy's been really good to us.
And we knew that
none of us killed her.
If you let her off the bus in the middle of nowhere
in that condition, you may as well have.
When Eddie told me where she got off
the bus, I went back and looked for her.
I must have driven that road for an hour.
I figured she hitched a ride back.
You figured? He figured.
Maybe Monte made a bad call
in letting the girl off.
But she wanted off.
So he was just doing what she asked.
- Except for the sex part.
- You know what? You can't prove that.
I wouldn't bet against her.
- So, is Monte still in his office?
- No.
He, uh, had an appointment
back at the Iguana Club up in Maryland.
Okay.
[Sighs]
You know what? I'm in America. We're men.
Let's drink coffee, not tea, eh?
Oh, I say.
- You're doing a marvelous job.
- Thank you.
[Exhales]
That's not coffee.
- Oh. What is it?
- I don't know what the hell it is,
but it sure isn't coffee.
You tend to do things well,
don't you?
- Make coffee, build barbecue machines.
- It's not really a machine.
Solve crimes, raise a son,
love women, leave women.
Whatever you aim at,
you hit.
- Is that bad?
- By no means. No, of course not.
- Except...
- Oh, yeah, okay. Here we go.
Let me have it, Doc.
Except it is indicative of a need
to control your environment.
Again, I ask, uh, is that bad?
No, of course not.
No. Except...
- Except?
- Except when you shoot a clown.
You know, you make it sound like he was
walking around making balloon animals.
For the most part,
your rebellions are small.
- Rebellions?
- Mmm, the colorful socks, the funky belt buckle.
They're a mechanism.
Quiet rebellions.
A way of asserting
your personal control...
over a homogenizing organization
like the F.B.I.
But shooting a clown
is not a quiet rebellion.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
- Shooting a clown is, quite literally, deafening.
- Booth.
- [Brennan] Hey, it's me.
Hold on. Why is it every time
I answer the phone, you walk away?
Why do you answer the phone
knowing it'll make me walk away?
Yeah, you know what?
Bones, I gotta call you back.
Well, I... Is...
Is Sully for real?
- What?
- I just can't decide whether or not
to take him seriously.
- Is he acting unprofessional?
- No. He's... He's very professional.
It's just... Can he really do
all he says he can do?
Oh, you mean that whole
master carpentry thing, yeah.
- What?
- Well, he made me a dining room set last year.
- He's a carpenter as well?
- As well as what?
- [Beeping]
- That's Sully calling right now.
We're, um... We're doing,
you know, what we did.
- You know, I'll be back soon.
- Okay.
- I'll talk to you later.
- [Beeps]
So maybe Monte can tell us why
he left the girl on the side of the road.
Hey, there's a storefront.
Sausage and pepper shop?
That's funny. Take my lead.
- I know what I'm doing. Didn't Booth tell you?
- Yeah. Take my lead.
Wait, wait, wait.
That's his car.
Monte Gold?
[Sully] We found him in a pool of
his own blood outside his club.
It's the last thing
you said to Monte, Isaac.
"His judgment cometh
and that right soon."
That's not even a Bible verse,
the judgment thing.
- It's a line from Shawshank.
- Who's that?
"Vengeance is mine," saith the Lord.
Look, if Monte's wicked deeds
cost him his life...
it was the work of a hand
far mightier than my own.
And where exactly have your hands been
the last five hours?
Working on my truck.
I got garage receipts to prove it.
- [Phone Rings]
- [Beeps]
- Hey, Angela, what's up?
- Hey. I, uh...
- I think that you might have the wrong man.
- What do you mean?
I made a mistake, Brennan.
I only wanted to scare him.
I didn't go there to kill him.
But what he said.
Three words.
He only said three words in his defense.
"She wanted it."
She didn't, Mr. Dowd.
That much we do know.
Is there anyone
you want to call, sir?
No. There isn't anybody.
[Sighs]
There was Judy.
JustJudy.
So this is the culprit, huh? The result
of your metal screw-headed thingy?
Zack managed to identify
this bone bruise.
Across posterior
six through eight.
- Show off.
- Okay.
I've got my weapons list and visual aids,
courtesy of Angela.
Now, we know the wound was caused by a blunt
steel dowel with screw threads at the top.
The bruising around it is the rough
size and shape of a harmonica.
Theoretically, the head of the wound struck,
leaving the bruising, but then broke.
Allowing the steel dowel beneath
to be driven intoJudy's back.
So possible weapons include...
shovel handle with a steel shaft...
- a golfer's wooden putter with aluminum shaft.
- Okay. A gear shifter?
It's an alloy gear shifter
with a grip-shaped handle.
This doesn't look like
it could cause the injury.
Unless it didn't have a handle.
Yeah. Though she probably would not
have been killed standing up.
She'd have to have been
thrown down and then impaled.
Preacher man had one of these
in his truck.
With a tennis ball
where the handle should've been...
hiding the exposed threads
underneath.
And he follows Monte everywhere.
[Police Radio Chatter]
Don't let us interrupt you, Isaac.
I was praying for his guidance
in bringing an end to this harassment.
- Well, he can't answer them all, can he?
- I'm tired of...
- Where were you headed?
- Home. If that's any of your business.
Back to your church, huh?
I gotta tell ya.
I wish I'd have called them
a little sooner.
- You did this? You called them?
- Yeah. You sure you weren't
headed back to Florida?
Stop along Alligator Alley,
make sure you left nothing behind?
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
Well, apparently your church kicked
your hypocritical ass out last year.
Something about you hitting on
young female parishioners.
Who-Who-Who... Who told you this, huh?
Hey, you can't get in there.
- Tennis ball for a gear shifter.
- Huh.
- Turn around, Isaac.
- All right.
Forgive them, Lord,
for they know not what they do.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what we do know...
is thatJudy Dowd was left
drunk and stumbling on Route 75.
And you, following Monte's bus,
pulled over to give her a ride.
Not a free one apparently.
No, no. That's a lie.
I never even saw her.
Oh, so this isn't her blood here?
It's someone's blood.
How many of Monte's castoffs
have you been with?
Huh? Girls too drunk to know?
- Before you picked upJudy?
- You went for it. She rejected you.
Next thing you know,
she's impaled on the shifter.
I may have picked her up.
But if I laid a hand, it was to heal
and to ask his redemption upon her.
Oh, man. You are shameless.
She was drunk. She went crazy.
Pushed me away and fell back.
It was an accident.
You know, the devil's work.
No. No. That was the part
where you fed her to an alligator.
There should be a sense of satisfaction
after solving a case.
But... most of the time,
I just... I feel drained.
Yeah. That's why you can only
do this job for so long.
Murders, death, corpses.
You do that
your whole life and...
There's gotta be more,
you know?
The sausage and pepper sandwich.
You gotta admit,
it was good.
[Both Chuckle]
So what do you and Booth
usually do now?
Is there a bar you go to?
A restaurant? Pilates class?
- There's a diner.
- Ah.
Booth says the pie is the best.
- Can I buy you a slice?
- Sure.
- I guess we're not working together anymore.
- Yes.
And since we have no professional
obligations to each other...
I can ask you out...
theoretically.
Theoretically.
- Perhaps after a 24-hour waiting period.
- Why?
So the brain can adjust
to alternate perceptions of each other.
I don't actually need it.
My brain adjusts quite quickly.
[Sighs]
[Chuckles]
- Oh, my good Lord.
- That's right.
How many bricks
did you use in the end?
Yep. You know, 180.
Right? So you can go sign away.
- What are those?
- Oh, those are two beautiful prime rib-eye steaks.
All right, being the barbecue master that I am,
I thought I'd show you how to barbecue, Doc.
Oh, but I don't want to be shown.
I want to learn by trial and error.
No, no, no, Doc. Come on, listen.
It's better to learn off of
hamburgers or sausages.
You know, those puppies
cost 50 bucks a pop.
Hmm. You know,
according to the F.B.I. reports...
there was no way you
could save Epps's life.
Your partner's report
says the same thing.
An F.B.I. sniper on the opposite roof
saw everything through his scope.
According to all witnesses,
you have nothing to feel guilty about.
Yeah, so?
So, why, in a fit of pique...
did you endanger innocent people in a public
thoroughfare by discharging your firearm?
[Lid Closes]
I'm a good shot.
I didn't put anybody in danger.
How many people have you killed?
Lost count.
Oh, you can remember 180 bricks,
but not how many lives you've taken?
- Epps makes 50.
- Fifty what?
- Fifty kills.
- But, Agent Booth, you didn't kill Epps.
You tried to save him, remember?
Or perhaps I'd better
put it as a question.
Did Howard Epps slip from your grasp,
or did you release him?
Oh, come now, man.
It's a simple-enough question.
Was he indeed
your 50th kill?
Or did you just happen
to be there when he died?
I don't know.
A man like you, in control
of every situation, and you don't know?
I don't know. I...
I had him,
and then I lost him.
And-And... something happened
in between.
I don't know.
I believe you.
Because for a man like you to admit
you don't know, to relinquish control...
that could indeed argue
a disruption in your self-view...
that was large enough
to motivate you to shoot a clown.
[Inhales] Do you know?
I think we made marvelous progress.
This is a place from which
we can certainly begin.
You know what?
I've changed my mind.
I would love you
to cook those steaks.
[Exhales]
I can do that.
Medium rare,
please, Mr. G-man.
I can do that.
What's that mean?