- [Booth] So, you ever been here before?
- [Brennan] No.
No, I don't mean here here.
I mean Baltimore.
[Brennan] Yeah, I've given several lectures
to the Baltimore Homicide Division.
- [Groans] God.
- What's wrong with your mouth?
- I got a tooth situation.
- Well, go to a dentist.
l-I will, if it doesn't get
any better. Ow. Man.
- Are you afraid of the dentist?
- I'm not afraid of the...
- Welcome to Baltimore.
This is a federal flood abatement project,
which is why we called you.
K-9 unit was usin' it for an exercise,
and one of the cadaver dogs went berserk.
- We dug up the cement...
- [Brennan] No, that's concrete.
Cement is an ingredient in concrete.
Yeah, that's a real important distinction
to make at this juncture.
So, what do we got, Bones, huh?
Do your thing.
- Nothing.
- Nothin'. Nothin'?
No, I can't see enough of the skull,
the tibia, the pubis...
- Nothing.
- Nothing? Wait a second. Nothing... Sorry.
Now we drove all the way here
so you could just tell me, "Nothing"?
All right, so what do you want me to do?
Uh, get the whole slab of cement...
- Concrete.
- Concrete. Whatever...
shipped back to theJeffersonian?
Yes. Yes.
- Sex?
- The mandible suggests male...
and the tibia suggests
he was between 5'6" and six feet tall.
Waffle-soled training shoes
and a tracksuit.
- You know who wears tracksuits?
- Athletes?
- No. Huge tubs of lard or retired people.
- [Chuckles] And rap stars.
- The teeth suggest early middle age.
- So, not a retiree.
Uh, calcified holes with radial fractures
in the left clavicle and scapula...
are consistent
with ballistic damage.
- He was shot to death?
- And stabbed, but neither killed him.
The wounds healed.
Shot, stabbed, but lived to die another day?
Rap star.
There's a small hole
in the back of the cranium.
Dig the skull out first
to establish cause of death...
then give Angela something
to work with to I.D. the guy.
Where is Angela?
I'm really not good at this kind of thing,
you know? I don't...
[Sighs]
I don't get the significance.
One year ago today,
you buried your mother.
You laid her to rest... here.
You're marking the anniversary.
- [Sighs]
- Angela, I...
simply don't believe my mother
retained sentience beyond death.
- Well, part of you is made up
of your mother, right?
- In a manner of speaking.
So honor that part of yourself.
Visualize a memory of her.
See what it brings up.
I have very few distinct memories
of my mother.
I'll wait in the car.
[Exhales]
Hiya, honey.
I was hopin' you might show up.
- [Beeping]
- I don't...
I don't want to talk to you.
You're standing here
in front of your mother's grave.
Obviously you've come
for some kind of answer.
Maybe I can provide 'em.
You're a killer.
You burn people.
Yeah. I'd like to report a sighting
of Max Keenan...
at Eternal Spring Memorial Gardens.
- He's a wanted fugitive.
- [Quietly] I love you.
Yes, I'm sure.
Because he's my father.
- Did you talk to your dad at all
before you called the cops?
- No. Why would I?
Well, I haven't seen my dad
in a long time, and...
if I had the opportunity to talk...
Ow. God.
- Go to a dentist.
- Well, I will if it doesn't get any better.
[Zack]
Based on decomposition of the tracksuit...
Hodgins is estimating
a postmortem interval of two years.
- Based on bone deterioration, I like three years.
- Well, what killed him?
The victim was dead shortly after this hole
was punched into his skull.
Hmm. Too small for a projectile.
- No radiating stress lines.
- A slow entry. A piercing wound.
Like a... a screwdriver?
Nail gun? Ice pick?
- Yeah, something along those lines.
- [Beeping]
- Cold steel in the brain... Would that kill him?
- Depending how far it penetrated.
Yeah, it's Booth.
I need, um, all murders in which...
a penetrating wound
to the back of the head figured.
- Great. Thanks.
- [Beeps, Closes]
- [Max] Don't freak out.
- Oh!
You broke into my house?
That is not acceptable.
- This, uh, little device here...
- [Phone Beeping]
- It jams cell phone frequencies.
- [Static]
- That is illegal.
- Unfortunately, illegal is what I do best.
I'm not staying.
I just want you to do something for me.
- I want you to take a look at my rap sheet.
- Why?
Why? Because I want a chance
to talk to you...
actually talk to you...
without you calling in the 82nd Airborne.
How is reading your police record
going to change my mind?
- [Door Closes]
- Just do it.
I think our victim
was killed by Ice Pick.
Angela did a facial reconstruction
of Cement Head.
- "Concrete Head," you mean.
- No, "Cement Head." It's got a nicer ring.
So I ran it through Interplus,
and I got a match.
"William Raymond 'Billy Ray' McKenna,
West Virginia.
"Assault, manslaughter, kidnapping...
- torture"...
- This here?
This here is, uh, Hugh Kennedy.
- Uh, I think he killed Cement Head.
- Why?
Well, West Virginia,
likes to use an ice pick on his victims...
plus Ice Pick and Cement Head
were both employed...
by a regional crime boss
from West Virginia...
named Gallagher.
- Well, what are we gonna call him?
- "Gallagher."
What, he runs most of the, uh,
prostitutes, strippers...
gambling, bootlegging, meth, extortion
in West Virginia.
Five years ago,
the West Virginia state police...
began pressuring Gallagher's criminal operation,
making a lot of arrests.
Including Ice Pick and Cement Head.
Cement Head goes to jail.
- Ice Pick? Out on bail, babe.
- You say that like it means something.
I talked to the officer in charge,
and he said that Ice Pick wouldn't say anything...
so they punished him
by lettin' him out on bail.
- How is bail punishment?
- 'Cause it makes Gallagher think...
that Ice Pick cooperated
with the cops.
Ah, it's criminal psychology,
Bones, you know?
You wouldn't get it. Just... read.
Just continue reading there, will ya?
Half-a-million-dollar bond.
Kennedy jumped bail.
Hmm. Killed in a car accident while fleeing
a"bail fugitive recovery agent."
- Bounty hunter.
- Car burned the remains to ashes.
All they got was a severed leg.
They didn't actually get Ice Pick's body.
So, we gonna talk
to the bounty hunter?
No, I am. You're gonna make sure that
that severed leg actually belonged to Ice Pick.
- Someone kept the leg?
- The severed leg was frozen as evidence.
So... you think Ice Pick
might still be alive.
As a friend of mine likes to say,
"Don't jump to conclusions...
until all the evidence is in."
But if the facts are in, then it's not jumping
to conclusions. So I never said that.
I never said that the friend is you, okay?
[Strains]
Does it have to be completely thawed
for you to examine?
No. My interest lies only in the femur.
I need to get some tissue
for D.N.A. testing.
- [People Chattering]
- [Cash Register Rings]
Mmm.
I'm the bounty hunter you want to talk to...
Veleska Miller.
You wanna know about Kennedy's leg?
Anything you wanna tell me
outside the official report, that's great.
Sure... how it smelled,
his body cooking over the fire.
Otherwise, I stand by the record.
How'd you find him?
Tip from someone I know
who provides documents to fugitives.
Tailed him. He made me, took off.
Boom.
Found his leg about 30 yards
from the vehicle.
And you saw him burn?
Yeah. Why?
- [Sighs]
- That's it?
That's it.
I'm a little disappointed.
I was hoping you'd keep me here a while,
ask me some dumb-ass federal questions...
check me out.
How's about I buy you
a nice breakfast then?
[Cash Register Rings]
A guy like you
must be going crazy in the F.B.I.
What kind of guy is that exactly?
[Chuckles] I'm a bounty hunter, sport.
I read people fast or I die.
You are not standard
government-issue.
Take a walk on the wild side.
I have more fun, fewer rules
and a lotta money.
- You know, you make a compelling case.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
- [Beeps]
- Booth.
Coroner's report said Kennedy's leg
was severed in the car accident.
We don't call him "Kennedy."
We call him "Ice Pick."
Hold on for one second.
Sorry.
Yeah... Ah.
Listen, I got the, uh, bounty hunter here.
She was an eyewitness to the crash,
saw him incinerated.
Tell Booth that Ice Pick's femur
is sliced cleanly at 90 degrees.
I can hear you, Bones, okay?
It's a speakerphone.
Look, amputation like that
could happen in a bad wreck. Right, Cam?
- [Saroyan] Yes.
- [Brennan] Well, there are kerf marks.
- [Saroyan] She's seeing evidence of a saw, Booth.
- I know what kerf marks are.
Booth should arrest
the bounty hunter.
I can hear you, Bones.
What am I gonna arrest her for, huh?
For lying. For perjury.
For aiding in a cover-up.
[Saroyan]
If she's there with you, just detain her.
- [Honks Horn]
- Okay.
I'll let you know how that works out.
Hey, huh? Look at that, huh?
D.N.A. is a match.
West Virginia state troopers
got a D.N.A. sample at Ice Pick's arrest.
This is definitely his leg.
Was she pretty?
Ice Pick is a male.
I mean, the bounty hunter
who gave Booth the slip.
- You know, she didn't get away
'cause she was pretty.
- She was a she?
- No, she was a... Oh, God.
- What's wrong with your mouth?
I'm guessing the anterior molar
on the left side is infected.
The leg was surgically amputated.
- Go to a dentist.
- He's afraid of the dentist.
These kerf marks are consistent with a type
of wire saw used to remove horns from heifers.
Ah, so Ice Pick and his bounty hunter
set up a car accident...
with a dummy victim
so everyone stops lookin' for him.
Two years later, he kills Conc...
Cement head.
She hoodwinked you
'cause she was hot.
Look, you know what? She wasn't hot.
In fact, she looked like a man.
The amputation was probably performed
by a livestock veterinarian.
- Hey, Bones, I got that other thing
you want to discuss.
- Oh. Let's...
go to my office so...
we don't disturb Cam.
Booth... livestock amputation? That is one tough,
determined old criminal. Be careful.
- You know, I was goin' through your father's crim...
- [Brennan] Shh!
[Quietly] criminal record,
and he was right about one thing.
- He never ended anyone's life
who didn't have it comin' to 'em.
- He's a sociopath.
Well, maybe, but at least he aimed
in the right direction.
- Ow! God!
- Let me take a look at your tooth.
All right. Just... go easy.
You promise?
- Okay.
- All right?
- Open up.
- [Mumbling]
- What?
- In the Old West,
he would have been considered a hero.
- Yeah, well, the Old West was a time of chaos...
- Ow!
- Uh!
- and violence that, anthropologically speaking...
- our country is still trying to recover from.
- [Groaning]
Yeah. I was right.
Anterior molar on the left side... It's infected.
Your father never killed any hardworkin',
tax-paying citizens or honest cops.
- Ow.
- You still think that society should forgive him?
I'm saying, if I have an opportunity
to arrest him, I will.
But you know who maybe
should forgive him?
- His daughter.
- [Cell Phone Beeping]
Oh. Look at that.
Our small-town crime boss is here.
Let's go have a little chat with him,
shall we?
Billy Ray McKenna
shortly before he became "Cement Head."
- I like nicknames.
They're universal mnemonic devices.
- Why are we doing this?
Don't we know that cause of death
was brain scrambling due to an ice pick?
The technical term is "pithing."
And it's not how he died.
It entered the medullary pyramids...
and bevelling on the entry site
suggests it was...
I don't believe there's an English word
that adequately describes...
- "Wiggling." Up and down is "wiggling."
- Okay...
wiggled, thus paralyzing the victim
and causing some difficulty breathing.
- But he would live for upwards of several hours.
- Smart.
Very little blood spilled.
How did the victim die?
Ugh, this is the bad part.
It appears that the concrete
was poured over him while he was still alive.
Oh, God.
These chunks of concrete
are in the shape of...
a sinus cavity...
bronchial tubes...
plus a kind of a hollow
around the middle finger.
You said he was paralyzed.
Well, if the ice pick was inserted
and then waggled...
it would affect the median nerve
and the T1 nerve roots.
Which control the flexor carpi radialis.
Anterior palm, thumb, index
and middle fingers.
- But if it was...
- Wiggled...
the victim would lose the ability to move
the ring and pinkie fingers.
We think he wiggled
instead of waggled.
Because he could still move
his middle finger.
It's a terrible way to die.
Our conclusion is that he was trying
to swim to the surface...
using only his middle finger.
The last time I saw Billy Ray McKenna,
he was "So long, suckering" me...
from his F-150 and headin' off
on a well-earned vacation.
Well-earned by torturing a journalist
who was talkin' too much.
Well, I resent your inference.
Get 'em my, uh... what-you-call-it...
tax papers, employment records.
- Did I get that right?
- Not quite.
You resent his implication.
He is implying that you're a criminal.
You're taking the inference
from his implication.
Uh, according to this,
Mr. Lightner is your flight instructor.
That is correct.
I have, uh, wide-rangin' enterprises.
Clark here is helpful
in gettin' me where I gotta get.
And William Raymond McKenna
is down as a media liaison.
Yep, by breakin'journalists' fingers.
You know, you never asked me
about, uh, Billy Ray McKenna there, big dog.
[Chuckles] Well, I assume, big dog,
that Billy Ray is deceased.
- Why?
- He was a valued employee.
Disappears for three years,
I gotta assume the worst.
His body was found
encased in concrete.
[Sighs] Tell you what. We're gonna claim
his remains. We'll bury him proper.
- Where'd you send him on vacation?
- Canada.
- Was it the mounties that found Billy Ray
encased in cement?
- Concrete.
- Hmm?
Not cement.
It's a common error.
- Baltimore police.
- Is Baltimore on the way to Canada?
Well, the most efficient route
is up through Detroit...
but Billy Ray...
how he loved Vermont so.
Do you have any idea
who might want to kill Mr. McKenna?
[Chuckles]
- Oh, well, yeah. He, uh...
Well, how would you put it?
- Aggressive...
both socially and sexually.
How about Hugh Kennedy?
- Hugh Kennedy.
- Yeah... handy with the ice pick.
According to this,
you hired him as...
a "liquor license consultant"
on a per-case basis.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. I remember.
Taciturn type, very dour.
Right. In jail for murder once,
manslaughter twice...
and suspect in four unsolved murders
all involving ice picks.
You know, good old Hugh
did not put none of that on his résumé.
If I recall, Mr. Kennedy was killed in a car accident
fleeing a bail enforcement officer.
Guess he got burned up.
Well...[Sighs] you guys look us up
if you're ever in western West Virginia.
- We're at Snackie's Roadhouse and Grill.
- Where the 119 hits the 64.
I'll make a note of that.
119 hits the...
- 64.
[Knocking]
[Lock Rattling]
Hey, T, look. Snickerdoodles.
What are y...
Oh, come on.
You used to love 'em...
when you were a little girl.
I got a message for you
from your brother.
What message?
Uh, he says, um...
He says hi.
Have you turned Russ
into a criminal too?
Hey, I haven't committed a crime
in over 15 years. I'm straight.
Except for killing, gutting and burning
the deputy director of the F.B.I.
He was tryin' to kill Russ,
and then he was going after you.
It is not a crime
to protect your family.
Well, some fathers do it
without killing.
- Did, uh, you and Booth
take a look at my, uh, rap sheet?
- Yes.
- And?
- He'll arrest you if he has the chance.
What else?
[Paper Bag Crinkles]
So, these snickerdoodles...
Come on. You don't remember?
You loved them as a little girl.
I don't remember.
I'd come home, and then you'd be jumpin' around.
You were five or six years old.
You'd say, " Why don't you put on the 'trying song'?
Put on the 'trying song."'
- The "trying song"?
- It was my favorite song.
I used to sing it.
It was, uh, by Poco? The band?
# I've been thinkin' about all
the things you told me #
# I know you're full of doubt
Cannot let it be #
# But I know, if you keep on
comin' back for more #
# Then I'll keep tryin' #
# I'll keep on tryin' #
It's a good song.
[Max]
Hugh Kennedy...bad guy. But he's dead...
about five years ago in a car crash
in West Virginia.
Recent evidence suggests otherwise.
How do you know him?
Well, him and his ice pick were, uh,
pretty famous in some circles. I gotta go.
- Now?
- Yeah, you speed-dialed Booth.
Now he's been listening to everything,
and the... the SWAT team's on its way.
I mean, I'm just guessing.
But there is somethin'
I do want to say to you.
- Mom.
- It's not about Mom.
It's about you. And it's about stuff
that she wanted you to know.
She never got the chance
to tell you.
[Pats Hand]
Hey, Booth, there's a couple of things
that you should know about this guy Kennedy.
He's got an addiction
to model airplanes.
Try some of these again.
You'll love 'em.
[Drops Bag]
Wait. Dad, what's...
- What's the second thing?
- Mmm. He's wily.
You be careful, okay?
Did you get that?
[Small Engines Buzzing In Distance]
- [Whirring]
- [Engine Puttering]
Well, I gotta tell you,
you're right, Zack.
Every model airplane freak
from Baltimore is here.
- We prefer the term "pilots."
- Yeah. Okay, so you're into this stuff too, huh?
Forensic anthropology is only one of
my doctorates. The other is in applied engineering.
- I'm extremely adept at practical aeronautics.
- Do you see Ice Pick?
A lot of these guys are kinda old.
You know, they're wearin' those, uh...
those sunglasses that wrap around their heads?
Well, how many of them
only have one leg?
Well, half of them are sittin' down.
Okay, how am I gonna get them to stand up?
- Crashes bring everyone to their feet.
- Shoot down one of the planes.
That's great, huh? Next thing you know,
I'm being evaluated by my shrink again.
- That's not gonna happen.
- Drive onto the field.
- What?
- Put your car where they like to land.
Everyone will stand up
and yell at you.
- [Sighs] This better work.
- [Shifts Gears]
Now just stay with me here.
- Oops. [Chuckles]
- Look at that guy!
Look at that, huh?
It seems to be workin'. Ha-ha.
- Ooh, they're mad.
- [Shouting, Protesting Continues]
- Do you see him?
- They're all wearin' long pants.
I mean, how could I tell if any of'em
are wearing a prosthetic?
The prosthetic will cause
a slightly unnatural alignment of the spine...
which will result in
a compensating adjustment of...
Booth, the instinct will be for these men
to step toward you.
One man will be standing
perfectly still.
[All Chattering, Muttering]
- [Man] Aw, forget him.
- [Man #2] Get off your phone!
Okay.
Yep, I got him.
Sorry. Apologize.
Just passing through.
- Afternoon.
- Anybody askin' after me?
Nope.
[Elevator Door Clatters, Closes]
[Elevator Motor Starts]
- What the hell?
- I'm gonna need his room number.
Maybe I can help you.
- [Clattering]
- What'd you... What'd you hit me with?
Huh? Only reason I ask, 'cause my tooth...
It doesn't hurt anymore.
You know, you're the first guy
that's got the drop on me in 10 years.
Yeah, I used to get that a lot.
Can I ask you a question?
As long as you answer one for me then.
Yeah, so what... what happened to you
three years ago, huh? What's your story?
[Drawer Closes]
Billy Ray got in the back of my cab.
Don't know which one of us
was bigger surprised, but...
must have been Billy Ray,
'cause he's the one that ended up dead.
[Booth]
Okay, what's your question?
- [Cartoon Plays On TV]
- How you people find him under all that cement?
A dog.
- A dog, huh?
- Yeah. So why am I not dead?
I never killed nobody for fun.
It was my job.
And I'm retired.
Now listen. I know you fellas get in trouble
if you lose your gun.
- I'm takin' the bullets, though, if you don't mind.
- Whoa!
- Oh. Well, what about me?
- Settle down.
- Wha...
- Settle down. Relax.
[Muffled Chattering]
- Someone'll find you.
- [Muffled Protesting]
- You have a good day now.
- [Muffled Protesting Continues]
- [Door Closes]
- [Muffled Chattering]
[Body Hits Floor, Muffled Yelp]
I just want to talk about your mother.
Booth is missing.
It's been over 18 hours.
He tried to take down Hugh Kennedy
by himself?
He's only got one leg, and he's old.
Yeah.
You know how he got old?
By bein' fast and paranoid.
He cut off his own leg.
- Booth is tough.
- What does the F.B.I. say?
Nothing.
- Yeah. "Need to know," right?
- Mm-hmm.
I want to do something,
but I don't...
I don't know what.
Are you asking?
You'd help find the man
who's going to put you in jail?
Well, Booth will...
will do the best he can.
I'll do the best I can, and we'll see
how it works out when we get there.
Wh-Where did he find Kennedy?
Baltimore.
[Muffled]
Ow. God!
I'm afraid that's not Hugh Kennedy.
What's that called
when they wrap a sausage in a pancake?
- [Muffled] Pig in a blanket.
- Pigs in a blanket.
- [Spits]
- Now how'd you get here?
[Spits]
How'd you get here?
Um, Billy Ray was killed by an ice pick in Baltimore.
We asked around.
Was it Hugh Kennedy
that bundled you up in a carpet?
I can't discuss ongoin' investigations with civilians.
So just cut me out of here.
Hey, what are you doin' with my gun?
Put that down! [Grunts]
- Okay. Time to step out
of your comfort zone, people.
- What comfort zone?
We've stopped working.
I'd like to start again.
We process evidence.
There's no more evidence for us to process.
He's right.
We process. Booth interprets.
- I'd like to give it a try.
- No, we suck at interpretation.
- We absolutely blow.
- Um, what do you want us to do?
Work what we know. McKenna was probably killed
by Kennedy. Booth ran afoul of Kennedy.
I'm with you.
I'm with you, not ahead of you.
Okay, is there any forensic evidence on our victim
that might lead to Kennedy and Booth?
I mean, I... I finished the inventory
on McKenna's tracksuit.
There were flakes of tobacco,
fibers from the upholstery of a Crown Victoria...
popcorn, chocolate,
a host of other wool and cotton threads.
- Okay. What does that tell us?
- That the man was a pig?
Look, there were also, uh, cellulose fibers
consistent with newsprint...
and gum from a number of different mouths.
Uh, he had dried chunks of human mucous,
a half-dozen filaments of nylon...
- consistent with women's hosiery...
- [Zack] Oh!
Uh, Kennedy was a transvestite.
Keep going.
The rest was just waxy buildup
from soap or upholstery cleaner.
[Sighs]
Let's assume, all this adds up to a place...
crime scene.
Close your eyes and imagine the smell
of all those things.
[Saroyan, Clears Throat]
Tobacco...
snot, gum...
popcorn, a lot of clothing,
chocolate...
- Porno movie theater.
- You can't smoke at the movies.
I don't know about porno.
Upholstery cleaner,
Crown Victoria...
I got it... a taxicab.
McKenna was killed in a taxicab.
Yes.
- Where are you going?
- To tell the F.B. I...
they're looking for a one-legged cabbie
in Baltimore.
[Man On P.A.]
Tiger Moth, you're up.
P- 51 Mustang on deck.
You know, you guys, it's not like
we all know each other off the field, so...
But you know a man
with a prosthetic leg.
- Uh, yeah. I've seen him around.
- We need his name.
Honey, he'd be using a fake name.
We need to know where he lives.
- Well, maybe he's listed under his fake name.
- He's too careful for that.
# [Cell Phone Melody]
- [Cell Phone Beeps]
- He drives a cab.
- How do you know that?
- My associates are very good, Dad.
Can I ask a question? Do you guys
have any, like, official I.D. or anything?
- I can have the F.B.I. here in 20 minutes.
- Screw the F.B.I.
No, no. Hold on.
Easy. Take it easy, pal.
- Where does he live?
- I don't know!
- Dad!
- All right! All right! H-Halton Inn on Decatur.
- No! No! No!
- Dad, he told us.
- Are you lyin' to me? If you are, I'll know.
- Halton Inn on Decatur!
Just past the tracks! Easy. Wha...
Wh... What's that all about?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome. Your dad's a psycho, by the way.
- You have no idea.
- Bye.
Do you have a one-legged old man
staying here?
Give me 40 bucks.
- Room number, please.
- [Choking]
Dad!
Dad, I... I have the money.
[Brennan]
Dad! Look out!
- Who is she?
- I don't think she's gonna tell us.
Come on. Help me.
Pull! Pull!
[Max]
She reminds me of your mother.
- Hey. Hey, listen to me. I like you.
- [Groaning]
[Max] But if you make another move on me,
I will hurt you, understand?
If her name's Veleska, she's the same
bounty hunter who brought in Kennedy's leg.
How'd you find him?
It's not that hard to find
a one-legged, old white hit man in Baltimore.
- Why is she after him?
- She has to make sure that Kennedy stays gone.
I helped a wanted fugitive evade arrest.
I'm not going to jail.
- What do you got?
- It's a left anterior molar.
It's Booth's tooth.
Now, where's Booth?
- Temperance, honey.
- Kennedy has Booth, Dad. He's got Booth!
Okay.
Perhaps he didn't see Kennedy.
Yeah? Now how'd you come
to that thought?
Well, Kennedy would've left him
with an ice pick protruding from his head.
Just one simple question, big dog.
Did you see Kennedy?
We could get our own ice pick,
make it look like Kennedy killed him.
You know we can't let you live, right?
You've been struck and restrained.
Technically, kidnapping a federal agent
is as bad as murdering him these days.
How would you like to kill him?
First I gotta know for sure...
if Kennedy's dead or alive.
Good luck with that one, big dog.
- Big dog.
- Oh, I suppose we could do that thing
that McKenna used to do.
- But I'd need a blowtorch
and a sharpened screwdriver.
- Just tell us.
[Quietly]
Woof.
- Ah.
- Oh, cute.
Must be his kid.
Huh.
Head like a anvil. I hurt my hand.
All right.
Gonna let you take a look at your sweet boy.
Consign his face into your memory...
and then I'm gonna ask you
which one of your eyes you like best.
[Yells, Grunts]
[Blows Continue Landing]
- [Zack] Definitely Booth's tooth.
- I knew it.
[Saroyan]
Brennan.
- You're not alone in this.
- I know I'm not alone.
- We all want to find Booth.
- I know.
This is one of those times
when I have no idea what's happening.
- [Angela] Brennan, wait.
- I have to go, Ange.
- What's goin' on?
- I've got to find Booth.
- I'm coming with you.
- No.
I can't fight or shoot a gun,
but if something bad happens...
I can spit with deadly accuracy.
- Thanks, but no.
- What can't you tell me?
- By definition, I can't tell you.
- All right, all right.
Hodgins is outside in his fastest car.
It's Italian.
- One call, and he follows you everywhere.
- Angela...
All right, you're after a crazy, old,
ice-pick hit man who has Booth. You need help.
Look at my face.
Do you really see me backing down?
I... I already have help, Ange.
- From whom?
- From someone worse than Kennedy.
- Are you serious?
- Don't say it.
- Your father is helping you?
- I have to go.
My...
[Whimpering, Yelping, Muffled]
- [Brennan] Dad!
- [Yelping Continues]
- Was it Booth's tooth?
- Yes. Stop that.
- What are you doing?
- We have to know for sure
if Kennedy is alive or dead.
I mean, what if she and her friends
took Booth?
- [Yelping Resumes]
- l-lf this bothers you, maybe you should go.
No. Alpha male, man of action...
I... I get it.
[Yelps, Gasping]
Now. Tell us.
Okay. Okay.
[Breathing Heavily]
Kennedy's alive.
I was chasing him for the bail.
He was smarter than me,
and he gave me a choice...
help him fake his death
or die myself.
Where'd you get the body?
We stole some dead old geezer
from a mortuary in Charleston.
Where's my partner?
When I got here,
no one was here. I swear.
What do we do with her?
Oh, God. No!
The room is paid for
through the end of the week.
- Kennedy does not have Booth.
- How do you know?
- He's only got one leg.
- So?
Well, so he's retired. He's like me. He just...
He just wants to disappear.
[Sighs]
Then who's got Booth?
Well, there's only one other
significant player in all this.
Gallagher.
What am I gonna do with you
when I get to the lab?
Mmm, I'll just take a nap
here in the car.
Been an awfully exciting day
for an old guy like me.
- Booth is being held by Melvin Gallagher.
- That's a leap. How do you know?
- Can we just go with this please?
- Of course not.
- Obviously Brennan found out from her father
who is a wanted fugitive.
- Ange!
- Now that I can go with.
- We need to figure out
where Gallagher is holding Booth.
Has anybody noticed that,
every time there is a panic situation...
all eyes turn to Hodgins?
- It's okay.
- What's he supposed to do?
- Shoes.
- Shoes?
Gallagher said,
the last time he saw McKenna...
he was leaving for vacation
after a tough night of work.
You think Gallagher might have
a place he takes people for that sort of thing.
Let me go over Cement Head's shoes,
see what they tell us.
[Beeping]
- Methyl ethyl ketone.
- It's a solvent.
See if it has any specialized uses.
Also chromic acid.
[Computer Beeping]
M.E.K. and chromic acid
are both used to prepare metals.
- Prepare metals for what?
- Coating... uh, painting mostly. Electroplating.
- I'm seeing microthin deposits of aluminum here.
- Shavings?
No, it's more anodized.
Vapor deposition.
Gallagher flies everywhere?
An aluminum propeller requires a coating...
that could withstand between 10 and 20 tons
of centrifugal force...
preferably anodized.
These are Gallagher's tax returns.
We're looking for the purchase...
of any machine
that can be used for anodization.
- What, like a copier, or...
- Oh, that's so cute, but no.
Look for the words
"lamination," "electroplating"...
"Alloy membranes,"
"catalytic bed reactor"...
- "Serial thermal processor."
- "Vacuum pyrolysis."
"D-330 vacuum plating processor"?
- Yeah. That's it.
- That's it.
Yes. This is Dr. Brennan at theJeffersonian.
I just received a call from Agent Booth
that he's being held at...
the Purdue Airfield
in Oakville, Virginia.
Send backup.
I'm going in.
You just lied your ass off
to the Federal Bureau of Investigation.
That is so hot.
- # [Soft Rock]
- [No Audible Dialogue]
[No Audible Sound Effects]
# [Continues]
- If you lie really still, you may not die.
- # [Continues]
- I need your car.
- Max Keenan, you're under arrest.
- Not if I get the keys.
- They're in the ignition.
- [Exclaims]
- Well, it's not like I actually gave him the keys.
# [Continues]
# [Ends]
Why didn't you just...
just tell 'em about Kennedy?
Well, you know,
I needed to give you time to find me.
Ah, I've been tortured worse.
So, uh, you hear anything
from your old man?
He left my car in the garage.
He'll be back.
- How do you know?
- Max Keenan does not strike me...
as the kind of guy who, uh,
leaves things undone.
Next time he shows up,
what do I... do?
Do I call you? Do I knock him on the head?
What's my obligation?
If I were you, Bones, I'd wanna know what he has
to tell you about your mother, but, uh...
that's just me.
There's, uh, this old song.
- It's called "Keep on Trying."
- Yeah. Poco.
You know it?
# I've been drinkin' now #
- #Just a little too much #
- # Much #
- #And I don't know how#
- # Don't know how #
# I can get in touch with you #
- #You #
- [Both Chuckle]
[Together]
#And there's only one thing for me to do #
- # It's to keep on tryin' #
- #Tryin' #
- [Together] #To get home to you #
- [Chuckles]
Yeah, what about it?
It's a good old song, right?
Right.
# [Soft Rock Resumes]
# [Ends]
What's that mean?