[Woman On Radio]
Coroner Van 3, what's your E. T. A?
[Radio Chatter]
[Booth] They found the victim
in the filtration system.
Just, you know, some bones,
and nobody knows what to make of them.
I mean, look at this.
Millions of tax dollars
are spent to clean and treat tap water...
and yet people spend billions
on bottled water.
Well, it's cleaner.
Look, it comes from a clean mountain stream.
Yeah, which contains
fecal matter from animals.
There's no bones in it, though, is there?
Don't want that in your water.
Excuse me. Um, do you know
how long this is gonna take?
- Department wants to know
when I can get back on line.
- [Man] Bag that and mark it.
Any way to determine
where the body originated?
Water comes here through pipelines
that travel through five different states.
That's why I called the feds in.
Great. How many miles of pipe?
About 1,800.
I'm gonna need a schematic
of the entire system as soon as you can.
- Sure.
- Yeah. Bones?
Swirl treatment sped the rate of decomp.
Death was most likely less than three months ago.
The sacrum is small, still developing.
A kid.
A little girl...
about eight to 10 years old.
[Chattering]
[Booth]
Hey, any luck with the cause of death?
[Zack] Eh, postmortem trauma
makes assignation of cause difficult.
Great. "No" would've been just fine.
There are bands of discoloration on the ribs.
Cam might find out why with a tox screen.
I'd like those clothes as soon as I can get 'em.
Lots of crusty bugs and slime.
All yours.
Zack, spend some time with the teeth.
- They should be more discolored.
- Everything okay here?
Yeah, sure. Hey. You know?
- How's things?
- You know, murder and stuff.
Just another day at the office.
How about you?
Same old same old.
Listen, the Bureau's running location checks
for registered pedophiles in the area...
but we can't do much until we,
you know, I.D. the girl.
I'm running D.N.A. on the hairs
I pulled from the skull.
There's something funky about it.
The roots confirm brown hair.
The blonde is from oxidized thiols
evident in the hair shaft.
- Her hair was bleached?
- Wait, come on. I mean,
what nine-year-old dyes her hair?
Well, that might explain why my sketch...
isn't getting any hits from
the missing children's database.
Zack, look at the remains again
with a focus...
on any physical anomalies that
could hamper identification.
- I've got results cooking, so...
- Sure. Yeah. See you later.
- Don't you have work to do?
- Don't you?
[Chuckles]
Right. Right.
I should be able to run a tox screen
with the tissue left on her clavicle.
The scrapings that I took from the cheek
and eye socket contain propylene glycol...
- fragrance, dyes and lanolin.
- She was wearing makeup?
I was going to use dentition
to narrow down the age range, but look.
She has false teeth?
What the hell happened to this kid?
- The false teeth replace
the missing deciduous teeth.
- Baby teeth.
And the other teeth were veneered.
What is she?
A midget stripper?
[Angela] Okay, this is the color
she would've had from the bleaching.
[Hodgins] I think the alkaloids
would make the color brighter.
Okay, so some twisted psycho killer gives
this little girl a makeover before he kills her?
I hate working with kids.
Childhood should be all about swings.
- Swings?
- Yeah. You know, how high can I go?
If I twist the chains,
how fast will I spin?
What if I try to jump off
before the swing stops?
- Exactly.
- [Hodgins] I miss that feeling.
- Yeah. Me too.
- I miss organic chemistry class.
- Those were good times.
- I miss my first microscope.
Great. Yeah.
And I miss normal people. Can we go on?
- Factor in the teeth.
- [Beeping]
Yeah, you know? Because, uh,
this isn't weird enough.
Hodgins supplied the types of makeup.
And that's what we've got.
- She looks 30.
- Okay, run the image against the database now.
[Beeping]
Oh, my God.
That's Brianna Swanson.
- Who?
- The little beauty queen
who disappeared a few months ago.
[Angela]
In the middle of the Little
Miss Junior Patriot Pageant.
Just nine years old.
What do you mean...
there isn't even
enough of her for me to see?
The body traveled
through miles of piping.
And then after three months...
[Crying]
She was so beautiful, wasn't she?
I always thought someday she'd come back.
I even filled out her application
to theJunior Miss Starlite competition.
She would've won her division.
We're very sorry for your loss.
Ms. Swanson, I discovered dental work
on Brianna one doesn't usually see on a child.
The veneers and the caps? Yeah.
A lot of the girls had them.
Statistically, that's... that's not true.
Well, Brianna took some antibiotics
when she was a baby that stained her teeth.
She was very self-conscious about that,
so I wanted her to feel good about herself.
A nine-year-old is hardly mature enough
to make an informed decision about...
You were at the competition in Delaware
when Brianna went missing, correct?
Yeah. I never missed a pageant.
I never would.
But you weren't... you weren't with her
when, uh, she disappeared?
No. I left her alone
in our room for a minute.
When I came back, she was gone.
There's not a day that goes by
that I don't hate myself for that.
According to initial reports, you suspected
your ex-husband of kidnapping Brianna?
Well, he was trying to get custody of her
for over a year. Yeah.
David was not fit to be a father.
He wanted Brianna out of spite.
And he tried to drown me
in lawyer fees.
Was your ex-husband violent
with you or Brianna?
Not physically, no.
But once when we were fighting...
he said that he would rather have Brianna
end up in a ditch somewhere than turn out like me.
It's the "evening wear" category
that gets me.
My evening wear's a ratty
T-shirt and a mud mask.
There's bleeding evident
under the mental foramen.
There was complete disruption
of all ventral ligaments...
between the victim's skull
and the first and second vertebrae.
Her neck was broken.
Dislocated fracture of the mandible
suggests her death was caused...
by a strong blow to the chin
by an object heavy enough...
to leave markings
on her mental foramen.
I found fragments of steel
in the victim's jacket.
There was also an excessive amount
of polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons.
I assume that means something.
Polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons
are found in soot...
pesticides, creosotes, roofing tar.
The original police report said
Brianna's father was a roofer.
Yeah.
Interesting coincidence, huh?
- I'll call Booth.
- About this?
- You have a roofing business?
- Uh, yeah.
I... I... I went out on my own
when Brianna was born.
Thought I could make
some more money, you know?
Do you use mastic asphalt
in your work?
Uh, yeah, for waterproofing.
- Why?
- Were you working
the day your daughter disappeared?
No. It was the weekend.
What are you guys getting at?
We're just trying to piece things together.
That's all.
Damn it! I answered all these questions
when Brianna first went missing.
- This is Jackie's doing, right?
- You wanted your daughter back.
Sometimes in a divorce, the emotions get
a little high, you don't know what you're doing.
No. I know exactly what happened.
Jackie wasted so much time having the cops
check me out, the case went cold.
This is all Jackie's fault.
Look.
This was my little girl.
Not whatJackie turned her into.
This is who I wanted back.
You, uh...
You didn't give her
the remains, did you?
No. We can't release them.
Not before the investigation
is completed.
I want her buried right.
I don't want her funeral to be some
disgusting show Jackie puts on.
I want to bury her
with some love, you know?
[Beeping]
How's it going?
F.B.I. sent over the security tapes from
the hotel where Brianna's pageant was held.
I'm running them through
the body mass recognition program.
Maybe we'll find a shot of her
leaving with somebody.
- [Hodgins] Could you ever do this to your kid?
- [Angela] You know me.
I'm all about the swings.
- Did you bring me something?
- Uh, yeah, yeah.
This was in the zippered pocket
of what was left of Brianna's jacket.
It's treated cellulose.
Can you get any details from it?
I'll give it a shot.
Listen, Angela.
We've been dancing around this
for months now...
like two pieces of neodymium
caught in a magnetic field.
- [Chuckles] Is that good?
- Yeah.
But if the field weakens, they fly apart.
Which is why I thought
they should go on a date.
- Hodgins...
- You can't say that you don't feel it.
Come on.
We owe it to ourselves to give it a try.
I... I just don't think
it would be a good idea.
I mean, we work together, Jack.
- Angela...
- I'm sorry.
You're making a mistake.
I'll examine the paper
after I go through the videos.
Sure.
This is the rib cage
of a healthy 10-year-old girl.
And this... is our victim's rib cage.
Ouch.
This is an X-ray of a teenage
girl who died in 1872.
- What caused the deformity? Was it genetic?
- It was a corset...
tightened a little more each day.
Based on the degree of misshaping...
I'd say Brianna slept in one every night.
- That's torture.
- [Brennan] I imagine it was to give her...
an hourglass figure, which wouldn't be
possible naturally until well into puberty.
You gotta be... You're telling me
her mom did this to her?
People have done much worse for beauty...
neck stretching, foot binding...
- Okay. And you're saying that makes it okay?
- Well, of course not.
Any major alteration of our underlying
architecture demeans us.
You know, we all have aspects of ourselves
we might wish were different.
Yes. I wanted larger biceps before I became
comfortable with my mental acuity.
- [Grunts]
- Here, you can see...
cribra orbitalia, suggesting Brianna
suffered from long-term malnourishment.
There's no enamel erosion
to indicate bulimia...
so it's more likely she's been
on a calorie-controlled diet for at least two years.
- Oh, it gets better.
- Oh, how can it not?
Her tox screen came back
with traces of somatropin...
tetracycline and glycopyrronium bromide.
[Zack] Human growth hormone,
broad-spectrum antibiotic used to treat acne...
and a chemical mixture
that controls perspiration.
All with serious side effects.
No prescriptions were ever issued.
So Mom bound, starved
and drugged her.
That's heartwarming.
Our society puts a premium on beauty.
Common in declining cultures.
Hey, guys,
you should take a look at this.
This was time-stamped a half hour...
beforeJackie Swanson
reported Brianna missing.
- There.
- Brianna, come on! Right now!
- [Brianna] Let go of me!
- [Shouting Continues]
She said not a day goes by
that she doesn't hate herself.
[Booth]
I can see why.
lfJackie's willing to risk her child's life
to win these pageants...
What would happen
if her daughter refused to compete?
What you have to understand
is that this was Brianna's dream, not mine.
You put your nine-year-old
daughter in a corset, Ms. Swanson.
- A corset.
- Yeah. Brianna ordered that
off the Internet herself.
And I didn't tighten it up very much.
Did you ever think to tell Brianna...
that she didn't need to alter
her physical appearance in order to be loved?
- Did Brianna disappoint you somehow?
- No. She was a perfect angel.
She won every competition, even her first one.
And after that, it was music and dance classes.
- She was a real competitor.
- And when she won, it reflected well on you.
That way you wouldn't have to deal
with your own physical identity.
- I don't like her.
- Whoa.
Let's... play a little
show-and-tell, shall we, hmm?
How about this?
Can you explain these? This there.
And then that one... my favorite one.
Okay, these...
these are right before
she disappeared.
- We had a... disagreement.
- About the pageant?
No. About her piano piece.
I suggested she use her elbow...
to hit the last note with her head in her hands,
give the audience a little smile.
- It's called dazzle.
- And she didn't want to do that?
No. She didn't want dazzle.
She wanted to finish it perfectly.
But it seems very silly now.
- Only now?
- What happened immediately following this?
I sent her up to our room, and I sent myself
to the hotel bar for a very large glass of rosé.
And believe me, I was not the only mother
doing the exact same thing.
Great. I'm sure you can provide me
with a list of the other mothers. Hmm?
Blood would've rushed to the injured areas
that are evident on her X-rays...
but there's no evidence of blood flow
here or here or here.
So she was beaten after she died.
The blows appear to be
consistent with kicking...
but the dispersal pattern
is abnormal.
Can you tell anything about the shoes?
Size? Make?
Only that they are quite rigid,
possibly steel-toed.
And Hodgins said he found
fragments of steel in the jacket.
[Exhales]
- Hodgins asked me out.
- [Gasps]
Is that why you're hiding in here?
I'm not hiding.
I need advice.
What?
On a personal matter?
- Yes.
- From me?
- But romance is sort of...
This is like me asking you
advice on phylogenetic systematics.
Phylogenetic systematics.
I have no idea what that is.
- Exactly.
- Well, I can't ask Cam.
- Can't ask Cam what?
- Oh, Hodgins asked Angela out on a date.
- Brennan!
- What? Was it a secret?
It was a secret.
I just came to ask if you'd made
any progress on the cellulose.
- No.
- Okay.
Wait. You can't pretend
you didn't hear about this.
- Fine. What'd you tell him?
- No.
- Why?
- Because it would be a disaster.
All of a sudden,
you have an opinion on this?
You should never indulge in a romantic
relationship with someone you work with.
- Why not?
- Well, anthropologically?
There's an anthropological answer?
An efficient workplace
is predicated upon a simple hierarchy.
Romance undermines that hierarchy.
This is like when I had an affair
with my thesis supervisor in college.
Don't think we have time for that.
I say go.
- What about this hierarchical-sexual?
- Won't be an issue.
It's always fun to flirt
in the workplace.
But out there, when fantasy
becomes a reality, it's a drag.
What? The date will be bad?
It will be awful.
You'll both realize it's not meant to be.
There'll be a couple days of awkwardness,
and then everything goes back to normal.
If I were you,
I'd go with Cam on this one.
- Why?
- Phylogenetic systematics.
I have to go to dance class.
[Sighs]
- # [Background: Disco]
- [Booth] Becky Swanson's alibi checks out.
She was in the bar
when Brianna disappeared.
Can't we just prosecute her
for being horrible?
That the dance teacher?
- [Booth] Yeah. That's Charlotte Craft.
- Good.
She owns the studio.
She also runs theJunior Miss Patriot Pageant.
I mean, she's gotta be able
to give us something, right?
I always wanted to take dance...
- but I was so gawky and uncoordinated.
- What? You?
Later I understood that
the gawkiness was caused...
by an asymmetrical development
of the iliac crest.
Oh, yeah. Because you know what?
That's what I would've guessed.
- The old, uh, iliac crest.
- Hi. Which one's yours?
- Hmm?
- Which what is what? What? Mine? Ours?
Ours? Oh, no, no.
Whoa. We're not...
[Chuckles] No. No, no. That's not...
[Clears Throat]
We're... F.B.I.
- Oh, wow. Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, are you here
about Brianna Swanson?
- Did you know Brianna?
- Yeah. Very well.
I'm Kristen Mitchell.
That's my daughter Ariel by the bar,
with the gray leg warmers.
They... They took classes together,
were in the same pageants.
Sometimes I can't help but wonder,
what if it had been Ariel who got kidnapped?
Why do you assume she was kidnapped?
Well, I can't imagine Brianna
just running away.
Well, these pageants are very competitive.
There was a lot of pressure probably on her.
[Scoffs]
To Brianna? Uh, no. No way.
I mean, she had the face of an angel,
but underneath...
let's just say she had her sights set
on winning that pageant.
Why?
- I don't understand the question.
- What's the draw here?
Oh, my God.
The girls, they love it.
They get to dress up all glamorous,
all the attention, the lights and the music.
All right, girls. That's enough for today.
Thank you very much.
There's enough pressure
on young females...
without making them
prematurely sexualized.
[Scoffs] I am sorry, but that is just
narrow-minded prejudice.
I was in pageants my entire childhood.
I loved 'em.
And they sent me to college
on a full scholarship.
- Hey, Mommy, I'm finished.
- Hey, hon.
Nice job.
And good focus.
- Thanks.
- [Chuckles]
Well, I hope you find
the man responsible.
Agent Booth?
I've got about 20 minutes till my next class.
- Okay.
- Okay. Okay.
- Oh, you know, why don't, uh...
why don't you go mingle?
- What? Why me?
- Because you're a girl.
- What?
Listen, because it's illegal for me to question
any of these kids without their parents, okay?
Look, you're a civilian.
Okay? So take your pick.
Good point.
Behold the keepers of mystery...
the Sphecius speciosus
and his trusty sidekick, the Tibicen lyricen.
Ooh. Aah.
What mystery?
If Brianna Swanson was kidnapped,
they didn't take her far.
The presence of these two species
together suggests that...
she died within a one-mile radius
of the hotel where she disappeared.
That whole area was thoroughly searched
within hours of her disappearance.
Yeah. I think her body was jammed
into a storm culvert for over a month...
until those thunderstorms
two weeks ago...
Washed the remains
down to the treatment plant.
F.B.I. forensics should check out
the culverts and drains...
- large enough for a nine-year-old girl
around the hotel.
- I'll tell Booth.
[Chuckling]
Hey.
Don't come around again
looking for a second chance.
That was a one-time offer, baby.
Really? Hmm.
No. What? No.
No, no.
Not... Not really.
I mean, it never occurred to me
that you would...
Okay, now you talk.
I accept going on a date
with you soon.
- Tonight?
- [Chuckling]
Wow. That is soon.
I don't wanna give you time
to change your mind.
What do you wanna do?
You asked me.
Figure it out.
Thank you.
- [Beeps]
- I took this at the pageant...
about a half an hour
before Brianna disappeared.
- Did you show it to the police?
- No.
- Why not?
- Because he's not some murderous pedophile.
- He's the 17-year-old brother
of one of the contestants.
- Then why'd you take his picture?
Well, to show his parents how
creepy he seems hanging around.
He could be such a good-looking boy.
What's his name?
Jeremy Ferrell.
Look, I know he dresses in black and mopes
around, but he's totally harmless.
- Hmm. I'm gonna need a copy of this picture.
- Certainly.
[Girl]
Is that a real skeleton?
Yes, of a 12-year-old
from the Bronze Age.
These bones show
she'd already had children.
- What killed her?
- Having the children.
She should've waited to be
married before she had sex.
You said "sex."
Were you girls in theJunior
Miss Patriot Pageant?
- I came in fourth.
- If Brianna was there, you'd have been fifth.
It must have been hard
to lose your friend like that.
Brianna was kind of mean.
She said Liza had cankles.
- What are cankles?
- Where your calves and your ankles
are the same thing.
She took my birthday watch too.
She'd take anything she liked.
- So you weren't friends?
- You had to be friends with her.
- Why?
- Because Brianna was the queen.
So yours was a cultural structure...
predicated on the equation
of beauty with power.
You instinctively align
yourselves with someone...
who holds the greatest potential
for societal supremacy.
It's a Darwinian pressure
you're too young to bear.
Okay. Come on, Bones.
Up you go.
[Grunts]
There you go.
- You have huge muscles.
- [Booth] Thanks.
Learn anything?
- Yeah, I learned about cankles. How about you?
- I found a possible suspect.
Well, Cam and Zack said that Brianna
was kicked with a steel-toed boot.
Looks like my possible suspect
just became our primary suspect.
Of course.
I'm at every pageant.
Okay, you see what happens?
Look, I make him come...
to carry Haley's changes
and the props for her talent competition.
Well, you know, a lot of kids his age,
they'd... they'd just refuse.
Okay, so what? So then
I'm a... I'm a bad kid because I'm a good kid?
Mmm.
What do you call this look?
- It's not a look.
- Emo. It's called emo.
- No, it's not.
- It's short for overly emotive.
No, Mom. No, it's not. Okay?
I like these clothes. I like this hair.
It's not emo.
It's not anything.
- You have a girlfriend?
- He does.
She looks exactly like him.
Are you guys, like,
real boyfriend and girlfriend?
What do you mean?
What? Do we have sex?
- I don't know. You tell me.
- Why? Because if we don't...
then I'm just... I'm some pervert
who's got a thing for little girls?
The day that this, uh, picture was taken,
did you speak with Brianna Swanson?
- Yeah.
- Jeremy?
- She was picking on my little sister.
- Oh. And did you argue?
You don't argue with a nine-year-old.
You call each other names.
Are you wearing the same shoes
that you wore that day?
- No.
- Yes. He's worn the same thing
every day for a year.
- Would you be willing to give us those shoes?
- No.
- Yes.
- Mom!
Just this once, Jeremy,
do what I tell you, okay?
I... I know you didn't do this, honey.
I know who you are under all this.
Give the F.B.I. your shoes.
[Hodgins]
Not the shoes.
- How do you know?
- First, the caps are plasticized chrome,
not stainless steel.
And they're too broad and rounded
to have caused the damage...
- to Brianna Swanson's bones.
- Tell Cam and Booth.
- You do it.
- Why?
Because I have a date.
Here's the thing, Angela.
I know you've been out with a lot of guys.
Hey, you have a different
girlfriend twice a month.
Yeah. So imagine the pressure
to come up with a date...
that neither one of us
has ever been on before.
So what's up?
We here to walk a dog or something?
I remember what you said
about how you used to feel on a swing.
[Whirring]
It looks like colored dots,
but it's so faded.
Could this be a candy bar wrapper?
I don't think Brianna
was supposed to eat candy.
There were a lot of things I wasn't
supposed to do as a kid. I still did them.
- I haven't changed much.
- Bones, anything on the emo shoes?
- Not a match. Sorry.
- What's with the, uh, Milk Blast Bar wrapper?
Milk Blast Bar?
- Yeah.
- What's a Milk Blast Bar?
It's about the cheapest,
worst ice cream bar you can get.
[Imitating TVAnnouncer]
Available only at Red Shed convenience stores.
- [Chuckles]
- [Together] # Red Shed #
- #What you need now, and how #
- Yeah!
I thought they stopped making them.
Yeah. I thought I just ate 'em all.
[Chuckles, Snorts]
Well, maybe we should determine
how Brianna Swanson got ahold of one.
Brianna Swanson?
- Hodgins found the wrapper with her remains.
- [Dialing]
Yeah, it's Booth.
Listen, I need a search...
for any Red Shed
convenience store...
within a one-mile radius of
the Hyperion Hotel off of 171.
Thanks.
Look, I wouldn't have laughed so hard
if I knew it was Brianna Swanson.
- Oh, my God. I'm gonna puke.
- Put your head back. Head back! Head back!
Oh! I'm gonna puke.
I'm gonna puke.
- No, don't. You all right?
- [Laughing]
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Not... Don't do it again.
It was fun.
I never thought
I'd be doing this again.
- Really?
- Really.
You know, I had a little dream
about it last night.
- Did you?
- Yeah. It ended well too.
- I'm sure it did.
- But you know what? You look much better here.
Better than a dream, huh?
You're shameless. All right,
you better get... get...
You are gonna kill yourself.
[Chuckles]
I wouldn't do that.
- No?
- Not yet.
What now?
Well, they carry Milk Blast Bars.
That's a start.
- These are good.
- Are you kidding me?
These are God's food right here.
So the F.B.I. forensic units
are sweeping the culverts near the hotel.
So I figured, you know, while we were waiting,
we'd just go have a look around.
- Right there. There it is.
- [Brennan] Well hidden.
Yeah.
Well, big enough to stuff
a child's body into.
Oh, what do we got there?
It's a pageant medal.
Looks like we got
our crime scene, huh?
Crushing and scraping injuries
to the scapula...
are congruent with
Brianna Swanson being forced...
into a culvert this size
in a prone position.
The kicks to the back
were the attacker's attempt...
to force the body farther into the culvert
where it couldn't be seen.
"Little Miss Raspberry Blossom,
Culpepper, Virginia. "
There were remnants of blood
on the medal before I cleaned it.
- I'm waiting to see
if it belongs to Brianna Swanson.
- It's dated 1976.
I got something.
Okay.
- I don't know if this helps you.
- [Beeping]
[Angela]
"Lisa Fisher, 1976 Raspberry Queen.
"Holly Walters, Raspberry Princess.
Kristen Madigan,
Little Miss Raspberry Blossom."
That face.
Kristen Madigan.
The mother that I spoke with
at the dance school was named Kristen.
- Kristen Mitchell.
- Oh, my God.
It's like that Texas
cheerleading thing...
where the mother took out
her daughter's main competitor.
Yes. My daughter did win the pageant
after Brianna disappeared.
That's not a secret. The winner, Ariel,
went on to the national competition.
And how did Ariel do in the nationals?
- Very well. Finished in the top 10.
- Top 10? Wow.
That probably wouldn't
have happened if, uh...
Brianna Swanson
hadn't gone missing, right?
You don't know that.
Nobody knows that.
Where'd you get this?
Oh, we found it...
at Brianna Swanson's crime scene.
Can you explain that?
Brianna Swanson was a thief,
Agent Booth.
I mean, ask anybody.
She probably took it out of my bag.
Did you report it missing?
I'm not saying another word
until I get a lawyer.
One, two...
three, four.
And she was kicked twice in the
same place here, twice as deep.
So five, six.
There's an asymmetry
both of force and distance to these kicks.
The fracture pattern suggests
a slight rotation to the blows.
- How slight?
- About 30 degrees.
- Left side only?
- Yes.
[Dialing]
Hey, it's me.
Are you with Kristen Mitchell?
Yeah. We're just sitting here,
you know, waiting for a lawyer.
- Why?
- Okay, I need to know if her hips are even.
Is that slang
or do you really mean "even"?
Stand behind her, place your hands on her hips.
Then move your hands up to her rib cage...
gauging if it's an equal
distance on each side.
That's so not gonna happen.
- Well, you're videotaping the interview, right?
- Of course. We have to.
Okay. Then beam me
some footage ofher walking.
Okay. All right.
Coming at you, Bones.
What was that about?
Do me a favor and beam those images
of Ms. Mitchell pacing to theJeffersonian. Thanks.
What's going on here?
Where's my attorney?
[Clears Throat]
Okay, try and get a shot
of her buttocks and freeze it.
Okay. I'm applying
a biometric graph...
right here.
[Beeping]
No.
- You might as well let her go, Booth.
- Why?
She has very nice
symmetrical buttocks.
Well, yeah. I know that.
But, um, what's that
got to do with anything?
Brianna Swanson's attacker
has a thoracolumbar curve.
- Scoliosis.
- Sure. Meaning what?
Kristen Mitchell is definitely
not the killer.
- Thanks.
- [Phone Beeps]
Ariel Mitchell says that she showed Brianna
her mom's medal the day of the pageant.
Now, Brianna... she must've stolen it.
All right?
We're... We're nowhere.
Well, we might've found
the murder weapon.
The murder weapon?
Okay, well, what is it?
- A fore-stop trammel.
- A what?
- Hello.
- It's from the parking lot
at the Red Shed convenience store.
The F.B.I. forensics team found
minute traces of blood on it.
We brought it in here to compare the edging
with the marks on the victim's chin.
- [Brennan] And we can see here...
- It's a match.
The angle and force of the blow
suggest Brianna fell forward...
was unable to break her fall
and caught her chin here.
- Broke her neck instantly.
- [Hodgins] Wanna hear about the steel?
- In a minute.
So she was carried from the curb to the culvert?
- [Hodgins] Dragged.
- Wanna hear about the steel?
- How do you know she was dragged?
Remember the polycyclic aromatic
hydrocarbons I talked about?
- Absolutely not.
- Turns out that they weren't from roofing tar.
- They were from asphalt.
- So what you found on herjacket
was from her being dragged?
Exactly.
Wanna hear about the steel?
It wasn't from work boots.
It is the exact same steel used in tap shoes.
It's from another contestant.
Okay, Booth, you're looking
for a tap-dancing beauty queen with scoliosis.
Right. Gotcha. Wait.
Half these kids have tap shoes.
Well, we just need to examine
the symmetry of their hips.
I'll go with the shoes.
You do your thing.
- [Girls Chattering]
- Oh!
[Woman]
Can I help you? What are you doing there?
- Excuse me.
- [Gasps]
- It's okay. I'm a scientist.
- Molester! Molester!
- What?
- Bones?
- [Brennan] No.
- What are you doing?
I'm... I'm not a molester.
I'm a forensic anthropologist.
Okay, F.B.I. business.
Everybody just simmer down.
- She touched me on my rear!
- [Crowd Gasps]
No. Back and rear have totally
different connotations. Point of clarification.
- I touched her back.
- [Girl] What's going on?
Look, scientist or not,
F.B.I. or not...
she can't just go around
feeling little girls.
What? I wasn't feeling like that.
That makes me sound like a pervert.
- She was just touching. That's all.
- Just, well, examining really.
Examining, see? Okay, listen, bud,
we're after a murderer here, okay?
Dr. Brennan just got
a little overly excited.
How does feeling little girls
solve a murder?
- One of them is the murderer.
- [Booth] Okay, look.
- I know that's hard to believe.
- You know what? It's really not.
So, what do you need?
I mean, aside from the touching.
If I could just... watch them?
Just watch.
# [Show Tune]
# [Continues]
[Clapping]
That was good.
- That was good.
- # [Continues]
# [Continues]
That's her.
# [Ends]
[Applauding]
[Murmurs]
Oh, dude.
Not again.
I thought you said
Jeremy was cleared.
We know it's notJeremy.
- We'd like to talk to Haley for a moment.
- No. I don't want to.
This is a special day, Agent Booth.
- You're upsetting her.
- Don't be afraid.
No. You know, she should be afraid.
I didn't do anything.
I promise.
- We know you didn't mean to, Haley.
- Honey, what did you do?
Yeah.
What did you do?
Brianna said she was gonna
buy me an ice cream.
But she just made fun of me.
She said I was ugly.
She said I'd never win anything.
That must've hurt your feelings.
I didn't mean to push her
so hard. Honest.
Oh, God.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- [Crying] The pageant was starting.
I wanted to win.
Oh. Oh, God.
Hi.
We didn't really
get a chance to talk today.
Yeah.
I was avoiding you.
That whole swing thing wasn't good enough, right?
'Cause I can do better.
- It was perfect.
- It was?
- Maybe the best date I've ever had.
- Really?
Great. That's great.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
That's not great.
How can a great date be not great?
Because it was
supposed to fall flat.
That way, we'd both know
that this wasn't meant to be...
and we'd go back
to the way we were before.
I don't like the way it was before.
Look, Brennan
is my best friend...
and... Zack is...
whatever the hell he is.
And when this goes wrong, it...
it pulls everybody else into it.
And what the great date tells us...
is that when it goes wrong...
It'll go really, really wrong.
Yeah.
So...
we go back, right?
Friends.
Sure, friends.
Just one question.
What if it doesn't end that way?
What if it doesn't go wrong?
Friends.
This is what happened
when Rome fell.
What? Uh, people ate
stale doughnuts?
Objectification of women,
beauty as self-esteem.
Well, I think, um...
you know, some of those kids
actually had a good time.
The girl in the pink
could really dance.
But then again, Nero could
really play the fiddle.
You know, Bones,
I like to think that, um...
someplace deep inside,
people really know what's important.
It's hard to believe when you see women
trying to disguise or change themselves.
- Mmm.
- I never understood that.
- Well, I mean, no, of course you wouldn't.
- Why?
Well, it's just, you know,
someone who looks like you...
well, wouldn't...
Just because of the way you look.
I don't understand.
What... way do I look?
Well, you know, you're...
you're structured...
very well.
As are you.
[Sighs]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
It's just... Whew.
I just... I remembered
that I had an appointment.
Oh. So, um, I'll see you tomorrow?
No. You know, you have all the
paperwork for the case, right?
No. I was...
I was gonna stay and do it anyway, so...
- No. You know, it's our case. I wanna help.
- You don't have to, Booth.
- Bones, just drop it, okay? I'm here to help.
- # [Soft Rock]
Well, what about your appointment?
Uh, it's... You know, it's no big deal.
I'll tell you what.
How about I order some takeout
and I ditch these doughnuts?
Sure.
[Together]
Thai food?
[Chuckles]
# [Continues]
This time, I'm ordering extra mee krob
because you ate it last time.
- All of it.
- What? I thought you were done.
- Oh, right. I was done?
- Yeah.
- You finished all of it.
- I did not. You were pretty focused
on the fried rice.
- Can we just order? Okay?
- Fine.
[Dialing]
- # [Continues]
- [Chattering]
# [Ends]
What's that mean?