[Brennan]
It's getting thicker and thicker in here.
That's why the forensic team got lost.
I've sent somebody back to find 'em.
You sure you know
where you're goin'?
I still have trouble,
and I've been here for three years.
That's why we advise hikers
to stay away.
I know I'm pining for concrete.
You just, uh...
You stay close, all right, Bones?
I don't want you to get caught
out here when it gets dark, okay?
Bones? Bones?
Where the hell are you?
Bones?
I'm right here, Booth.
- Don't do that, all right?
- What?
- Take off like that, okay? You heard the guy.
- I saw this.
It's some sort of talisman.
These are bones from a bird.
And the coloring on the ornament
looks like dried blood.
There are more of'em too.
[Booth]
These, they look like eyes.
- Okay, this is weird. You see a lot of these?
- Not me.
But I've heard some other folks have come
across some pretty strange stuff in here.
- Word is it's Maggie Cinders.
- There's a woman who lives out here?
Did.
Died in 1780.
Folks around here thought
she was a witch and beheaded her.
Legend is she still haunts the woods
looking for her severed head.
And you believe this, Ranger Edison?
Look, I'm just telling you
what I heard.
Yeah, I'd prefer we keep moving, okay?
[Edison]
This is one of the only clearings around here.
The pit was covered
with sticks and leaves.
One of the hikers fell in on the body,
freaked, and ran.
Maggie Cinders did say she'd kill
anybody who dared to look for her.
So you talked to Miss Cinders? That must've
been difficult since she doesn't have a head.
Bag the eyes.
Give me a hand.
You want me to
go down there with you?
- No. I don't want the remains compromised.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- [Insects Buzzing]
So, uh, how'd she kill 'em,
you know, in the legend?
Like she was killed.
She cuts off their heads.
Iliac crest and pubis show it's male.
Epiphyseal fusion puts him
between 18 and 25 years old.
He's on a... a video camera.
Cause of death?
Well, since I can't find his skull...
I'd say... his head got cut off.
Since we don't have a head,
do we have enough for an identification?
We'll look for older injuries
that might be found in medical records.
More wood splinters.
Could've been the handle
of whatever lopped off his head.
If a ghost isn't comprised
of matter but is merely ectoplasm...
which is actually the clear outer layer
of cytoplasm on amoeboid cells...
how can the victim have suffered
bruising and multiple fractures?
Because there are
no such things as ghosts.
I thought you never
jump to conclusions?
Well, it's safe to dismiss
fantasy and deluded perceptions.
My mother came to me
the day after she died.
I wasn't some kid.
I was 23. She came to me...
She came to me and told me
to look in her dresser...
third drawer,
behind her pink blouse.
There was something there for me.
[Hodgins] The European hornet queen
I found on the remains...
puts the time of death
at November of last year.
- We have more splinters.
- Wood.
It's from a Betula uber...
a subspecies of round-leafbirch tree
that's been extinct since 1800.
The legend says that
Maggie Cinders kills her victims...
with the same old ax
used to decapitate her in 1783.
Anyone else feeling tingly,
or is it just me?
I checked missing persons. A film student from
U. V.A. went missing in the woods last year.
He was making a documentary
on the Maggie Cinders legend.
Graham Hastings, 21,
5'10", 176 pounds.
- That explains the video camera.
- [Angela] I, um...
I got something from the videotape.
I cleaned a section of the tape
with an isopropyl alcohol solution...
and fed whatever digital information
I could salvage into a restoration program.
- I didn't get much.
- [Woman Screams]
Maybe I got too much.
- Brian? Brian!
- [Chopping Sounds]
[Man] Lori, wait!
Where are you going? Lori, stop!
- Stop, Lori!
- [Lori] Brian! Brian!
[Lori Screams]
No! It's blood!
[Panting]
Oh, God. The noises are getting closer.
- I've lost Lori, and Brian's disappeared.
- [Chopping Sounds Continue]
[Sobbing]
Oh, God. It's her. I can hear her.
She's here. She's here!
Oh, God, she's here!
Lori, where the hell are you?
Lori!
Oh, my God.
Help!
Help me!
Oh, God!
Somebody help me!
Somebody help me, please!
[Screaming]
[Zack]
I just keep hearing the screams.
- I've never heard screams like that, Dr. Brennan.
- Neither have I.
Narrow focus trauma
on the left humerus, posterior side.
- Indicates an attempt by the victim
to shield his head.
- From the ax attack.
What?
It's always an ax, isn't it?
- Remember The Shining?
- My palms perspired profusely during that film.
Until we complete a series
of blade comparison tests...
there's no way to know
what type of weapon was used.
- Forensic team found this near the pit.
- Looks organic.
Definitely decomposing.
Victim's preliminary tox screen
came back negative. No drugs.
- That's too bad.
- Why?
Because drugs would explain the writings
I found inside Graham's backpack.
I'm cleaning them and taking mud samples,
but I think Booth should show 'em to a profiler.
They're handwritten, scrawled.
And so far, all I can make out is...
"Maggie came to me again, calling me."
And last but not least...
"They will scream for air,
but their lungs will fill with blood. "
I'll redo the tox screen.
I may be alone in this,
but I think one of us...
should remain a rational human being
during this investigation.
Got it. Comminuted fracture
to the ulna. Professionally set.
From the degree of callous formation,
that's a childhood injury.
One that could give us the I.D. we want.
I'll call Booth, tell him to contact next of kin.
Zack, place some garlic
around the remains...
and chant the Hmong ritual
for preservation of souls.
Really?
[Chuckles]
This is going to be a long case.
[Man] Graham broke his arm
sliding into second base.
Um, he was eight.
It's a match.
I'm very sorry.
Thanks.
Look.
I can't say that I'm surprised.
He, uh... He was missing for a year.
But still, when you hear...
It was just us, you know?
My parents died in a car accident.
I was 18 and he was 13, and, uh...
When something like that happens,
when you lose your parents at that age...
it's just people don't understand
how close you become.
I lost mine when I was 15.
It was just me and my brother too.
And he was 19.
Sorry.
Did Graham live with relatives,
or did he go into foster care?
God, no. I would never
let him go into the system.
I, uh...
I dropped out of college.
I joined the fire department
to support him.
Your brother didn't...
It was a difficult situation for him.
I understand.
I mean, you know, it seems like
you turned out okay though.
Do you know who Graham was with
the night he disappeared?
Yeah.
A couple of film students from school.
There was a guy and a girl.
I tried to get the guy...
Brian, his name was...
to help with the search.
But he was too freaked to go back into
the woods. I've never seen someone so scared.
So you were involved
with the search?
I've led a lot of search-and-rescue operations
as a firefighter. Um...
I should've found him.
- It's not your fault.
- I should've locked him in his damn room.
I mean, everyone knows
weird things happen in those woods.
The chatter marks mean the vertebrae
weren't split in one blow.
Makes sense.
Hacking off someone's head's...
more like cutting down a small tree
than splitting a log.
I find your imagery
both colorful and accurate.
Thank you. Let me know when you've
narrowed down the weapon category.
Dr. Saroyan? When you say
your mother visited you...
She appeared... in my room.
It was early evening.
- And you were frightened?
- No. I felt... loved.
- Dr. Brennan says that's impossible.
- What do you think?
I think it would be wonderful
if it were possible.
I found rust flakes on the neck
that were from hand-forged iron.
- 18th century.
- You got it.
- [Grunts]
- My God! A little warning, Zack.
I don't usually announce
each phase of my experiments.
- Yeah, maybe you should start.
- Nice follow-through, dude.
It doesn't look like
it was a machete.
Dibs on the next weapon.
- Looks like you have this under control.
- [Hodgins Grunts Loudly]
Graham had a fellowship
at the school.
It was a free ride
worth about 30 grand a year.
Brian, the other kid from the woods,
he applied for it and lost out to Graham.
After Graham disappeared,
the fellowship went to Brian.
Hmm?
Did you hear me?
Yeah.
Doesn't look good for Brian Andrews.
You okay?
I... I wonder what my life
would've been like if Russ had raised me.
Well, you know,
since he was a petty thief...
you know,
in and out of jail all the time, I...
I imagine it wouldn't
have been very good.
If he'd accepted responsibility
for raising me...
[Exhales Deeply]
I'm romanticizing. It's foolish.
Everyone does it, Bones, okay?
It's normal.
It's a useless fantasy, no different than
the childish legend about the headless woman.
I mean, look at Will.
He sacrificed everything for his brother...
and still couldn't save him.
By walking out,
maybe Russ gave me my life.
Well, you know, what Will said,
he was right. You turned out okay.
- I'm going to have coffee with him.
- Mmm.
- That was quick.
- He understands something
no one else I know does.
I mean, people need connection,
Booth, even me.
Obviously, you have one with Cam.
- So...
- What?
I thought you'd mention it.
I mean, isn't that what partners do?
- Tell each other about their lives?
- Wait a second.
- Look, Bones, I...
- Sorry.
I'm sorry. I forgot how self-conscious
you are talking about sex.
I am not...
I'm...
Graham was kind of the star at school,
so we all wanted to work with him.
And he thought the legend was true?
Said that Maggie Cinders
was talking to him in his dreams.
She told him where
her head was buried.
And you believed him too?
Not at first.
When we were out there
in the woods...
Stuff like that doesn't happen.
What kind of stuff?
Chopping sounds.
There... There was eyes
hanging on all the trees.
Something was moving out there
that wasn't us.
Look, I know what you're thinking.
But you weren't out there.
Okay, Lori, she freaked.
She took off into nowhere.
And... that's when
we all got separated.
Okay, look. The police report said...
that you brought Lori out of the woods.
When I found Lori, she was just
curled up on the ground shaking.
So you took her out of the woods,
but you left Graham?
I thought he had left us, okay?
You don't get it
what it was like out there.
His brother asked you to go on
the search with him, but you didn't go.
Why didn't you go?
I'm not proud of myself, okay?
But I just couldn't go back out there.
I couldn't.
Uh, Lori seemed to have
disappeared from school.
You wouldn't happen to know
where we can find her?
I haven't seen her since that night.
The last I heard,
she checked back into the psych ward.
I checked back in because I couldn't sleep.
I haven't slept for days.
Thanks for meeting with me, Lori.
Sure.
There's not much else to do in here.
Hey, do you mind if I ask you
what happened that night in the woods?
I've told the police everything.
But Graham is the only one
that can make things right.
He just got a little lost in there.
But when he gets back,
he's gonna make sure that I'm safe again.
Graham...
He promised to take care of you?
Well, sure.
He's my boyfriend.
He doesn't want anything
to happen to me.
Your boyfriend?
We keep it a secret.
Other girls get jealous.
Everyone loves Graham.
Did... Did you go into the woods?
- Is that why you're here?
- Yeah.
You found Graham?
He said he was gonna talk to Maggie.
Is that where you found him?
He wasn't with Maggie.
No.
N-N-No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Lori? Lori, just calm down.
- She killed him.
I'm sorry, Lori,
but we need to know what happened.
- That's what happened!
- We need to know what happened to him.
Did she take his head?
Oh, God!
No!
The blood!
- I called for help, but Brian wasn't there!
- Relax.
Relax... Relax, Lori.
You're safe here.
There was so much blood!
[Sobbing Hysterically]
I tried to run! Graham!
Graham, she's coming! Run!
Graham! Graham!
She freaked, Bones. It was like she was
out there in the woods with that witch.
Don't let anyone else hear you
talking like that, Booth.
I'm just saying, you know,
I've seen a lot of weird things.
It was like, you know,
Exorcist weird or Elm Street weird.
- What are you talking about now?
- They're movies. Okay, Bones?
- Movies so scary that
you end up peeing your pants.
- Good to know.
I noticed some damage
to the subdeltoid bursa.
Looks like the subscapularis
was torn away.
They're fracture lines.
This was a postmortem trauma.
Meaning what?
The victim's shoulder was
dislocated just after his death.
The injury doesn't fit into
our established scenario of the struggle.
These marks near
the vertebrocostal junction...
there's massive hinge fracturing.
Zack, lie down on the ground.
- Faceup or facedown?
- Faceup.
- This should be good.
- And give me your right arm.
Okay. If Graham Hastings was dragged
to the pit by this arm in this direction...
the trauma to the back of his ribs
would result in hinging.
And the exposed wound
where the head was severed...
would've been collecting
particulates along the way.
Tell Hodgins we might have enough for him
to determine where the victim was beheaded.
Oh, yeah!
Double yeah.
I'm waiting to hear from the psych ward
to see if we can talk to Lori again.
Well, I'll ask Will
what type of relationship...
Graham and Lori really had
when I have coffee with him.
Wait a second. You know,
we're investigating his brother's death.
Don't you think that
can get a little messy?
I can compartmentalize... same as you.
Mm-hmm.
The blood on those talisman things
hanging from the trees...not human.
I'll be back soon.
I just wanna thank you
for everything you're doing...
to find out
what happened to Graham.
Is that why you called...
to thank me for doing my job?
That and, uh...
I didn't think you'd come,
so I guess I'm a little nervous.
Caffeine affects the adenosine
receptors in the brain.
- It causes increased heart rate, so...
- There are other causes.
My partner warned me
to stay focused on the case, so...
- If you got questions, that's cool.
- Okay, um...
What kind of music do you like?
That's a good question.
Um... Snow Patrol.
And Leonard Cohen.
I like Leonard Cohen.
Gravel voice,
but somehow it's soothing.
Yeah.
I wonder why that is.
There's actually no empirical way
of assessing something like that.
- But you didn't mean that literally, did you?
- Uh-uh.
[Sighs]
I'm sorry. My...
My social skills are very limited.
Trust me, they're fine.
You know, it...
it took a long time for me to understand
how my brother could leave.
And now, it's just as odd
to meet someone who stayed.
I thought about leaving all the time.
I mean, I was a kid.
I didn't know how to be a parent.
I mean, I guess it was my fault
that his head got so big.
He was bossing people around
like he was already Steven Spielberg.
Well, Graham couldn't have been all bad.
- I mean, my partner says
that Lori seemed to love him.
- Poor kid.
I liked her.
She deserved better.
- Graham didn't treat her well?
- No.
He juggled a lot of girls.
I don't know how he did it...
- but no one ever found out about each other.
- So he cheated on her?
Doesn't run in the family,
by the way.
I have to get back to work.
- Did I say something?
- Maybe.
If I offended you in any way,
I'm sorry.
Do you like Massive Attack?
[Chuckles]
I don't know Massive Attack.
Very impressive integration
of radical politics into their music.
I'll play 'em for you next time.
# [Rock, Indistinct]
[Screams]
I know where
Graham Hastings was murdered.
- # [Clicks Off]
- Are you trying to kill me?
What's with the music?
It helps muffle the screams
so I don't pass out every few seconds.
Smart. We have to go through
all the video again.
Hastings was killed in a patch
of eastern hemlocks like this.
They grow in clusters
throughout the forest.
We have to spot the cluster
Graham and the others were near.
Wait, wait.
We have to go through all the video again?
Don't worry.
I'm right here for you.
[Graham]
There is no way that this is natural.
I mean, it's like... it's like
she left this here to guide us or something.
Make it stop!
Make it... Make it stop!
[Brian] Graham, there's something
seriously wrong with Lori, okay?
- We should go back.
- No! This is...
[Screaming]
- No! No!
- [Brian] What is it? Graham!
- [Lori] Make it go away!
- [Voices Overlapping]
- Come on! Let's go!
- [Lori Sobbing] Graham, get back here!
- No, Graham!
- What are you doing? Let's get out ofhere!
[Lori Screams]
Lori was not Graham's only girlfriend.
He had lots of girlfriends.
But he somehow managed
to keep them secret from each other.
- So what would happen if
a very jealous Lori found out?
- I don't know.
- That's... That's more your territory.
- What?
What, about cheating?
I just meant that
you use psychology.
You're very touchy.
- Perhaps because of all your skulking around?
- I am discreet.
Okay? It's different.
A gentleman is discreet. Okay?
- [Zack] What are we talking about?
- Nothing that concerns you.
- Booth.
- But I'm quite literally in
the middle of the conversation.
And it seems very interesting.
However, your glaring indicates that
I shouldn't press for further information.
Mm-hmm. Good genius.
Yeah.
So, Lori loves Graham.
Thinks he loves her...
but finds out that he doesn't.
So she goes all O.J. on him. It's a perfect cover,
right? "Headless witch did it, not me."
The whole insanity thing
might be an act.
But the victim sustained
extensive defensive wounds.
This was a very powerful attacker.
When a woman finds out that a man has been
cheating on her, she can get pretty mad.
That's what I heard. Okay, look,
we got motive and opportunity. It fits.
No, it doesn't fit.
Graham Hastings was 5'10" and 176 pounds.
Lori is 120 tops. The injuries aren't
consistent with a woman Lori Mueller's size.
Of course, people on P.C.P. have been
known to exhibit extraordinary strength.
P.C. P?
Who was on P.C. P?
Hodgins' report on the organic matter
from the baggie found at the scene...
showed that it contained psilocybin
mushrooms injected with phencyclidine.
Whoa.
What a trip.
Well, if Lori ingested those, it's possible
she could've caused Graham's injuries.
Not to mention combining dissociative
anesthetics with hallucinogenic compounds.
It can have a devastating affect
on people with fragile brain chemistry.
So her mental condition
is probably genuine.
I'm gonna go talk to my buddy Brian
and see if he knows anything...
about the magical mystery tour
that Lori might've been on that night.
- If I could clear the forest...
- Then what?
[Booth]
Hey, Brian.
Hey, Agent Booth.
This is Nate Gibbons, my film teacher.
This is Agent Booth.
I told you about him.
Hello.
Hi.
- You're here about Graham Hastings?
- Yeah.
Was he one of your students?
Yes. He was, uh,
an incredibly gifted kid.
What happened out there
was horrible.
- Mmm.
- What are you doing here again?
- You wanna find out what
happened to Graham, don't you?
- Of course.
Yeah.
So what were we watching?
- That's pretty cool.
- Nothing, really.
It's this film I'm doing
for, uh, my degree.
Brian's being modest.
He wrote and directed...
an amazing modern take
on the Gilgamesh story.
Nate produced it.
I got it accepted into Sundance.
Oh. Congratulations.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to talk to Brian alone.
Sure.
We'll finish up later.
All right.
- Call me if you need anything.
- Mm-hmm.
Brian, listen, we have evidence suggesting that
Lori was taking drugs that night in the woods.
No.
Those woods are too thick.
We knew that we had
to keep our heads on straight.
So as far as you know, Lori Mueller wasn't
under the influence of any hallucinogens?
- No.
- When she was with Graham, was she violent?
- No way.
- Did you know that Graham was cheating on her?
Man, that was none of my business.
Sure, Graham was a hound,
and everyone knew it.
Maybe Lori found out,
got angry with Graham.
No, okay? There's no way.
It wasn't her, okay?
Whacked out or not, it wasn't her.
There was something else
out there that night.
[Lori]
Where are we going? I can't see.
[Brian]
Don't worry. Just stay close.
What is that?
We're supposed to be looking
for eastern hemlock.
It's much more effective
with your eyes open.
I just know what's gonna
happen here, okay?
This is where they freak out
because they hear the witch.
[Lori Screams]
Wait. There.
Did you see that?
Yeah. But where are they?
Go... Go forward.
Stop. Dense crown, fine branches,
scaly bark and wide ridges.
Those are eastern hemlocks.
Love your eyes.
Now we need a landmark.
You have to be quiet, okay?
There's something out there.
No! No!
Wait a minute.
[Speaking Backwards]
[Hodgins]
2:37 a.m.
- So?
- We have a date plus an exact time.
I can estimate the position of the moon
from shadowing patterns on the forest floor.
We should be able to get
the approximate latitude and longitude.
- Yes.
- [Brian] Graham, leave the camera!
- [Graham] What about Lori?
- [Lori Screams]
Let's just work out
the coordinates.
- Yeah.
- [Lori Screams] Graham?
Graham?
The ax was found
buried over there.
Dried blood on the trunk.
Whoa.
Make that a lot
of dried blood on the trunk.
Someone should do a scraping here.
Where did you find the skull?
Buried just beyond those bushes.
But there's something else.
[Booth]
A second skull.
- [Edison] I'm afraid so.
- Are there any other
outstanding cases in the area?
No, there aren't.
Well, based on bony architecture...
this skull's consistent
with that of Graham Hastings.
[Saroyan]
I'll confirm with the blood from the ax.
- And the other skull?
- Female. Mid-30s at the time of death.
Which was between
the mid-18th and mid-19th centuries.
You know, this ax handle is birch.
Betula uber.
Same extinct species as
the wood fragments we found in the bone.
I'm almost done with her face.
Why are you spending time on that?
It won't help the case.
Come on.
Let the kids have some fun, Mom.
Both skulls have depressed fractures
on the parietal bones.
They could've been killed with a blow
to the head before they were decapitated.
[Brennan]
In Graham's case, yes.
But on the female skull,
there's evidence of new growth.
What looks like...
This person underwent trepanation.
An antiquated form of brain surgery.
Practiced in the 1700s
on those suspected of witchcraft.
- Do you think that skull is your Maggie Cinders?
- [Hodgins] Of course not.
I mean, there's no way to know, right?
I'm just saying...
it's interesting.
Hey, Bones, you know those papers that
Hodgins found in Graham Hastings's backpack?
- His hallucinogenic ramblings?
- Mm-hmm. You got it.
They were written on the back
of pages from his screenplay.
I don't see the significance.
Graham was a film student.
Of course he wrote screenplays.
Yeah, but this was a modern day take
on the Gilgamesh story.
The same story that Brian Andrews
is using for his film.
He stole Graham's screenplay.
Yeah.
Look familiar?
What...
Where'd you find these?
Graham Hastings's backpack
near his murdered body.
Care to explain why a movie
that's about to make it to Sundance...
sounds a lot like the screenplay
that your dead buddy wrote?
- Look, I know what you're thinking.
- Oh, really?
- Because what I think is that you killed him.
- No.
I think you're the one who drugged Lori
so she wouldn't know...
- what the hell was going on that night.
- No, I didn't.
Look, I know that this may look similar,
but this is mine.
Really? Because, you know, we found
an e-mail on Graham's computer...
sending you a complete
first version draft to you.
- He wanted you to read it, get your thoughts.
- So, what'd you think?
I thought...
I thought that it was better
than anything I could ever write.
So yeah, you know,
after Graham was missing a few months...
Nate thought it would be safe
to pass off as our own.
But I didn't kill Graham.
Anything else you forget
to mention, Brian?
Oh, come on, Brian.
You love the movies, right?
So this is the time where
the innocent guy comes clean...
or the guilty guy
asks for a lawyer.
Okay, so which movie is this gonna be?
That night...
Lori... When... When I found her,
she was covered in blood.
It wasn't hers.
I was afraid.
- You think she killed Graham?
- It wasn't her fault though.
She was nuts, okay? She said that
the blood just rained down on her.
I wanted to protect her.
So you got rid of the bloody clothing?
I hid them in the woods.
They're still out there.
- Okay, great. You can take us there.
- No!
Look, I'll tell you what I remember...
but I'm never going out there again.
You can lock me up
for the rest of my life.
I'm never going back out there.
The kid said he hid her clothes
in a hollow log near a stream.
Thanks. Angela looked at the video again.
Tell the forensic team...
to fan out across the area
south-southwest of the cabin ruins.
Did you hear that, Lou?
Yeah, south-southwest.
Yeah, I know it gets cold
when the sun goes down, Lou.
Well, you should've brought your blankie.
Just call me when you find her clothes.
Man!
[Sighs]
What?
- He was being a baby.
- I didn't say anything.
But you're looking at me
like I'm in trouble and you're a teacher.
- You're very touchy lately, Booth.
- Look, Bones.
I don't know why
I didn't tell you about Cam.
- Did I mention Cam?
- I just didn't want it to get weird, I guess.
Weird?
We're partners, you know?
Together all the time, right?
You're a woman, and I'm a man.
And I never had a relationship
like this where we were...
like two guys, except you're not,
you know, a guy.
- Yeah.
- No. No, I'm not.
Should I feel odd about
wanting to hang out with Will?
No, of course not.
You know?
Because essentially, I mean,
you're a guy like me, but not really.
That would mean that to me,
you are essentially a woman.
- Yeah, I can see that.
- No, no, no, no.
I'd prefer not to be a woman
if you don't mind.
- I'm merely trying to follow your reasoning.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
Okay, fine. What do you say we just,
you know... We'll drop it for now.
Yeah, it's Booth.
They found the clothes.
- That was fast.
- Well, good work, Lou.
All right, now you can come home
before all the monsters get you...
Hmm. Hung up on me.
I thought it was funny.
The blood from the ax
was from Graham Hastings.
Okay, was the blood
on Lori Mueller's clothes a match?
- Nope.
- Then there's another victim out there?
Yes, and she's probably named Bessie.
- Bessie?
- It's cows' blood.
The hormones and antibiotics affirm
that it's from a butcher shop.
Dr. Brennan, the witch's skull
was cut with a Stryker saw.
Wait.
Don't you use those in your autopsies?
They're also used
in teaching institutions.
I found a faded serial number behind the
occipital condyle. It's from the university.
So the skull was stolen
from the medical school.
Someone set up one hell of a horror show
to kill Graham Hastings.
- Have a seat.
- I'll help in any way I can...
but I do have a class
starting in 45 minutes.
Yeah, well, you know, it's film class.
Have 'em watch Wedding Crashers.
I can assure you, Agent Booth, that
film class is a lot more than watching movies.
Were you aware that
the medical school at the university...
has an anatomical
specimen collection?
I don't even know what that means.
This is about Graham, right?
The research collection can only be accessed
by a faculty member with a key card.
Yours was recorded entering
the building last November 7 th...
three days before
Graham Hastings disappeared.
You often go into a medical school
at 2:43 in the morning?
I reported my card missing last November.
You'll find a record of that.
Yeah.
It's convenient.
- Very convenient.
- Are you accusing me of something?
Someone stole a skull,
planted it in the woods...
along with animal bones,
blood, weird amulets.
Tricking people into believing that
Graham was murdered by a ghost.
Okay, but why? Why would I possibly
want to do something like that?
- Ride his coattails, you know?
Escape the faculty ghetto.
- He shut you out.
And maybe you were feeling just
a little bitter about that, huh, teach?
I'm entitled to an attorney,
aren't I?
Okay, maybe it was Graham
who stole the skull himself.
Are you suggesting that it was
some convoluted suicide scheme?
- He chopped off his own head?
- No.
Look, I'm just saying things,
they got out of hand, right?
He wanted to make it look
like a documentary, right?
As scary as possible.
So he sets everything up, right?
He gets Nate to
help him out that night.
But Nate sees an opportunity.
No one knows he's out there.
And before you know, it's chop-chop,
and "I'm going to Hollywood."
I found someone else in the woods.
I think it's a person.
Have you finished with
the particulates from the ax handle?
I've determined that the assailant
was wearing rough-hewn leather gloves.
- But I still have to check.
- Then why are you in here?
Because I want him here.
Okay, look.
I ran it through
a mass-recognition program.
That's Graham,
and that is our mystery guest.
- It's not Brian?
- No. Different height and weight.
This person is about 6'1 ".
As you can see,
that includes a head.
So it's definitely not Maggie.
Nate Gibbons is about 6'1 ".
I'll ask Will ifhe can tell us
anything about Graham and his teacher.
Maybe he threatened Graham.
[Lori Screaming]
His professor?
Did Graham tell you anything
about his relationship with him?
He said the guy wanted to help produce his film.
Graham said he wanted to do it on his own.
His professor is producing his film.
Brian stole Graham's screenplay.
He and the professor are making it.
The teacher killed Graham
for a script?
It would make his career.
Brian's too.
I've seen people murdered
for a lot less.
It's not certain yet.
We're just looking for evidence that
links one or two of them to the remains.
With all this going on,
when I'm with you...
I feel like
everything's gonna be okay.
I'd like to see the world
the way you do.
Then you would be looking...
at a very beautiful woman.
[Saroyan] Preliminary tests show
only one type of D.N.A. on the ax.
But now the follow-up tests
are showing two.
- Something wrong with
our electrophoresis machine?
- No, I double-checked it.
So this means you got
the killer's D.N.A.
Right. The attacker must've been cut
by Graham during the struggle.
I'm trying to separate out
the two types of D.N.A., but it's hard.
It's easy. I'll just get a warrant
for a blood sample for Nate Gibbons.
The glove fragments on the handle
were coated with diammonium phosphate...
and a guar gum-derivative thickener.
- Do you speak English?
- It's a flame retardant.
Exactly. Isn't that only used
by professional firefighters?
Wait.
Graham's brother is a firefighter.
He's also about 6'1 ", right?
And he has a head.
That explains why it looks like
there was only one blood source.
Siblings share so many
of the same chromosomes.
Will Hastings killed his brother.
- That certainly explains my results.
- Brennan.
Wait.
She's with him now.
[Siren Wailing]
- Good and funny.
- That's your opinion.
I don't think you're the one
that should be telling me what...
Booth.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
- You're under arrest for
the murder of your brother.
- Wait. What?
- You have the right to remain silent.
- What is this, Booth?
He did it.
Cam found his blood on the ax...
and Hodgins found chemicals that
only a firefighter would have access to.
I didn't kill Graham.
We fought. That's all.
You were out there
in the woods that night?
Please don't look at me like that.
Please? I was just helping my brother.
He said the film
was gonna make him famous.
So you got the animal bones,
the blood...
and you made the chopping sound
with the ax.
He wanted me to stay out of sight.
But the girl... Lori...
he slipped her drugs.
And she was screaming,
and I said I wasn't gonna help anymore.
And I said I wouldn't throw
the blood on her, so he did it.
And she went crazy, and you saw her.
Graham did that to her.
- Will...
- I had to stop him, okay?
I can't be responsible for
raising a monster like that.
- So you hit him with the ax.
- He was just lying there and
I was waiting for him to move.
And I've never... I've never even hit him before,
no matter how difficult he got.
Then you chopped off his head and you buried
him to make it look like some witch did it.
No.
She did it.
She did it. Maggie Cinders
was out there that night...
and she made me do it.
She told me never to tell anybody.
Maggie Cinders made me
cut off his head.
That's the only way it could happen.
You know me.
He was my brother.
I could never kill my own brother.
It was her!
What are you waiting for, Booth?
- You have the right to remain silent.
- No!
You understand me?
- Anything you say...
- No, please.
- Wait, please.
- will be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to speak
to an attorney.
Yeah. The F.B.I. needs me to finish
cataloguing the restored footage.
It's cool.
I don't have anywhere else to go.
You've been great today, Hodgins.
I know.
I haven't seen that piece.
[Angela]
Yeah, I was working on it before.
It just finished rendering.
Uh... Uh, it could...
could be a reflection.
- [Hodgins] Had to be. Or some moonlight.
- Yeah.
Uh, moonlight sounds right.
Can I stay at your place tonight?
Sure. No problem.
# [Pop Ballad]
[Sighs]
I sure know how to pick 'em, don't I?
Well, you know.
Our perceptions are always colored
by what we hope...
and what we fear, what we love.
We do the best we can.
I'm afraid my best isn't good enough.
I can read bones, not people.
Well...
You know, you had no trouble
seeing through me.
- It's a good thing I like being alone.
- You know what? You're not alone.
Okay? Come on.
- Booth.
- Hey.
You're my partner.
Okay?
It's a guy hug.
Take it.
All right?
# [Continues]
# [Ends]
What's that mean?