[Miss Parker] Apparently
Jarod's been working at this university...
doing some type of genetic engineering
with plants.
- You think he's in here?
- [Miss Parker] Lights are on.
Somebody's home.
- Willie, go get him.
- My pleasure.
Jarod! Freeze!
- [Grunts]
- Time to come home, genius.
L- I'm-I'm not him!
[Grunts]
- You're not who?
- Whoever you're looking for.
Well, then, who the hell are you?
L-l-I'm the guy
who waters the plants.
- Name's Francis.
- Well, Francis, do you know this man?
Jarod. Yeah, he's the, uh...
scientist who used to work here.
- "Used to."
- Yeah. Like I told the other guy
that was looking for him...
- he's gone.
- Someone else is looking forJarod?
Yeah. The blind guy-
kind of Chinese-looking.
Said his name was Mr., uh-
[Snaps Fingers]
Lee.
[Man, Asian Accent]
I have absorbed all the files on Jarod.
Yes, everything you gave me
from his childhood to the present.
No. He's quite
an interesting man.
There are seven people
I need to speak with.
You get me those seven people,
and I will deliverJarod.
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already
demonstrating more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent
every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
[Miss Parker]
He defends the weak and abused.
Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
[Woman] For those who can see,
we must really be a sight.
- Why is that?
- You know, the blind leading the blind.
- [Both Laugh]
- Please, no more blind jokes, Miss Newton.
- No, you can call me Rachel.
- Ah, Rachel.
- And I am Mr. Lee.
- Uh, who-who's typing?
Ah. Her name is-
[Speaking Chinese]
- Anna, for short- my new associate.
- How exactly can I help you?
I believe you once knew
a man named Jarod.
Ah.
Jarod helped me after I lost
my sight in a terrorist bombing.
He's helped lots of people
who have been victimized.
He taught me to see again...
so to speak.
Why do you want
to know aboutJarod?
I have reason to believe
that he is in trouble.
- I need you to help him.
- How can I help?
I'm sure you realize...
that the loss of vision...
often nurtures deeper insight.
And you feel
I've developed this insight?
But of course.
That is why I brought you here.
Please, tell me howJarod...
helped you and affected your life.
I metJarod
while I was still in therapy...
not long after the bombing.
I was... drawn to him
right from the start.
It was like he felt my pain,
my fears.
[Rachel's Voice]
Six... seven...
eight... nine... ten-
- You can stop counting. You're here.
- Oh.
- [Chuckling]
- You must have stepped into the room.
- It's 11 steps to the door.
- I did. That's very good.
- It's a beautiful day. Why don't we go outside?
- Oh, no.
L-l- I think
I'd rather stay here.
Rachel.
You have
to go outside sometime.
I was supposed to work
in my studio...
but it was such a nice day,
I decided to go on the rooftop of city hall.
That's what happened
the last time I went outside.
You were in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
That is not your fault.
You can't stop living
your life because of it.
You know, when I had my eyes
behind the camera...
I could see things
no one else could see.
I can remember details
of nearly every picture I ever took.
That's ironic.
They tell me he was there that day.
I must have seen the man who did this
to me as he was setting his bomb.
But as hard as I try,
I can't remember.
So, are you saying that...
Jarod connected with you
emotionally?
Oh, it was more than that.
It was almost like he became me.
He seemed to know me,
understand me...
more than I knew myself.
The way he enabled me
to face my life again was magical...
like an artist
painting a picture, only...
Jarod was the painter,
and I was the canvas.
- [Rachel] Is this some kind of new therapy?
- [Jarod] Call it a simulation.
I'm going to create
an environment...
with all the stimuli
you need to recreate an event.
- And for you to become someone.
- Who do you want me to become?
- Yourself.
- [Gasps]
Oh, my camera.
Oh, I haven't touched
this since the-
well, since the day at city hall.
Now, I want you
to develop that roll of film-
- [Camera Clicks]
- the pictures you took that day.
- Oh, but there's no film in it.
- I know.
I want you to develop
the pictures in your mind.
I'm on the rooftop
at city hall.
The natural light
is at its perfect angle.
The building is-
is closed. It's Sunday...
and I'm getting last minute shots
for my gallery opening.
- [Jarod] Are you alone?
- I think- I don't see anyone.
I don't-
I don't see anyone...
but l- I feel a-
tingle on the back of my neck.
- Go on.
- I don't see anyone, but I hear something.
- What do you hear?
- Footsteps walking... quickly away.
It's right before it happens.
Rachel, do you see the bomb?
It's only an instant
before the flash.
- Do you see him?
- No.
But I smell something.
- I smell-
- You smell him.
It must be-
It's cologne.
Thank you.
Because of what he found
in my mind...
Jarod was able
to catch the bomber...
and help me find the courage
to believe in myself again.
That's very interesting.
Anna?
Thank you for everything.
My assistant, Anna,
will take you home now.
You know, you were right
about insight, Mr. Lee.
You don't want to helpJarod.
You want to catch him.
[Chuckles]
But you won't succeed.
He's too smart,
even for you.
[Miss Parker]
Who the hell is Mr. Lee?
What does a blind Chinese man
want with Jarod anyway?
The same thing anyone else would-
an advantage.
Jarod's a very valuable commodity.
Question is...
- who wants to trade in him?
- None of this makes any sense.
Broots, go back toJarod's last lair.
Check the neighborhood...
the airport, the train station-
- anywhere that someone
might have seen this Mr. Lee.
- Okay.
I'm also interested in finding out
about our sightless friend.
Keep Bridget up to speed on any new
developments. She's my liaison in this thing.
[Giggles]
Since when do I need
a liaison to my own father?
Since you're not
the only ones afterJarod.
But don't worry, angel. It shouldn't be
that hard to catch a blind man.
- All you have to do is open your eyes.
- Mmm.
[Man]
What's goin'on?
- [Buzzer Sounds]
- Some people want to talk to you.
[Indistinct Shouts]
- [Cell Door Slams]
- [Man Scoffs] So what's this...
free egg roll night
on the "Ginsu"?
"Ginsu"-
That's Japanese.
A man of such erudition...
a scholar, a physician.
[Chuckles]
This imprisonment must have reacquainted
you with the low, common man.
[Snickers]
Perhaps that's his idea.
Hmm. Dr. Fein,
you may address me as...
Mr. Lee.
Well, Mr. Lee.
I don't know
what this is about, but-
This is about an acquaintance
of yours whom I'm searching for.
His name is Jarod.
You gotta be kidding.
For 18 months, I've been trying
to tell people aboutJarod.
But there's no trace of him.
It's like he never existed.
- You seem frustrated.
- Frustrated?
That psycho's the reason I'm spending
the rest of my life in an eight-by-eight cell.
- Sue me if I'm frustrated.
- [Laughs]
Dr. Fein, you did bury
an innocent man alive.
- You got a point?
- Yes.
Jarod, in his unique way, merely
exposed you to the rest of the world.
What is one man's justice
is another man's revenge.
Yeah, well, a lot of good
that's gonna do me now.
[Rattling]
Dr. Fein,
would you like to seeJarod...
in an environment
worse than this?
- Can you do that?
- If you tell me what he did to you.
What he did?
He tried to kill me.
He tried to bury me alive.
[Grunting]
Ugh!
- [Gasps]
- Trick or treat.
- You scared the hell out of me.
- Well, that is, after all...
what this holiday
is all about, isn't it?
Oh, you're too late.
He's gone.
- Who's gone?
- Enrique, the young man you killed.
- What kind of sick prank are you tryin' to play?
- Oh, this isn't a prank.
It's a life lesson.
You know,
in some cultures they believe...
that the spirit of a man
killed in anger returns...
to exact revenge
upon his perpetrator.
- Spooky, huh?
- I'm gettin' out of here.
Oh, no, you can't leave,
Dr. Fein.
This is the Day ofThe Dead.
And you, sir, are the special guest.
Let me out ofhere!
Jarod! This isn't funny!
I know. It would be awful
to be buried alive...
especially with that
on your shoe.
Jarod! Jarod!
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
There's no reason
to wake the dead.
- You're gonna be joining them soon enough.
- Jarod, please!
Did Enrique discover
that you had killed...
one of the research subjects
he recruited for you?
- You're crazy!
- Uh-uh-uh. That is not a very nice thing to say...
to a man with a shovel...
- is it?
- Jarod, please!
You took an innocent
homeless man...
and you turned him
into your guinea pig-
someone to test
your heart drug on...
someone that you didn't think
would be missed if it didn't work.
Well, it didn't work, did it?
And someone did miss him- Enrique.
So you buried him alive
to save your research, didn't you?
Didn't you?
Didn't you? Didn't you?
Yes! Yes!
Now let me out of here!
Screaming isn't going to help
you conserve your oxygen.
And believe me,
you're going to need all you can get.
- No. No. No, Jarod!
- Happy Halloween.
Jarod. Ja-Jarod.
Jarod! Jarod!
Jarod!
[Cackling]
[High-pitched Vocalizing]
[Laughing]
I can imagine.
Perhaps that's his way
of dispensing emotional justice.
How's any of this
gonna help you find him?
Oh, you helped me
a great deal already.
You told me who he is...
and what he is.
[Chuckles]
And, oh, yes...
I'll catch him.
[Whirring]
Mr. Lee here.
After interviewing the first few subjects...
I'm finding Jarod
even more challenging...
than initially anticipated.
[Chuckles]
Jarod, I'll never be able to do this.
Sure you can.
We'll keep on practicing.
His desire to help other people
and his determination for justice...
are unyielding.
[Chuckles]
But they will also prove
to be his downfall.
Mmm.
- [Typing]
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- [Typing Continues]
In many ways, Jarod is the most
compassionate man I've met.
It's almost as if it's
his natural state ofbeing.
- [Mr. Lee] How is that, Miss Granger?
- He has a way of connecting...
with others-
to their souls-
in a way that I've never seen
in any other person.
- It's ironic, really.
- Ironic?
He can be so there
for other people.
And yet inside,
he's so alone.
I'll never forget the day
he walked into my office.
[Granger] Mrs. Morgan, we may
have a sighting on your daughter.
If all goes well, you should have your arms
around Catherine by tomorrow night.
Thank you.
God bless you too.
How can I help you?
I don't know who I am.
[Granger] As I looked
in his eyes, I could feel his pain...
- his sadness.
- So, Jarod came to you...
- for help.
- Yes. That's what I do-
reunite families,
find missing children.
I help people find their pasts,
so they can have a future.
- [Mr. Lee] I see.
- I thought I'd seen it all...
until I heard Jarod's story.
- I'm looking for my parents.
- Are they still alive?
I don't know.
I was never told the truth.
Well, why not use the police database
to initiate a search?
I can't. Look, this is probably
gonna be hard to understand...
but I don't have
much time- 72 hours.
- Without a name-
- I have a picture.
It's my mother. At least,
that's what I was told.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Thank you.
So, you were able to giveJarod
the identity ofhis mother.
No. These people came
and took the information.
They destroyed it beforeJarod
even had a chance to see it.
That must have
decimated his soul.
Actually, it seemed to inspire him...
to help other people
who experienced a similar loss.
- Really?
- Over the last three years...
he's helped me
locate and reunite...
nine children
with their families.
And each time,
he refuses to take...
any credit or recognition
for what he's done.
- A very resilient soul.
- Like I said...
Jarod's the most compassionate
human being I've ever met.
[Foghorn Blowing]
[Buoy Ringing]
You were right.
It wasn't that hard to track Mr. Lee.
I mean, most people you talk to have
never seen an old blind Chinese guy.
Well, at least
not since Kung Fu.
Well done, Grasshopper.
[Clears Throat]
I found out...
Mr. Lee's a pretty infamous guy
in Hong Kong as well.
Not only does he find people, but he
makes them disappear in little pieces.
If we play our cards right,
we'll bring him in in one piece.
- Let's move.
- Get in position.
[Sam]
Yes sir, Mr. Lyle.
- It's more difficult than I thought.
- [Typing]
I'm learning thatJarod
is very complex-
very yin and yang...
dangerous and yet in control...
full of great pain...
but a source of healing
to others.
[Chuckles]
Yes.
He's, uh, capable
of bringing justice...
against the powerful
and yet showing mercy to the weak.
He helps the lost
to find themselves...
but is unable to discover
his own true nature.
[Chuckles]
- Ironic, isn't it?
- [Typing Continues]
Anna?
I think we have visitors.
[Miss Parker]
We need to move.
Patience, Parker. The Sweepers
aren't even in position yet.
Lee has no idea we're out here. You start
stumbling around, and you're gonna blow it all.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
We're gonna go in...
and bring out
the blind man.
Let me show you
how this is done.
[Door Opens, Bell Chimes]
You idiot, we've been made.
Get in!
- [Engine Starts]
- Miss Parker, that's a wall.
Yeah, and this is a rental.
- [Tires Screeching]
- Whoa! Whoa!
[Tires Screeching]
Damn!
He was right here!
- So, this is how it's done?
- Outside! He couldn't have gotten far.
- Wow. Mr. Lee's like a Shaolin priest.
- What are you talking about?
Well, you know,
"Look, for he cannot be seen.
- Felt, for he cannot be touched."
- Oh, get a life, Kato.
What's this?
Braille. Great.
- In case you've forgotten.
- What is it, Syd?
Names
of people involved with Jarod.
- Why?
- He's been interviewing them.
- How would Mr. Lee know
about them in the first place?
- Someone at the Centre.
Broots, I want you to trace all calls
coming into and out of this warehouse.
Let's find out who Mr. Lee's
working for and why.
- Okay.
- Sydney, who do you think they are?
Whoever they are, these must be
some very special people.
- Love the shoes.
- Thank you very much.
Do you always wear that...
getup?
Well, I can see
you don't fully appreciate...
the incredible burden
of my responsibility.
You'll have to excuse Mr. Lyle.
[Sucks Teeth]
He's not a fan.
But I am, Bernie.
And I do appreciate you taking time...
out of your busy schedule
to talk to us.
Well, I always got time
to spend with a pretty lady.
[Chuckles]
Tell us, what did Mr. Lee
want to know aboutJarod?
[Sighs]
How I felt about him...
minute by minute,
from the very instant we met.
Now don't you little ladies forget.
Come and see my show tonight.
There's no cover, there's no minimum,
and there's free hot...
- [Women Squealing]
- hors d'oeuvres, huh?
- I'll see y'all later. Bye-bye.
- Bye!
Thank you very much.
[Grunts]
Hey, there, teddy bear.
You comin' to rub elbows
with the King of Rock and Roll?
No, I'm tryin'
to understand this.
You dress up
in a rented costume...
- and you pretend to be a dead singer?
- "Singer"?
Son, do you have any idea
who I am?
- Well, actually, I would-
- You are looking at a national monument-
Mount Rushmore
in blue suede shoes.
There's not a human bein'
on God's green earth...
that has ever demanded
the attention and respect...
of the man you are lookin' at
this very moment.
Hey, Bernie? Some guy
at the craps table says...
- he'll give you five bucks to goose his wife.
- I'll be right there.
Well, my fans beckon.
I must go.
Thank you very much.
To tell you the truth,
I'd read Jarod all wrong at first.
- How so?
- Well, just like I told Mr. Lee...
it turned out that
he was the only person...
who really cared about
what I was goin' through.
Hey.
Well, welcome
to the Heartbreak Hotel.
[Laughs] What are you doing here?
You should be on stage.
Oh, no. There-There's
no more stage for the King.
The casino fired me.
Did it have something to do
with that bird thing?
- Bird thing?
- The goose.
No. No, they said they'd
had complaints about the show.
So I put on 20, 30 pounds. You think
it's easy bein'the idol of millions?
- I would guess no.
- Well, you're damn right it isn't.
I sacrificed everything.
I did it 'cause I loved it.
It's what the people wanted.
I just wish some of those casino bigwigs
could spend one hour wearin'the cape, huh?
Just one hour.
I tell you what-They'd walk away singin'
a different tune. I guaran-damn-tee you.
Couldn't you get a job
at another casino?
No, buddy boy.
After 24 years
of makin' people smile...
singin' the songs and...
spreadin'
the good vibrations...
afraid it's the end
of the line for the King.
We did have one hell
of a ride, though, didn't we?
- I bet you did.
- Now, look. I'm- I'm sorry. L-
I'm spillin' my guts
and I don't even know your name.
Jarod... Felson.
Bernie Baxley.
Well, it's nice to meet you,
Thanks.
Jarod?
I'm scared.
- Of what?
- Him.
Jarod helped me
to face my fears...
to find me again.
L- I got to admit, he, uh,
kind of rubbed off on me a little bit.
But I'll tell ya-
I think I rubbed off on him a little bit too.
[As Elvis]
Well, thank you very much.
After that, I left Vegas.
Never looked back.
And thanks toJarod,
I've got my own place in Branson...
where the King's legacy
is kept alive 363 days a year...
closed only for New Year's
and, of course, the King's birthday.
Ow. I threw out my hip
dancin' about a year ago.
ButJarod had taught me
that you gotta keep on adaptin'.
You know, keep-
keep lookin' for new and-
and better ways to move
and groove forward.
So I broadened
my repertoire.
Thought maybe I'd treat you folks
to, well, just a taste of my new act.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome to the stage...
Tiny King.
Huh?
[Chuckles]
Hey, TK, don't you want to say
somethin' to the pretty lady?
Ooh, you look better than a fried
peanut butter and banana sandwich.
- [Chuckles]
- [Forced Chuckle]
- Thank you very much.
- [Laughs]
[Chuckling]
Sam? Get him out of here
before I step on his blue suede face.
Yes, Miss Parker.
Excuse me, King?
- Yeah?
- It's time to leave the building.
Ah!
- Got to TCB.
- [Clucks Tongue]
You did say
these people must be... special.
What the hell
is going on, Sydney?
Lee has been interviewing
every one of those people...
about their emotional connection
toJarod...
in order to anticipate...
his next move.
Miss Parker.
Uh- Uh-
- What is it?
- I traced the last call from Mr. Lee's warehouse...
to the Centre, and you won't believe
where it ended up.
- Spit it out, Broots.
- Well, it went to your father's office.
- [Footsteps]
- Mmm. [Chuckles]
Uh-huh. Yes.
The next subject may be
reluctant to cooperate.
- Let me bring him in.
- [Chuckles, Speaks Chinese]
Violence was not
on your résumé.
[Chuckles]
I'll have to write a new one.
Hmm.
[Reads Aloud In Chinese]
Trouble?
Oh, yeah.
The battery's busted or something.
Oh, well,
maybe I can help.
- Really? You don't mind?
- Um...
I'm not much of a mechanic,
but I am pretty good with my hands.
[Groans]
[Handcuffs Rattling]
- Ah. Mr. Lee.
- [Speaks Chinese]
I believe you have met
my assistant, Anna.
Met her?
She kidnapped me.
Oh, really?
[Laughs]
Please, sit down.
I don't feel like
sitting down.
Oh. Excuse my urgency...
but it is important
that I know about...
your relationship
with Jarod.
Really? Well, I'd like to know
about your relationship with Jarod.
Mr. Lyle,
in life it is primary...
that one knows
his position.
And you, sir, are not
in position to ask questions.
Look, I don't know
what you're up to...
but I think it's time somebody
taught you some manners.
[Grunts]
[Groans]
[Lyle Grunts]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I hurt you?
It is not only with sight
that one sees.
Let me help you.
- Once again, Mr Lyle, go sit down.
- [Grunts]
- And tell me your story. Hmm?
- What do you want to know?
- I want to know...
what motivates Jarod...
why he risks himself
to help others...
why he runs...
but does not vanish.
Well, why do you think
I can help you?
Coochie, coochie, coochie, coochie.
[Laughs]
Because you have a very
unique relationship with Jarod.
You did try to kill him,
did you not?
All in the interest of science.
- [Instruments Beeping]
- Clear!
Clear!
- It really wasn't my idea anyway.
- [Laughing]
I believe you also
kidnapped Jarod. Huh?
Desperate times
call for desperate measures.
"Desperate times call
for desperate measures," Anna.
So, you weren't content
just to kidnapJarod, were you?
You also have to shoot
his brother and kill him.
That was an accident,
pure and simple.
This is beautiful!
It's just one big happy family, isn't it?
It's the end
of the line, Lyle.
There's no place
left for you to run.
I'm disappointed in you, Jarod. You know
me better than that. Drop the cannon, kid.
- Shoot him, you moron!
- Shut up!
Stay back, or I put
a very large hole in big brother.
- Kyle.
- Threats and pain...
that's all
you've ever offered us.
You stole our lives,
and you killed our spirit...
and now you think you can
threaten us with death?
It doesn't matter, Lyle.
Because we never made a difference anyway.
I'll kill him.
I swear I will.
And then I'll kill you.
Don't do this,
little brother.
- [Grunts]
- [Groans]
[Yells]
[Kyle Groans]
There's another part
about what drives Jarod that l-l-
I don't understand.
- And that is?
- [Chuckles]
Why, after all
you've done to him...
he has not killed you.
After all...
he is more resourceful
and intelligent than you are.
Maybe he just likes me.
Not.
[Chuckles]
Shall we start from the beginning,
all over again, huh?
- [Miss Parker] Where the hell is Lyle?
- [Sydney] I don't know...
but he seemed genuinely
disturbed over the revelation...
that Mr. Lee is in contact
with your father's office.
Well, we're not
waiting any longer.
- Let's go ahead and talk to this guy.
- Hmm.
- Hi.
Hi,J.R.
My name is Sydney. This is Miss Parker.
Miss Parker?
You sure look familiar.
I have one of those faces.
Listen,J. R...
it's very important that you tell us exactly
what Mr. Lee wanted to know aboutJarod.
Is Jarod
in some kind of trouble?
- He might be.
- I'll do anything to help him.
He saved my life twice.
Once before I even met him.
J. R? Honey?
Sweetie, can you hear me? J. R?
- [Jarod] He's in shock.
- Wake up.
- He's still breathing.
- [Mother] He's hypoglycemic.
- When was the last time he ate?
- He had cereal for breakfast three, four hours ago.
J. R? Come on, honey.
What do you think
you're doing?
I need to stabilize his blood sugar.
Stick this in your mouth.
I want you to let it dissolve, okay?
Good boy.
- Mom?
- Oh! Oh!
It's okay, honey.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Mr. Lee seemed real interested
in the fact thatJarod knew I was sick.
- Your heart.
- I needed a transplant.
My mom had pretty much
given up hope that I'd get one in time...
untilJarod came into our lives.
- How is he feeling?
- [Mother] Better.
He has a heart condition.
I noticed the bluish tint
to his fingertips and his lips.
I'd say by the looks of it,
you have a very sick boy.
- Are you a doctor?
- Not at the moment.
Why hasn't he had
a heart transplant?
Because he's on a waiting list.
Because he has AB-negative blood,
which is very rare.
- It only happens in certain families.
- One in 300,000.
I know.
I have it too.
You said Jarod
saved your life twice.
He found me a heart.
You stay with me, little brother.
I'm gonna get you to a hospital.
[Weakly]
It's too late, Jarod.
Don't you say that.
Look at me!
Come on, just-just think-
Think about all the good times
we're gonna have together.
- I'm sorry, Jarod.
- For what?
F-For everything.
[Kyle Gasps]
No.
[Sobs]
- Jarod gave you his brother's heart.
- Yeah.
And ever since
the transplant, he calls.
Notjust to check up on me...
- but to see how I'm really doing.
- Mmm.
Jarod's like the older brother
that I never had.
Mr. Lee seemed to think
that was real important.
Thank you,J.R.
Sam will take you home.
Come on, Tin Man.
[Basketball Bouncing]
Mr. Lee's
really narrowing it down.
Compassion, empathy,
desire for justice-
all the things
that makeJarod, Jarod.
Do you think he'll be able
to anticipateJarod's next move...
- to actually catch him?
- Unless we get there first.
- [Metal Clanging]
- Miss Parker? Miss Parker.
[Clears Throat] About that phone call
from Lee to your father's office?
- What about it?
- Well, it wasn't actually for Mr. Parker.
Well, did it go
to his office or didn't it?
Yes. Tech-
I mean, technically, yes.
- Technically?
- Well, there was a second phone line...
recently installed
in your father's suite.
It seems now he's sharing
his office with someone else.
And I traced the call
from Mr. Lee to that new line.
And just whose new line
might that be, as if I didn't know?
- Brigitte.
- Well, why did I even ask?
Hold on, she's not there. I, uh-
[Clears Throat]
L-I just intercepted another call
between her and Mr. Lee.
She just left in a limo.
Mr. Lee's limo.
They're goin'to getJarod.
[Mr. Lee]
We're going to getJarod now.
- So, tell me how you found him.
- Simple.
- [Typing]
- By interviewing people whose lives
Jarod has touched...
I've been able
to understand how he thinks.
And more importantly,
how he feels.
We were able to break the code-
the pattern ofhis behavior.
Jarod has a need to defend
those abused by power.
Because of this need,
he's drawn to predictable situations.
- Such as?
- Those that are related...
to the trauma of his childhood, and the guilt
he feels over the abuse of his work.
Anna has extensively researched
potential scenarios...
that would attract him.
We've successfully isolated
the one that will lead us to him.
It's a shame my future stepchildren
won't be there to share the moment.
- [Chuckles]
- [Giggles]
- You're deliciously naughty. [Laughs]
- [Giggling]
Why, thank you,
Mr. Lee.
A blind Chinese guy,
a bimbo and a limousine-
how hard can that be to find?
[Slams Down Receiver]
Two and a half years
we've been chasing Jarod...
and that bitch
is gonna bring him in.
Lyle, are you all right?
You look terrible.
- You ought to see the other guy.
- Bad hair day?
I was abducted by...
several of Lee's men.
They obviously
got the best of me, but I...
put a whole lot of hurtin'
on 'em in the process.
Lee questioned me for hours,
but finally gave up.
Had his enforcers drop me off
in the middle of nowhere.
[Clucks Tongue] Oh.
Well, you can thank Bridget...
- for your quality time with Lee.
- Brigitte?
- [Affirmative Grunt]
- He's working for her.
Yeah. She's gonna bring Jarod in.
Well, not if we get there first.
I've triangulated the signal
from Brigitte's cell phone.
And this should lead us
right to Brigitte and to Mr. Lee.
Oh, and they'll lead us
right toJarod.
[Laughs]
- [Chattering]
- [Beeping]
[Computerized Voice]
Thank you, Jarod.
You're welcome.
Abner gets to come home
where he should have been all the time.
How can we ever repay you
for all you have done for us?
- This is repayment enough.
- Oh.
Good luck, Abner.
[Brigitte]
Ironic place to find Jarod.
A genius at a facility
for the mentally challenged.
Yes, Jarod has discovered
that many of the residents...
have been intentionally
misdiagnosed.
The director keeps them here
in order to defraud their insurance...
and their parents.
They're trapped- prisoners in an
institution that denies them their freedom.
And Jarod's here to liberate them.
How noble.
- Wait.
- [Helicopter Approaching]
No. No, no, no, no!
I don't believe this!
- What the hell are you doing here?
- Good to see you too.
- Where is he?
- I'm supposed to bring him in!
- Like hell you are.
- Nobody's cuttin' me out of this,
least of all you.
Stop your arguing!
We must get toJarod now!
He's gone.
You have a gift
for the obvious.
He knew
we were coming.
He's known all along.
Intercepted your memo.
- What memo?
- From Brigitte to Daddy...
requesting the unique services
of Mr. Lee to catch Jarod.
- He couldn't have done this alone.
- You blew it, angel.
[Mr. Lee]
Someone informed him of our presence.
Anna.
[Helicopter Rotors Whirring]
Thank you
for all of your help.
After all the people
you've helped...
it was about time
that someone helped you.
What you did took a lot of courage.
You bought me the time I needed.
I'd do it again in a heartbeat. I mean,
what you did for my family and my nephew-
I'm the one who should
be thanking you.
- I hope someday we'll meet again.
- I hope so too.