[Slapping Sound]
I don't understand, Sydney.
Why are these guys hitting each other?
- F.E.S., Broots.
- F.E. S?
Forced External Stimulus.
I'm studying the way twins react
to identically implied aggression.
[Scoffs] Looks to me like they're just
beatin' the bejesus out of each other.
- Did you need something, Broots?
- Oh, yeah.
I, uh-This came for you.
Looks kind of important.
"Your immediate attention is needed"?
In Jarod's handwriting.
You've never seen this.
Seen what?
[Chuckling]
[Imitating Curly]
Nyuk, nyuk, nyuk. Yee!
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent
every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
[Miss Parker]
He defends the weak and abused.
Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
Hey, Barker! You got a visitor!
- What?
- You got company!
- There's a guy out front wants to see ya.
- A guy?
- Yeah, with the dogs.
- Dogs?
[Barking Continues, Growling]
[Kissing Sounds]
That's it. Take it. Mm-hmm.
[Laughing]
Come on. Come on.
Do you like dogs, Mr. Barker?
Not as much as you do.
Roman fighting rottweilers.
Pound for pound, the most perfect
killing machine on four legs, huh?
Give me a dog over a person any day.
Oh, Jack Brevins. I'm your P.O.
Parole officer?
We weren't supposed to meet
till next week.
Yeah, I know. I was in the neighborhood.
Big Daddy here needed to be wormed.
The baby needed to be wormed,
didn't you, sweetie?
- Yeah. So, how you gettin' on?
- Fine.
- No problems with the job?
- It's a little slice of heaven.
That's funny. You're a funny guy.
- I gotta get back to work.
- Uh, let's take a walk.
- It's not my break yet.
- Hey.
It's okay.
[Dog Growls]
[Boat Horn Blows]
You know, a lot of guys have trouble
adjusting to freedom after bein' locked up.
You were up for, what- six and change?
- Mr. Brevins.
- Jack.
Look, I appreciate all the personal attention,
Jack, but I have to get back to work.
I can't afford to lose this job. I don't want
to end up back in prison, now do I?
You don't know how it works, do you?
You behave yourself,
you do exactly what you're told...
everything's gravy.
You get an attitude,
you disrupt the program...
I pick up the phone, and you got a number
on your back before breakfast.
We'll continue this later.
Oh, hey. I read your file.
[Sniffs]
Consider that an advance.
That's good stuff. None of that
jailhouse crap you used to shoot.
I'll be in touch.
Come on, babies. Let's go. Let's go for a ride.
Come on. Come on. Yes. Yes.
- Go for a ride in the car. We love the car. Yeah.
- [Barking]
I hope you came alone.
I believe you're safe, for the moment.
- You look good, Sydney.
- You too. And I like the artwork.
Just trying to blend in.
Are you going to tell me why I'm here,
or is this some kind of game we're playing?
Oh, it's no game, especially to them.
[Sydney's Voice]
Michelle, am I his father?
[Michelle's Voice] Sydney,
Nicholas doesn't know he's your son.
I don't understand. Why did you-
[Water Running]
What the-Who are-You're-
The word is-
[Whispers] "naked."
I bought groceries.
[Chuckles]
- Hope you like sugar.
- Who are you?
Sandi, with an "I."
- How did you get in here?
- Desk clerk.
He's a friend ofJack's.
- Jack Brevins?
- Is there another?
You want something to drink?
I've got kiwi-papaya juice.
A friend turned me on to it.
It's fantastic.
In fact, it's fantastically fantastic.
So, you got an awesome view.
It's a lumberyard.
Well, they used to be trees,
so that almost makes it a forest.
- You said thatJack sent you?
- Mmm. Like a housewarming gift.
He said to think of me
as a "living, breathing welcome mat."
There is no way this is going to happen.
- What-What are you doing?
- Look, I'm really exhausted.
I had a really long day.
I can't go. If you send me away,
Jack'll think I pissed you off.
Jack can get real nasty
when he doesn't get what he wants.
Hey. Pretty lady.
Who is she?
[Scoffs]
She's my mother.
No. Really? Oh, that's so sweet.
God, I haven't seen my mom
in nearly, uh, two years.
So, what were you in prison for?
- Does it matter?
- Well, a girl likes to know who she's drinkin' with.
I mean, you didn't kill somebody,
did you?
Okay. I can drop you off on my way downtown,
or I can call you a cab.
- Those are your choices.
- Or I could go with you.
Are you in some kind of trouble?
- Well, that depends.
- Depends on what?
On you.
We should get some more
of this kiwi juice.
It's a passion fruit.
Can I help you?
Oh, I'm Dr. Sydney. I was called in
to consult on the Stamatis case.
I wasn't told about any consultation.
Well, there must have been some kind
of clerical error, Nurse... Roberts.
I've traveled a long way, and I'm tired.
Now, we can get on with this,
or I can take it up with your supervisor.
It's up to you.
[Sighs]
That's Mr. Stamatis's room.
Oh, Nurse. How's he doing?
Considering he may have
only hours to live...
he and Mrs. Stamatis are doing fine.
Thank you.
I think it's sad when things change.
I used to come here when I was a kid.
There was this gigantic slide.
It must've been 50, 60 feet high.
Kind of like this monster?
[Chuckling]
But... it was so much bigger.
Maybe because you were
a little peanut back then.
Uh, excuse me. I'll be right back.
Don't eat the sand, baby.
It's almost like looking into a mirror.
Yes, it is.
Do you mind if I sit down?
It's a public park.
I used to wonder what it would be like
to grow up so close to somebody...
to have a bond like that
that could never be broken.
You sound like a man
who misses his family.
Is it that obvious?
Some people wear their lives
in their eyes...
and some on their skin.
- How long you been out of prison?
- Almost a week.
I wish you luck.
Come on, boys. Mama's gotta
get home and get supper started.
They look just like their father.
What did you say?
- Who are you?
- My name is Jarod.
Bobby, your husband, and I...
we were in the same cell block
at Mayfield Pen.
This picture?
It was taken three days
before he was released.
Lupe, I don't mean to upset you.
I know it's only been a few weeks
since Bobby was-was killed.
Bobby had so much going for him
when he got out of prison.
The boys, a goodjob, me.
It doesn't make any sense.
He wasn't a violent man.
- It doesn't make any sense.
- I know.
That's why I'm here.
No, you listen to me!
You miss one more appointment
at this office...
I'm gonna slap a warrant on your ass so fast,
you won't know what hit you.
Yeah. Right. Right.
You're not as stupid as you look.
8.00 tonight.
So, how's freedom treatin' you
on this fine morning, Jarod?
- It takes gettin' used to.
- It's a big world, full of surprises.
Kinda like that surprise I found
in my shower yesterday.
She didn't give you any lip, did she?
No. Just wasn't expecting guests,
that's all.
It's like ridin'a bicycle.
You know how to ride a bicycle, don't ya?
You get on and you just-
[Laughing]
- Now, that's funny.
- Yeah.
You know what else is funny? Here I am, fresh
out of prison, and already my parole officer...
he's supplied me with enough smack
to kill a horse...
and a female
who may or may not be underage.
Now, if the intention is to ease
the inmate back into society...
this seems a little bit rushed.
Well, I didn't expect you to shoot
the entire bag in one sitting.
As for the bimbo,
she's 22 goin' on 15.
Come on. Sit down.
I just like my people
to be relaxed when they work.
And by "work," you don't mean
the metal shop, I assume.
Jarod Barker.
Arrested at age 14...
for petty larceny.
Spent six months
in the Krendler Youth Camp.
Three convictions for narcotics
and weapons charges.
Two aggravated assault convictions...
and a handful of parole violations.
I won a spelling bee once
when I was seven.
Look.
You know how many opportunities are out there
for an ex-con with a history of violence?
Zero. Nada.
Life as you know it is over.
Be at this address tonight at 10.00 p.m.
Oh, and, Jarod, one more thing.
Stay away from Lupe Harmon.
How'd you know I talked to Lupe?
It's my job to know what you do.
You did time with her husband up in Mayfiield.
What's his name?
- What was his name?
- Bobby.
Right. Bobby. Terrible situation.
- He was one of your guys, wasn't he?
- Just stay away from the widow.
She can only cause you trouble.
You're the boss, right?
May I join you?
Sydney.
What are you doing here?
I thought you might need a friend.
Yeah.
- I like it here.
- Mmm.
Especially in the morning,
when everything still seems possible.
Sorry.
It's all right.
Thank you.
He's only 54 years old, Sydney.
It's not fair.
No, it's not.
How did you know that George was here?
An old friend sent me a message.
Michelle, if you want someone
to talk to...
someone to hold on to, I'm here.
- [Sighs]
- What is it?
It's Nicholas.
He's not handling this very well.
He's so, so angry.
It's painful
to lose someone you love.
He still doesn't know
that you're his real father.
It's not important now.
My husband is dying, Sydney.
Would you pray with me?
Of course I will.
[Sandi]
I started dancin'when I was 17.
- Were you with the ballet?
- Yeah, right.
Cleared 400 a week,
and that was just workin' topless.
Topless?
What? You've never been
in a strip joint before?
Naked women swinging
around metal poles?
Strange men cramming sweaty wads
of money into strange women's panties?
- I would remember something like that.
- Yeah.
Did you, uh, tellJack
that we took a walk in the park?
I might have mentioned it.
What you workin' on?
I'm tryin' to figure out why a man
with a wife, two kids and a future...
would throw it all away for 256 bucks.
Did you know Bobby Harmon?
No. That's terrible.
You know,
I read he had small children.
Twin boys.
Five years old.
I gotta go.
Hey, Jarod?
I only danced for a couple of months.
And I never-you know, for money.
I just don't want you to think
that I was that kind of girl.
What kind of girl is that?
[No Audible Dialogue]
Dr. Stamatis, my name is Sydney.
I know who you are.
I have had this conversation
in my mind a hundred times.
I want you to know that I have
the highest regard for you...
and your relationship
with Michelle and Nicholas.
Do you still love her?
You don't need to answer.
I see it in your eyes. [Gasps]
Oh.
Thank you.
[Panting]
Nicholas... doesn't know
that you're his real father.
No.
I want you to tell him after.
I want you to take care of our son, Sydney.
- We don't have to-
- Promise.
Promise.
I promise.
Nicholas.
- [Groans]
- Nicholas. Nicholas!
- [Men Cheering]
- [Rock]
Hey, Jarod.
Right on time.
You didn't have any trouble
findin'the place, did you?
It's amazing. You tell the cabdriver
where to go, and he gets you there.
Ain't it though? Let me introduce you to your
new partner. Pat Rush, Jarod Barker.
Jack says you did time at Mayfield.
Six years, eight months, three days.
I did a two-spot there.
I don't remember your face.
That's because I like to hang by myself.
[Scoffs]
That's cool.
If you dogs are through sniffin'each other,
I'd like to get down to business.
My source informs me that there is
a very accessible situation out in Meadowhills.
That's a new development
out near the lake.
Houses start at half a million.
Gentlemen, it's rotting on the vine.
All we have to do
is go out there and pick it.
- I don't know.
- What did you say?
I got a bad feelin', that's all.
Son, you don't know...
what feelin' bad is really all about.
[Growling]
Yo, Jack! Phone call!
- Take a message.
- It's the Mexican.
You boys have a beer,
and when I get back...
I'll tell you all about
Myra and Stanley Bellows.
Guy's certifiable.
Word is he's been runnin' this
home invasion scam for almost five years.
- "Word is"?
- A guy who knows a guy.
Well, someone should stop him.
One call from Brevins,
and we're both back inside.
Don't even think about runnin' to the cops
unless you want to end up like that Harmon dude.
- Bobby Harmon?
- The kid wasn't blown away by accident.
My guy says Harmon was about to go to the D.A.,
drop Brevins's whole operation on the table.
That's quite a little scam he's got goin'.
Career criminals do his dirty work...
and if we refuse, well, he violates
our parole and doubles our time.
Not to mention those frickin' dogs.
Guy loves those frickin' dogs.
How did he know that Bobby Harmon
was gonna turn him in?
Have you made one move since you've
been out he didn't know about?
[Bell Tolling]
How'd you find me?
- Your father said you might come here.
- Ha!
"My father"? That's a laugh.
This will be hard for you to understand...
and you have every right to be angry,
but there were reasons-
Reasons?
What reasons could there be...
for hiding the truth from someone about
who they are and where they came from?
Just before you were born...
I was involved with some people-
very dangerous people-
who made threats against my life.
To protect me, your mother left
without telling me about you.
- Did you look for me?
- I told you.
I didn't know you'd been born.
And now I don't have a father...
or a family or a life.
Nicholas.
It isn't true.
You have a wonderful mother
and a father who loves you.
He's not my father.
You're wrong, Nicholas.
Being a father is more than giving life.
It's being there in the middle of the night
when you're sick or afraid or alone.
And it's teaching you how to ride a bike,
how to catch a fish...
how to tie a tie.
Being a parent
isn't about the big moments.
It's about the little ones.
Have you ever felt those things
for anyone?
There was someone- a child.
Your father loves you very much-
as much as if he'd given you life.
- Don't throw that away.
- Why are you here?
After everything is said and done...
maybe you and I can be friends.
[Leaves Rustling]
Hello? Is someone there?
[Brevins] The key is to convince these people
that you are serious...
that you will kill them...
if they do not do exactly
what you want them to do.
- And what about Bobby Harmon?
- What about him?
I don't want to end up dead on someone's
living room floor because you forgot something.
[Sighs]
Harmon was a mistake.
End of story.
How much money did you say
these people keep in the house?
It could be north of $100,000. Apparently,
the old gentleman does not trust banks.
Just make sure you kill this power box
before you enter the house.
That disables the floodlights,
the security system.
It'll keep the rent-a-cops off your tail.
And what do we do when we're finished?
You stop by my house, and we split up the money.
We go in 12 hours.
Everybody ready?
Ready.
They say it takes the patience of a saint
to tend to a prosperous garden.
You know about flowers?
I know about patience.
I used to send Bobby
a single red rose every Friday.
He used to put them
in the window of his cell.
He said they made him feel like
there was something worth living for.
You know,
Bobby wrote me twice a week.
He never mentioned anyone named Jarod.
Oh, yeah, he probably wouldn't.
I was transferred to Bobby's cell block
three weeks before he was released...
so, you know, he probably had...
other things on his mind.
- Come here, baby.
- You have great kids.
You know, in the park you said
you'd come here for a reason.
I think Bobby was set up.
Set up?
Why would anyone want
to hurt my husband?
That's what I'm trying to find out.
Where are my manners? Uh, please,
can I get you something to drink?
- That would be very nice.
- It'll have to be water or kiwi juice.
- Kiwi juice?
- Yeah, kiwi-papaya. It was Bobby's favorite.
There must be a dozen bottles
left in the refrigerator.
[Chuckles]
- Busy day?
- Oh, God.
Jarod, I didn't see you standing there.
That's surprising. I thought
you were keepin' a close eye on me.
I bought some steaks and a bottle of wine.
I thought maybe we could go up on the roof
and have ourselves a cookout.
- You knew Bobby Harmon.
- Jarod, l-
Please don't lie to me.
I knew Bobby.
Why didn't you tell me?
I was scared.
I mean, Bobby and me were friends.
No, it wasn't like that.
He loved his wife and his kids.
You told Brevins that Bobby
was going to turn him in to the police.
No. No, I never mentioned that
to anybody except for-
Except for who?
Pat Rush.
And what about me?
What's the deal with me?
Jack wanted me to get close.
Jarod, I had no choice.
This has something to do with that guy
I saw you talking to at the convalescent home.
- You followed me?
- Who was he? Just another sucker?
Or maybe just a former client
that you took pity on?
He's my little brother.
His name is Michael. The doctors say
he'll never be any better than he is now.
It was raining, and Michael had
invited me to dinner and the movies.
He loves the movies.
I, uh, never saw
the other car run the light.
Is that why your mother
won't speak to you?
Yeah, I was his big sister, you know?
I was supposed to be
looking out for him.
I thought that paying for Michael's
medical care might turn things around...
and make her understand
that it was an accident.
Private hospitals are expensive.
Three thousand dollars a month.
That's how you got involved
with Brevins.
You needed the money
to take care of your little brother.
I had nothing to do with
what happened to Bobby, I swear.
After Bobby was killed, I got scared,
and I was gonna go to the police, but...
Jack threatened to hurt Michael.
I didn't know what else to do.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
I promise.
[No Audible Dialogue]
You down for this?
Cut the power, bust open the side door,
wait for you to come through the front.
- Everything by the numbers.
- By the numbers.
- You don't seem convinced.
- We screw this up, we're both dead men.
Well, we better not screw it up then.
Notify all cars in the area
of Fourth and Grove.
Bank robbery, First National.
[Angry Grumbling]
[Footsteps]
[Grunts]
Oh, Jack?
- Wake up!
- What?
- It is okay if I still call you Jack, right?
- Barker?
Is that you, Barker? You stinkin' punk!
- I'm gonna burn you for this!
- I told you this was gonna blow up in our faces!
Rush? Is that you, kid?
Kid, listen to me! You're makin'
a life decision here! Make the right one!
- Let's just split right now!
- Would you just chill out?
You said he's been doin' this
home invasion thing for the last five years.
- So what?
Open your eyes, dumb-ass!
Look around!
There's more loot here than we're ever
gonna find in any cul-de-sac in the suburbs.
- Ain't that right, Jack?
- You clowns are robbing me?
That's what this is all about?
You're robbing me?
It stings, don't it, Jack?
Just like it must've stung...
Bobby Harmon...
when you killed him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Why are you talkin' about Harmon?
Let's just do this and get out of here!
- A little change of plans, Pat.
- What are you talkin' about?
You see, I'm not exactly
who I pretend to be.
The truth is, I've never been arrested before,
but you will be.
I'll make sure they put you away for aiding
and abetting in the murder of Bobby Harmon.
- Kill him, Pat!
- Who are you?
I'm still tryin' to figure that one out.
But as for you? It's over.
- I don't think so.
- Are you gonna shoot me?
- I'll do it. I swear.
- Go ahead.
- Do it!
- [Clicks]
[Angry Grunt]
Back off, Barker!
It was a pleasure
doing business with you.
Well, looks like
it's just you and me, Jack.
What do you want from me?
Did you kill Bobby Harmon?
You're gonna rot in prison, Barker.
- Answer my question!
- Go to hell!
Okay, fine.
I'm just gonna have to take it up with
your four-legged friends in the next room.
Hey, what are you doin'?
Let's just see how much you
really love those little guys.
Actually, I'll start with the little one.
[Whimpering]
Junior? Hey, Barker,
what the hell are you doin'?
- Junior? Here, Junior!
- Barker, don't hurt that dog!
- [Gunshot]
- [Dog Whining]
No! You son of a bitch!
You killed my dog?
Well, are you ready to answer
my question now, Jack?
Look, you leave
Big Daddy alone, huh?
Well, Big Daddy's gonna fry
unless you answer my question.
You hurt that dog, man,
I will cut your heart out!
- All right, Jack. Have it your way.
- No. Barker?
- All right, Big Daddy. You're up.
- Barker! No, wait! Barker!
All right, I did it! I did it!
You did what?
You... did... what?
I killed Bobby Harmon.
I made it look like it was a robbery.
How many other home invasion robberies
using parolees were you involved with?
- L-
- [Shouts] How many?
Uh, 10, 12.
Come on. Take this blindfold off me,
will you, man?
- Sure thing, Jack.
- [Dog Whining]
What the hell? Hey!
I heard my dogs.
- I heard you shoot!
- What, this?
Neat trick, huh? Oh, one other thing.
- Look at this!
- [Tape: Dog Barking]
Huh?
[Dogs Barking In Rhythm.
"Jingle Bells"]
- [Continues]
- Merry Christmas, Jack.
I'll get you, Barker! Damn you!
[Barking Continues]
- Barker!
- [Stops]
Pardon me, Mrs. Stamatis, but the doctor
thinks you should say good-bye now.
- I don't think I can do this.
- I can go in with you.
No, no.
L- I need to be alone with him.
But Nicholas should be here.
He needs to say good-bye to him.
Hi.
- Hey.
It's all right. Don't be afraid.
- I'm not.
- [Sniffles]
I love you... so much.
Always.
It just doesn't seem fair.
We have so much to do.
We have so much more to share.
Shh.
We will be...
together again, I know it.
Come here. Come here.
- Oh, my baby.
- [Quiet Crying]
Where's Nick, huh?
Oh.
Sorry I'm late.
- I'm here, Dad.
- Nick.
- I'm here.
- Hey, buddy.
Hey.
[Monitor. Steady Beeping]
[Bell Tolling]
"Thank you" will just never be enough.
I'm glad I was of some comfort to you.
What now?
Well, I go home and try to get on
with the rest of my life.
A good life.
Good-bye, Sydney.
Until we meet again.
I never thought I could feel
more alone than I did...
when I heard my father was dying.
- I was wrong.
- Time's a great healer.
Time. Is that how you got over
losing your family?
I will never get over that...
not as long as I live.
My office number at the university...
if you ever-
if you ever want to talk.
Who shall I say I am,
if your assistant asks?
You can say that you're my friend.
[Engine Starts]
That's a pretty good start.
Well, a man can't ask
for more than an opportunity.
And I owe any chance I have
of knowing my son to you, Jarod.
Well, everyone deserves to have a family.
Jarod?
Didn't I teach you how to tie a tie?
Yes.
Yes, you did.