[Dogs Yipping]
[Helicopter Whirring]
[Broots]
Miss Parker, this must be what hell looks like.
You know, frozen over.
Looks like
an old research lab.
What do you think
Jarod's father was looking for?
[Sydney]
What is it, Miss Parker?
It's a brass trigger
for an incendiary device.
Whatever was going on down here,
Jarod didn't want anyone to find out about it.
Yeah, but why would he want to
cover his tracks now?
Maybe it wasn'tJarod
who set off the bomb.
[Miss Parker]
Then who did and why?
Combo to Al Capone's vault?
Ah, just some burned-out trash.
- [Sam] Miss Parker!
- [Miss Parker] What is it, Sam?
- We found another body.
- [Broots] Do you think it's Jarod?
No. Jarod's been a phoenix one too many times
for me to believe he's still in these ashes.
Give my daughter my ring.
And this photo.
Tell her that I love her.
[Jarod]
I will.
Captain, what was it
that my father found here?
Wasn't just any human D.N.A.
They were deciphering.
It was yours.
[Gasps]
Demons live in your dreams.
[Jarod]
They visit.
The ones who cause
you and your father trouble...
were at the research station.
What did they find?
What they search for
is no longer there.
Before your father left,
he told me he was going to find his son.
He would stare for hours
at the constellation...
talk about the son that he knew
he would one day find.
- The constellation?
- Yes, uh-
Gemini.
He told me if I ever met you
to give you these.
Is this him?
- Is this my father?
- Yes.
Gemini. What does it mean?
He left a message for you.
This is where you'll find him.
This is where
you'll find your father.
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent
every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
[Miss Parker]
He defends the weak and abused.
Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
- [Chattering]
- [Wheels Squeaking]
I received a call from the Triumvirate
this morning. Big Mutumbo himself.
He knows thatJarod and his father
were in the Arctic...
and he knows about how our project up there
has been compromised.
[Mr. Parker]
Damn. What did he say?
Except for the fact thatJarod's still out there,
he was, strangely enough, elated.
He's taking the compromising of the research as-
and I quote- "a sign from God."
Well, that's an odd comment
coming from an admitted atheist.
Mutumbo's ordered the acceleration
of Project Gemini.
- He wants delivery A.S.A.P.
- [Elevator Bell Dings]
- Is that a problem?
- No.
But Miss Parker might be.
Like mother like daughter.
You know how Catherine
felt about Gemini.
Secrecy has always been
the key to Gemini.
I'll handle my daughter.
Everything's gonna be just fine.
[Wheels Squeaking]
[Young Jarod]
I finished my building.
I'm finished!
[Young Sydney]
This one's been with us for only 36 hours...
and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
- [Young Jarod] Hey. I'm finished.
- Hi, Jarod. I'm Sydney.
- I'll be taking care of you for a while.
- Why? Where's my mom and dad?
[Clears Throat]
I, uh, know it's none of my business, Syd...
but sometimes memory lane
could be a dead-end street.
You're right, Broots.
None of your business.
What is it?
Um, the bodies found in the Arctic
came up negative forJarod.
Still, I can't figure out how
he escaped that inferno.
- [Phone Rings]
- Jarod's always been too smart
for anyone to figure out.
- [Beeps]
- [Jarod] It's cold in the Arctic, Sydney.
Almost as frigid as the Centre.
- Thank God you got out of there alive.
- Barely.
- But I made some interesting discoveries.
- Tell me.
What? The boys in Blue Cove haven't kept you
in the D.N.A. Loop? Or should I say strand?
I wasn't even aware
that we had a facility up there.
- None of us were.
- They're stirring the genetic stew, Sydney.
Deciphering the human genome.
And not just anyone's. Mine.
My God.
Did you find your father?
No. But I know he risked his life
to find the same answers that I did.
Does the word Gemini
mean anything to you?
The zodiac sign?
- Why?
- I'll ask my father.
- I'm on my way to see him now.
- How will you know how to get there?
- He left me the stars to navigate by.
- [Beeps]
[Door Opens]
Syd, I've known you
all my life.
You knew my mother- how she had a psychiatric
session with you just hours before she died.
- Uh- [Clears Throat] I'm gonna go.
- Sit.
Now, I'm gonna
ask you a question...
and I need to know
the truth.
What is it you want to know?
Did my mother
ever mention a project-
a reference code, anything-
that had to do with the word Gemini?
I'm sorry.
Never heard of it.
Damn it.
My father, Mr. Raines, Lyle-
They're shutting me out of something big.
Something they called
Project Gemini.
Uh, you mean like the twins.
Since Dr. Know-Nothing
can't help...
I guess that's, uh-
No. We're going to find out.
[Door Opens, Closes]
Excuse me.
Number seven, please.
- Right there.
- Thank you.
[Phone Disconnect Signal Beeping]
[Rattle]
[Shouts]
- Where is he?
- Please don't hurt me, man.
Where is my father?
Jarod?
- Are you all right, Coop?
- Yeah, Sarah. Everything's fine.
- You just go back to work.
- Are you sure?
Ah, absolutely. You go on now.
Thank you very much.
- [Door Closes]
- You'reJarod?
- You're the major's son?
- Yes, I am.
- Where is he?
- He left real fast.
- Almost like someone was hot on his trail.
- Men in Town Cars.
And the scariest man
was a woman.
A brunette?
Blonde.
Suckin' on a lollipop.
Shejust left.
Was my father hurt
when he left?
No. That-That's my blood.
They pushed my nose into the wall.
They-They damn near
broke my nose too.
Like I said, I thought maybe
you was them comin'back.
I'm sorry that you had to
get involved with this, Coop.
I didn't tell 'em anything.
Really, I didn't.
I'd do anything
for the major.
- I'm gonna miss our talks.
- Did he stay here a lot?
Well, off and on
for the past 20 years.
Never was sure which direction
he was headed to next...
but I knew it was wherever
he thought you might be.
Did he give you any idea
where he might be going?
No. He said I'd be
safer not knowin'.
- Do you have another phone book around?
- Sure.
Sarah, you got an extra
phone book on your cart?
Yeah. Here.
Take two.
Thanks, darlin'.
- What you lookin' for?
- What isn't here.
- I found something bizarre.
- What?
- Like hair on your head?
- No. That would be fantasy.
This is real.
This is very real.
[Miss Parker]
An inter-Centre memo?
[Broots] A very old one.
From your mother to the Triumvirate.
"I vehemently disagree with
Dr. Raines's conclusions about Gemini...
"and despite some humane
advances being made at Pakor...
"I cannot in good conscience
endorse moving forward with the project.
"While it represents a potentially major
breakthrough for mankind...
"one must wonder if mankind is
or ever will be prepared for its ramifications.
Catherine Parker. "
This is dated just days
before she was killed.
Gemini. Isn't that the same thing you overheard
your father talking about?
- Mom was against it.
- I'm still searching Gemini...
and I can't seem to find
anything about it.
Well, let's keep pushing, Broots.
And while you're at it, let's find out about Pakor.
[Broots]
Okay, Miss Parker.
[Airplane Passing Overhead]
[Man On P.A.]
Attention. Ground school group class B-5...
will be held today in
Instruction Room 204.
Please make note of the change.
Excuse me. I'm sorry to bother you,
but I'm looking for someone.
Have you seen this man?
The new instructor?
Sure.
- Is he here now?
- Right behind you.
Not behind you behind you.
Behind you.
Up there.
Does he have a radio with him?
Just wait. He's almost finished.
Why? You know him?
He's my father.
Oh, my God.
No. Dad.
No.
- No!
- Gotcha.
Let's go.
We're done.
Move! Move!
Let's go!
- We need help!
- Dad!
Dad!
[Man]
Oh, my God. It's Dan Wilson.
It's tragic. Dan sneakin'up in your dad's plane.
Major Charles's quarters
is right back here.
Your father must have left
early this morning.
Looks like he left
in a hurry too.
Thank you.
[Shotgun Cocks]
Give me one reason
not to shoot you.
Carrie.
Your father sent me.
My father?
He wanted you to have these.
My father's dead,
isn't he?
[Broots] I didn't find what I was looking for,
but I found some good stuff.
Nothing about Gemini
or Pakor, I'm afraid.
But- But...
maybe something about
your father's secretiveness.
- And?
- I'm- I'm pretty sure it's aboutJarod's father.
They know where he is.
Well, your father and Raines have been
focusing in on one of the Arctic victims.
A Captain Russ Osborne.
Raines suspects that Osborne
was chummy with Major Charles...
and may have even helped him
get away from the research station.
- We got an address?
- Osborne's only next of kin was his daughter...
and she owns a small flight school
down in Barney Fife territory.
Uh, North Carolina.
So the assumption would be that-
Major Charles might be there.
- Syd know this?
- No.
He's been in nonstop meetings
all day in the Tower.
Get him.
He'll drop it forJarod.
We're out of here.
Floyd's holding an empty barber chair
for you, Broots. What's the problem?
Well, see-
[Clears Throat]
This is where your father's
secrets come in.
[Miss Parker]
Centre travel records.
My father already sent Bridget.
[Woman On TV] The cause
of this bizarre crash is still undetermined.
However, several eyewitnesses who I spoke to
here at the Osborne Flight School...
indicated that they heard
a small explosive sound-
Jarod's father is not dead.
[Woman]
Dead on the scene is the pilot, Dan Wilson.
[Groans]
I'd be sick to my stomach too.
Excuse me.
Here I go again.
[Sighs]
Morning sickness.
Hell of a price to pay
for an heir.
No Sweeper team, no backup.
No follow-through.
Heirs have disappeared around here
for a hell of a lot less.
- That's enough, angel.
- No. Not enough, Daddy.
You sent a rank amateur...
to do a job you knew
I wanted myself.
We're talking about
the man who killed Mom...
and you didn't trust me.
Shame on you.
[Carrie's Voice]
To fathers.
You know, the last time
I talked to my dad...
he mentioned seeing an old friend
who had recently arrived in the Arctic.
- My dad.
- Mm-hmm.
He admired your dad
a lot, Jarod.
His courage and tenacity.
They were workin' together toward
exposing the research being done up there.
God, I just wish he could have
finished what he started.
Carrie...
your father's death
won't be in vain.
I promise you.
But in order to stop
what's going on...
I have to find my father
and help him.
Did he say anything while he was here
that could help me?
He spent most of his time reading files
and working on his laptop.
Most of all
he loved to fly though.
He said it was
his one release.
Sure left here in a hurry.
Mm-hmm. He rushed back from town,
said some strangers were askin' about him.
He said hejust had this gut feeling
that it was time to go.
And then he made me promise
to ditch his car.
You have his car?
- Find something?
- Yes. The one with nothing.
And a phone number.
[Sighs]
[Beeping]
[Line Rings]
[Woman]
Pakor Frozen Foods is closed.
Our office hours
are 8:00 a.m. To 5:00-
- [Beeps]
- What'd you find?
[Jarod]
Hopefully...
my father.
[Miss Parker] Sydney, what do you mean
you're not going to North Carolina?
[Sydney]
New duties beckon.
Since when isn'tJarod
a priority one for you?
I'd love to wax philosophical...
but right now I'm busy.
And you have a trip to take.
[Chuckles]
I'll call you
from North Carolina.
Good luck with
your new duties, Syd.
[Mr. Parker's Voice]
I do have an office, you know.
Gemini.
Gemini is not something two people
chat about at a urinal on SL 10.
Gemini?
There are very few secrets,
Mr. Parker.
Unfortunately,
that's a fact.
[Clears Throat]
What do you want, Sydney?
I want Gemini.
If it is the reality
I know it to be...
I want to be
project coordinator.
Raines might give you
an argument about that.
Not even Raines can deny
that I am the most qualified.
- There are younger people.
- And how many haveJarod on their résumé?
Very good point.
I'll think on it.
Sydney, let me ask you something.
LfJarod were still at the Centre...
would you be making
this pitch to run Gemini?
LfJarod were still
at the Centre...
there'd be no need
for Gemini.
Don't look so scared, sweetie.
I'm only twice as mean as I look.
Well, it takes a hell of a lot more
than high heels to scare me, Miss-
And you're sure
Jarod's already left town?
Look, like I said, I kicked his butt
when I saw him sleeping in there.
All right? All he said was
somethin' about headin' down to Florida.
Thank you for your time.
- So, south, Miss Parker?
- She's lying. We're heading north.
[Man On Speaker]
This is Mark in Sector 7.
All clear here. Over.
[Man #2]
Roger that. Checking hallway.
- Security breach in East Wing.
- [Alarm Blaring]
[Grunts]
Oh, my... God in heaven.
It's you!
Dad!
Let me look at you.
Look at you.
It's been so long.
- It's you!
- Dad!
Ah. They found each other.
The question is
what else did they find?
Jarod's father
hit the jackpot.
He got into the data bank
and made off with several disks.
- The embryo disks.
- [Groans]
[Mr. Parker] Then it won't be long
till they find out about Donoterase.
- I'm gonna have to tell Big Mutumbo something.
- [Raines] If I were you...
I'd come clean about
the Centre mistakes...
and hope for benevolence
from Mutumbo.
Tell him everything's
moving along swimmingly...
and we look forward
to his visit.
When in doubt, lie.
Sweetheart.
You go find Jarod
and his father, hmm?
Raines, call Donoterase.
We transfer Gemini
in 24 hours.
[Major Charles]
Doesn't look like much, but we should be safe here.
Looks like all the places
that I've hid out in over the years.
Like father like son.
For years I would
lie awake at night...
wondering what
you would be like...
what you would look like.
But all those sleepless nights wouldn't
prepare me for how nervous I feel right now.
I've missed you so much.
The first few weeks
after you were kidnapped...
we got by on hope
and prayers alone.
Then it wasn't long
before I realized...
that if we were gonna find you,
we'd have to find you ourselves.
And all that time
running for your lives.
Yeah. It seemed that...
everywhere we turned was just
another place to run from Sweepers.
I know the feeling.
But bein' here with you now
makes all that pain go away.
- [Chuckles]
- I really want to see Mom and Emily.
So do I.
I've been searching
for your mother and sister...
almost as long as
I've been lookin' for you.
In an attempt to rescue you, l-
I was separated from them.
What happened?
A woman named Catherine Parker
tried to help...
but things went wrong.
The Centre came after me.
And when it was safe, I went back.
But your mother and Emily
were gone.
I don't even know
if they're still alive.
But they are.
I saw them...
two years ago.
Thank God.
We'll find them together.
There's something else.
Kyle.
- He's, uh-
- Yeah. I know, Son. I heard.
I came upon that little town about two days
after your brother was gunned down.
But I'm proud of you, Son.
It's amazing after all
you've been through...
that you still have
the compassion to help others.
I wish I could take
some credit...
for your upbringing-
that I could have
been there with you.
There's some-
something I have to ask you.
Something I was told
and I don't want to believe.
What is it?
Did you kill
Catherine Parker?
What do you think?
[Broots] Donoterase.
Does that name mean anything to you?
Sounds like
an Italian mime troupe.
I was down in
the communications room last night...
and I intercepted a call from Raines
to a place called Donoterase.
Now he said your dad ordered that Gemini
be transferred from there in 24 hours.
- Any clue where Donoterase is?
- Well, I'm working on it.
Now this is their surveillance footage
from Jarod and his Dad.
Besides finding Jarod,
Major Charles also stole some data disks.
And he didn't seem to mind
who saw him do it either.
Any man who'd walk into the Centre and shoot
my mother has the brass ones to do that.
Any way to find out what was
on those disks he lifted?
Well, I'm running an anonymous
sequencing search right now.
- This is a Centre facility?
- Yeah.
And the footage comes from a well-buried
Centre location in Baltimore.
Uh- [Clears Throat]
Bearded...
- by the name of Pakor Frozen Foods.
- Pakor.
My mother referred to that name in the memo
that she wrote about Project Gemini.
Exactly. But why would Jarod's father
be interested in Gemini?
- And what does this have to do with your mother?
- I wish I knew.
- [Computer Beeps]
- What?
Data from the disks he stole.
Broots.
Succotash isn't the only thing
frozen in there.
What kind of nightmare
is this?
[Muttering]
Hey. Wake up. Hey.
It's okay.
You're just havin' a bad dream.
I'm sorry. L-
I've never been much of
a sound sleeper.
Well, what I found
probably won't help.
I broke the code on
one of the disks I stole.
The Centre's
outdoing themselves.
[Jarod]
Pakor Frozen Foods is a biological storage facility.
[Major Charles]
Body parts, fetal tissue.
Cows, sheep, horses.
You name it.
It's Old MacDonald's farm from hell.
And Old MacDonald.
There's human embryos.
- Oh, God.
- What is it?
Ayear ago...
I went searching for my past,
and it led me to...
the fertility clinic that
you and Mom went to to get pregnant.
I found out that it was
owned by the Centre.
My God.
The doctors took
your mother's eggs.
My guess is the Centre has them on ice
somewhere at Pakor Frozen Foods.
Gemini.
I don't know what it all means,
but it's all happening at a place called Donoterase.
[Miss Parker's Voice]
You found Donoterase?
Yeah. And one thing's for sure.
The Centre didn't want anybody to know about it.
It's only about 15 miles from here. That's where
they're gonna transfer the Gemini from.
And if we figured it out,
so haveJarod and his old man.
[Major Charles]
The Centre database was specific on this location...
- but there's nothing here.
- [Jarod] That's what they want people to believe.
[Cow Moos]
- [Jarod] This is Donoterase?
- I don't get it.
- What is it?
- Tire tracks.
- Dual rear wheels.
- Transportation vehicles.
The question is
what are they transporting...
and where is it going?
Hey. What are you
doing here?
[Groans]
I'm not as old as you think.
[Monkey Chitters]
[Chicken Clucking]
[Sheep Bleats]
- [Chicken Squawking]
- [Coos]
[Sheep Bleats]
[Major Charles]
What do you think Old MacDonald's up to?
[Wheels Squeaking]
Time to transport him.
What are you doing here?
Did you really think you could
keep me from finding out about Gemini?
Let me tell you
a little secret about myself.
I love to be underestimated.
So, are you gonna tell me what's goin' on here,
or are we gonna do this dance?
[Footsteps Approaching]
[Sheep Bleats]
[Monkey Chittering]
What are they?
Designer livestock.
Hey! What are you guys
doin' in here?
- Hey!
- [Alarm Blaring]
[Gasps]
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Get 'em!
[Groans]
Move! Move!
[Groaning]
[Alarm Continues]
You all right? Who was that boy?
You looked like you saw a ghost.
Not a ghost.
That boy is me.
They cloned me!
Let me help you. I'm just gonna put
a field dressing on it.
Then when we get somewhere safe,
I'm gonna clean and re-dress it.
- Where we headed?
- As far from the Centre as possible.
- We have to go back.
- No, Jarod. You're hurt.
I'm fine.
We have to go back.
No. I've been searching all my life
for the family the Centre took from me.
And after all these years,
I'm reunited with my son.
I'm not about to risk
losing you again.
This isn't about me.
It's about him.
I don't know who
or what he is.
He's a boy.
And he's part of us.
I've known the Centre to do
some unspeakable things...
but to create a child-
How were they even
able to do it?
Years ago, they asked me to perform
a cloning simulation.
A cell containing the D.N.A. Blueprint
of the desired organism...
is fused into a host ovum.
The newly fertilized egg
develops into an embryo...
and then it's implanted
inside a surrogate mother.
That's why they had
your mother's frozen egg cells.
They implanted my D.N.A. Into her egg,
knowing that it wouldn't reject it.
- It should never have happened.
- But it did.
Regardless of how that boy
came into this world...
he is here,
and he is our family.
We can't let the Centre possess him
like they possessed me.
We need help from the inside.
Do you know anyone
in the Centre you can trust?
[Phone Rings]
This is Sydney.
Please tell me that you had
nothing to do with this.
- With what?
- They took my genetic material...
and like I was some kind of farm animal,
they cloned me.
There were rumors,
of course, but...
- I didn't want to believe them.
- [Jarod] Well, believe it.
I saw him.
I saw me.
It was like looking into a mirror,
only the reflection was 20 years younger.
My God.
This is beyond words.
Sydney, you're the only person
at the Centre we can trust.
Please help me.
- I'll do what I can.
- [Beeps]
[Dial Tone, Beeps]
- [Mr. Lyle] He's magnificent.
- [Mr. Parker] Well, he's a little nervous.
He's never been
outside of Donoterase.
No wonder secrecy has always
been the key to Gemini.
And no wonder Mother
was against it.
- Angel.
- Don't angel me.
- They all knew about this, and I didn't.
- It was a Triumvirate directive.
Eyes only. Hell, I've only known about it
a little while myself.
He is an amazing specimen
though, isn't he?
Is there no depth
to which we won't sink?
- What's bothering you?
- You let Raines play God.
Your father doesn't
let me do anything.
Gemini has always been mine.
- [Wheels Squeaking]
- Gene manipulation, cloning-
It's the cutting edge
of technology.
Welcome to the new millennium,
Miss Parker.
We're 20 years ahead of the sheep cloners
we hear about on the news.
[Mr. Parker] We're producing
the finest beef at our place in Argentina.
Each one designed to be exactly the same.
Now that is progress.
Daddy, Raines didn't design
a better Big Mac.
He designed a human being.
Oh, my God.
He is young Jarod.
Sydney, don't tell me
you knew about this too.
Only four of us
knew about this.
And Mutumbo's people
at the Triumvirate.
Sydney, I've been thinking
about your request...
and, uh,
we're gonna do it.
- I'm overwhelmed, sir. Thank you.
- [Wheels Squeaking]
What request?
I'm making Sydney project
coordinator on Gemini.
And I want him to find out
how he compares to the original Jarod.
There's no way he's going to
test my Pretender.
The boy doesn't belong to you, Raines.
He belongs to the Triumvirate.
And before we deliver him,
I want a performance comparison...
done by the man who knows
more aboutJarod than anybody else!
[Whispers]
Sydney, you're not really gonna participate in this.
Parker, please.
My name is Sydney.
I'll be taking care of you
for a while.
[Jarod's Voice]
What is this place?
[Major Charles]
An old hunting shack.
You, me and your mom were
campin'near here when you were a boy.
A big storm came up
and washed out the road.
We had to take shelter here
till it blew over.
That's funny.
- I don't remember.
- I didn't see it before, but it's still here.
- What?
- The scar.
You were entertaining
your mom.
You climbed up on that ladder, tryin' to
take her mind off the storm, and fell.
You cut your back.
It was just the three of us
for two days.
It was like we were
the only people in the world.
It was only about a week
before the-
The Centre took me.
Jarod.
Catherine Parker told me
some things.
Some awful things happened
to you at the Centre.
- Doesn't matter now.
- It matters to me.
What did they do to you?
[Young Jarod]
I can't do it, Sydney! I can't figure it out!
- You have to.
- How much oxygen is left?
- Less than 48 hours.
- What caused the explosion?
We don't know.
- Fuel?
- You've shut down your gauges.
Data is sketchy,
but little.
- Oxygen?
- You've asked that already.
- Now focus!
- There's nothing that can save us.
It is your job.
It is your duty to save your crew!
- No. I can't do it.
- Of course you can!
Shut down now,
and we all die.
- You too!
- Wait a minute.
I can use the gravitational pull
of the moon to help get us back.
- Pretty good.
- I knew you'd save us all if you wanted to.
- He did well.
- [Raines] Eighty-five seconds quicker...
than Jarod's record
doing the same sim.
[Sydney] But factoring in the technological
awareness available to the boy...
his accomplishment
only just matches Jarod's.
Either way,
it certainly proves his capabilities.
I can't wait to
show him to Mutumbo.
You sound like horse trainers talking about
your prized three-year-old.
[Brigitte]
Another one of your morality issues?
- Like you'd know anything about morality.
- Oh, Miss Parker.
No. Sydney, don't you
even talk to me.
I can't believe you'd even
participate in this.
What is it? A chance to relive
the twisted experiments of your youth?
You know what they must have done
to create that boy.
Do you want your experiment back so badly
that you'd take his replicant instead?
[Whispers]
Miss Parker, you don't understand.
You're right.
I hope I never do.
[Raines]
His inception was flawless.
I even think your mother would have
agreed that the entire Project Gemini...
has been run
completely aboveboard.
[Miss Parker's Voice]
Aboveboard, my cute little ass.
- I don't really feel comfortable
discussing that subject.
- Cloning?
No. Your cute little-
Yes. Cloning.
And I can't believe Sydney
would be involved in this mess.
- Yeah, well, nothing around this
nuthouse surprises me anymore.
- You could say that twice.
Well, they didn't keep Gemini from me
because there was nothing to hide.
I'm gonna find out the truth-
what really happened.
And I guess I'm gonna
help you. Hmm?
You bet your cute little ass.
[Sheep Bleating]
[Broots] I rerouted the sensors,
so we should have a halfhour...
before anyone finds out
we're down here.
[Miss Parker]
Since we don't have much time...
- why don't you keep your eyes
open and your mouth shut?
- That's fine with me.
'Cause I don't want to
be down here anyhow.
Check it out.
This must be
where they kept him.
Wow.
Not much of a place to spend
the first 14 years of your life, is it?
Nice view.
Miss Parker.
Over here.
[Miss Parker]
"Specimen Anomalies Dissection Storage."
What does that
sound like to you?
Oh, a freak show
I don't want any part of.
What's that smell?
Formaldehyde.
Oh, that's never a good sign.
Oh, God.
What are they?
Oh, l- I think
they're the "befores."
- Before what?
- Before they figured out what they were doing.
The same thing happened with
the early cloning of sheep and other mammals.
They didn't just re-create
Dolly the Sheep after the first try.
She was, like, the 375th.
What happened to
the first 374?
They ended up like this.
Mutations.
Only they weren't human.
Oh, look at this.
It's got the body of a boy
and a face like... Colonel Sanders.
It's called progeria. It's a genetic defect
that causes accelerated aging in children.
They can be seven years old,
but their bodies are a hundred.
- Oh, no.
- [Clangs]
- [Gasps]
- Broots!
I'm sorry. Ew!
Look at this place.
Raines was playing God.
And he unleashed the devil.
[Jarod]
No. No.
No.
No. Please.
No. Please. No.
What did they do to you?
I can't open the hatch!
It's too hot! L- I can't think!
I'm burning!
[Young Jarod]
I can save him!
- No!
- This is your last chance.
I did tell the truth.
I'm at peace.
I feel tired.
My legs hurt.
I set myself on fire because
I'm convinced it'll send a message, Sydney.
[Young Sydney] It's been three days, Jarod,
with temperatures over a hundred degrees.
- All you have to do is submit.
- It's not for me.
- I'll never give up.
- [Jarod] It's not your fault.
[Sighs]
- But-
- We're together now.
That's all that matters.
That...
and saving the boy.
[Computer Twitters]
[Major Charles]
I'm into the Centre's mainframe.
Damn! They're onto me.
But I'm into Gemini.
They're transferring the boy
to the Triumvirate.
- When are they going to transfer him?
- I don't know.
Damn it! They've shut me out. There's gotta be
some other way we can find out.
Someone who can tell us.
[Beeps]
[Ringing]
[Ringing Continues]
- [Line Ringing]
- Come on, Sydney. Answer the phone.
- Are you going to answer it, or shall I?
- [Ringing Continues]
- It's not important.
- [Beeps]
What we have to say is.
The timetable on the transfer
of our young Pretender has been moved up.
He goes at dawn.
My work won't be completed.
It can't be avoided.
The mainframe's been compromised...
and we suspect
Jarod and Major Charles.
My father says you can continue your work
with the boy once he's been transferred.
We expect
your full cooperation.
You have that.
[Miss Parker's Voice]
"I vehemently disagree...
"with Dr. Raines's conclusions
about Gemini...
"and despite some humane
advances being made at Pakor...
"I cannot in good conscience endorse
moving forward with the project.
"While it represents a potentially major
breakthrough for mankind...
"one must wonder if mankind is
or ever will be prepared for its ramifications.
Catherine Parker. "
[Door Opens]
[Exhales Sharply]
You got anything to drink?
Preferably something that burns.
Need to cleanse
your palate?
No. My soul.
I backtracked the cloning records
from Donoterase.
Over the years, they fertilized 289 ova
before they were successful with the boy.
The results of which
we saw at the specimen lab.
Well-
[Clears Throat]
Some of them.
[Coughs]
And if you can believe it...
that sideshow wasn't
the weirdest part of the circus.
They couldn'tjust grow those ova
in an incubator.
- They needed donor wombs.
- Surrogate mothers.
Seems Raines found
the women himself.
Mostly disenfranchised,
homeless, loners or coma victims.
Women who wouldn't be missed
if there were complications.
And-And believe me,
there were plenty of them.
Most fetuses
never reached term.
And-And...
the ones that did-
Well, they didn't even
make it through-
- Childbirth.
- [Scoffs] Well, if you-
if you could call it that.
All of the surrogates who made it that far,
though, they- theyjust-
- Disappeared.
- Without a trace.
That's what my mother was talking-
talking about in this Gemini memo.
What she feared
could happen at Donoterase.
What should I do?
Well, whatever it is, you better decide pretty
quickly, because they're moving the boy at dawn.
Where?
Triumvirate station, Africa.
Your mom's first priority was the children.
What would she do?
The same thing
she was trying to do when...
she was killed:
Rescue the children.
I'm over here.
I'm sorry.
I didn't hear you come in.
Do you want me
to do something for you?
No.
I just came to talk.
Talk? You don't want anything?
Just to see you.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
Ready to work.
- You were crying.
- No, I wasn't.
L- I just-
Don't tell Mr. Raines.
He gets angry if I show any emotion.
It won't happen again. I promise.
It's okay to cry.
No, it's not.
Not for me.
I'm here to serve-
to do what I'm told.
Is that what
Raines taught you?
Yes.
That I have been gifted with the intelligence
designed to help others.
Mr. Raines says emotions
get in the way.
If you don't want me to work,
then why are you here?
When I was your age,
I knew a boy just like you.
Exactly like you.
I felt for him...
but I never let him know.
I saw...
pain... in his eyes...
but I looked the other way.
I see the same pain
in your eyes.
But I can't look away anymore.
I don't understand.
Do you want to be here,
or do you want to do what other kids do?
What do other kids do?
Play. Have fun.
Experience life.
- Is this a simulation?
- No. No. This is real.
I'm doing what I want to do:
Sims to help others.
Then why were you crying?
L- I wasn't.
I just-
It's okay.
If Mr. Raines finds out,
he'll get angry.
And when he gets
angry, he-
He-
- He-
- I won't let him hurt you anymore. I promise.
Now we gotta
get you out of here.
He's not going anywhere
with you.
[Miss Parker's Voice]
I can't believe this, Sydney.
You're going with them.
- Yes.
- Sydney, why?
- You too, Broots?
- You certainly fooled me for the last three years...
bumbling around the globe
like a benevolent Dr. Spock...
when you're really
a, uh, psycho Dr. Mengele.
You don't know
what you're saying.
[Phone Rings]
It's your original lab rat.
- What are you gonna tell him?
- [Ringing Continues]
- [Beeps]
- Sydney.
They're going to move the boy.
I need to know when.
I can't help you anymore.
Sydney, I need
your help. Please.
[Wheels Squeaking]
And another excursion into
the mainframe would be useless.
There is no refuge
for you anymore.
[Beeps]
He hung up.
He's helping them.
What did he say?
He said that another excursion
into the mainframe would be useless.
Why would he tell us
where not to look?
Because someone else
was there.
It was his way of telling us
where to look.
He said the mainframe
was useless.
There would be
no..."refuge."
I knew I could
trust you, Sydney.
- Straight to the airstrip. No stops.
- [Engine Starts]
The transfer plane is meeting us
just after first light.
[Car Engine Starts]
- You gotta be kidding me.
- What the hell is goin' on?
Let's go, junior.
We got places to be.
[Coughing]
[Broots]
Miss Parker, what's goin'on?
Jarod.
[Car Approaching]
- Miss Parker.
- Get him in the truck!
- Where are you going?
- Just get him out of here now!
Get in.
- [Engine Cranking]
- Get out!
Dad.
- [Coughing]
- Oh! Damn!
Who are you?
I'm you.
[Angry Chattering]
- You were the problem.
- You need to get off my back.
[Chattering Continues]
[Clanging]
Carelessness...
leads to chaos...
chaos to anarchy...
anarchy to ruin.
This is the Centre.
Ruin... is not an option!
- Mutumbo, if I may-
- Excuses are only yesterday's failures.
Only solutions matter now.
Mutumbo, we all-we all want
the same thing here: The boy and Jarod back.
I am listening.
So we fumbled the kid.
We intercepted Jarod's father.
He's our trump card.
- Let's play him.
- [Miss Parker] And I guarantee you, sir.
You give me 10 minutes
with Major Charles...
and I'll have every answer you want
about whereJarod and the boy are.
Brigitte will handle
Major Charles.
Thank you.
If I may, sir-
You will honor my wishes.
Good answer.
In the meantime,
we haveJarod and the boy to track down.
Mr. Lyle will lead that effort.
[Miss Parker]
Sir, with the possible exception of Sydney...
I knowJarod
better than anyone here...
and he will not allow
that boy to be captured.
Yes. But what you are
forgetting is the boy himself.
He wasn't raised to cooperate.
Especially with Jarod.
I'm just saying it's a waste of manpower
and money to go afterJarod...
when the key to it all is the man
sitting down in Renewal Wing.
- Daddy.
- Well, uh, Mutumbo has a good
plan here. We need to follow it.
[Mutumbo]
Then it is settled. Two points of attack.
Two generals, one plan.
[Wheels Squeaking]
[Chattering]
Now I know what
dirty laundry feels like.
- Not here, angel.
- Yes, here.
How could you just stand there
while Mutumbo shut me out?
For God's sake,
we're talkin' the Triumvirate here.
Every action, every thought,
every word I utter could be a death sentence.
We both know I'm the one who should be
down there with Major Charles.
And we both know sometimes
I have to play things the way I play things...
whether you like it or not.
"Play." Oh, my God.
We're talking about
the man who killed Mom.
We're talking about our family.
I'm talking about survival.
The things I do,
choices I make...
you probably never will
understand.
Tell me, Daddy. Are you
really afraid of Mutumbo...
or what I may find out
from Major Charles?
[Elevator Bell Dings]
I thought I was off
your Christmas card list.
You were.
Until our nosy little bald friend Broots
confirmed my suspicions with this.
You left e-mail forJarod
in a box called "refuge."
You let him know when
and where to find the boy.
I had you pegged for
the wrong witch in Oz, Sydney.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to confide in you.
Or in Broots either.
Human cloning- I... don't think
I probably would have believed you anyway.
When I went down to talk
with the boy, it was, um-
It was so surreal
being with him.
It was like I was suddenly
11 years old again.
And yet-
And yet?
And yet the boy is Jarod...
in every way except
the most important one.
He doesn't have
Jarod's soul.
And he didn't have you.
Miss Parker.
When I found out
they had made anotherJarod...
I knew that if I didn't
take control...
something important
would be lost.
If facing Major Charles
is important enough to you...
then go.
Take it.
And everyone else be damned.
[Thunderclap]
[Jarod]
Must be some matches around here somewhere.
Aha. Yes.
Little light in here.
There we go.
[Thunder Rumbling]
You cold?
It's probably too damp out there
to hunt for firewood...
but maybe I can break up
some of these old chairs.
I don't understand.
Why are you so afraid of me?
- Is this a bad man?
- [Raines] Very bad.
- What did he do?
- [Wheels Squeaking]
This is the man
who killed your parents.
How can one feed
such a terrible lie to a child?
Raines could feed candy
to a diabetic and sleep like a baby.
He doesn't seem
like a killer.
He seems sad,
Mr. Raines.
Like there's this void in his life
that's depriving him of any true happiness.
Perhaps loss of a loved one.
Or the loss of family.
Maybe he feels
the same way I do...
not knowing who he is
or where he came from.
You're not concentrating.
He's no different
from any of the others.
I don't know.
I just-
I feel I have
a connection with him.
- This boy's good.
- Mmm. Almost as good as the real thing.
Wait a minute.
What am I saying?
He is the real thing.
[Raines]
If you can't find him...
he'll go out and kill
another little boy's parents...
just like he killed yours.
Do you understand me?
Good.
[Jarod] I swear to you I had nothing
to do with the death of your-
[Thunder Rumbles]
Of your parents.
- Then what happened to them?
- It's complicated.
You're a gifted young man.
You have the ability to grasp
difficult concepts.
When I was a boy I used to look
in the mirror and think about my past...
try to picture my future.
- Do you ever do that?
- Yes.
But I can't see a past.
When I was a boy...
I was stolen
from my parents...
and I was held prisoner
at the Centre.
[Thunderclap]
They exploited my mind.
They made me do things.
Things I never
should have done.
The same kind of things
that they made you do.
When I got older, I realized that
they were using these things to hurt people.
Even to kill them.
So I ran away.
You escaped.
Yes. But not all of me.
They kept part of me behind.
Some of my-
Some of my D.N.A.
I guess they had a plan.
A way to always
keep me prisoner.
I don't understand.
I think you do.
If you could look into that
mirror and see your future...
it would look
exactly like...
me.
But my parents.
They don't exist.
They never did.
At least not in the way
you were taught.
No. You're lying.
Mr. Raines said you were clever.
You're lying.
I wish to God I was.
But I'm not lying.
I'm sorry.
I want to
show you something.
That's me
when I was your age.
[Young Jarod]
No. I can't do it!
- [Young Sydney] You shut down now, you all die!
- I'm you?
- I come from nowhere?
- You come from here.
And I come from two people
who love me very much.
[Thunder Rumbling]
It's okay to cry.
I can't.
Mr. Raines won't let me.
[Thunderclap]
- [Young Miss Parker Screams]
- [Young Sydney] No! Keep her back!
- Keep her back.
- [Young Jarod] Leave me alone!
[Young Miss Parker]
Mama! [Sobbing]
[Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
[Water Dripping]
You can beat me
all you want.
I'd rather die
than give up my son.
You're going to die,
but it's not about your son.
It's about my mother.
You look just like her.
You should know.
You killed her.
That's my gun.
The one you used
to shoot her.
No.
It's the one a man named Raines stole
from me the day your mother was killed.
She knew trouble was coming.
[Chuckles]
Why should I believe that?
Because it's true.
It was the day I was supposed to help her
rescueJarod and two other children.
Raines shot me,
left me for dead...
took my gun.
I still carry the bullet
in my back.
You bought yourself another second.
Talk fast.
Your mother located me.
She knew I was
searching forJarod.
She was afraid of something
called the Triumvirate.
She said we'd have to
move fast-
that this Triumvirate
threatened her husband...
because of her action
to rescue the children...
and her opposition to
something she called Gemini.
- They threatened Daddy?
- They threatened his wife and his daughter.
You were the other child
we were trying to rescue.
Your mother was gonna take you
to Europe the next day.
Don't you remember?
My father knew about these rescues?
My rescue?
That was how I saw it.
But I can't be certain.
But I do know for sure...
your mother was scared
for your safety and his.
Afraid ofhow
the Triumvirate controlled him.
Raines was the Triumvirate
watchdog then.
He's still howling.
I didn't understand why he took my gun
all those years ago, but I do now.
All your mother and father
ever wanted was what I wanted:
To love
and be with our children.
- [Birds Chirping]
- [Jarod] Good morning.
Breakfast.
That isn't wheat grass
and tomato juice.
No. That's what they feed you.
It's called ice cream.
You'll never forget the first bite.
Go ahead. Try it.
Go ahead.
- [Chuckles]
- Mmm.
It's very good.
There are so many incredible
things in the world to try.
Hope they're all
as good as ice cream.
So, what are we
gonna do now?
Right now I have to
figure out a way to get my-
our father out of the Centre.
Maybe we should trade them
for something just as important.
I can't believe I doubted him.
All these years.
All these years I've- I've wondered
why Daddy hid things from me...
lied to me, dissuaded me
from digging into her past...
but it was all for my own good.
We all want to believe that our parents
have our best interests in mind. But-
I finally find some peace of mind,
and you want to lobotomize it?
Isn't there an apparent conflict
between your newfound joy...
and your loading
of this weapon?
It's very simple.
Raines dead...
me happy.
Not an easy man to kill.
Can't help it
if you're a lousy aim.
I don't plan to miss.
Miss Parker.
Y-You both.
- You gotta come quick- to the lobby.
- Later, Broots.
Oh, no, no, no. Trust me.
You're not gonna believe this.
- [Elevator Bell Dings]
- He's right here.
Move.
Remember me?
[Miss Parker]
Where'd you find him?
[Sam]
We didn't.
He came in on his own.
Three years on the run, and it's finally
homesickness that brings you back.
Well, actually,
I came to cut a deal.
Broots, go get my father.
[Jarod]
Oh, he's not in his office.
What kind of game is this?
It's a simple one. You'll get
your father back...
when I get mine.
So you're proposing
an equal trade.
Your father for my husband.
I wouldn't say that it was
equal, but it will do. Yes.
And how do we know
you're not bluffing?
[Gun Cocks]
Seeing is believing.
I'll call you in two hours
to arrange the exchange.
One of you will bring me
my father.
- Only one.
- That'd be me.
That'd be Sydney.
Sydney? This is my father
we're talking about.
Our father.
All the more reason
to keep cool heads.
Sydney's the only person I can trust
to play by the rules.
- Where will the exchange take place, Jarod?
- Like I said, I'll call you.
I wouldn't want anybody showing up early
and complicating things.
I really have to go now.
Do you want to see
your father again?
Alive?
- [Wheels Squeaking]
- And you letJarod walk right out?
He has my father!
And we had him!
I made the only move there was,
you son of a bitch!
It was your last one,
Miss Parker.
The Centre's
chain of command is clear.
As long as
Mr. Parker is absent...
Mr. Raines is in charge.
And your plan is,
Mr. Raines?
We organize two Sweeper teams.
Once we know the location,
one will scout and secure-
[Wheezing]
And the other will execute.
No. No. No.
You're gambling
with my father's life.
We do this just as Jarod said.
Well, Raines's experience
with Jarod is just administrative.
Look...
- I know how this guy's mind works.
- This is not a democracy.
My decision stands.
[Phone Ringing]
- Jarod.
- [Jarod] Interstate Road 40.
Iversonville,
North Carolina. At 3:00.
Not 2.59. Not 3.01.
3:00.
- That barely gives enough time for Sydney to-
- Then he'd better get moving.
Jarod, I want to
talk to my father.
- Daddy, are you there?
- [Beeps]
Sydney, go.
- [Door Opens]
- Get Major Charles.
Let's move.
[Wheels Squeaking]
Like I said, two teams.
[Wheezing]
And I'll need our best sharpshooter.
I'm your man.
Jarod will not walk away from this.
No. I wantJarod alive.
And the boy too.
It's Mr. Parker who's outlived
his usefulness.
That waste of skin Raines
is gonna get my father killed.
Well, I don't thinkJarod would hurt your father.
I don't think.
Jarod's been searching for his father
his entire life...
and he's gonna do
whatever it takes to get him back.
I could see it
in his eyes.
- Well, then what do you think we should do?
- Same thing. Whatever it takes.
Miss Parker.
Jarod isn't
the only enemy this time.
Don't worry, Bridget.
I wouldn't forget about you.
I know what you think of me...
but believe me, we both want
the same thing this time.
Mr. Raines is planning
to kill your father.
Why should I believe you?
Because if you don't, somebody we both love
very much is going to die.
With or without you,
I'm going.
Let's do this together.
Please.
[Major Charles]
I'd like to thank you, Sydney.
- What for?
- For raising my son.
What he's become
is a reflection of you.
What was he like as a child?
Someone a father would feel
very proud to call his son.
I'm sorry you never
had that chance, Major.
In fact, I can't imagine
anything worse...
than what
you've had to endure.
I can.
- Not ever finding him at all.
- [Jarod On Walkie-talkie] Sydney, are you there?
Yes, Jarod.
You'll see a road a quarter of a mile up.
Turn right.
My father will know
where to go from there.
[Sydney On Walkie-talkie]
All right, Jarod. I'll follow his instructions.
Well, he- he didn't say where.
Only that his father knew.
Great. We're in the middle
of nowhere with no Sydney...
and no idea
where he's going.
- I know exactly where he's going.
- Yeah?
Well, where might that be?
To the beginning
of this little odyssey.
[Sighs]
Well, I gotta
hand it to you.
Capturing the king
is inspired.
Walking into the Centre
to cut your deal.
- Real bold.
- Not bold.
Prudent. Necessity.
Exhibition of resolve.
You people only understand
one thing: Power.
Whatever it was,
it was brilliant.
No wonder my people have
such a hard time catching up to you.
Of course, that's why we want you back.
'Cause you're brilliant.
I'm not going back.
Neither is he.
I do have one question.
It's your nickel.
Why? Why do you do it?
Why the Centre?
Give and take.
For a cause bigger than
both of us.
Oh, hell. I don't expect
you to understand it...
but in the end,
it does all add up.
You steal children.
You create them.
How does that add up?
Rape, incest, murder.
Survival.
Given enough incentive,
man is capable of almost anything.
[Car Approaching]
It's time to go.
Dad.
Now take care of your father.
And of yourself.
Thank you, Sydney.
Come on, Dad.
Jarod.
I'm glad you found
your family.
[Car Rapidly Approaching]
- I told you. Sydney comes alone!
- Jarod, I had no choice.
They're planning to kill my father.
- Who?
- [Helicopter Approaching]
Daddy, get back!
- I've got him.
- Shoot him!
[Gunshot]
[Gunshots]
- God, no!
- [Jarod] She's losing a lot ofblood.
Keep this compressed
against the wound.
[Raines]
Forget Parker. Stop the plane!
Jarod, let's go!
- You go ahead without me!
- Jarod.
That boy needs a father.
Now go! We'll catch up later!
I love you, Son!
I love you too, Dad.
Go! Go! Go!
[Jarod's Voice]
I've got to get her to the hospital.
You're not going anywhere.
Looks like you're out of luck.
Now, you want to do this the easy way,
or do you want to end up like her?
Stop him!
Welcome back
to the Centre, Jarod.
Angel, don't leave me.
Don't leave me, angel.