[Rattling]
[Screams]
[Whimpers]
- [Dog Whines]
- Come on, boy.
[Chattering]
Good boy.
Search. Search, boy.
Diagrams indicate this is
the last unsearched pod.
The survivors should thank their lucky stars
these torsion barriers took the brunt.
[Whimpers]
It's a damn miracle
anything survived this hell.
We got somethin'.
[Mr. Parker]
Give me a hand, angel.
- It's good to see you out of the infirmary, Daddy.
- Thanks.
Ah. You look tired.
I haven't had a decent night's sleep
since the explosion.
- [Phone Rings]
- Ah.
Yes.
Oh.
Yes. Keep me informed.
Disposal team discovered a body
in SL 27 last night.
Sydney?
It's too soon to tell.
They need more pieces.
Daddy, if- if the remains down there
are Sydney's, then-
Forget Sydney.
I didn't put this bombing report
together as a condemnation.
Sydney planted the bomb...
but he acted out of a misdirected sense
of guilt and compassion.
Misdirected guilt and compassion killed
your mother. I will not allow it to kill you!
What's going on, Daddy?
Triumvirate is applying great pressure
for a change in strategy.
They're not removing me
from Jarod's pursuit?
[Chuckles]
Oh, no. I would never allow that.
Ah, 'twas a bloody fight.
Most important,
none of it was yours or mine.
Then what?
Well, they insist
on adding a new player.
Their selection
is due in tomorrow.
Is that necessary?
Desperate times.
[Click]
Centre Records lab.
Surveillance feed
came through this morning.
[Miss Parker]
Jarod.
His body survived the blast.
I'm not so sure about his mind.
[Jarod Grunting]
[Panting, Shouts]
- [Jarod] Kri kra toad's foot.
- [Man] Help!
Kri kra toad's foot.
Geese walk barefoot.
- Hold him!
- Come on!
Kri kra toad's foot.
Geese walk barefoot.
- Who the hell was that guy?
- I don't think he knows. Let's go.
Where are my mom and dad?
[Screams]
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent every moment
searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
[Miss Parker]
He defends the weak and abused.
Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Did you hear about
the body?
- Was it Sydney?
- No. Thank God, no.
It was that bleached-out
Sweeper. That guy Gar.
Hmm. There's one less
vacancy in hell.
- Oh, man. It's all too weird.
- Tell me about it.
- Haven't seen that ghoul all week.
- [Broots] Oh, no one has.
- I hear he's practically living over in Renewal Wing.
- Renewal Wing?
That's for head cases
and invalids.
Well, he is sort of both.
What? Do you think
he's up to something?
He's always up to something.
Sydney blew up his old playground.
- I'm gonna go see if he's found a new one.
- What? In Renewal Wing?
- Have you gone crazy?
- Everyone has.
[Jarod]
Geese walk barefoot.
Kri kra toad's foot.
Wagon from County
brought him in.
John Doe. No I.D.
They found him lassoin'Harleys
over at the, uh, Dairy Queen.
Kept insistin'
he was a rodeo clown.
Hardly a reason
for a straitjacket.
Hey. You're the shrinks. All I know is
it took six troopers to subdue him.
- Thanks, Jimbo. We'll manage from here.
- All right then.
Well, he definitely looks troubled,
so let's give him...
a comprehensive evaluation and determine
what level security to put him at.
Kri kra toad's foot.
Geese walk barefoot.
Hi there.
I'm Dr. Goetz, and this is Dr. Blythe.
Geese walk barefoot.
- [Goetz] We're both here to help you.
- Kri kra toad's-
Where are my mom and dad?
- Why don't we start with a name?
- Jarod.
What's your last name?
I don't know.
It changes every week.
[Man]
You know Mr. Raines is looking for you?
- [Man #2] He wants to see me now?
- Yeah.
Come with me.
Who's there?
My God. Sydney.
Miss Parker.
- I thought you were-
- Dead.
Give them time.
What the hell have they been doing
to you down here?
[Woman Screams]
I believe the term
is "reeducation."
But I would plant the bomb again
to save that child.
Sydney, there's nothing
I can do to save you from this.
I'm not interested
in saving myself.
Jarod. Was he able to
make it out safely?
In body, yes.
Jarod flipped out...
pulled a psycho Martha Stewart
at a Centre Records lab.
[Sydney]
That's what I've been afraid of all this time-
that one day the pressure of living
in the outside world...
and the truth about his past
would come crashing down upon him.
I need your help.
I have to bring him in...
and I need to know
exactly what I'm up against.
The anguish in his cry-
It comes from deep within.
[Panting, Shouts]
Hmm.
Oh, Sydney.
You can't see.
Call it poetic justice.
There must be something.
Bring me anything Jarod left
behind before he did this.
They will never
let me out of here.
And there's little time.
This may be my last chance
to helpJarod...
or you.
[Goetz] Why don't you tell me
who you are and where you came from?
You wouldn't believe me.
Try me.
I was stolen from my parents as a child,
and I was raised by a place called the Centre.
Think hell.
With nicer furniture.
Where exactly is this Centre?
It's everywhere.
Can I draw a picture?
I like to draw.
Maybe later.
Why don't you tell me
a little bit about this Centre?
No windows.
No doors.
No light.
No hope.
They take all that away.
- They?
- The ones that decided...
what I ate, when I slept...
who I saw, when I talked.
They decided everything I did.
How did they do this to you?
They had eyes in every ceiling,
every wall. They never blinked.
They were always on me.
Every minute, every hour...
every day of my life.
Why'd they do this to you?
To control me.
I'm a Pretender.
I can become
anyone I want to be.
Except I don't know
who I am.
I've been a shrink before.
It's really very overrated.
You don't believe me.
Only you know the truth.
The truth, the whole truth and nothing
but the truth, so help me God.
I was a lawyer once too.
[Man]
Never would have pegged him as a fake.
This Jarod you're looking
for was a janitor here.
A damn good one.
Very convincing.
Always is.
I don't suppose you put together
any kind of missing inventory list?
Uh, we're just
a records office really...
and none of the physical
archives are missing.
And has any data
been compromised?
[Broots]
Miss Parker. I found it.
J-
Jarod.
[Whispers]
Jarod tapped into the two ban six file.
Major Charles. He was looking for
his father in the Centre records.
[Broots]
Catherine Parker.
He was looking for a connection
between his father and your mother.
This is everything he had in his locker.
Hope it helps.
Oh, my. Heavy-duty drugstore.
[Miss Parker]
Yeah. And the library for the shattered mind.
You think whateverJarod found out about
his father and your mother caused this?
- [Gunshot]
- [Screams]
[Gunshot]
- [Gunshot]
- [Screams]
[Jarod] Miss Parker's mother
was murdered by the Centre...
and her father-
[Chuckles]
Mr. Duplicity himself-
He runs the place.
Then there's Mr. Raines...
the Centre's answer
to Dr. Mengele...
an emphysema-riddled corpse who
drags around his breath of life in a tank.
Is there anyone else
you want to tell me about?
The thumbless man.
Mr. Lyle.
He killed my brother.
He killed me once too.
And of course...
Sydney.
- Who's Sydney?
- Pavlov to my dog.
Provider. Protector.
Patriarch.
He created me.
You see, I'm extremely
valuable to the Centre.
And while I search
for who I am...
they search for me.
[Goetz]
He certainly believes it.
[Blythe]
That's what scares me. I say keep him restrained...
and place him in a
max security section.
[Goetz] There's a tormented boy inside,
but I don't think he's dangerous.
[Blythe] Carla, it took
six policemen to subdue him last night.
- Let's not take any chances.
- [Goetz] I want to work with him.
[Blythe]
You will have time.
With his paranoid delusions
and multiple personalities...
I doubt he's ever
gonna leave this place.
[Sydney] Neuro-inhibitors,
antidepressants, antipsychotics.
- Self-medicating.
- Not likeJarod.
Well, the man who destroyed
that room is not likeJarod.
- Well-
- Oh.
"Shedding Light
on the Schizophrenic Mind''....
"Dementia. The Phantom Within,"
"Dementia Praecox."
They're all books on a-
on a troubled mind.
If we'd only gotten
to him sooner-
I wish things were
different too, Syd, but-
but all the pieces
to this crazy jigsaw fit.
Hmm.
[Broots]
Not this one.
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
It's okay.
My name is Jarod.
I'm sorry it took me
so long to get here.
[Miss Parker]
I have a brother out there.
[Jarod] I've narrowed your brother's identity
down to these two files.
One of these files
belong to him...
and the other
to a boy named Bobby.
But you know him better
as Mr. Lyle.
I need a drink.
A big one.
Who killed my mother?
- Jarod's father.
- [Gunshots]
[Screams]
[Angelo]
Miss Parker. Confused.
Scared.
Are you my brother?
Hope.
- Maybe I'm the crazy one.
- [Broots] Miss Parker!
Miss Parker.
- [Panting]
- You're starting to sound like Dr. Fester.
I'm sorry, but I was tryin' to find you
all over this place.
- Well?
- He's here.
- Who's here?
- Him.
I believe "him"is me.
What the hell
are you doing here, Lyle?
I'm here to help you
catch Jarod.
It's good to be home again.
[Jarod]
She looks very sad.
[Jimbo]
Mary? Yeah, she is.
She wasn't so bad when she first
came in here for nervous exhaustion...
but one night about two years ago,
she broke out, tried to offherself.
Gotten worse ever since.
She should've listened
to her doctors.
You should too.
[Lock Clicks]
[No Audible Dialogue]
- Thank you for releasing me from my shackles.
- You're welcome.
This is for you.
For your drawings.
You know, you've told me an awful lot
about where you came from...
and all the people
that were there...
but the one thing that you haven't
told me about is Jarod.
That's because
I don't know who I am.
[Jarod]
Mary.
Do you know who this is?
- Erica.
- Yes.
She had a pretty bracelet.
You ran away with Erica
that night.
[Mary]
Through the woods.
Run. Erica,
we have to get away.
Erica ran through the woods,
but she got away?
Erica's gone.
- Where is she?
- Erica's wet.
[Gasps]
The water's so cold. L-
- Erica's in the water.
- [Whimpers]
Can't find her.
I'm coming, Erica.
Hang on.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Mary. Mary.
Mary, Mary, Mary.
I want you to listen to me. Listen to me.
Listen to me.
I want you to stop
taking your medication.
It's been making your mind
sick when it's really not.
Someone has been trying
to make you forget...
and it's very, very important
for you to remember.
Okay?
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
ClearlyJarod's crazy.
Which, in my opinion, is the only
explanation for his carelessness.
The question is why?
Why has Jarod gone off the deep end?
- And how did he manage to-
- Wait. Stop.
Just how in the hell
did you get back in here?
I believe the Triumvirate...
as well as your father...
see me as a man who's willing to literally
sacrifice his own flesh and blood...
- for what he believes in.
- As opposed to...
kidnapping, embezzling
murderer?
It's all perspective.
Some see a missing thumb.
Others, four perfectly
good fingers.
I'm having a hell of a time
getting this thing to heal over.
But like I said, sacrifice.
You know they actually offered to transplant
my big toe to re-create a new thumb?
Nobody re-creates
quite like you, Bobby.
Tell me, Parker.
Exactly what are you
willing to sacrifice?
[Miss Parker]
Well, my mother sacrificed more than her thumb...
and I'm willing to give
just as much as she did.
Ow.
Sorry.
[Miss Parker]
It'd be a shame to lose both of those.
Why would Maryjump in the water?
She didn'tjump to kill herself.
She jumped because Erica
was in the water.
If I were you, Sydney,
I would eat.
I question how many more opportunities
you'll have to do so.
[Apple Crunches]
What more, Raines?
Who's there?
A friend.
- Ow.
- Sorry.
Florence Nightingale I'm not.
- Truth.
- Yes, Angelo.
I'm searching for the truth.
[Door Opens]
Oh, oh. Oh, oh. I'm not very good
with blood, Miss Parker.
What did you find out?
Who brought Mr. Lyle back?
Actually, it was your-
your father.
My father wanted Mr. Lyle?
Well, from what
I could find out, he-
he pulled strings from Europe to Asia
to get him reinstated.
What the hell
are you doing with this?
Broots, I want you...
to D.N.A. Fingerprint
these samples.
Okay.
It's time I shook up the family tree,
see who falls out.
[Keys Jingle]
Stay put,
and stay out of trouble.
Thank you for caring.
Give it.
[Jarod]
Kleptomania is a hard habit to break.
Mm-hmm. Fingers aren't.
[Beeps]
[Lock Clicks]
[Goetz]
You're hiding something.
- Why do you say that?
- Oh, you're a textbook case, Jarod.
You did just the right things to get yourself
in here. Not too much. Not too little.
You didn't hurt yourself
or anyone else doing it.
The question is why
you want to be here.
You're the shrink.
Well, it's not uncommon
for released prison inmates...
to commit offenses to
return them to the security...
of an institutionalized
environment.
The Centre sounds like
such an environment.
I just don't think that
you want to go back there.
No.
Which brings us back to
why you're really here.
To heal.
[Cell Phone Rings]
- What?
- [Jarod] Did Sydney get his eyes back yet?
How the hell do you know
about that?
Calm down, Miss Parker.
Stress left unchecked
creates madness.
Well, then Hitler
should have taken up yoga.
How'd you get out
after the blast?
Well, if I told you that, Miss Parker,
it wouldn't be any fun.
How did Daddy make out?
Better than yours will-
when I find him.
Misplaced aggression
causes madness too.
You cause madness, Jarod.
Or should I call you Freud
or Houdini this week?
Well, that is what makes me mad, Miss Parker.
You see, I don't know who I am.
But, of course, you have the same reason
now for sleepless nights.
How does it feel?
Trying to define the branches
of your family tree.
The identity of my brother
is my problem.
It's both our problems.
Of course, the Parker family picnic
will never be the same.
[Beeps]
[Sydney]
I'd know that Chanel anywhere.
Sydney.
What are you doing here?
We're working.
Together.
As a team.
Whoop-de-do.
Just one big
happy family, huh, Syd?
I'm sorry. I must still have some ringing
in my ears from that bomb blast.
You remember the blast,
don't you, Syd?
[Mr. Lyle]
Interesting about that.
Upon further review, I realized
you'd reached the wrong conclusion.
Sydney wouldn't have
planted that bomb.
- It was Gar.
- Gar.
Gar couldn't light a stick of dynamite
if he had a road map to the fuse.
- And why would he?
- Well, the truth...
unfortunately,
goes to the grave with him.
Tragedy.
But a fortunate one
for you, Syd...
that the Ken doll here
corrected overnight...
the mistakes my report
took a week to find.
No. The fortunate thing is the powers that be
agreed with my findings.
Would that be the powers
from Europe or from Asia?
The ones that count.
Gee. Syd, I know
you're blind. L-
I just didn't realize deaf and dumb
came with the package.
You don't understand,
Parker.
It's crystal clear.
You've sold your soul to save your ass.
I just hope you don't get burned by the guy
with the horns and the little red pitchfork.
L-You know, l-
I believe you're confusing
intelligence with guile.
- We do have work to do.
- Yes.
"We."
There's the operative word.
[Mr. Lyle]
Are you in on this pursuit or not?
Jarod contacted me earlier.
He sounded different. Disturbed.
I came here to research
the Centre records ofhis psych profile...
try and understand
his behavior.
Great minds. Sydney and I were just exploring
Jarod's dive off the deep end as well.
You think he's really
gone crazy?
Maybe he's pretending
to have lost his faculties...
so as not to stand out from
others who have lost theirs.
- [Mr. Lyle] Like in an asylum.
- Hmm. Well, he'd certainly fit in around here.
I stopped taking them,
like you said.
Good girl.
Mary, I found the car
in the water.
I found Erica.
Mary...
do you think you could tell me about
the night that you tried to escape?
Oh, I see things in my head.
- I'm not sure what to believe.
- Trust yourself.
Dr. Blythe doesn't have
control of your mind anymore.
Well, Erica and I
had become friends here.
She was kind and funny.
After a while, l-
I could tell there was...
something bothering her.
Then she told me.
What did she tell you?
That she was going to
have a baby.
Dr. Blythe gave her
the baby.
He took advantage of her
during her therapy sessions.
Dr. Blythe wanted the baby
to go away.
She was scared.
Confused.
So I decided to...
help her escape.
So you ran away
through the woods...
- but something stopped you.
- Oh!
[Mary]
Headlights.
Dr. Blythe.
Yeah. He called out to her.
- He- He said he wanted to talk
to her about keeping the baby.
- Come here.
No!
I told her
not to believe him.
[Jarod]
But she went to talk to him anyway.
There was no talk.
It all happened so fast.
He hit her so hard
she stopped moving.
I can see he was panicked.
I was frozen with fear.
I didn't know what to do.
Erica in the water.
You tried to save Erica...
but Dr. Blythe saw you.
You surprised him because he thought
that Erica tried to run away by herself.
He held me under the water
until the car came.
- [Jarod] Car?
- [Mary] The orderly.
[Jarod]
Jimbo?
- So now he had a witness.
- Dr. Blythe!
So he couldn't kill you, so he-
he dragged you out of the water...
and then he concocted this story
about two escaped patients-
one who got away and the other
who was suicidal and incoherent.
I'm not crazy.
No. Mary, you are not crazy.
Dr. Blythe gave you
this medication...
so you would think you were crazy
so you couldn't tell this story.
But it's time that someone
told the truth.
For Erica.
And for you.
[Phone Rings]
- [Jarod] Dr. Blythe.
- Yes.
This is Trooper Raines,
Maryland State Police.
Sorry to get you up so early.
I'm a busy man. I get up early every day.
What- How can I help you?
Well, it's not what you can do for me.
It's more what I can do for you.
Good news.
We found your car.
- My car?
- 1994 Mercedes. ZYP 959.
A couple of fishermen found it submerged
out at Wilson Lake.
Did they, uh,
find anything... in the car?
Well, it's still too dark
to be sure of anything...
except the fact that
it is indeed your car.
- It is funny though.
- Funny?
Well, looks like it's been down there
for a couple of years, but...
you never missed a registration payment
and you never reported it missing.
- I guess you are a busy man.
- [Beeps]
[Dial Tone]
Of all the psychiatric
institutions in North America...
20 have had John Does
admitted in the last few days.
- Anything?
- Well, we're getting close.
I'm down to
the last 10 here.
[Beeps, Twittering]
Pleasant Wood Psychiatric Institute,
Towson, Maryland.
It all seems way too easy.
Believe it.
Cuckoo Boy's there.
- But why would he leave us a trail right to him?
- Simple.
It's Jarod's way of telling us
he's still in control.
Bus is leaving.
Save you a seat?
[Ducks Quacking]
[Jarod]
Erica's not in there.
I gave her the dignity
that you wouldn't.
- What are you doing out of the asylum?
- Repaying a debt...
for two women.
One whose life you stole...
the other whose mind
you nearly destroyed.
- You're mad.
- Well, it's a mad, mad world.
But don't worry.
You're not going to be in it much longer.
You're no patient.
- And you are no doctor.
- Ow!
Just another coward
running from the truth.
Let go of me!
Let me out of here!
- Thought maybe you'd like to go
for a little ride in your car.
- Please?
Erica didn't get to plead
for her life. Did she?
Or Mary, when you began feeding her
hallucinogens to make her think she was crazy.
You don't understand! I didn't have any choice!
So please let me out of here!
Mmm. No.
- Three victims. Three ruined lives.
- No! Don't!
- One who died.
- [Screams]
One who has to live
with that memory.
[Blythe]
Let me out!
And an unborn baby
who never got a chance.
Now I wouldn't want all that
on my mind when I met my Maker.
- I'd feel like-
- Please, no! Let me out!
- Like you do right now.
- No!
Let me out!
[Shouts]
[Man] You know, he's lucky you came along
when you did, Dr. Ratched...
or he'd have drowned
himself sure enough.
- But, uh, we'll take care of him.
- No!
He's suffering from classic
paranoid schizophrenia.
Delusional behavior
and total self-destructive tendencies.
I'm ordering full-time restraints
and complete isolation.
You gotta help me.
This guy tried to kill me.
Sure he did, pal. We'll make sure
he doesn't try to hurt himself again.
No! He's not a doctor!
He's a mental-
- I'm the doctor!
- We'll be back to do an evaluation in, oh...
72 hours.
Don't believe him!
I'm the doctor! I'm the-
l- I'm not crazy.
I am not crazy.
Ow!
Doctor, tell me again.
Where did you say you practiced?
Our primary clinic is in Delaware,
which is whereJarod is maintained.
Here we are.
And there he went.
Jimbo, notify the gate
we have a possible escapee.
Your family's very excited
about you coming home, Mary.
You're gonna be okay.
- I know I am.
- Come on.
[Miss Parker]
I'm the one who missed Boy Wonder again.
Why are you the one who looks like
you swallowed a razor?
[Chuckles]
Well, l- I might feel better if I had.
Um, the genetic blood test results on your brother.
[Clears Throat]
- Conclusive?
- Oh- Oh, yeah.
Tell me it's Angelo.
Well, l- I wish I could.
[Door Opens]
- This is Sydney.
- How's your sight?
My sight is gone for now.
But my vision is in some ways
clearer than ever.
I see you've found
a way to survive again.
As have you.
- It's a crazy world.
- But you're not.
- You're just lost, Jarod.
- For now.
But somewhere out there
I'll find my way.
And I'll find out who I am.
[Beeps]
Maybe I will too.
- [Man] Hop in.
- Thanks.