Everyone likes to guess.
Heads or tails?
Tails or heads?
Go ahead, try it.
Chances are you'll be right at least half the time.
Will it be a boy or a girl?
Everyone thinks they know--
and chances are good at least half the people will be right.
The candidate you want?
Or the other guy?
Nice to see you, Bud.
Appreciate your support.
Nice to see you, Mike.
Good choice, Mike.
I know I can count on you,
Allison.
Hey...
you all right?
What's going on?
Oh, it was nothing.
It was just a bad dream.
It was just a...
just a normal bad dream.
Just... anxiety about Devalos.
About the election.
Aha. I see.
My wife is suffering from "electile" dysfunction.
Now that's scary.
I'm voting for Mommy's boss.
Are you voting for Mommy's boss?
What are you talking about?
You can't vote.
Yes I can; I can do whatever I want to.
Mommy says I can do anything,
if I put my mind to it.
This has nothing to do with Mommy.
You're not old enough.
It's against the law.
What do you mean "against the law"?
Are you old enough?
Duh! I can't even drive yet.
Okay, look, this is how it works:
When you're 16, you get to drive and see R-rated movies.
When you're 18, you get to go to college and vote,
and at 21,
you get to drink and do whatever you want.
Says who?
Sorry, but there'll be no drinking, driving,
and nobody in this family is going anywhere
until you girls learn how to make your beds
and do your own laundry.
But that stuff is hard!
Tell me about it.
Wow!
Look at all this stuff!
All stuffed and ready to go.
Did anybody remember to get a sitter?
Uh, I don't know.
Anybody?
Marie, did you remember to get a sitter?
Are you guys going out tonight?
Yep.
It turns out the temperature in Hades has finally plummeted below zero,
and your mother and I are going to go out and we're going to see a movie
and maybe we're gonna get some dinner-- alone.
With just each other.
Wow.
Everybody's gonna think I have a little workshop of elves working for me.
Hey, look at this:
There's a special sneak preview tonight of Memoirs of a Geisha.
Didn't you like that book?
Yeah, I really liked it.
We should try to get in.
What's a geisha?
Ask your mother.
Well, things are going to be a little different under my watch,
Mr. Mayor.
Yeah, trust me.
I'm not afraid to knock a few heads from time to time.
Yeah, you can count on me.
Allison...
What's the matter?
No... nothing.
I'm well aware that, traditionally,
the candidates only debate once,
but why not give the voters a second chance to decide? Hmm?
I mean, you can't have too much democracy.
Oh, come off it, Nate.
We'll be lucky to fill the damn hall
for one debate, much less two;
quit grandstanding.
There are no cameras here.
All right,
Mr. District Attorney.
Have it your way.
I get it.
You're ahead in the polls.
You don't see any up-side to debating me more than once,
but, remember,
things can change very quickly in politics.
A young woman is raped and murdered in her own home.
Just this week, this man,
Clyde Morton,
was arrested in connection with the attack--
the same Clyde Morton who was arrested for breaking into an elderly
couple's home with a firearm,
just three years ago.
Why wasn't this dangerous criminal behind bars?
Why did an innocent woman have to die?
Because District Attorney Manuel Devalos
refused to prosecute
to the full extent of the law.
Isn't it time Phoenix had a prosecutor tough enough to do the job?
Vote Nathan Bradley: new blood,
new breed, solid values.
Paid for by the Committee to Elect Nathan Bradley.
Clyde Morton?
What are you talking about?
He's a scared kid.
At least he was three or four years ago.
Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah, that's him.
He was arrested for breaking and entering--
14, maybe 15 years old.
Remanded to juvenile detention.
Is he out yet?
Should be.
About a month ago.
I remember the mayor made a big stink about this.
Wanted me to try him as an adult.
He was carrying this ancient weapon, with one bullet--
in his pocket, as I recall.
The bullet wasn't even in the gun.
And according to the old man and old woman whose apartment he broke into
the gun never came out of his pocket.
Now, what in the world does this have to do with my opponent?
Apparently, sometime between now and the election,
Clyde Morton is going to rape and murder a young woman here in Phoenix.
And you know this...?
I saw an ad that your opponent is going to air after it happens.
I mean, I saw it in my head.
And I saw Bradley.
I saw him here.
Right where you are,
behind your desk.
We have to find a way to stop this,
save this woman's life.
Bradley is going to use this against you.
So what are we gonna do?
I don't think there's anything to do.
I can't protect the victim.
We don't know who she is.
And I can't very well arrest Clyde Morton for a crime he's yet to commit.
Well, I know that, but can't we send
someone there to keep an eye on him?
Can't we send the police to his house,
let him know that he's being watched?
I could give his parole officer a call.
Well, I don't think that's going to do it.
Well, give me a name of the victim,
or at least a description.
I'll put her under round-the-clock protection.
I don't have it.
Well, then, I don't know what to tell you, Allison.
I could've tried this kid as an adult,
locked him up for a long, long time,
but my gut told me not to do it.
My gut told me that he just made a stupid mistake.
That he's basically a decent kid who could use a second chance.
And now you're telling me that he's gonna kill somebody?
Considering that I don't have a lot of options,
I hope you understand when I say that I'm hoping...
with all my heart...
that you're wrong.
Two for Memoirs of a Geisha, please.
Uh, is that the line to go inside?
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
So, what'll it be?
Food? Call the kids?
- Little of both?
- Candy.
Oh, my God! Joe?!
Joe Dubois?
Karen!
- Karen, I don't believe it...
- Joe.
I thought I heard you lived in Phoenix.
Hey. What are you doing here?
This sure beats physics.
This is physics.
Everything is physics.
Well, Steve's folks live here. Steve?
This is my husband Steve.
This is an old friend from grad school,
Joe Dubois.
Uh, hi.
Allison--
This is my wife Allison.
This is Karen Jane.
Herzfeld now.
Karen Herzfeld.
Um...
Wow, we were research fellows in grad school,
many moons ago.
Well, not that many moons ago.
Well, nice to meet you,
"research fellow".
Nice to meet you,
research fellow's husband.
Research fellow's wife.
So what have you been up to?
Me? Well, I've been up to kids.
And dogs,
and this guy,
and our real estate business.
Real estate. Wow.
Well, who'd-a thunk it?
And you are the chairman of what physics program at what university?
Oh, well,
none of the above.
I'm a project engineer at Aerodytech.
Okay.
I can see that.
So what are you guys here to see?
Uh, the, uh, the geisha movie.
Oh, we just got out.
You're gonna love it.
Well, good.
Oh, wow, okay,
look, that's us.
God, it was great to see you.
You, too.
We should all get together.
We should.
Yes, absolutely.
I'll call you at your office.
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
- Do that.
- Okay then.
Okay.
So nice to meet you,
Allison.
Nice to meet you.
She's pretty.
That's how you get to be a geisha.
No, I meant Karen.
Oh, yeah. I guess.
I don't think I remember you mentioning her before.
We had a seminar together for, like, one semester.
I think after that,
she transferred away or something.
Man, for a second there,
I almost couldn't remember her name.
Do you think she noticed,
or did I cover okay?
Oh, no, you cover great.
Hang onto that one.
Oh, damn, I left the window open this morning.
The cat's going to have gotten out.
Me? I'm hanging in.
No, nobody yet.
I'm just not ready to get back out there, you know?
Titu? Where are you?
Besides, I have a cat.
Or at least I had a cat.
Titu?
Oh! He must have gotten out.
It's all right.
He'll come back when he's hungry.
Is that your other line?
All right. Talk to you later.
Bye.
Titu? Where are you hiding?
Titu?
Titu! Hey!
Good morning.
Hey, what's going on?
You looking for another movie?
Yeah, I was just hoping we could run into more old girlfriends.
Okay...
Is there something you want to talk to me about?
I don't know--
is there something you want to talk to me about?
Are you still mad about last night?
I run into an old friend,
an old married friend.
What is the big deal?
Is she in the paper or something?
I had a dream last night.
I saw this woman.
She came home from work.
There was a stranger in her house. He...
I just thought...
Maybe it happened last night.
Maybe it's in the paper.
And this woman was Karen?
You know what? Forget it.
Forget about that.
I'm just a little thrown,
that's all.
I can see that.
You want to tell me why?
I don't know.
I guess I thought I knew about everyone.
I guess I thought that we told each other everything.
We have. We did.
Well, clearly,
you left someone out!
I don't think so.
You know what?
Remember who you're talking to and try that one again.
I have no idea what conversation I'm in.
- Fine.
"This is physics.
Everything is physics".
Oh, look, it's all coming back to him.
Oh, man.
I understand.
There were so many back then.
Who could keep track?
Allison, come on.
It was 15 years ago.
It only happened once and we were very drunk.
But it did happen!
I forgot, okay?
Hell, she and I never even talked about it.
We just pretended it never happened.
It was one of those things where we both knew
it was a bad idea the second it was over.
Well, it didn't look that way to me.
You are really overreacting.
Oh, really?
How would you feel if you had a porno movie starring me playing in your head?
You mean, you saw it?
Trust me. It's not something I sought out.
It's not like I saw it in the TV Guide and put it on my must-see list.
It just popped into my head.
You're kidding me.
That is so not fair, Allison.
Not only is that not fair,
it is creepy.
You have no right to get inside my head like that.
Wait a second.
What makes you think I got it out of your head?
Maybe I pulled it out of her head.
This is an absurd conversation.
Maybe she didn't forget about it.
Maybe she didn't think it was a mistake the minute after it was over.
Do you hear yourself?
You're railing at me for something that happened
before I met you that I never think about,
that I actually forgot about.
And what are you yelling at me for?
I have no control over what goes on inside her head!
Besides, it's 15 years ago!
What are you going to say when she calls?
What are you talking about?
She's not going to call.
Yeah, she is.
No, she was just being polite.
She wants something from you,
I can tell.
Wants something?
I guess you didn't notice the significant other she had on her arm.
I didn't mean she wants another physics lesson!
Allison...
Joe Dubois.
Joe, hey. Uh, it's your old physics buddy, Karen.
Karen?
Karen, hi.
Hi. You didn't think I was going to call, did you?
Uh, actually, no, I didn't.
Surprise.
Look, I know you're busy. Um...
No, I'm good.
You sure?
'Cause...
The thing is...
I need to talk to you about something.
Sure.
But I'd really rather do it in person.
Uh-huh.
But I like it there.
It's weird.
Daddy, tell her she has to take it down.
Have you noticed the eyes seem to follow you no matter where you're standing?
Not funny.
Daddy...
Hey.
Half this room belongs to your sister and she likes it there,
and I like it, too.
Mommy's right.
Nothing wrong with a little political awareness.
Yeah!
You don't even know what he's talking about.
You just like the colors.
Ariel, sweetie, we'll figure it out in the morning, okay?
Okay.
Sleep tight.
You, too, Mommy.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
Night.
Good night.
So he's counting on you to be wrong?
That's his plan?
Apparently.
He's right. There's nothing he can do.
I didn't give him any information he can use.
I am wrong from time to time.
Okay, stop.
Who are you, and what have you done with my wife?
No, I'm serious. He's right.
I misinterpret things...
I overreact.
Sometimes I see smoke where there's no fire.
I'm sorry.
What are we talking about?
Politics.
Old girlfriends.
I'm sorry if I overreacted.
To be fair,
if I found a bunch of dirty pictures of you and an ex,
I think I'd probably be walking around with a dark cloud over my head, too.
And besides,
if it makes you feel any better,
you weren't completely wrong.
She did call today.
Oh, yeah, what did she want?
Lunch, Thursday.
Really? Just the two of you?
Hey, relax.
There's no smoke, there's no fire,
no combustion of any kind.
I invited her to join me in the cafeteria.
Just me and a lunchroom full of my closest colleagues.
Good thinking, Lincoln.
We aim to please, Louise.
You the new valet?
I need a favor.
I've never done this pre-emptive crime-fighting thing before.
Do I at least get one of those flying motorcycles like Tom Cruise had?
Oh, absolutely.
It'll be waiting for you when you return to City Hall.
You sure you're comfortable with this?
Stopping by the kid's house,
letting him know we're watching,
Keep an eye on him?
I'm okay with that.
especially if you think it's gonna make a difference for Manny.
I think it might save a life.
I mean, I know it's not the way it's normally done,
and I... I know it's kind of wrong.
He doesn't know, you know.
Who's that?
Devalos. He doesn't know we're doing this.
I think he'd be upset if he did.
All the more reason not to tell him.
Can I help you?
My name is Lee Scanlon.
I'm a detective with the Phoenix Police Department.
We were hoping to talk with Clyde Morton.
I'm his mother.
He's not in right now.
He's out looking for a job.
Something the matter?
Is he in trouble?
We were just hoping to speak with him.
You don't look like police.
Actually, I work with the D.A's office.
Oh.
Well, I hope he wins, your boss.
He's smart,
and I think he cares.
He could've sent my boy away for years and years,
instead, he exhibited some mercy,
something you don't see much of around here--
Mercy.
Well, that's sort of why we're here, actually.
Make sure that he's okay.
We wouldn't want to see him get himself into any kind of trouble.
I thought that's what the probation officer was for.
You can tell whoever needs to know,
my son doesn't go around looking for trouble anymore.
That's behind him now.
Glad to hear it,
ma'am, but we'd like to talk to him just the same.
Any idea when he's gonna be home?
Been getting in late.
Uh, I think he found himself a girl.
There's no law against that now, is there?
No, ma'am.
If you'd just tell him we dropped by.
Let him know we'll check back.
Well, that felt horrible.
All this Minority Report stuff's not all that it's cracked up to be,
but if it makes you feel better,
Jeffrey Dahmer's mother thought that he was a saint, too.
Clyde?
Clyde Morton?
Stay here.
Hey!
They're saying he's got swelling on the brain.
Could be a couple of days before they know if he's going to make it or not.
So what happened?
Why did he run?
I don't know.
We couldn't find anything on him.
Maybe just panic 'cause he figured me for a cop.
It was an accident.
It was a...
stupid, horrible awful accident.
You wouldn't happen to know the definition of "accident" would you, Allison?
I-I'm sorry, I meant the car part.
An accident,
by definition is a chance event.
So am I to simply assume that it was by chance that you
and Detective Scanlon went over to Clyde Morton's house?
Despite the fact that you and I had already discussed it?
Despite the fact that I'd already made it abundantly clear that it is not
the policy of this office to harass citizens based on the possibility
that they might commit illegal acts?
I asked you a question!
Hey, back off. We went there to help you.
Help me?
By violating this man's rights?
By putting him in the hospital?
By using the name of this office?
Thanks, Lee.
thanks for your help.
I'm sorry.
We apologize.
We weren't driving that car.
Right.
Get me the name of the physician attending Clyde Morton.
See if I can speak with him, please.
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
Don't apologize to me
I'm not the one lying in a hospital bed fighting for his life.
Yeah, go.
I'm trying to locate that doctor and you're ten minutes late for court.
Thank you both very much.
I'll take care of this from here.
Night, honey.
Good night, Daddy.
Good night.
Isn't Mommy going to say good night?
She's going to sneak in later,
when you're asleep.
Well, then, how will I know she did it?
You trust your mom don't you?
I guess.
Tell her that maybe I'll sneak in later while she's asleep
and kiss her good night, too.
I will definitely let her know.
You still waiting?
Hi. Yes.
I'm calling regarding the condition of Clyde Morton.
Thank you. Thank you.
He's still in I.C.U.
Okay.
How do you feel?
Does it, matter?
It matters to me.
Awful.
Sad.
Guilty.
Confused.
I'll go say good night to the girls.
Okay.
Love you.
Nah, didn't make it to the gym,
had to do something after work.
Nothing, I'm fine.
Just a little beat, that's all.
No.
Damn.
I left the window open this morning.
The cat's gonna have gotten out.
Really. I'm fine.
Something happened to somebody I know and I'm kinda bummed about it.
Titu!
Where are you?
Can I just tell you about it some other time?
I just want to take a shower,
watch TV, and veg.
Titu?
Here, boy.
Okay. I'll talk to you tomorrow.
You, too. Bye.
Scanlon.
Hi.
It's Allison.
Clyde Morton's out of I.C.U.
Great. I'll be sure and send him a card.
I want to talk to him.
What for? He's obviously not gonna hurt anyone now,
not in the near term, anyway.
I had that dream again last night.
Same woman, same everything.
- A little different clothes, but other than that...
- Allison.
He might know something.
He might be able to shed some light.
You know your boss,
my old friend,
practically had an aneurysm yesterday.
I need to find somebody to look after my kids,
I don't think I can be there till late afternoon.
Do you just not hear "no"?
You want to say 5:00?
- Hey, you.
- Hello.
Thanks for coming all this way.
Well, thank you for seeing me.
I know you're very busy.
No. You said it's important.
So, what's good here?
Nothing. The chairs.
It's close. Hi.
Mr. Dubois.
Thank you.
Ah, you like fish?
Yeah.
Two... whatever the fish is today, two of those.
And you still like iced tea?
I do.
And two of those,
too, please.
Thanks.
So.
Were you as stunned as I was that we ran into each other the other night?
Yeah, I was pretty stunned.
She's lovely, your wife.
Thank you. She came to me that way, actually.
I had nothing to do with it.
Steve seems nice.
He is. Nice. Very.
Do you believe in fate?
It's funny you should say that.
I didn't used to,
but since I got out of school...
well, since I've been married, really...
Well, here's the thing.
For the past few years or so I, I've had this, um...
It's like a hollow inside me,
and I've been trying to figure out how to fill it.
what it is and what to do with it,
and just last week I realized what it was.
I'm smart.
Not that Steve isn't, but...
You know, selling houses.
I don't know.
It's not quantum physics.
It's not any type of physics.
So now you're supposed to say, "Everything's physics".
Everything's physics.
Anyway, then I ran into you,
that's the fate part.
You lost me, Karen.
I want to start working again.
I want to be an engineer, I want to use...
my head for something more than calculating mortgage rates.
Aha.
Steve and I are thinking of moving the business here.
His parents are getting older.
He'd like to be closer.
Sure.
Funny thing is...
There happens to be a job opening
at your company that I think I might be right for.
Oh, really? Wow.
That's, um, that's great.
So, um...
I was hoping, as long as you're comfortable with it,
you'd put in a good word for me.
Assistant vice-president of systems sales and marketing.
It says here that they're looking for a masters in engineering.
I know, and I never get mine.
which is stupid because I have a1most all the credits,
but I was kind of hoping that my experience in business would make up for it.
And,
well, your going to bat for me.
Right. Um...
The thing is, they're looking for somebody with a masters.
I know, but...
Clients want to feel like they're dealing with someone who
understands what it is that we're selling.
I get that, I do,
but I'm a closer, Joe.
You get me in that room,
and I will show them that I have the perfect résumé for this job.
Look, um...
I know how management thinks around here.
If they say they're looking for a certain degree,
you got to walk in that room with that diploma.
It's that simple.
But even if someone like you weighs in on my behalf,
don't you think they'll meet me?
I don't know.
Isn't it at least worth a try?
I mean...how fantastic would that be,
working together again,
rubbing elbows,
pulling all-nighters.
What are you doing, Karen?
I'm closing, Joe.
I'm closing...
Well, stop.
Look, I am flattered by your proposal, both proposals,
but frankly, you're not qualified for either position.
The first one is clearly way above your head educationally,
and the second one is permanently filled
by someone who knows more about physics
than you and me combined.
Enjoy your fish.
Mr. Morton?
It's Allison Dubois from the district attorney's office.
May I come in?
Sure, I guess.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize you had a visitor.
Can I help you?
If you're here about the accident,
somebody already spoke with him.
No, no, no, that's not why I'm here.
I'm not here to take a statement, really. I...
I wanted to ask you a question.
I'm sorry, you are...?
Catherine Croshaw.
I'm Mr. Morton's case advisor at the employment office.
Have we met before?
No, not exactly.
I can come back.
That's okay. I only have about five minutes left on my parking meter.
Yeah, you'd better get home and feed that cat.
Clyde...
Cathy,
come on,
enough of that.
This woman doesn't care about our business.
I just woke up from a coma.
Damn, girl, get over here and give me a proper kiss.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Call me when you get home from the gym.
Mm, think I'll skip the gym today.
I just want to take a shower.
- See ya.
- Nice to meet you.
She seems nice.
Yeah. She's going through a, uh, tough time right now.
The guy she's divorcing is crazy.
Nuts.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, he's one of those...
Hey.
Oh, no, get-get him out of here!
- Nurse!
- What's the problem? Did I do something?
Get him out of here!
He's the reason I'm in this hospital, okay?
Nurse!
- He's a police officer.
- Get him out of here, all right.
- I'm supposed to be safe in here!
- This is Detective Lee Scanlon.
- What?
- He's with me.
You're not Cathy's ex?
I'm not anybody's ex and damn proud of it.
Wait a second.
Who did you think he was?
You were never married to Cathy?
Is that the lady I just passed in the hall?
I don't even know who Cathy is.
Is that why you took off on me yesterday?
You thought I was...
her husband?
Her ex-husband.
He put her in the hospital last year.
I'm sorry.
I guess I was wrong.
He told me that he knew where I lived and that he's been driving by my house.
Can I talk to you outside?
It wasn't Clyde.
It was never going to be Clyde.
What was never going to be Clyde?
He was never gonna to kill her.
He was just gonna be accused of it.
Okay.
His fingerprints,
his DNA is probably all over her house.
They would have found her body,
looked at his record,
figured it was an open and shut case.
What was an open and shut case?
- Her murder.
- Whose murder?
Cathy.
The Cathy I just saw walking down the hall?
I hate to be the bearer of good news,
but she's not dead.
No, but she was going to be before Clyde got hit.
- But now she's not...
- No.
Yes.
Oh, my God, she was wearing the same clothes that she was wearing in my dream.
It's tonight.
Lee,
it's gonna happen tonight.
No, I didn't make it to the gym.
I had to do something after work.
Nothing. I'm fine.
Just a little beat, that's all.
No.
Damn, I left the window open this morning.
The cat's gonna have gotten out.
Really, I'm fine.
It's just,
something happened today to somebody that I'm kind of bummed out about.
Titu? Here, boy.
Titu?
I'll tell you some other time,
okay?
I just want to take a shower,
watch TV and veg.
Titu.
Titu?
I'll call you in the morning, okay?
You, too.
Bye.
You ever play rock, scissors,
and paper, Mr. Croshaw?
This is just like that,
except it's called knife,
gun...
You're dead.
Mommy!
It's him!
Who?
Him!
Hello?
Good morning.
Good morning,
Mr. District Attorney.
"Mr. District Attorney"?
Wow, that bad, huh?
Well, I guess you had every reason to be angry.
Did I?
Turns out you saved the woman's life
and kept an innocent man from going to jail.
So does that mean I ought to send out my résumé?
Allison, as long as I have a job, you have a job.
By the way, you wouldn't have
any inside information on that, would you?
Sir, clearly I'm not the person to ask.
I am the one who saw Bradley standing behind your desk,
but well...
for what it's worth,
I do have a good feeling about tomorrow.
Me, too.
Things are gonna be different under my watch, Mr. Mayor.
Trust me.
I'm not afraid to knock a few heads from time to time.
No, I'm just... I just stopped Manny Devalos' heart, I think.
No, it's his office I'm in.
He's the only guy around here working at this hour.
So, when I realized that I'd forgotten my keys and my cell phone,
I almost locked out of my office.
I didn't know who else to ask for help.
So thank you for running them over here,
and I will be standing in the lobby. Yeah.
wife.
And...
She thinks I ought to concede as well.
Well, I don't know what to tell you.
If it were me,
I'd ride it out.
As a wise man once said,
"You can't have too much democracy".
Thank you, Manuel.
I will see you on TV tomorrow.
You, too.
Hey, listen,
if you see an exterminator looking lost out there will you point him this way?
He's supposed to do a big number on my office today.
Consider it done.
Oh, my gosh, with everything on,
I completely forgot to ask you.
How was your lunch yesterday?
Didn't happen.
What? You're kidding!
She stood you up?
Actually, uh...
I did the standing up.
You did?
I don't know.
What's the point of going out for a
hamburger when you have steak at home?
I'm taking the kids to school.
I'll call you from work.
That's so funny.
I was sure you'd ordered the fish.
Transcript : Raceman - Synchro : Alucardo
www.forom.com