No, wait. The cocktail napkins
were delivered here
for some insane reason, okay?
So be outside in 20 minutes,
I'm gonna do a drive-by, all right?
Please let me have my keys!
They're on the counter.
Oh, sorry,
I didn't mean to scare you.
That's okay, I'm just a little frazzled.
I've gotta check on Chris,
and then I gotta get to the store,
and then I gotta go
and pick up Wyatt early
and make cookies
for a Valentine's Day party.
And then I gotta take these to P3.
All of which pales in comparison
to what you're going through.
No, you know, life goes on.
I'm just happy
to have Christy back, I guess.
- But?
- But she hasn't even said anything.
I mean, I told her
I wanted to call Mom and Dad
and she closed up even more.
Well, you know,
it's only been a couple days.
Yeah, but what if I never
get through to her?
You will. I mean,
you just have to be patient.
She's been through something
none of us can even imagine.
So, I mean, the only thing you can
really do is just be there for her.
And if you need anything,
we are just a call
or an orb away, okay?
Knock, knock.
Hey, I brought you some breakfast.
Christy?
Christy, it's okay, you're safe now.
You're gonna be okay.
They're coming.
Well, I guess we figured they'd try
to get Christy back sooner or later.
Yeah, I just wish it was later
rather than sooner.
Give the girl time to heal.
I just wish we knew who "they" were
and why they're coming.
And why they want her back.
Well, it doesn't matter, because
they won't be getting her back.
That's why we're here, sweetie.
How is she?
Very scared.
Well, has she said anything? You
know, who these demons might be,
when they're coming?
No, nothing.
Okay, well,
we need to try to come up
with some sort of game plan,
don't you think?
But we don't know anything. We don't
know why they've been keeping her.
Which is why we have to find out
what she knows, get her to open up.
I just think it's too much
for her right now.
Look, they held her captive
for 15 years,
she must know something,
at least be able to ID them.
I just don't wanna pressure her
right now.
Well, sweetheart,
she's already under pressure
because she knows
that they're coming.
Do you think they're contacting her?
Well, maybe.
Then again, maybe she's got some
sort of telepathic thing going on.
It would actually kind of figure
that she'd have powers, right?
Maybe that can be why
they wanted her in the first place.
And why they want her back.
You have to talk to her.
I just don't think she's ready for that.
Look, if it's coming from you,
she'll be okay.
She's your sister. There's no
stronger bond than that, trust us.
All right, I'll try.
Okay, I'm gonna whip up
a quick potion
and you go to the "Book" and make a list
of all the telepathic demons, okay?
Oh, you're in a hurry.
Yeah, well, I got a new condo
to enjoy.
Lamp!
Excuse me, but I don't think
you recognise my entrance.
Fear not, ladies,
I'm one of the good guys.
The best, actually, so...
Oh, yes, the legendary manor,
where generations of Halliwells
have blossomed into witches.
Who are you
and what do you want?
Of course. Ladies, I am
Simon Thaddeus Reginald Marx,
and I'm here to take
Paige Matthews as my wife.
We've been at this for two days.
If you want your suffering to end,
you will tell me who took the witch.
I don't know.
- I swear!
- Come on, you were in on it.
Why else would you
leave your post?
I told you, I was called away.
Please, you've gotta believe me!
Do you think they'll believe you?
They, who could decimate
our entire clan on a whim.
They chose us to watch over her.
To break her down, and in return,
we'd share in the ultimate power
for which she is the key.
If we don't get her back,
we're all dead.
I've questioned all of the Scathers.
No one called him away.
Last chance.
Who are you working for?
He may not even know.
He may have been tricked,
perhaps telepathically.
The witch has answered
to unseen voices before.
We've seen it.
If so,
he's a liability.
He's been breached.
Gather the witch's things.
We'll find her another way.
We cannot use dark magic.
They may sense it.
They'll know something
has gone wrong, we cannot risk it!
We have to risk it.
We must find out who took the witch
if we are to survive.
I know all about the Charmed Ones.
I... I grew up on stories
of the Warren line of witches.
Grams and her many, many lovers.
And of course,
Patricia's tryst with her whitelighter.
Goodness, you're a randy bunch.
Is there some sort of
magical "Enquirer" I've not heard of?
Wow, our families worked together
during the Salem witch trials?
That is so cool.
Well, you know,
I'm just saying, he checks out.
I am a descendant of the Mighty Marx,
which is a very powerful,
very noble line of witches.
To be honest with you,
I'm a little surprised
you don't know who I am, but...
My goodness, you're fetching.
Oh, that's so sweet. Did you?
But you're not half-whitelighter,
which is a requisite for my future mate,
so sorry to disappoint you.
- But you, on the other hand, are.
- Did you just say "future mate"?
No, no. That was... That was...
It came out wrong, apologies.
Okay, here's the deal.
We're actually super, super busy,
so it would be fabulous
if you could just orb yourself
off now.
I'll ignore that, but, Paige,
I'm not leaving without you.
After all, we are destined to be wed.
Okay, who says?
Well, only 40
of the most powerful oracles
and soothsayers
from around the globe,
plus a wizard or two, so...
When you think about it, Paige,
it makes all the sense in the world.
Bringing our two magical lines
together,
we would be
the ultimate power couple.
Okay, we're not gonna be
bringing our lines
or bringing anything together,
for that matter, okay?
- But why not?
- Because I don't want to!
And because I have a boyfriend.
A boyfriend? I see.
And who is he?
A witch? A whitelighter?
His name is Henry
and he is a parole officer
by trade and he is a mortal.
Oh, an immortal, no less.
Very impressive.
No, not immortal,
a mortal, as in non-magical.
With all due respect, that makes
absolutely no sense to me at all.
Having a mortal around whilst
you're fighting evil is, well,
let's face it, irresponsible.
Okay, you need to go now.
Unless you wanna stay
and help us vanquish demons.
But of course, ma'am.
Having a powerful witch around
like myself can only be an asset.
Tell me, how does Harry fare
in a magical battle?
Henry, and he fares just fine
in whatever he wants to fare in.
I'll be honest with you,
I'm a little surprised
you're not taking to this.
You know, me?
I mean, imagine, if you will,
the evil we could vanquish
as a couple.
We are not now,
nor will we ever be, a couple!
Well, that did not go too well.
Piper.
May I be of some assistance?
Bags.
Are you crazy?
What if somebody saw that?
Well, what if somebody were
to see you shopping?
A witch of your standing? No, no.
After all, there are people
for things like that.
- Who are you?
- I am Simon Thaddeus
Reginald Marx.
Of the Marx line of witches?
It's a very noble, very... Never mind.
Moving on.
First of all, I'm here to state my case.
Great. Well, I don't have time for that,
because I have to go pick up my son.
Again with the magic.
Piper, I'm here to appeal to you,
you being the practical Charmed One.
Now, listen to me: It is my destiny
to marry your sister, Paige.
Oh, for God's sake.
Forty of the most powerful oracles
and soothsayers
from around the globe
have predicted it.
Plus a wizard or two.
Good luck with that.
According to your sister,
a demon could be attacking
at this very moment,
and I want you to know that I am
fantastic at vanquishing demons.
Well, that's great,
but we can handle our own demons.
You'll see,
it is my fate to be with Paige.
Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh, God!
- I'm so sorry, I wasn't even looking, I...
- That's okay, don't worry about it.
- Greg?
- Piper?
Hi.
Oh, my God.
Look, Christy, you're safe now.
I promise,
I am going to keep you safe.
But I need your help to do that.
Do you know who they are,
who's coming?
Do you hear them, like voices?
Yeah?
That's good, that's really good.
What do they say?
What do they want?
You know, it's okay.
You know, we can talk about it later.
Don't worry, it's okay.
I mean,
who does this guy think he is?
He just shows up and announces
that we're destined to be together?
Well, according to 40 oracles
and a soothsayer,
your future husband.
That is really not funny.
I'm sorry.
How's the list coming?
Well, I have a dozen
that have telepathic powers.
Well, hopefully
Billie can convince Christy
to narrow it down for us a little bit.
Who's here?
Rats, I forgot.
Henry and I have a lunch date.
Oh, you might wanna reschedule
in case a demon attacks.
Oh, look at you,
you sound like Sir Full-of-Himself.
Well, he might not be your Mr. Right,
but he does have a point.
Paige, I don't run away
from a fight, okay?
Come on, I deal with violent,
dangerous criminals every day.
But those violent, dangerous criminals
do not throw fireballs at you.
Well, what about Piper's kids?
I mean, they're here all the time.
They have powers
to defend themselves.
They do?
So please just go?
I will call you in a little bit.
Well, hold it, hold it, hold it.
If I run away every time
a demon attacks,
I'm gonna be running away
all the time, right?
Okay.
Okay, come on, baby.
Oh, hi, sorry. Oh, thanks.
- Go on. Wyatt's really gotta go.
- Okay.
If you could just put those
on the dining-room table,
that'd be great.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Sweetie,
don't forget to wash your hands!
I hear we have demons attacking?
- How did you hear that?
- You know, your friend, Simon?
British? Very cocky?
- Who's Simon?
- Nobody.
Okay, I have two seconds
for you to catch me up. Go.
Okay. Christy finally spoke.
Unfortunately,
she said something weird:
- "They're coming. "
- Who's coming? When?
It's okay.
Phoebe and I got this under control.
We didn't tell you because
you've got a crazy day.
Crazier than you think.
Guess who I just ran into, literally.
- Whom?
- Greg.
- Greg?
- Fireman Greg.
Oh, he was the hot Greg.
You gonna go out with him?
Oh, God, don't be ridiculous.
Christy, what is it? What's wrong?
- Christy, please, I wanna help you.
- I'm afraid.
I know you're afraid.
Nothing's gonna happen to you,
you're in a very safe place.
- You can't stop them.
- Stop who?
- Christy, please.
- You can't stop them from coming.
When? When are they coming?
Now.
So how long does it usually take
for demons to attack?
Well, it could be any time, really.
You know, it depends.
- On?
- On timing, you know.
Usually the worse it is for us,
the better it is for them.
You know, that kind of thing.
Mustard?
- No, thanks.
- You can still opt out if you want.
Not a chance.
Incoming!
What? What is it?
They're here.
Get down!
Sweetie, why don't you
orb up to your room?
Fireball!
No!
It's okay, I'm all right, I'm okay.
Are you okay?
What's going on? What happened?
Ask the firestarter.
Paige...
You know you could
have been killed?
- Paige, I'm okay.
- No, you're not okay.
You were hit by a fireball.
Which was actually my fault.
No, it was not your fault.
I'm a grown man, I chose to be here.
Henry,
I really think you should leave.
We don't know
if they're coming back.
Paige, I'm not leaving.
I am not having this on my head,
okay? So please? Please.
All right.
I know that was
probably hard for you.
I guess it would have been harder
if I was planning his funeral.
Well, looks like Christy has a few
more powers than we realised, huh?
Yeah, maybe more
than even she knew about.
Maybe that's why those demons were
holding her hostage for all those years.
Maybe they were trying to co-opt
her powers for themselves.
But I don't think she's that powerful.
I mean, unless they know
something that we don't.
Well, all the more reason for her
to open up so we can find out.
I just think she's too freaked out.
Well, she needs to get
un-freaked out, and fast.
Okay, I'm gonna go drop off Wyatt
with Dad and Chris
and get one of the other moms
to take over cookie duties.
Wait, why?
What do you mean, "why"?
Why do you think?
We can handle this, Piper.
- Yeah, but...
- No buts.
Listen, you bake
and spend time with Wyatt
and hopefully we can figure out
who we're up against
before they come back.
Or before Christy
burns down the house.
- Christy.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
No, it's okay,
you didn't do anything wrong.
- Did you know you could do...?
- No.
But they did.
"They"? You mean the demons?
Were those the same ones?
Who are they?
I don't know.
- I never knew.
- It's okay.
I told you we'd protect you,
and we did.
Look, I am not gonna
let them hurt you anymore.
I promise.
It's over, don't you see that?
The Charmed Ones
are protecting her now.
We still have time.
- They haven't sensed anything yet.
- How do you know?
How do you know
they are not deciding
our punishment as we speak?
Because they would have acted
by now if they had.
They're not known for their patience.
We have to get the witch back
somehow.
Impossible.
We do not have the power to go up
against the Charmed Ones
and survive.
Still,
it would be better to be vanquished
by the witches than by the Triad.
That would be a fate worse
than death.
Then perhaps we should escape,
hide from them.
They're the most powerful evil
ever known.
They'd find us.
- Prepare the ritual.
- The ritual?
For the Triad?
We cannot tell them we've lost her,
that is suicide.
We have no choice.
They're the only ones
who can get the girl back now.
We'll just have to hope
they show us mercy.
- Hi.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
Hey, I'm sorry just to show up
like this, Piper, but I've got...
You've got a little something there
on your cheek.
Frosting?
No, I was just baking cookies
for my son's party.
- Anyway...
- Anyway.
There's a guy in my station,
he used to work at a body shop,
and he says he can fix our cars
for next to nothing.
- Oh, that's great.
- But there's a catch.
You see, he's leaving this afternoon,
his next shift isn't for, like, four days.
But if we get your car
down there right now,
he can take care of everything.
Well, I can't go.
I've gotta bake a zillion cookies
and drop them off at Wyatt's school...
I smell smoke.
Well, you know,
I burned a few cookies.
Looks like you burned
more than a few cookies.
Well, you know, kids.
Those are the cookies.
All right, you go, I'll watch him.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, little man, what's up?
Pretty cool truck.
Master Wyatt, it's an honour.
Harry.
Now, you must understand
that your kind
and our kind
simply can't commingle.
Where did you come from?
There is a reason why mortals
should stick to their own.
- Well, actually, there's a few reasons...
- Mortals?
- Simon?
- Darling.
What are you doing here?
I'm just explaining things
to Harry here.
If you mean Henry, that is not him.
In fact, I don't know who that is.
I'm Greg. We met once before,
when I was dating Piper.
Oh, right, Greg.
Okay, excuse us.
You need to get out.
- Are you insane?
- Are you?
Those were Windsor roses, my dear.
From East Sussex, very rare.
We do not practise magic
in front of mortals.
Must be very trying.
But I can assure you, Paige,
once we are wed...
We are not going to be wed.
Not now, not ever. Get out.
You take that one, I got that one.
Let's crash them.
- Come on.
- Hey. How's it going?
Not so good.
Simon just orbed in
in front of your friend.
- Luckily, he didn't see anything.
- Oh, thank God.
Did you find
who that shoe belongs to?
No, we haven't yet,
but we're on top of it,
and it's not your job,
so don't worry about it.
Hey, Piper, if you want my buddy
to fix the car, we better get going.
Oh, gee, that's really great, but...
Come on,
we'll drop off the cookies on the way
and Wyatt can play on the firetruck.
- We can catch up.
- Yeah, hold that thought.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Actually, I think it's a great idea.
What with Simon orbing in
and out of here willy-nilly,
and demons are trying to attack...
No, that's not what I mean.
I mean, spending the day
with another man,
while Leo's frozen and all.
Piper, it's not a date,
he's just a friend of yours.
A friend that I used to sleep with.
Well, don't sleep with him.
Easy solution to that problem.
Go have fun.
Remember how to do that?
My word, this man is a pig.
Who are you?
I, sir, am your girlfriend's
future husband.
Nothing.
You got anything yet?
Yes, I see my new condo
with me not in it.
- I should just move back here.
- Here's what I'm not understanding.
If we've identified them
and know who they are,
why can't we find them?
And the Scather demons
don't even have telepathic powers.
Maybe I was right, maybe Christy
does have some power of telepathy
and she contacted them.
You know, maybe she's suffering
from that Stockholm syndrome thing.
Well, possibly, but it doesn't explain
why we can't find the demons.
Oh, God, maybe we should
have accepted Simon's help.
Oh, are you still thinking
about the Brit?
No, I'm not thinking about him.
He just may have had a point,
that's all.
The age-old question,
to date or not to date a mortal.
I just keep thinking, if that fireball
had been two inches to the left,
there would be no Henry to save.
Does that make me selfish?
Only you can answer that, sweetie.
Right.
Okay, well,
back to the matter at hand.
You realise that once
we summon them,
there is no turning back.
They will come.
Proceed.
Why have you summoned us?
How could you let her escape?
Why did you not summon us
immediately?
My lord, we thought
we could get her back.
You failed us,
just as I predicted you would.
We didn't fail you.
For 15 years we held her for you,
and now...
We mustn't let our anger
get the best of us.
We can't lose sight
of the bigger picture.
There is no bigger picture
without the witch, Asmodeus.
She is the key.
And without her, we can't possibly
hope to get the power we need.
We should decimate
this miserable clan
before anything else goes wrong.
No, wait. You don't understand.
- The witch was rescued by her sister.
- So?
So they are both under the protection
of the Charmed Ones.
- The Charmed Ones?
- That's why we summoned you.
We don't have the power
to go up against them.
- Neither do we.
- Not yet, we don't.
Not unless we get the witch back.
And if we do,
you'd better not lose her again.
Look, just because demons
use their powers to do bad things
doesn't mean all powers are bad.
You can use yours for good.
Look, you are in
the light now, Christy.
There is good magic all around you.
You just have to believe it.
You have to trust it.
How?
Well, like this.
See? It's easy. Just focus on what
you want and you can do it.
All right, why don't you try now?
Come on, don't worry,
you can do it. I'll be right here.
Come on. Come on.
Now, I want you to focus
really hard on what you want, okay?
See it in your mind's eye.
- I did it.
- I told you!
Whoa, that's a lot,
maybe I should put that out.
You know, it's not easy
having magical powers.
But then again,
you will never understand that.
Where'd you say you're from,
again?
Sussex, with homes in Devonshire,
Manchester, London.
And when...
When Paige and I are wed...
Listen, I told you
that's not gonna happen, got that?
Paige is my girl.
Is it really fair of you
to be keeping Paige away
from the magical world
she's destined to be in?
I'm not keeping Paige away
from anything.
But you are.
You see,
it is destiny to combine the Marx
and Matthews magical line.
Once we are a couple,
we will be the most powerful force
of good the world has ever seen.
Well, I think Paige and her sisters
are doing fine without you.
But I think Paige deserves
so much more,
and I can give it to her.
I'm getting tired of you insinuating
that I am not good enough for Paige.
I'm not insinuating it, I'm saying it.
All right, look, pal,
I may be new to this magical world,
but I'm not afraid of demons,
and I'm definitely not afraid of you.
- Not afraid?
- No.
I tell you what, let's wait until you've
had a fireball thrown at your face
and then we'll have a little discussion
about how brave you think you are!
Already happened this morning.
I'm still here.
And how embarrassing
that must have been.
Let me guess,
Paige had to heal you. Correct?
Yeah. So?
So it is only a matter of time
before you are beyond healing,
leaving poor Paige too devastated
to fight the great fight.
- You know what? We're finished here.
- Are you blind, man?
Can't you see that you're a liability
in every sense of the word?
And the fear of you being blown up
will make it impossible
for Paige to ever truly
be honest with you.
Look, pal, I don't know who you are,
and I don't really care.
You're not getting Paige,
you got that?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, if you won't listen to reason,
then I guess there's only
one thing left for us to do.
I guess so. What's that?
I challenge you to a duel.
Are you sure I can't pay him
something more for this?
No, he's good. Don't worry about it.
Well, it doesn't seem right,
especially since it was my fault.
It's no big deal, he's a fireman.
He likes to help people.
Is that why you became a fireman?
I guess. I mean, it sure ain't the pay.
You know, I wanted to call you,
stay in touch.
But I felt weird after I heard you
and Leo got back together.
Yeah. Of course.
Hey, I don't mean to pry or anything,
but I couldn't help notice
that he didn't seem to be around.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, sure.
You know, it's great.
So is he around?
Well, Leo's been away.
Away?
Away.
Excuse me.
- Hello?
- I think you need to come home.
What do you mean? Why?
Well, we've ID'd the demons
that took Christy,
but we can't find them anywhere.
Well, they're low-level,
they shouldn't be that hard to find.
Yeah, we think something is going on,
like maybe they're being protected
by other demons.
More powerful demons.
Like who?
- What was that?
- Hurry.
Phoebe?
- Phoebe?
- Is something wrong?
Actually, I need my car now.
- But it's not finished.
- Oh, that's okay.
Do you think you could watch Wyatt
for me for a little while?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay, thanks, bye. I owe you.
Help!
Jacket!
Oh, my God! Billie, what happened?
I cannot believe this,
I cannot believe what just happened.
What?
Christy just attacked me!
What? Where is she?
Where'd she go?
She just left
with one of the demons.
I don't understand, you guys.
Everything was going so well.
I mean, she was laughing,
we were having fun, and...
Oh, I just don't know
how this happened.
Hang on a second.
Start from the beginning.
What were you guys
doing right before?
Well, I was showing her
how to control her powers,
the same way you guys showed me,
and she was getting it.
- She was really excited.
- And then?
And then she started hearing
some voices,
voices she started talking to.
- What was she saying?
- First, she wanted them to go away.
And then it was something
about being the key,
or that she didn't wanna
be the key or...
Wait a minute, what key?
To the ultimate power?
Excuse me?
- Oh, no, not another one.
- Yeah, I don't know.
Well, that explains
why they took her now.
And then the weirdest thing
happened.
She just changed.
Her expression got very dark.
Then that demon
from before showed up
and before I knew it, I was on fire.
What?
Well, it's just, if that's true,
the demon that took her
didn't have telepathic powers.
Which means
she had to contact them.
That's ridiculous,
why would she do that?
Because they're all she knows.
No. No, that's not what happened,
okay? You guys weren't there.
Christy and I connected as sisters.
So if those demons didn't contact her,
then some other demons did, okay?
That's a possibility.
So, what are we waiting for?
How do we find her?
Well, I guess we could start
by trying to figure out
who this Ultimate Power is.
And maybe they tie in to how
we're supposed to get Leo back.
Henry?
Paige,
what do you know about duels?
- Duels, why?
- En garde, sir!
Wait! What are you doing?
I have to go.
What the hell?
Paige, yes, great.
Best for you to see this yourself,
first-hand.
Now, I know this might look
a little extreme,
but I am determined
to make my point.
- Simon, knock it off!
- But you see, my dear, I can't.
For your sake as well as his,
it's far better
you face the truth now than later.
- Look, for you to be with Harry...
- Henry!
Whatever. For you to be with him
instead of me...
...would be a terrible mistake.
I got him right where I want him.
All right, you pompous son of a bitch,
you think you're the perfect man
for Paige just because
you know a little magic?
Yes, as a matter of fact, I do.
- You don't know anything about her.
- On the contrary, sir,
I know everything there is to know
about Paige Matthews, thank you.
- Where is she ticklish?
- Ticklish?
Third toe, left foot.
Right below the neck.
Did you know she only salts popcorn
on the right side, never on the left?
And every time she watches
"The Wizard of Oz," she cries.
Every time, did you know that?
No, why would you?
Because you don't even care.
You just want some trophy witch
so you can have a nice power couple.
I care about Paige.
- I love her.
- And I love him.
Paige. Paige, you can't be serious.
Yeah, we're both serious.
Beat it, pal.
What he said. Cross the pond.
I told you I never run from a fight.
- Thank you.
- Sorry, sorry.
That's okay. That's okay.
Nothing except stuff about all
the other Ultimate Powers we faced.
Billie, did Christy say anything else
that might be able to help us?
She's calling for me, I can hear her.
She wants us to reverse
the "to call a lost witch" spell
so we can come find her.
- How does she know about that spell?
- It doesn't matter, we're not going.
She doesn't want you guys
to go, just me.
Well, no, it could be a trap.
It's not a trap. I trust her.
Even though, you know,
she did try to kill you?
I have to. I can't lose her again.
Okay, fine.
But if you're not out of there
in five minutes,
we're coming in to get you.
Christy?
Are you there?
Your sister can't be saved,
and neither can you.
Christy, help me, please!
Don't let them make you do this.
You have the power
to stop them, use it!
Christy, look, we're sisters, okay?
They can't come between us,
nobody can.
Hold your fire. No!
We don't want to hurt the key.
We can combine our powers together
and put an end to this once and for all.
We can do this together. Trust me.
Surround her.
- Well?
- It's over.
So why did you want to come here?
I don't know, it's just kind of...
It's, like, our place now, right?
I mean, ever since you told me
that you were...
A witch?
It's okay, it's not a bad word,
you know.
Oh, no. No, not at all.
- Henry, are you okay?
- Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, great.
Top of the world. Literally, right?
- Do you want me to heal that for you?
- No.
No, I like it.
It's like a battle scar, right?
It says I fought for my girl and I won.
Yes, you certainly did.
I mean, I faced demons and fireballs,
magical suitors, orbing.
I mean,
I think I passed the test, right?
What test?
You love me, don't you?
Yes, I love you.
Because...
Paige,
will you marry me?
Yes.
Hello!
- Hi, Mommy.
- Hi. Looks like somebody had fun.
- Can you say thank you?
- Thank you.
- We gotta get it back here, kiddo.
- There you go.
There you go.
You're welcome, buddy. Anytime.
Hey, why don't you go play
and I'll be right there, okay?
He's a great kid.
Thank you for everything.
Oh, it was my pleasure.
I'm sorry.
No, no, it's okay.
I mean, no, it's not okay.
It's definitely not okay.
I just thought, you know,
with Leo gone...
No, I mean, he's not gone.
I didn't say he was gone, he's just...
You know, he's away.
Okay.
Listen, Greg, you're a great guy,
really, and if, you know,
the situation was different...
But Leo is coming back.
I understand.
Well, it was really great
to see you again, Piper.
You too.
What am I wearing?
Oh, that's a John Stamos T-shirt.
You were totally obsessed.
I was not.
Yes, you wanted to marry
Mr. Full House.
Well, you wanted to marry Pee-wee.
No, I didn't.
I'm sorry about attacking you.
That wasn't me.
I was being controlled.
I would never hurt you.
Oh, stop, I know. I know.
Is it really over? I mean, for good?
I'm not gonna let anyone
take you away ever again.
I promise.
Phoebe!
- You scared me.
- What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing?
I'm eavesdropping. I don't get to do
that anymore now that I moved out.
Well, stop it!
Spoilsport. What's wrong with you?
- Your fireman?
- No, thank you.
Christy.
Oh, well, don't worry about her,
she's doing fine.
That's not what I mean.
She's the key, and whatever
that means, it can't be good.
Well, maybe it is,
maybe she's here to help us fight
whatever comes next, you know.
Maybe they both are.
Well, I guess we're just
gonna have to wait and see.
She's in position.
We're almost there.