All right, come on.
Come on, come on.
Billie?
Oh, hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
Scrying.
At 7 in the morning?
Well, actually,
I've been doing this all night long.
I'm just trying to find my sister.
Now that I know a demon took her,
I have to try, right?
Billie...
I know, I know he's got
a 15-year head start on me,
but, you know, I just figure,
if I keep doing this,
then sooner or later...
You think she's still alive?
She has to be.
Okay, here's the thing.
If she's alive, we'll find her.
I promise you that.
But you can't let yourself
become obsessed with this.
I can't exactly let it go either.
But you don't want it
to consume your life.
I know, it's hard.
Aren't you supposed to be at school
or something?
No, I can't focus on anything,
not school right now especially.
I think maybe going to class
would be a good thing for you.
No, I can't. What if there's a demon
and I'm not here?
I can't help out.
I don't see any demons.
Do you see any demons?
Time to make room for another.
What the hell?
Where am I? What's going on?
You're out of time, J.D.
You're no longer useful to me.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Oh, my God!
Is he still alive?
I think so.
Call 911.
Hey there, can I borrow your car?
Mine's running on fumes.
Sorry, mine is too.
- What? I just filled it up.
- Well, now it's empty.
Honey.
- Yeah?
- No, we're out of honey.
Put it on the list.
Well, much as I'd like to stay here
and watch you two snipe at each other,
I don't want to be late
for my interview.
What interview?
Oh, social services.
I'm gonna try to get my old job back.
- Why?
- Why? Because I like it, that's why.
I only quit because of
the whole magic thing
but now that we've got Billie
to help out...
I think that's great.
Hey, maybe you can help me
adopt a child.
- What?
- Well, yeah.
I'm sort of thinking that adoption
might be my only option at this point.
But, Phoebe, that's ridiculous.
Why? What's wrong with adoption?
You were adopted.
That reminds me, we need eggs.
Oh, eggs I have,
it's the sperm I'm missing.
Gross.
I'm just saying, I can't just sit back
and wait for love to find me.
I gotta hurry up.
At least, according to my tea leaves.
Tea. Leo?
Tea, you already told me.
- Sniping.
- I wasn't sniping.
Oh, my God, that's perfect.
What?
Why didn't I think of that before?
Gotta go.
How did I wind up
the only sane one here?
You're telling me.
So do you want me to go
to the store with you?
No, you should...
I think you should pick up the kids.
No, I got it.
It's fine, I got it.
Thanks.
Hey, you're not just gonna leave
like that, are you?
I tried to help clean up but...
No, no, no,
I'm not talking about the milk,
I'm talking about you two.
You've been walking around on pins
and needles for over a week now.
Why don't you guys just talk?
You know, no offence, Paige,
but it's really none of your business.
Actually, it is, because I live here too
and this is affecting us all.
Look, we know you guys
have this epic destined marriage,
but it doesn't mean
that you're immune to problems,
especially with everything
that's gone on lately.
- I know.
- Well, if you know,
then why don't you
do something about it?
I've tried. We've tried and it always
just ends up in an argument.
Well, I don't know. Why don't you try
seeing a marriage counsellor?
We tried that once too, remember?
Try somebody else.
Try another one.
You guys owe it to yourselves.
I don't think you're gonna have
much problem getting that job.
Unless I get there soon,
I am going to.
So please, just go talk to her.
Please?
Hello, Paige.
It's good to see you.
Sam?
Don't you mean "Dad"?
Multiple abrasions, bruises,
concussion, yet no internal bleeding.
He's a lucky kid, although
we haven't been able to ID him yet.
So for now, he's a John Doe.
Have the authorities
been notified yet?
Yeah, like over an hour ago.
Well, when he comes up from the ER,
best put him in a private room,
until we find out who he really is.
- All right, Doctor?
- Vaklav.
I'm filling in for Dr. Winfield.
His name is
Jonathan David Williams...
...though he goes by J.D.
He's my charge, a future whitelighter,
or he was supposed to be.
- Yeah, and?
- He disappeared in 1955.
I have heard nothing
from him since.
Not until he was hit by a car
this morning
and rushed to a hospital.
- Well, how old is he?
- The same age as he was then.
He hasn't aged a day.
I don't understand it either, Paige,
but I gotta believe
that whoever or whatever
made him disappear 50 years ago,
doesn't want him found now.
Which is why I need your help.
You're a whitelighter,
why don't you orb him to safety?
Many people have seen him,
it would raise too many questions.
- Well, what do you want me to do?
- Help me get him out of there.
Maybe cast a little spell.
What, I'm the only witch you know?
- You are my daughter.
- Genetically, maybe.
I can't do this right now,
I'm late for a job interview, okay?
An interview?
Why do you need a job?
You're a witch, a whitelighter.
Maybe if you came around
more than once every three years,
you would know this
about your "daughter. "
Look, I'm sorry, Paige.
I just...
I didn't want to intrude.
Whatever, doesn't matter.
I'll call Phoebe,
see if she can help, okay?
Paige, can't Billie do it?
I'm kind of in the middle
of something,
and isn't she our magical go-to girl?
No, she was up all night
trying to find her sister,
which is why I was hoping that you...
Would you describe me
as gregarious?
No, I would describe you as evasive.
Where are you anyway?
I'm just exploring my options.
- But don't worry, I'm not committing.
- Not committing to what?
- How we doing?
- Oops, I gotta go.
Phoebe, Phoebe.
Who's gonna help Sam?
You know what, I don't know.
He's your dad.
No, he's not.
- Sorry.
- What'd she say?
Okay, here you go.
So, what's next?
Next we try to match you up
with the perfect donor.
Do you think I'm gonna get
to meet him?
This isn't a dating service,
Ms. Halliwell.
It's a sperm bank.
Right.
I blame you for this, you know.
You're the one that had
to open your big yap to Leo.
Remember what happened
the last time we went
to marriage counselling?
Jeez, I was just trying to help.
Don't go if you don't want.
Oh, no, we're going now.
Only this time, we're going to some
magical quack that Leo knows.
He's not a quack, he's a soothsayer.
Like I said. Which way?
So wait, you're not gonna help me
get Sam's charge out of the hospital?
No.
Why don't you try Agent Murphy?
Maybe he can help you.
If he had enough clout
to get our identities back,
he should be able
to help you out with this.
What about my job interview?
I don't know, don't ask me,
ask your dad.
He's not my...
Never mind.
Shall we go?
Any idea where this soothsayer
is hiding?
No, I just know
that he hangs out here.
Okay, and how exactly
do you know this guy?
From my whitelighter years.
Look, trust me, all right?
He's helped plenty
of magical couples over the years.
Leo, I don't know about this.
It's worth a try, isn't it?
Actually, you know what?
We've been through worse.
And we should be able
to fix this ourselves.
Okay, but we haven't, have we?
You know what? We're just
a little out of sync, that's all.
It happens.
There's nothing wrong with getting
some outside help once in a while.
We owe it to ourselves.
Flowers are not so much different
from marriages, really.
If you don't tend to them...
...nourish them...
...they wither.
Three-thirty is perfect.
Thank you so much for rescheduling,
I really appreciate it.
Okay, bye.
I don't understand
why we couldn't orb here.
- It would have been faster.
- Want my help?
- Drive like everybody else.
- We're not like everybody else.
- Speak for yourself.
- Paige?
Oh, sorry we're late,
really horrible traffic.
Of course,
that could have been avoided.
Sam, Agent Murphy.
Agent Murphy, Sam.
Long story short,
Sam's charge was hit by a car.
He's here in the hospital.
We need you to check him out
before something bad happens to him.
Wow, that was short.
Hold on a sec. Wait, your charge?
Sam's basically a guardian angel.
We call it a whitelighter.
- Like Paige is.
- But I wanna be a social worker.
But that isn't
what you were born to be.
Don't make me regret saving you
years ago.
You two related or something?
- No.
- Yes.
Anyway. Okay, we need you to get
J.D. Out of here as soon as possible
before this demon comes for him.
Demon? What demon?
I'll take it from here.
There's my charge, there's J.D.
Dirty boots.
Doctors don't wear dirty boots.
Freeze! Don't move.
What happened?
Okay, why would a demon
take him out of 1955
only to try to kill him now?
He must have gotten something out
of keeping J.D. Alive all these years.
Yeah, but what?
And why hasn't he aged?
That's creepy
even by our standards.
Now you know why I came to you.
Well, just heal him,
maybe he'll know something.
- No, I don't want him awake.
- Why not?
Because he'll wake up 50 years
in the future, that's why.
I don't want him to freak out.
He'll take off, I know him.
I barely got him to trust me
before he disappeared.
I thought you said
he was a future whitelighter.
Yeah, if I can keep him
out of trouble,
which I obviously haven't done
a very good job of.
Well, I've surrounded this room
with crystals so he's safe here.
It'll give us some time to figure out
who this demon is.
But how? We didn't get
a good look at him
and if there's nothing
in the "Book of Shadows... "
Agent Murphy
might have leads.
He told me this wasn't
the first case he'd heard of
where someone just vanished
into thin air.
What part of the government
does he work for exactly?
The super creepy part.
Look, he's helped us out
with some magical problems.
Okay, we trust him, he trusts us.
I'm gonna go talk to him,
see what he knows,
- and I'll call you, okay?
- The whitelighter way?
No, Sam, the regular way.
Answer the phone if it rings.
Their wings old and tired,
the two butterflies clung
to a broken branch.
And together,
they floated down the river,
each breathing life into the other
as they made their final journey home.
Yoo-hoo, anybody home?
Earth calling.
Come on,
give him a chance.
I have, for the last 52 minutes
and 23 seconds.
- So, what, that's it? Time's up?
- You think?
You stopped listening to each other.
It's common.
Look, I didn't wanna come here
in the first place, okay?
Our problems are not magical, Leo,
- they're normal.
- They were caused by magic,
- that's why we're here.
- No, we are here
because you didn't care what I wanted.
You just cared what you wanted.
How many times a day
do you have sex?
A day? What, are you crazy?
No wonder you wanted to see him.
Are you kidding me?
Really. Hang on.
Oh, shucks, look.
Family emergency, gotta go.
Just remember,
it is always darkest before the dawn.
What the hell?
- Leo?
- Piper?
Yup.
Nope.
This one is not right either.
But we've been through
over 50 donor candidates so far.
Yeah, I know.
Maybe I'm just not being specific.
What I need is a little girl
with brown eyes,
sandy blond hair, little button nose,
that likes to save innocents,
you know.
Kicks butt,
works well in groups of three.
I mean, that's all.
- That's all?
- Yeah.
Miss Halliwell...
Oh, you know what,
call me Phoebe.
And please, I mean,
we're talking sperm here, right?
Phoebe...
...I don't think specifics
are the problem here.
I mean, let's face it,
you have an incredibly specific image
of who you want your little girl to be.
Too specific, actually.
Oh, to be honest...
...she doesn't have to have
the little button nose, okay?
We specialize in helping
to create families here.
We're dedicated
to promoting an open approach
to helping anybody who wants
to start a family but can't.
And I totally respect that.
I mean, that's why I'm here.
But...
...we're not a substitute for love.
I've been doing this
a long time, Phoebe.
And I know from experience
that when someone can't find a match,
they don't really want to.
What they want
is outside these walls, not inside.
Paige, where are you?
Sam? Sam.
It's okay, J.D.
You just go back to sleep. You rest.
But what...
What happened?
Oh, God.
Close your eyes.
Go on.
Trust me.
I feel better.
How?
- What's going on?
- It's a long story.
But you still need to rest, okay?
It's important,
you've been through a lot.
Okay, but what happened?
Where am I? How'd I get here?
What do you remember?
Well, I remember
getting nailed by a car.
Before that.
I don't know, I...
I was at the drive-in.
It was the middle of the flick
Rebel Without a Cause.
I went to get a soda and...
- And what?
- I don't know.
Some creep
scared the hell out of me.
Took a flash photo, blinded me.
Next thing I know,
I'm inside somewhere and he's...
He's what?
What did he do?
Yeah, I must have bashed
my head in pretty good.
Stay put.
Piper, the soothsayer
must have done this for a reason.
I am not gonna spend the rest
of my life tinkling standing up.
Actually, guys don't tinkle, we...
Hey, you guys, will you knock it off?
You're driving me crazy.
Look, either you find the spell
to reverse this
or you find a magical
divorce attorney.
Hey, Sam, how's it going?
Wow, that's quite a handshake,
Piper.
That's because I am Piper
and that's Leo.
Yeah, it's a long story, don't ask.
We'll be upstairs,
we've got a few things to work out.
Gee, you think?
And Paige thought Billie
could help you.
- She's really good...
- Upstairs, mister.
So I'm pretty much caught up here
but I charge 10 bucks an hour
to babysit.
- Babysit?
- Yeah.
That's what I'm doing here,
right?
It's not exactly a demon hunt
but in for a penny, in for a pound, huh?
Okay, look, I need to find Paige.
I need you to look after J.D.
Do not let him out of the house.
If he finds out what year it is,
he'll go crazy.
Okay, fine,
I'll just cast a spell on him.
No, no spells.
He doesn't know anything
about magic, and he can't either.
He's had more than enough magic
used on him already.
Fine, 12 bucks an hour.
When you find Paige,
tell her I've a midterm to study for
and a sister to find.
She owes me big for this.
- This is so ri...
- Hey, baby.
What's shaking?
No charge.
What the hell is taking so long?
Where'd you come from?
- I just got here.
- Yeah, well,
- you wouldn't have if you'd orbed.
- I didn't want to orb.
Which is why I had to.
- J.D.'s awake.
- Who's with him?
Billie. I don't know how long
she'll keep him
from figuring out where he is.
Did he say anything
about what happened?
Not much, just that somebody
took a flash photograph of him.
Nearly blinded him.
Flash photo, huh?
Wasn't one of the last victims seen
with a photographer?
What a cool television.
Where are the ears?
The ears?
Yeah, you know. Antennas.
Oh, the antennas, right.
It doesn't... This thing's
been broken for ages.
Why don't we sit down and chat?
Boss.
Did you just say boss?
Are you from a different country
or something?
- No, why do you ask?
- Because you don't seem to know
much about ours.
Plus, the way you're dressed.
Yeah, okay, let's talk
about something else. So...
- Where are you from, J. D?
- Where's Sam?
Sam, he went out on an errand,
he'll be right back.
Hey, what are you doing?
What, you want one?
No. Hello? Cancer.
What are you talking about?
Oh, jeez.
- What is that?
- This is nothing.
This is just...
It's a new musical device.
My dad's an inventor.
- What's going on around here?
- Wait, J.D., I can explain.
Yeah? I'm listening.
Okay, well, maybe I can't explain,
or at least I'm not allowed to, but...
Look, all I can promise you
is that you're safe here.
Safe from what?
Oh, gee.
Where am I?
J.D., it's okay. No, wait, let me try...
Hold on.
Piper, Leo!
I cannot believe this.
So beautiful.
She was an angel.
I've racked my brain trying
to understand what happened.
Thirty years.
It all feels like yesterday.
I just hope and pray
that she'll come back to me again.
You mentioned in the police report
that you saw a flash of light.
Any idea what that was
or where it came from?
The camera, I assume.
She was having a picture taken
for her mother's birthday.
At a photography studio?
- Yes.
- Do you remember where that was?
It was somewhere over on Knob Hill
but it's not there anymore.
And that's the last you saw of her.
Yes.
What about the photographer?
Anyone ever track him down?
They tried, I tried,
but it's as if he disappeared too.
Your demon, maybe?
Think you can find that studio?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
She wanted to be a teacher.
She had such a good heart,
always helping others.
She sounds like a wonderful girl.
I still miss her.
A father never stops
loving his daughter.
Yeah.
All right, I gotta go, bye.
So it turns out that studio
used to be a few blocks away
from where your friend
was hit by that car.
Which means the demon
might reopen for business.
What, taking pictures?
Stealing lives.
I think we should handle this.
What? Why?
Well, in case you don't remember,
firearms and fireballs don't mix.
Maybe we should call your sisters,
just in case.
I think I can handle
one lousy demon alone, thank you.
But what if you can't?
Oh, what,
are you worried about me?
We should get going.
What am I supposed to do?
Am I dead?
No, but you're gonna be
if we don't get out of here.
Unreal.
J.D., I'm telling you, okay,
we have to go.
We can't...
Did you see that?
It didn't make a sound,
like right out of "Buck Rogers. "
It's a hybrid. It runs on battery.
Battery, why?
Are you kidding?
With gas at three bucks a gallon?
Three bucks?
No way, it's like 25 cents...
Hey, it's okay, it's all right.
They're not gonna hurt you,
it's just a cop.
A cop?
I don't understand.
I know, I know, I'm sorry.
November 6, 2005,
but that's not possible.
Is it?
What else could it be?
Look, I know this is a lot to handle,
okay? I don't know what to tell you.
All I can say is Sam can explain this
to you in a safer place.
- So we should go.
- My dad.
I gotta see my dad.
Hey, watch the face will you, Leo?
I just got a peel.
Would you please just try
to find a spell to change us back?
I know what I'm doing, Piper.
People who know what they're doing
don't cause explosions.
You know, it's one thing
to have my wife
constantly criticize everything I do.
It's another thing when you do it
from my own body.
Well, since I figure
you'd never listen to me,
you might listen to yourself.
No romantic dinners,
no walks on the beach,
there is no way
I can be inseminated.
I tried, I just couldn't do it,
it didn't feel right.
- That's gross.
- No, what's gross
is me pushing the issue
because of some stupid premonitions.
You know? I want love first.
I want what you guys have.
Not today you don't. Trust me.
Why, what's going on?
Talk to your sister.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
Did Wyatt switch you guys again?
No, it was a marriage counsellor.
Actually, it was a gardener,
and it was Leo's fault.
Okay, that's too weird.
Never mind, we'll figure it out.
How's Billie doing downstairs
with J. D?
- There's nobody downstairs.
- What?
Hey, are you all right?
They said that...
...my dad...
...just died.
Oh, God, J.D., I'm so sorry.
They said he was 93 years old.
Ninety-three, how could that be?
He had nobody left.
Not my mom, my brothers.
They said he buried me
50 years ago
even though he never stopped
looking for me.
I mean, how could he bury me?
I'm still alive!
I know, I know. We are gonna
figure this whole thing out.
Listen, look at me.
J.D., listen, you can trust me, right?
You know you can trust me.
I'm gonna tell you something you're
not gonna believe, but you have to.
It's the only way this whole thing
is gonna make any sense to you.
Okay.
What happened 50 years ago to you,
whatever is going on,
Sam is figuring that out.
All I know is, whatever it is,
it has something to do with magic.
- Are you crazy?
- No, I'm not. It's real.
Okay, just like what the demon did
to you, that's real.
And that he's trying to kill you,
this is all very real.
Look, I know this is hard
to handle, okay?
Believe me, I'm new at this myself.
I just found out a week ago
that a demon kidnapped my sister.
Believe me,
I know what you're going through.
At least, I kind of know
what you're going through.
Just don't run away from me,
I can protect you from this.
I promise.
Anything?
No.
Maybe we should take something back
to try and scry for him.
Everything all right?
Can you feel that?
Feel what?
The pain, innocents.
I can sense them, they were here.
Future whitelighters,
that's what he's after.
This could be a trap,
you've gotta get out of here.
No, I'm not a future whitelighter,
I am a whitelighter.
But you're not embracing it.
Otherwise, you'd sense it too.
That makes you vulnerable.
No, that makes me sane.
Look, you've gotta stop
fighting this, Paige.
You gotta stop fighting yourself.
Whether you like it or not,
you are my daughter,
which makes you a whitelighter.
It's about time
you accepted that.
The hell it is.
Look, for your information,
my father, my real father,
the one who raised me, loved me,
and took care of me
until the day he died,
was a firefighter, not a whitelighter.
So how dare you show up here
and act like you're my dad.
Because I have news for you,
you're not.
Paige?
Daughters, they tend
to outlive their fathers.
Grieve longer.
Wait. Don't.
Smile.
Any luck finding J.D. And Billie?
No, because Leo won't let me try.
Because Piper's powers
are still in her body.
But the knowledge
of how to use them isn't.
Oh, yeah?
Wanna see me freeze you?
- Like you even know how.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- What the hell is going on here?
- Well, first of all,
- we're in each other's bodies.
- Well, yes, obviously,
but the question is why.
Stupid gardener.
- He's a soothsayer.
- He's a quack.
Okay, well, whatever it is,
I think he knows exactly
what he's doing.
Come on,
every shrink wants couples
to walk a mile
in each other's shoes, right?
This guy just did it literally.
- Well, it's not working.
- Isn't it?
Look, you've only been
in Piper's body a few hours
and already,
you see what she has to juggle.
You know, being the breadwinner,
a mom, a Charmed One.
- See?
- And you.
You finally get a good understanding
what it feels like to be Leo
and not have any powers,
and to be married to a witch.
He has to do all the legwork
around here,
pick up all the slack,
it's a thankless job.
You guys have forgotten
how great you are together.
Everybody wants what you have.
Trust me, I want what you have.
Don't take it for granted.
She's right.
I know.
We need to find more time
to spend together, Piper.
Just the two of us.
- So we can talk.
- And listen.
- We're back.
- Oh, thank God.
Thank the shrink.
Now hurry up and find Billie.
There's no need for that.
J.D. Needs to talk to Sam.
What do you mean
he knows everything?
I thought Billie was supposed
to wrangle him.
Yeah, I'm here
but I'm not seeing Sam.
Well, just have J.D. Call him,
he's his charge.
All right, all right already.
Criminy.
Sam?
Looking for someone?
Who are you?
Well, not to be defined by my work,
but let's just say,
I like taking pictures.
Tripod.
Tell me where Sam is.
Oh, you love your father
more than you think,
which means
you'll miss him terribly.
You see, I'm an expert in pain.
It's my bread and butter, really.
I feed off it.
- What do you want?
- To keep my collage complete.
When J.D. Escaped,
I was forced to take Sam.
If you want
to see your father alive again,
bring me J.D.
We don't swap innocents,
the demon must know that.
Well, he wasn't after J.D.
He was just a loose end,
someone that got away.
Someone that he wants to finish off.
Well, he's got who he really wants.
- Sam.
- Yeah, thanks to me.
I should have listened to him.
Maybe you didn't want to.
Hey, what's the problem?
If he wants me, let him have me.
Well, the problem is,
he's gonna kill you.
I got away from him before, didn't I?
Yeah, how did you do that?
Something I learned from my dad.
Hey, it works every time.
No, not this time, it's too dangerous.
Well, it doesn't matter, I owe him.
He turned my life around.
I don't know what
I would have done without him.
Why don't we take this up to the attic
and see what Leo's come up with.
We'll be back.
Well, what about Sam?
Oh, they'll figure something out.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Where do you think?
Look, I can't let you...
Hey, you know
I can stop you this time.
Billie, I have to go.
You know, besides,
this isn't my time anymore.
What are you talking about?
Look, everyone I've ever loved,
ever known, is gone now.
I'm not supposed to be here.
- But you are here.
- Yeah, by some strange twist of fate.
My time has passed.
But Sam's still got a family,
he's still got friends.
He can still help people.
But you're here for a reason,
I believe that.
Well, maybe it was to do this.
To do good.
Or maybe it was just to meet you.
J. D...
Promise me something.
You won't waste your whole life
looking for your sister
like my dad wasted his
looking for me.
I don't understand. I don't...
I was lucky to know you, Billie.
Sam?
Sam.
You let Sam go. You got me now.
Still, I need Sam
to complete my collage.
Just like I needed you.
But not anymore.
- If you don't free him, the sisters...
- Will never find me.
Once I've taken care
of my last loose end.
Billie, it's not your fault.
Yes, it is.
I should have stopped him.
If you could have, you would have.
He didn't want you to.
It's just so unfair.
Why would J.D. Come back
after all this time just to die like this?
We can't save every innocent.
We're witches, not gods.
I promised to protect him.
Promises can be tricky.
Sometimes, you just have
to let things happen
in their own time.
In their own way.
Everything happens for a reason.
Paige, you're not gonna find Sam
that way.
Oh, yeah? Watch me.
How do you know
he's even in the city?
You don't know who the demon is.
You're right.
You make a vanquishing potion,
the strongest one we've got.
You know, there is
another way to find Sam.
- Yeah, how?
- Call him.
I already tried that, thanks.
You called for Sam.
I think you need to call
for your father.
He's not my father.
He's not your only father,
but he is still, in fact, your father.
You're connected.
At least as a whitelighter.
Dad?
Paige.
Okay, everybody, let's back up.
We're gonna have some company.
Oh, I don't understand.
How did you free them?
I didn't. She did.
I guess my whitelighter side
is stronger than I thought.
- Smile.
- No!
I think I'll have this one framed.
What about them?
You may as well show up.
I know you're lurking
around here somewhere.
Nothing wrong with those
whitelighter instincts of yours.
Figured you'd wanna talk.
Actually, I wanted to apologize.
For?
For being so hard on you.
- Paige, look, you don't have to...
- Actually...
...I do. I guess I hadn't
realized how much,
you know, it hurt me,
the whole not showing up thing.
I don't blame you.
I should have come by long ago.
But out of deference...
...to your real father's memory, I...
Not exactly sure how I fit in.
Well, I think there's room
for both of you in my life.
Agent Murphy managed to track down
all the innocents' families?
Yes, he did.
I think it's safe to say Mr. Sawyer
got the shock of his life.
It'll be a tough adjustment.
Better late than never.
Yeah, unfortunately, not for J.D.
Oh, I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Might have taken him
an extra 50 years,
but I think he finally managed
to prove himself a future whitelighter
by saving another, you.
See you around?
Definitely.