The world
will have to deal with us.
Previously on The 4400...
You're
the alternative we need
to Collier and his
promicin-pushing radicals.
Does that mean you'll run
for city council?
It means I'm gonna run
and I'm gonna win.
I intend on attacking you
right up until the day of the election.
There are a lot of people out there
that are afraid of what you represent.
I have my eye on something greater
than just city council.
- You hate all the 4400.
- So what if I do?
I have reason to believe
that you're capable of terrible things,
and that you have an evil
living inside of you.
I'm supposed to eliminate
the 4400.
All this talk of a catastrophe
the 4400 are supposed to prevent?
- It's lies.
- So you keep telling me.
Everything in that book
is going to come true.
Collier will lead
the human race to salvation.
You will help him.
I found the guy for the job.
His name's Robert Shaftoe.
Ex-Marine.
Dead-eye sniper.
He did some work
for our...
organization,
out of Kansas City.
If you want someone killed,
until they're completely dead,
then Shaftoe's your man.
Sounds good.
Bring him in.
Are you sure
you wanna go through with this?
Because once I bring Shaftoe
through that door,
there's no going back.
The target...
is a dead man.
- Completely.
- Oh, my God.
Come on, the acting, the dialogue,
this is horrendous.
- Marco, why are we watching this?
- Just, shh...
The best part's coming up.
The assignment is dangerous.
In fact, it might be
the most dangerous assignment
you've ever been assigned.
But if you succeed,
the danger will be worth it.
And the rewards?
They will be worth...
the danger.
Danger is my business.
Consider the target dead.
Completely...
dead.
That's our guy.
That's Curtis Peck.
He's an original recipe 4400.
Correction...
- He's our favorite original recipe.
- Before he disappeared,
Curtis wrote, directed,
and starred in horror movies.
Real low-Budget stuff.
You know,
the sets were mostly in his house.
The actors?
Pretty much
just his friends and family.
Really?
I never would have guessed.
After he came back,
Curtis kept on making movies,
but he shifted genres.
Each one of his movies
is about an unsolved mystery.
He did one about
Jimmy Hoffa's disappearance.
He filmed a costume drama
in his backyard
about the lost colonies at Roanoke.
You just saw his take
on JFK's assassination.
That's great, Marco.
I'm glad this guy has a hobby.
It's not just a hobby.
Some people think that
making these films
- is Curtis's 4400 ability.
- Come on, guys,
you're not telling us
that that movie...
tells us what really happened
to president Kennedy?
There's no way
to know for sure,
but, I mean,
there really is an ex-Marine
named Robert Shaftoe,
and he really was in Dallas
on november 22nd, 1963.
You can't prove Curtis is right,
but you also can't deny
that his theories are compelling.
Some people want to think
everything is a conspiracy,
and I'm sure that this guy
is really appealing to them,
but, Marco,
we've got  a lot of stuff on our plate,
and we just don't have time
to look into something
that might be a 4400 ability.
Don't think I could sit through
another one of those movies.
We didn't ask you down here
to tell you about his ability.
Curtis disappeared.
Nobody can find him.
About 10 days ago,
he stopped posting on his myspace page.
We noticed, so we tried
to get in touch with him.
He's not picking up the phone,
he's not answering emails.
I know, I know,
no big deal, right?
I wasn't really worried
until he missed his last NTAC check-in.
Curtis Peck has dropped off the map.
Somebody should look into it.
- What is this place?
- I don't know,
Cassie just said
we should come here.
I think it's an old bomb shelter.
We should be safe here. It doesn't look
like anyone's been here in years.
I don't understand
why we came to Seattle.
We just led a hundred people
into a city
where everyone's looking for us.
Nobody has a place to stay.
Nobody knows what to do next.
Are you telling me
this is the answer?
- This place is a mess.
- We'll repair it.
Thank you for finding this for us.
You have a truly
extraordinary ability.
Get everyone settled in.
This place is perfect.
We begin here.
How much you wanna bet
we're about to wake up a man
with a crushing  hangover?
Curtis!
Curtis Peck!
You think someone
broke into the place?
Maybe, or else this guy's
as bad at housekeeping
as he is at making movies.
It doesn't look like anything's missing.
All his video equipment is sitting here.
Are you looking for Curtis?
Yes, we are.
We're from NTAC.
- Do you know him?
- Of course.
I'm Neal Handler.
I live around back.
I'm Curtis' neighbor.
And... his collaborator.
I'm proud to say
I've been in more of his movies
than anyone else.
- Yeah, we've... seen your work.
- Thank you.
I haven't seen Curtis in a few days.
Is he all right?
Well, that's what
we're trying to find out.
Do you know
if Curtis had any enemies,
or anyone who might want
to break into his house?
Enemies?
Take your pick.
The CIA, the mafia...
the freemasons.
Curtis exposed
a lot of people.
So you...
you believe his movies are real?
Of course.
That's why
they brought him back
in a ball of light.
To tell the truth
to a reluctant world!
I'll tell you what, though,
if someone did toss this place,
I can guarantee you they didn't find
what they were looking for.
Curtis has...
a secret hiding place.
He keeps his journal in there.
All his script notes.
Could you show it to us?
We just want to help out your friend,
That's all.
We really like his movies, too.
I mean,
we just saw the one on JFK,
and it was... good.
You were really good.
It's here.
Here.
Curtis uses those
for inspiration.
If you're watching this,
then that means I'm in trouble.
Deep trouble.
Don't believe anything you hear
about a car accident or a suicide.
If I'm gone,
it's because they came after me.
I have an idea for a new movie.
It's big.
It's so big,
it's going to change everything
if I get to make it,
and that's
what they're scared of.
That's them.
They're here now.
You need to know,
Jordan Collier...
the 4400... they're not the ones
you should be scared of.
There's something else out there,
something worse,...
it's much worse,
and they're coming for me now.
Season 4 - Episode 06
The Marked
[ Transcript ]
www.ragbear.com
[ Synchro ]
Benj!
aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
...consider the target dead.
Completely dead.
According to Curtis, Jimmy Hoffa
was buried in the Florida everglades.
If you really believe that,
you should read this.
I ran a background check
on Curtis.
He owes money
to credit card companies, the IRS.
He's three years behind
on his alimony payments.
I talked to his ex-wife.
She moved to Wisconsin
just to get away from Curtis.
She hasn't heard from him
in nine months.
Look, if anybody's coming
after this guy, it should be...
creditors, or movie critics.
But he has almost 6 figures
of outstanding debt.
Isn't it possible
he just skipped town?
I don't know.
He looked genuinely scared
at the end of that video we found,
and I don't think Curtis is
a good enough actor to fake that.
Besides...
if making movies is really
his 4400 ability...
aren't you even just
a little bit curious ?
Don't you want to know what's out there
that's bigger than Jordan Collier?
Until we have evidence
that tells me this guy's legit,
all I want to do
is make sure he's okay.
Look at the credits.
Ever since Curtis got back,
his movies have been produced
by a guy called Stuart Henley.
I checked him out.
He's a retired lawyer.
He lives nearby.
Maybe he'd know something
about Curtis' latest movie idea.
It's worth a shot.
At the very least, I'd like to look
into the eyes of the man who put up...
good money to pay for
"I dismembered Jimmy Hoffa."
No, I don't think that
my announcement
that I intend to run for mayor
will mean that
I'll be spending less time
monitoring
Shawn Farrell's candidacy.
If anything,
I think that the mayor's office
would allow me a stronger platform
with which to oppose him...
Mr. Farrell?
- This just came by messenger.
- Thank you.
We're going to be working together
every day. You can call me Shawn.
Hey, Shawn...
it's Kyle.
Where are you?
I've been worried about you.
I'm fine, man.
I'm better than fine, actually.
I'm as good as I've been
in a long time.
Did you get the package?
You sent this?
We did.
Look, it's really important, man.
You need to read the whole thing
before your meeting.
What meeting, Kyle?
Jordan's nearby.
He wants to see you.
You're with Jordan?
What does he want
to see me about?
It's important, okay?
Call me on this number
after you finish the book.
We'll send someone
to come get you.
Mr. Henley?
I can hear a radio
playing inside,
and I swear I heard
someone moving around.
Mr. Henley!
He's back here.
Stuart Henley, wait!
Just wait!
I promise
I won't tell anybody!
- Don't kill me!
- Just relax.
- Nobody's going to kill you.
- We're from NTAC.
We're just trying to locate
Curtis Peck.
You won't find him.
They got to him.
Who are they?
Why'd you run from us?
What are you so scared of?
The people from Curtis' movie...
"The Marked."
That's the name of his movie?
Can you tell us about it?
About a month ago,
he came to me,
said he had an idea
for a new movie,
called "The Marked."
He said it was
his biggest film yet.
I was fascinated,
so I asked him to make me
a short trailer.
I like to see what the movie's about
before I write a check.
He gave me the trailer
about two weeks ago.
Do you still have a copy?
And you're more than welcome
to it, because...
if what Curtis is saying is true,
Then I wish to God
I had never watched it.
This is the world.
Look familiar?
It should,
and it shouldn't.
We all know it changed forever
when the 4400 came back.
Their mission?
They were sent back
by the future
to stop a catastrophe.
But not everyone
from the future
thought they were
a good thing.
There's a faction of elites
who want the future
to stay exactly as it is.
I call them...
The Marked.
10 agents from the future,
inserted into the bodies
of 10 prominent people
from today.
Their bodies and minds
have been hijacked
to pursue the agenda
of the future.
Their goal?
To guide world events...
and to stop the 4400.
The only evidence they exist?
a mark behind
their left earlobe.
The remnant of the procedure
that grafted
a new consciousness
onto their victims.
My movie,
"The Marked",
will tell the chilling tale
of this global conspiracy.
It will name names,
starting with the appearance
of the first marked,
a man named...
Matthew Ross.
Matthew Ross was a lobbyist
with access to Jordan Collier.
After he was marked,
his job was to guide
The Marked's ultimate weapon,
Isabelle Tyler,
into accepting her role
as the agent
of the 4400's destruction.
Isabelle, I told you.
You have to accept your role
as the agent
of the 4400's destruction.
But everything did not go
according to plan.
I don't think so, Matthew.
Today's graduation day,
and you're...
my diploma.
But The Marked do not accept
defeat lying down.
They continue to plan.
They have their greedy fingers
on the marionette strings
of the world,
and we, their puppets,
don't even know it.
The group gathered
for the first time
at the behest of Drew Imroth.
That's right.
The CEO of the biggest
software company in the world
is one of The Marked.
I know it's dangerous for us all
to meet like this,
but the information I have
is important...
Very, very important.
It better be important,
Mr. Imroth.
It's easter.
Do you know how hard it is
to get away from the vatican
at easter?
Take it down a notch,
your eminence.
I have big news.
Jordan collier is back,
and we need to stop him...
completely stop him.
"The Marked."
A direct market thriller
available in all territories
in 2008.
I am so buying that movie.
So either that's
the ramblings of a madman,
or Curtis Peck has just exposed
the biggest conspiracy of all time.
According to that movie,
Matthew Ross was one of these guys,
The Marked,
and Isabelle Tyler killed him.
And we always wondered
if that were true.
What about Imroth?
I mean, the CEO
of Ubient Software
is supposed to be some kind
of double agent from the future?
Everyone always says that company
is trying to take over the world.
Now we know it's true.
The only thing we know for sure
is that Curtis Peck is a horrible,
horrible film-maker.
Though, I do have to admit,
there are a bunch of questions
I'd like to ask him.
But since he's in the wind, I guess
we'll have to settle for his producer.
Get Stuart Henley in here.
Mr. Henley,
it's Diana Skouris from NTAC.
We need to talk.
Can you open up?
It smells like exhaust.
Stand back.
No big surprises
in the coroner's preliminary reports,
Stuart Henley died
of carbon monoxide poisoning.
There's no suicide note,
but there's no sign of foul play either.
So...
do you really think
he committed suicide?
Henley was an odd guy.
I mean, He'd have to be to pay
for Curtis' movies,
so I guess it's possible.
But I don't know,
the timing seems off.
Why would he commit suicide
right after NTAC
got in touch with him?
So, what then?
Executed by the marked?
I'm not ready to go there yet.
Yeah, me neither.
But I...
I got a lot of questions.
You know Drew Imroth
is in that movie.
Ubient's based in Seattle. Maybe we can
get in and see him tomorrow morning.
And ask him what exactly?
Oh, I got it,
"Excuse me.
"When you're not running the biggest
computer company in the world,
"are you by any chance involved in
an enormous...
"intercontinental conspiracy?"
Maybe.
Or maybe we could just ask him
whether
Curtis Peck ever tried
to get in touch with him.
Sounds good.
I'll see tomorrow.
- What, you're not going home?
- No, not for a while.
Meghan asked me to put all this
in an email.
I told her I'd get it off
to her tonight.
- Want a hand?
- No, I got it. Go ahead.
Spend a little time with your daughter
while she's still awake.
- Thanks.
- Good night.
We appreciate you taking
the time to meet with us, Mr. Imroth.
It's really not a problem.
I'm a huge supporter of NTAC.
You guys have tough jobs.
Please,have a seat.
I only wish I could be
more helpful.
I've never heard of this guy.
You said his name was
Curtis Peck ?
Yeah, that's right. He's a...
He's a 4400 who...
who makes movies,
and you,
well, you're a character
in his latest film.
Really?
Who plays me?
I always hoped
it would be Jeff Goldblum.
It's more of a low-budget
kind of thing.
What's it about?
Well, it's interesting.
It's creative.
It's a global conspiracy
in which agents from the future
have taken over
the bodies of...
prominent people
from all around the world.
I have to say,
I'm the subject of
a lot of conspiracy theories,
but that's the most innovative
one I've heard yet.
So, are you here to ask me
if it's true?
Because you have to figure
I wouldn't tell you even if it was.
No, actually, we came to see you
because Curtis Peck has gone missing.
There's a chance one of his
investors may have been murdered.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Should I be worried for
my own safety?
No, we don't think so,
but if Curtis should try
and get in touch with you,
or if anyone should ask you
about a movie called
"The Marked",
could you get in touch
with us?
- Absolutely.
- Thank you.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
Actually...
This may seem like
a really strange request.
Do you think we could take a look
behind your left earlobe?
Let me guess,
this has something to do
with that movie.
Have at it.
Has that mole
always been there?
Ever since I was born.
My dermatologist tells me
I have to keep an eye on it.
So give it to me straight.
Does this mean I'm one of the...
What was the name
of that movie?
"The Marked?"
Kyle, what's with all
the spy game stuff here?
Am I really this far outside
of the Collier circle of trust?
It's just a precaution.
I need you to promise me that
you're not going to freak out, okay?
I would just like
to take this thing off, please.
Hi, Shawn.
- What the hell is she doing here?
- She's with us. It's okay.
She just wanted to talk to you
before you saw Jordan.
I'm glad you're awake...
and I'm sorry.
For everything.
I know I was wrong,
and I know
what we had wasn't love.
Yeah, you're right, it wasn't.
I don't expect you
to forgive me...
Ever...
But I just needed you
to hear it.
Well,
there's no one so far gone
they can't find their way
back to the movement.
Even if I told the world that you
were wrong to hand out promicin?
I wasn't surprised
they had you speak against me.
Politics is compromise.
That's why
I never pursued it myself.
I understand that you are
wanting to build a bridge
between positives
and the rest of the world,
but, Shawn, I'm telling you,
events are moving past that.
We have big plans here,
and when we're finished,
the 4400 won't need the mainstream.
The mainstream will come to us.
Is that what your book told you?
I've read it.
Frankly, it scares me.
Are you saying that you're gonna
bring God to the world?
If the word "God" frightens you,
substitute "paradise".
We're gonna make it happen, Shawn.
You should be here with us.
Yes, but who's
in charge of paradise?
How many martyrs
will it take to create it?
Jordan, you've done
great things for the 4400.
You have done great things
for me, but...
you are on the wrong path here.
And you have always been rebellious.
But I think you're afraid
of change, Shawn,
or it is just me?
I'm against anyone
who wants to accumulate power
that won't tell me exactly
what they wanna do with it.
Not just you, anyone.
There's a man by the name
of Gabriel Hewitt.
He's running for mayor.
He's dangerous.
Maia Skouris
saw him in a vision.
He's in charge
of prison camps,
and they're
rounding up 4400s.
Even if I wanted to
drop out of the race,
even if I wanted to join you,
I can't,
because I have to stop him.
Well, it sounds like you have
your hands full already.
Good luck
in your political career.
I'm sorry.
I don't know, but that birthmark
behind Imroth's ear?
It was definitely
shaped like an "x".
Exactly like the ones
in Curtis' movies.
It was weird, yes,
but it could be
a coincidence.
We're looking for
a paranoid 4400.
That doesn't mean we have to
become paranoid ourselves.
This man is here to see you.
My name's Walt Saperstein.
I'm a psychiatrist
at Feeney Memorial.
I have instructions
to bring you to the hospital.
You're being placed under
a 72-hour psychiatric hold.
What? Why?
You sent an email last night.
It alleged some of the most
powerful people in the world
are united
in some kind of conspiracy.
No, it didn't allege anything.
It's a summary of our work
on a case.
Well, nevertheless,
someone in Washington read it.
They've reviewed your files,
agent Baldwin. They're worried
- you've had a psychotic break.
- Shut up.
You sent my email on to D.C.?
I do that every time
we open a case. I'm sorry.
I never would've done it
if I knew this was gonna happen.
Get your hands off me!
It's only going to
get worse for you
if you put up a fight.
It's only temporary.
You need to go with them. We'll do
everything we can to end this quickly.
Fine.
Well, I don't understand.
What do you mean that no one
can get in to see him?
Well, how long is Tom
going to be in isolation?
Okay, forget it.
I'll call back in the morning.
Don't move.
What are you doing down here?
Don't shoot me.
I'm the one
you're looking for.
Curtis?
You're alive.
I am.
If you can keep me that way,
I'll tell you
all about The Marked.
So how did you find me?
I've been in hiding ever since
I made that movie trailer.
I knew they'd be coming for me.
My buddy, Neal,
sent me an email
after you and your partner
came by my house.
He thought I could trust you.
What can you tell me
about these people?
Well, not everything.
I haven't finished
writing the script.
That's how
my ability works.
Ideas just jump into
my head while I'm writing,
but I don't know the whole story
until I write the end.
Let's see,
they don't have abilities.
The procedure
doesn't work that way.
I do know that all 10 of them
had a meeting in 2005.
That was the only time
they were all together.
It was in Tunis.
That's a city in North Africa.
No other names
other than Drew Imroth?
Not yet.
That's why I came to you.
I need a safe place
where I can write.
You're a fan of my movies.
Cool.
Yeah, I've seen them all.
Uh, it's a pleasure
to have you here.
Yeah, you can work right there
if you want.
Thank you so much, Marco.
I really appreciate this.
We were careful on the way
over here. We weren't followed.
It's okay.
I'll keep him working.
It's been a while since you've seen
the inside of my place, huh?
We should make
a pot of coffee.
Do you mind staying up with me?
I like to have somebody I can...
bounce ideas off.
Coffee.
Hey, Joanna, I'm going to need you
to juggle around
a couple of my healing
appointments for today.
What is it?
Gabriel Hewitt
had a stroke last night.
- What?
- It's bad.
I guess he has brain damage.
They're saying he's going to
have to resign his seat
on the city council,
and withdraw
from the race for mayor.
I just got off the phone
with the hospital.
Tom is fine.
If I keep the pressure on,
there's a chance
they may end his psych hold
a day early.
- What are you working on?
- You want me to tell you,
or should I just
put it an email?
That's not fair.
I had nothing to do with
what happened to Tom.
If I could've stopped it,
I would've.
Tom's psych hold had nothing
to do with his state of mind.
We were getting close to something,
and they sent us a warning.
Who? The people from
Curtis' movie, The Marked?
Well, I can't prove that,
but I do know that Drew Imroth
was in Tunisia of June, 2005.
If The Marked ever gathered,
that's when it happened.
At the same time,
Wesley Burke was also there.
The political advisor
to the president?
What was he doing in Africa
while the White House
was gearing up
for mid-term elections?
I don't know,
but he had company.
That's cardinal Emmanuel Calabria.
Rumor is, he finished third
in the last papal election.
This is all interesting,
but Drew Imroth heads up
the world's largest
charitable foundation.
He travels to Africa
all the time,
and these other guys,
well...
Who knows why they were there.
Well, I'm going to find out,
And I'm also gonna learn
who else was there
to play that week.
Let me know if I can help.
The Marked have no way of
getting in contact with the future.
It's a one-way ticket.
They're cut off here.
Okay, Curtis,
that's very interesting,
but there are
no new names here.
We need some facts
and things that we can verify.
They'll come.
I'm on a roll.
Tom, are you okay?
They did something to me, Diana.
They changed me.
Whoa, just take it easy.
Where are you?
The hospital.
They just let me out.
Can you come and get me?
Are you sure
it wasn't there before?
I'm positive.
They did something to me
last night, Diana.
Those people who came into my room,
They were dressed
for an operation.
They put something into me.
What? Like another person?
Another consciousness?
Hey, Tom, I don't think
it works that way.
Curtis is working on
his script right now,
and according to him, The Marked
are cut off from the future.
They can't just
make more of them.
Yeah, but one of them's dead.
Matthew Ross.
What if they took whatever was
inside of him and put it into me?
No, you can't be sure of that.
Tom, just...
please just tell me
that you're still you.
I think so.
I mean, for now, anyway.
It's crap.
I can't get this scene right.
they're at the meeting
in Tunisia.
They're face to face
for the first time.
Imroth is introducing them
to each other.
I know what the scene is.
I just can't...
- nail it.
- Look...
I have to think creatively
for my job, too.
I mean, I share an office
with two of the most
annoying guys on the planet.
Believe me,
I get stuck all the time.
Know what I do?
I shut my eyes,
and I think of song lyrics.
Sounds dumb, right?
But I swear,
it almost always works.
What are you thinking of?
"The trooper", Iron Maiden.
Hey, whatever gets you going.
Be right back.
Did you do this?
Did you order
one of your followers
to give Hewitt a stroke?
Have we grown that far apart?
You actually believe
I'm capable of that?
Jordan, I don't know what
you're capable of anymore.
All I know I that two days ago
I came in here ad I told you
that Hewitt as dangerous.
Now he has brain damage
and he probably
won't have a career.
Then it looks like
fate intervened on our behalf.
You're not answering my question.
Because I find it offensive!
You're the one who's always
saying that we're at war.
Why wouldn't Hewitt just
be another casualty to you?
Just like all those people
that died taking your shot?
Those people made a choice.
They knew the risks.
I knew the risks.
I did not order anyone
to attack Gabriel Hewitt.
I don't believe you.
I can't begin to tell you
how disappointing that is.
Well, it's true.
That's why
I can't follow you anymore.
Did you see the license plate
on the car that took him away?
I'm sorry.
What do we do now?
We need to tell Meghan,
bring the whole building into this,
hope we find Curtis
before the worst happens.
They just told me
you were released.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Pretty much.
We were coming to see you. We need
to talk to you about Curtis Peck.
He came to me for protection
a couple of nights ago.
We tried to keep him safe,
but we lost him.
We think The Marked took him.
Guys, Curtis Peck is
in the building.
He came in about an hour ago.
He went straight down
to NTAC medical for his checkup.
Sorry I had to rush out.
I know this is going to
sound weird,
but I got a call from this...
from this big movie producer
who's in town.
He's a big fan of my work.
He offered me a deal to direct
a big Hollywood movie.
Don Incubus, demon P.I.
It's a comic book adaptation.
It's perfect for me.
I'm in business, guys.
This is what I always wanted!
But, Curtis,
what about the conspiracy?
- What about The Marked?
- You were almost done.
You were just about to
tell us all the names.
The names?
Well, there are no names.
Not really.
I made the whole thing up.
I'm putting that project on the shelf.
I couldn't finish it.
What, they got to you.
they bought you off, huh?
You really believed that stuff,
didn't you?
Look, I'm flattered,
but you need to calm down.
There's no such thing
as The Marked.
Just like Robert Shaftoe
didn't shoot JFK.
They're just movies.
So... I'm sorry I missed my checkups.
It won't happen again.
Can I leave now?
I gotta pack.
I'm going to Hollywood.
There's nothing unusual there.
I spent all afternoon
in NTAC medical,
and as far as they could tell,
there's nothing different with me.
Well, that's good, Tom.
It's all a mind game.
They just want us to back off.
Well, it's not going to work.
We're gonna find out
the truth about these people
with or without Curtis Peck.
Excuse me, agent Baldwin?
agent Skouris?
Sorry for the surprise.
I asked my driver to make a detour.
I can't get that crazy movie
idea out of my head.
What was it called,
The Marked?
You know damn well
what it was called.
I guess I do.
I keep thinking
what it would be like
to actually be
one of those guys.
Imagine if you were
stuck in the past,
just cut off from your friends
and your family.
That'd be quite a sacrifice,
wouldn't it?
They sound kind of like
heroes to me.
Well,
heroes don't have people killed,
They don't consume the personalities
of innocent men and women.
I don't know exactly
what The Marked are up to.
I haven't seen the movie.
You never will now.
No one will.
Maybe it's better that way.
Seems to me their work would be
best done in secret.
If they are out there,
I would think
people like you
would consider them,
I don't know, allies?
After all, they'd have
the same goal as you, right?
To stop Jordan Collier's
global revolution,
and all the chaos
and unrest that it could bring.
I'd just think of them
as back-up.
Valuable back-up.
If...
- they exist.
- That's right.
If they exist.
Anyway, it was good
to see you two again.
I have to pick up my wife.
We're being honored
at the world
health organization tonight.
Those look like x-rays.
is everything okay with you?
It didn't work.
Whatever you tried to do to me,
it didn't take.
I'm still me.
Of course you're you.
We're all ourselves, aren't we?
I mean, who else would we be?
He made you doubt me,
didn't he?
Your cousin,
he made you doubt me.
It's just weird timing,
Hewitt's stroke.
If you have something you want to
ask me, Kyle, I'll answer honestly.
Was this you?
Did you have this done?
I did not.
I believe you.
I'm sorry Shawn didn't.
I'm sorry, too.
Shawn was like a son to me,
and I've lost him.
But I've found you.
Thank you.
Don't thank me, just change.
I think we can rest easy.
It's all going to be fine.
Tell the others that I went to see
the NTAC agents.
Baldwin thinks
it's some kind of ploy,
a mind game...
When we need him,
he will be there for us.
[ www.seriessub.com ]
v1.00