SeriesSub presents...
The world
will have to deal with us.
Previously on The 4400...
I'm putting together profiles
of the people...
who've taken the shot.
Pretty soon, Kevin thinks
he'll be able to predict
who will survive the shot
and who won't.
Are you really asking me
to tell people not to take promicin?
Only for a few months.
I am not making
any announcement.
Who are you?
I'm Lindsey.
This is Maia Rutledge.
She was the first one to disappear
as far as we can tell.
They're dead, aren't they?
There's a faction of elites
who want the future
to stay exactly as it is.
I call them "The Marked."
What about Imroth?
The CEO of Ubient software's
supposed to be some kind of
double agent from the future?
Tell the others
I went to see the NTAC agents.
Baldwin thinks
it's some kind of ploy.
When we need him,
he'll be there for us.
You're becoming
your new self.
Do what Tom Baldwin would do.
Find Isabelle Tyler.
You...
have to take
your abilities back.
Then you're going to bring
Jordan Collier to me.
Tom, what's going on?
I felt restless.
I kept tossing and turning,
I didn't want to wake you.
So you were just...
- sitting here?
- No. I was watching you sleep.
It's kind of relaxing.
Well, I'm awake now.
So... why don't you
come back to bed?
There.
Isn't this more relaxing?
Andaluca's?
Isn't that
a little bit fancy?
So?
I'm not a little kid anymore.
I just miss the days
when the only place you'd eat was...
Charlie's pizza palace.
Mom, that was, like...
a long time ago.
Oh, yeah,
at least a year.
Besides, it'd be fun
eating spanish food with Ben again.
I hope you're not
getting your hopes up for nothing.
I know that Ben said
that he might make it, but...
London is a long way off.
I promise
I won't be disappointed.
On my birthday,
it's just been...
I don't know,
just you and me,
and with Ben,
it would feel more like family.
Excuse me!
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- What's that?
Is this real money?
Certainly looks like it.
"These little green
scraps of paper
you're fighting over
are worthless."
"Welcome to
the new world."
"The new world". That's right out of
Jordan Collier's playbook.
It sounds like it,
but can we be really sure
that these ATM malfunctions
are being caused by some 4400 ability?
Because it could be the work
of some sophisticated
computer hacker who's just...
looking to create some havoc.
Actually, I have to go with
a p-positive here, Diana.
So far, 58 ATMs from four separate
banking institutions have been affected.
That means four separate computer
mainframes have been compromised.
Thousands of dollars
are being randomly dispensed.
Every time they shut down an ATM,
another one goes haywire.
I'd like to meet the computer hacker
that can pull that off,
you know, without an ability.
Pretty aggressive move, though,
I mean, even for Collier.
If you want to create a new world,
first, you have to destroy the old one,
and disrupting the economy's
a pretty good way to start.
I wouldn't mind driving.
- Does that work for you?
- Be my guest.
I'm gonna need an hour or two
before we go see Collier.
- Is there something wrong?
- Hopefully not.
I've got an appointment
for a cat-scan.
It's just a precaution.
Ever since the mole came back,
I've been a little on edge.
- You don't feel any different, do you?
- You mean, am I one of the marked?
Some kind of zombie
controlled by a future human?
Not... not yet, anyway.
I'll call you
when I'm done with the hospital.
Are you sure you won't
reconsider, Mr. Chatha?
Taking the shot
would be...
hugely beneficial,
not only to you,
but to the millions of your readers
who would follow your example.
Yes, but you have to
understand that...
there is no guarantee that
this alleged compatibility test
of Shawn Farrell's
will ever be perfected.
Yes, well,
if you change your mind,
the door's always open.
We have your cousin
to thank for that.
Maneck Chatha's name is on the list
in the white light book.
We already know
he can survive the shot.
It's his followers
he's worried about.
Why risk their lives
when Shawn's announced
it's only a matter of time
before the test is available?
Too bad you lost Chatha.
It wouldn't have happened
if you'd done what I told you to.
Yeah, I know.
Stop Shawn, right?
What does that mean exactly?
I was hoping
you'd figure that out for yourself.
Shawn's not developing
this test by himself.
What you need to do
is get rid of Kevin  Burkhoff.
Get rid of him?
What am I supposed to do exactly,
kill the guy?
I expect you to do whatever it takes
to fulfill the prophecy
and help Jordan Collier
bring heaven to earth.
Good morning, Isabelle.
I hope you're feeling at home.
You know, I have to say...
of all of our real estate holdings,
this place is my favorite.
I thought you'd like to know,
tomorrow, your father's being moved
from Seattle
to an NTAC holding facility in Virginia.
Which means you need to agree
to take your abilities back
before Richard steps on that plane,
because if you don't,
he's not getting off it.
You already caused
your mother's death.
Do you want to be responsible
for your father's, too?
Even if I agreed to take the shot,
what's the point?
The government doctors already told me
that promicin will kill me.
We can change that, Isabelle.
I guarantee you'll live
to fulfill your original mission...
To destroy the 4400, and anyone else
with trace of promicin in their system.
And you will start
by bringing us Jordan Collier.
You know, Kyle used to
talk about you all the time.
He said
you were a decent man,
but then you're not Tom Baldwin,
are you?
Tom Baldwin was a confused
and unhappy man.
I've given him the clarity of purpose
he desperately needed,
and I want to give that
to you, Isabelle.
After all, I created you...
Placed you in your mother's womb
to make sure you were sent back
in that ball of light,
so you could protect the world
from the 4400.
Promicin is evil.
People who use it are evil.
Their goal isn't to change the world,
it is to end it.
You can stop them.
You have to stop them.
It's what you're meant to do.
How can you say no
to your destiny?
Season 4 - Episode 11
Ghost In The Machine
[ Transcript ]
www.ydy.com
[ Synchro ]
Benj!
aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
Manual labor
in Promise City?
Isn't that
a bit old school?
Nothing wrong with old school,
when it comes to a little...
sweat and muscle.
Having an ability can
lead to complacency,
and complacency...
is the measure
of a dying society.
Welcome to the new world.
You're here about the attacks
on the banking system.
- You know about that?
- I try to stay current,
but I can assure you
that despite the attacker's...
utopian signature,
nobody here had anything to do with it.
Can you really be sure of that?
You must have, like, 500 people
living here by now.
Nobody here would do something like that
without Jordan's consent.
Which I didn't give.
Well, just proove it to us.
Let us talk to your people,
and if...
nobody did it, maybe they can
help us find out
- who the hell is responsible.
- I'm afraid I can't do that.
You mean you won't.
I mean... Whoever's doing this
has my best wishes.
The system you live in
is obsolete.
Any society that worships
at the altar of wealth is doomed,
so why not flood
the streets with money...
All those little pieces of paper
are as worthless as confetti.
Christ, Tom, no!
Dad, don't.
Please don't...
Please don't, dad.
Because the future
I believe in,
is one that exists
without the need for money.
It's a world where miracles
are common currency.
Now, excuse me,
I have some work to do.
It's not just ATMs anymore.
We're looking at computer system
failures all over the country.
Make that the world.
Federal agencies,
financial institutions,
private businesses...
Even your friendly neighborhood laptops
are all crashing,
victims of the same corrosive virus
that infected the ATMs.
And these attacks
are anything but random.
Every malfunctioning computer,
including the original ATMs
has one thing in common.
They all run Ubient's
Enzyme operating system.
Ubient?
That's Drew Imroth's company.
So, I guess the question
we have to ask is this...
Are these attacks against...
Drew Imroth,
the multi-billionaire corporate giant?
Or Drew Imroth...
the alleged member of the global
conspiracy known as The Marked?
The operative word
is "alleged."
We don't even have any hard evidence
that The Marked exist.
Tom and I are pretty certain.
Yeah, that's right.
But even so, Ubient is one of
the biggest corporations in the world.
If it goes under,
we're all in trouble.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
No...
Everybody, this is Abigail Hunnicutt.
She's new.
We were lucky
to grab her.
Abigail's been teaching a course
in combinatorics and probability
at M.I.T. since she was 22.
I also worked my way
through graduate school
in the men's department
at Sak's. So...
Who knows?
Maybe I can...
teach these guys
how to dress like grown-ups.
I thought
everyone should see this.
It's some kind of manifesto.
Every computer
infected with the virus
is printing it out.
It's calling for the destruction
of all Ubient software.
Which is why, marked or not,
we need to speak with Drew Imroth.
Hello?
Hey, Maia.
It's me Lindsey.
- Happy birthday.
- Hi. I can't believe you remembered.
You know, it's not
for another two days.
Whatever.
I have got the coolest gift for you.
- You want to come over?
- It's not that kind of present.
You have to come to Promise City
and see it for yourself.
My mom really wants me
to stay away from there.
She doesn't have to know.
You are so going to thank me for this.
I guess I can come by
tomorrow after school.
Great. Meet me at the southwest corner
of Beacon and 64th street at 3:30.
I've got some friends here
who will help us sneak past
the government blockade.
Okay, bye.
Yes, Mr. Secretary,
I understand how sensitive
your department records are.
I promise that once we get
the problem resolved,
Ubient will do everything possible
to retrieve your lost data.
Believe me, sir,
I feel your pain.
I'm a stockholder, too.
I warned you
that something like this
was going to happen.
Jordan Collier and his followers
are bent on global revolution,
and this assault on my company
is the opening salvo.
We just came from Promise City.
Collier's denying any involvement.
I don't believe that,
and I certainly hope
you two don't either!
Whether it's Collier's people
or some rogue p-positive,
it doesn't really matter,
we'll find him.
When will that be?
Will I still have
a company left by then?
We're doing our best.
All of this could
have been avoided
if you people had done your jobs
in the first place.
But, no, you were too busy
chasing after imaginary conspiracies.
How about it, agent Baldwin?
Would you like to check
my mole again?
That won't be necessary.
Glad to see you finally have
your priorities straight.
I just hope it's not too late
to save my company.
With all your success over the years,
you must've made your share of enemies.
Thousands of them.
In fact, I keep a list...
of everyone who's ever sent me
a threatening letter or email.
Organized by level
of vehemence.
It's a hobby.
Is Steve Jobs
on page one?
You might want to give him
a promicin test.
Dr. Burkhoff,
you ready for a break?
Not now.
I lost quite a bit of data
when this computer crashed.
Right, that's that Ubient virus.
The net's down in the entire building.
Is that supposed to
make me feel better?
I have to reconstruct
a 74-page document from memory,
and I'm on, like, what...
Page 12?
I appreciate
your dedication,
but I kinda promised Tess I'd get you
out of the lab once in a while.
- You spoke to Tess?
- Yeah, just now.
Sounds like she's having
a great time with her niece.
Grand-niece, actually.
Tess was born in 1937.
Right, sorry.
I forgot.
You need a break.
I got a surprise for you.
Come on, it's a massage.
- She's waiting upstairs.
- No, thank you.
I don't like strangers
touching me.
The human hand can be so...
clammy.
Okay, but I already paid
for the hour.
Well, be my guest.
Enjoy yourself.
I'll just be down here,
working to save
thousands of lives
and change the world
for the better.
Thank you.
You know...
Imroth was not joking
when he said he had a lot of enemies.
This is going to take all night
to get through this.
- I think I'm gonna take my half home.
- That's a good idea.
You really surprised me today
at Imroth's office.
The way you reacted
when he got in your face.
The guy was having a rough day.
I was trying to be diplomatic.
I mean, considering
what we suspect him of.
Because he brought up the Marked,
and you didn't even...
well, pursue it.
Neither did you.
It's not like he was
going to admit to anything.
I promise, the next time
he gives us some attitude,
you'll see
some fireworks, okay?
Good night.
Did you...
get the results
of the cat-scan?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thanks for asking.
- Good night.
- Hello?
- Hello.
Hi, Kevin.
I'm back.
Out here.
See me?
Come find me.
I thought you weren't
coming back for a few days.
Kevin, I'm over here.
Where are you?
You found me.
I brought your breakfast.
Come on.
Orders are you're supposed to eat.
Let her go!
We're not supposed
to hurt her.
Morning, Diana.
Read any good
death threats lately?
Too many.
So, what do we got,
like, 8 000 suspects?
Good luck
tracking them all down.
So how was your night?
It was kind of strange.
I was on my way home
when I got a phone call
from Drew Imroth.
Yeah, I know,
it threw me, too.
Anyway, he told me
he had to see me right away,
alone at Madison park.
It all felt a little...
cloak and dagger,
but what was I gonna do?
- I guess you had to go.
- Exactly.
Turns out, he wants me
to pass the case off to another agent.
He's worried that I'm still obsessed
about proving he's one of the Marked.
What did you tell him?
The truth. That he had
nothing to worry about.
That I'd do my job
to the best of my abilities.
Then I asked him to name
every member of the marked,
which led to some of the fireworks
you were hoping for.
I better take this.
I'll see you in there.
Baldwin...
When?
Is Isabelle all right?
Fine. I'll have
to make an excuse here.
I'll be right over.
What happened?
Where's kevin?
I don't know. The cleaning
staff came in this morning.
This is how they found the place.
All his work is missing, too.
This was Jordan.
It had to be.
He knows about the compatibility test.
It's so strange.
All those people willing to risk
their lives to get an ability.
Thinking it'll make them
feel less alone,
more powerful.
I never felt more alone
and less powerful
than when I had
limitless abilities.
It overwhelmed my entire life.
Became my identity,
cut me off from everyone...
My parents...
Shawn...
It's only when I lost everything
that I found myself,
and now you want me
to go back there,
- become that person again.
- That person is who you are.
It won't be that bad, Isabelle.
These past few months,
you got a little vacation,
you spent a little time
out in the world,
but now it's time
to go back to work.
It was nice to be normal...
At least for a little while.
Okay,
so this is a modification
of a document authorization program
Abigail designed
while she was at M.I.T.
We used it to cross-reference
the language
in the anti-Ubient manifesto
with the hate mail
directed at Drew Imroth.
We were looking for
idiosyncratic phrases
and word choices
with a high degree of similarity
in both documents.
Now, you can see
whoever wrote the manifesto
likes to use semi-colons
by the handful.
He's also fond of "who" or "which"
instead of "that",
and he refers to Imroth
as "Mr. Puppetmaster",
a phrase he repeats
a total of 6 times.
And... what do we find
in the hate mail department?
This document.
Semi-colons.
"Who" and "which" used again
instead of "that",
and finally, our old friend,
"Mr. Puppetmaster".
So the two authors
are one and the same.
Do you have a name for us?
This e-mail is signed "Swindled".
Imroth put his people on it.
They traced it
to a Warren Trask.
Turns out,
back in the early '80s,
Trask designed
a primitive version
of the Enzyme operating system.
When Imroth came out with
a very similar program,
- Trask sued.
- Let me guess. He lost.
No, no, it never
went to court.
Imroth offered Trask
an out-of-court settlement.
Trask wound up with $100,000.
Meanwhile,
Enzyme has made Imroth billions.
- So the guy's pissed.
- Wouldn't you be?
You can ask him yourself.
He lives right here in seattle.
Well, nice work, Marco.
Actually, it was all Abigail.
She buy you that suit, too?
Stop looking so freaked out.
We're almost there.
I told you I can't stay long.
- If my mom finds out...
- She won't.
I promised you
a birthday surprise, right?
Well, here it is.
Mom?
Dad?
Maia, is it really you?
Vic, can you believe
how big she's gotten?
She's still
my little girl.
I only wish I could give you
a great, big birthday hug.
Me too.
But you can't.
You're just somebody's
4400 ability.
Whatever we are,
we're your parents,
and we love you so much.
Excuse me.
I'm agent Baldwin,
this is agent Skouris. We're with NTAC.
We're here to see
Warren Trask.
I'm his daughter, Eileen.
- What's this all about?
- We'd like to ask your father
some questions
about Drew Imroth.
Well, you can ask him
anything you want.
Just don't expect any answers.
My dad had a stroke
three months ago.
He hasn't moved a muscle
nor said a word since.
My father was a brilliant man,
but he was naive and trusting,
and Drew Imroth
took advantage of that
to cheat my father
out of his life's work.
His career, his marriage,
his... health.
My father lost it all.
So when did he take
the promicin shot?
About six months ago.
As far as I know,
it didn't do anything,
no ability, nothing, and then
he had the aneurysm.
Do you really still believe
he's behind
what's happening to Ubient?
All these machines
he's hooked up to,
they're run by computer,
so he's connected to networks
for emergency response
monitoring.
If his mind is still functioning and
he's got an ability, then, yeah...
he could be
the ghost in the machine.
Well, that would be...
wonderful.
Daddy,
if that's true,
I am so happy for you.
Don't stop until you ruin Imroth
like he ruined you.
That's enough of that.
- You're hurting me.
- Tom, let her go.
She's an accessory
to a half-dozen felonies.
If there is anything you are holding
back, you'd better tell us now.
I don't know anything,
but if my father
is bringing down Drew Imroth,
I'd consider that justice.
Am I mistaken, or am I looking
at a xerces blue butterfly?
I believe
that's what it's called.
The xerces blue
has been extinct since 1941.
Not here.
Not anymore.
We have a resident
who can modify DNA
to recreate
extinct species.
Only insects so far, but he hopes
to work his way up to mammals.
I don't know about you, but I'd love
to see a woolly mammoth in the flesh.
I'm impressed...
And I'm not easily impressed.
A man of your intelect
could do just about anything
here in promise city.
Which might be
a more persuasive argument
if I weren't a kidnap victim
being held against my will.
It was my idea to bring you here.
Jordan knew nothing about it.
Is that supposed to make
everything all right?
Kyle's method
might have been extreme,
but I can't fault his motive,
you belong here...
in Promise City,
with us, Kevin.
You are the father
of the promicin movement.
Without your discoveries,
Promise City wouldn't even exist.
I made
a scientific breakthrough...
But I didn't start
a religious cult.
Kevin, like it or not,
you're revered by everyone here.
However, I cannot allow
your research to continue.
A promicin compatibility test
would be death to this movement.
All I'm trying to do
is save lives, Jordan.
So are we.
We're just thinking
a little more long-term.
So...
Until you share our vision,
I'm afraid I'll have to insist
you remain our guest.
Tomorrow at 8:00 A.M.? I was kind
of hoping for something sooner.
No, no, we can't prove conclusively
that Trask's our man,
but we know he took
the promicin shot.
Okay, if that's
the best you can do.
Okay, thanks.
We can't get a court order to move
Trask to NTAC medical till morning.
But Ubient is hemmoraging
millions of dollars an hour.
The stock market is down
over 500 points,
I don't know about you, but my
pension plan is pretty much history.
We've done all we can
to isolate him.
We've cut off the phone services
and internet to his home.
We don't even know if he needs
a phone line to access the net.
We need to get Trask
on the inhibitor,
- and we need to do it now.
- It's not an option.
His doctors have ruled it out.
Given the state of his health,
it's way too risky.
Well, maybe
it's worth the risk.
Just keeping Trask
under wraps at NTAC
is no guarantee that the attacks
against Ubient will stop.
What are you suggesting, Tom,
we kill him?
Of course not!
It's just... Look,
it's just frustrating, for all of us.
Anyhow, I guess there's nothing
we can do till morning.
Hey, birthday girl, I'm home!
Why aren't you dressed yet?
The dinner reservation's for 7:00.
I'll be ready in time.
Then we come home
and open the presents, all right?
That'll be good.
What's wrong?
Did something happen today?
I told you not to get
your hopes up about Ben.
I told you, I'm past all that.
That's good,
because I don't know about you,
but I'm ready
for some birthday cake.
So lets get going, okay?
- Yeah?
- It's me.
Tell me you've got good news.
Because at this rate, Ubient software
will cease to exist in three days,
which means we lose
all our financial backing,
not to mention
our spyware program.
I get it.
Don't worry.
I'm taking care of it.
I hope so.
Oh, my god, daddy?
Daddy?
Come on!
Come on.
Half a dozen residents
claimed they heard the crash.
- But nobody saw anything?
- Apparently not.
Morning.
Court order
come through yet?
Uh, yes, it did.
Not that it matters anymore.
- Why not? What's going on?
- Last night, someone stole a car
and plowed it
into a telephone pole
a few blocks
from Warren Trask's house.
Blacked out
the entire neighborhood.
Life support system shut down.
It ran on battery power for a while,
but we had his daughter's
cell phone jammed.
By the time she got
to a phone that worked...
Trask's dead?
Try not to sound
so broken up about it.
I'm just surprised, that's all.
What about the attacks
on Ubient?
As of this morning,
Ubient software is running virus-free.
Seems Imroth's company
is going to survive,
and so's the economy.
Stock market's already up 200 points.
Weird way for things to work out,
but I guess we'll take it.
Yeah, we all got lucky,
except for Warren Trask.
What happened to your head?
Oh, I banged it
on the medicine cabinet
in the middle of the night.
Next time I'll turn on the light.
Good idea.
You have five minutes, Shawn.
Tell me what you want.
I want you to release Kevin Burkhoff.
Don't tell me he's not here.
Dr. Burkhoff is here.
He's my guest,
and he'll remain that way
for the time being.
Tell me, Jordan,
since when did kidnapping
become part of this
new religion of yours?
That seems like a pretty twisted way
to bring the world closer to god.
You want to get back
in my good graces?
It's simple.
Hold another press conference,
announce you've had a change of heart,
and that you now support
the taking of promicin.
You know I can't do that.
Then Kevin Burkhoff
remains my guest,
and you...
You're no longer welcome
in Promise City.
Goodbye, shawn.
How is my girl feeling?
Like I'm going to die.
Ah, it's just
your body ridding itself
of the anti-promicin
allergens.
It's all part of the process.
Look this way.
There you go.
Now...
It's time for the next step.
Don't.
It's okay, Isabelle.
In a few seconds, you are
going to feel a lot better.
You see?
That wasn't so bad.
Oh, and...
Isabelle, I know
what you're thinking.
Once your abilities return,
you're gonna use them against me.
It worked once before
when you murdered Matthew Ross,
but I wouldn't try it again.
This time, we're not
taking any chances.
We placed a deterrent inside you
while you were in prison.
Call it a... kill switch.
If you move against me,
or disobey me in any way,
it will be activated, and you will die.
Now, you just...
rest for another hour or so,
and when you get up,
you'll be the most
powerful person on the planet...
Again.
So, what do we have?
The lab ran
the test you asked for.
The glass sample they pulled
was pretty degraded.
It's going to take a couple of days
to get conclusive results,
but we do have
the preliminary results.
I'm sorry, Diana,
but there's about an 80% chance
the blood belongs to Tom Baldwin.
These last few weeks, I could tell
there was something wrong.
It's like he was the same guy,
but different, you know?
And I kept telling myself,
"it's okay, it's still Tom."
Well, I didn't want to
believe it either.
He's been my partner
and my friend for years.
Talk about
sleeping with the enemy.
I don't know if he told you,
but... Tom and I...
No, he didn't,
but the possibility
had crossed my mind.
Okay, so we're past that.
The question is,
what do we do now, Diana?
Well, we have to find a way
to get the real Tom Baldwin back,
and we can't let him suspect
that we know anything.
We just to have to
force ourselves
to act like
nothing's changed.
That's not going to
be a problem in the office,
but outside, I mean...
It's not going to be easy.
The physical intimacy thing, I'm...
I'm not sure I can handle it.
So you two got it all
figured out?
Whatever it is
you're talking about.
Tom, what are you doing
in the office so late?
Just catching up
on some loose ends.
- What about you guys?
- Just... just the same.
You know, I was thinking about
catching a bite. Who's with me?
I can't.
I'm supposed to be at my dad's.
Oh, I got to get home.
Well, I'm just going to
finish up here.
- You two have a good night.
- Yeah, you too.
Good night.
I have to say,
you did wonderful work.
With Trask out of the way,
the company
has finally rebounded.
The next two fiscal quarters
will be shaky at best,
but thanks to you,
Ubient lives.
You're not celebrating.
what's wrong?
One of the last things
Trask did
was spread your personal data
all over the internet.
Names, phone records,
financial statements.
They're all out there
for all eyes to see...
To study.
It could lead to
some very dangerous questions.
So, we do damage control.
Delete all we can
and deny the rest.
That'll only feed
the conspiracy theorists.
So it's been decided, Drew.
We're going to have to take
a more radical approach.
What do you have in mind?
Hi, mom!
Hi, dad!
Hello, sweetheart.
did you have a fun birthday?
Pretty fun.
I just... wish you
could have been there.
- So do we.
- I'll bet you got some nice gifts.
I got a new iPod.
It's like a record player,
only it plays
thousands of songs.
- Any Sinatra?
- Tons of Sinatra.
Next time I come,
I'll bring it with me.
Are you sure
you can get away?
You know, we wouldn't
want to interfere
with any homework
or anything.
You're not interfering.
I like coming here
and seeing you.
I wish I could
come every day.
So do we.
But you're here now.
Jordan's never
going to let Kevin go.
So that's it? The compatibility test
isn't going to happen?
It has to happen.
I have to make it happen.
Get on the phone,
get ahold of Tess.
We're taking Kevin
out of Promise City.
It's all settled.
He understands
what he has to do.
He may have been
a little disappointed at first.
After all, he had a good run,
but in the end, he took it well.
He knows it's time to move on.
I'm sure he considers it
an honor...
Especially after he heard about
the new host we have lined up for him.
He made an excellent
Drew Imroth,
but he'll make an even better
Jordan Collier.
[ www.seriessub.com ]
v1.00