SeriesSub presents...
The world will have to
deal with us.
Previously on The 4400...
- Who's Cassie?
- I'm Kyle's ability.
You ever go visit
your cousin, Shawn?
Maybe someone should try injecting him
with a big old dose of promicin.
It's all about to happen.
What's going to happen?
Thumb through the book,
if you'd like.
A lot of it is written
in a code or something.
- Maia, this is my friend, Ben.
- I've heard a lot about you.
You saw me getting married
to my sister's boyfriend?
These shots are free.
Give them to anyone
who wants them,
but be careful
to explain the risks.
There are no guarantees.
There never are.
Is this seat taken?
It is now.
I'm April,
by the way.
Peter. Barton.
So, what's good tonight?
I recommend
the lemon drop martini.
Bartender,
can I get two more?
Is that okay?
I don't want you to think
I'm hitting on you or anything.
So, what do you do, Peter?
I'm V.P. of client relations
for ANEXXO.
We're in the fortune 500.
Energy. Communications.
Some defense work...
I get it. You're one of the guys
that runs the world.
Me? No, but...
I work for those guys.
So, what brings you to Seattle?
The company's in the midst
of a major project, and...
they hit a little snag, so...
I'm here to do some triage.
You're going to save the day?
Hopefully.
And how are you going
to do that?
I'm gonna bribe someone
to look the other way.
I can't believe
I just told you that.
Look, do me a favor...
- forget what I just said.
- It's already forgotten.
So, how much money
are we talking about?
$300,000. I'm picking it up
tomorrow afternoon.
Oh, my God.
I don't know why
I'm telling you all this stuff.
Did they put something
in this drink?
- Who are you anyway?
- I'm just a girl you met in a bar.
Don't ask me
any more questions, okay?
What room are you in, Peter?
315.
What I just told you,
don't repeat it.
It would be bad for you,
for me, for...
everyone.
Let me guess...
- The truth hurts.
- It usually does.
So what do we got?
Cheating husband? Tax fraud...
Try corporate intrigue.
Try bribery.
Try $300,000
arriving tomorrow.
- Room 315.
- 300 grand?
Baby, you're good.
Wow. Okay.
All right, so we'll hit him up
for 20% to keep quiet.
That's... 60,000 bucks.
Love me?
I do.
And it's not like
I can lie to you.
No, you can't.
No one can.
Glad I remembered
this place.
I had a lot of fun summers
up here when I was a kid.
It's pretty much
a ghost town till june, which is...
a good thing, because
the whole world's looking for you.
Maybe I should just
turn myself in.
Spend the rest of your life in prison?
I don't think so.
It was no coincidence
I was there when that van crashed.
I was sent
to help you get away.
This is all happening
for a reason.
And what would that be?
Truthfully, I'm not sure yet.
Maybe the answers are in this book.
I just hope they're not in this code,
or whatever this is.
Do you believe that
Jordan Collier is a Messiah?
And that promicin's
gonna save the world?
Yeah, I do.
Even if that's true,
what does it have to do with me?
My abilities are gone.
My body can't tolerate promicin.
I'm the enemy. I hurt shawn.
I tried to kill Jordan Collier.
I did kill Jordan.
Believe me.
I know what it feels like...
to be in prison and think
you're never getting out.
To feel you've done things
that no one will ever forgive you for.
But no one's so far gone
that they can't be forgiven,
don't have a role to play
In this new world of Jordan Collier's.
I'm meant to be
a part of that world.
To help bring it about,
and so are you.
Colin?
You're a hard woman
to find, April.
I've been looking everywhere
for you.
Well, you found me, Di.
Now what are you gonna do
with me?
Season 4 - Episode 04
The Truth & Nothing But The Truth
[ Transcript ]
swsub.com
[ Sync ]
Benj!
aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
It wasn't terribly smart using
mom's maiden name on your credit card.
If I'd known you were gonna come
looking for me,
then I would have been
more creative.
I can only imagine how pissed off
you must've been
when you'd heard
I'd taken the shot.
I wasn't terribly happy about it,
you're right.
But you are my sister,
and I was very worried about you.
Besides, I knew you never would have
taken the shot...
if it hadn't been for what happened
between Ben and me.
Feeling a little guilty, are we?
Well, don't.
You and Ben
may be why I did it...
But taking the shot
was the right thing for me to do.
I've got money, clothes,
a great guy, Colin,
who loves me,
and a pretty great ability.
How many times a week
are you and Ben having sex?
Three.
Wait, that's not...
- That is none of your business.
- I know.
And you told me anyway.
That's my ability.
I ask a question,
you tell the truth...
every time.
That's a pretty interesting ability.
It doesn't work on you, does it?
You mean make me
tell the truth?
Thankfully, no.
What am I gonna do
with you, April?
with you?
Go back to Spain, Di.
Any guilt you feel
about you and Ben...
Consider yourself
absolved.
Enjoy your life...
and let me enjoy mine.
That's wonderful, dad.
I'm so glad you're walking better.
I can't wait to see it.
I have to go.
I love you, too.
Garrity said
you wanted to see me.
Have you seen the doctor's final report
on your nephew's recovery?
Yes, I have.
Well, now so has D.C.
Those high levels of promicin
that were found in his system...
People are wondering
where they came from.
Yeah. Beats me.
Come on, Tom.
Someone
walked into the hospital
and gave your nephew
a massive dose of promicin.
Your sister and your son
were the only ones with him at the time.
Now I'm willing to dismiss Susan
as a suspect,
but I think you need
to have a talk with Kyle.
Excuse me?
Mr. Farrell.
Senator Lenhoff's
here to see you.
Senator Lenhoff?
Are you sure?
She's sure. I'm sure. And I can see
you're beginning to believe it yourself.
Roland Lenhoff.
The devil made flesh.
We need to talk.
In private.
Senator, if you're here
to try to force me
- to shut down the center again...
- Relax, Farrell.
I don't want
to shut this place, hell!
I want you to heal
as many people as possible,
which is surprising, I know.
After all...
I'm the guy that passed the bill
forcing all you 4400s
to register your abilities.
And you were
just warming up.
I seem to remember one speech
where you said
that if it were up to you,
we'd all be living behind barbed wire.
I knew you were
going to bring that up.
Have a seat.
Come on, sit down.
I'll admit...
I have been waging
a kind of war against you.
Trouble is,
I just chaired a committee,
which is about to issue
a 1600-page report,
which states,
in no uncertain terms,
that I'm losing that war
and you are winning it.
Promicin
isn't going away.
Jordan Collier
made damn sure of that.
If you're here
to sign terms of surrender,
- I could have some drawn up.
- Who's talking about surrender?
I fought in 'nam.
I have the medals to prove it.
And last year,
I took my wife
on vacation to Saigon.
I figure if I can make my peace
with Charlie,
I can make my peace with you.
They're holding
a special election
to fill a vacant seat
on the Seattle city council.
I want you to run for it.
City council?
Senator, I'm not a politician.
The hell you're not.
You stepped into the spotlight
when you reopened this center.
I want you to leverage
some of the good work
that you've been doing here
into something more.
You're the alternative we need
to Collier and his
promicin-pushing radicals.
You can walk the middle path
that will unite both 4400s
and non-4400s.
And this middle path?
You're planning on walking it with me?
Right down the center.
Probably lose any chance
of re-election.
My anti-4400 colleagues
will see to that.
But it's what
the country needs.
What the world needs.
So, what do you say,
Farrell?
You ready
to dance with the devil?
You should've seen
that hotel suite.
It must run
at $600 or $700 a night.
The dress, the shoes.
Moving around from city to city.
This ability of hers,
however she's using it,
she's going to get herself into trouble.
What are you
smiling about?
Diana, come on,
April's alive.
The shot didn't kill her.
She's not even living on the street.
She's even involved with a guy.
This is... a win.
It just doesn't
feel like a win.
She's going to screw up.
NTAC are going to get a hold of her,
and then what?
Listen to me.
Come here for a second.
You traveled 6,000 miles
to find your sister, right?
You offered her help.
She refused.
It's over.
And now we can move back
to Spain.
I guess we can.
- You guess?
- No, I mean... we will.
It will take a little time.
I mean, the whole work thing.
Come on, Diana,
it's not that complicated.
All you got to do is go in there,
turn in your gun and badge,
and we're on a plane
by tomorrow.
I can't just do that.
Not to Tom, to Meghan.
You just give me a week or so
and then we're out of here.
- We'll tell Maia tonight?
- Yeah. As soon as we get home.
You're sure you don't want me
to go with you to pick up the money?
Nah, you'd just freak
the guy out.
Barton knows you put some kind
of whammy on him, right?
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
Still thinking
about your sister?
I just can't believe she came
all that way to look for me.
I didn't think she cared enough.
April, she's a judgmental bitch,
and I say good riddance.
Besides, you don't need her anymore.
You got me.
So what do you say we meet in the bar
a little after 7:00,
- for a celebratory cocktail?
- Okay.
Where are we off to next?
I figured we'd go crash
with my brother in south beach.
He just moved there
from Phoenix.
Jeff says there's
money to be made in Miami.
People there are holding onto
all kinds of dirty little secrets.
Dirty little secrets.
Got a minute, buddy?
Not really.
I'm meeting some friends.
It's about Shawn.
What about him?
The way he woke up from his coma
with all that promicin in him.
People are starting to wonder
if you had something to do with it.
By people, do you mean NTAC?
What exactly
are you accusing me of, dad?
I'm not accusing you of anything.
I'm asking you.
The day at the hospital,
did you give your cousin
a shot of promicin?
No, I didn't.
Kyle, listen to me.
- If you're involved in something.
- In what ?
I don't know. Last few nights,
you haven't come home...
- Dad, I'm 23 years old.
- I know that.
Kyle, if you're holding
anything back,
Please...
tell me now.
I got nothing to say.
Except I'm glad
Shawn's up and about.
For all I know, whatever isabelle
zapped him with, it wore off.
Or not.
I guess we'll never know
the truth, will we?
We all got to get used to that.
Can I go now?
This is Colin.
Leave a message.
Colin?
Babe?
It's colin!
He's been shot!
There was so much blood.
Maia, will you go to bed now,
please, sweetie?
Help me, Di.
Please, help me.
April, did you honestly believe
that this guy, Barton,
was just gonna hand
you over $60,000?
Seemed like such an easy mark
and it's always worked before.
So that's how you've
been using your ability?
- To blackmail people.
- Oh, God.
Don't start lecturing me
on right and wrong.
- No, it's a little late for that.
- Yeah. It is.
- So save your breath.
- All right, ladies, just calm down.
Let's just stay calm, okay?
Focus on what's
important right now.
Barton?
He did it, right?
He killed colin?
Well, I would say
he's our number one suspect.
But this $300,000
that ANEXXO's paying out
in bribe money...
Barton didn't happen to mention
where it was going?
Does it matter?
Colin, the way he looked
lying there on the floor...
The hotel suite.
It was in Colin's name, right?
Yeah.
Or one of his names.
He used a couple.
And when they find the body,
there's nothing there
to connect you to it,
is there?
I don't think so.
Ben, will you stay here?
I'm gonna drive April
to a motel,
or somewhere away from here
and away from Maia.
I'm sorry, you'll have to stay there
until we figure this out.
Are you going to turn me in?
We just have to make this up
as we go along.
So I can count on you, right?
If my dad asks you,
and he probably will...
I'm not going to tell your dad
that you gave me a promicin shot.
It's hard, you know?
I mean, I love the guy so much,
but the things I'm doing,
- he just wouldn't understand.
- I get it, Kyle.
I really do.
It's just I've got...
all of this other stuff
I'm dealing with.
If you mean Isabelle Tyler,
don't think you have to worry about her.
- She's probably long gone from Seattle.
- That's good to know.
I'll fire the extra security
I had on.
Anyway, I wasn't
talking about her.
This is going
to sound weird.
Roland Lenhoff...
wants me to run for a seat
on the city council.
The guy behind
the Dinstman-Lenhoff bill?
He sees it as a "If you can't beat 'em,
work with 'em" kind of thing.
And he knows he can't beat us.
That's great, Shawn.
- You said yes, right?
- I'm thinking about it.
You have to do this.
You get elected,
that puts a 4400 into the mainstream.
They'll have to start
taking us seriously.
Who knows? You could become mayor,
maybe even governor.
Just one step at a time.
I don't even know if I can get
elected to city council.
You heal people with your hands.
Show me an opponent
who can beat that.
- Do you wanna be my campaign manager?
- No.
But you got my vote.
That's one.
Not a problem.
I'll have the test results
back tomorrow.
- What name do I log the samples under?
- No name.
- What if they're promicin positive?
- No name, Marco.
I want any paperwork
handed to me and me alone.
Are we clear?
Actually, Tom,
I still have some questions.
Do me this favor, please.
But I won't ask them.
Thank you.
Hey, Marco.
They told me you were down here, Tom.
- Have you got a minute?
- Yeah, yeah, sure.
I know my sister's made
a lot of bad choices in her life,
but I also know that April
would never have taken that shot
if it weren't for me.
I understand you want
to protect your sister, Diana,
but if she knows
the identity of a murderer...
I can't be responsible
for sending April to prison, Tom.
She's promicin positive.
It's a life sentence.
You know the deal.
Besides, I mean,
there's a chance
that the police could get
to Barton on their own.
But what if they don't?
What then?
Then I'll tell the authorities
everything I know.
After I've bought April
a one-way ticket to Marrakech.
April Skouris, right?
I'm a friend of Colin's brother, Jeff.
- Jeff?
- No, I'm Larry,
but Jeff heard what happened
and he...
He sent me here
to get you outta Seattle.
Really? Well, where
are we going to go?
My car's right out back.
We're gonna go to Phoenix.
- What about my clothes?
- You can get some new ones, ok?
If we hurry,
we can catch the next flight.
Wait, Phoenix?
Jeff moved to Florida.
- It really doesn't matter.
- Oh, my god, help!
He's trying to kill me!
Help! Help!
Di, I really need to know
what's going on
because none of this
makes any sense.
Why kill Colin?
Why come after me?
We never got our hands
on any of that money.
Well, that bribe money
that ANEXXO is paying out,
they clearly don't want anyone
knowing about it.
I guess it's time we have a talk
with this Peter Barton guy.
I'm coming with you.
You want the truth?
I can get it for you.
You sure about that?
I mean...
People beat lie detectors
all the time.
Tom, do you like my sister?
Diana? Yeah, sure.
She's my partner, my friend.
Ever had a sexual fantasy about her?
Once or twice.
We were working late.
Diana mentioned we were the only
two people working in the building...
You can come.
Peter Barton,
I'm agent Baldwin.
This is agent Skouris.
We're with NTAC.
Oh, God, not her.
You murdered Colin, didn't you?
Murdered? No.
I wasn't even in the room
when your boyfriend showed up.
The money.
It wasn't me
you were trying to blackmail.
It was the corporation.
I had to warn them.
The bribe money.
Who'd you pass it off to?
I tell you that, I lose my job.
What was his name, Peter?
Alex Lupone.
He's the director of advanced
combat systems for the pentagon.
Ask him why ANEXXO
was paying Lupone.
Don't. Just...
Don't.
ANEXXO won a contract
to develop
a new interceptor ballistic
body armor for the military.
It was supposed to be impenetrable.
So this body armor,
it was defective?
There were some design flaws
which left parts of the side
and shoulders unprotected.
I was supposed to pay off Lupone
to look the other way.
You interfered,
and it was taken
out of my hands.
Who did you tell
about Colin and April?
Donald Mitchell. He sits
on our board of directors.
He called me personally
to handle the payoff.
Flew me out here
on ANEXXO's dime.
Where can we find Mitchell?
He's staying at
the Dorchester hotel.
I didn't know anyone
was gonna die.
I don't like
standing up here
and calling Roland Lenhoff
a liar,
but the truth is,
he's been one for 40 years.
He did not single-handedly
hold off a platoon
of viet cong troops
while his men
lay wounded around him.
I know that for a fact
because I was one of those men.
Turn that damned thing off.
...performed
by staff sergeant Stephen...
Guess some of my colleagues
heard that you and I
were meeting.
Didn't waste any time
letting me know
they weren't
real happy about it.
Senator,
I have to ask,
did you falsify your war record?
No, I did not.
That fellow who gave
that little speech...
I saved his life that day.
They must've paid him a lot of money
to get him to lie like that.
Well, I guess
if what he says isn't true,
then it doesn't really matter.
Doesn't have to be true.
It's on the television.
I can tough this out.
The question is, can you?
'Cause they're gonna be giving you
the same kind of treatment.
If not worse.
People have been
telling lies about me
ever since we came back
in that ball of light, so...
Does that mean
you'll run for city council?
It means I'm gonna run
and I'm gonna win.
That's what I wanted to hear.
I knew I picked myself
the right man.
So what happens now?
The first thing
you got to do
is let people know
where you stand.
That means telling the world
you're against Jordan Collier
and everything
that he's been doing.
You want to win this election?
Then Jordan Collier is the enemy.
Your enemy.
- Hey, Kyle.
- Hey.
How's it coming?
I'm trying to decipher
these coded pages,
but I'm not a cryptographer.
Can I have a look?
I may have lost my abilities,
but I did read
the encyclopedia from A to Z.
And you remember all of it?
Yeah, pretty much.
How are you with puzzles?
Well, I guess we'll see.
But you did say you brought me
here for a reason, right?
That I'm part of all this.
So maybe this is my chance
to prove it.
I don't care
what Peter Barton claims.
ANEXXO doesn't bribe
government officials.
That's not the way
we conduct business.
Mr. Mitchell,
did you authorize the payment
of $300,000 to Alex Lupone?
I did not.
We never paid
Alex Lupone a penny.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have an $80 kobe beef filet
growing cold on the plate.
- Then what was the money for?
- It was a down payment.
A down payment for what?
To have Alex Lupone murdered.
I didn't mean that.
I don't know why
I'd say such a thing.
Why have Lupone killed?
I'm not answering
any more questions.
Was it because you were selling
the military defective body armor?
Lupone would have exposed us.
we had no choice.
- I'm calling my lawyer.
- No.
Not till you cancel
the hit on Lupone.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
How do we reach Lupone?
- What is his phone number?
- There isn't one.
He's on vacation
in the Brazilian jungle.
The men we hired
are already down there.
I have no way
of contacting them.
Is this really necessary?
Absolutely, it is.
So what do we do now?
Well, we'll get in touch
with the Brazilian authorities
and hope that they get in touch
with Lupone first.
But in the meantime,
I'm going to need you
to come into NTAC
and make sure that Mitchell
repeats his confession
for the record.
I can't do that.
I walk into NTAC,
I don't come out.
No, I'll speak to Meghan.
We'll explain the circumstances.
What if that doesn't work?
Can't take that chance.
April, without some coaxing
from your ability,
Mitchell is going to deny
everything he just told us.
He's going to get away with murder.
He's gonna get away with Colin's murder.
- Do you want that?
- Look, I can't do that.
- I'm sorry.
- April, you've been running away
your entire life.
From your family, from school,
from responsibility.
And I don't know, maybe I'm...
Maybe I'm to blame for that.
Maybe I pushed you away.
Maybe I wasn't there for you.
I don't know.
But this time...
This time, you can't run away.
Watch me.
All right. Time to get
to the tough questions.
Do you think the average citizen
is ready to vote for a 4400?
Well, I'm hoping so,
being there's a lot more non-4400s
out there than people with abilities.
But more people
are taking the shot all the time.
How do you feel about that?
Do you agree with
Jordan Collier's decision
to hand out promicin
to anybody who wants it?
No. I don't.
Half of those people
are going to die.
Thousands already have.
Are you calling Jordan Collier
a mass murderer?
I think that Jordan...
should've waited until the odds
of survival were better than 50/50.
A lot better than 50/50.
If he wanted to change the world,
there are safer ways
of doing so.
Like running for city council?
Well, that's a start anyway.
April, it's me.
- Go away.
- Not until we've talked.
Now just let me in.
Come on, open up.
So where do you go now?
I really hadn't thought
that far ahead.
I never do, do I?
Maybe this time you should.
You want to hear
something funny?
I thought when
I got this ability,
it would change my life.
And it did.
Changed my circumstances anyway.
I got better clothes.
I eat in better restaurants.
Fly first-class
for the first time in my life.
But it didn't change me.
No ability is going to do that.
You have to change yourself.
And you can.
How?
By marching into NTAC?
That would be brave.
Except I'm not brave, am I?
Another one of my many faults.
It's not too late.
You can still be the person
that you want to be.
Look, I...
I can't say that I approve
of what you've been up to.
But you did say that
you loved this guy, Colin.
And if you did,
if that's true,
then you have to
speak up for him.
And only you can do that.
The man is guilty of multiple felonies
and he's threatening to sue us?
Mitchell's claiming harassment,
intimidation, oh, and false arrest.
And ANEXXO's lawyers have the muscle
to make a case like this stick.
Come on, Meghan.
He's responsible for
one murder we know of,
he plotted two others,
and his corporation is trying
to defraud the U.S. government,
and we're just
gonna let him walk?
You tell me this guy deserves to be
locked up and I'll believe you,
but I need more than your word.
I need that woman, the one
that got his initial confession.
Look, I know
she's promicin positive,
but you need to convince
her to come forward.
I don't think that's gonna happen.
Then there's no way we're going
to get an indictment against Mitchell.
Not without proof.
I have the proof
you need right here.
Hey, Kyle.
- Everything all right?
- No, it's not.
I'm driving in my car,
turn on the radio,
and I hear you tell the world that
Jordan Collier's a mass murderer.
That is not what I said.
I said that he was wrong
to hand out promicin.
And that's what I believe.
Everything that you are,
this building you're standing in,
you owe it all to Jordan.
You're willing to betray
him for some votes?
Hey, I built this place
just as much as Jordan.
He used my healing abilities
to raise money for it.
He used me for a lot of things.
Not anymore.
I'm my own man now.
I make my own choices.
Well, you're off to a great start.
You're not only
betraying Jordan,
you're betraying yourself.
You're a traitor, Shawn.
Don't you see that?
Traitor.
How long has it been?
Since the last time you asked,
about 10 minutes.
Since your sister's been in there
with Mitchell, about two hours.
Mitchell's been with ANEXXO
for what, 14 years?
Imagine the secrets
he's saved up.
We could be here all night.
We got a signed confession.
Whether it holds up in court
remains to be seen,
but we've got enough
against him
that at least a couple
of these charges should stick.
- And April?
- I'm sorry, Diana.
We have to take her
into custody.
It's okay, Di.
Everything's okay.
I didn't say
I'd go for it either but...
You must've been pretty convincing.
Excuse me,
I'm sorry to interrupt.
But I have been up all night
and what we're doing
to April just isn't fair.
She didn't have to come forward.
Mitchell could be
a free man right now,
instead of having his picture
plastered all over the papers.
But no, she did the right thing,
and we're locking her up?
We need to offer her some kind
of amnesty, not punish her.
Skouris, we're not punishing her.
We're hiring her.
According to Meghan,
NTAC...
The attorney general's office...
The FBI...
They're already fighting over
who gets me when.
And all I have to do
is ask people questions.
It's not always going to be
at a bar over drinks.
Some of the people you meet
and the questions
you have to ask...
Some of the answers
you're going to hear...
It can get pretty ugly.
Meghan was pretty upfront
about that.
Still, it's gotta be
better than prison.
I must say,
the perks are pretty good.
I get an apartment,
a nice salary,
health insurance,
even a clothing allowance.
And let's not forget
Eric and Ralph.
Or is it Ralph and Eric?
I'm sure
you'll figure it out.
Their job is to make sure
I show up
wherever I need to be.
Knowing me, it won't be
as easy as it sounds.
You think I'm gonna
screw this up, don't you?
April, maybe the question
you should be asking me is
if I want you to succeed,
and the answer
is a definite yes.
Well, I'll try not to let
either one of us down.
And I promise
to call or email
and let you know
how I'm doing.
So...
When are you leaving?
You know, for Spain,
or wherever you guys decide?
I'm not leaving.
I'm staying right
here in Seattle.
Did I just say that?
Does Ben know?
No. I hadn't realized it
until just now.
You're gonna
have to tell him.
I'm really happy
for both of you.
I really am. But...
we're not leaving this table
until we've made a decision.
Are we living in France or Spain?
Neither.
Diana?
Don't hate me, Ben. Please.
Oh, God...
I quit work.
I went to Spain.
I tried. I really tried.
But I belong here.
With Tom, and with NTAC,
the search for Collier.
I'm a part of that.
My daughter's a part of that.
And now my sister is, too.
So what happens to us?
We go back to our own lives?
Back to our work?
What, see each other
a few days a month?
For now.
We could have
so much more, Diana.
Maia said
that we'd get married.
And Maia's never wrong.
Well, I hope not.
Me too.
The lab report
you asked for.
The one and only copy.
Samples came back
positive for promicin.
Someone's definitely
walking around with an ability.
Thanks, Marco.
"When the chosen
have taken the elixir
"and proved their faith
in the Messiah,
"then all will follow
in their wake.
"Only then will the father
reveal his true face,
"and paradise and the world
will be as one."
I think that's a pretty
accurate translation.
The elixir,
that's gotta be promicin.
And we know Collier's
supposed to be the Messiah.
And the father?
I don't know. God, I guess?
- But who are the chosen?
- Flip the page.
It's a list of names.
Yeah. 200 in all.
And most of them
you'll recognize.
Politicians, scientists,
athletes...
These people,
they're all alive today.
But this book was written
85 years ago.
I know.
All right, so...
all these people
have to take the shot?
And...
That's supposed to influence
more and more people
to do the same, right?
Until what?
Everyone has an ability?
Those who survive, anyway.
And that's when god's
supposed to show up?
I think you'd better look
at the last name.
My dad?
He has to take the shot?
If you believe in the prophecy.
In some kind of
paradise on earth
led by Jordan Collier...
Then, yeah...
Your dad has to take promicin.
[ www.seriessub.com ]
v 1.0