Salutations!
This is Sally Calypso
with the traffic news at 10.15
We've got reports of a multiple
stack pile at Junction 509,
with a spate of car jackings
reported on New Fifth Avenue,
so you take care now!
Drive safely.
They're gonna get in,
there's no stopping them.
The police are on their way,
I promise, I've sounded the alarm.
Repeat, this is Car One Zero
Hot Five,
we have a problem,
require urgent assistance.
'Thank you for your call,
you are on hold.'
It's all your fault, you lied to the computer,
you said there were three of us, you told them three!
Repeat, urgent assistance,
Car One
Zero Hot Five, this is an emergency.
Help us! Oh, my God,
I'm begging you, please, help us.
'The weather is at 36 degrees and
it's blue skies all the way home.'
This is Sally Calypso signing off.
Missing you already!
Just one trip,
that's what I said, one trip
in the TARDIS and then home.
Although. . .
I suppose we could...
stretch the definition
One trip into the past, one into
the future,
how do you fancy that?
No complaints from me.
How about...
a different planet?
Can we go to yours?
Aah, there's plenty of other places.
Come on! I mean, planet of the Time Lords,
that's gotta be worth a look.
What's it like?
Well, it's beautiful, yeah.
Is it like, you know,
outer space cities, all spires and stuff?
Suppose it is.
Great big temples and cathedrals?
Yeah.
With lots of planets in the sky?
The sky's a burnt orange
with the Citadel enclosed in a mighty glass dome,
shining under the twin suns.
Beyond that, the mountains go on
for ever,
slopes of. . .
deep red grass,
capped with snow.
Can we go there?
Naah, where's the fun for me?
I don't want to go home!
Instead...
This is much better!
The year 5 billion and 53, planet New Earth!
Second home of mankind.
50,000 light years from your old world,
and we're slap bang in the middle of New New York.
Technically, it's the 15th New York so it's New
New New New New New New New New New
New New New New New York,
one of the most dazzling cities ever built.
Oh, that's nice(!)
Time Lord version of dazzling.
Naah, bit of rain never hurt anyone. Come on!
Let's get undercover.
He has arrived.
What should I do?
Find him.
Before it's too late.
It looks like the same old Earth to me.
On a Wednesday afternoon.
And the driving should be clear and easy,
with 15 extra lanes open for the New New Jersey Expressway.
That's more like it, that's the view we had last time.
This must be the lower levels,
down at the base of the tower, some sort of Undercity.
You've brought me to the slums.
More interesting!
It's all cocktails and glitter up there.
This is the real city.
You'd enjoy anything.
That's me!
Ah, the rain's stopping.
Better and better!
When you say "last time",
was that you and Rose?
Um, yeah, yeah, it was, yeah.
You're taking me to the same planets that you took her?
What's wrong with that?
Nothing.
Just, ever heard the word "rebound"?
Oh, you should've said.
How long have you been there?
Happy, you want happy?
Happy, happy.
Customers, customers.
We've got customers.
We're in business!
Mother, open up the mellow!
Happy happy, lovely happy happy.
Anger! Buy some anger.
Mellow, makes you feel bendy and soft all day long!
They'll rip you off. Do you want some happy?
No, thanks.
Are they selling drugs?
I think they're selling moods.
Same thing, isn't it?
Oi,
you, over here! Over here.
Buy some happy, happy. happy.
What can I get you?
I want to buy forget.
I've got forget, what strength?
How much do you want forgetting?
My mother and father.
They went on the Motorway.
Oh, that's a swine.
Try this,
Forget 43,
that's two credits.
Sorry, but,
hold on a minute, what happened to your parents?
They drove off.
Yeah, but
they might drive back.
Everyone goes to the Motorway in the end.
I've lost them.
But they can't have gone far, you could find them.
No, no, don't!
Sorry, what were you saying?
Your parents,
your mother and father, they're on the Motorway.
Are they?
That's nice.
I'm sorry, I won't keep you.
So that's the human race five billion years in the future.
Off their heads on chemicals.
I'm really, really sorry. We just need three, that's all.
Let her go!
I'm warning you,
let her go!
Whatever you want,
I can help, both of us can help you, but first, you've got to let her go!
The Doctor is so gonna kill you and never mind him, I'm gonna kill you myself.
Let go of me!
Give her some sleep.
That's enough!
Don't you dare!
It's just Sleep 14,
Don't you put that thing on me.
Don't fight it. That's it, come on,
that's it.
Get on board.
Engaging antigravs.
Hold on!
MARTHA!
She's all right,
she's breathing. Pulse is fine,
no harm done.
She looks rich.
She must've got lost.
She's worth her weight in gold to us.
This is Car 465 Diamond 6, we have three passengers, repeat, three.
'Access granted.'
Oh, yes!
Thought you'd come back.
Do you want some happy happy?
Who were those people?
Where did they take her?
They've taken her to the Motorway.
Looked like carjackers.
I'd give up now, darling,
you won't see her again.
Used to be thriving, this place.
But they all go to the Motorway in the end.
He kept on saying three, "We need three.
" What did he mean, three?
It's the car-sharing policy, to save fuel.
You get special access if you're carrying three adults.
This motorway, how do I get there?
Down the alley, keep going to the end, you can't miss it.
Tell you what,
buy some happy happy,
then you'll be smiling, my love!
Word of advice. All of you. . .
cash up,
close down and pack your bags.
Why's that, then?
Because as soon as I've found her alive and well,
and I will find her alive and well, then I'm coming back
And this street is closing.
Tonight!!
# Car 465 Diamond 6 heading for the Fast Lane.
. . .Thank you very much.
# - You just settle down. It's all gonna be worth it.
# -Yeah.
# The view from the windows.
# You can see all the way to the open sky.
They say the air smells like apple grass, can you imagine?
And houses are made of wood,
there are jobs going in the foundries - everyone says so.
Take me back.
Whoever you are, just take me back to my friend,
that's all I want.
I won't cause any trouble, just take me back.
I'm sorry,
that's not a real gun.
Yeah, well, you would say that.
Where do you get a gun from these days?
I wouldn't even know how to fire.
No, nor me.
OK.
What's your name?
Martha.
Martha Jones.
Well, I'm Cheen, and this is Milo.
And I swear, we're sorry,
we're really, really sorry.
We just needed access to the Fast Lane.
As soon as we arrive, we'll drop you and you can go back to your friend.
Seriously?
I swear, look!
Honesty patch.
All the same,
it's still kidnapping!
Where are we, anyway?
We're on the Motorway.
What's that, then? Fog?
It's exhaust fumes.
We're going out to Brooklyn.
Everyone says the air's so much cleaner,
and we couldn't stay in Pharmacytown, cos. . .
Well, cos of me.
I'm pregnant.
We only discovered it last week.
Scan says it's going to be a boy.
Right!
What do I do now, congratulate my kidnappers?
Oh, we're not kidnappers,
not really.
No,
you're idiots.
You're having a baby and you're wearing that?
Ow!
Not any more.
We'll be as fast as we can.
We'll take the Motorway to the Brooklyn Flyover. . .
and then, after that, it's gonna take a while, cos there's no Fast Lane,
just ordinary roads, but it's direct.
It's only ten miles.
How long's it gonna take?
About six years.
What?
We'll be just in time for him to start school.
No, sorry, hold on.
Six years?
Ten miles in six years?
How come?
Hey,
you daft little streetstrut,
what are you doing, standing there?
Either get out or get in! Come on!
Did you ever see the like?
Here you go.
He's just standing there, breathing it in.
says back in the old days, on Junction 47,
this woman stood in the exhaust fumes for a solid 20 minutes.
By the time they found her, her head had swollen to 50 feet.
Oh, you're making it up.
A 50-foot head, just think of it!
Imagine picking that nose.
Stop it, that's disgusting!
What? Did you never pick your nose?
Bran, we're moving.
Right, I'm there. I'm on it.
20 yards - we're having a good day.
And who might you be, sir?
Very well dressed for a hitchhiker.
Thanks. Sorry. I'm the Doctor.
Medical man!
My name's Thomas Kincaid Brannigan,
and this is the bane of my life, the lovely Valerie.
Nice to meet you.
And that's the rest of the family, behind you.
Ah, that's nice.
Hello!
How old are they?
Just two months.
Poor little souls,
they've never known the ground beneath their paws.
Children of the Motorway.
What, they were born in here?
We couldn't stop.
We heard there were jobs out in the laundries, on Fire Island,
thought we'd take a chance.
You've been driving for two months?
Do I look like a teenager?
We've been driving for 12 years now.
I'm sorry?
Yeah,
started out as newlyweds.
Feels like yesterday.
Feels like 12 years to me.
Ah, sweetheart, but you still love me.
But 12 years! How far did you come? Where did you start?
Battery Park, five miles back.
You've travelled five miles in 12 years?
I think he's a bit slow.
Where are you from?
Never mind. I've got to get out.
My friend's in one of these cars - she was taken hostage.
I should get back to the TARDIS.
You're too late for that,
we're past the lay-by.
You're a passenger now, Sunny Jim.
When's the next lay-by?
Ooh,
six months.
How many cars are out there?
I don't think anyone knows.
There we go.
Hungry?
Oh, thanks.
But how far down is it to this Fast Lane?
Right at the bottom, under the traffic jam.
Not many people can afford three passengers,
so it's empty down there.
Rumour has it you can reach up to 30mph!
Wow, that's like, crazy(!)
But how are you supposed to live inside this thing?
It's tiny.
Oh, we stocked up!
We've got self-replicating fuel,
muscle stimulants for exercise, a chemical toilet at the back,
and all waste products are recycled as food.
OK.
Another gap - this is brilliant!
Car 465 Diamond 6 on descent to Fast Lane, thank you very much.
#Please drive safely.#
I need to talk to the police.
'Thank you for your call.
You have been placed on hold.'
You're the police!
"Thank you for your call."
"You have been placed on hold.'"
Is there anyone else?
I once met the Duke of Manhattan.
Is there any way to contact him?
Oh, lordly!
I have to find my friend!
You can't make outside calls.
The Motorway's completely enclosed.
What about the other cars?
We have contact with them yet.
"What's some of  the many way?"
They must be on your Friends List.
Now, let's see, who's nearby?
Be still your hearts, my handsome girls,
it's Brannigan here.
Get off the line, Brannigan, you're a pest and a menace.
Come on, now, Sisters,
is that any way to talk to an old friend?
You know full well we're not sisters, we're married.
Oooh, stop that modern talk, I'm an old-fashioned cat.
Now, I've got a hitchhiker here, calls himself the Doctor.
I'm looking for someone called Martha Jones.
She's been carjacked.
She's inside one of these vehicles, but I don't know which one.
Wait a minute!
Could I ask, what entrance did they use?
Where were we?
Pharmacytown.
Pharmacytown about 20 minutes ago.
Let's have a look.
Just my luck, to marry a carspotter.
In the last half hour,
53 new cars joined from the Pharmacytown Junction.
Anything more specific?
All in good time.
Was she carjacked by two people?
Yes, she was, yeah.
There we are.
Just one of those cars was destined
for the Fast Lane.
That means they
had three on board,
and the Car number is 465 Diamond 6.
That's it! So how do we find them?
Ah, now, there, I'm afraid,
I can't help.
Can we call them?
We've got their number.
Not if they're designated
Fast Lane, it's a different class.
You could try the police.
They put me on hold.
You'll have to keep trying.
There's no-one else.
Thank you.
Do you see?
Another ten layers to go,
and we're scorching.
What's that?
It's coming from underneath.
It's that noise, isn't it?
It's like Kate said.
The stories, they're true.
What stories?
It's the sound of the Air Vents,
that's all.
Exhaust fumes travel down to Air Vents
at the base of the tunnel.
No, but the stories are much better.
They say people go missing on the Motorway.
Some cars just vanish, never to be seen again.
Cos there's something living down there,
in the smoke.
Something huge.
And hungry.
And if you get lost on the road,
it's waiting for you.
Like I said,
Air Vents!
" That's the end of the next lay-by"
Except, look out there.
Does it look like the Air Vents are working?
No.
So what's that, then?
Nah,
kids' stuff.
Car 465 Diamond 6 on descent.
We've got go to the Fast Lane. Take me down.
Not in a million years!
You've got three passengers.
I'm still not going!
She's alone and she's lost.
She doesn't even belong
on this planet, and it's my fault.
I'm asking you, Brannigan, take me down.
That's a no, and that's final.
I'm not risking the children down there.
Why not? What happens down there?
We're not discussing it.
The conversation is closed.
So we keep on driving?
Yes we do.
For how long!?
Till the journey's end.
Mrs Cassini, this is the Doctor.
How long have you been on the Motorway?
Oh, we were amongst the first.
It's been 23 years now.
But in all that time,
have you ever seen a police car?
I'm not sure.
Look at your notes.
Any police?
No.
Not as such.
Or an ambulance?
Ever?
I can't keep a note of everything.
What if there's no-one out there?
Stop it!
The Cassinis were doing you a favour.
Someone's got to ask.
Cos you might not talk about it,
but it's there,
in your eyes.
What if the traffic jam never stops?
There's a whole city above us -
the mighty City State of New New York.
They wouldn't just leave us.
In that case, where are they? Hmm?
What if there's no help coming, not ever?
What if there's nothing -
just the Motorway,
with the cars going round and round and round
and round, never stopping, for ever?
Shut up!
Just shut up!
This is Sally Calypso
and it's that time again.
The sun is blazing high over the New Atlantic,
the perfect setting for the Daily Contemplation.
You think you know us so well, Doctor.
We're not abandoned.
Not while we have each other.
This is for all of you out there on the roads.
We're so sorry.
Drive safe.
# On a hill, far away
# Stood an old, rugged cross
# The emblem of suffering and shame
# And I love that old cross
# Where the dearest and best
# For a world of lost sinners was slain
# So I'll cherish the old, rugged cross, rugged cross
# Till my trophies at last I lay down, I lay down
# I will cling to the old, rugged cross, rugged cross
# And exchange it some day for a crown. #
'Fast Lane access, please drive safely.'
We made it.
The Fast Lane.
If you won't take me, I'll go down on my own.
What do you think you're doing?
Finding my own way.
I usually do.
'Capsule open.'
Here we go.
Look after this.
I love that coat.
Janis Joplin gave me that coat.
But you can't jump!
If it's any consolation, Valerie,
right now, I'M having kittens.
This Martha,
she must mean an awful lot to you.
Hardly know her.
I was too busy showing off.
And I lied to her.
I couldn't help it, just lied.
Bye, then!
He's completely insane!
That, and a bit magnificent!
'Capsule open.'
Who the hell are you?
Sorry, Motorway Foot Patrol.
I'm doing a survey.
How are you enjoying your Motorway?
Not very much. Junction five's
been closed for three years!
Your comments have been noted.
Have a nice day.
'Capsule open.'
Thank you for your co-operation.
Your comments have been noted.
Do you mind if I borrow this?
Not my colour, but thank you very much.
'Capsule open.'
Don't mind me!
Try again.
'Brooklyn Turnoff One closed.'
Try the next one.
'Brooklyn Turnoff Two closed.'
What do we do?
We'll do the whole loop. By the time
we come back round, they'll be open.
You're still calling that Air Vents?
What else could it be?
What the hell is that?
It's just...the hydraulics.
Sounds like it's alive.
It's all exhaust fumes out there,
nothing could breathe in that.
'Calling Car 465 Diamond 6.
Repeat, calling Car...'
This is 465 Diamond 6. Who's that?
Where are you?
I'm in the Fast Lane, about
50 yards behind.
Can you get back up,
off the Fast Lane?
We only have permission to go down.
We need the Brooklyn Flyover.
It's closed. Go back up.
We can't. We'll just go round.
Don't you understand?
They're closed,
they're always closed.
We're stuck down here!
And there's something else out there,
in the fog. Can't you hear it?
That's the Air Vents.
Jehovah! What are you,
some stupid kid?
Get out of here!
What was that?
I can't move, they've got us.
But what's happening?
What's got you, what is it?
Hello!
Just drive, you idiots,
get out of here! Get out!
Just drive!
Do what she said -
get us out of here!
But where?
Straight ahead and fast!
What is it?
What's out there?
'Scuse me,
is that legal?
Sorry, Motorway Foot Patrol.
Whatever. Have you got any water?
Certainly. Never let it be said
I've lost my manners.
Is this the last layer?
We're right at the bottom.
Nothing below us but the Fast Lane.
Can we drive down?
Both two of us.
You need three to go down.
Couldn't we just cheat?
I'd love to, but it's an automated
system - the wheel would lock.
If you'll excuse me.
You can't jump,
it's a thousand feet down!
No, I just want to look.
What's that noise?
I...
I try not to think about it.
What are those lights?
I just need to see.
There must be some sort of ventilation.
If I could transmit a pulse through
this thing, maybe I could trip the system,
get a bit of a breeze.
Just what we need - pirates!
I'm calling the police!
The Doctor - where is he?
That's it!
Might shift the fumes a bit, give us a good look.
What are those shapes?
They're alive.
What the hell are they?
Macra.
Go faster!
I'm at top speed.
'No access above.'
But this is an emergency!
'Thank you for your call.
You have been placed on hold.'
Turn everything off!
You've gotta be joking.
No, listen, it's all fog out there,
so how can they see us?
Maybe it's the engines,
the sound or the heat.
Turn everything off. They might not find us.
It can't be worse than this. Just do it!
They've stopped.
Yeah, but they're still out there.
How did you think of that?
Saw it on a film.
They used to do it in submarines.
Trouble is, I can't remember what they did next.
You'd better think of something,
cos we've lost the aircon.
If we don't switch the engines back on,
we won't be able to breathe.
How long have we got?
Eight minutes - maximum.
The Macra used to be the scourge of this galaxy.
Gas,
they fed off gas, the filthier the better.
They built an empire with Human
slaves, mining gas for food.
They don't exactly look like
empire-builders to me.
Well, that was billions of years ago.
Billions, they must've devolved down the
years and now they're just beasts.
But they're still hungry
and my friend's down there.
Oh, it's like New Times Square in here,
for goodness' sake!
I've invented a sport!
Doctor,
you're a hard man to find.
No guns. I'm not having guns!
I only brought this in case of pirates.
Doctor,
you've got to come with me.
Do I know you?
You haven't aged at all.
Time has been less kind to me.
Novice Hame!
No! Hold on, get off!
Last time we met, you were
breeding Humans for experimentation.
I've sought forgiveness, Doctor,
for so many years. . .
under his guidance.
And if you come with me,
I might finally be able to redeem myself.
I'm not going anywhere. You've got
Macra living under this city!
Macra and my friend's stuck down there.
You've got to come with me! Right now!
YOU'RE coming with ME.
We've got three passengers, now!
I'm sorry, Doctor. But the situation
is even worse than you can imagine.
Transport.
Don't you dare! Don't you dare!
Oh!
Rough teleport.
Ow! But you can go straight back out
and teleport people out, starting with Martha.
I only had the power for one trip.
Then get some more!
Where are we?
High above,
in the Overcity.
Good, cos you can tell the Senate
of New New York, I'd like a word!
They've got millions
trapped on the Motorway!
Millions!
But you're inside the Senate,
right now.
May the Goddess Santori bless them.
They died, Doctor.
How long's it been like this?
24 years.
All of them?
Everyone?
What happened?
A new chemical,
a new mood.
They called it Bliss.
Everyone tried it.
They couldn't stop.
A virus mutated inside the compound
and became airborne.
Everything perished,
even the virus in the end.
It killed the world
in seven minutes flat.
There was just enough time to
close down the walkways and the
flyovers, sealing off the Undercity.
Those people on the Motorway
aren't lost, Doctor.
They were saved.
So the whole thing
down there is running on automatic?
There's not enough power to get them out.
We did all we could to stop
the system from choking.
Who's "we"? How did you survive?
He protected me.
And he has waited for you,
these long years.
Doctor!
The Face of Boe!
I knew you would come.
Back in the old days,
I was made his nurse,
as penance for my sins.
Old friend, what happened to you?
Failing.
He protected me from the
virus by shrouding me in his smoke.
But with no one to maintain it,
the City's power died.
The Undercity would have fallen into the sea.
So he saved them.
The Face of Boe wired
himself into the mainframe.
He's giving his life force
just to keep things running.
But there are planets out there.
You could've called for help.
The last act of the Senate was
to declare New Earth unsafe.
The automatic quarantine
lasts for 100 years.
So the two of you stayed here...
..on your own, for all these years.
We had no choice.
Yes, you did.
Save them, Doctor,
save them!
How much air's left?
Two minutes.
There's always the Doctor.
That friend of mine.
He might think of something.
Martha, no-one's coming.
He looked kind of nice.
He's a bit more than that.
Are you and him...?
Sometimes, I think he likes me, but...
sometimes I just think
he needs someone with him.
I never even asked.
Where's home?
It's a long way away.
I didn't really think,
I just followed the Doctor, and...
They don't even know where I am,
my mum and dad.
If I died here, they'd never know.
So, um, who is he, then,
this Doctor?
I don't know.
Well, not really.
There's so much he never says.
But that means that...
the only hope, right now, is. . .
a complete stranger.
Well, that's no use.
It is, though,
because you haven't seen the things he can do.
Honestly,
just trust me,
both of you.
You've got your faith,
you've got your songs and your hymns.
And I've got the Doctor.
Right.
'Systems back on line.'
Good luck.
And you.
Car 465 Diamond 6,
it still registers! That's Martha.
I knew she was good!
Novice Hame,
hold that in place.
Think, think, think! Take the
residual energy, invert it,  feed
it through the Electricity Beds.
There isn't the power.
You've got power. You've got me!
I'm brilliant with computers.
Just, just watch!
Hame, every switch on that bank,
up to maximum!
I can't power up the City,
but all the City needs is people.
So what are you going to do?
This!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
The transformers are blocked,
the signal can't get through.
Doctor...
Yeah, hold on, not now.
I give you my last...
Hame, look after him.
Don't you go dying on me,
you big old face!
You've got to see this.
The open road! Hah!
What in Jehovah was that?!
It's coming from above.
What is it? What's happening?
Hold on, May.
By all the Cats in the Kingdom...!
What is it?
It's the sun!
Oh, Brannigan!
Children!
It's the sunlight.
Sorry, no Sally Calypso,
she was just a hologram.
My name's the Doctor.
He's a magician.
And this is an order.
Everyone, drive up!
- Right now!
- Is he serious?
I've opened the roof of the
Motorway, come on!
Throttle those engines. Drive up,
all of you. The whole Undercity. Drive up,
drive up,
Here we go.
drive up!
We've got to clear that Fast Lane.
Drive up and get out of the way.
Oi! Car 465 Diamond 6.
Martha,
drive up!
That's the Doctor!
We can't go up, we'll hit the layer.
Do as he says, go up!
You've got access above!
Now, go!
It's daylight!
Oh, my God,
that's the sky, the real sky!
He did it!
I told you, he did it!
Did I tell you, Doctor?
You're not bad, sir. You're not bad at all!
You keep driving, Brannigan,
all the way up!
Cos it's here,
just waiting for you,
the City of New New York.
And it's yours.
And don't forget, I want that coat back.
'I reckon that's a fair bargain, sir.'
And Car 465 Diamond 6,
I've sent you a flight path.
Come to the Senate.
'On my way!'
It's been quite a while since
I saw you, Martha Jones.
Doctor!
Over here.
Doctor, what happened out there?
What's that?
The Face of Boe. It's all right.
Come and say hello.
And this is Hame,
she's a cat. Don't worry.
He's the one that saved you, not me.
My lord gave his life . . .
to save the City.
And now he's dying.
No, don't say that.
Not old Boe. Plenty of life left.
It's good to breathe the air once more.
Who is he?
I don't even know.
Legend says the Face of Boe
has lived for billions of years.
Isn't that right?
And you're not about to give up now.
Everything has its time.
You know that,
old friend, better than most.
The legend says more.
Don't, there's no need for that.
It says the Face of Boe will speak
his final secret . . .
to a traveller.
Yeah, but not yet.
Who needs secrets, eh?
I have seen so much.
Perhaps too much.
I am the last of my kind...
..as you are the last of yours, Doctor.
That's why we have to survive.
Both of us.
Don't go.
I must.
But know this, Time Lord.
YOU are not . . .
alone.
All closed down.
Happy?
Happy happy.
New New York can start again.
And they've got Novice Hame.
Just what every city needs - cats in charge!
Come on, time we were off.
But what did he mean,
the Face of Boe?
You're not alone.
I don't know.
You've got me,
is that what he meant?
I don't think so.
Sorry.
Then what?
Doesn't matter.
Back to the TARDIS, off we go.
All right. You staying?
Till you talk to me properly, yes.
He said "last of your kind".
What does that mean?
It really doesn't matter.
You don't talk. You never say.
Why not?
# Fast falls the eventide... #
It's the city.
# . . .The darkness . . .#
They're singing.
#. . .deepens. . . #
# Lord, with me abide
# When other helpers fail... #
I lied to you...
cos I liked it.
I could pretend.
Just for a bit, I could
imagine they were still alive,
underneath a burnt orange sky.
I'm not just a Time Lord.
I'm the last of the Time Lords.
The Face of Boe was wrong,
there's no-one else.
What happened?
There was a war.
A Time War -
the Last Great Time War.
My people fought a race
called the Daleks,
for the sake of all creation.
And they lost.
We lost,
everyone lost.
They're all gone now.
My family,
my friends,
even that sky.
Oh, you should've seen it,
that old planet.
The second sun would
rise in the south,
and the mountains would shine.
The leaves on the trees were silver,
and when they caught the light every morning,
it looked like a forest on fire.
When the autumn came,
# . . .The darkness deepens. . . #
-the breeze would blow through the branches
like a song...
# Lord, with me abide... #
It's the Statue of Liberty.
I always wanted to go to New York.
It's the Depression, sweetie.
Your heart might break
but the show goes on.
"Hooverville mystery deepens".
Arm yourselves!
Come on!
Who are we working for?
Behold your masters!
What do you mean, "creatures"?
What the hell was that?
Doctor!
RUN!
Hands in the air and no funny business.
Where's Martha?
He's insane! He's inhuman!
They always survive, while I lose everything.