Get down! Aargh! They're
following us! And the good news is?
Their lifespans are running out so
we wait for them to die. I must stop
being a Time Lord and become human.
Chameleon arch, rewrites my biology.
Journal of impossible things,
such imagination.
It's become quite a hobby!
He's different from any man
you've ever met, right? Yes.
He had to go and fall in love
with a human and it wasn't me.
If they find us, Martha,
open the watch.
Sometimes I say things,
they turn out to be correct.
Arghhh!
They found us.
Oh, my God, where's the watch.
What are you talking about?
This is not you, this is 1913.
Change back!
Arghh!
We need a Time Lord.
Which one of them do you want us
to kill?
Doesn't this scare you enough
to change back?
Your friend or your lover?
Make your decision, Mr Smith.
Perhaps if that human heart
breaks, the Time Lord will emerge.
Time Lord...
TICKING
All right!
One more move and I shoot. Oh,
the maid is full of fire!
And you can shut up!
Careful, Son of Mine.
This is all for you, so that you
can live forever. Shoot you down.
Try it. We'll die together.
Would you really pull the trigger?
You look too scared.
Scared and holding a gun's a good
combination! Want to risk it?
Doctor,
get everyone out, there's a door at
the side, it's over there, go on,
Do it. Mr Smith, I mean you!
Do what she said.
Everybody out! Now!
Don't argue, Mr Jackson, they're mad,
that's all we need to know. Susan,
Miss Cooper, outside, all of you!
THEY SCREAM
Back to the school, quickly.
And you, go on, just shift.
What about you?
Mr Smith, I think you should
escort your lady friend
to safety, don't you?
Get everyone out!... Latimer,
get back to the school, tell the
Headmaster...
Don't touch me!
You're as bad as them!
Don't try anything! I'm warning
you, or Sonny Boy gets it. She's
almost brave, this one.
I should have taken her form. Much
more fun. So much spirit.
What happened to jenny? Is she gone?
She is consumed. Her body's mine.
You mean she's dead? Yes! And she
went with precious little dignity.
All that "aah!" - screaming!
Get the gun!
Good work.
Don't just stand there! Move! God,
you're rubbish as a human, come on!
PEOPLE SCREAMING
EXPLOSIONS
Run! Oh, this is super! We've been
hiding for too long, this is sport!
I can smell the schoolteacher,
he's gone back to his academy.
And what do we know about her?
This body has traces of memory.
Was once her friend.
Martha would go walking to the west.
Husband of Mine, follow
the maid's scent, go to the west.
Find out what she
was keeping secret.
Soldiers!
As for you, Mother of Mine...
...let's go to school.
RINGS BELL
What are you doing?! Maybe I can't
fight them. But this school teaches
us to stand together! Take arms!
You can't do that. You want me to
fight, don't you? Take arms!
Take arms! Take arms!
I say, sir! What's the matter?
Enemy at the door, Hutchinson!
Enemy at the door! Take arms!
They're sounding the alarms! I
wouldn't be so pleased, Son of Mine.
These bodies can damage and die,
that's why we need the Time Lord.
Indeed, they will have guns.
Perhaps a little caution.
Sister of Mine.
You're such a small little thing.
Find a way in and spy on them.
We can't do this, Doctor! Mr Smith?
Redford, maintain position,
faster now. They're boys!
They don't stand a chance.
They are cadets, trained to defend
the King and all properties.
What in thunder's name is this?!
Before I devise an excellent and
endless series of punishments for
each and every one of you, could
someone explain, very simply, and
immediately, exactly is going on?
Headmaster, I have to report the
school is under attack. Really? Is
that so?
Perhaps we should have a word in
private. Sir, I was in the village,
with Matron.
It's Baines, sir, Jeremy Baines, and
Mr Clark, from Oakham Farm, they've
gone mad, sir, they've got guns.
They've already murdered people
in the village, I saw it happen.
Matron? Is that so? I'm afraid it's
true, sir. Murder? On our own soil?
I saw it, yes.
Perhaps you did well then, Mr Smith.
What makes you think the
danger's coming here?
Well... they said, uh...
Baines threatened Mr Smith, sir.
Said he'd follow him.
We don't know why. Very well.
You boys, remain on guard.
Mr Snell, telephone for the police.
Mr Phillips, with me.
We shall investigate.
But it's not safe out there.
Mr Smith, it seems your favourite
servant is giving me advice. You
will control her, sir.
Gotta find that watch.
'Hold me, keep me safe,
keep me dark.
'And keep me closed -
the time is not right.
'Not yet,
not while The Family is abroad.
'Danger.'
So... Baines
and one of the cleaning staff,
there's always a woman involved.
Am I to gather that some practical
joke has got out of hand?
Headmaster, sir! Good evening, sir!
Come to give me a caning, sir,
would you like that, sir?
Keep a civil tongue.
Come on, everyone, I suspect
alcohol's played its part in this.
Let’s just calm down. And who
are these friends of yours, Baines?
In fancy dress?
D'you like them, Mr Phillips?
Look.
S'called molecular
fringe animation!
Fashioned in the shape of straw men.
My own private army!
S'ever so good, sir!
Baines, step apart and
come inside with me.
No sir, you sir,
YOU will send us Mr john Smith.
That's all we want, sir, Mr john
Smith and whatever he's done with
his Time Lord consciousness,
then we'll be very happy
to leave you alone.
You speak with someone else's
voice, Baines. Who might that be?
We are the Family of Blood.
Mr Smith said there had been deaths.
Yes, sir! And they were good, sir!
Well, I warn you. The school is
armed. All your little tin soldiers!
But tell me, sir...
will they thank you?
I don't understand.
What do you know of history, sir?
What d'you know of next year?
You're not making sense. 1914, sir.
Because the Family has travelled
far and wide, looking for Mr Smith,
and oh, the things we have seen.
War is coming.
In foreign fields. War of the
whole wide world, with all your
boys falling down in the mud.
Do you think they will thank the
man who taught them it was glorious?
Don't you forget, boy.
I've been a soldier.
I was in South Africa.
I used my dead mates for sandbags.
I fought with the butt of my rifle
when the bullets ran out,
and I would go back there tomorrow
for King and Country.
Etcetera... etcetera.
HE SCREAMS
Run along, Headmaster. Run back
to school. And send us Mr Smith!
LAUGHTER
Mr Phillips has been murdered,
Mr Smith. Can you tell me why?
Honestly, sir, I have no idea.
And the telephone line's been
disconnected. We're on our own.
If we have to make a fight of it,
then make a fight we shall.
Hutchinson! We'll build a
barricade within the courtyards!
Fortify the entrances!
Build defences!
Gentlemen, in the name of the King,
we shall stand against them!
Yes, sir!
Barricade the kitchens,
secure the passageway to the stables.
You little coward.
You'll do your duty, Latimer.
With the rest of us!
Sandbags to the north and west!
Williams, you take charge!
Quickly now...
Pemberton, load the spare magazines
with bullets!
Take the magazine cut-off out!
They've got an army...
...So do we.
Soldiers!
SOLDIERS!
Ashington, we need water
for the Vickers Gun, see to it!
Faster, all of you! Faster.
Lockley, when firing commences,
you're in charge of the gathering.
Peterson, that's not acceptable,
report to your senior officer.
War comes to England,
a year in advance.
'Family of Mine, wait.
'Hold the soldiers back. The Time
Lord is playing some sort of trick.'
'Discover him, Sister of Mine.'
I know it sounds mad! But
when the Doctor became human,
he took the alien part of himself,
and stored it inside the watch.
It's not a watch,
it just looks like a watch.
And "alien" means?
Not from abroad, I take it?
The man you call john Smith.
He was born on another world.
A different species? Yeah.
Then tell me.
In this fairy tale... who are you?
Just a friend, I'm not...
I mean, you haven't got a rival!
As much as I might...
just his friend.
And... human, I take it?
Human, don't worry! And,
I don't just follow him around,
I'm training to be a doctor...
Not an alien doctor, a proper
doctor, a doctor of medicine.
Well, that is nonsense.
Women might train to be doctors,
but hardly the skivvy. And hardly
one of your colour.
Oh, d'you think?
Bones of the hand.
Carpal bones, proximal row,
scaphoid, lunate, triquetrum,
pisiform, distal row, trapezium,
trapezoid, capitate, hamate,
then the metacarpal bones,
extending in three distinct
phalanges, proximal, middle, distal.
You read that in a book.
Yes! To pass my exams!
Can't you see? This is true.
I must go. If we find that
watch, then we can stop them.
Those boys are going to fight.
I might not be a doctor, but I'm
still their nurse. They need me.
Son of Mine, Wife of Mine. 'Father
of Mine, what have you found?'
His Tardis!
The Doctor can't escape.
You're with Armitage and
Thwaites, they know the drill.
Joan, it's not safe.
I'm doing my duty,
just as much as you.
Fine evening we've had together.
Not quite as planned.
Tell me about Nottingham.
I'm sorry?
That's where you were brought up.
Tell me about it.
Well... It lies on the River Leen,
with its southern boundary following
the course of the River Trent, which
flows from Stoke to the Humber.
That sounds like an encyclopaedia.
Where did you live?
Broadmarsh Street. Adjacent to
Hockley Terrace, in the district of
Radford Parade. But more than facts.
When you were a child,
where did you play?
All those secret little places,
the dens and hideaways
that only a child knows.
Tell me, john, please tell me.
How can you think I'm not real?
When I kissed you, was that a lie?
No, it wasn't, no.
But this Doctor, sounds like some,
some romantic lost prince.
Would you rather that?
Am I not enough? No, that's
not true. Never. I've got to go.
Martha was right about one thing,
though. Those boys, they're children.
John Smith wouldn't want them
to fight, never mind the Doctor,
the john Smith I was getting to know.
He knows it's wrong.
Doesn't he? Mr Smith, if you please.
What choice do I have?
Get those bags piled up, filth,
they'll be the difference
between life and death for us!
Not for you and me.
What are you babbling about?
We go to battle together.
We fight alongside.
I've seen it. But not here, not now.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means that you and
I both survive this.
And maybe I was given this watch...
so I could help.
I'm sorry.
Latimer! You filthy coward!
Yes, sir. Every time.
What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
'Beware. ' Beware of what? 'Her.'
Keep away. Who are you?
I saw you at the dance.
You were with that family,
you're one of them.
What are you hiding? Nothing.
What have you got there? Nothing.
Show me, little boy.
I reckon whatever you are,
you're still in the shape of a girl.
How strong is she, d'you think?
Does she really want to see this?!
Time Lord! Inside the device!
Everything he is. Concealed away.
In the hands of a schoolboy.
But now we know. That's all we need
to find - the boy, and the watch.
What are we waiting for?!
Attaaaaack!
Stand to!
THUDDING AND CRASHING
At post! Enemy approaching, sir.
Steady. Find the biting point...
PANICKED BREATHING
CRASHING
Fire!
LOUD GUNFIRE
RAT-A-TAT OF MACHINE GUN
CHOIR SINGS
Cease fire!
Just straw.
Like he said.
Straw. Then no-one's dead, sir.
We killed no-one.
Stand to!
You child, come out of the way.
Come into the school,
we don't know who's out there.
It's the Cartwright girl, isn't it?
Come here, come to me.
Mr Rocastle, please.
Don't go near her.
You were told to be quiet.
Just listen to me. She's part of it.
Matron, tell him.
I don't know, I think you should
stay back, Headmaster. Mr Smith...
She was...
She was with Baines, in the village.
Mr Smith, I've seen many
strange sights this night.
But there is no cause on God's Earth
that would allow me to see this
child in the field of battle, sir.
Come with me. You're funny.
That's right. Now take my hand.
So funny.
HE SCREAMS
Now who's going to shoot me?
Any of you? Really?
Put down your guns.
But, sir. The Headmaster...
I'll not see this happen.
Not any more.
You will retreat. In an orderly
fashion. Back through the school.
Hutchinson, lead the way.
But sir... I said, lead the way.
Well, go on then, run!
Soldiers! Come on! Reanimate!
PANICKED SHOUTING
Out you go, quick as you can.
Don't go to the village,
it's not safe. And you, ladies.
Not till we've got the boys out.
One of these boys has got the watch.
This one?
No. This one? No.
This one? No. Get off me!
I said get off!
This one, is that him?
No.
Right, then we can kill this lot.
'Lord of time.' That's him!
Upstairs.
Don't just stand there.
Outside, come on, out!
I insist, the pair of you, just go.
If there are any more boys inside,
I'll find them.
I think... retreat!
Doctor!
Doc-taaaar!
Come back, Doctor! Come home!
Come and claim your prize!
Out you come, Doctor!
There's a good boy!
Come to the family!
Time to end it, now!
You recognise it, don't you?
Come out, Doctor!
Come to us.
I've never seen it in my life.
Do you remember its name?
I'm sorry, john,
but you wrote about it.
The blue box,
you dreamt of a blue box.
I'm not...
I'm john Smith.
That's all I want to be. John Smith.
With his life. And his job.
And his love. Why can't I be
john Smith? Isn't he a good man?
Yes, yes, he is. Why can't I stay?
But we need the Doctor.
And who am I, then? Nothing?
I'm just a story?
One more phase, and
we won't have to hunt.
The Doctor, Mr Smith,
the boy, the watch -
they will come to us!
Soldiers, guard this thing!
This way!
I think I know somewhere we can hide.
We've got to keep going. Just listen
to me for once, john, follow me!
Power up! Fully armed and ready.
Mother and Father
and Sister of Mine,
prepare the armaments.
I doubt that England
is ready for this.
Fix targets. And counting down.
Here we are. It should be empty.
Oh, it's a long time
since I've run that far!
- But who lives here?
- If I'm right... no-one.
Hello?
No-one home.
We should be safe here.
Whose house is it, though?
The Cartwright’s', that little
girl at the school,
she's Lucy Cartwright.
Or she's taken
Lucy Cartwright's form.
If she came home this
afternoon, and if the parents
How easily I accept these ideas.
I must go to them.
Before anyone else dies.
You can't! Martha, there
must be something we can do.
Not without the watch. You're this
Doctor's companion, can't you help?!
What exactly d'you do for him?
Why does he need you?
Because he's lonely.
And that's what you
want me to become?
KNOCK ON DOOR
What if it's them?
I'm not an expert, but I
don't think scarecrows knock.
I brought you this.
Hold it. I won't.
Please. Just hold it.
It told me to find you,
it wants to be held.
You've had this watch all this time,
why didn't you return it?
Because it was waiting,
then because I was so scared.
Of the Doctor. Why?
Because... I've seen him.
He's like fire. And ice. And rage.
He's like the night and
the storm and the heart of the sun.
Stop it. He's ancient and forever.
He burns at the centre of time, and
he can see the turn of the universe.
Stop it, I said stop it.
And he's wonderful.
I've still got this - the journal.
Those are just stories.
Now we know that's not true.
Perhaps there's something in here.
LOUD EXPLOSION
What the hell?
This'll flush him out.
This'll do it. Super, super fun!
They're destroying the village.
The watch. John, don't.
Can you hear it?
FAINT VOICE MURMURS
Like he's asleep.
Waiting to waken.
Why did he speak to me?
Oh, low level telepathic field,
you were born with it,
just an extra synaptic engram,
causing...
Is that how he talks?
That's him. All you have to do
is open it, and he's back.
You knew this. And yet you
watched, while Miss Redfern and I...
I didn't know how to stop you.
He gave me a list of things to watch
out for, but that wasn't included!
Falling in love.
That didn't even occur to him?
No.
Then what sort of man is that?
And now you expect me to die?
It was always gonna end.
The Doctor said, the Family's got
a limited lifespan, that's why
they need to consume a Time Lord.
Otherwise, three months,
and they die.
Like mayflies, he said.
So your job was to execute me.
People are dying out there!
They need him. And I need him.
Cos you've got no idea what he's
like. I've only just met him.
It wasn't even that long ago, but...
He is everything.
He’s just everything to me,
and he doesn't even look
at me but I don't care,
cos I love him to bits, and I hope to
God he won't remember me saying this.
LOUDER EXPLOSION
It's getting closer.
I should have thought of it before!
I can give them this!
Just the watch! Then they can
leave and I can stay as I am!
You can't do that! If they want
the Doctor, they can have him!
He'll never let you do it.
If they get what they want, then...
Then it all ends in destruction.
I never read to the end.
Those creatures would live forever.
To breed and conquer. War,
across the stars. For every child.
Martha. Timothy.
Could you leave us alone, please?
SHELLS WHISTLE OVERHEAD
If I could do this instead of you,
then I would.
But my hopes aren't important.
He won't love you.
If he's not you, then
I don't want him to.
I had one husband and he died,
and I never thought, ever again...
And then you...
You were so... And it was real,
I wasn't.
I really thought...
Let me see. Blasted thing.
Blasted, blasted thing.
I can't even hear it.
Says nothing to me.
BABY CRIES
LAUGHTER
They're all safe, aren't they?
The children.
The grandchildren.
Everyone's safe? Everyone's safe.
And they all send their love, john.
Well, then. It's done.
Thank you.
Did you see?
The Time Lord has such adventures.
But he could never have a life
like that. And yet I could.
What are you going to do?
We'll blast them into dust,
then fuse the dust into glass,
then shatter them all over again.
FOOTSTEPS
just...
PINGING NOISES
just stop the bombardment,
That's all I ask. I'll do
anything you want, just stop.
Say please.
Please.
Wait a minute...
Still human.
I can't pretend to understand,
not for a second. But I want you
to know, I'm innocent in all this.
He made me john Smith, it's not
like I had any control over it.
He didn't just make himself human,
he made himself an idiot.
Same thing, isn't it?
I don't care about this Doctor, and
your Family, I just want you to go.
So I've made my choice.
You can have him,
just take it, please, take him away.
At last.
Don't think that's saved your life.
Family of Mine.
Now we shall have the
lives of a Time Lord.
It's empty. Where's he gone?
You tell me.
Oh, I think the explanation
might be you've been fooled by a
simple olfactory misdirection.
A little bit like ventriloquism of
the nose. It's an elementary trick
in certain parts of the galaxy.
And it's got to be said,
I don't like the look
of that hydrokinometer.
It seems to be indicating you've got
energy feedback all the way through
the retro-stabilisers feeding back
into the primary heat converters.
Cos if there's one thing
you shouldn't have done,
you shouldn't have let me
press all those buttons.
But, in fairness,
I will give you one word of advice.
Run.
Get out! Get out!
WARNING ALARMS WAIL
ALARMS ESCALATE
ALARMS REACH CRESCENDO
'He never raised his voice.
That was the worst thing.
'The fury of the Time Lord.
'And then we discovered why.
'Why this Doctor, who'd fought
with Gods and Demons, why he'd run
away from us, and hidden.
'He was being kind.'
HE SCREAMS
'He wrapped my father in
unbreakable chains, forged in
the heart of a dwarf star.
'He tricked my mother into the event
horizon of a collapsing galaxy.
'To be imprisoned there... forever.'
'He still visits my sister,
once a year, every year.
'I wonder if one day he might
forgive her, but there she is.
'Can you see her?
He trapped her inside a mirror.
'Every mirror. If ever you look at
your reflection, and see something
move behind you, just for a second.
'That's her. That's always her.'
'As for me I was suspended in time.
'And the Doctor put me to work,
standing over the fields of England
'as their protector.
'We wanted to live forever.
'So the Doctor made
sure that we did.'
Is it done?
It's done.
The police and the
army are at school.
Parents have come,
to take the boys home.
I should go,
they'll have so many questions,
I'm not sure what to say.
Oh.
You look the same.
Goodness!
You must forgive my rudeness.
John Smith? He's in here somewhere.
Like a story.
Could you change back? Yes.
Will you?
No.
I see.
Well, then.
He was braver than you, in the end.
That ordinary man...
...you chose to change,
he chose to die.
Come with me. I'm sorry?
Travel with me.
As what? My companion.
Oh, but that's not fair.
What must I look like to you, Doctor?
I must seem so very small.
No. We could start again.
I'd like that.
You and me, we could try, at least.
Cos everything that john Smith
is and was,
I can't.
Please come with me. I can't.
Why not?
John Smith is dead.
And you look like him.
But he's here.
Inside.
If you look in my eyes.
Answer me this.
Just one question, that's all.
If the Doctor
had never visited us, if...
he'd never chosen this place,
on a whim...
Would anyone here have died?
(You can go.)
Right then. Molto bene!
How was she?
Time we moved on.
If you want, I could go and...
Um. Meant to say.
Back there, last night, I would've
said anything to get you to change.
Yeah, course you would.
I wasn't really...
No! No, no. Good! Fine!
So there we are, then.
There we are then, yes.
And I never said.
Thanks for looking after me.
Doctor! Martha!
Tim, Timothy, Tim!
I just wanted to say goodbye,
and thank you,
because I've seen the future,
and I now know what must be done.
It's coming, isn't it?
The biggest war ever.
You don't have to fight.
I think we do.
But you could get hurt.
Well, so could you,
travelling around with him.
But it's not going to stop you!
Tim.
I'd be honoured if you'd take this.
I can't hear anything.
No, it’s just a watch, now.
But keep it with you. For good luck.
Look after yourself.
You'll like this bit.
METALLIC THRUMMING
SHELLS WHISTLE
Incoming!
'In June 1914, an Archduke of
Austria was shot by a Serbian.
'And this then led, through nations
having treaties with nations,
like a line of dominoes falling,
'to some boys from England
walking together in France,
'on a terrible day...'
One minute past the hour. It's now.
Hutchinson, this is the time.
It's now.
SHELL WHISTLES
To the right... To the right.
We made it.
Thank you, Doctor.
Come on, old chap.
Leave me. Not gonna make it.
Oh, yes, you are. Didn't I
promise you, all those years ago?
Now come on! That's an order!
SHELLS WHISTLE AND EXPLODE
VICAR READS
They went with songs to the battle.
They were young, straight of limb,
true of eye, steady and aglow.
They were staunch to the end
against odds uncounted.
They fell with their faces
to the foe.
They shall grow not old, as
we that are left grow old.
Age shall not weary them,
nor the years condemn.
At the going down of the sun
and in the morning,
we will remember them.
Don't blink. Blink and you're dead.
Don't turn your back.
Don't look away.
And don't blink.
Good luck.