Kathy?
(voice from television)
Your life could depend on this.
Don't blink!
Don't even blink.
Blink and you're dead.
They are fast,
faster than you can believe.
Don't turn your back,
don't look away, and don't blink.
Good luck.
PHONE RINGS
Hello?
Bit freaked.
Need to talk. Making you a coffee.
(Kathy)
Sally Sparrow,
it's one in the morning.
You think I'm coming round
at one in the morning?
No.
(Sally)
I'm in the kitchen.
What's that on all those
screens in your front room?
Oh, God!
Oh, God! Sally, you've met
my brother Larry, haven't you?
-No.
-You're about to.
(Larry)
OK.
Not sure, but really, really hoping.
-Pants?
-No.
(Kathy)
Put them on! Put them on!
I hate you! What were you thinking?!
Sorry.
My useless brother.
Sally! What's wrong?
What's happened?
(Kathy)
OK! Let's investigate!
You and me, girl investigators.
Love it!
Hey! Sparrow and Nightingale!
-That SO works!
-Bit ITV.
I know!
(Kathy)
What did you come here for, anyway?
(Sally)
I love old things.
They make me feel sad.
(Kathy)
What's good about sad?
(Sally)
It's happy for deep people.
The weeping angel.
(Kathy)
Wouldn't have that in my garden.
It's moved.
It's what?
Since yesterday.
I'm sure of it. It's closer.
It's got closer to the house.
(Sally)
How can my name be written here?
How is that possible?
DOORBELL RINGS
Who'd come here?
What are you doing?!
It could be a burglar!
A burglar who rings the doorbell(?)
OK. I'll stay here in case of...
-In case of...?
-..incidents?
I'm looking for Sally Sparrow.
How did you know I'd be here?
I was told to bring this letter
on this date at this exact time
to Sally Sparrow.
-It looks old.
-It is old.
I'm sorry, do you have anything
with a photograph on it,
like a driving licence?
(Sally)
How did he know I was coming here?
I didn't tell anyone.
How could anyone know?
(Man)
It's all a bit complicated.
I'm not sure I understand it myself.
(Man)
I'm sorry, I feel really stupid, but
I was told to make absolutely sure.
It's so hard to tell with these
little photographs, isn't it?
(Sally)
Apparently.
Well, here goes, I suppose.
(Man)
Funny feeling,
after all these years.
Who's it from?
Well, that's a long story, actually.
Gimme a name.
Katherine Wainwright.
But she specified I should tell
you that prior to marriage
she was called Kathy Nightingale.
-Kathy?
-Kathy, yes.
-Katherine Costello Nightingale.
-Is this a joke?
A joke?!
Kathy, is this you? Very funny(!)
Kathy?
COWS MOO
Kathy? Kathy!
Please, you need to take this.
I promised.
(Kathy)
Excuse me?
Where am I?
I was in London.
-I was in the middle of London.
-You're in Hull.
No, I'm not.
-This is Hull.
-No, it isn't.
You're in Hull.
I'm not in Hull. Stop saying Hull.
(Sally)
Who are you?
Why are you here?
-I made a promise.
-Who to?
My grandmother.
Katherine Costello Nightingale.
(young man)
Don't have that in London. There's
no call for it. It's all Hull.
(Kathy)
1920?
-Your grandmother?
-Yes.
She died 20 years ago.
-So they're related?
-I'm sorry?
My Kathy, your grandmother -
they're practically identical.
Where are you going?
"My dearest Sally Sparrow,
"if my grandson
has done as he promises he will,
"then as you read these words
it has been mere minutes
since we last spoke. For you.
"For me, it has been over 60 years.
"The third of the
photographs is of my children.
"The youngest is Sally.
"I named her after you, of course."
This is sick!
This is totally sick!
Kathy? Kathy!
Kathy?
No, wait! Hang on!
"I suppose, unless I live
to a really exceptional old age,
"I will be long gone
as you read this.
"Don't feel sorry for me.
I have led a good and full life.
"I've loved a good man
and been well loved in return.
"You would have liked Ben.
"He was the very first person
I met in 1920."
(Kathy)
Are you following me?
(Ben)
Yeah.
(Kathy)
Are you going to stop following me?
(Ben)
No, I don't think so.
"To take one breath in 2007
and the next in 1920
"is a strange way
to start a new life,
"but a new life
is exactly what I've always wanted."
1902?
You told him you were 18?
You lying cow!
"My mum and dad are gone
by your time, so really
there's only Lawrence to tell.
"He works at the DVD store
on Queen Street.
"I don't know what you're going
to say to him, but I know
you'll think of something.
"Just tell him I love him."
Excuse me, I'm looking
for Lawrence Nightingale.
Through the back.
Hello?
Quite possibly.
'Fraid so.
Oh. Hello.
Can I help you?
Sally: Hi.
Doctor: 38.
Er, just a mo.
Hang on. We've met, haven't we?
It'll come to you.
Oh, my God!
-There it is.
-Sorry.  Sorry again about the whole...
-Message from your sister.
-Oh! OK!
What?
What is it? What's the message?
She's had to go away for a bit.
-Where?
-Just a work thing.
Nothing to worry about.
-OK.
-And...
And what?
She loves you.
She what?!
She said to say.
She just sort of mentioned it.
She loves you.
There, that's nice, isn't it?
-Is she ill?
-No! No.
-Am I ill?
-No!
-Is this a trick?
-No. She loves you.
(Doctor on TV)
People don't understand time.
It's not what you think it is.
Who is this guy?
Sorry, the pause thing
keeps slipping. Stupid thing.
Last night at Kathy's, you had him
on those screens. That same guy.
Talking about,
I dunno, blinking or something.
Yeah, the bit about
the blinking's great!
I was checking to see
if they were all the same.
What were the same? What is this?
Who is he?
An Easter egg.
Excuse me?
Like a DVD extra, yeah?
You know how on DVDs they put
extras on, documentaries and stuff?
Sometimes they put on hidden ones,
and they call them Easter eggs.
You have to look for them,
follow clues in the menu screen.
(Doctor on TV)
Complicated.
(Larry)
Sorry.
It's interesting, actually.
He is on 17 different DVDs.
There are 17 totally unrelated
DVDs, all with him on,
always hidden away, always a secret.
Not even the publishers know
how he got there.
I've talked to the manufacturers,
right? They don't even know.
It's like he's a ghost DVD extra.
Just shows up
where he's not supposed to be.
But only on those. Those 17.
Well, what does he do?
Just sits there
making random remarks.
It's like we're hearing
half a conversation.
Me and the guys are always
trying to work out the other half.
When you say you and the guys,
you mean the internet, don't you?
-How do you know?
-Spooky, isn't it?
Very complicated.
(man at counter)
Florence? Need you!
'Scuse me a sec.
People assume that time is a strict
progression of cause to effect,
but actually from a non-linear,
non-subjective viewpoint,
it's more like a big ball of
wibbly-wobbly, timey-wimey stuff.
Started well, that sentence.
It got away from me, yeah.
OK, that was weird.
(Sally)
Like you can hear me.
Well, I CAN hear you.
OK, that's enough.
I've had enough now. I've had a
long day and I've had bloody enough!
Sorry.
Bad day.
Got you the list.
What?
The 17 DVDs.
I thought you might be interested.
Yeah, great, thanks!
(man at counter)
Go to the police, you stupid woman!
Why does nobody ever
just go to the police?
(Sally)
Look, I know how mad I'm sounding.
Shall we try it from the beginning?
OK. There's this house,
a big old house,
been empty for years, falling apart.
Wester Drumlins, out by the estate.
You've probably seen it.
-Wester Drumlins?
-Yes.
Could you just
wait here for a minute?
SHE SIGHS
THUNDER RUMBLES
OK, cracking up now.
Hi. DI Billy Shipton.
Wester Drumlins, that's mine.
Can't talk to you now,
got a thing I can't be late for,
so if you could just...
Hello!
Hello.
Er, Marcie, can you tell them
I'm gonna be late for that thing?
Sally:All of them?
Billy: Over the last two years, yeah.
(Billy)
They all still had personal items in them
and a couple still had the motor running.
(Sally)
So over the last two years the
owners of all of these vehicles have
driven up to Wester Drumlins House,
parked outside and just disappeared.
(Sally)
What's that?
(Billy)
Ah! The pride of the
Wester Drumlins collection.
We found that there, too. Somebody's
idea of a joke, I suppose.
But what is it? What's a police box?
Well, it's a special kind
of phone box for policemen.
They used to have them all over.
But this isn't a real one.
The phone's just a dummy, and
the windows are the wrong size.
We can't even get in it.
Ordinary Yale lock,
but nothing fits.
But that's not the big question.
See,
you're missing the big question.
OK, what's the big question?
Will you have a drink with me?
I'm sorry?
Drink, you, me, now?
Aren't you on duty,
Detective Inspector Shipton?
Nope. Knocked off before I left.
Told 'em I had a family crisis.
-Why?
-Because life is short and you are hot.
-Drink?
-No.
-Ever?
-Maybe.
Phone number?
Moving kind of fast, DI Shipton.
Billy. I'm off duty.
Aren't you just!
Is that your phone number?
Just my phone number.
Not a promise, not a guarantee,
not an IOU, just a phone number.
-And that's Sally...?
-Sally Shipton. Sparrow!
Sally Sparrow.
I'm going now. Don't look at me.
-I'll phone you!
-Don't look at me.
-Phone you tomorrow.
-Don't look at me!
Might even phone you tonight.
-Definitely gonna phone you, gorgeous girl!
(Sally)
You definitely better!
Ordinary Yale lock,
but nothing fits.
(Doctor)
Welcome.
(Billy)
Where am I?
(Doctor)
1969. Not bad,as it goes. You've got
the moon landing to look forward to.
Oh, the moon landing's brilliant.
We went four times.
-Back when we had transport...
-Working on it!
-How did I get here?
-The same way we did. The touch of an angel.
Same one, probably,
since you ended up in the same year.
No, don't get up.
Time travel without a capsule,
nasty. Catch your breath, don't
go swimming for half an hour.
I don't. I can't.
Fascinating race,
the weeping angels.
The only psychopaths
in the universe to kill you nicely.
No mess, no fuss,
they just zap you into the past
and let you live to death.
The rest of your life used up and
blown away in the blink of an eye.
You die in the past, and in the
present they consume the energy
of all the days you might have had,
all your stolen moments.
They're creatures of the abstract.
They live off potential energy.
What in God's name
are you talking about?
Trust me.
Just nod when he stops for breath.
Tracked you down with this.
This is my timey-wimey detector.
It goes ding when there's stuff.
Also,
it can boil an egg at 30 paces,
whether you want it to or not, so
I've learned to stay away from hens.
It's not pretty when they blow.
I don't understand. Where am I?
1969, like he says.
Normally, I'd offer you a lift
home, but somebody nicked my motor.
So I need you to take
a message to Sally Sparrow.
And I'm sorry, Billy,
I am very, very sorry.
It's going to take you a while.
PHONE RINGS
Hello?
Billy, where are you?
Where?
Billy?
It was raining when we met.
It's the same rain.
-She looks nice.
-Her name was Sally too.
(Sally)
Sally Shipton.
(Billy)
Sally Shipton!
I often thought about looking
for you before tonight,
but apparently it would've torn a
hole in the fabric of space and time
and destroyed two thirds
of the universe.
Also I'd lost my hair.
Two thirds of the universe.
Where'd you get that?
There's a man in 1969.
He sent me with a message for you.
-What man?
-The Doctor.
-And what was the message?
-Just this.
Look at the list.
What does that mean?
Is that it, look at the list?
He said you'd have it by now.
A list of 17 DVDs.
I didn't stay a policeman back then.
Got into publishing.
Then video publishing.
Then DVDs, of course.
You put the Easter Egg on?
Have you noticed what
all 17 DVDs have in common yet?
I suppose it's hard for you,
in a way.
How could the Doctor have even known
I had a list? I only just got this.
I asked him how, but he said
he couldn't tell me.
He said you'd understand it one day,
but that I never would.
Soon as I understand it,
I'll come and tell you.
No, gorgeous girl, you can't.
There's only tonight.
He told me all those years ago that
we'd only meet again this one time.
On the night I die.
Oh, Billy.
It's kept me going.
I'm an old, sick man.
But I've had something to look
forward to.
Ah, life is long.
And you are hot.
Oh, look at my hands.
They're old man's hands.
How did that happen?
I'll stay.
I'm going to stay with you. OK?
Thank you, Sally Sparrow.
I have till the rain stops.
PHONE RINGS
Banto's.
Sally: They're mine.
Larry: What?
The DVDs on the list. The 17 DVDs.
What they've got in common is me.
They're all the DVDs I own.
The Easter Egg was intended for me!
You've only got 17 DVDs?
Do you have a portable DVD player?
-Course, why?
-I want you to meet me.
-Where?
-Wester Drumlins.
You live in Scooby Doo's house!
For God's sake, I don't live here!
OK, this is the one
with the clearest sound.
Slightly better picture quality
on this one, but I don't...
Doesn't matter.
OK.
There he is.
The Doctor!
Who's the Doctor?
-He's the Doctor.
-Yep. That's me.
OK, that was scary.
No, it sounds like he's
replying, but he always says that.
(Doctor)
Yes, I do.
Larry: And that.
Doctor: Yep, and this.
He can hear us.
Oh, my God, you can really hear us!
Of course he can't hear us. Look!
I've got a transcript,
see, everything he says.
"Yep, that's me". "Yes, I do".
"Yep, and this". Next it's...
BOTH: Are you going to read
out the whole thing?
-Sorry.
-Who are you?
I'm a time traveller.
Or I was. I'm stuck in 1969.
We're stuck. All of space and time,
he promised me.
Now I've got a job in a shop,
I've got to support him!
-Martha!
-Sorry.
I've seen this bit before.
(Doctor)
Quite possibly.
1969, that's where you're talking from?
'Fraid so.
But you're replying to me.
You can't know exactly what I'll say,
40 years before I say it!
-38.
-I'm getting this down!
-I'm writing in your bits!!
-How? How is this possible?
-Tell me!
-Not so fast.
People don't understand time.
-It's not what you think it is.
-Then what is it?
-Complicated.
-Tell me.
Very complicated.
I'm clever and I'm listening.
And don't patronise me because
people have died, and I'm not happy.
Tell me!
People assume that time is a strict
progression of cause to effect,
but actually from a non-linear,
non-subjective viewpoint,
it's more like a big ball of
wibbly-wobbly, timey-wimey stuff.
Yeah, I've seen this bit before. You
said that sentence got away from you.
It got away from me, yeah.
Next thing you're going to say is,
"Well, I CAN hear you".
-Well, I CAN hear you.
-This isn't possible! No!
It's brilliant!
Not hear you exactly, but
I know everything you'll to say.
Always gives me the shivers, that
bit.
How can you know
what I'm going to say?
-Look to your left.
-What does he mean by, "Look to your left"?
(Larry)
I've written tons about that on the
forums. I think it's a political statement.
He means you. What are you doing?
Writing in your bits.
So I've got a complete transcript
of the whole conversation.
Wait till this hits the net.
This will explode the egg forums.
(Doctor)
I've got a copy of the finished
transcript. It's on my autocue.
How can you have a copy of the
finished transcript. It is still being written.
I told you. I'm a time traveller.
I got it in the future.
OK, let me get my head round this.
You're reading from a transcript of
a conversation you're still having?
Wibbly-wobbly, timey-wimey.
Actually, never mind that.
You can do shorthand?
So?
What matters is we can communicate.
We have got big problems now.
They've taken the blue box, haven't
they?
The angels have the phone box.
The angels have the phone box!
That's my favourite,
I have it on a T-shirt!
What do you mean, angels?
You mean those statue things?
Creatures from another world.
They're just statues.
Only when you see them.
-What does that mean?
-Lonely assassins, they were called.
No-one knows where they came from.
They're as old as the universe,
or nearly.
They've survived this long as they
have the most perfect
defence system ever evolved.
They are quantum-locked. They don't
exist when being observed.
The moment they're seen
by any living creature
they freeze into rock.
It's a fact of their biology.
In the sight of any living thing,
they literally turn to stone.
And you can't kill a stone.
Course,
a stone can't kill you either.
But then you turn your head away,
then you blink, and oh, yes, it can!
Don't take your eyes off that!
That's why they cover their eyes.
They're not weeping, they
can't risk looking at each other.
Their greatest asset
is their greatest curse.
They can never be seen.
The loneliest
creatures in the universe.
And I'm sorry, I am very,
very sorry, it's up to you now.
-What am I supposed to do?
-The blue box, my time machine.
There is a world of time energy in
there they could feast on forever.
The damage they can do
can switch off the sun.
You have got to send it back to me!
How? How??
And that's it, I'm afraid.
There's no more from you on the
transcript, that's all I've got.
I dunno what stopped you talking,
but I can guess. They're coming.
The angels are coming for you.
Listen, your life could depend on
this. Don't blink! Don't even blink.
Blink and you're dead.
They're fast, faster than you can
believe. Don't turn your back,
don't look away, and don't blink!
Good luck!
No, don't, you can't!
I'll rewind him!
What good would that do?!
You're not looking at the statue?
Neither are you.
Keep looking at it,
keep looking at it!!
(Larry)
There's just one, right,
there's just this one.
We're OK if we keep staring at this
one statue, everything will be fine.
-There's three more.
-Three?!
They were upstairs,
I think I heard them moving.
Where? Three, moving where?
I'll look around, I'm going to check.
Keep looking at this one,
don't blink.
Remember what he said,
don't even blink!
Who blinks? I'm too scared to blink.
OK. We're going to the
door. The front door.
OK. We can't both get to the door
without taking our eyes off that
thing. You stay here.
What?!
I'll be round the corner, stay here!
They've locked it.
They've locked us in!
Why?
I've got something they want.
What?
A key I took last time I was here.
They followed me to get it back.
I led them to the blue box!
Now they've got that!
Give them the key!
I'll check the back door,
you wait here.
Give them the key,
give them what they want!
(Larry)
Sally, no, what if
they come behind me?!
(Sally)
Hang on!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
(Sally)
It's locked!
Sally! Sally!
(Sally)
It won't open!
(Larry)
Sally, please, I can't do this!
Sally, hurry up!
(Larry)
Where are you?!
Larry! They've blocked off the
back door, but there's a cellar.
There might be a way out,
delivery hatch or something.
I'm coming, I can't stay here!
OK, boys, I know how this works.
You can't move
so long as I can see you.
Whole world in the box,
the Doctor says.
Hope he's not lying, cos I don't see
how else we're getting out.
Oh, and there's your one.
Why's it pointing at the...
..light?
Oh, my God! It's turning out the lights!
-Quickly! I can't find the lock!
-Sally, hurry up!
They're getting faster, Sally,
come on!
It won't turn!
Sally!
This is security protocol 712.
This time capsule has detected
the presence of an authorised
control disc, valid one journey.
Please insert the disc
and prepare for departure.
Looks like a DVD player.
There's a slot.
-They're trying to get in!
-Well, hurry up!
(Sally)
What's happening?
Oh, my God! It's leaving us behind!
Doctor, no, you can't!
THEY SCREAM
Doctor!
Look at them. Quick, look at them!
I don't think we need to.
He tricked them, The Doctor tricked
them. They're looking at each other.
They're never going to move again.
(Larry)
Can you mind the shop? I'm just
nipping next door for some milk.
Yeah, no worries.
What's this?
Nothing.
Oh, Sally!
Can't you let it go?
Of course I can't let it go!
It's over.
How did the Doctor know where
to write the words on the wall?
How could he get the transcript?
Where did he get
all that information from?
Look, some things you never find
out. And that's OK.
No, it isn't.
Ever think this might be getting
in the way of...other things?
We just run a shop together.
That's all it is, just a shop.
Anyway...
..milk.
Back in a mo.
Doctor! Doctor! Doctor!
Hello! Sorry, bit of a rush,
there's a sort of thing happening,
fairly important we stop it.
My God, it's you, it really is you.
Oh, you don't remember me, do you?
We don't have time for this!
Migration's started!
Look, sorry,
I've got a bit of a complex life.
Things don't always
happen to me in order.
Gets confusing, especially weddings,
I'm rubbish at weddings, especially
my own.
Oh, my God!
Of course, you're a time traveller.
It hasn't happened yet! None of it,
it's still in your future!
What?
Doctor! 20 minutes to red hatching!
It was me.
Oh, for God's sake, it was me
all along. You got it all from me!
-Got what?
-OK. Listen.
One day you're going
to get stuck in 1969.
Make sure you've got this with you.
You're going to need it. Doctor!
Yeah, listen,
got to dash...things happening.
Well, four things.
Well, four things and a lizard.
OK. No worries, on you go.
See you around, some day.
What was your name?
Sally Sparrow.
Good to meet you, Sally Sparrow.
Goodbye, Doctor.
Don't blink!
Blink and you're dead!
Don't turn your back.
Don't look away.
And don't blink!
Good luck!
We're going to the
end of the universe.
The call came from across the stars.
Over and over again, come to Utopia.
Doctor.
Captain.
It's the Futurekind.
-Utopia is?
-The last of the humans scattered across the night.
Humans are coming.
Not even the Time Lords
came this far. We should leave.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd