SHERWOOD FOREST
Gone to meet his Maker.
- Get rid of him.
- Just seeing if he's got a purse.
I'll show you my purse
if you show me yours.
This is an ambush.
- You don't say.
- This is how it goes.
There's poor people going hungry.
Tell us what you've got...
- be honest with us.
- And we take one tenth...
- so the poor can eat.
- Lie...
- or resist
- And we take it all.
So what's it gonna be?
Well, what have we got here?
My babies.
Get them.
- I don't wanna hurt you
- Oh, sure you was.
I've got the girl.
Time to disappear!
My gang, this way!
The woman you'll find.
Where did they go?
Gone to meet their Makers.
Take me to Nottingham. Idiots.
Come on.
- Great work, Will.
- That was nothing.
Nothing?
Jesus. I love our camp!
DEEP IN THE HEART OF ENGLEND
LIVES A LEGEND
::: ROBIN HOOD :::
Credits
Season 2 episode 1
~ SISTERHOOD ~
NOTTINGHAM CASTLE
Tell me. You would rather
have a woman, Gisborne?
Tell me, you would rather
have a woman...
than all this... power?
We are so close.
Indeed.
Talking of our lady,
leperfriend..
it's time to go get
the pretty one and her daddy.
Edward and Marian.
If they resist, shall I use force?
Get them to speak, Gisborne.
Use force anyway.
- How're we doing, Allan?
- Could have been nasty.
OUTLAW'S CAMP
- Those men were well trained.
- Woman wasn't bad.
- Nearly had you for a minute there?
- No. I doubt that.
- What's that?
- Boss-lady's ring.
I know it.
That's the Sheriff's insignia.
So what?
What, we robbed
a friend of the Sheriff.
It is more than a friend
if she shares the Sheriff's insignia.
Ah, the glamorous one.
The successful one.
So... so, how was your journey?
I ran into an old friend of yours.
Hood.
- He didn't hurt your babies?
- No.
- But I do want him caught.
- Don't worry.
Everything is in place.
Tomorrow, when our friends gather...
they gather to watch him die.
- The plan is?
- The whole garrison, 400 men.
Men is good...
But a woman... is better.
KNIGHTON HALL
And that's all I'm taking off
until you go away.
You are spoil sport, Marian.
What do you make of this?
The Sheriff's insignia.
We took it off a woman
on her way to Nottingham today.
And she had men,
and they were well trained.
It was like a military unit.
And she's been granted
the Sheriff's insignia.
- And what does that mean?
- I don't know.
I was hoping you or
your father might know.
I get the feeling we're not too
welcome in the corridors of power.
Good.
Come and join my gang.
- In your dreams.
- Wait.
Listen.
- Did you hear it?
- What?
- That kiss spoke volumes.
- Did it?
What did it say?
It said...
"Marian wants to come
and join your gang."
Really?
That's not what I heard.
What I heard was
a little voice saying...
"Abandon your home,
abandon your father...
give up any hope
of a normal life and...
take up arms with a man who thinks...
resistance is about
showing off with the bow."
- That's not fair.
- And to do what?
To wait for a king, who lets face it,
may or may not make it home.
What?
See, I've been thinking about it then.
Sir Edward, Marian!
Out, now!
Sir Guy!
- Halt there!
- I'm gonna kill him.
- You shoot first, think later.
- I will not allow this.
- Do you want my father killed?
- Marian!
Who'll give you respect,
when you do nothing?
Come down now or
I'll torch your house!
- Do you respect me?
- Don't keep me waiting!
I respect you.
- Father!
- You come when I say!
- I'm unhurt.
- What do you want?
You're coming to the castle. Sheriff
wants you, where he can see you.
No, we're not!
My father is frail, release him!
You do not tell me what to do!
- Burn the house.
- Guy, no.
- Please, sir Guy.
- Better.
Sir Guy?
Beg!
Sir Guy. Please, I beg you...
Much better.
But still not good enough.
No!
Come on! To the castle, move it!
Come on, you did it to us!
Do something!
Move out!
NOTTINGHAM TOWN
Something's up.
That is proper lockdown.
Can't just be freight with Marian.
Now, who is that?
Why not just knock on
the door and ask the Sheriff?
We're not gonna find that much standing
around here all morning, are we?
What do you recommend?
Since you ask,
I was gonna go to the tavern...
Some new tricks I wanna try,
here look at this...
- Three cups, right?
- Come on.
No, no, come on.
Robin, this is lovely. Honest.
Since when have we been
tavern tricksters, Allan?
Didn't it get all funny about Marian,
why did you let Gisborne...
- grab her in the first place?
- Be careful.
The sanctimonious old fart...
and her father.
I gather you've been callous
with the wood fire.
- You know full well that is not the case.
- Tell me...
Who's side are you on?
Mine or King Richard's?
The real world or the old world?
Yours.
Come along. We both know
that's not true, do we?
I believe in justice. I believe
in the rights of the free men.
Who cares what you believe in?
I have a plan...
and I will not tolerate descent.
So...
You are under house arrest,
here in the castle.
Until I can find some use for you.
- My Lord Sheriff, I must protest.
- You must?
My father is unwell.
He must be allowed to stay...
One more word out of you missy...
and your father
will never be unwell again.
My Lord. Another one of
our friends has arrived.
Good.
Guy!
Please.
The castle is
no place for an old man.
You think you can humiliate
a man at the altar?
A man like me, and get away with it?
You're wrong.
- Marian's in there.
- Yeah, she's probably having...
- cakes and ale with the Sheriff.
- You just don't get it, do you?
No. I don't get anything.
That's what I'm saying.
You know, we risk our lives to get
money, then we give all of it away.
What's that about? I'm not being
funny. We should get something.
If we don't get anything
we're gonna get weak...
get demoralized. Then how
are we gonna help the poor?
- You're not weak.
- No, but I might get weak.
- Anyway, it doesn't matter to you.
- Why?
You've always been weak.
Very funny.
You know, why don't you just...?
- Just!
- Why don't I just what?
- Why don't you just jigger off?
- Jigger off?
You what?
What does that mean, jigger?
- You know what it means.
- What?
What? Where are you going?
- Master?
- Just let him go.
He needs to cool off.
We've forgotten about the poor today.
We said we'd be here to hand down.
The Sheriff's not
forgotten about them.
Look at that... folk woman.
Caught her to that old pile and
try to humiliate one of them.
For now, we'll try the west gate.
Come on.
All right.
- Just that your wages?
- What's it to you?
I thought you might fancy
doubling your money.
There's another one.
I know that man.
Foster of Rotheram.
- Who is he?
- He's a schemer.
And he's nasty and
he's an enemy of the King.
The day Foster and the Sheriff get
together is a blood day for England.
And if all those visitors
are the same, then...
Go back to the camp and
tell the others to get ready.
And tell them the castle is
locked down. And tell Will...
to think of a way
to get over that wall.
Where are you going?
What if we get in,
we'll need uniforms.
- Why do you offence?
- I need your uniform.
I'm not being funny.
Cost me money every time.
Oh! Shame, shame.
Thank you very much.
Oh! Unlucky, unlucky.
Another go? Have another go!
Unlucky.
Felt you but might.
Gotcha.
This is the Sheriff's work?
Just go away.
Look, I don't want any sympathy
and I don' want any monkey food...
thrown at me. So, unless
you've got a better idea, go away.
- Ma'am. How about I rescue you?
- No, thanks.
I'm Robin Hood.
Really?
No, thanks. I'm taking
a punishment for my children.
They were caught stealing
scraps from the castle kitchens.
Go on, shoo.
I've got to stay or they get it.
It's just for a day.
So do me a favor and get lost.
If you and your children
need extra food...
my men and I can help.
Every few days...
we bring those who need
a little food or money.
I can add you to our list.
- If you give me your name.
- What? You think...
because you've given me a coin
I'm gonna tell you my name?
I have to go. You don't have
to give me your name.
Just be on the market on Thursdays.
My men'll find you.
Hey!
Rose.
My name is Rose.
Thank you.
Excellent, my tiny tricksters.
Now, where's Gisborne?
Tell Gisborne it's showtime.
Good. Very good.
What?
What do you want?
So, tell me...
- Where are your friends?
- What are you talking about?
Oh, not this again.
You think I'm one of
Robin Hood's men, don't ya?
One who looks like me,
what's his name?
Allan, right?
No, no. My name's Tom.
Tom.
Don't insult me.
What's happened?
Robin Hood kick you out?
Tricky working within taverns doesn't
sound very Robin Hood to me.
I told you, I don't know Robin Hood.
Show me some respect and maybe
we can talk about a deal.
Sir Guy.
Sheriff says it's showtime.
Torture him.
Hang on! I admit, all right?
I'm Allan-a-Dale.
Too late.
Come on, a deal? You said a deal!
Too late. No need anymore.
People.
My dear people.
There two young scallywags here
think because they are children...
They can escape justice.
They have committed a crime.
One of my men saw fit...
to take pity on them
and their mother...
and allowed her to take
a punishment for them.
Very generous but misguided.
They must lose a hand.
No.
- It is the law.
- No.
No! My children, no!
Motherly compassion.
The sweet charming.
Bring out the equipment.
Please, they didn't...
they meant no harm.
- Please, don't take their hands.
- Shut up!
Come along. Chop, chop.
I, Vaizey...
Sheriff of Nottingham, hereby
pronounce sentence of...
Little Tiny Billy and Tiny Little Jay
blah-di-blah-di-blah...
Chop off their hands.
Somebody save my children!
Touch those children and there's
an arrow here for you, Sheriff!
Do it.
Rose! Children!
- Run!
- They can't! Help!
No, Robin. Don't go down.
The locks, quickly!
Now!
Clever.
- Very, very clever.
- Put down your weapon, Hood.
So... tell me.
- Are these even your children?
- Children?
Now.
You show me your face...
and I'll show you mine.
Did I tell you I had a sister, Hood?
My friends.
Our time has come.
King Richard is marching on Jerusalem.
By the time the year is out
he will be home.
So...
Operation "Shah mat" must
move to the next phase.
Mobilize your men.
Bring me your bids for funding.
We must be ready.
Wherever King Richard
lands on English soil...
we must be there to greet him,
to embrace him.
Oh, our king is dead.
Long live the King.
So, meanwhile...
today's entertainment.
My friends. Allow me to introduce...
From high lord, to low criminal.
From noble, to nothing.
From rank, to skank.
From hero, to zero.
Robin Hood.
Welcome to my new chamber, Hood.
We are the Black Knights.
Why so coy, Vaizey?
Why not call yourselves the traitors?
An operation "Shah mat"?
Why not call it "Checkmate"?
- Or better still, "Kill the King"?
- Very good. He knows his Persian.
- Very clever.
- The taxes. The money you've raised.
What did you think? Did you think
I was gonna buy myself a new rug?
You don't know me at all, Hood.
Myself and my friends,
we have no interest in money.
It's for an army of mercenaries.
We want power.
Between us we will
run the new England.
- We are the new England.
- Well then God help us.
Yes, what God is he when
he can't help you now. Shame.
Because I really rather
enjoyed thy little skirmishes.
Davida.
My babies.
Death by fang.
- Listen, this can make it so...
- Surely.
How about little pay?
You're paid man,
how about a little wager?
That's no, by the way.
Inch by inch, Hood...
you'll be lowered to your death.
My friend sir Guy would like
to ask you a question...
before we say good bye.
Tell me, Hood.
Who is the Nightwatchman?
I don't know, Gisborne.
But I do know I'll kiss him when
I see him, for stealing from you.
And for showing, it's not just me.
You see, there are people like me...
and the Nightwatchman,
all over England...
who will stand up for justice.
Look here. An enlightenment
player through the wood.
For what?
So you could be King of the paupers?
Do you think they'd love you?
Did you think they'd
kneel to your name?
Trust me.
You're not dead yet,
they forgot you already.
- The Nightwatchman.
- What?
The Nightwatchman! Get after him!
A double execution! Very good.
My friends. I suggest
you retire to your quarters...
and we reconvene tonight.
Thank you.
So, handsome.
I almost regret tricking you now.
A clue, no.
Remember this, Nightwatchman?
Take off your mask.
I wanna see your face when you die.
Mistake, my friend. You should
have run when you had the chance.
Get up, you idiots!
Gisborne!
- Get him!
- Don't worry. He's mine.
What's the matter?
Does nobody love you?
That's your real weakness, isn't it?
You need people to love you.
It's better than needing
reptiles to love you.
- My brother loves me.
- Like I said.
Looks like you're gonna die
without an audience, Hood.
Think, think!
What's he doing?
Why's he running away?
He's creating a distraction!
You're wasting your time, my friend!
Robin Hood is already dead!
Yes.
Impressive.
What were you thinking
you would do, if you did escape?
Between us, we have 10 000 men.
What was your plan?
Were you going to save England,
single-handed?
Not single-handed.
There's five or six of us.
Help.
Get me out!
Help! Get me out!
- Davida?
- Brother?
What have you done? Would you get
my sister out of there, right now!
Don't make any sudden...
movements.
Get her out. Get her out!
There must be a cure.
Some medicine, yes?
- No.
- Sheriff?
Give me one good reason
why I shouldn't kill you now...
- and put an end to your treason?
- Shut up, Hood.
Then you die with your sister.
You haven't told him, have you?
Prince John has made
the Sheriff a promise.
If my brother should die
an unnatural death...
then the county of Nottingham and
everything in it shall be obliterated.
Every town and village will be burned.
Every man, every woman...
and every innocent
little child, hanged.
Would you lay all that
on your conscience...
pretty boy?
So long.
Don't die.
You're strong.
You're my strong sister.
I'm not strong.
I was being you...
so you'd notice me.
So you'd...
love me.
I love you.
I've always loved you.
I want him dead.
Gisborne, whatever it takes,
I want him... dead.
NOTTINGHAM TOWN
- Robin?
- Who died?
You did.
The Sheriff said you were dead.
The Sheriff.
The Sheriff
has plotted to kill the King.
With his friends, the Black knights.
They're already dividing
England between themselves.
- You can't go back into the castle.
- We must get word to the King.
- Nottingham is not safe.
- It's not just Nottingham.
Black knights.
The Black knights, they're everywhere.
They're taxing the poor unto
pay for an army of mercenaries.
Wouldn't we stop them?
I must go back to the castle.
It's too dangerous.
Having a spy on the inside when
there's a coup being plotted is useful.
- No. For once, just listen to me.
- And my father is in there.
- Robin, I have to go back.
- Marian...
- I can't protect you in the castle.
- Two minutes ago...
I thought you were dead and
I would have given anything...
- for another chance to be with you.
- Well then take that chance.
And come with me.
- Listen.
- What?
Little voice, saying yes.
When the King is home, safe.
Hood. You have failed saying goodbye.
Take aim.
What?
No more public humiliation, Gisborne?
- No more beating and parading?
- The Sheriff doesn't wanna...
say goodbye either.
He just wants you dead now.
See you on the dark side.
Shoot him!
So it is good night from me.
And good night from me.
Guards!
What!
Pepper. Ouch!
You see, Gisborne?
That's why I didn't say goodbye.
Because I did wanna see you cry.
- Time to disappear?
- Yeah.
My gang. This way, come on.
We're having fun.
Hood was, did you know...
Didn't try and rescue you.
So, I was thinking...
- One chance to live.
- I will not help you kill Robin.
- M'not helping you kill anyone.
- Yeah, I respect you for that.
So lets look at this
another way, shall we?
An exchange. As we go along.
Little information, a little money...
a conversation.
- What sort of conversation?
- Oh, harmless one.
If I need extra guards
in a building, you let me know.
If I need to reroute a convoy.
That sort of conversation.
I am not robbed.
Robin is not killed.
In between us pulls a service.
You and I.
We are the ones, who make our
supposed betters look good.
And they take us for granted.
But what happens when they move on?
Then it's our turn.
You wanna help the poor?
Help yourself first.
Make provision for the future.
You'll never be named,
you'll never be implicated.
This is just between you and me.
You'll be my eyes and my ears.
And when all this is over...
You will have money and position.
And you can help the poor
they hearts content.
It's not the end of the world, is it?
I mean Marian's all right,
basically and...
- We've got a camp.
- Much.
The Sheriff and the Black knights
are gonna kill the King.
- Take over England.
- Huh, true.
It is the end of the world.
But if we have learned one thing
today it's that you're never going...
to Nottingham alone again, ever.
Because if you had died,
especially now...
If I had died...
today, Much.
Or if I die tomorrow,
you'll carry on without me.
- How? We are Robin Hood's men.
- No. You are Robin Hood.
- What?
- You're all Robin Hood.
And you are, and you are.
All of you.
- We're not that, are we?
- Listen to me. Listen.
We are not just six
outlaws in the forest.
We are the spirit of England
and that is Robin Hood.
And that lads, that...
is this country's only hope.
We are Robin Hood. Come on.
Hi, old lads.
What happened to you?
- Trick one panacea me.
- Or I could have told you.
- We are Robin Hood.
- What?
Just say it.
We are Robin Hood!
NEXT TIME
They are expecting a visitor today.
He's a gambler.
We will extend the count
every courtesy and then...
we shall take every penny he's got
- Stop.
- How did Robin Hood...
- find out about the Strong Room?
- Robin, please be careful.
- England needs me.
- England needs us.
And I need you.
- Men are so obvious.
- Much, don't touch that!
subtitles: olivervogue
subs.sab.bz
adaptation : ScarHand
For the SubWood Team