Hold hand.
You know the law.
I know the law is an ass.
The price for one of the King's deer
is your right hand.
Let's go.
No...
Please, have mercy...
My wife...
What ?
My wife expects a child.
We have no food.
She must eat or we'll lose the baby.
Then...
when she has the baby,
you will say you must steal because
you have another mouth to feed.
Bring him.
Please, no, I need my hands.
We can punish you now,
if you admit your guilt and save us the time
the punishment is lessened we can take a finger
but you will have no right to trial,
no defense, no appeal.
I will lose a trial
and my hand.
Take the finger.
Good.
Come on !
Put your hand on there
like this.
No.
I've changed my mind.
No appeal.
What the...
Who is there ?
Seems I missed your hand.
Let him go before my aim improves!
Show yourself !
You interfere with the law of the land.
The last time I looked,
the law punished poaching with
a tanning or a spell in the stocks.
The law is under threat and must
be severe if it is to be respected.
If the law wants respect,
shouldn't the punishment fit the crime ?
I do not make the law.
I do not decide.
But you enforce it.
And my men and I suggest
that you decide to go on your way.
We got surrounded, Sir.
And let this man feed his only wife.
I don't know.
You know.
And what does that prove ?
Missed again.
Let him go !
God bless you, Sir.
God bless you, all gensy.
Come on !
We leave these rogues to their crimes.
Assholes...
Rogues...
Don't show your faces here again.
Cowards !
Quiet !
Why ?
We have won and they should be ashamed !
Shame on you !
Come back here again and my master and I
shall see that you leave with more
than just your tails between your legs.
"My master and I..."
There are only two of them !
I shouldn't have said that !
Run, Robin !
Run !
Awesome.
Five years in battle, Much.
And you still forget the last man !
I've always so much to remember.
When I see the river train, I'm gonna weep.
I'm gonna cry like a baby.
For all the pain we suffered in Palestine.
The horrors we have witnessed.
And because I am so hungry.
When we get to Locksley
I'm gonna have beef.
Yesterday you said pig.
Oh yesterday I was not so hungry.
I mean I could have pig
and the beef.
And lamb.
I'd like that,
very much.
In fact,
I can feel a song coming on.
No.
No song !
Absolutely no song !
It'd be a cheery song !
And it would be a tragedy too !
A tragedy for you to have survived the Turk,
and made it to within a few miles of Locksley,
only to be killed by your own master !
You know it is lucky I do not readily take offence.
You know, a smaller man will be offended.
A smaller man would be wounded.
And a cleverer man would sing fewer songs.
So master, no stop in here, allright ?
No stop in anywhere, no more heroics.
We're going home. We're going straight...
home.
My friend...
You two are on the run.
No.
We're returning to Locksley after a long absence.
You look like you're on the run.
Want to get me out with this stitch ?
There's a good meal in it.
Me daughter Sarah and I.
We've a proper roasting?
Master we could, couldn't we ?
Much we are nearly home.
Please...
Please
I love you.
Haven't I said that ?
Go on, dig it !
Rust
Have you ever done a proper day's work ?
Rust.
Poke.
Thank you !
Where you two headed ?
Home.
To Locksley
It's going late.
You and your friend should stay in our bound tonight.
That is very kind but I...
don't think it would be.
Someone special waiting for you, Sir
In Locksley ?
I doubt it.
- Listen my friend and I...
- Then what's the hurry ?
Your father !
He'd kill you...
If he saw...
- Sarah ! I'd...
- But he won't !
...see.
Sheriff wants clothes dyed for his men,
in rough taxes
Taxes that I can't afford because
nobody has any money to buy my clothes.
Well !
You know he's a... fair-minded old man.
I'm sure if you explain...
your difficulties to, and if you...
Kissing.
- Kiss him ?!
- Kiss his ring !
He will understand.
You really have been away.
The old man is finished,
we've got a new sheriff these last four years.
- Where is that food?
- Really ?
True, that is interesting !
Because...
he's a fair-minded old man.
I told you.
With a new younger...
You're not listening ?
Robin !
My daughter !
I made no offence.
I do not wish to fight !
Oh bad luck !
I do !
You put the wrong man to mess with.
I did not always wear clothes
I once wore metal.
Never beaten with a sword
nor by a knight nor by a knave.
Much !
Master !
Much.
Fetch the packs.
Run !
Wo-oh ! Sir !
Sir !
You have me !
Allow me one final request.
What's that?
One last kiss !
I told you. I said no slubbering.
Why do you ever ever listen !
Faster. Go.
Not saying anything ?
Hey there !
Where is everybody ?
Dan Scarlett !
Dan ! It's me, Robin !
Robin ?
Yes.
- Is it really you ?
- Of course this is ! We are home unscathed.
Well !
Scathed.
Very scathed.
But happy,
and hungry,
mostly hungry !
Blessed Mary, it's you !
- An accident ?
- Hum... an incident !
No matter !
- What's done is done !
- Tell me !
Guy of Gisborne runs your estate
for the Sheriff.
Does he ?
We have one tide after another
for the King in the Holy Land
making ends meet.
It was wrong,
but my boys, they took some gain
I went to stop them, but so did Gisborne law.
They got caught.
Me too.
Someone had to lose a hand.
Better me than Will
A little lucky.
I'm old.
They got years ahead of them.
This is madness.
You are a skilled man.
You built half this village.
I won't allow this. You will be compensated.
I see my boys in good health
and I am happy.
It's alright boys !
This is Master Robin.
You're allright !
Come on !
This is my bow.
My-my dad made it for me.
Why has yours got these curves in it?
Well, this... is a Sarrasin bow.
It is recurved.
The bow straighten..
when you draw.
Makes it small,
but powerful.
Is it true you can...
hit a man from a mile away?
If I practice everyday I'll be able to do that!
Well, let's hope you never
have to shoot the man, Luke.
Yeah, that's what dad says.
But you killed loads of men
when you fought with the King!
Look !
Ok, give me channel
And remember to...
to take a breath first.
Wait ! Wait !
He's a credit to you and Jane.
No.
Two years.
They told us she wasn't eating
Told me she was...
Couldn't see a boy starve.
The whole village has suffered.
Not just us.
Jane.
Your good strong wife.
Come on ! Come on, stand there !
And don't move !
Ten sacks of flour have gone missing from the store.
They will be found !
Go on, get out of here with the rest of them !
You'll be accounted for !
Come on, stop stroking !
Good, get out of here !
No more, Sir !
Who helped this...
runt ?
Step forward now and I may show lenience.
No
The main perpetrators would be found.
This crime would be punished, bring the boy.
Wait !
- Guy of Gisborne
- Sir Guy of Gisborne to you.
and bow before your master !
Sir Guy of Gisborne.
My name is Robin. Earl of Huntington
and Lord of this manor.
Your services here are no longer required.
Charles !
Thomas !
Welcome back, Sir !
A bath for the Master !
And... and fresh clothes immediately.
Merig !
And me too !
Pardon ?
Thornton,
Much is no longer my manservant.
Hum ?!
In recognition of the services
to me in the Holy Land.
He's to be made a free man !
I'm granting the fields of Lodget Bondchett.
Until then...
he's a guest... in my house.
And I would like a plate
of something while I bathe.
Very well.
That is the way to the servants' quarters.
I knew that!
Welcome back, Locksley !
Now.
I have... kept your lands for you !
I have managed your estates to the best of my
ability, under the guidance of the Sheriff.
And I would appreciate more respect
in front of the populace.
How many years have you been here ?
Three years, four winters.
And yet you still do not have the respect of the populace.
- My men and I will leave directly for Nottingham !
- My servants will help you pack !
How was the Holy Land ?
Bloodthirsty.
I understand the King is winning, thanks be to God.
He's killing more people.
How is that not winning ?
Show me an argument, ever settled with
bloodshed and then I'll call it winning.
Do not pretend that you do not love war.
I've seen you fight.
When ?
I do not recall.
I have changed.
A council of nobles meets tomorrow.
Nottingham have no doubt the Sheriff will
call a feast to celebrate your safe return.
Goodbye !
One thing !
I should celebrate my safe return too.
By pardonning any wrong doers from my
estates waiting trial and punishment.
Only the Sheriff can pardon, you know that !
It is custom for the Sheriff to acceed his nobles requests on such matters.
Well then I suggest you take it with the Sheriff.
Was it horrible ?
The war ? What was it like ?
War is for...
for men.
You would be upset.
Little one.
Yeah ?
I heard that dying men always ask for their mums.
That's for the bath.
What ?
Rose petals !
I knew that !
Much !
Get dressed !
We're gonna visit the old Sheriff.
Really ?
I would prefer... I have to say... the whole
food,
bath,
sleep
thing.
Of course.
I forgot my promess to you.
You don't have to go.
Is something wrong ?
England is wrong.
And Nottingham Sheriff worse.
The old Sheriff would never've allowed this.
I have to hear his story before I go to Nottingham tomorrow.
Sleep well, my friend !
You've earned it !
Master !
Master, the food !
Go to the village.
Bring every family here, and feed them.
Nobody here eats until they do, including me.
Those who're ill,
Take the food to them.
Yes, master !
Here
I hope that you don't mean that
by "nobody eating"?
No. No of course not.
That's fine !
That's... fine !
Has anyone seen my horse ?
Get out !
Get away from here !
Edward !
It's me, your friend. Robin of Locksley !
I know who you are !
Crooks, come to deceive me !?
I allow none of you here !
I swear, I come in friendship !
Get away !
I'm no longer the Sheriff !
Leave me to live here my days in peace.
You heard my father, leave !
Marian.
It's me, Robin.
Congratulations.
Leave.
How are you ?
- I thought of you.
- Leave !
We're leaving.
Sir Edward, if you do not remember me,
remember Nottingham !
Remember your people !
- Interesting.
- Interesting ?
It's unbelievable !
He used to treat us like...
like sons !
She's still unmarried.
Oh !
And I thought you come
to see the old Sheriff !
I did !
Please !
Bless you, master Robin !
- We have all eaten well.
- Is there any food left ?
I must confess I'm anxious !
Robin !
Jeffrey ?
Do you remember this ?
Remember this ?
My egg
My egg, where's it gone ?
- You've eaten it.
-No, I haven't !
Here, it is !
You used to love that
when you were a lad.
Have you had lots to eat ?
You're a good boy !
Thanks for feeding us !
Come on, Ben !
Bring those eggs !
Come on !
That man is a show-off !
If there are no eggs left
I'm going after him.
Dan ?!
What's wrong ?
Young Benedict got frightened
He told Gisborne's lot
who took the flowers.
Your boys ?
They've taken them to Nottingham !
Robin !
I will resolve this !
I will talk to the Sheriff,
I promise !
Where is everybody ?
Funny Wednesday, it used to be market day !
I think Wednesday may still be market day.
I'm sure there's some mistake.
My Lord, I do not think that
this is a laughing matter !
Sorry, remind me !
How many men do you have ?
Twenty-four.
- And he had...
- One.
- But the point is...
- How did you let him take the house ?
Technically it is still his property.
I would have appreciated more support
in this matter.
Relax !
I'll give it back to you within a month
Twenty-four... One...
It has been a good month,
we've collected nearly 300 pounds.
Would you want to be the King in Antioch?
Clue : No.
Trying to feed a starving army on 300 pounds,
You promise...
500 pounds.
It's...It's more than we've ever managed before.
Oh ! Youpee !
So, the King...
is starving in the Holy Land
and you have failed him.
But !
"It's more than we've ever managed before."
Robin of Locksley !
Good morning, everyone !
Sheriff !
Oh, carry on !
Locksley !
Welcome back ! I saw Sir Guy of Gisborne
manage your estates to your satisfaction.
I believe you he may have managed them to your satisfaction.
Some of your peasants are unruly by the way.
We have two in custody awaiting punishment.
Three.
Oh, discipline
will be a problem. Be warned ! Laugh brown.
Sheriff, thank you !
- I propose...
- Discipline has never been a problem on my estates.
Times have changed.
Not for the better !
It seems...
You, of all people, should know that
the King needs funds to fight our Holy War.
Is it our Holy war, or is it Pope Gregory's ?
We stand shoulder-to-shoulder with Rome.
And we fall shoulder-to-shoulder too.
I have seen it.
And then what is your proposal
to raise money for the King ?
Stop all taxes !
Today !
Amusing
I did not joke.
Today is market day,
and yet there is no market.
And your point is ?
If a man can make more
than he needs for his family,
he can take what remains to market.
He can trade.
The shire can
take its share.
But until then we must help every man,
every peasant, every peonman, every ??
provide for his family.
Get him trading again.
A hungry man
who can
"provide"
for his family is a
comfortable man, a lazy man !
doesn't want to work.
What we need are hungry men !
Our noble friend
seems to forget
that hungry men
are virtuous.
There is a celebration of my
return tonight in the Great hall
Indeed.
Won't I trust none of those "virtuous men"
will be festing?
My father seems to think he should see you.
Our house is watched.
Come after midnight tonight.
Very well.
You're looking... striky
And if you still live with your
father, that must mean...
Take care not to be seen.
Don't worry.
I can look after myself.
I don't care about you, I care about my father.
Are you really as naive as you seem ?
You think you can peak fights with
this people and get away with it ?
You think you can slight them in public ?
You're a fool.
Marian, wait !
Now is not the time, I know.
I must say, you are...
more than ever...
Your eyes...
and even when you look at me in anger...
I feel you.
I believe
you can still,
even after all this time,
you can see into my soul.
Five years and you're still
peddling the same old drivel.
Does it ever work ?
You'd be surprised !
Amazed !
Bring out the Locksley's lot !
Hey, jailer !
Jailer, that's me !
Jailer, are you listening ?
I'm from Locksley !
Jailer ! I'm from Locksley !
Give your names !
Will and Luke Scarlett.
What is your crime ?
Living at the wrong place at the wrong time.
Living under an evil Sheriff. Where do
our taxes go ? They go to Nottingham.
To the Sheriff !
To his birds !
Name ?!
Benedict !
Son of Richard Giddens.
Servant of Locksley.
What is your crime ?
Stealing flower !
Are you guilty ?
What is your punishment ?
Don't know !
Hanging!?
No, surely not !
Hanging!
- Robin !
- No.
- No, please !
- Dad told me you would save us !
Do you mind ?
We don't tell them what is the dangle
They kick up the hell of a stink !
For stealing flour !
Hanging?
The Sheriff wants an example !
We just have word...
I'll be speaking to the Sheriff !
Meanwhile you treat these prisoners well,
or you'll have me to want it too.
We've got one more.
You are not from Locksley.
I know.
But you saved me once before.
That was a long way from
Nottingham, here I am known !
Will you save me ?
For my wife !
My newborn bab'.
You said your wife was expecting !
Nope, she had it !
Your lies today may be your own doing.
I cannot save the others and now
I fear you'll share their fate !
What fate ?
I'm not from Locksley.
Did-did I say Locksley ?
There's been a mistake, here.
I'm from Rocksdale.
Rocksdale !
That's why they called me Allan A. Dale.
- Yeah, and I'm from Wild Willus.
- No !
Throw him with the Locksley lot.
Huntington, you are missing your feast.
Rumours abound.
What rumours ?
That you're weak, that you've returned
weakened from your exertion in the Holy Land.
My master returns with honors, honors from the King !
What a great honor,
it would have been to **
I have visited my peasants in your dungeons.
They have committed grave crimes.
- Master surely...
- Which would make all the more compassionate your gesture of pardoning them.
Pardonning them?
I will see them hang.
In the morning you yourself, said that
we risk rebellion. We must have order.
It is custom for the Sheriff to hear
is noble request for damned sake...
By the way ! In your absence we nominated
you to oversee tomorrow's entertainment.
No.
You don't want these rumours witnessed to spread.
Best to *** them now.
Otherwise we don't ***
Marian !
Might I have the pleasure of your company ?
Well !
Don't just stand there, if the Sheriff's men see.
What ?
You might give them the pleasure of your company !
Grow up !
Forgive me !
I could not welcome you before.
How did this monster become sheriff ?
I did not watch my back.
Prince John gives out the Shires
in his brother's absence.
My bid was not accepted.
What can be done ?
I can do nothing !
I'm watched !
And I must think about my daughter !
When I do speak out, no one listens.
Robin, it is done to you, my friend.
What can we do ?
Play Nottingham's game.
Speak to the Lords.
Slowly, you can turn them. But do not make the mistake
I and others have made, and make your dissent public.
Consolidate your position quietly.
I do not have time.
Tomorrow, I am to order the hanging
of four of my own peasants.
It will be the long game, I'm afraid.
Will and Luke Scarlett cannot wait.
Benedict Giddens. Alan A. Dale.
You must let them die, it is a test.
Fail it and there will be consequences.
- Perhaps !
- Definitely !
This is not a game...
My daughter speaks when she should not.
But she is right !
You have no choice, Robin !
Hide your temper.
Bide your time.
until you can act decisively.
Or kiss your lands, if not your life, goodbye.
Murderer ! Murderer !
Robin.
It's not your fault !
Lords ! Ladies !
People of Nottingham ! We are gathered here
today to witness the caring out of justice
In the name of God and King Richard !
Bring out the prisoners !
Robin Locksley, Earl of Huntington
having recently returned from the Holy War with a
personnal commandation from
the King himself, will read
proclamation.
Enjoy.
Oh, and no second thoughts, Locksley,
or your friend, Much, will be drop in
on us as our special guest today.
"Let it be heard and known,
about the lands and realms of Richard,
his majesty, King of England,
that on this, the 26th day of April,
in the year of our Lord 1192,
the following men,
having been tried on the law and found guilty,
Benedict Giddens of Locksley,
Will Scarlett of Locksley,
Luke Scarlett of Locksley,
Alan A. Dale of Locksley,
these same men have been
sentenced to hang by a rope
until they are dead."
Will ! Luke !
- May the soul...
- Wait !
Please, don't kill my brother, my little
baby, my inbred cousin !!!
On behalf of Anthony, our bishop, I claim
benefit of clergy for these men.
They cannot hang.
These are not holy men,
these people cannot plead the cloth.
Get on with it.
I came last night to administer their Last Rites.
So ?
And each one came to God through me,
repenting their sins and asking to take the cloth.
I felt duty-bound to consult the bishop
and he, in turn, conferred status
of novice onto each man.
Shut up.
"I, Anthony,
Very Reverend vicar apostolic,
- hereby confer..."
- Shut up !!
Is this possible ?
They could not have become novices overnight.
They are become postulants !
Novice novices, if you like.
And so are under protection
of the Church !
"Novice novices" ?
How novel !
Well, hang them... and arrest him !
Mister Drum !
Watch and enjoy, Robin !
Owe your prisoners a talk
and then you'll be done for, my friend.
May the souls of these men find the innocence and health.
I love you, boys !
I love you, Will ! Love you, Luke !
People of Nottingham !
These men have committed no crime
worth more than a spell in the stocks.
Will you tolerate this injustice ?
I, for one, will not !
This one !
What the hell !
You, Locksley, will say farewell to your little Mooch !
His name is Much !
Well it'll be Mooch in a moment.
Master, look out !
Robin !
This way !
You understand ! Now, get after him !
Well let's return to Locksley.
Dissent for good.
Master !
Archers ! what do we do ?
Let's get them something to shoot at !
Go, go, go !
I'm just getting some pinion.
Be honest with me.
This does not bode well for my lodge.
My Bondchett
I knew it !
This is your lodge here now, my friends !
- Sherwood Lodge.
- I'm not your friend !
Excuse me !
This is our forest !
Transcript/Synchro : Scrattie.
Un grand merci à AspirantNemo.
O~~ www.seriessub.com ~~O