My name
is melinda gordon.
I justot marri,
just moved to a small town,
just oned up an antique shop.
I might ust like you.
Except from the ti
that was a little rl,
i knew that i coul
talk to the dead.
Grandmotr:
'S all right, honey.
Earthbound spiri,
my grandmother called them,
the ones who have not
crsed over yet
because they have unfinished
business with the living,
and they come
to me lp.
To tell you my story,
i have to ll you theirs.
I dot think that wiiter
got your sense ohumor.
I think it's becausewas
lookinat you so much,
he didn't evenear me.
Are you gonna pick up
your mom tomorw
at the train?
. no, no. she insists
on taking a cab.
She liketo think
she's low maintenance.
Ah, don't we all?
She ways has her reasons
what?
This is extly
where i parked thear.
Are you sure?
Yeahremember?
We almost tripped
over thacrack there.
I am n enjoyin
this moment.
Jim:
That's quick work, billy.
Y, slow night.
At can i say?
We caught him
running a st sig
few blocks away.
Damnear dre right
on the lawn of this house.
A joyride, i'm guessing.
A joyride ofne?
He's got couple
of mdemeanors,
no major prior
what you guys wanna do?
Mis nsen,
thboy's father.
I reallypologi
for th.
My son, 's in that
oublemaker phase, i gues
noneas ht.
That's all that maers.
Um, i know
this is asking a lot,
but would you consider
t pressing charges?
I'll pay for the damages.
Re. Yeah. It's ok.
Reallyppreciate at.
What is it witkid?
I practiy had
to leave a patient
at the operating table
to getere.
Metimes i wish hd wake
and be 21 and have all
this teen crap behind him.
Well, i'm an emt
overmercy
in case you need me.
Oh, yeah. I'm rry.
Honey.
[Progressive music pla
oh, heessed
with your stations.
We should prosecute.
Let's go back.
I ne to wake up
and be 16...
woman: I don't...
and get over
all this adult crap.
Pull ovefor a se
what, are the cell pho
transmissions? What?
I don't think so.
I think these
are spirit voices.
Wait a minute. Normal guy.
How come can hear them?
I'm not su.
How you know
the spirits?
I feel it.
I can feel the
whatthe cas haunted?
I don't know.
I've neverun
into thibefore.
Thers a name for it.
Cool. I mereepy.
Woma i... am... here. Hmm. Ok.
Won: I. Am... re.
Hello. S there handsome
paramedic this house?
You have 4 mesges.
Man: Your dry cleaning
is ready.
Hey, it's drea.
You were right
out the estate sale
in prmont. Call me.
M, it's tommy.
Can you take the 4
to 12 shift next tuesd?
You all right?
Do you hear that?
Tatic crackling]
Barely. But ah.
I wond who it is.
You ok?
Ye. Except for
a headache all of sudden
hey.
You're gon
be all right
You t headache,
my mother arrives.
Interesting.
Hey. Hey, dling.
I'm so happy
to s you
gosee u, mom.
Hi.
Melia!
Hey. Here you go, man.
Thank u.
Thanks very much.
Jim!
You just tipped
myriend ellis.
Sorry. Ell conway.
Th is my son jim.
Ya there, jimmy.
Hey.
And beautiful
daughter-in-law melinda.
Melinda. Heard
a lot about you.
Ni to meet you.
Well, look, i got
another bag to get.
Beight back.
Isn' sweet?
O is he?
Well, yoknow.
I don't.
He my, m...
ll, boyfriend is just
ridiculous, isn't it?
He's,,
a special friend.
Boyfriend. Mom, you
didn't mtion this.
Didn't i? Melinda,
you look wonderful.
And u, faith,
you' just glowing.
Mom...
m, pleast
be boring about this.
Llxplain more late
at a fantastic house.
Great. I got it.
Thanks.
Here, darling.
Ok, well...
yone hungry?
Mmm.
Yeah. Su.
Hey. You'rsupposed
to pay for those.
I'm keing track.
All righ what's up
th you and ell?
Whatbout me and ellis?
You haven't
spoken 2 words to the guy.
It nothing.
Well, does it bother you
im and your mom...
hey, hey. Do we
to p a name on it, huh?
I n't get it. He sms
like a perfectly nicguy.
Then how ce he's
checking out thablonde who
is carly not my mother?
Becae, jim, that blonde
is a nordic goddess
th huge...
pastri.
A priest would be
rgiven for glancing.
That's not a glance.
Th's a leer.
I don't know. Sothing
doesn't feel right.
S your mom dated anybody
since your dad pasd ay?
Not that i know of.
Say noore.
I can't liev
you tried to put their bags
separate ros.
I was kidding.
They are adults.
I dot know. Something
out thisllis guy
just doesn't seem right.
You kn how themet?
He was installing
her w alarm system.
He sms sweet
and charming to me.
Ah, yeahif you like
that sort thing
wh is this reay about?
I don't know.
U know what it is?
He's too nice.
I'm not bu it.
Oh. Cynil.
Dad's only
been dead 3 years.
He's just... he's really
dient from my dad.
Maybe u should just
get usedo e id
that your mother...
ah.
Is dating.
Oh.
Are you all right?
Damn headache.
Gie that.
Is it the same
as ones before?
Yeah. The were
weird voic ain
on the answeringachine
i listed to em twi,
and i've been sick all night.
Don't listen to 'em.
That is so me.
I lovehat.
Seems simple me.
Are u sure these things
aren't explainable,
likeell phontransmissions?
No, theye no
you know
hoi can sensspirits,
like can feel
what they're feeling?
Now i'm on overload.
It's like tasting
too ma foods at once.
Don't likethiss making you sick.
Should i get you
some aspirin?
You know what always makes
myeaches go away?
Oh, yeah.
Man: Wait.
Hold tse doo.
Plse.
Thanks. You're a pal.
Obably sed me
abha an hour.
Whicfloor?
Ll, same ayou.
E yohere to see
huffman?
How did you know?
Psychic.
Th, and ere's
only o offic
on the third floor.
H makes you dr. Huffman.
You seem
little surprised.
Nono. M sorry.
Der on the phone. E...
i've actually d
a lot oflind dates
which began wi
that samphrasing.
Melinda gordon.
Talked this morning
about my messages.
Ohyes! Of course.
Eltronic
voice phenomenon
evp, as we and all
thgeeks li to say.
How mu do yo
know about it?
Oh, not much. St
what i learned on the net.
Your name kept coming up
on my searches
you seem to be
the go-to for evp.
Yet the airman
of my departme
remains unimesd.
Would you care
for some chee?
Smoked gouda.
Oh. I'm. Thanks.
Do you mostly work
in paranormal studies?
I don't think of it
asaranor
i'm simply tg to apply
scientificxpnation
to phenomena
that seem unexplainable.
Is evp common?
Hard to know. We don
exacy keep stistics.
Most of the voic seem
to mostlco thrgh
the va bandwidth
een regular
broadcast ions
but 's not just radio.
Itou happen
with anything electronic.
Tv monitors, vcrs, eteter
most peoplreally don't know
exactly how or w it works.
Most peoe liev
it caused by ghosts.
Do youelve in ghosts?
Do you?
I'answerhat uthfully,
but i y be
endangering my tenure.
Let's just say
i like to keep an open mind.
Now, you said
you have messages.
Oo y. Um...
the voices are hidden
under my other messages.
And i'm also hearing vces
ony car radio.
Ere.
Good call on t cheese,
by the way. 's dreadfu
it's just been
driving me crazy
that ian understand
what's beingaid.
See, there's a lot
of wping. Watch this.
Very typical.
Most of the voices seem
to be in mid-conversation.
Me askg questis.
Ths one femaleoice
which ses to pop.
She doesn't seem
to be in conversation
as much as trying
to g someone to hear her.
You suddenly seem un.
No, i'm good.
Can you just tl me
whathey're sg?
Woman: I am waiting for him.
I waiting.
Am waiting for him.
And you think these ices
are mang you sick?
It's not
h the voices.
It's just a loof spirit stuff
happeninall atnce.
It feelsike head's vibrating.
You are oking a litt
green around the gills.
You look goo too.
Why n't u just ghome?
I can handle things here
don't be ridiculous.
I'm fine
Woman:'m here... claremont.
Noisin the woods.
Noise in the wood
claremont...
thise...
i'm sorry. I have go.
who are you?
What are you doing here?
O am i?
I'm thwoman
whose cayou stole.
And u should
try bepote.
Thanks to me, you' not
stuck in jail right now.
Answer my queson.
You firs
what are you doing here?
I'm walkg.
It's a til.
Were youed here, t?
At are you talki abo?
Led he by who?
Someonto me to ce here.
A ma
did she tell you, too?
You hear the voices, too,
don't you?
U're...
you're nuts.
...i don't know
what you're tag about.
You don't have
to do this.
I'll feel better
in the mni.
Of course i do.
I can't sleep anyhow.
Don't ll me
you're obsessing
what if he's a gold digger?
What if he's just
after hemoney?
Th is a class
thing, isn't it?
I think you know me
beerhan that.
Come on, admit it.
Yodon't ink he's
good eugfor yo motr.
It's not that.
What then?
I don't ink he's
good enougfor mother.
Feelter?
I felt bter urs ago.
I've beetotally
milking it
at's my girl.
Yoknow...
can i ask you a qution?
Mm-hmm.
You've beethrough a lot
with this whole spirit game.
Bh ve.
True enough.
But i'veer seen it
make you sk re.
Don't ke a big deal
out of this.
I just can't get
ntrol of this one.
My point.
It's a bad thing.
Do you ever think
there'lle a day
where you casay,
"sorryi can'help you.
"You're not good for me.
You're makinme sick.
You're ming me cry"?
Do you thi that day
will eveme?
I don't ow.
What suld i do?
I'm gonna go downstas
d gt a glass of water.
Yowant anything?
Wiom andatiee.
Alwaysn short supp.
Saine crackers
e gonna have to do.
ohwho are you?
Who are the other voices?
Cr
woman: I'mere... by the woods.
I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
In toods.
Claremon... aremont...
i'm sorry. I'm sry.
U all right?
I'm sorry. Oh!
Clemont... in the woods.
What are you
tryi ttell me?
My son.
Hi.
Damn. I forgot to send
the check for thca
can do that right no
no. E insurae company's
taking care of it.
I just wanted come by
and eck on kirk.
Kirk.
Ye. Just see
how he's doing.
Uh, you said you weren't
gog to p charges
nestly, i'm not.
I just... i don't know...
want to talk to m,
ma se therwas
no hard feings.
Are you a social worker
or somhing?
I get that lot
not really. No.
Well, uh, it's nof you
to take an interest.
But, uh, he's not.
He'sever here.
Where does he go?
I'm not privy
to that informatioanymore.
It just the two of you?
Excuse me?
Oh, i was justondering
my wife passed away,
ifhat's what you're asking.
You ow, my son was
a od kid until then.
Made gd grades.
Heas happy.
When his mother pass away,
he jusspiraled.
All sudden,
it wasgs a petty crime.
He doesn't say a word,
not to me anyone else.
And believme, i try.
I reallyry.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, i got
to cat a pla.
Right.
Hey, i'm sorry
hold you up.
Can i just
e a card?
Ju in ca
he does wanna talk
you are a social
worker, aren't you?
Maybe you're rht.
Go ahead.
'Ll probably come home
when he's sure i'm gone.
Excuse me.
How did his mother die
it w an accide.
She di in the woods.
Womaed gve...
billy.
Hey, jimmy
dog a training
thing he or somethg?
No. Actual,
can i talk to you?
You're not gonry
toire me or mething?
Maybe if you're lucky,
next time.
What you need, by?
Ok, uh, i wodn't
ask you this
if i wasn't...
what?
Well, my mom started
seeing this guy.
Don't know. Juot
a weird feeling about him.
Wed how?
I don't know.
I was wondering if you
could rua check him.
Heives in philadelphia.
Phadphia. Wow.
Don't know
what i can g from here.
Maybe dm court records.
It'd be a shot in the dark.
I'd apprecte
anythiou could do.
Ok, we...
what's wrong? Tbacks?
What his name?
Ellis conway.
He an electrician.
Philadelphia.
Oh, it is so cute.
He all twitchy
about faith's boyfriend.
Thank you.
He seemsike
such a nice guy.
Oh, he is.
He reallis
but it's jim mom,
and he's always goa
look after her.
E's little impulsive.
Oh, that's great.
I love impulve.
Hey!
St!
Hi.
Can yomake this st?
Woman: Remember when...
remember when...
[stac crackling]
Who do youhink it is?
Don'care who it is.
I just want ito stop.
It your moth, isn't it?
What d your mother do?
She was
elerical engineer.
Design circu boards.
What differee
es that make?
So she knew a lot
abt eltronics.
I guess.
Spirits ne
our energy to manifest.
She's out the woods.
There'no one there
for hetoraw on
she's obablyrying
to commucate on e only
thinthat'samiar.
How do you know all is?
It's what i do.
The spirit part yway.
I ink your mothe
trying to get
a ssage ou.
And e's there.
E's waiting for you.
Don't want
any messages from her.
I just want the voices to stop.
You said you could
he me, so dot.
Doou know anything
aboua d glove?
My mother's a liar.
I dot want anything
to do with h,
ng or dead.
What hpeneto you
in these woods?
Anutn day.
Beautiful sun.
Everything felt so good,
so right
fr. I felt
like a girl again.
He did that for me.
We met years ago
we were friends, that's l.
But my marriage waso cd,
and bob dee feeloved.
It was just a ttleall.
Didn hur
lacy!
He!
Lp!
How could i explain?
My sonirk ted me.
Held never understand.
Everybody knew.
Knew what?
That we were lovers.
Family was devasted.
Wasn't there
to explain or apologiz
everyone betrad.
Kirkost faith.
Angry.
Wastg his talent
what about his father?
Doesn't understa.
Doesn't understand what?
The red glove.
He doe't know at...
red glove.
. th is e jensens'.
Ave us a message.
Kirkit
menda gordon again
if could just talk
toou for 5 minutes.
It's really impoan
if you could jt
call my stor my cell.
Anyou.
Hey. Re y ok?
You look worried.
Yeah. I guess i'm always
worried about somethin
here. You chop the, and
i will take re of threst
this is fun.
I ver come home for lunch.
Now i know why jim's
such a good cook.
To tell you the truth,
i lened more from him
than he did om me.
He haslways been
terested in food.
Let's hope
heives pr els
a few crumbs at least.
Does it both you?
It's wt i expected,
pretty much.
He's very protecve.
But he'll come aroun
ellis can win ybody over.
You know, i ha to admit.
I envy whayou and jim have.
I wishhat
mother and i...
oa. Careful
what yish for.
[Laughing]
It's not ey,
espeally
the growing-up par
i can't even count
the number of tis
we were furious
with each other.
Still happens.
But he always kn
meonhahis back.
He always knew
someone was out there
who understood h.
Wellyou and m
have quite a bond.
Nothing's gonna change that.
Now weust have
to me him se
that eis isn't trying to.
That was fast.
Ift was my moms,
i'll be fast, too.
N i get yocoee?
No. I got to run.
What have yogot?
Plenty, and it isn't good.
You call me later
ifhere's anythel
you want me to do.
Thanks, billy.
I owe you one.
i'm here... in the wood
noisin the woods.
Noise in the woods.
I'm iting.
Ise in the woods.
Noise in the woods...
mom.
You again?
You have amazing ting,
i'll give you that.
What's wrong?
Lce to my sos
latest cri see.
He just broke into
an electnics storend
trashed the place or something.
Is there
anytng i cano?
'S almost like
he wts untile knows
m at my busiest
before hlls is crap.
Doubt at it haanything
to dwith you, mr. Nsen.
Well, please, tell me,
what is it about?
He'sriing.
Ost his mother.
I lost, too.
Talk aut having the g
pulled out frounderneath you
i' done my best
thhakid.
I taught him to be tough,
with a thick skin.
How el can you
survive in this world?
Inead,
thws garbage cans
rough storwinds.
Oh, mr. Jensen,
you left your door...
open.
I'm waiting.
The woods...
byheoise...
noise in the woods...
claront...
b the nse...
aremont...
red glov
Claremont...
Under me...
red glove...
where it should be...
under me...
red glove.
Where it should be...
can i have a ment?
It's my son.
Thanks.
Why are you ing is?
Mean, is it that bad?
I told you i'd send you
to a psychiatrist
a counsor.
Maybe if you'd actually
talk to somebody.
But you can't
keepoing this.
Weyolet me know
when you find me
somebody to talk to.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
They told meo one
has baed youut.
Yeah. He's
aching me a sson.
In the grandview jail
to turn a guy around.
I'm sorry.
It'se. At least
ll get a good nighs sleep.
They don't allow
anytng electronic in here.
I know what ppened
withour mother.
How?
She told me.
Yeah, ok. Whatever
she knowhow any
you are ater.
I doubt.
People make mistakes.
She feels badl
e should feel ba
she lied.
I know why shead
to lie to my o m
but why dishe
have to lie to me?
I told her everyin
about myself.
How could she
keep thaom me?
She didn't love him.
Well, ybe she
di't love me either.
You ow tt's not true.
Sometimes
we don't understand
why people d
wh thedo.
Everybody fights
their own battle.
We may n even ow
what that is.
Where the hell
did you get this
you know what it's about.
It'sbout aoung man
who doesn't know how ttell
his fatherhat he's gay.
???
this doesn't make up
for what you did.
Maybe to mit does.
U had no right
to rthis.
It waseautiful.
It made me cry.
Anit was oiously
written by somebody
with a great heart.
You should keep writing.
It's none of your business.
Who the hell
are you anyway?
Why e you even
involv with this?
Becait was my car
you chose to steal.
And e
that was no accident.
Hey, does your father
know that yowre?
What do you think?
Why not?
He wouldn't understand,
and neither do you.
Lo, thks for the bail.
I' pay you back.
Thank ur father.
He was the one that gave me
permission to pick you up.
Fantastic.
I'm out here.
Thank you.
Was surewouldn't getny good
italian food o here.
Was g.
No. I goit.
You' a man
few wor, jimmy.
I admire that.
Holo he you been
an electrician, ellis?
An electc...
well, i'ven
in the busines
a good 14, 1years now.
Realeveron
anything on the side?
On the se?
I keep myself
busy enough.
I bet you do.
I n't think i get you.
Writing bad ecks
internet scams,
telephone frd.
My mother ow you spent
2 years in a federal prison?
You checki up
one, jim?
I'm checking up
on you, ellis.
May i see at?
Right.
We, you see,
there's a problem here.
I by "ellis,"
but that's my middle name.
My real name is vincent...
vinny conway.
This here "ell conway,"
that's somebody se.
So why don't
go back to your guy
and you give him the name
"vincent e. Conway,"
see what he comes up with.
You kn, mmy?
Your mother
rned me about you.
He wait a minute.
So wt, d y chae
your name oromething?
I didn't change it.
I just dropped it.
Thk you.
Look, when i got
my business started,
i thoughg by "elli
wod ke me sound
more high-class.
You know how narrow-minded
some pple could be
about the things.
Look, mmy.
I understandi do.
Ur mother's
a wonderful woman.
We both know tt.
T she's been hurt,
shs lost,
she's vulnerable.
You're lking outor her.
That's something else
i admire.
Ellis, i don't kno
where to begino apolize.
Forget it, huh
i've bn through
a few things myself.
Ups and downs
in business.
First wife passed away.
Ah, we aave
our wounds, kid. Ight?
T as big as the one
i'd like to inflict
on myself rit w.
I manot be
a college guy,
bu uh, i've made
some good moves in my time.
Meeting your m
was one of 'em.
Hey, wan go get
so ice cream?
T'say
weet some ice cream.
Then let's go get
some iceream.
And you can pay.
I can't believe.
I cat believe
u iled the kid o.
I couldn't just
let him sit there
in tt cage.
It didn't cost that much.
Are yomad?
Mad? Let me see.
Just when i think i can't
ssibly love you more,
you prove me wrong.
N you imagine having
eep a secret like that
from the one pern
whs supposed to love y
no matr what?
, speaking of secrets...
Woman: 415 overton.
W we know
thatddress
it was
on the police report.
At's where
the kid to our car
whene stole it.
At areou doing
i'm going with y.
We can both leave
in theiddle of theight.
L look wei.
I'll call
i need your hp.
I'll be fine.
Hey. Ey, what
are you doing here?
This is his hoe.
This is come on. Don't do this.
Really wjust talk toe.
Don't rry.
He doesn't le here anymore.
The man my mother
ally loved,
he med ay.
Hey.
She ows how mad
you e at her.
She knows how much
thaffair hurt you.
But at's not just it, is it?
She says you hurt
even more than you know.
Al? Mo hurt
than even i know? Wo
that's a l of hurt.
And you hurt because
she was the only one
who could possibly
unrstand you.
She had your back.
It wasn't
her fault, ight?
The ing part, at lea.
She wanted y
to have peac
she was ke my ma
you know
she cod always
figure out
where i was or where
i wanted to go
just by talking to her.
Even when i felt
like freak...
could ok at me
and i knew that...
everything was gon be ok,
no matter wh.
And i beeved her.
I never got to s good-bye.
Can i talk to her?
She's he.
Shcan feel your love
it giving her strength.
I miss y so.
I feel so lost.
Whgonna tell m
that everything's
nna ok now?
You wi.
At's what she wants.
You can keep her alive
in everyinthat you write.
And she wants you to know
that s's proud of you.
Tell him to be kind
to his father.
E's saying that
yo fhes a good man.
He's jusafid
of h heart.
And he nds
toe taught howo love.
It's so hard.
I know.
But 's worth it.
Thanks.
She's sa good-bye.
Sooon?
It'se.
Good-byemom.
Are you ok?
Ye.
You?
Yeahyeah, really ok.
No more headaches.
I feel much better.
One more thing
left to do.
I can't.
I n't give it toim.
Mom, i did
a pretty spid thin
this is about ellis.
Oh
yeah. Did he mention it?
No.
Um...
i olized to him, and...
i'd like
to apologize to you,
because, u
i've been ki of a jerk
when it come to ellis.
Kind of?
A total, complete,
yodot even wanna kno
kind of jerk.
I wouldn't have brought him
if i thought he couldn't
handle it.
Wait. You knew
that i was...
instct sd ju show up
and let ellis be eis
and jim be jim,
and all
just sort itself out.
I think u might regret
the "let jim be jim" part.
Do you know where son is?
I'm worried about him.
He's ok now.
www.tvsubtitles.net