My name
is melinda gordon.
I just got married.
Just moved to a small town.
Just opened up an antique shop.
I might be just like you.
Except from the time
that i was a little girl,
i knew that i could
talk to the dead.
It's all right, honey.
Earthbound spirits,
my grandmother called them.
The ones who have not
crossed over yet
because they have unfinished
business with the living,
and they come
to me for help.
To tell you my story,
i have to tell you theirs.
It'll be a great chance for us
to break out and meet new people
and make new customers.
You do not have to be
the one standing up
in front of a jillion strangers.
You are gonna be great.
Besides, i set up
50 auctions in the city.
They're fun.
Where's the light?
Does all this junk
have to come out?
Yeah. Everything.
Look, i can get a pro
to do the auction,
but it's gonna
cost us so much.
And you're beautiful, and
everyone's gonna listen to you.
Then how come you don't listen
to me when i tell you no?
I'm listening to you. I'm just
not paying you any attention.
You're funny.
An auctioneer could be a cool
thing to have on my resume.
Thank you.
You're gonna love it.
Ooh. Cool.
Creepy.
You smell smoke?
It's probably
the old furnace.
What was that?
You feel that?
Oh, god. What is it?
Rats.
Oh, i hate rats.
Ok. Uh, this will be me
calmly going back upstairs.
I know you're there.
This is our stuff.
Leave it be.
Yeah. Who do you
think you are?
Now, get out of here before
we do something you don't like.
was it rats?
No. Little boys.
Ghost little boys?
One or two that
i saw and a dog.
A dog? A ghost pet?
They wanted us
out of there.
Works for me.
No, i'm serious.
It looks like they've
been here for a long time.
My grandma used
to always say
that if a child ghost
gets attached to a place,
it's really hard
to cross 'em over.
What do you do
if they won't leave?
Makes my job harder, but i
can't just leave 'em here.
They have to have somebody
waiting for them on the other side.
Good morning, ladies.
How's it going?
We're getting there.
It's a lot of stuff.
I don't believe
we've met.
I'm andrea moreno.
I'm melinda's partner.
Dirk abrams,
the last occupant
of kensington arms.
Mr. Abrams
is also the owner.
Former owner,
sorry to say.
Where did you
find this?
Oh, down
in the basement.
So was it a hotel
back then as well?
An orphanage.
It was an orphanage?
St. Michael's
home for boys.
Built in the '20s.
Wow. This place
has not changed a bit.
Oh, it has.
There was
a bad fire in 1956.
Destroyed
half the place.
Was anyone killed
in the fire?
Uh, several
young boys.
Uh, very sad.
It was a big story
around here
for a long time.
Andrea, why don't you
show mr. Abrams
everything that we brought up
so far, and i'll be right there.
Ok.
Uh, so... take a look.
All right.
* he played one *
* he played knickknack
on my thumb *
* with a knickknack
paddywhack, give a dog a bone *
* this old man
came rolling home *
he played one *
* he played knickknack... *
oh!
Oh!
Here you go.
Ok.
Rat wants
to talk to you.
And who's rat?
You'll find out.
Follow me.
You, come here.
Excuse me?
We got ourselves
a problem here, lady.
Let's try names.
I'm melinda.
He's rat. I'm marty.
And victor's hiding
somewhere. That's what he does.
Who dialed your number?
Sorry, rat.
How come you can see us?
Um, it's a gift i have.
I was born with it.
Some gift.
What makes you think
you can just walk out
of here with our stuff?
It's not really your stuff.
It belongs to mr. Abrams, and he
hired us to auction it off for him.
Now, do you boys
understand why?
We know we're dead, lady.
We ain't stupid.
We are?
Shut up.
Look, we don't want
no action.
Auction.
Whatever.
This is our house. This is where
we live, and that's our furniture.
We want it back.
Now, run along.
You know, let me explain
something to you, r...
do i really need
to call him rat?
Ok.
Man, i wish
i was there for that.
Now, wait. How is it they
can make things explode again?
They build up so much energy
that they can get really powerful.
Then...
they break things.
Great. Another fun fact
from melinda.
I'm gonna go back to the shop
with these guys and unload.
See you later.
Meet you down there.
Wait for me.
Excuse me, young lady.
May i ask
what you're doing?
And you are?
This is my property.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I'm melinda gordon.
We're getting ready
to have an auction.
Tobias northrop.
Oh. Hello.
Mr. Abrams has told me
a lot about you.
He said that you saw this place on the
internet and bought it over the phone.
I wanted to check
with mr. Abrams
and make sure he'll have
everything out by sunday.
We're right on schedule.
What are you gonna do with it?
Bed and breakfast?
I'm gonna tear it down.
But why?
Good day, miss gordon.
Go.
Nice to meet you.
Marty said you
told him we were dead.
You didn't know?
Yeah. I knew.
I mean, we never
get hungry.
We never sleep.
Really?
And nobody can see us.
Except you.
It's got to be dead.
Wow.
You are very smart.
Yeah.
But i'm afraid
of the dark.
Oh!
Me, too.
Will you spend
the night with us?
What?
Oh... sweetie,
i don't think i can.
I have to go home.
Do you ever leave the inn?
No. Rat says our feet
will catch fire.
Why would he say that?
He's real smart
about that kind of stuff.
What did you say
your name was again?
Vic.
I wish i could help you.
Nobody stays no more.
Everyone just leaves.
No. Lew peterson?
He's the only friend i have who
actually knows how to put a furnace in.
But is he reliable? You
haven't seen him in months.
Yeah, since our wedding.
I know lew's not exactly a poster
boy for good manners, but...
he's your friend.
Yeah.
And i respect that, and i wouldn't
come between the two of you.
But let's face it.
He's rude and he's crude.
He's an eighth-grader
with a car.
He speaks well of you.
He doesn't like me.
He thinks i'm the yoko ono
of your friendship,
that i stole you away from
the bars and the nightlife.
All right. I'll ask him to stay
somewhere else while we work on the house.
You asked him to stay here?
Now we're gonna have to host
him tonight and for the rest...
actually, i was kind of hoping
that you would host him tonight.
I got paged for the midnight
to 8 shift, and i really...
well, in that case,
there is something
that i have to do tonight
that i forgot to tell you.
Well, it's
a little extreme.
3 little boys
need my help.
3 dead boys.
You're gonna spend the
night in a haunted house...
the bush.
Your plant.
A haunted house alone?
I feel like i'm
in a john carpenter film.
I'll probably sleep better
there than here with party boy.
And if the inn is destroyed with them
in it, they'll be earthbound forever.
And i'm not gonna be alone. Mr.
Abrams still has a room there.
Oh. Old mr. Abrams
has a room there.
That makes me feel better. The
guy could be a serial killer.
It's safe. I promise.
You promise?
I promise.
Ok. Just keep thinking about
how much money we're saving
with lew helping me
put in the furnace.
Oh, whatever it is,
it's not worth it.
He's changed.
You'll see.
Whoo-hoo!
Oh! Oh!
It's ok.
He just grazed it.
Hey, mel.
Hey, lew.
You look great.
Oh, you're too kind.
Don't burn the house down.
She's still
pissed at me.
Well, you did pass out before
the wedding even started.
And now you just ran over
her favorite plant.
My bad.
Hello!
Mr. Abrams?
Uh...
it's melinda gordon.
Hello!
Oh!
Working late?
Hi.
Mr. Abrams, i hope
i didn't scare you.
Just thought
i'd spend the night
and get an early
start on tomorrow.
You only live
a mile up the road.
Yeah, well, it is
our first auction.
You know... lot to prove.
Whatever.
Well, i met
mr. Northrop before.
Strange sort of man,
isn't he?
Did you tell him that this
used to be an orphanage?
Nope. He never asked.
Did you know that he's
planning to tear it down?
He's got the demolition
scheduled for monday.
He does?
I could really use
that extra time.
You could?
Well, yeah.
The extra time to convince him
to not tear down
this great old place.
Thank you.
Uh...
do you believe in ghosts,
ms. Gordon?
Uh...
yes.
I do.
I think they're here... now.
They're all around.
Brrr!
Brr.
Yeah.
I thought you boys
wanted company.
You guys have been practicing this
stuff for a long time now, huh?
Ain't much else to do.
What are you doing here?
I thought you asked...
i mean...
um, i know that you boys
are as tough as nails.
Especially you.
And i thought
maybe i could help.
You wanna help us?
Then come downstairs.
Ok.
Peter pan.
That's our favorite.
Can you read?
No.
None of us can.
Ernie could read. He
knew all of the words.
Who's ernie?
He's a pal of ours.
Is he here with you?
No. Not for a long time.
So...
why don't you
tell me about rat
and why he's so mad
at everybody.
He says you can't
trust anybody.
He trusts you.
Yeah, he does.
And he trusted
his brother.
He had a brother?
Mikey.
It was his
little brother.
How come no one
ever adopted them?
Somebody
adopted mikey.
But they left rat here.
There was a lot of crying
when that happened.
So he has
a brother out there.
He got drowned.
Big wave hit him
at the beach.
That's when rat said we
can only trust each other.
So tell us the story
about peter pan.
Uh, that would be easier
if there was some light.
You are very talented.
Ok.
"There was only one boy
who never grew up,
"and his name
was peter pan.
"See him there,
floating over their beds?
"He came in through
the open window
"while wendy, michael, and
john were sound asleep.
"He taught them
to think happy thoughts
and sprinkle them with
pixie dust so they could... "
boys: Fly.
I know what you're
trying to do.
You're trying
to get us out of here.
Melinda, you slept
at the inn?
Those kids needed me.
They're under the influence
of this older kid, rat.
There's
a ghost named rat?
Yeah. If i don't get them to cross over
before that building is torn down...
torn down? But that's
such a great old place.
That's why the new owner is gonna hear
from the grandview historical society.
I didn't know there was a
grandview historical society.
There isn't yet.
Hey, you should
be vice president.
I got a "no. "
Anybody got a "no"?
I got a "no"
in the back.
I got a big fat "no. "
Sold.
Grandview
historical society.
Never heard of it.
Well, it's
a small group.
We wanna present you with some options
so that you can still make a profit.
Ms. Gordon, what's wrong
with providing
luxury housing for hundreds,
as opposed to an old hotel
that nobody stays at anymore?
Can you just
postpone the demolition?
Give us some time to...
to what?
To look for a way to preserve
a crumbling structure
that once housed
hapless orphans.
Ms. Gordon, i appreciate the
good work you're trying to do,
but new construction
it will be.
Jim?
Baby?
Sorry, mel.
I didn't hear you.
That's ok.
I'm used to it.
This stuff really works.
I can feel my skin tightening.
It, uh, tingles.
Where's jim?
Don't know.
I'm exhausted. Can you just get
him out of here for the night?
Take him to the movies
or something.
You don't like him
at all, do you?
No, it's not that.
It's just...
i don't get you two.
I've known the guy
since we were 14.
He's the kind of guy you can
always call 3:00 in the morning
if you car wouldn't start
or you were lost or worse.
He's always been there
for me, no questions asked,
and that counts
for a lot.
Ok. I get it.
I'll find something
for us to do tonight.
But it ain't
gonna be the movies.
Why not?
No margaritas.
Oops.
Hi, mel.
Did you guys have fun?
I kept him
out of trouble.
Honey, you remember
terry and ralph.
Uh, hello.
Guys, um, get a beer.
Get a beer.
I'm real... i'm sorry about
the intrusion. I'm sorry.
No, it's fine. I should
get back to the inn anyway.
Wait a minute. What, now?
It'll be quieter there. I
need to talk to mr. Abrams.
I won't be long.
I'll keep 'em quiet. I'll
put 'em in the backyard.
No, it's ok. You guys have
your fun. I just figured it out.
It's not about me
not liking lew.
It's about me not liking
who you are around lew.
I'm sorry
that it's so late.
Oh, nonsense.
I'm happy for the company.
I've been doing a lot
of reading on the fire,
and it said
that 4 boys were killed.
I thought there
were only 3.
No. 4.
Rat, uh, vic,
marty, and, uh...
ernie. Ernie sutter.
He and rat were
the best of friends.
They were inseparable.
When they found
their bodies,
you would have expected to find
ernie lying right next to rat.
But that's not
what happened.
They never found
ernie's body.
The 2 little ones were...
were holding hands.
The dog was
right there with them.
Tell him to shut up.
He doesn't know what
he's talking about.
Later.
Sorry?
Late.
It's getting late.
Right you are.
He's always shooting
his damn mouth off!
Oh!
Well...
like i said...
it gets spooky around here.
You see how wendy
takes care of peter
after he returns home
hurt from his battles?
Like a mom would do.
Ah, but she was so much
more than a mom to peter.
She was his friend, and they
had lots of adventures together.
And that is what made
tinkerbell very jealous.
Oh.
Boys, come back.
Did i scare them off?
It is so good to see you.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
When you didn't
come home, i got worried.
What's wrong?
It's the boys.
They break my heart.
Maybe we should
stay here tonight.
It's a small bed.
I think we'll manage.
Ok.
Hey.
What's the matter?
It's something.
Oh, i can't believe it.
They're getting ready
for monday.
If northrop tears
this place down,
it's like cutting
the string on a balloon.
These kids will have
nothing to hold on to.
Hello.
I was just hooking the
power up to the fuse box.
The whole thing just sort of shorted
out on me. Sparks were flying.
It scared
the hell out of me.
There's no... fire.
There's no fire, though.
You're just gonna have
to do some rewiring.
I'll be right there.
A little, uh, emergency.
Oh, what, the house?
Lew's there.
Oh, no. It's, um,
nothing we can't handle, ok?
I can do...
you're gonna be all right?
Yeah.
All right.
Good-bye.
I heard what you
said last night.
Whoa. What are you
talking about?
Old man abrams.
Tells the fire story
all the time?
He don't know
the most important part.
What's the most
important part?
I knew the way, all right.
Wake up! Wake up!
I always knew what to do.
Get up, everyone!
Wake up!
Get up, everyone! Get up!
That's why they followed me.
No, rat! No!
Up here! Come on!
Except this one time.
Ernie, you're going
the wrong way!
This one night...
the doors were locked.
Who knows why?
New janitor, new rule.
Come on.
I never knew.
I looked down at the guys.
I could see they were scared.
Don't sit down, you guys.
We got to find our way out.
Come on.
It was my fault.
I got them all killed.
It wasn't your fault.
Yes, it was.
You were trying
to help them get out.
How could you know that
those doors would be locked?
They trusted me.
I let them down.
That is not true.
They still love you,
don't they?
Most of the time they do.
That's because you're a
family, rat. You're peter.
They're the lost boys,
and they need you.
That why
i keep 'em together,
make sure nothing
happens to them.
You can come in, boys.
It's time for you
to move on.
You can't
stay here forever.
We don't know
anything but here.
Did you see
the bulldozer out front?
They're gonna
tear this place down.
And you'll just have to trust
me that there's a better place.
There's nothing...
nothing to be afraid of.
You think they want us at
the place she's talking about?
Nobody wants us.
This is the only place
we know we're safe.
That's why
we stay together.
I'll tell you what.
Just come outside
with me for one day.
Let me prove to you
that you can be safe
somewhere
other than here.
Sounds ok.
Don't you think, rat?
If you want your feet
to burn, go ahead.
no fire.
He lied.
Maybe not.
Maybe he really thinks
they do go on fire.
Come on, boys.
Why can't we just
stay with you?
Well, because...
we both love you
and everything.
You could be
our mother.
I would be proud
to have you two as my sons.
Any mother would.
Then why can't we?
Because you don't
belong here anymore.
There's
somewhere better.
Can you go
swimming there?
Eat ice cream?
Uh, i don't know
for sure.
But what i do
know is that...
you'll be wanted there.
And no one will ever
abandon you again.
But you won't
be there, will you?
Someday.
Someday i will.
And for you, it'll feel
like no time at all.
If rat don't go, we don't go.
We're moving on to our next
item, ladies and gentlemen...
lot number 85,
which is a beautiful
late '40s-era cradle.
We're gonna start
the bidding at $20.
150!
200!
2,000!
Wonderful. $20.
Shh.
25. ok, wonderful.
Uh, 25.
3 million!
Can i get 30?
A trillion!
Shh!
So that's how it works, huh?
Take our stuff, sell it,
keep the dough.
You see that store
over there? Go.
Now.
Andrea: Whoa! Hey! It's
not me that's on sale.
We're gonna move on
to lot, um, 86.
This isn't about old beat-up
furniture, is it, rat?
There's something
i got to ask you.
What is it?
And you can't lie
to me either.
I got to know the truth.
Grown-ups always lie.
I promise.
Am i gonna see
my brother mikey again?
Will he be there
once we cross over?
Yes, rat.
Your brother will be
right there waiting for you.
They said i'd see him again.
A family took him...
and not me.
They lied.
It's the truth
this time, i promise.
And marty and vic,
they'll come?
They're your family.
You'll all be together.
Thank you.
Well, he can fix it.
I knew it. I didn't
think it was that bad.
Lew, i can't do this,
all right?
Do what?
Play along, make believe that
this does not piss me off.
Take it easy.
No "take it easy. "
You come into my house,
you act like a fool.
You disrespect my wife.
I did not...
lew, wake up, ok?
You're my friend,
but we're not 18 anymore.
Look, pack your stuff.
I'll see you later.
Fine.
Andrea: 25. ok. Wonderful.
We're at $25.
This lovely
lamp here for $25.
Do i hear 30? $30.
30. anybody with 35?
$35, sir.
$35.
Is there anybody for 40?
Anybody? Ok.
I think i might just
bid on this piece.
Should've made it part
of the deal with abrams.
You're ernie, aren't you?
You're the boy
that got away.
That's how you knew that the
kensington was an orphanage.
You were there.
You don't have to pay me.
It belongs to you.
You have me confused
with somebody else.
Ernest sutter. That was
your name, wasn't it?
No idea what
you're talking about.
Best of luck with
the rest of the auction.
Don't go, please.
I cannot tell you how
important this is to me
and the boys
who died there.
You were there,
weren't you?
I wanna level
that horrible place.
I wanna turn it into a grave.
I've spent 50 years trying
to outrun those memories.
And every child
i pass on the sidewalk,
every photo
in a magazine, i see them.
They died and i lived. Why?
You were only a child.
They were my family.
I can help you.
How?
Boy: Come on!
I used to hide
in the basement.
My alone place.
No one ever looked
for me down there.
Sometimes i'd just
sleep or daydream.
Or sometimes i'd read.
I kept my little
secrets down there...
matches, candle.
That night, though...
that night
i heard homer barking.
I thought he
was in trouble.
I went to find him.
I meant to come back.
I meant to blow out
the candle.
But one thing
led to another.
They called bedtime.
I forgot all about it.
Wake up!
I didn't even
remember it until later.
When the fire started, i was just
trying to get out like everyone else.
No, rat! No!
Ernie!
Ernie, it's
the wrong way! Come on!
No! Up here!
Ernie!
Up here! Come on!
And when i saw it burning
and i didn't see
the boys get out...
i ran.
I just kept running.
Somehow i knew
that no matter what,
i was not coming back here.
Next day i saw the front
page of a newspaper.
I saw the pictures
of the fire
and the boys,
and one of them was me.
12-year-old orphan,
ernest sutter, was dead.
I remember climbing
into a trash bin and crying
till my throat hurt.
This was my friend
rat's hideout.
Ronald aikens tracy.
R.a. t.
He hated his name.
Loved his nickname.
He was one
tough customer.
Nobody messed with you
if you were ok with rat.
You got to tell him.
What if i told you
that rat was still here?
What?
The boys are still here.
I don't understand.
They're not dead?
They are dead.
But their spirits...
well, they were
afraid to move on.
That can't be. I don't
believe in that kind of stuff.
Yeah. Most people don't.
Tell him...
it's still there...
where he hid it.
Uh, he says
that it's still there
where you hid it.
This must be a dream.
Rat, is that you?
Tell him to use his indoor
voice. We ain't deaf.
He says for you to use
your indoor voice.
We ain't deaf.
Son of a... it is rat.
Tell him homer's here.
You got your teeth fixed.
You're really getting old.
Hey, one at a time.
Ok. They want you to know
that homer's here.
Marty thinks you're getting old,
and rat says your teeth are fixed?
No cavities.
They're all false.
Mine fell out.
They're laughing.
Where's rat?
Right in front of you.
You were
the brave one, rat.
You were trying
to save us.
You always knew
the right thing to do.
I can't tell you
how many times
when i was
out on the road
and i'd think back on all
the things you taught me.
Not book things. Like how to
survive and laugh at yourself.
And i'm still
always thinking,
what would rat do
if he was here?
You're so full of it, ernie,
it's coming out of your ears.
He wants to know
if you really think that.
Yes, i do.
Rat.
I would give all the money
i have in the world
to see you one more time.
All of you.
You ain't gonna
make me cry, ernie.
He's crying.
Don't tell him that.
Tell him...
that he could tear down
the inn if he wants.
We're going.
Rat says they're leaving.
Where are they going?
On a new adventure.
Good-bye, pal.
Do you see it?
Yeah.
A light.
Handsome.
I'm telling
everybody...
that you're my mom.
I ain't
scared, rat.
Me neither.
Mikey.
I can see my brother.
He's laughing at me.
Wherever i've been,
he wants to know.
Good-bye, wendy.
Good-bye, peter.
Are they gone?
Yes.
I never felt
like this before.
Like i'm... i'm...
free.
Thank you.
I hate to admit it,
but now i kind
of feel sorry for him.
Me, too.
He changed, i guess.
I don't know.
I don't think
he changed. You did.
All i know...
is that i'm glad
i have you.
Um, do you wanna
explain that?
Tomorrow. Let's
just go back to bed.
Yeah.
Stop.
www.tvsubtitles.net