Guys.
Give us a hand.
Your end.
1... 2... 3. 1... 2... 3. Go.
Bobby, i'll be right back.
En route with
a 25- to 30-year-old male.
John doe. Victim of
a motorcycle accident.
Arrived on scene
and found the following.
Obvious right femur fracture.
No deformity. Puncture
from the broken bone.
Distinguishing marks...
tattoo from head to toe.
Bobby, what's our e. t. a.?
We're 15 out.
E.t. a. 15 minutes.
Radio: 10-4.
Woman: 911 operator.
Yeah. I'm on forest road,
about 2 miles north
of stoneybrook.
There's been an accident.
Jimmy?
Operator: Are you injured?
Man: No.
There's an ambulance
upside-down in a ditch.
I don't know how bad
anybody's hurt.
Bobby: Jimmy?
Melinda:
Hello?
Woman: Melinda gordon,
please.
Yeah?
This is mercy hospital.
Your husband's
been in an accident
and we need you to come down
as soon as possible.
Do you know where
we're located?
Honey?
Cinnamon.
Oh!
Oh, wow.
I'm sorry.
Would you hold?
Oh. Sorry.
Sorry.
More?
Melinda.
Bobby.
Jim's ok.
He's gonna be ok.
Oh. I was so afraid.
I thought...
i know. I know.
He's ok.
He's gonna be fine.
He's gonna be just fine.
Wait a minute.
Can you see me?
I need your help.
Please? My husband
needs your help.
Is your partner
gonna be ok?
Yes. He'll be fine. This is
jim's clancy's wife, melinda.
This is brad polson. He came across
the accident. Called 911. thank god.
Thank you.
No problem.
Ok, see?
My husband helped you.
Now you have to help him.
Please?
I'm desperate.
Can you see us?
I was driving.
Where are you going?
We had a blowout.
I couldn't hold it.
Hey!
We were transporting.
Patient didn't make it.
Oh, my god.
Does jim know?
No.
Guy had a broken leg,
ruptured femoral artery.
Doc says he
might've died anyway.
Hello?
I need your help!
I need to be with
my husband right now.
Hey, no problem.
If it wasn't for mine, you may
not have a husband right now.
Tell jim i'm sorry.
Oh, am i dead?
No.
Hmm. You never know
with you.
Bobby?
He walked away
without a scratch.
Wh... the patient?
Jim...
look... hey...
no.
No?
Sorry.
Nobody can see me
except you.
Why?
Uh, it's a gift i have.
Can i just tell you,
you're a little pushy.
If you were in my position,
you would be, too.
Don't you think?
Sorry.
It's been a long night.
Who are you?
My name is hope.
Paulson.
How long have you
been dead?
Since july 4th.
They said everything
was gonna be fine.
They told me i had
an ectopic pregnancy.
I didn't even know
i was pregnant.
I'm only 26 years old.
This wasn't supposed
to happen to me.
Not now.
I was gonna be a mommy.
How is that fair?
It isn't.
Sometimes...
in situations like this
after people have passed away,
i help them cross over.
Do you know
what that means?
Yes.
Is that what you want?
No.
No, um...
my husband hasn't been
the same since i...
he blames himself
for what happened.
That's why you
have to help him.
Have you been
with him since...
yes. He hasn't been sleeping,
or all he does is sleep.
He doesn't see his friends
or his parents or mine.
He hasn't read a book
or gone camping.
See, i know him.
He's a wallower.
He could wallow in this
for the rest of his life.
And i don't want that.
You have to make him
see that.
Please?
I'll try.
Oh, hey, whoa. Whoa.
I'm sorry, luv.
That's ok. I gotta go. Call you back.
I didn't hurt you,
did i?
No bumps?
No bruises?
I'm fine. Really.
'Cause i would hate to
have to buy you lunch.
Oh, you're too late.
Oh.
Love the accent, though.
Morning.
Hey!
How's jim?
Coming home today.
Sexy, sensitive,
and indestructible.
I've gotta get me
a man like that.
Oh, i think you just did.
Tall, australian, hot.
Oh, yeah, mate.
The previous owner of
this 14 karat yellow gold
oyster perpetual
with matte dial,
luminous mercedes hands,
center second sweep,
and screw down crown.
Ooh. Screw down crown,
my favorite part.
Guess how much
i paid for it.
Can i see it?
$1,100.
And he was happy
to get it.
Oh. I think that's worth a
little shrimp on the barbie,
don't you?
Hmm...
what?
It's a fake.
No... no. No way!
Vietnamese, probably.
If it was real, you'd see
the model number. Sorry.
Ooh! God, i can't believe
a guy that cute is a crook!
Oh, and i bet his stupid
accent was fake, too.
It is possible that he did not
know that the watch was fake.
I have a feeling
he'll be back.
Ok...
he found a sucker
he could sell to.
A sucker, huh?
When he comes back, we'll
tell him we want our money,
or we call the cops.
Gee, thank you.
I just wanna thank you again
for being such a good samaritan.
Oh, i... i didn't do
anything. Anybody would've.
No. Not anybody.
Thank you.
How long have you
been married?
7 months.
3 years next march
for me.
My wife hope,
she died last summer.
So... i know what you were
going through last night.
You want to talk
about it?
I mean, you don't
have to. Just...
sometimes it helps.
It was the fourth of july,
we were at a barbecue.
We were having a fight.
I don't even remember
about what.
Something stupid.
She was complaining about
having a stomachache.
She wanted to go home.
I was having too much fun
to go home.
I thought... she doesn't wanna be here,
so she's making it difficult for me.
Typical, huh?
So we stayed.
Played softball
like we did every year.
She just fell over.
I thought she was messing
with me, you know?
She wasn't.
She was really hurting.
Someone said to call 911.
So we did.
She was really hurting.
When we got to the hospital,
she was in shock.
Then they told us
she was pregnant.
And i thought this will be
a good story to tell the kid.
There'll be no problem
whatsoever.
The doctor told us the
fallopian tube had ruptured.
She was hemorrhaging.
That's why she had
the stomachache.
They were gonna
have to do surgery.
Afterwards,
everything seemed fine.
The doctor said everything
went smoothly.
So i sat with her
for a little bit.
She was still so out of it...
so i thought it'd be ok
to go home...
take a shower
and change my clothes.
And that's when i
got the call.
There was a nurse there
when i got back.
He had been in the surgery
with her.
He was crying.
When i saw that, i knew.
I just didn't expect that.
But it wasn't your fault.
It was my fault.
And now she's dead.
uh, i'm looking for
my husband, jim clancy?
Cat scan. Room 133.
Thank you.
Ahh! Oh.
Do you have to do that?
Sorry. Have you
talked to brad?
Yes.
And?
You two really loved
each other, didn't you?
Yeah. Yes, very much.
Did he tell you we
met in high school? No.
Detention. I got caught gluing
sharon scomer's locker shut.
He was there because he refused
to tell the principal
that our friend david went to new
york city with our other friend...
yeah. There are
a lot of us here.
How's jim?
Fine.
Yeah. I get to
take him home today.
Oh, i'm sorry.
I'm a crier.
I cry at the drop of a hat,
just like my mother.
I lied to you before.
When i told you i didn't know
i was pregnant.
I did.
I just hadn't told brad.
I knew the moment
we conceived her.
And i just knew
it was a girl.
He wanted a girl.
I had such big plans.
We had so many plans.
Where were you?
Oh, i, uh...
i know. I figured
the hospital...
you must be
in hog heaven.
You know, sometimes it's not
all it's cracked up to be.
Who is it this time?
A young woman
about my age.
Oh, yeah?
What's her deal?
Her deal i'd say is she will
never get to enjoy with her husband
all the things
i love about you
and will never ever take
for granted.
Good answer.
Hey...
i'm happy that it's
not you i'm helping.
Me, too.
Ok, let me
get the door.
Oh, yeah.
I don't have any money.
I can't tip you.
Yeah, right.
Don't get used
to it.
Hey, jim get home ok?
Safe and sound.
And why aren't you
there with him?
As soon as i finish this, i'm
going back and making him dinner.
And he likes this special parmesan
that you can only get at bianchi's.
What?
Well, well, well.
Speaking of
foreign cheese.
All right.
Wait.
Wait. Let me do it.
What, you think
i can't handle it?
I just think maybe we should
keep the emotion out of it.
Fine.
Hi.
Oh, it's you.
Can i help you?
How lucky
am i?
Yeah. I don't get out much.
Pity.
Isn't it?
Look, i was wondering if i
might interest you in something.
Antique, art deco platinum, european
cut diamond and pearl necklace.
May i?
Elegant lustrous spheres...
strung between diamond clusters
with a perfectly formed
teardrop pearl
just hanging from the strand.
It's lovely.
Now i can let it go
for say $2,800.
Suppose i sell you
something...
for, let's say, $1,100 and nobody
but you and i know the truth?
What are you suggesting,
i sold you a bad watch?
Oh, i'm not saying
it's bad,
i mean, it keeps very
good time for a fake.
So you say.
So i say.
Now, how do i know you didn't replace
my watch with that piece of junk?
How do i know you're not
trying to highjack me?
This is a small town,
you know.
Why don't you take that into
account when casting aspersions?
And how'd that go down?
It's better with cheese.
I got the kind you like
from bianchi's.
Do you believe in fate?
Or do you believe we've got some
kind of control over our destiny?
Is that a trick question?
Nope. Serious.
Ok, i guess i'd say
i believe in free will.
What do you mean?
I don't have to love you.
I want to.
I choose to, and however
that affects my destiny,
or whatever god, or the gods
have in store for me,
so be it.
What about, um,
accidents?
Hey, do you wanna talk
about what happened?
I should've checked
the tires on the rig.
Yes. Today you know that.
I knew it yesterday.
It's what i do before
every shift, you know.
I check the meds,
i check the supplies,
i check the gas,
the oil...
i check the tires,
but i didn't yesterday
because
i was late for work.
Because i made you late,
you mean.
No, no.
I didn't mean that.
I didn't mean that
at all.
I love that you, uh...
wanted to make me
french toast
for breakfast.
I love that you
wanted to do that...
for me.
Jim, it was an accident.
It cost someone
his life.
Yes, it did.
You didn't.
Accidents happen. They're
a necessary part of life.
So this happened to me
for a reason.
Now a person is dead.
What kind of reason
is that?
You don't have to be in
for 2 hours.
Yeah, i know.
But i should
get there.
2 hours early?
What are you working on?
"Hope paulson. "
Related to brad?
His wife.
Aw, man.
He saved me.
You save her.
No. She's already dead.
I don't know if you can call
what i'm doing saving her.
It's weird how things
work sometimes.
True.
What are you gonna do?
Brad mentioned a nurse.
His name is derrik lee. He was
there during hope's surgery.
If i can get him to tell brad
exactly why his wife died,
specifically that
he's not responsible,
then maybe i can help
get him some closure.
Hmm.
What?
You realize this all
started with you...
making me french toast?
Yeah. Track it. It led to the
accident, which led to brad,
which led to the hospital,
which led to hope.
I mean, are we
the puppet masters...
or are we just the puppets?
You know, i learned
a long time ago,
never question the cosmic
law of french toast.
Gotta go.
All right.
The what?
Hope: He does this
every day,
hammers the sign
into the ground,
pulls it up before
he goes to work.
Hi.
Wanna buy a house?
Got one. Thanks.
You moving?
Yeah.
I hate this house.
It's nice.
That's what she
used to say.
Can i ask you
something?
About hope's surgery?
Put me in a good mood.
I know it's none
of my business.
It's just you were so
helpful to jim and me,
and i'd like to
return the favor.
You wanna set me up
with someone?
No.
Good.
I have this ability to help
people during otional crisis.
I'm not a shrink
or anything or a kook.
It's just something i've
always been able to do,
and i would love to...
you know what?
I don't need any help.
I don't deserve any help.
Brad, wait.
You know how many houses
i've sold since my wife died?
Exactly none.
I just think it would be
helpful if you'd maybe
talked to someone who was
actually there when hope died.
What's the point?
Because i think what's
causing you so much pain
is the guilt you're feeling
because you weren't there.
I already talked
to the surgeon
and the hospital
administrator.
I even hired a lawyer
who charged me 5,500 bucks
to tell me that whatever we
accomplished wouldn't bring my wife back.
So, you just wanna be
like everyone else
who tells me to get on
with my life. Well, fine.
How 'bout you get on
with my life?
I'll take yours any day.
There. That's derrik lee.
May i?
Mm, please.
Thanks.
Melinda gordon.
Derrik lee.
I haven't seen you
around.
What department
do you work in?
Oh, i'm not
with the hospital.
Oh.
I, um...
how should i say this?
I represent
a former patient of yours.
Former, as in
discharged?
Former as in
dearly departed.
Hope paulson.
You were her surgical nurse,
right?
Are you her lawyer?
No, no, no.
Um, i'm her advocate.
Actually, i'm here
about her husband brad.
I think you met him.
I've a favor to ask.
I'm sorry,
but i can't help you.
Oh, uh, mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee?
Mr. Lee, please.
Derrik, how are you?
I'm good, doctor.
That's the doctor
who operated on me.
Hi, i'm melinda gordon.
Oh, how you doing?
I'm dr. Devine.
You know, derrik was just telling
me what a wonderful surgeon you are.
Really? Well, you know,
without his help,
i'd probably be bagging
groceries down at the supermarket.
That's what happens
when they put old codgers
like me out to pasture.
I doubt that very much,
doctor.
Hope to see soon again,
mrs. Gordon.
Nice to meet you.
What do you want?
Your help.
Really, that's all.
Brad paulson hasn't been doing
so well since his wife's death.
He blames himself.
You were there.
I thought maybe you
could just talk to him.
It won't do any good.
Why not? It's not
like i'm asking you to...
hey. You don't know
what you're asking.
I am asking you to have
a little empathy
for someone whose wife died
in your care.
Ok.
Ok, you wanna know
what happened?
I'll be in the hospital
archives after my shift, 4:00.
I'll show you.
Long time no see.
You stalking me,
sweetheart?
Hardly.
It's a small town.
Perhaps we're just
fated to meet again.
Hmm.
Allow me.
7 bucks.
Fate is cheap.
You're quite funny.
You're easy.
Have dinner with me.
I said you were easy.
Why not?
Are you married?
No.
Boyfriend?
Not at present.
I'll let you choose
the restaurant then.
I'll think about it.
Lovely.
Hello?
Aah!
Are you crazy?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to scare you.
I just about
had a heart attack.
Ok, well, you weren't
in the archives,
so i came looking for you.
I got lost, ok?
You know, they say
this place is haunted.
I've got news for you.
They're right.
Now let's go.
I don't know
where i'm going.
What's this?
You'll see.
Doctor on videotape:
Suction. Suction.
Doctor, the back
of the tube...
dr. Devine closed without suturing
the backside of the fallopian tube.
That's what i think
killed hope paulson.
What? How is
that possible?
Ego, incompetence.
An accident.
Things happen.
But if you've
got it on tape,
why hasn't anybody
done anything about it?
Because dr. Devine
has been here for 30 years.
He's respected and beloved,
so he's damn near
untouchable.
So nobody did anything?
You didn't?
I tried. Ok?
I filed a complaint
with the review board.
It was investigated
and dismissed.
It's my word against his,
and nobody's gonna take my word.
I can't believe it.
Look, melinda, i'm sorry,
but...
that's just the way it is.
Can i keep this?
Yeah, why not?
This case is dead and buried.
So how did a nice girl like you
end up in a small town like this?
Shouldn't you be off running
the world somewhere?
Actually, i already did.
I was an assistant d. a.
In new york.
Fraud cases, mostly.
Tough guys.
You sold me a counterfeit
watch, didn't you, anthony?
Hi. Would you like
to hear the specials?
Hold on, junior.
You're gonna do the
right thing here, anthony,
starting with
paying me back.
And if you don't,
i'm gonna make it my singular
ambition to put your ass in jail.
I can just come back.
That's no problem.
Don't bother.
You know where
to find me.
Ah, just the check then?
Ok. Ok.
Woman: I love you.
Bye-bye.
Drive carefully.
See you tonight.
Come in.
Mrs. Devine?
Yes.
Hi. I'm melinda gordon.
Yes?
I was just wondering if i could
talk to you about your husband.
My husband has an illness.
Early onset dementia.
I was in denial for years.
On any given day,
he still is.
He's this bad?
Not yet.
But he will be.
I made those cards for him.
It'll help here
in the house.
But i can't protect him
out there.
At work, for example.
It must be so devastating to see
your husband going through this.
I've been praying for somebody
to help me help him.
I don't know
where you came from,
but you are a blessing.
I think my husband
might say it's fate.
Fate or not,
mine won't go gently.
No.
But you'll be right
there to hold his hand.
Yes, i will.
Dr. Devine's
losing his mind?
Losing his mind
would be a blessing.
It's deteriorating
slowly.
Sometimes people know what's happening
to them and are able to hide it
until they can't,
and then...
sometimes
people get hurt.
You mean like me.
Yes, like you.
Because of his illness,
dr. Devine forgot to properly
suture your fallopian tube,
something he's done
a thousand times.
He made a mistake?!
Is that what
you're telling me?
I'm sorry.
Am i supposed
to feel good
that my wife
was the victim
of a doctor's
stupid mistake?
No. But if you'll allow
yourself, maybe relieved.
At least now you know
you weren't to blame.
Brad, if you could talk to hope
right now, what would you say?
I can't,
so what's the point?
Why can't you?
She's dead.
Can you talk
to the dead?
He always was
a know-it-all.
Brad, if you could say
anything at all,
anything, what would it be?
I'd say...
i'd say...
good-bye.
I can't.
"Brad...
"i know you feel
like this is your fault,
"but i want you to know
that i don't blame you.
"You've always taken better care
of me than i have myself.
"From the day i first...
hope, takes over: ... laid
eyes on you in detention.
And that hasn't
changed today.
I never felt more
in love with you
than when i watched you all
worried and sweaty and care-worn,
running beside the gurney
when they wheeled me in here.
So please, please...
don't wallow.
Oh, and if i'm not awake
when you get back...
don't forget to feed
daisy and walk her.
Melinda's voice joins:
See you tomorrow.
I love you.
Hope. "
Well...
i guess we're even.
Thank you.
Oh. Heh.
Can i help you? Um, do
you have an appointment?
No. No, but i'd like to help you
if you'll let me.
What do you mean?
I don't, uh...
i know about your condition.
What condition?
I talked to your wife.
Margaret?
Yes.
I've been to your house.
I've seen the cards.
She told me everything.
I don't believe you.
She would never...
your wife has been dead
for 2 years.
Margaret?
For god's sake.
You have to stop practicing
medicine, matthew.
That's why i stayed.
That's the only reason i
stayed, to help you do that.
She says you have to stop
practicing medicine.
She stayed to help you.
You had such
a wonderful career.
You've achieved everything
you ever wanted to.
It's time to let go.
I'm calling security.
Wait.
There was a proverb he used
to quote. He'll remember.
She says that you used
to quote a proverb.
Who is this skilled physician,
but he who prevents illness?
She says, who's this
skilled physician...
but he...
it's he...
who can prevent...
illness. Yes.
You're not that man
anymore, my love.
Margaret:
I think you know that.
But how?
How could you
possibly have known?
She says it
breaks her heart,
but you're not
that doctor anymore.
You don't have
to pretend anymore.
She's giving you
permission not to.
Hey! Guess what miracle
happened while you were out.
Can't imagine.
The watch guy showed up.
Apparently, he just
couldn't live with himself
knowing
he'd ripped us off.
Huh...
i guess the glass
really is half full today.
Thanks, bobby.
Bobby: Hey,
no problem.
That was bobby.
You told him no softball tonight, right?
The police id'd
my john doe.
Turns out he was released
from prison last week in ohio.
7 years
for attempted murder.
God.
Told his cellmate
that when he got out
he was gonna find his old
lady and "fix her for good. "
He was 2 miles from her house
when he crashed the motorcycle.
So... if i hadn't
picked him up
or if he'd recovered...
he might have come back
and killed his wife.
Well...
once again...
cosmic law of french toast.
]sighs]
Come in.
oh...
www.tvsubtitles.net