So are you a knick fan?
10 million a year
they're paying Larry Brown.
You're from here?
No.
Out of town?
Suit yourself.
You sure this is where
you wanna be?
Did you hear me?
Walter Derbin, age 52.
His body was found
in his cab in east harlem.
He was blindfolded
and shot once in the chest.
Death was caused by
knife stab through his ear.
he broke off
the handle
and put the blade
lodged in his brain
it's the same signature
as two other murders.
Rachel Holman, 24,
found in her apartment
3 weeks ago on the lower east side.
And kaveh surrani, 30.
The police found him
2 weeks later
in his painting studio
in hell's kitchen.
Different locations,
different victimology.
It's possible we're looking for someone
who'll hunt indiscriminately.
- Nypd have any leads?
- Guy's a ghost
he kills at night.
There's no witnesses.
Is the nypd feeling
the strain?
Well, they've withheld details so the press
hasn't sniffed out a link between the murders.
With no discernable victim patterns,
the killer's practically impossible to stop.
Did you know the original zodiac killer
actually continually changed his victims.
Young, old, men, women,
white, black.
Exactly, and he killed for 30 years
without ever being caught.
Criminal Minds
Season 01 Episode 17
W.H. Auden said:
"Murder is unique
"in that it abolishes the party it injures.
"So that society must take
the place of the victim,
and on his behalf,
demand atonement or grant forgiveness."
This is not how I planned to spend
a few days home in new york.
I'd kill for an afternoon at barney's
and dinner at il cantinori.
I'm looking forward
to seeing new york.
You've never been
to new york?
We've never had
an unsub there.
I thought you were gonna talk to Reid
about taking some vacation time.
What's vacation time?
Reid, it's a one hour flight.
Well, if we have some time,
I'll show you around.
It's 3 hour
train ride, man.
Ok, here's what we know.Blitz attackers
are almost always male.
He got picked up in the pouring rain
by a new york cabbie,
so we definitely know
he's not a brother.
The fact that he kills
in a major urban setting
without detection
indicates he's highly intelligent.
How intelligent
can he be?
And blitz attackers
are textbook disorganized killers.
Yeah, but he brings along
a murder kit.
Blindfold, knife.
How disorganized can he be?
We'll split up.
We'll take the last two crime scenes.
In the meantime, let's talk about
what we can agree on.
A blindfold likely
means one of two things.
The unsub might
blindfold them initially
if he's unsure of killing them
and wants to avoid detection.
Exactly.
But since we know the cab driver
couldn't have been blindfolded when
he drove the unsub,
we're looking at reason number 2.
Blindfolding a victim
suggests the unsub feels remorse.
Doesn't want his victims
to look at him...
as he kills them.
What's in that building?
Nothing.It's been vacant for
a couple of months.
This train goes express after midnight.
It doesn't even stop here.
He picked this spot beforehand.
His last fare was logged in an address
on church street.
You have any idea
what's there?
Church is an entry point
for brooklyn.
There's a dive there where the cabbies
stop for coffee before the overnight shift.
Explains how
he got a cab.
This guy's definitely
not disorganized.
Rachel holman.
"Change of address" card.
She just moved in. Hadn't even
filled out yet.
So she probably didn't
know her neighbors,
and they weren't likely
to check in on her.
Nope.
I also found this.
It's a printout of A.A.
Meetings in the area.
She was starting a new life.
Hey, you guys, check this out.
The cops' theory is that
she was home and the unsub broke in
through the front window and surprised her.
But look. This is
the gunshot to the chest.
This is the knife
to the head.
So then after
she was shot,
she tried to run away
from him toward the door.
Exactly.
He was already in the apartment
when she got home.
The hallway's the only
room in the apartment with no windows.
No one could see him,
so he just waited patiently.
So...
she comes home...
and she opens the door...
and she walks in the hallway.
She walks down, and then...
bam, he shoots her
right here.
But she tries
to run away...
and he's on her.
So why didn't he just
shoot her again?
Why stab her and break the blade
off in her head?
Well, there are a number of
possibilities.
Through the ear is
the softest path to the brain.
Snapping the handle's
also common in prison shankings.
Break it off,
other guy can't
pull the blade out.
What's the other
possibility?
Lawrence bittaker
and roy norris
drove ice picks into their victim's heads
and broke off the handle.
It's possible our unsub
is sort of a, uh,
serial-killer groupie.
So is this guy an ex-con
or some nut job with an amazon account?
This particular unsub
presents a mixed profile.
No offense,
then what good is it?
The profile's just a starting point
for narrowing down the suspects.
For instance, the fact that the unsub
shoots his victims first
suggests that he needs a quick and
effective means of controlling the situation.
It's possible that he
feels he can't overpower his victims.
It could be that he has
a physical problem.
Or that he's not confidant just
because he's small.
We now know he has a high
degree of organization.
That coupled with the fact
he hunts at night
means he probably has
a steady job.
So we're looking for
a small, angry white guy with a day job?
Maybe it's wilson.
Cut it!
No, that's all right.That's all right.
You're right.
There's a lot
we still don't know, but
we do know this:
These are not
blitz attacks.
They're too controlled.
These are absolutely
executions.
An unsub's signature--
is his own extremely
rare combination of m.O. And ritual.
An unsub kills to
satisfy an inner need,
and he'll continue
killing until that inner need,
which is based on
a ritual, is lived out perfectly.
Because reality
never lives up to fantasy,
this becomes an impossibility.
In other words,
he's not gonna stop killing
until we catch him.
Ok. Hit the streets
and keep your head on a swivel.
Thank you very much.
Hi. Jennifer jareau.
We spoke on the phone.Detective bennett.
- Hello.
- Agent Hotchner.
So I spoke to
your point man.
I reiterated how important it is
to keep the crime scene details under wraps,
but it would go a long way if it came
out of your mouth, too.
You got it.
If this guy's who we think he is, we're talking
terror like New York hasn't seen since sum of sam.
May I help you?
Are you ok?
So this is where
terror starts.
How'd they find him?
- Night janitor.
- He see anything?
No, but he remembered
a parishioner who was here earlier.
- So there's a potential witness.
- Right there.
- This lady?
- Mm-hmm.
- Help?
- Yeah.
First public killing.
He's getting bolder, huh?
He didn't let his surroundings
alter his method.
He's meticulous.
Presentation is
important as the kill
as soon as the police
asked me if I'd seen anything,
I had a sickly feeling.
- So you saw him?
- Not his face.
He had a hood on
and he kept his head down.
But something about
his behavior unsettled you?
I'm sorry.
I should have known.
There's no way that someone could know
something like this.
It almost felt like
he couldn't hear me,
like he was in his
own world, you know?
You spoke to him?
I just asked if he was ok.
And he didn't speak?
He didn't even look up.
I couldn't stop
watching his hands.
They were moving,
like he was playing a piano
or fingering
a rosary maybe.
He could have killed me.
Unless he's not
killing at random.
And whatever these people have in common's
what got them killed.
I'm sorry.
Would it be possible to maybe...
slide that thing
out of his ear?
I thought maybe he was uncomfortable
being in this parish.
Why would it be uncomfortable?
Because of all that...
business.
A year ago, the rector
was indicted for pedophilia.
A lot of people
stopped worshipping here.
But father Breeman was tried in a court
of law and found innocent.
It's not my place
to question that.
He's not using just any knife.
It's made of flint.
As in stone?
In egyptian mythology, flint was the symbol
for protection and retribution.
With hieroglyphics, they used to depict
dangerous animals
like scorpions
and snakes being
cut with flint knives
in order to render them powerless.
Anything strike you as strange?
The blood's all
on the inside.
Fount of all knowledge.
Check my flow.
I need you to check all the victims
and see if any were charged with a crime.
Ok. You wanna time me, or should I just
dazzle you off the clock?
Ok. Kaveh surrani.
Vehicular manslaughter.
Tried and found not guilty
july 2002.
Rachel holman. Convicted
of cocaine possession, 2004.
oh, baby girl.
Just say no.
No acquittals?
Uh...wait.Hold on.
Same case. She was also
up on charges for administring
a fatal dose of heroin to her boyfriend.
Jury found her not guilty.
Can we go 3 for 3?
Yahtzee.
Our cabbie,
walter derbin.
Spousal battery.
Bastard!
- But he was innocent?
- If you wanna call it that.
Charges were dropped
mid-trial 4 months ago.
- You're a genius.
- You're just saying that 'cause it's true.
Thanks.
If the victim was blindfolded first,
the blood would have flowed over the blindfold.
He puts it on
after he kills them.
All 3 charged with a felony.
All 3 found innocent.
And that didn't show up
on your men's radar?
Acquittals? No.
Why is it important?
Because we have
a new profile.
We know believe these killings
aren't random.
We might be dealing
with a vigilante.
The unsub first shoots his victims
in order to subdue them.
Flint knife then provides
both an efficient kill
and symbolic retribution.
Finally, the victim is blindfolded,
like the statute of lady justice.
This particular unsub,
he displays both
a heightened--
it's actually almost
a poetic sense of right and wrong.
Serial vigilantes
are extremely rare.
The exaggerated drama of these killings
suggest that they're somehow personal.
He, or someone close to him,
is likely the victim of a violent crime.
His first killing was possibly
against his original attacker.
And since then he's developed
an overblown sense of justice
in order to justify that killing to himself.
Because he chooses
the imagery of lady justice,
it's possible we're
dealing with someone who works
in or around
the criminal justice system.
Lawyer, paralegal,
bailiff, even a judge.
We'll cross-check
unsolved murders
against suspects
in assault cases
and victims who work
in the system.
Whatever the unsub's job,
he's someone who's
a cog in the machine.
He's overworked,
undervalued.
He's used to not being
noticed.
His sense of theatrics
is a way to enhance his own self-esteem,
convince himself
he has a higher purpose.
And he also knows that people look
right through him.
Being faceless is his best defense
against protection.
He's everyone.
One last thing.
We need you to close ranks.
The more details slip out,
the more he'll feed off it.
We don't want him believing he captured
the public's fear or imagination.
Too late.
The afternoon edition's leading
with the vigilante story.
How did they get it?
I don't know.
You were worried about this guy becoming
another son of Sam.
Now we might be dealing
with a vigilante folk hero like bernhard goetz.
So you know there was a big hole
in the profile you presented back there.
Can you pass the moo shoo, please?
What's the hole?
I left out the possibility
our unsub might be a cop.
Well, the do know the system.
They're definitely
overworked and underpaid.
They see so much
injustice every day
they can easily take matters
into their own hands.
When someone like
our victim is killed,
police refer to the murder
as a public-service murder.
You know how many rapists
i saw walk during my sex-crime days?
None of the victims,
they didn't want to press charges.
Or the juries, they said
that she was asking for it.
It was enough
to make you explode.
It's a long way from
feeling like that
and actually committing
murder, don't you think?
Not really.
Excuse me. Can I get
a fork, perhaps?
Did you know that
experts credit confucius
with the advent of
the chopstick?
He equated knives with
acts of aggression.
You don't know how
to use them, do you?
It's like trying to forage for dinner
with a pair of number 2 pencils.
Ok, here,
let me help you.
- Oh, the rubber-band.
Well, new york city cops do have a lot of
pressure on 'em.
Every move they make
is scrutinized.
You know, the first cases
of criminal profiling
happened when
a new york city cop
asked a criminal
psychiatrist friend
to help with
the mad bomber case.
The mad bomber was a major inspiration
for the unabomber.
He eluded cops in new york for 16 years,
starting in 1940.
But he kept his promise and never set off
a single bomb during the second world war.
Psychiatrist james brussels,
he developed a profile
so accurate
he predicted that when
they caught the bomber,
he'd be wearing a double-breasted suit
and it would be buttoned.
You guys,
we're here in new york
and even when we're not
talking about our case,
we end up talking about
another profiler.
You're right.
So, elle...
are you seeing anyone?
Uh, gideon...
why didn't you tell the cops
that it might be one of their own?
If we're gonna catch the guy,
we need all the help
the cops can give us.
The last thing i want to do
is accuse one of them of murder.
Gideon.
It's absolutely
incredible.
1.3 billion people
stay nourished using these things.
Yeah. Ok. I got it.
He just took out a cop killer.
His name's shawn cooley.
One year ago, he killed
2 port authority cops.
And he walked
because the only witness against him
was shot 6 times outside his apartment.
It might be worth having your
men re-canvas this morning.
People are more likely
to talk in the day.
- They feel safer.
- I'm already on it.
More bad news.
It's the same reporter every time.
Ncwagner.
He's practically
deifying him.
I'm not even happy with the results
when god plays god.
You know, a few of the men were talking about
making him wish list of other dirtbags.
"Some day a real rain will come
and wash all the scum off the streets."
Taxi driver.
This town loves a
psychopath.
Why hasn't he contacted
the press yet?
Reid's right.
He's got the symbolism,
the inflated sense of duty.
He should be
seeking out acclaim.
Maybe it's not about
acclaim with him.
He's on a mission.
Maybe it's about the work.
Yeah, but the last 2 cases were a cop killer and
a pedophile priest.Those are higher profile cases.
he's getting more confident
he's growing until his role is the
cities judge and executioner
I'll check the press archives
for controversial acquittals.
Maybe we can target the victim before the unsub,
have the police waiting on him.
Hey, guys. Listen to what
came off the tip hotline.
I got a tip.
Let the guy be.
How come the nypd wants
to catch this guy?
Are you jealous he's doing the job
better than you?
It goes on for half an hour.
He's a hero.
The exact same thing happened with the
goetz-new york subway shooting in the early eighties.
You weren't even born.
I read a lot.
- Hey, talk to me, baby.
- Who do you love?
That depends
on what you're giving me.
Oh, don't be such a man.
I ran the names
of the 5 victims like you asked.
No overlap in arresting officers,
public defenders or district attorneys.
- Do I sense a but
- small but.
Atne not what
i was jonesing for.
you're killing me
with entendres.
But each one was processed at the manhattan
criminal courthouse at 100 centre street.
Do you have any idea how many cases
run through there every year?
122, 998.
But at least we've eliminated
4 other boroughs, hmm?
Yeah, great.All right.
It's a start.
Thanks.
Ta.
Do you have any idea
how many cases--
122, 998 cases a year.
We'll check it out.
Maybe there's someone with a history of
erratic behavior who worked in the building.
Crime groupies.
A security guard
that fits the profile.
Get with J.J. See what you
can make of her case list.
Ok.
I'll go with you.
Ever crossed your mind?
Taking the law into my own hands?
Not the law, justice.
What's this about?
The boys in iowa?
It's just a question.
I guess if I think if I ever let
my mind go there,
then the unsubs would be getting into my head
instead of me getting into theirs.
That wouldn't be a good idea, now,
would it?
The cops have already been down here asking
their questions.
I just want to give you
a description of someone,
see if he sounds familiar.
He's quiet. He...
body language gives the impression
he's seen too much.
Work in this building long enough,
we all get that way.
He's small, meticulous.
You might not notice him at first,
but when you do, you realize he's heard
everything around him.
He might have had a personal brush
with crime.
When it happened, he talked bout it
all the time.
But now you realize he hasn't mentioned it
in quite a while.
And when the subject of the vigilante
comes up, he expresses his support,
but it's not something he would bring up
in conversation himself.
Well, if people are
being honest with you,
that's most of the people in
this building.
How old are you?
24.
I'll give you 6 years.
That point, a tiny part
of your brain will be asking
if what this guy's doing
isn't the right way to go.
- anything?
- Uh-uh. You?
No.
What happened in iowa?
it was one of the first cases
hotch and I worked together.
Small town, 2 boys had been murdered,
same signature.
The profile led us
to the local 4-h leader.
We went to interview him.the guy,
he was suiciderly ???
Our guns were drawn.
At some point, he turns
the shotgun on hotch.
Instead of firing, hotch talks him down
the guy surrenders.
Sounds like pretty good work.
At trial, the guy's wife gave him
an alibi for both murders.
Small town.They all knew each other.
The jurors believed her.
Eventually they got him
when he killed another boy.
any luck?
this guy's not
doing us any favors.
His access is unbelievable.
He's practically scooping us.
The fbi needs help and they get you
to do their bidding?
i am an fbi special agent.
The rest of the team is too busy.
they're out in the field.
Yeah, and they're doing
a bang-up job, too.
Look, the fact is you've scooped every other
reporter in new york.
You've even managed
to be ahead of the cops a few times.
A good crime reporter needs to be better
than the police.You got less to go on.
Well, that's why agent gideon was hoping
you'd accept this invitation to help.
Jason Gideon?
He used to be
one of the best.
- He still is.
- Yeah. He had kind of a famous meltdown.
And a whole string
of success since he's returned.
Yeah, yeah. Meltdown's
make better copy.
Maybe you can take that
up with him yourself...
you know, if you
decide to come in.
So how did you put together
the vigilante angle so quickly?
I covered the original trials
of all the victims.
You must have a good memory.
A lot of killers can't remember details
from their own crimes.
Some cases just stick
right in your brain.
Tell us about the victims.
All right. Well, this girl,
she was just a waste case.
The jury bought into the whole
"addiction as disease" bs.
And this old guy,
he was a thug.He beat his wife,
but the case fell apart
because she wouldn't testify.
Surrani?
He drank and drove.
It was a tragedy, but...
it was the kind of thing
that could happen to anybody.
So who do you think we're looking for?
What's his background?
My guess is he's a crime victim.
Probably something violent.
But you do think he's a hero.
Well...
you know, this city make you
swallow a lot of crap.
It's hard not to feel
for someone who won't take it anymore.
These haven't been released to the press.
They're pretty grim.
I've seen plenty
of crime scenes.
Right.
We're stuck on the ear.
Is it for killing efficiency
or symbolism?
Why would you stab someone through the ear
into their brain?
What's going on here?
The profile leads us to think
that he works close
to the criminal justice system.
What do you think?
No, no.
You didn't bring me in here
because you wanted my help.
The profile suggests this guy'd contact
the media.He hasn'T.
And we thought the killer wouldn't need
to contact the press if he were the press.
You're single-handedly turning this
psychopath into a folk hero.
So what happened?
You get your men killed on the job
and you think everybody else
must be a killer, too?
- Watch your mouth.
- It's ok, hotch.
- Not our guy.
- You're damn right.
I didn't kill anybody.
What about you?
Wagner.
You're right.
You're not the killer.
Mm-hmm.
Everything you feel is vicarious.
You don't have it in you to act.
This psycho's
the last chance for you.
You've screwed up other jobs.
You drink too much.
Probably have a broken
marriage or two.
You're actually hoping
he doesn't get caught for a while.
Part of you knows that's twisted
and pathetic, but hey...
you're just reporting
the news, right?
Hey! Hey!
The reporter is not a vigilante.
Yeah, we know.
How do you know?
There was just another
shooting in central park.
You say shooting.
What about the rest of the signature?
Officers heard the shot,
but he ran off before they got there.
The victim was
an undercover cop.
I think you're
looking for me.
Put the gun
on the ground!
- On your knees!
- Drop the gun!
Get down.
Don't move.
No, you don't understand.
I did this all for you.
We're in this together.
His name's will sykes.
He's a security guard at a boutique in soho.
He was a mugging victim last year.
Spent 2 days in intensive care.
Fits the profile.
How's it going in here?
He just confessed
to all the murders.
So what were you doing
in the park?
It's full of animals.
Muggers and scum,
drug dealers.
I knew one of them
would try to prey on me.
That's not your
usual method.
I mean, you target them.
You don't let them target you.
I made that point,
now I'm making this one.
Which is?
If you hunt us
on the street,
you will die
the way you lived.
So why turn yourself in now?
I can't change the city
without help.
People need to be inspired.
They need to see me.
They need to hear my voice.
Can you tell me about
the cab driver, derbin?
He was a thug.
A wife beater.
And the priest?
What's to know?
He preyed on young boys.
Is that why you stabbed him
in the groin?
It's what he deserved.
Thank you.
Why would he confess
to murders he didn't commit?
Because he has
narcissistic delusions.
He wants the glory.
He wants to be a star.
He went into the park hoping that somebody
would mess with him.
He killed your undercover officer
but not the others.
So where dos that leave us?
We know our unsub has a heightened sense
of right and wrong.
If he knew that he inspired a would-be
vigilante to murder an undercover cop,
he might feel remorse.
You think you might be able to mend fences
with the reporter, wagner?
If it played to his ego, yeah.
We might be able to draw the unsub out.
That's a good one.
Wagner said this morning that the cop's blood
is all over the vigilante's hands.
How did J.J. Get him to cooperate?
The unsub may feel
a need to be there,
to physically mourn
for what he caused.
If that article lures him,
wagner gets to claim he caught a murderer.
It's the ultimate scoop.
Will they know
how to spot him?
I briefed your men.If the unsub's there, he'll
be alone, out of place, not speaking to anyone else,
probably not even
making eye contact.
Hopefully, he'll panic,
draw attention to himself.
I can never get that sound
out of my head.
Wakes me in the middle of the night.
If there was any justice,
cop killers would have
to hear it for an eternity.
Hotch.
Hey, hotch.
Hotch, it's morgan.
Thank you--listen,
something's funky, man.
I'm here trying to get transcripts
from the victims'original trials.
I thought maybe there cod have been a
disturbance at the courthouse,
or maybe the unsub even made himself known.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Ok. Well, here's the thing.There are no records
available yet from the cabbie's trial.
The clerk told me that
your average court reporter
is 3 to 6 months behind
in transcribing his notes.
That means that anyone who knows the details of
that case had to have been in the courtroom.
Court reporters take their work
home with them.
They get paid overtime.They take their notes
in court and finish transcribing them at night.
You know what bennett said about not being able
to get the sound of bagpipes out of her head?
Maybe that's why the unsub stabs
the ears.
Killers often harm their victims in ways
that they themselves have been harmed.
Court reporters, by definition,
are a faceless cog in the machine.
He sits there day in and day out
transcribing testimony.
What if the voices wouldn't stop when
you left the courtroom?
They witness at the church
said that the unsub
- was playing a piano-like motion.
- Or transcribing.
Killings a good way to get
the voices to stop, huh?
Holla.
I need the name of the court stenographer
in each of the victims' original trials.
Same one every time.
Marvin doyle.
Cross-check him against crime records.
See if he was ever the victim of a violent crime.
Not him.
His parents killed in
an attempted robber, '04.
That's his stressor.
Is he still working?
100 center,
courtroom 12-b
we've got him.
Marvin doyle.
Is that him?
Doyle called in sick.
We were in this
courtroom yesterday.
He saw us.
Tell your judge
i need a warrant.Take that.
Marvin doyle.
Fbi. Open up.
Clear!
It's clean.
He's gonna keep
the voices out.
He sound-proofed
the entire place.
He ripped the speakers
out of the television and the radio.
And here is life insurance check
for $250, 000.
It's 2 years old.
He didn't cash it.
He won't accept blood money.
Here's a box full of flint knives.
There's got to be a hundred of 'em.
Hey, guys. Come take
a look at this.
It's a stenography machine.
Look at the keys.
They're all worn out.
It's like he was trying to transcribe
the voices in his head and he couldn't keep up.
Looks like
hieroglyphics.
It's called steno.
It's basically
a phonetic series
of syllables.
No court reporter takes notes the same way so no
one can translate them but the reporter himself.
He's getting paid overtime
to study potential victims.
He knows we're onto him.
He's racing us now.
Someone in these boxes
is targeted to die.
We need to get inside his head and figure
out who so we can stop him.
Let's go.
Start fishin'.
this is a lot of boxes.
How are we supposed to narrow it down?
Check and see if it ended in acquittal.
If it didn't, toss it aside.
It has to be a capital case.He's escalating.
The more brutal the better.
Why not go by most recent?
Judging by his elaborate filing system,
doyle obviously has obsessive-compulsive disorder.
People with ocd often finish tasks
then go back to the beginning and start over.
So he continually goes through the transcripts and
the first one to trigger him becomes his next victim.
Here's one.
This is a liquor store owner
who was shot with his own gun.
Flip to when they present the defense.
Did the defendant testify?
No.
Stick with the ones where
the accused took the stand.
This is personal.
He hears their voices.
Doyle's victims all claimed to be a type
of victim themselves.
They first two threw themselves on
the mercy of the court,
pleading alcohol
and drug dependency.
The priest said he was
a victim, victim of recent hysteria.
Look for key phrases:Victim, mercy, anything that
signifies they thought their crime wasn't their fault.
I think I might have one, guys.
Ted elmore.
He shot and killed both his parents after claiming
self-defense for years of physical abuse.
Doyle lost his own parents.Hearing someone get
away with killing their own, that would haunt him.
Hello?
Is ted elmore there?
Not right now.
Can I take a message?
Who's this?
This is his wife.
My name is jason gideon.
I'm with the fbi.
Honey, the fbi
is on the phone?
Mrs. Elmore!
Come on!
He's there.
I think I can
talk him out.
I have snipers up high.If they get
a clean shot, they have my order to take it.
We might be able to reason.
We rushed him.
He doesn't want to have
an innocent hostage.
He has an exaggerated sense
of right and wrong.
And so do I.
Talking's worth a shot.
I'm coming with you.
Shut up!
He didn't do anything to you.
Tell her how you lied.
Tell her how you
killed your parents
and pretended they'd
been hurting you.
They did hurt me.
I'll kill him.
Then you wouldn't get
to hear the truth.
If he admits the truth,
the voices will stop, right?
They always lie.
Do you have the shot?
Negative.
Let us interrogate him?
Put the gun down.We're the fbi.
We'll get the truth.
Marvin, I'm gonna put my gun away.
We'll do this together, ok?
Tell him the truth.
Tell him how you lied
on the stand.
They did hurt me.
Don't listen to them.
If he dies,
they'll go away!
What do you think?
They won't come back?
Beverly, iowa, 1999.
A man kills 2 boys only to walk away free
and kill another one.
Stop.
Haskins, georgia, last year.
3 white guys kill
a black teenager--
just because 4 witnesses see it.
The jury finds them not guilty--
just because.
The first 2 boys were 14 years old.
The third was only 12.
- Stop!
- It doesn't stop.
Diallo, blake, simpson,
t cullen davis.
You can't kill
fast enough to keep up.
They killed my parents.
I know.
I'm so tired.
Marvin, listen to me.
Why don't you just
give me the gun?
Promise you...
I will get you a place
to rest.
Are you clear now?
I heard there was a secret code
the day that played
and it pleased the lord
but you don't really care
for music, do you?
Well, it goes like this
the fourth or fifth
the minor fall
and the major lift
the baffled king
composing, hallelujah
hallelujah
Gandhi said,
"it is better to be violent
"if there's violence in our hearts
than to put on the cloak
of non-violence
to cover impotence."
Gandhi also said,
"I object to violence
"because when it appears to do good,
"the good is only temporary.
The evil it does
is permanent."
he got what he deserved.
He only did what the rest of us
wish we could do.
I felt safer when he was alive.
This is why we need gun control.
The guy's a murderer.
He got his own. Death penalty.
I say he's a hero.
They only killed him because they were
afraid no jury would convict him.