morgan, your friend's resort
better be as nice
as you say it is.
hey, i never said
it was his.
he just manages
the place.
but trust me when i tell
you it is off the hook.
hot sunny days,
cool breezes at night,
never-ending
tropical drinks with
the little umbrellas,
and nothing but young,
beautiful adults
looking to make
vacation memories.
male and female, right?
elle, 2 weeks of
pure heaven.
i can't imagine what
2 weeks away from this
ple is gonna feel like.
well, you better thank
your man upstairs for
making it the whole team,
otherwise you know they'd
find a reason
to bring us back
up in here.
why? they got
other teams.
okay, you can go on
beeving that if you want to,
but i am not answering
my cell phone.
ok.
oh, there he is.
pretty boy.
last chance.
i can get my man
to swing you a hotel room
for practically nothing.
even you might get
a little lovin' out there.
thanks anyway.
come on, reid.
live a little, huh?
i have to go--
i'm going home.
have a good one, guys.
bye.
he look ok to you?
he looks about
the way i would
if i was gonna spend
2 weeks with my family.
hey, don't knock family.
i'm gonna get nothing but
for the next 336 hours.
morgan: good for you.
haley's got a list
of chores a mile long.
i can't wait.
the biggest decision
i gotta make is what
i'm gonna do first.
i bet you she has a thought
or two about that as well.
hotch: bring it on.
i'll be lost in a cabin
in the woods for
the next 2 weeks.
do not call me
for anything.
have a great time.
you all deserve a break.
seriously,
don't call.
don't worry.
yes?
thank you.
darling?
bye, darling.
i must go out now...
for a while.
but i promise you...
it will all
be over soon.
one way or another,
it will all be over.
gideon:
writer elbert hubbard said,
"no man needs a vacation
much as the man
who has just had one."
come on.
did i lie to ya?
you did not lie.
ha ha! oh, yes!
thank you.
cheers.
welcome to paradise.
there you are.
ha ha! yes, sir!
my man mr. gerald dupree.
how you doing?
i'm wonderful.
look at you.
you're holding it together.
i'm trying, baby.
this right here
is my partner
from the fbi,
miss elle greenaway.
you didn't tell me
she was beautiful.
would that have gotten me
a better deal on the room?
you want me to show you
a brochure with the real rates?
hey, i'm done. i'm done.
your resort is beautiful.
thank you.
always wondered
what it would be like
to work in paradise.
turns out
it's not half bad.
anything else you need?
yeah, i think...
ooh! wait a minute.
look at that
right there.
lord have mercy.
i think i need
to handle something.
you need any backup?
you better watch
your mouth.
elle you gonna be
all right?
no, i'm fine.
you go.
that's such
a good answer.
get outta here.
so how about you?
anything i can
get you?
no, thank you.
i'll let you know
if there's anything.
thank you, gerald.
i'll be around.
all right.
sorry about that.
no problem.
hey, uh...you alone?
completely.
do you wanna play?
uh, honey, you're supposed
to be dumping things,
not examining them.
pirate number 4.
cute.
yeah, but do you really
want to remember
your first and last
appearance on stage?
i wasn't very good,
but i was very
committed.
yeah...i'd dump it.
do i have to?
ok, i'll make you a deal.
come up with a good reason
by the end of the day,
and it stays.
you drive
a hard bargain.
[in the mood playing]
garcia:
"my humble servant?"
why can't the real world
be like this?
"my heart doth swell
at the sight of thee,
"my brave sir kneighf.
i shall follow
where you lead."
you're still here?
i don't get the same
vacation time as
the rest of the team.
gotta make sure there's
plenty of work for them
when they get back.
what are you doing?
i'm in camelot.
camelot?
yeah. it's an online world.
see?
i'm just outside
the magical city of camelot
adventuring with
the incredible sir kneighf.
oh, the incredible
sir kneighf.
j.j., this guy is amazing.
please tell me you
don't have a crush on
a fictional character.
he's not fictional.
he's the online alter ego
of a real person.
mm-hmm.
but you don't know
anything about him--
or even if he is a him.
look, we meet online
at specified times
that he is never late to.
we spend hours adventuring
and chatting
during which time
i have his undivided attention
and he lavishes me
with flattery.
wow.
when's the last time you
had a date go that well?
see if he's got
a fictional brother,
all right?
yeah. he doesn't.
cousin, uncle,
grandfather, whatever.
we heard a rumor
you were here.
how's she doing?
schizophrenia
is a lifetime illness.
the meds stabilize
the worst of her symptoms,
but she still has bad days.
what makes her most happy
are her journals and...
your daily letters.
she is exceptionally
proud of you.
she is?
talks about you
all the time,
to anyone who will listen.
staff, other patients.
her journals are filled with
the cases you write her about.
calls them your adventures.
mom's of the belief that
you can find adventure
all around you
if you just look.
that's what happens when
you're a professor of
15th century literature.
she's gonna be so excited
that you were finally able
to get here in person.
maybe it's better if
i just let her rest today.
rest?
yeah, i'll come back
tomorrow.
but, doctor--
can you give this
to her?
it's margery kempe.
her favorite.
it would be really
good for her if--
please?
thank you so much.
well, you all right there,
greenaway?
go away.
see you tomorrow?
afternoon.
after noon?
don't speak.
he's sound asleep.
so we have a few hours
to ourselves.
dinner was amazing.
well, it's nice to have
someone here to cook for.
well, it's...
nice to be here.
what'cha looking t?
reflections 1987.
oh, boy.
[laughs]
i remember the day
i got this.
it was the end
of my junior year.
i was walking down the hall,
and i accidentally walked into
a theater club rehearsal.
and i saw you.
mm-hmm.
and i knew i was
gonna marry you.
aww.
and i went home that night...
and i looked you up.
haley brooks,
tenth grade.
[gasps]
look at my hair.
and...
i though how could i have
missed you for 2 years?
so the next day,
i knew i had to meet you.
so i went in and i joined
the theater club.
and that's how i was in
the pirates of penzance
as the worst fourth pirate
in history.
aaron?
hmm?
keep the hat.
ok.
[yearbook hits floor]
[you go to my head playing]
i always forget
what a great cook you are.
more wine?
jason, you know i'm not
responsible for myself after 2.
thank you.
do i sound old if i say
they don't make music
like this anymore?
yes.
it's good to be old.
hotchner.
man:
agent hotchner,
don't waste time
on the first victims.
they were unrepented
bad men.
she's the important one.
remember, everything
starts at the beginning.
who is this?
there won't be
much time.
the youngest
holds the key.
you must help him
save her.
what's going on?
i don't know.
it was an
anonymous call.
a man.
he said there had been
a murder in room 19.
and i called security
to check it out,
but when they saw...
i thought it would
be best if i called
you right away.
you have a key?
yeah.
no...no.
no. no.
no. no, no, no.
no, no!
oh, my...
no!
sorry.
no one should be
coming here.
go wait in
the bedroom.
jason gideon?
yeah.
woman: what is it?
nellie fox.
no! stop it!
stop it!
hold still!
no!
let go!
who are you?!
i'm sorry. i just--
i just never, ever saw
anything like this--
come here.
get in my car.
i'll drive you.
ok. thank you.
contact me at the bau
when you're finished.
i wanna know who the hell
that used to be.
do you know anybody
in jamaica?
no.
that's the postal zone
where it seems
the package was
sent from.
montego bay, jamaica.
you think i didn't see that?
i don't know anybody
in jamaica.
then how did the blood
get outside your door?
i have no idea.
there wasn't any blood
inside, was there?
who was the victim?
for the hundredth time,
i didn't even know
that there was a victim
until you dragged me
out of bed!
where's
the victim's head?
well, i must have dropped it
on my way in here.
come on. you know that
i have nothing to do with this.
i'm an american fbi agent.
i'm here on vacation, man!
i'm the police,
just like you.
are you the "her"?
excuse me?
i don't care where
the blood led, detective,
you made a mistake.
we are fbi agents.
bau profilers
here on vacation.
profilers?
yes.
we handle serial
criminals.
we consult
police departments
all over the world.
oh. so if i called you
to consult on this,
would it be your advice
to let the woman
who we found at the end
of the blood trail go?
agent greenaway
is not a killer.
can you explain
why the blood went
right to her door?
obviously somebody
would like you
to think she is.
look, my supervisor
is flying down here
from virginia.
he'll be here anytime.
when he gets here,
we will figure this out.
his name's marty harris.
at least that's who
rented this room.
hey!
why are you telling him?
um, sorry.
i'm just...
my mistake.
i'm sorry, ma'am.
when did this harris
check in?
a couple of days ago
with another man.
giles. frank giles.
he has
the adjoining room.
we tried calling him,
but he doesn't answer.
looks like frank giles
is in the wind.
you might have yourself
a real suspect now.
i'll get crime scene men
in here.
all work
and no play, huh?
all work and no play?
just wait 'til i'm
through with you.
[ring]
what?
garcia. i need a rundown
on a guy.
no.
what?
the information
superhighway is closed.
what are you
talking about?
someone had the nerve
to run a blackhat op
into my computers, morgan.
they hacked me, ok?
but you can bet
your sweet ass
i will find them.
i've got honey pot farms
hidden behind uml kernel
data packets
and a first generation
honeynet i personally
programmed.
my snort logs list
every visitor,
every server request,
every keystroke on
this entire network.
if i have to back-hack
his i.p. all the way to
the frickin' stone age,
i will find this
son of a bitch, ok?!
so bye.
gideon, i've been trying
to call you.
why?
someone sent you a head?
from jamaica.
morgan and elle are
in jamaica right now.
there was a murder.
the body was headless.
elle's been arrested
for it.
what?
hotch headed down there
last night
with some bureau lawyers
and a crime scene unit.
he should be there
by now.
if you talk to him,
have him call me right away.
yes, sir.
gideon.
yeah.
baseball card and envelope
that were attached to the box.
we processed them.
there's nothing.
no prints--and we're still
working on identifying the head.
try contacting
the montego bay police.
apparently
they have a headless
homicide victim.
got it.
what time did you
go to bed?
around midnight...i think.
i don't really know.
it was late.
were you alone?
by the time i got back
to my room, yeah.
detective st. pierre,
i'm ssa hotchner.
i'm agent greenaway's
superior.
we're not finished here.
agent greenaway
only arrived
in your country
yesterday afternoon.
thank you.
so?
i brought
a forensic expert
and he's examined the body
at your morgue,
and he's put
the time of death
at no less than
24 hours ago.
now this is based on
advanced rigor mortis
and the contents
of the stomach
which contained a meal
that he ordered
from room service
2 days ago.
your coroner concurs
with the findings.
what this means is
that agent greenaway
wasn't even here when
this man was killed.
now, i appreciate that you
have a difficult situation,
and agents morgan
and greenaway are happy
to cooperate in
any what that they can,
but they'll do it
from our offices in
quantico, virginia.
oh, well, that's
great, hotch.
gideon wants you to call him
as soon as you can.
uh, i think i better
let him tell you.
ok. call me if you
need anything.
bye.
"searched for."
oh, doctor reid.
someone delivered this
to the desk last night for you.
what?
"she will die unless
you save her, dr. reid.
call gideon. he knows."
[knock on door]
come in.
hey, um, i just got
a really strange delivery.
strange as a head
in the middle of the night?
that's a pale clouded
yellow butterfly.
they're indigenous
to europe.
britain mainly.
"she has been searched for
yet never found."
what the hell
is going on here?
you guys are sure
you don't want to go home
and get some rest?
take a shower?
like hell!
we're good.
how much sleep
have you gotten in
the last 24 hours?
hotch, i spent
half of the night in
an interrogation room.
i am not sleeping
until i find this
frank giles.
frank giles left jamaica
last night on the red eye.
he flew to florida,
then got onto another flight
to virginia.
virginia?
you mean that
son of a bitch
is from here?
i don't know if he's from here,
but this is where he flew to.
arlington.
he's got a long
criminal record.
manslaughter,
robbery, rape.
what about the victim,
marty harris?
uh, he's a two-time
convicted fetish burglar,
registered child
sex offender.
and we have his head.
csu just positively
identified the one
delivered to my cabin.
"don't waste time on
the first victims.
"they were unrepentent
bad men.
they only got
what they deserved."
morgan: what is that?
i got a phone call
last night
before you called
from jamaica.
any mention
of a "her"?
"you must help him
save her."
so there's
a him now, too?
i think he means reid.
what?
we need to regroup.
so, clearly we have
a psychopath
intent on drawing us
into his game.
playing with us.
then let's return
the favor.
he kept telling us repeatedly
to save "her". what "her"?
the items he sent must
be some kind of clues.
let's get them up
on the board.
i got a nellie fox
baseball card from 1963,
and i got
a head in a box.
i got a rare butterfly
in a shadow box.
and repeated messages
to save "her"?
i got the decapitated body
and a nice visit to
the jamaican police
headquarters.
reid called from nevada.
he's on the way back
here with a skelton key
and a note he got, too.
and the guy who called me
said the youngest one
holds the key.
that's reid.
ok, but wait a minute.
unsubs, they don't
contact us this way.
i mean, they might
taunt us,
dare us to catch 'em.
but they don't drag us
into their fantasy.
why not?
because they're
sexual fantasies.
i mean, taunting us
is a show of power,
but making us
the object is...
i don't know
what the hell that is.
something else
about the baseball card.
nellie fox was one
of the stars of
the 1959 white sox.
i went to almost
every game with
my father that year.
fox was my hero.
so is it a coincidence
that he sends this to me?
or does he know
how i feel about him?
i collected butterflies
when i was a little girl.
that's how i knew what
butterfly was in the box.
so then he knows us.
i got an anonymous message.
i got a police raid.
but he knew exactly
where we were.
hotel in jamaica.
gideon at the cabin.
reid in vegas.
you at your home.
he got that from
the bureau computers.
your locations are
always in there
so they can find you
if they need you.
i checked the log.
the hacker was definitely
in the personnel folders.
there were room numbers
to the hotel in jamaica,
the address of
gideon's cabin.
there's a lot of information
in those databases.
have you figured out
how he was able
to get into
the bureau's computers?
i'm--i'm still
working on that.
garcia,
if you know something--
no--um...
it's...
i...
i was playing
a game yesterday.
an online game.
a game?
not on the bureau
computer, sir.
on my own personal laptop.
oh, garcia!
no, no, no, no.
i don't understand.
wireless internet.
by wirelessly hooking
into the net here to get online,
the hacker could have
gotten into my computer first,
and i have far less
protection on my own laptop.
and he could have gotten
into the entire bureau
computer system this way?
yeah, it's possible.
playing a game?
how could you be
that stupid?
information, files.
you have
a responsibility.
i know, sir.
i'm so sorry.
but i found him.
you what?
i know who he is,
the hacker.
his name is giles,
frank giles.
he lives in arlington, virginia,
4 miles from here.
i have his address.
garcia, you said giles?
clear!
frank giles! fbi!
come out, giles!
you gotta be kidding me.
hotch, gideon,
i think you're gonna
want to see this.
hotch: he's definitely
playing with us.
elle:
his identification
checks out.
that's frank giles.
there's a big old
bag of money sitting
right here on the dresser.
so giles took harris
to jamaica to kill him
and the unsub
killed giles.
yeah, but he
paid him first.
left the cash?
he apparently
well-funded.
he said these were
unrepentant bad men.
are we looking for
some kind of vigilante?
no.
the bodies are nothing
but a way to get us interested.
they're game pieces.
the killings are secondary.
well, this guy likes
to write things in blood
on the walls.
all kinds of cult
and demonic significance
to that.
"thy? doth? quest?"
"thy quest doth
truly begin."
why start phrasing things
like this now?
all the other messages
were in modern english.
[morgan]
maybe this is the first one
the unsub actually wrote.
so we're looking
for shakespeare?
hey, guys?
yeah?
there's something
etched on the blade.
"to learn of what
should next be done,
leave the blade
'til the hour be none."
"hour be none?"
"leave the blade."
elle, move for a second,
move to your left.
the bed's in
the middle of the room.
which isn't by chance.
and maybe
the light from here
casts a shadow
and points to something.
come on.
are we in the middle of
an indiana jones movie?
"the hour be none?"
midnight is 00:00 hours
in 24-hour time.
would that be none?
midnight wouldn't
cast a shadow.
"hour be none."
3 p.m.
garcia, told me
where to find you.
3 p.m.?
it's medieval.
the days used to
be broken into
hourly intervals.
the canonical hours
of the breviary.
prime: 6 a.m.
terce: 9 a.m.
sext: 12 noon.
none: 3 p.m.
and vespers:
6 p.m.
reid, do not ever
go away again.
medieval. that's why
the language changed.
"doth."
everything this guys
does is a clue.
ok, but, guys,
it's 4:35.
what do we do?
leave the blade in
'til 3 p.m. tomorrow?
not if we can
block that window out.
do you have any
spotlights in your car?
sure.
thanks.
the sun is right
here at 5 p.m.
morgan, follow
the shadows.
i move
the light higher.
ok. and do what?
tap.
it's hollow.
definitely
an indian jones movie.
feels like the wallpaper's
been replaced.
tear it open.
it's a box.
take it out.
reid: we sure it's safe?
what, you think
it's a bomb?
you think he'd be
playing this game
just to blow us up?
he'd have
already done that
as long as we've
been standing here.
locked.
you want me to break it?
no. we should
process it first.
"the youngest
holds the key."
[music box playing
forellenquintett]
schubert.
the trout quintet.
5 people
fishing.
"never would it be night,
but always clear day
to any man's sight."
well, that was worth it.
the lid.
little tab
right under the lock.
"thy quest."
hotch: he moves funny.
looks like he's injured
or something.
man, on video:
i assure you...
you'll all understand
in the end why
it must be that way.
you might even
thank me.
don't hold your
breath, scumbag.
man: you know now
you're on a quest.
a young girls life
depends on the successful
completion of it.
as you can see,
she's quite beautiful...
and in distress.
now please listen closely
for there is one rule
and this rule
must be followed.
the one rule is...
only the members
of your team
may participate
in the quest.
jason gideon,
aaron hotchner,
derek morgan,
elle greenaway,
spencer reid,
jennifer jareau,
penelope garcia.
a quest must be completed
in the proper way
or it isn't
a quest, is it?
that's it.
one rule. simple.
now, you will be receiving
an item soon
that will hold
the final clue
you'll need
to finish the quest.
you will find you will
also need a book
which has inspired many
an adventure like mine.
believe me when
i tell you
i'm truly hope
to see you all soon.
it will mean a successful
end to this adventure...
for all of us.
this guy's got
pictures of us?
what do we do now?
the lock of hair's
being analyzed for dna.
there might be
something on file.
i'll get video to enhance
the shots of the girl.
hotch: let's get the clues
up on the board.
maybe we can make
some sense of something.
elle: wait. we're gonna
play this guy's game?
do we have a choice?
be right back.
you guys keep working.
jason.
what is it?
what's wrong?
what's the matter
with you?
i, uh...
i just have nothing left.
yeah, i'm tired, too.
no, no, no.
i needed a place...
where i didn't have to know
what was out there.
where i could...
just close my eyes
and not see...
bodies torn to pieces or hear
children calling out for help.
that cabin was
the only thing i had left.
this guy took it
away from me.
jason--
maybe i'm outta gas.
i'd like to be alone.
please?
haley?
i've been trying
to call you,
but you haven't been
answering your cell.
my battery died.
we just got back.
what's wrong?
a man came to the door
with something
he said you would need
right away,
that a girl's life
depended on it.
he came to the door?
yeah.
??
what did the guy look like
who came to the door?
look like?
um...i don't know.
young, dark hair.
did he look injured?
injured?
yeah. did he seem
injured in any way?
no. he was just a guy.
he told me what
he was giving me
you needed right away.
that a girl's life
depended on it.
that's not
a normal delivery.
i know.
what do you mean?
they don't come with
detailed messages
like that.
did he say all these
things to you?
were they in a note?
no, he said them.
if he isn't the unsub,
he probably talked to him.
what's going on?
it's the case
we're working on.
what did he deliver?
um, a piece of paper
with numbers on it.
the team's got it.
it's in the conference room
my eyes are so heavy,
i can barely see it.
i think it's a coded
message of some sort.
the unsub said we needed
a book, didn't he?
yeah. "a book that inspired
many an adventure."
it's a book code.
each one of these
sets of numbers
represents
a particular word.
for instance,
page 118, line 3o, word 3.
we need to figure out
what the words are
and fill in the blanks.
yeah, but from
what book?
i don't know.
the trouble is it has
to be the exact same edition
of the exact same book
that he used.
just got a dna hit
on the lock of hair.
rebecca bryant.
she's been missing
out of boston for 2 years.
2 years?
guys, how are we
supposed to figure out
which book this code
is copied out of?
i have no idea.
we need haley to sit
with a sketch artist
and get a picture
of this guy.
we can have j.j.
get it out on
the news wires.
tell the world.
tell the world?
we may have seen this
son of a bitch.
didn't he say that we had
to keep this within the team?
yeah.
get a sketch artist
up here.
he said we have
everything needed to
complete the quest.
the answer's gotta be
up there somewhere.
j.j, get some reporters
here as soon
as possible.
for what?
just say we need help
on a new case.
press conference?
haley and the baby
get into a hotel?
yeah.
good.
you think this
is going to work?
i think it's gonna send
the right message.
we're looking for
this man
in connection with
several murders.
he's approximately
25 years of age.
he delivered a package
to one of our agents
last night.
if anyone has
any information
regarding this subject,
please contact your local
fbi office immediately.
man: no, no, no, no.
rebecca?
i'm afraid i must
go out again.
a pale clouded
yellow butterfly
indigenous
to great britain.
how's it going?
the answer to what
book we need has
to be in here.
yeah, but we sure as hell
can't see it.
yet.
elle.
i'm awake.
i'm sending you home.
no.
you need to get some rest.
we won't do anything
without you, i promise.
elle, seriously,
we're not any closer
than we were.
get out of here.
go home.
but--
that's an order.
let's go.
anderson.
take greenaway home.
yes, sir.
no, i'm fine.
i'll have your car
brought over later.
[sighs] all right.
come on, anderson.
get some sleep.
yeah.
i sent elle home
with anderson.
she hasn't slept
in 36 hours.
good.
cync by lanmao
www.1000fr.com
i told you.
it was one rule.
no.
one rule!
agent greenaway.
stop.
do you not consider
that holding
a press conference
is going outside
the team for help?!
listen--
one rule!
listen to me.
we can talk about--
i told you
this was important!