- The princess is going to play.
- Where’s the princess ?
- Where’s the princess-- ?
- Right there.
Which one ?
Put this one...
This is how they
need to get around, right ?
Go inside the train.
Hello ?
Madison ?
Honey ?
Hi.
Oh, hey.
So...
... how was your day ?
Send it to Graeme Peel.
Graeme has better things to do
than look over my nonsensical scribbles.
Well, they didn’t look nonsensical
to me.
Okay, fine, they did.
l’m an English major.
What the hell do l know ? Send it.
Look, what’ve you got to lose ?
- Good night.
l’Il get it.
- Jean Miller ?
- Yes.
Hi, l’m Lieutenant Colonel Samantha
Carter of the United States Air Force.
Okay.
Did you send a math proof...
... to Professor Graeme Peel
of the California Institute of Technology ?
Was l not supposed to ?
Sorry to interrupt.
You need to pack your toothbrush,
head back to Earth.
- l do ? Why ?
- Carter needs help.
- With what ?
- Your sister.
- Welcome back to Earth.
- Yes, yes. What has my sister done ?
Good to see you too, McKay.
Greetings, salutations, pleasantries.
What’s she done ?
l thought that--
Well, it’s certainly
some very interesting stuff...
... but, no, can’t be her work. l mean,
she’s been out of the game for years.
The game ?
Yeah. She hasn’t published a single
theoretical-physics paper in four years.
Oh, that game.
She was on a fast track
to some pretty exciting grants...
... doing some interesting work.
l mean, she was no me, of course,
but she was at least a you.
Anyway, she got herself knocked up
by some English major...
... and priorities shifted overnight.
Tried to talk some sense into her,
but she’s a tad on the stubborn side.
When was the last time
you spoke to her ?
- Four years, maybe.
- Four years ?
Not that l didn’t check to see
if she’s published.
You realize what this proof means,
right ?
- Yes, if the math checks out.
- l’ve been over it. It checks out.
Well, no offense, blue eyes, but l’d like
a little more time with it myself.
It checks out.
She said it just came to her ?
She was playing with her kid
and she got a notion.
A notion. That is just beautiful.
She’s gonna love this.
You didn’t tell her l’ve been trying
to prove something like this ?
- Not exactly.
- Oh, good, because she would just--
Wait a minute. Why not ?
That’s part of the reason
l asked you here.
She’s been cleared by the Pentagon...
... but she refuses
to sign the confidentiality agreement.
She says she wants nothing
to do with us.
To be honest,
she’s been a bit of a pain in the ass.
Forget her, then.
She’s made her choice.
We’Il just have to figure out
how to implement it on our own.
Let’s see.
Now, upon first glance,
there are certainly some missing pieces...
... that aren’t exactly spelled out
in the proof, but...
What ?
This would go a lot faster
if your sister were onboard.
- She’s not gonna listen to me.
- You’re her brother.
Exactly.
- Hi.
- Long time no see.
- To say the least.
- Aren’t you going to invite me in ?
- Why are you here ?
l can’t just stop by
and say hi to my little sister ?
We haven’t spoken in four years.
You’ve never done anything like this.
So, no, you can’t.
l’ve been kind of busy with work,
doing a lot of traveling and such.
And l was called back on business.
So l was in town...
... and l thought l’d, you know...
- Wait a second.
- What ?
You’re not here
because of the physics proof, are you ?
- No. That’s part of the reason l’m here--
- You work for the U.S. government ?
No, l work for a multinational
oversight advisory that--
You know what ? l don’t care.
l already told that colonel person...
... l don’t want anything
to do with them.
- Do you know what you’ve written ?
- A math proof. Some theoretical physics.
l am willing to wager
it has no practical application at all.
- l’Il take that action.
- What does that mean ?
- Just sign the damn agreement.
- No.
Getting all proprietary
about our research and ideas...
... is everything that’s wrong
with science today.
Did you know
that one-fifth of our genes...
... the very building blocks of our being,
have been patented...
... by major pharmaceutical corporations ?
One-fifth.
If there’s any benefit at all
to what l’ve written...
... it’s that it’Il spark an idea
in someone.
l am not gonna sign away my rights,
least of all to the U.S. military.
It has sparked an idea in someone,
a big one.
- Like what ?
- No. Can’t tell you.
- Not till you sign the agreement.
- l’m not signing till you tell me.
- Is everything okay ?
- Look who showed up.
Hey.
It’s my brother.
Right. Hey.
Hi.
- Hello, little one.
- Did you bring me a present ?
- Madison.
- What ? No.
- l didn’t know it was a rule.
- It is.
Well, l guess l broke that rule.
l made some dinner.
Would you care to join us ?
Well, that’d be great.
l’m starving. You have no idea
what time zone l came from.
Well, l sure hope you like tofu chicken.
l sure hope he’s kidding. Here you go.
Not a fan of vegetarian cuisine, eh ?
Yes, well, l suppose l was just
in the mood for, well, food.
l’Il give Maddie her bath.
You two catch up.
- Okay, hon.
- Hey, pop your head in before you leave.
- What ? Why ?
- Children like to say goodbye.
Oh, the-- Yeah. Sure. Sure.
Boy, Madison’s sure grown, huh ?
Since she was born ?
Yeah, yeah, she has.
Okay, look, l don’t wanna waste
any more of your time.
You need to come with me.
Your proof could lead
to something groundbreaking.
- How long would l be gone ?
- Well, like, a couple months, tops.
A couple of months ?
Are you joking ? l--
Madison has her first ballet recital
next Tuesday.
She’s 4.
How good could she possibly be ?
- That’s not the point.
- Hey, she’s not gonna remember.
- l’Il remember me not being there.
- This is bigger than your responsibilities.
Okay, we’ve had this conversation
before.
You belittle my choices,
l get furious at you...
... and we don’t talk for four years.
l’m not all that anxious to do that again.
This is not what Dad
would have wanted.
No, he would have wanted us
working together side by side...
... toppling problems and sharing credit.
Oh, you share credit now, do you ?
This is important, Jeanie. It’s much more
important than you could ever imagine.
For you, l am sure it is.
But this, me being here,
this is important for me.
Why can’t you accept that ?
- You know, you leave me no choice.
- What ?
- Give me your hand.
- Why ?
Please just give me your hand.
Will you just. . ?
- Okay, what the hell just happened ?
- It’s okay. You’re perfectly safe.
l don’t feel perfectly safe.
You’ve been teleported to an interstellar
vessel in orbit around the planet.
Please. Teleportation is about as likely
as time travel.
Yes, well...
- Oh, my.
- Oh, yes.
Is that. . ?
Why aren’t we weightless ?
Artificial gravity.
And, yes, that is North America...
... and you are in geosynchronous orbit.
We work for something
called the Stargate program.
Stargate ?
It’s a device that creates
stable artificial wormholes...
... that allows us to travel between
other planets, even other galaxies.
What have you gotten yourself
involved in here, Meredith ?
- Meredith ?
- It’s a long story.
- It’s his name.
- Your name is Meredith McKay ?
It’s Meredith Rodney McKay, yes,
but l prefer to go by Rodney.
Could we stick to the point here ?
Look out the window.
- Much more interesting than my name.
- Your name is Meredith ?
So this is, like, a spaceship ?
This is a U.S. Air Force vessel
called the Daedalus.
Your equation
has real-world applications...
... l’m certain you’ve never
even considered.
You see, there are some
very bad creatures out there...
... that want nothing more
but to destroy this planet...
... and everything that you hold dear.
Did you say creatures ?
- Like alien creatures ?
- Yes.
Look, the work we could do is important,
Jeanie. It’s not just to you or me...
... but to every living being down there.
And that includes Madison and...
- Kaleb.
- Kaleb, yes.
- We can’t do this without you.
- Let’s not go overboard.
- l mean, she’d be an asset, but--
- McKay.
So, what do you say, Mrs. Miller ?
- Jeanie ?
- It’s just a lot to take in right now, okay ?
Just give me a second, Mer.
So somewhere down there, my husband
is giving my daughter a bath.
You have to go.
l know.
- What did you tell Kaleb ?
- The truth.
What ? Do you have any idea
what nondisclosure means ?
Just because we don’t keep secrets
doesn’t mean we’re incapable of it.
Well, what did he say ?
He’s concerned that me telling him
will get him assassinated.
- That-- That won’t happen, right ?
- Oh, probably not.
I’m sorry I couldn’t come with you,
but there’s too much going on here.
It’s fine.
I thought I could
help get Jeanie up to speed...
... before you guys
are out of comm range.
About a year ago, your brother came
across an abandoned alien experiment...
... called Project Arcturus.
It was an attempt
to generate zero-point energy.
That would be virtually limitless power.
What happened ?
A slight problem. It was the creation of
exotic particles in the containment field.
He destroyed a solar system.
- Meredith.
- It was uninhabited.
Your brother, with others,
has been trying to figure out a way...
... to draw zero-point energy
from a parallel space-time.
Which would get us around the creation
of dangerous exotic particles...
... in our own space-time.
And my theory
is about bridging universes.
Exactly. And we’re hoping
to use your proof as a theoretical basis...
... for building a bridge
from a parallel space-time to ours.
The energy you’d need would
be enormous to the point of absurd.
« Absurd » we can do.
We have a zero-point module...
... which does what we’re attempting
on a smaller scale :
Extract energy from subspace-time.
- So subspace is real ?
-You’re flying in it.
Aren’t you worried about the exotic
particles crossing back over my bridge ?
That’s the beauty of your theory.
It should not only allow us
to build a bridge...
... it should also allow us
to manage the flow rate of energy.
Like a faucet.
- Well, it’s something like that.
-It’s exactly like that.
What about the parallel universe ?
Aren’t you just shifting
the exotic-particle problem to their side ?
Potentially. But when you consider...
... that the number of possible
parallel universes that we could access...
... borders on the infinite...
... the odds of us choosing at random
one that’s inhabited...
... are astronomically slim.
I know, it’s an awful lot
to take in at once.
l solved your problem
in my spare time.
- With finger-paints.
- Here we go.
l just can’t imagine
how you’re surviving the humiliation.
If it wasn’t for my work,
your theory would be useless.
Whoa, whoa, siblings, please.
- Sorry.
What ?
Well, it’s just that you both said « sorry »
in that cute little Canadian way, and I--
Sorry. Touch base when you get back
to Atlantis. Good luck.
These creatures must be quite the threat
for you to even try what you’re doing.
Now, l don’t wanna scare you,
but you need to know the stakes.
We’re at war.
- Did you start it ?
- What ? No.
- Come on.
- Well...
You’ve got a nota bene by
the cosmological constant. Why is that ?
Jeanie ?
Hey.
Yeah. Why you’re here, remember ?
Thank you.
- So there’s your problem, right there.
- What are you talking about ? It’s here.
- And you made a mistake.
- No, l didn’t.
Okay, so we need a yea or nay
on the equations.
Yea.
Atlantis already has
a containment chamber we can use.
I’Il forward the necessary modifications
to zelenka.
If he doesn’t mess it up,
he can make the changes we need...
... before we even get there.
Ready ?
Now, we’ve been through
these calculations...
... and we’ve settled
on a containment-field setup...
... that should work for us.
l just wanna show you these...
Yes, we have it, people. Good work.
Good work, everybody.
Just in time.
- Has he talked about his sister with you ?
- Once or twice in passing.
Usually like,
« Come on, even my sister can do it. »
- You know, that type of thing.
- How’s it coming, Radek ?
The simulations are in the green.
We’re ready to try power-up.
- Just in time.
- That’s actually what l just said.
Holy cow.
Now, that can’t be good for you.
Nothing to worry about.
l’ve done it dozens of times.
John Sheppard.
Yeah. She’s married
and she’s my sister.
- l’m just saying hi.
- Yeah, l know exactly what you’re doing.
l’ve seen that look before, Kirk.
Hello, Mrs. Miller. l’m Dr. Élizabeth Weir.
Welcome to Atlantis.
Thank you.
Mer’s told me so much about you.
All good, l s--
- Did you just call him Mer ?
- It’s her pet name. Where are we ?
Simulations are in the green.
We’re ready to try power-up.
Really ? So soon ? That’s amazing.
Excellent work, Radek.
- Thank you.
- Yes, we try not to encourage him.
He’s got a bit of an ego.
In-chamber conditions are green.
Containment field is in the green.
- Monitors are green.
- Everything’s green.
- He likes to do the checklist.
- ZPM levels are well into the green.
And backup terminals are green.
We’re ready to initiate power-up.
- Good luck.
- All right. Here we go.
Want to turn it on together ?
- Why would we do that ?
- Because it’s both of our work.
There’s only room on the button
for one finger.
- Well, then can l do it ?
- Yeah, but l’m right here, so--
He likes to push the button.
- Fine, go.
- Powering up to 5 percent.
Containment field is holding.
Power generation is steady.
- What about exotic particles ?
- Jeanie, please, l’m on it.
We are holding at 5 percent.
Good. Now what ?
The safe thing to do is hold at 5 percent
for the next while.
Yeah, she wasn’t talking to you.
- It was an open question to the floor.
- Shared credit, huh ?
We’Il do this together.
Dad will be so proud.
- This is not the time or the place.
- Fine.
- l’m going to my quarters.
- Yes. Well, good night. Thank you.
So ?
Well, obviously we hold at 5 percent
for the next while...
... and see if any problems turn up.
Right.
l should probably
try to get some rest myself.
Could you. . ?
What the-- ? Shut it down.
Foreign object. Go get Dr. Zelenka.
It worked.
- What are you doing ?
- Radek.
Yes.
l need to speak to whoever’s in charge
of this project.
But that’s you.
Well, then,
l guess l need to speak to me.
- What is this ?
- Hey, Meredith.
Oh, wonderful.
John here was kind enough
to show me around...
... offer me a warm meal, and introduce
me to some of your friends.
- What have you told them ?
- We weren’t talking about you.
- Oh, you weren’t ?
- No. We were discussing many things.
Now, when the issue of bed-wetting
happened to come up...
... she may have mentioned something
about your childhood.
That is not true.
- Relax. We all have embarrassing stories.
- Of course we do.
One time, the school bullies made me eat
lunch with my underwear on my head.
Oh, wait, that was you.
- And this is revenge for what, exactly ?
- You don’t even know, do you ?
Colonel Sheppard and Dr. mcKay
to the Isolation Room immediately.
Isolation Room ?
Come on.
- What in the world ?
- That’s you.
No, that is a live closed-circuit feed...
... of a man we have
in the Isolation Room.
What ?
He appeared in the containment chamber
in some sort of force field.
- What do you mean, he appeared ?
- Out of thin air.
l have Zelenka working on it.
Obviously we shut down the project.
Well, how did he get in there ?
He claims to be from
a parallel universe.
You said the odds against this
were astronomical.
- You saw the math.
- Well, we got it wrong.
He’s here now, so the question is,
what does he want ?
To talk to you.
All right, you want shared credit ?
You’re coming in with me.
Now, l figured you’d be here,
but Jeanie ?
l always hoped we’d work together
in Atlantis.
Well, this is a first.
- For me too.
Have a seat.
Now, l presume you go by--
Rodney.
Rod.
l could never get anyone
to call me that.
Okay, l’m gonna make
some assumptions...
... based on what l’ve seen here...
... and from readings we’ve taken
in my own space-time.
Please stop me if l’m wrong. One :
l presume you’re running
some sort of experiment...
... that’s designed to bridge
between parallel universes ?
And, two, it has something to do
with power generation.
- Warm ? Cold ?
- Hot.
Well, l’m sure the experiment’s
been a success on this side...
... but it’s having some rather serious
repercussions in my universe.
- l told you.
- Not now.
Dangerous particles that don’t belong
in either of our universes...
... are being created
on your side of the bridge.
So you knew this could happen ?
It was a slight risk, yes.
- This is weird.
-Well, you’re quite correct, Jeanie.
Because these particles don’t behave
according to any laws of physics...
... in our space-time...
... they’re creating a tear
in the fabric of our universe.
- First a solar system, now a universe.
- Yes. How exactly did you get here ?
Well, we detected the anomaly about
20 hours ago in space above the planet.
We maneuvered one of our Jumpers
in close...
... and tried to broadcast a signal
to whoever was on the other side.
We would be unable to detect that signal
from within the containment chamber.
So Sheppard and l came up with a plan
to beam a person into the anomaly.
They would be protected by an Ancient
personal force field that we discovered.
l depleted ours.
Still, it was an incredible risk.
Well, it was Sheppard’s idea.
We decided it might allow one of us...
... to cross the bridge
and bring the problem to your attention.
There was very little time
and, well, there seemed no other way.
- We drew straws.
- You lost.
No. l won. What, the prospect
of saving an entire universe ?
No, it was-- No-brainer.
Oh, sure.
l can’t begin to say how sorry we are.
Yes, well, you could start
by shutting down the experiment ?
Already done. And after hearing
what you’ve told me...
... l see no reason
why we’d start it up.
Great. Then my work here is done.
Mission accomplished.
Well, yes, but how did you plan
on getting, you know, back ?
l mean, to your own universe.
The matter bridge you created
is unidirectional.
- But that means--
- Yes. Yes, it does.
So, Jeanie, you have three kids
in this universe ?
No, just the one.
Well, l’m sure you’re as great a mother
in this space-time as you are in mine.
This’Il blow your mind.
l have photographs of your alternate life.
Wanna see the kids you haven’t had yet ?
Absolutely. Oh, look at Maddie.
- Who’s that ?
- That’s Bradley and Robbie.
All right, what’s the game plan ?
Put him up in the guest quarters
till we can find something permanent.
Something more permanent ?
We’re not keeping him.
- He can’t go back.
- That doesn’t mean he has to stay here.
- He’d rather be on Atlantis than Earth.
- l see. So he gets his way and l don’t.
How can you not wanna be with him ?
He’s you.
He’s not me. l’m me, the real me.
l suppose it’s all relative. To Rod,
his reality is every bit as valid as ours.
To him, we’re the impostors.
What does Élizabeth have to say
about this ?
Two McKays are better than one.
There aren’t two McKays.
There’s one McKay and him.
Whatever you say...
... Meredith.
Nice shot. Easily 275.
You know, l’ve been meaning
to put up buoy markers...
... but who has the time, huh ?
This is great. We don’t have
one of these where l’m from.
Besides, you’d need to take a cattle prod
to the Sheppard l know...
... to get him up this early.
Late nights partying, huh ?
If you could call it that.
He’s very active with the Mensa club
we have there.
They have a lot of functions.
Well, can’t blame a man
for his intelligence.
No, but l can blame him
for reminding me all the time.
- He doesn’t.
- Trust me.
My Sheppard makes your Rodney
seem modest in comparison.
Well, l got to admit,
between you and me...
... you’re a lot different
than our Rodney too.
How so ?
It’s the little things.
You like golf.
You say please and thank you. You’re...
What’s the opposite
of condescending ?
Now, l can help you with that hook.
- What the hell is this ?
- Hey, sleepyhead.
- Yeah, hi.
- l had a breakfast date with Jeanie.
l guess it ballooned into a group affair.
Sit down. We’re tracing back our lives...
... trying to find differences
between our pasts.
Rod is an honorary member
of the Athosian Council.
And is godfather to his niece
and nephews.
- Yes, well, how wonderful for him.
- Well, it’s easier for me.
Our Earth has a ZPM too, so it makes
the back-and-forth a lot simpler.
Doctors mcKay, please report
to the containment chamber.
Doctors mcKay.
- Excuse me.
- Hey, Rod, are we still on to spar later ?
- Absolutely.
What do you mean you started it up ?
Shutting the experiment down only
made things worse for us, not better.
The matter bridge is still active,
but we are not drawing any power...
... creating pressure like a dam.
If we didn’t turn it on, it could have
resulted in a catastrophic overload.
- We should have thought of that.
- Don’t look at me.
You’re willing to take the credit
but none of the blame ?
l never wanted all the credit.
- Oh, no one is blaming you.
- Oh, really ?
Look, this is just a temporary solution.
The Zelenka in my space-time estimates
that there is at least a week and a half...
... before the tear expands
as far as the city.
- My city.
- What’Il happen when it does ?
Imagine what would happen if you threw
the laws of physics out the window.
Entropy. Chaos.
Worst-case scenario, the entropy
expands as far as the subspace layers...
... underneath our space-time.
It could travel instantaneously. Your
universe could flash out of existence.
We need to mend that tear
before it becomes irreparable.
l have some thoughts.
Is there a place we could go to work ?
Oh, yes, of course. Follow me.
- Jeanie, we could use your help.
- Thank you.
Do you mind running up
these power requirements ?
Done.
What were you doing
having breakfast with him ?
l don’t often meet people
from another universe.
l found myself curiously interested.
Well, l don’t want you hanging around
with him anymore.
- What ?
- Look, l am your real brother.
- In what sense ?
- Oh, what is that supposed to mean ?
You haven’t been a brother to me
since l quit school.
You were making an incredible mistake.
l was trying--
You were trying to control my life, Mer.
l disagreed with you. l still do.
What, because of that,
you stopped being my brother ?
- l never stopped being your brother.
- We haven’t talked in four years.
- Don’t put that all on me.
- It is all on you.
l had no way of getting in touch.
l was doing top-secret research
in another galaxy.
You could have sent me a message.
You know, call me on my birthday,
at Christmas.
Once a year,
that’s all l would have needed.
Just a,« ou » ?Hi. How are you ?
Are you happy ? Are you okay ? »
That would have been enough,
but you didn’t do that.
l was wrong and you were right.
So, what, l was not worth talking to ?
It wasn’t like that at all.
You don’t like me talking to Rod...
... because it makes you realize
how bad a brother you’ve really been.
Hey, you guys got something
over there ?
No. We don’t.
- He’s slowing me down.
- Really ?
l thought two of you
would have sped things up.
Yeah, he’s not me.
l know he’s not the same person,
trust me.
Just saying he’s a genius too,
isn’t he ?
- Unless he’s lying.
- About what ?
What if the people on his Atlantis were
sick of him messing up all the time, huh ?
So when it came time to send
some stooge to another universe...
... there was only one guy
they could do without.
Say what you want.
l know what this is about.
Oh, really ?
Mr. Mensa-ln-a-Parallel-Universe,
what is this all about ?
You think Jeanie likes him
more than you.
What ? That’s crazy. That’s-- That’s--
That’s possibly true.
Jeanie and l drifted apart.
l mean, that happens.
It wasn’t done maliciously.
Do l have regrets ? Yes, of course l do.
But who doesn’t ? l mean--
You know, l’m not very good at saying
l’m sorry or that l’m wrong...
... you know, possibly because
it happens so rarely.
So l didn’t call or write.
And when l realized that four years
has gone by, it was just a...
You’re right. Of course, you’re right.
She has every reason to hate me.
- l didn’t say she hates you.
- Yeah, well, she should.
- Well, if you insist.
- Yeah, l do.
Fine. Fair enough.
Dr. mcKay to the containment chamber.
Dr. mcKay.
Good talk. Thanks.
- Great, he’s here.
- What’s going on ?
l set up a way to pick up transmissions
inside the containment chamber...
... should Rod’s universe
try to contact us.
We, of course, still have no way
of communicating with them, but--
- They sent us a message.
- Yeah.
Their exotic-particle problem...
... is spinning out of control much faster
than they’d anticipated.
- Oh, boy.
- But they have a solution.
- They do ? That’s great.
- Well, not really.
Their solution
will not only destroy Atlantis...
... but tear a hole
in the fabric of this universe.
Oh, boy.
Now, l’m not saying that their attempt
would be successful, but if it was...
... it would flood the exotic particles
created on their side...
... into this space-time all at once.
- And that would--
- Be bad.
- Right. l got that, but--
- How bad ?
Well, to be honest, the science
gets extremely complicated...
... but simply put...
... the tear will eventually swallow up
the entire galaxy, possibly the universe.
So...
... very bad.
l think we can all agree that
that would be bad.
Their plan will take six hours
to implement.
l suggest we do something
before that.
- Well, we have an idea.
- Actually, Jeanie has an idea.
We think we can collapse the bridge with
a massive burst of energy from this side.
And stop the creation of exotic particles
on the other side by doing so.
- How massive a burst are we talking ?
- Everything we’ve got.
l mean, enough to severely deplete
our ZPM.
So instead of creating
a new powerful energy source...
... we’Il be sacrificing the one
we already have.
Yes. We’d still be able to dial Earth,
but much less frequently, of course.
And let’s just say, l wouldn’t wanna
be around here if the Wraith show up.
l don’t see that we have a choice.
All right. Do it.
Dr. Weir gave the okay for this ?
You’d rather the universe
was destroyed ?
- Not really.
- Rodney, can l talk to you for a second ?
Look, the Daedalus is still in orbit.
l thought--
l know what you’re gonna say.
If l can beam into the energy stream,
protected by my personal force field--
You’d be transported
back to your own universe. l know.
l didn’t bring it up because,
if it doesn’t work--
Well, l’m willing to take that risk.
l’ve already requested the Daedalus
to execute the transport...
... to the coordinates inside the chamber
on your mark.
That is, if you’re willing to do this.
Everyone loves you here.
Yeah, but it’s not home.
Look, what,
my Sheppard is a know-it-all...
... my Teyla is hard to talk to,
and my Ronon is--
Well, actually,
those two are pretty similar.
l guess what l’m trying to say is that,
for all their faults...
... they’re my team.
My place is with them.
Besides, they’re not looking
for another McKay around here.
- They already have one.
- It’s just a lesser model.
l envy you.
You say exactly what’s on your mind
no matter how it makes you look.
l can only imagine the freedom you must
have not caring if people like you or not.
- What, people don’t like me ?
- Trust me, you’ve got it great here.
Now, l’ve made some calculations.
When the readings reach the levels
l’ve indicated...
... you’Il know whether or not
l made it home.
Well, l guess you just need
to click your heels together, huh ?
Good luck, Rodney.
Yeah, you too.
Radek.
Jeanie.
- You’re letting him do this ?
- l tried to talk him out of it.
But you know Rod.
Hermiod, ready when you are.
l guess there’s nothing left to say
but there’s no place like home.
All right, all in the green.
Ready for forced power output.
Right. Then...
You wanna press the button ?
Yeah. Yeah. Sure.
Power is at full.
It’s working.
Hermiod, this is McKay.
Commence transport.
Transport is complete.
- The bridge is beginning to destabilize.
- It’s not yet enough.
- ZPM’s at 50 percent.
- It’s still not enough, Rodney.
- We have to max it out.
- Thirty percent.
The bridge is collapsing.
We’ve done it.
- Okay, we can shut it down now.
- Not yet.
According to these readings, if we
shut it down now, he won’t make it.
Give it a few more seconds.
- ZPM’s at 5 percent.
- Almost there.
Cut power now.
How much power did you drain
from the ZPM ?
All of it.
l drained all of it.
You did the right thing.
Well, l suppose l would’ve done
the same thing for...
... me.
l am so fired.
Jeanie, it’s your brother, Rodney.
I wanna say...
... family is important.
I’ve come to realize that
because the people here...
... have become a sort of
a kind of surrogate family to me.
I know what you’re thinking.
I’ve never been the poster child
for that kind of sentiment.
But when one’s contemplating
one’s own demise...
... one tends to see things
more clearly.
I really do wish you the best, you know ?
And I’m sorry we weren’t closer.
Perhaps...
... if, by chance, I make it out of this,
perhaps one day we can be.
And I would like that.
Now, if there’s time, I’d like to--
When did he record this ?
Couple years back when we thought
the bad guys were gonna get us.
Now l’ve seen three sides
of my brother.
Yeah.
What are you two up to ?
Nothing. Just telling stories about you.
You know,
trying to help her fall asleep.
l’Il leave you guys alone.
- Hey.
Hey, you should be packing.
Daedalus leaves in the morning.
l’m done. How’d it go with Weir ?
Well, she wasn’t too happy
about the whole killing the ZPM...
... but, you know,
in the grand scheme of things...
... we did prevent the destruction
of the universe.
So, you know, not fired.
- That’s good.
- Yeah.
Oh, right. Got this for Madison.
Yeah. Swiped it from Weir’s desk.
Well, it’s not like there’s a Toys R Us
nearby, so...
Well, it’s the thought that counts,
l guess.
- Well, l’d say,« ou » ?See you around, » but...
- Yes.
About that.
Which is to say...
Look, what l wanted to...
Thank you for trying.
How are you ? You happy ? You okay ?
Yeah, Mer. l am.
l really am.
Intergalactic Gate Network
should be completed soon.
So...
... maybe it won’t be four years
next time ?
Does this mean
l’Il see you at Christmas ?
If you can convince Kaleb
not to make Tofurkey.
No promises.
Am l just not getting
the team e-mails anymore ?
Take it easy.
We’re just talking about Rod.
- Oh, yes, well, of course you are.
- Do you think he made it back ?
Well, it’s hard to say, really,
but l doubt he’Il be back, though.
- Good. We found him a little creepy.
- What ?
l can’t stand people
who are nice all the time.
Makes me feel like
they’re trying to hide something.
- Really ?
- He kept trying to correct me...
... on my Athosian history.
It grew tiresome very quickly.
Why, well, he wasn’t that bad.
Yeah, well, let’s be honest.
Rod was annoying.
Well, l’Il be honest with you.
That’s kind of nice to hear.
Now...
... what else has been happening ?
Well, Teyla’s got the hots
for one of the new Marines.
- That is not true.
- You know it is.
Hardly new either.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]