Previously on Stargate Atlantis :
You have some Wraith DNA.
My father told people
that it was a gift.
l could help my people by warning
of the Wraiths’approach.
No matter how many Wraith ships
they destroyed, more kept coming.
You think Teyla might tap
into this Wraith psychic network ?
If she can...
... we’Il be able gather all the intel
we needed about them.
l would not consider asking you
to do this if l didn’t think...
... it could provide us
with vital information.
And Dr. Beckett will remain on hand
at all times to monitor your physiology.
l am on a ship...
You are all so pathetic.
« Shotgun, » is it ?
Come on.
Don’t know why l have to do this.
What ?
Nobody said anything.
You don’t have to.
It’s not my fault things are hard to find
on the bottom of the ocean.
Rodney, you said you knew
where it was.
l said l knew its last known location.
It is a mobile drilling station, remember ?
- That’s gonna take a few hours.
- If we don’t find it...
- ... this will be your last known location.
- Oh, zing.
Okay, kids, do l have
to pull this thing over ?
It’s hard enough being in this damn thing
for hours without listening to you guys.
Dr. McKay has managed to narrow the
search field to a remarkably small area.
Finally, a voice of reason.
Thank you, Dr...
- Graydon.
- Yes, yes, of course.
Well, welcome to the team.
l’ve been here almost eight months.
Really ?
It’s been that long, has it ?
Time certainly flies.
Unless you’re in a Jumper,
looking for a needle in a haystack.
You know what ? Shut up.
- You know what ? You shut up.
- l don’t hear Grayson complaining.
It’s Graydon, with a » D. »
What ? You sure ?
It’s my name.
No, l could’ve sworn the guy
l wanted was called Grayson.
Because l remember thinking
« Dick Grayson, » Bruce Wayne’s ward.
Well, it’s Graydon.
Guess that means
l hired the wrong guy.
Well, still glad you came ?
Oh, sorry. l was preoccupied thinking
about the geothermal drilling platform.
It shouldn’t take us much longer.
We just passed a thermal layer.
l’m getting some readings
a couple of hundred feet ahead.
If we did manage to find an alternate
and limitless power supply...
... well, that would make
even this insufferably long search...
... seem worthwhile.
Okay, kids, we’re here.
Well, hopefully it won’t take too much
longer to power up this station.
That wasn’t so hard.
All l gotta do is dock this thing...
... and we can find out
what this place is all about.
All systems are online
and functioning at full capacity.
You mean
we’re generating power already ?
Well, no, but we probably
could if we wanted to.
No, slow down. The Ancients
abandoned this project for a reason.
Let’s try to find out what that reason
might be before we start drilling.
Yes, well, fair enough.
Have we not been down
this hallway before ?
Every corridor looks the same.
Don’t worry, l have
an uncanny sense of direction.
l think she’s right.
We’ve been down this way.
That’s impossible. We took a left
and a left and then a right.
Hey, look, all l’m saying is--
What ?
l’m sensing a Wraith presence nearby.
Are you sure ?
We’re pretty deep underwater.
l cannot be certain, but l believe
it is onboard the drilling platform.
This is Sheppard.
Everyone drop what you’re doing, get
back to the control room immediately.
We did a complete life signs scan.
The first thing we did
when we stepped aboard.
Look, l promise you,
there is nobody here but us.
No, Rodney.
- And l’m sensing it even closer now.
- Maybe it’s the pressure.
- It’s known to do things to the mind.
- Just humor me and check again.
There. All of these life signs
have been accounted for.
Humored ?
Wraith don’t show up on life signs
detectors if they’re hibernating.
- l know what l’m sensing.
- There is no Wraith, l’m telling you.
- Has your sense ever been wrong ?
- Never.
And l cannot shake this feeling.
- l trust her.
- As opposed to irrefutable fact ?
- Machines don’t know.
- Never said they did.
There is a way for me to be sure.
If l can reach out with my mind
and establish a link--
- That’s a little reckless.
- If there is no Wraith...
... then there will be no mind for me to
link with and therefore no risk.
But if there is a Wraith nearby...
We need to know.
- l’m ready.
- You sure ?
The briefest contact will determine
whether or not l’m right.
That’s all we need,
so don’t stick around any longer.
And we will bring you out of it
at the first sign of trouble.
- Just to be sure--
- It’s already set to stun.
Sorry.
Teyla ?
l was mistaken.
There is nothing there.
Now, that’s good.
- l’m sorry.
- No reason to be sorry.
Perhaps it was the effect of
the pressure at this depth.
Well, if you’ve ever seen The Abyss,
pressure can make you nuts.
Not that l think you’re nuts.
It’s all right, John.
l’m relieved.
So am l.
Well, we have a lot of exploring to do.
We ?
Until Rodney delivers the preliminary
status report, l’m all yours.
Put me to work, colonel.
All right, let’s make up some time.
Break into teams.
Ronon, you’re with Teyla.
Élizabeth, you’re with me...
... or l’m with you,
however you wanna put it.
Either way or either way.
That was weird.
Well, we are at the very bottom
of the ocean.
Maybe you’re right, Teyla’s just
experiencing the effects of the pressure.
Hopefully not as bad as that guy
in The Abyss.
This place is big, huh ?
What’s wrong ?
- Nothing. Why ?
- You just haven’t said a word.
Have l not ?
No.
Has my silence made you
uncomfortable ?
No.
Your friendship is very important
to me.
l would hate to do anything
that made you...
... uncomfortable.
Okay. Well, l’m good.
Rodney ? What’s going on ?
- What do you mean what’s going on ?
-We just lost the lights.
What ?
- You’re right.
-Yes, we can see that.
We lost power to 40 percent
of the station.
Sensors are currently off-line.
Zelenka, what’re you doing ?
What do you mean, what am l doing ?
Have you lost power where you are ?
No, have you ?
- No.
-We have.
l wanna know what’s going on.
This station has been lying
idle down here for a few millennia.
Bound to blow a few fuses.
Look, l’Il have power back online
in a minute. Just hang tight.
Ronon, Teyla, report your position.
Ronon ? Teyla ? Come in.
Ronon ? Teyla ?
Rodney, we’ve lost contact with Ronon
and Teyla. Do you know their position ?
No. Internal sensors are out.
I have the location
where the power went down.
It’s an auxiliary control area,
search grid six.
The deck that Ronon and Teyla
were exploring.
We’Il meet you there.
Okay, Davidson.
- It’s Dickenson, sir.
- l was in the ballpark. Give me a break.
Get back to the Jumper...
... see if you can use its sensors to locate
our people within the drilling platform.
Graydon, you go with him.
There you are.
- Weapons fire.
- Nine mil. This way.
Oh, yes, let’s race towards
the gunfire.
Ronon, Teyla, come in.
Are you all right ?
- No.
- Did you see who attacked you ?
Yeah, it was Teyla.
- What ? Why ?
- Okay, until we know what’s going on...
... l’d like everyone in one place.
This is Zelenka. Someone has activated
force fields throughout the station.
- Can you make it to the control room ?
-Yes, I think so.
- Do it.
- Doesn’t make sense. What’s she doing ?
You and Élizabeth go to the control
room. Ronon and l will check on Teyla.
- Be careful.
- No kidding.
Drop it.
John.
What the hell’s going on ?
l do not know.
- Rodney, what’s the status ?
- As far from the quo as it gets.
Teyla didn’t just shut down several
key systems.
She scrambled
the existing operating codes.
This is going to take a while.
Can we contact Atlantis ?
The station’s communication is gone.
l can’t patch it.
She’s blown the control crystals,
shut down half the power...
... and set up a series
of emergency force fields.
To what purpose ?
This is Sheppard. We got Teyla.
- And ?
- And nothing.
She has no memory of anything
that happened in the last hour.
We’re on our way to crew quarters.
I’Il meet you there.
Let’s forget restoring
this station to its former glory.
Concentrate on internal sensors
and disabling force fields...
... that are cutting us off
from the Jumper.
Élizabeth, l’m so sorry.
Don’t worry about that.
- How are you feeling now ?
- l’m fine.
But to hear of the damage l caused and
yet to have no memory of my actions...
Just tell us what you do remember.
l was attempting to seek out the Wraith
presence with my mind, and then...
There is a Wraith ?
The most powerful mind
l have ever encountered.
- l tried to shut her out.
- Her ?
Yes.
l believe this Wraith is a queen.
- l hate queens.
- In that brief moment, l sensed...
... great power, the experiences
of many centuries.
Hunger.
And then...
... nothing.
My next memory is of Colonel Sheppard
and Ronon aiming their weapons at me.
There’s a Wraith
on the drilling platform.
Well, if that were the case, why’d she
use Teyla to do all that damage...
... and why didn’t
the detector pick up a signal ?
It doesn’t matter.
- If she’s here, l’Il find her.
- We’Il find her.
l would like to help.
l’m sorry, Teyla.
- But until we can determine what’s--
- Yes, of course.
l understand.
Dickenson. Any progress
on disabling those force fields ?
I’m getting indications that some
of them are going up and down.
-We could use the Jumper’s sensors.
- l’m doing my best, sir.
One of these days,
l’m gonna call him Dr. McCoy.
- l’d love to be there for that.
- The next time he calls me Grayson.
Actually, l know a Grayson.
- There really is a Grayson ?
- Yeah, he’s a damn good scientist too.
l’m surprised McKay didn’t hire him.
Did you do that ?
l don’t know.
But l’m happy to take credit for it.
- Check it out.
- Yeah.
l don’t understand.
What could the Wraith want with an
Ancient drilling platform ?
How did they even get here ?
- l don’t know, maybe on a ship nearby.
- Underwater ?
Who knows ? Teyla’s spidey sense
works for miles.
- Are the external sensors up ?
- Yes, they’re operational.
- They’re to scan the ocean.
- Doesn’t matter.
Coleman, look at the drilling platform’s
external sensors. See what you turn up.
- What am l looking for ?
- Anything.
How are you feeling ?
l’ve never been more ashamed.
- Oh, you can’t blame yourself.
- l should have been more careful.
A Wraith Queen’s mind
is extremely powerful, Teyla.
- You know that better than l do.
- Still.
If my actions while under her control
result in people getting hurt...
If you hadn’t done what you did...
... who knows
what could’ve happened.
At least now we know
what we’re dealing with.
If anything, l should thank you.
l certainly don’t blame you.
l would like to help them find her.
- Teyla.
- There is no risk.
l don’t know that.
Unless you suspect l am still
under her control even now ?
Would l be alone with you if l did ?
Then you think
l am somehow vulnerable to her ?
l think it is best to keep you away
from her for the moment, yes.
Look, l don’t fully understand
this capability you have...
... of linking with a Wraith mind,
but if it’s even remotely possible--
She was only able to control me
because l opened my mind to her.
If l choose to do so again...
... l will be ready.
- Teyla, l know you wanna help.
- l do.
The best way for you to do that is allow
Ronon and Colonel Sheppard to find her.
As you wish.
It’s about time. l was beginning
to think you had gotten lost.
Listen, did you manage to-- ?
Colonel Sheppard.
If you can hear me...
... please.
Help me--
Who am l talking to ?
What’s your location ?
McKay ?
Do you have any men
unaccounted for ?
Two guys l just sent back
to the Jumper.
l think they’re in trouble.
Can you get those force fields down ?
We’re working on it.
The Wraith presence
is even stronger than before.
She is aboard this station.
You must warn them.
Colonel Sheppard, Teyla is certain
the Wraith is aboard the station.
Understood.
Ronon, l’m heading back
to the Jumper. Meet me there.
l’m on my way.
Sheppard, help me. Please.
McKay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, almost there.
l can only do one at a time.
The Jumper’s sensors
should be able to locate them.
Graydon ?
Graydon’s dead.
-Fed upon.
- What about Dickenson ?
There’s no sign of him yet.
See if we can find him using the...
Sheppard ?
Sheppard, come in.
You are Sheppard.
The one who can fly this ship.
You will return me to the surface.
Kneel.
Sheppard, this is mcKay.
What have you got ?
Sheppard, can you hear me ?
Is something wrong ?
You will fly me to the stargate...
... and return me to my people.
Sheppard, this is mcKay.
Please respond. Sheppard, come in.
l’m here.
We had to throw the emergency
force fields up.
- The section you were in was flooding.
- l noticed.
You were thrown by the force of the
water clear of the force field bulkhead.
Ronon ?
l missed.
l noticed that too.
Everyone else is accounted for.
Any sign of Dickenson ?
Stand by, McKay.
Look, l don’t know what just happened,
but we are now cut off from the Jumper.
- l won’t miss now.
- Wait.
What for ?
Well, we lost the Jumper and we lost
communications with Atlantis.
Maybe she can help us
get out of this place.
Welcome back.
l trust you’re comfortable ?
That groggy sensation you’re feeling are
the sedatives we’re pumping you full of.
Just a precaution.
As for the other precautions...
Now, you’re gonna tell us everything
we want to know.
In exchange for ?
This is not a negotiation.
l disagree.
Let me get this over with.
How did you get aboard this station ?
Are there any more of you ?
You are all about to die.
Really ?
You care to elaborate on that at all ?
We should keep the force fields up till
Atlantis sends a rescue Jumper.
Station communications
are still down--
If l’d listened to Teyla,
this wouldn’t have happened.
- It’s not your fault.
- l sent those men back to the Jumper.
Well, the sensors indicated that
there was nobody here.
l don’t think there was, sir. The Wraith
arrived after we did the scans.
- What ?
- l did a search...
... with the remote sensors.
l found something.
We didn’t notice it on the way down
because it’s radiating very little EM.
Guys, head back here.
l think l have a few answers.
- A Wraith cruiser ?
- Seems completely buried in silt.
Which means it’s been here
a very, very, very long time.
- Yes, give or take a very.
- That doesn’t explain how she got here.
- Maybe she swam over.
- No, no. The pressure at that depth is--
Deadly to humans,
but she’s not human, remember ?
Yes, it’s difficult to imagine, but with
a Wraith’s ability to heal itself...
- And there are no other Wraith onboard ?
- No way to know for sure.
Our prisoner isn’t talking.
Other than,« ou » ?You’re all about to die. »
Which may or may not
be an empty threat.
- And you have no way of knowing ?
- She said it with a lot of confidence.
- There is a way to find out.
- We’ve already been down that road.
What is to stop her asserting
control over you again ?
She is heavily sedated.
And this time, l know exactly
what l’m dealing with.
You.
l was caught off-guard the first time.
That will not happen again.
It does not matter.
Well, we think it does.
Your fate is sealed.
If you have any reason to suspect
that l’m not myself...
... do not hesitate to use that.
l won’t.
l see her...
... leading the first wave of ships that
attacked Atlantis during the war.
Queen of a great alliance.
Her ship was damaged
during the battle.
It crashed into the ocean.
She fed upon
her own crew to survive.
Too deep to ever swim to the surface.
Waking between centuries...
... waiting for rescue
that never came...
... until finally she was alone.
She sensed our presence
during our descent.
She sensed...
... me.
And saw us as her one chance
at freedom from her prison.
The water was crushing...
... but she was determined.
Finally, after all these millennia,
a ship.
But she did not possess the gene
to fly it.
She used Dickenson to call for me.
Teyla ?
- You are all about to die.
- That does not sound like Teyla.
You are all about to die.
- Teyla, snap out of it.
- Wait.
She has activated the self-destruct
device of the Wraith cruiser.
It is set to detonate within two hours.
So not an empty threat.
- How’s Teyla ?
- She’s resting.
It took more out of her
than she’Il admit.
- What’s the news ?
- It looks like the Ancients...
... chose this section
because the planet’s crust...
... is remarkably thin below us...
... allowing to drill into the magma and
maximize the geothermal power output.
- Okay.
- Which means there’s a great deal...
... of potential energy directly
beneath this station.
That’s the news ? That this place
works as advertised ?
No, no, the news is that
if they were to detonate, say...
... the self-destruct of a Wraith cruiser
on such a wafer-thin crust...
- Oh, my God.
- All that thermal energy...
... directly beneath us
will be released all at once.
So bad news.
The explosion will be magnified a
thousand times.
- We’re talking catastrophic.
- So it won’t just be us.
No, Atlantis will be affected as well.
It’s within the blast radius.
- We have no way to warn them ?
- They’d never see it coming.
So we disarm the self-destruct.
- That’s brilliant, we need to get there.
- Without the Jumper ?
We’re behind schedule.
They’Il send a rescue Jumper.
Even if they’ve left,
the moment we were overdue--
- They won’t make it in time.
- How far is the cruiser ?
- Less than a kilometer.
- She swam that far ?
- What is she ?
- A formidable enemy.
l have an idea.
l found these in the database
when we first got here.
They were used to make
repairs to the exterior of the station.
- Very cool.
- You’Il be able to traverse the distance.
- You mean we.
- Yes, of course. We.
This must be how she got in.
Probably.
All right, let’s get suited up.
Right.
You’re breathing too hard.
Forgive me for being aware of exactly
how much pressure...
... is being exerted on this suit
right now.
Just think of it as a walk
on the beach.
A beach that’s about to explode.
That’s supposed
to make me feel better ?
No, it’s supposed to make you walk
faster. We’re on a clock here.
This is Weir. How close are you ?
Almost there, but we’re running
out of time.
We need Teyla to do her
Kreskin act again.
l’d rather not have to. l think it could be
much too dangerous for her.
So is exploding magma.
l am walking as fast as l can.
How do we disarm the self-destruct ?
You won’t survive the blast
any more than we will.
l can get the information we need.
If you were strong enough...
... you would have done so already.
l can feel how weak you are.
We shall see who is stronger.
- That took too long.
- Yeah, well...
... l probably won’t be able to disarm the
self-destruct in time, we’re not in a rush.
Why don’t we find it,
then you can be negative ?
This ship is remarkably preserved.
You’d think after 10,000 years
she’d wanna redecorate.
l’m serious. Hull damage is minimal.
They probably lost their main drive.
You’re saying this is salvageable ?
l have to assess damage to primary
systems, but it’s not out of the question.
You’d just go and blow it up or slam it
into a hive ship or something...
... and all that work
would be for nothing.
This way.
Teyla ?
You are weakening.
l think you should stop.
My concentration slipped
for a moment.
And in that moment, l could have
crushed you with a single thought.
Perhaps next time, l will.
- There isn’t gonna be a next time.
- l’m fine.
No, you’re not. l can see
what this is doing to you.
Let’s just give McKay a chance.
There it is.
What ?
l’m sure this is the device, l’m sure
it says we have less than half an hour.
So turn it off.
- What does that mean ?
- It’s not accepting commands.
There must be some kind
of a command code...
- ... that needs to be entered.
- Can you figure it out ?
Command codes are simple like the
number one or the letter A...
- ... like, in Wraith, which would be--
- Can you figure it out or not ?
Not if l stood and tried
for a million years...
... and we have just under
a million years less than that.
Élizabeth, you there ?
Any luck ?
Negative. We don’t get her
command code...
... in less than 30 minutes,
we’re dead.
- This is the only way.
- l told you, Rodney has another idea.
That may or may not succeed.
There is only one way to be certain.
She said she would kill you next time.
l will not let that happen.
No. We’re gonna give them
more time.
Ronon.
There’s an emergency in the control
room. Dr. Weir needs your help.
What about her ?
l will watch the prisoner. Hurry.
Watch yourself.
Are you fool enough to try again ?
l have very little to lose.
You are trying to hide something
from me.
There’s been a development.
You’ve been able to disarm
the self-destruct ?
No, but Rodney thinks if he can tie in
a Naquadah generator...
- ... he can get the cruiser to fly.
- After all these years ?
Damage was superficial.
Problem was the engines.
McKay’s restored power and l think...
- ... l can fly the ship to a distance.
- That’s a suicide mission.
If l can ditch the ship on the mainland,
maybe l can get far enough away.
- l gotta go now.
- Wait.
Let me try again. If l can get her to give
up her code...
- ... you won’t have to risk it.
- You’re in no condition to do that.
Sorry.
Well.
You’re a hell of a swimmer,
l’Il give you that.
You have restored power ?
It’Il fly.
You shall be rewarded
with a quick death.
She’s not dying
according to plan here.
l thought you’d forgotten about me.
l just had to wait for her
to disable the device.
Be thankful she didn’t feed on you
before she entered the command code.
- That’s why you didn’t wanna be bait.
- No...
... you had to be bait because she was
expecting you to fly the ship.
- She is dead, right ?
- Let’s get out of here.
How are you feeling ?
Much better, now that l no longer
feel the constant presence of a Wraith.
That was no ordinary Wraith. It took
a lot of bullets to take her down.
l wish l was there.
He’s right, you know. l mean, deceiving
a Wraith Queen ? That’s no small feat.
When there are so many lives at stake,
it’s easy to summon the strength.
Well, Zelenka’s finally got
communications back up.
Turns out Atlantis
had sent another Jumper.
- It should be here within the hour.
- That’s good news.
Yeah, no kidding.
l can’t wait to see the sun.
We haven’t finished what we came for.
Wraith’s gone.
We got a ton of research.
- Yes, we do.
- In fact, l’m sure we should be able...
... to come up with a way to get auxiliary
power online in a couple of days.
Is he serious ?
- Yeah, he is.
- Well, l for one...
... intend to spend
the next little while resting.
Same here.
Yeah. Same here.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]