Previously on Greek.
I'm so happy that you decided
to go into marketing
I'm thinking about
going back to law school
- That's great.
- I brought it up with Cap.
You have to live your own life.
You have to go after what you want
- and not worry about him.
- I'm not ready to graduate.
- What about you and Casey ?
- If she gets into CRU Law,
- it won't be an issue.
- If she doesn't ?
- I don't know.
- I'm sorry I tried to change you.
- What about graduation ?
- We'll worry about that in May.
Dana inspires me.
Do you need to talk to me
about anything else ?
I've been thinking. I enjoy our time
together, but I don't want to hide it.
No.
Sorry.
Why won't you tell me your plan ?
- There isn't one.
- I could help you.
But I also know if I have a problem,
I can come to you.
I wish you felt the same.
Ladies and gentlemen, as president,
it is my job
to nominate the one man
who can lead us to victory.
And our new Revenge Chair :
Rusty Cartwright !
Phase one is complete.
Phase Two :
Myrtle Beach.
After years of pranks and brawls
and pledge paddles, this is it.
Revenge on Omega Chi
has never looked so sweet.
And fun !
The first phase of Mission :
Probable is complete.
The next three are ready
and waiting in Myrtle Beach.
You might have to do
some of this without me.
I have a secret mission
of my own involving your sister.
And put Evan Chambers down.
What are you doing ?
Are you talking about
Casey's birthday ?
I thought you were cc'ed
on her gift wish list.
No, I'm pretty sure this is something
she won't be expecting.
No way !
Wait, is that the same lavaliere
that Beaver...
Don't ask questions.
You don't want to know.
This is Casey's last spring break.
I'm gonna get this right.
Find the perfect moment.
You know, if this works,
we're never gonna have to worry
about the Omega Chis again.
That's the plan.
Mini-car !
You're going down,
little Omega Chi pony !
B Team, rappel !
Boot stomps !
That makes my sixth interview
this week !
After graduation, I'm just
gonna have to live off the land.
Whatever that means.
- It went well ?
- If you ask me what my weaknesses are,
I'm gonna tell you !
Punctuality's
overrated anyway.
Fortunately, we have Spring Break
to delight and maybe even surprise us.
And take our minds off
of all this post-grad craziness.
By post-grad craziness, are you
referring to the fact that you're both
insanely checking your e-mail
for law school responses ?
So far I've been rejected
from Stanford, Georgetown and Texas.
I feel like Laura at a mixer.
- You still have George Washington...
- And CRU.
I just want to know already.
You know,
we did get some mail earlier today.
What ? Where is it ?
Where is it at ?
They say you can tell a lot about
whether you were accepted
or not by the size of the envelope.
I can't look !
- Like what they say about guys' feet.
- That's a myth !
Where's the damn mail ?
It's big.
It's really big.
Read it.
Open it !
My God, I got into GW Law School
in Washington, DC !
- That's awesome !
- I know !
My God.
This is really happening.
Yeah, it's happening.
And you know they really
did admit you because
George Washington University
cannot tell a lie.
Ash, did you get any mail from CRU ?
Not yet, right ?
Right.
- = 320 =-
"All Children... Grow Up"
Kappa Team
And since the KTs
were gracious enough
to suck at golf last week,
I'm proud to say we have a sic
party house in Myrtle Beach !
It's on the Strand, wet bar, hot tub.
It's gonna be awesome !
All right, but not
too awesome, guys.
I got a letter from Nationals,
they're seriously
cracking down this year.
"Given several incidents involving
illegal or untoward behavior
"by some chapters last spring break,
"members involved in any illegal
activity will risk immediate suspension
and the revocation
of their charter".
Well, there goes our South
Carolinian prostitution ring.
All right, next up,
house elections are after
we return from spring break,
so I'll now open the floor
to presidential nominations.
JP ?
I nominate Trip Sutcliffe.
Well, I graciously and humbly
accept this nomination.
I would like to nominate
Calvin Owens.
Me ?
Shocker.
Even though we broke up,
I still appreciate his integrity
and I would love to see him
lead this house.
Thanks, Grant.
Great. Any other nominations ?
All right, then campaign season will
commence after Spring Break
for Sutcliffe versus Owens.
Meeting adjourned.
- So that was pretty cool of Grant ?
- Yeah,
I'm glad to see you guys
are staying friends.
- I'm not sure he did you a favor.
- What do you mean ?
You know what I've been through
with this house, these guys.
How much of a jerk I've had to be.
I'm just no sure
this is a job you're wired
to handle.
Or even really want.
I've never been
to Myrtle Beach before.
It's so great.
There's this club, Paradox.
Are they gonna stamp our hands or give
us one of those wristband things ?
I couldn't get in.
But the beach is so great.
Provided you wear sun block,
which I didn't.
Sounds...
dangerous.
Well, the truth is,
I was actually only there for one night.
I ended up coming back
with Calvin and Dale.
See, Calvin and I were kind
of in a fight because
of the feud between our houses.
Your houses sure fight a lot.
Well, this Spring Break's going
to be different.
There are a few things I have to do for
KT while I'm there, but outside of that,
it's gonna be all Dana-Rusty,
all the time.
I can't wait. I was lucky to get a room
so last minute.
Well...
I know we've only been
going out a couple of weeks.
And the way the economy is...
We could share a room.
To save money.
Only if you want !
Because of the economy.
And stuff.
I wouldn't mind...
saving a little money.
That's great !
Because the economy sucks,
so...
we can be frugal.
Together.
Yes, sir. I completely see the irony
of asking you to do something illegal
regarding admissions to a school
that teaches the law, but
if I did get into CRU Law, could you
just like cough or sniff or something ?
One cough yes, two coughs no ?
Hello ?
Stupid laws.
I have some good news. I just got off
the phone with Nationals and next year
they're requiring all houses employ
a full-time house mother.
- How's that good news ?
- I meant for us,
because we're graduating.
I wish I was graduating.
Trust me, little sis, you don't.
Where are we on Casey's
surprise birthday party ?
We're set ! I reserved a section
at Tijuana Tony's.
Big banner, lots of balloons,
pink ones.
And make sure they have a lemon drop
waiting for her. Then keep them coming.
What ?
Casey's as predictable
as a Katherine Heigl movie.
So what's all this graduation talk ?
Just the thought of going
to spring break single ?
- It's kinda sad.
- And kinda my second year doing it.
- Sorry.
- No, don't be.
We can find fun new guys together !
I'm kinda missing my lame old one.
We need to shake this Evan Chambers
thing. You know what we could do ?
We could take a vacation
from ourselves.
Can we go somewhere better
than Myrtle Beach ?
No, but we can lie about who we are.
I used to do it all the time on family
vacations. On one trip to San Francisco,
I told this waiter I was
a teen prodigy in town
to play the cello
for Tony Blair and Oprah.
And I got free dessert.
It was awesome.
Trust me.
Hey, you heading back down
to Sin in the Sand Land ?
Yeah. I thought you were going
turkey-hunting again.
I thought I'd do something different.
Hang out by the pool, get some sun.
It's too bad you don't want to go
to Sin in the Sand Land.
I wouldn't say no.
You just called it
"Sin in the Sand Land."
- Why would you want to go ?
- For the sand. If I were invited.
My room is going to be occupied.
But I do know someone else
who has an extra room.
- I can call her and see if...
- Is that an invitation ?
Do you want to go to Myrtle Beach
with me and Dana ?
- Dana's going ?
- I'm sure she won't mind.
No, I just find her really grating.
Let me think about it.
All right, I'll pack my floaties.
You're wasting valuable
party time, Case ! Let's go !
Hold on, guys.
Hi... do you have any mail
for Casey Cartwright ?
I'm her. I mean, I'm she.
She's me. I'm me. Hi.
Hi. I can't deliver mail
to strangers.
You're going to have to wait
until I get to your house.
This might be my last spring break
with my boyfriend.
Because we're going down two different
life paths. I get into CRU Law School.
Law school ?
So you know it's illegal...
Irony, got it.
Regardless, if I get into CRU, that'd
buy us a few more years. If I don't,
I've to accept this is a college thing
and we'll have to go our separate ways.
- I deliver mail for a living.
- I'll pay you.
Also illegal. You know what ?
Never mind, here.
I'll give you a trick of the trade.
You can tell whether you were accepted
or not by the size of the envelope.
CRU Law, right ?
Sorry.
Thanks.
- Anything from CRU ?
- Just this underwear catalog.
- Can I have it ?
- We've talked about this, Beav.
This is gonna be a spring break
you'll never forget.
I think so.
It's as God-awful as I'd imagined.
You know, Dale, I really wish
I hadn't canceled that room.
I don't mind staying with you two.
There's gotta be
a Hide-A-Bed or something.
Where's it hiding ?
Sorry, Dana.
It's okay. I just thought
we were gonna...
save a little money.
We are. We're doing this three ways.
No ! Not in the way you're thinking.
But there can still be some savings.
We can save some money elsewhere.
I brought coupons,
for your pleasure.
Stone Phillips says a black light
is the best way to check for residual...
protein matter.
There it is.
Looks like someone saved money
all over the room.
On the phone ?
I call the floor.
Guess we get the bed.
Did you guys see the
hot tub out back ?
This place is better than the house
on Jersey Shore.
And with fewer
hair-gelled fame-whores.
I can't believe we lucked out
with this place.
I can't believe the KTs
lucked into this place.
What the hell are you doing here ?
This is my boss's house.
- There's been a misunderstanding.
- No, freaking kidding !
This is our house.
We rented it for the week.
No, these guys we know rented it.
What are you, stupid or something ?
You got exactly ten seconds
to get off this property.
Or what ?
Sir, we apologize to you.
And we don't want any trouble
so we will be leaving now.
Take these items, please,
as a gift, and...
Sorry.
It's a set-up. Kappa Taus wanted
us to win that tournament.
- Well, now we're homeless.
- Guess we kinda had it coming.
Had it coming ? Let's serve it back.
Let's find a place
to stay first, Trip.
Phase two is complete.
So that's it. I guess I'm leaving
Cyprus and...
leaving Cappie.
I'm sorry.
But I thought you'd
accepted your relationship
with Cappie would end
after graduation.
I did, but that's when everything
was... theoretical.
- And now it's retical.
- Exactly.
I'm gonna be 22 !
Do you know who's 22 ? Old people.
But do old people bungee jump ?
Come on, it's our last spring break
I'm not going to let you
angst your way through it.
I am gonna miss you.
I'm gonna miss you, too !
How could I not have
gotten into CRU ?
I mean, that was my safety school !
GW Law was sort of a long shot.
You got into law school ?
Congrats ! I went to Georgetown.
Really ? Any advice ?
Yeah.
It's really hard.
Don't flunk out.
Who wants shots
from the Margarito Bandito ?
You want a shot ?
God, yes ! Please !
Here !
My first fake ID.
I can't believe it worked.
- Thank you, "Chad Stewart."
- Don't thank me, "Penelope Holmes."
Thank Kappa Tau.
What's the matter,
"Francis Domingo" ?
There's an awful lot
of gratuitous flesh.
It's like the CBS Evening News
with Katie Couric.
Well, I might try the bar.
What should get ?
"Sex on the Beach".
"Sex in the Water".
"Sex Wading in the Water but
Planning to Come Back to the Beach."
What do you think, Rusty ?
Just get anything you want.
With drink names like that,
they're practically promoting
unwanted pregnancies.
You won't have to worry about that.
- Now that I'm sharing the room.
- Thanks, Francis.
Thank you.
I'm Taylor.
I'm a dancer from Portland
who loves pugs, moody floral prints
and the music of Muse.
And you are ?
Julia.
Well that's a start.
Who are Julia and Taylor
going to meet first ?
I think you got one.
I'm gonna go in for a closer look.
I'm Taylor.
I'm a dancer from Portland.
I love your top.
It seems leopard print's
really making a comeback.
OK... thanks.
I have this friend
who just broke up with his boyfriend.
I could call him.
Hi ?
Sorry, cutie.
This is just business.
We come down here every year
to observe trends,
check out the young people.
I like your look.
I'm Faith Flowers.
Well, Faith Flowers,
let me be clear.
I'm not interested in porn,
or lifting my top
or making out with a girl.
Shame on you.
Was that Faith Flowers ?
I didn't know you watched porn.
Faith Flowers is a trend forecaster.
My father hired her
as a consultant back in the day.
Companies pay her to tell them
what the latest trends are.
That's a real job ?
I'd be so good at that !
It's like being cool and psychic !
Do something about it.
- What ? Beg her for a job ?
- She's right there...
Oh, no !
She was right there.
It's like she's magic.
She's the Fairy Job Mother.
Look, we already
have a hotel, all right ?
So let's put everything behind us
and have some fun.
Hi, guys. How's the house ?
We sure are pissed we lost it.
That house belongs to someone else.
Someone armed.
And it's spring break,
so we're stuck in a crap hotel.
Sorry to hear about that, Cal.
Thanks.
Heath meant that sarcastically,
by the way.
When you guys are trying
to sleep in your crappy hotel,
I hope you dream of Jeremy,
Ferret and Wade.
You're still whining about that ?
We didn't mean for them
to get expelled.
Then I didn't mean to sleep
with your girlfriend, Bing.
Wait, yes I did.
Everyone remember
what Nationals said.
All right...
Happy spring break, Evan Pompeo !
Of Grey's Anatomy fame !
How's your first
college spring break so far ?
I never want to leave !
I heard about GW,
that's so exciting !
- Yeah, really exciting.
- Where are you going to live ?
- I haven't thought about it.
- Are you going to get a roommate ?
- I'm not sure.
- Do you even know anyone there ?
No.
You're probably not going to have
a whole lot of time to socialize.
I bet law school is super hard.
Are you ready for it ?
You know what ?
I don't know.
I'm not even 100 percent sure
that I'm going.
I mean...
I could just stay in Cyprus
for another year.
Maybe take
that housemother job at ZBZ.
You should totally stay !
Right ?
My parents say hi.
They can't sleep at night
knowing I'm down here.
Their only comfort is knowing
I'm below the Mason-Dixon line.
So what should we do today ?
You could do your own thing today.
But I'm not sure
how much fun I can have alone
on a plantation tour.
Why don't you come with me ?
Dana and I had kinda had
some romantic time planned.
What's more romantic than taking
in the architectural detail
of two-century-old
slaves' quarters ?
I read online that girls love them.
I appreciate you coming all this way
because you wanted to spend time
- with me.
- I didn't come for you.
Do you think I enjoy
being your third wheel ?
Then why are you here ?
Forget it, have fun
with your girlfriend.
Is Francis okay ?
I have no idea.
You know, we're alone.
Do you want to save some money ?
Crap ! I've got this KT stuff
I gotta do.
It's Phase Three,
I'll be right back.
I will wait here.
Or I'll go to the beach.
Wake up, Casey.
Hurry, wake up !
Happy birthday !
That's so nice.
My gosh, I am so hung over.
Yeah.
How are you not ?
Practice.
You were the life of the party
last night.
At one point, you put a lamp shade
on your head.
You were so cute and cliché.
It was fun.
Thanks for the... cruller.
- I actually had something else...
- I didn't get into CRU.
I'm sorry.
But, I've been thinking...
about us.
And my life in Cyprus
and the sorority.
And I have decided...
to stay.
I can defer GW for a year.
Maybe even two.
You're not still drunk, are you ?
I've even been thinking about
taking up the house
mother position at ZBZ.
I love my life at ZBZ,
and I love you.
Why would I leave ?
Do you know what I feel like
doing now ?
I hope so.
Stop it.
I'm gonna get some clothes on.
Let's go.
Well, nothing
on the Fairy Job Mother so far.
How are you doing
on boy patrol, Julia ?
None so far.
You're still on vacation
from yourself !
Look for boys.
I can't vacate.
I miss Evan.
Are you going to
do something about it ?
Right. Just pour my heart out
and plead for him to take me back.
He's right over there.
Just open up myself to him
and possibly have him shut me down ?
You and I have had
our set of issues.
If I can forgive you...
maybe he can too.
Can you give me a minute ?
I'll meet up with you.
- Hi.
Here's the thing.
I'm just gonna get to the point.
I screwed up... big time.
I hurt you and I'm sorry for that.
I still care about you.
A lot, actually.
And I miss you.
And I'd appreciate a second chance.
I can't.
I appreciate your apology.
And I can forgive,
but I'm honestly not sure,
if I can forget.
Or if I even really want to.
I'm still pissed.
I'm sorry.
So then...
there it is.
You can see a lot up here.
You can practically see forever.
Speaking of forever, they something
I want to give to you.
If you're gonna puke I'd throw it
more that direction.
I think I see some OCs down there.
You know, I'm okay.
Why don't you go first ?
I thought you wanted to do this.
Are you scared ?
I'm not scared.
It's just...
- What if the cord breaks ?
- That never happens.
- Does it ?
- Nah.
Nah, never happens.
Well, what if it's calibrated wrong
and I hit the ground, bounce back up,
hit the platform and the ground again ?
Seems a little Wile E Coyote.
There's some basis
in real physics there.
I think that's just
the fear talking.
So what if it is fear ?
Fear's natural. It's good.
It keeps you from making mistakes.
Doing things
that you're not ready for.
Not when it keeps you
from living your life.
Having fun.
I just don't want to do it.
So I'm going to crawl back down.
I'll see you on the ground.
Not if I see you first.
I ran into Rebecca earlier.
She apologized.
- Wanted to get back together.
- And ?
I said no.
I mean, are you kidding ?
You know you still like her.
Why don't you give her another chance ?
Because then if I get burned again,
I'm the fool.
No thank you.
See, Cal, you're too nice.
Guys. What the hell ?
Is that the guy from the house ?
And isn't that your little
KT buddy paying him ?
Are you buying some guns ?
Who ?
What ?
That guy ?
I've never seen that guy before.
You hired that guy to kick us
out of that beach house.
Joke's over.
You got me.
I must be going now.
No problems.
So, if that wasn't his house,
who's staying there now ?
- Nobody ?
- Nobody ? All right.
Then we're taking back our house.
All right ! Everybody listen up !
We
should toast the Omega Chis
for making this spring break memorable.
Cheers !
We said you could invite
one friend from school.
Cap, I'm sorry,
they caught me paying off Roy.
Listen, we're taking back this house.
We won it fair and square. So get out.
We're not leaving, Chambers.
You lied to me.
You got three of our brothers expelled.
Leave us the house,
- we'll call it even.
- No way.
If you want us gone,
then you're going to have to kill us.
"Kill" ?
What am I walking into here, boys ?
Officer.
Everything's fine.
We're gonna turn the music down.
And... these guys
were just leaving.
Who's house is this ?
It's ours.
It's theirs.
You heard the man.
We were just leaving.
Come on, KTs ! Let's go !
Cheese and crackers !
Is this your donkey, too ?
No, we've never seen that before.
What else here isn't yours ?
Who ordered the fat,
ugly strippers ?
What happened to the party ?
- That's not ours either.
- Have you been drinking ?
How old are you, son ?
I am 21, you jackass.
I got a card to prove it.
And that's
Senor Domingo to you, jefe.
Yeah, that's right.
You just look so young, Francis.
Let's get you outta here.
I'm shutting this party down !
Everyone go home !
Except for you guys. It's your place.
I need to see your IDs.
Officer, listen...
The fact is we just arrived.
Any illegal activity
has nothing to do with us.
And we're in a fraternity.
If we get in any trouble like this,
we could lose our charter.
Should've thought of that before
you involved that innocent donkey.
All right, Cap.
Come on, man, we could lose
our house. For real.
Well, that's not
what we intended but...
Seems fitting, don't you think ?
- Are you okay ?
- What ?
- Yeah. Hi.
- Do you want some company ?
Why not ?
I guess I've already lost...
Faith ?
Faith Flowers !
It's me ! Ash...
Taylor.
- Ashed Aylor ? What a delicious name.
- Thank you !
You can call me Ashleigh for short.
I just wanted to say
I'm really sorry
about the whole porn thing.
- What are you talking about ?
- I'm the...
someone you don't know.
But you should.
I'm graduating from CRU in a month.
I've interview for jobs ranging
from the assistant to the regional
manager of blah, blah to the junior exec
to the head of "Who Cares".
I don't love any of that.
So I just started to accept
that I was gonna get a job
I didn't love because that's
what people do. Until I met you.
Look at this dress. I made it out
of a couple of really old T-shirts
and dresses I had, because,
one, I'm in college and poor,
and two, I didn't want to throw them out
and have them sit in a landfill.
So, deconstructed fashion.
It's totally on the rise
because of the economy,
because of how green everyone's getting.
And I love realizing that.
I love being able
to imagine what the next thing will be,
not just in fashion, but in everything.
And the idea of being able to do that,
what I love, and get paid ?
That probably has to be the most
amazing thing anyone can do.
What I'm trying to say,
Fairy Job Mother, is that I love you.
I beg your pardon ?
I mean, I love what you do.
And I would love to do what you do.
Or learn from you.
Or get you coffee
or whatever.
What do you say ?
Did you guys witness
any activity with the donkey ?
Do something, Chambers.
They're going to shut our house down.
What do you expect me to do ?
They caught us with a freaking donkey.
Some president.
- Officer ?
- Trip, why don't you let it alone ?
At least he's doing something.
Officer Nixon,
we'd be happy to make a sizable
donation to your department
if you were to look the other
way on this whole thing.
Bribery, too ?
Against the wall, Big Red !
You boys are screwed.
Officer Nixon ?
Hi. Can we talk in private ?
I hope he doesn't screw this up.
After Trip, it can't get much worse.
We're going to lose our charter,
aren't we ?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
All right, guys. We're good here.
Let's go get some pancakes.
- What the hell did you do ?
- I handled it.
So let's get our stuff back in here
and resume our spring break !
Dude, you got my vote.
Way to go, little bro.
Maybe you do have what it takes
to become president of OC.
- Well, I learned from the best.
- Thanks, man.
You've shown me how incredibly loyal
and generous someone can be.
But you've also shown me how pride
can... really threaten
to ruin a guy.
It's not your family or your money.
It's your pride.
You're gonna lose
Rebecca because of that.
What you doing ?
I am
just getting ready for my surprise
birthday party. How about you ?
Did Abby tell you ?
It's a sorority, Ash. Not the CIA.
Good, because I have a secret
that I can't keep !
I... got a job !
It's not a job-job, more of
an unpaid internship with this woman,
Faith Flowers.
She's a trend forecaster.
- What ? That's perfect for you.
- I know !
I'm going to New York !
My God !
It's really happening.
Aren't you a little freaked out ?
No. I'm ready.
Case, when I started CRU,
I thought I'd just get a degree,
maybe get married.
I never...
really thought
I wanted that much for myself.
But...
then I met you, and because of you
and because of our friendship...
I've come to want more for myself
than I ever could've imagined.
You always go after what you want,
and I'll never forget that.
You're my best friend
and you always will be.
Even if I'm in New York
and you stay in Cyprus.
Wait, you knew ?
Yeah, it's a sorority. Not the CIA.
Maybe I'm not as strong
as you think I am.
Yes, you are.
Maybe you've just taken a vacation
from yourself.
Spinning !
Stop the spinning !
I'm so sorry. This is not
what I wanted it to be for us.
It's OK. We can save money
back in Cyprus.
Just say sex.
Good lord,
I'm from the South, not France.
Where were you all day ?
This is your fault !
You're like weed.
You're my gateway.
My fault ?
I didn't get you wasted.
Why'd you want to come here ?
Well, not for the sand.
I wanted a girl.
And not a landlady.
Or some sorority girl
that's too insecure to stick by me.
I wanted to have a real college
experience like you did.
And have fun.
Because I only got two years
left to do it.
Should we go get him some coffee,
or something ?
You look like Aliens vs. Predator,
but all in one human form.
I need you.
I need you, Casey.
What's up ?
I got into law school in Washington.
That's great !
It's not, because I'm not going.
I now see why Cappie doesn't want
to graduate.
What if I'm not ready ?
What if I fail ?
You're ready.
There are bigger things
out there for you now.
I'll be alone.
Remember when I first came to CRU,
I was terrified.
I was lonely.
I didn't have a world.
But if I had never came here,
I never would've joined
a fraternity.
Met Cappie and all those guys.
Calvin and Dale.
I never would've had the relationship
that I have with you now.
Now I have a whole universe.
- Did you ever read Peter Pan ?
- No.
See ?
I've never even read Peter Pan !
I have no business leaving school.
I have to stay.
The first line of Peter Pan is
"All children, except one, grow up."
Wendy knew that at two years old.
You're learning it at 22.
Everyone has to grow up.
Nobody's Peter Pan.
Not even Cappie.
Dale just threw up.
This is my sister, Casey.
I didn't know you have a sister.
My God, you should've seen your face !
You were so surprised.
Yes, I was. Thanks, Abby.
There are a lot of really
cute guys here.
You're still on vacation.
Not sure my vacation worked out.
So I'm calling it a night.
Despite Dale's vomit,
I'm really enjoying Myrtle Beach.
Here comes Calvin. No fighting.
We need some BattleBots or something.
So ?
Phase four is complete.
Even Trip said he'd vote for me.
Then may Congratulate
the future president of Omega Chi.
- What ?
- As president, I think
my first order of business
will be to declare a truce
- between Kappa Tau and Omega Chi.
- Wait, what ? It was all a joke ?
A series of phases, to be exact,
concocted by our Revenge Chair.
The entire plot was brought to you
by the brotherhood of Kappa Tau.
The mob guy was actually
Brother Rubik's Cube,
Class of '85.
The Myrtle Beach cops were Brothers Pez,
Paisley, Tricky Dick and Disco Dan.
All KT Brothers from the University
of South Carolina, class of '79.
Brothers for life.
What you gonna do now
that you don't have OC to kick around ?
Enjoy life ?
I saw Lambda Sig looking at me
funny last week.
I didn't care for that.
I'm go get to the bottom of it.
- How about we go on that walk now ?
- Okay. Yeah.
Rebecca ! Wait, wait, listen !
I'm...
You're what ?
I'm not the good guy.
I don't always do the right thing
all the time.
And I'm always blaming my parents
or the money.
But the only person to blame
is myself.
I let my pride get in the way
I don't want to lose you.
You can forget what a mess I am ?
You cheated on me
because you don't believe you
deserve happiness, but you do.
I do.
And we can find that together.
I'd like to try.
So, I've been...
waiting for the perfect moment
to give you something, and...
I think now's as good a time as any.
What is it ?
I want you to wear my lavaliere.
I love you, Casey.
I love you, too.
You're not as excited as I thought you'd
be. Is it because of where it's been ?
What ?
No, it's just...
I didn't bungee jump today
because I was scared.
And if I stay in Cyprus,
I'd be staying because I'm scared.
You're going to Washington,
aren't you ?
I have to do what's best for me,
and that's law school.
Don't you want me to go
and succeed ?
I do.
I guess I'm being selfish because
I know that means I'm gonna lose you.
Cap, you can come with me !
To Washington ! You could transfer...
I'm not sure I can leave.
And I can't stay.
But, I totally understand
why you're scared to go.
I'm not scared.
That's okay.
Leaving something can be terrifying.
Is that what you're doing ?
Are you leaving me behind ?
- I want us to move forward, together !
- I don't want to move forward !
- Because you don't want to grow up.
- What other choice do we have ?
We are two different people
who love each other very much.
It seems like the only place
where our differences
don't matter is in college.
Maybe this is just one
of those college relationships ?
If it is, it's the best one...
of all time.
Look, let's just
finish the year out together, and...
No, screw it.
You know what ? Why wait ?
If you don't have more faith in us
than that ? Then we should break up now.
- No, I don't want to.
- Too late. It's done. All right ?
I can't believe I was gonna
give this to you tonight.
I would've felt pretty college
doing something like that.
Cappie, please...
Merci d'avoir suivi cette saison
avec la Kappa Team.