Subtitles:
Breys, Tyno
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
We interrupt our scheduled programming
to bring you breaking news.
Good afternoon.
In the last several minutes,
KOB has received dozens of reports
of what appears to be
a crashed aircraft,
possibly two aircraft...
on Albuquerque's east side.
As of yet, details are scarce,
but callers describe witnessing
an explosion overhead,
followed by falling debris.
... crash investigators with
the National Transportation Safety Board
are expected
on-site as early as this evening.
But officials warn that,
with a debris field of this magnitude,
the investigation
and the clean-up may well stretch...
... the Boeing 737
was being re-routed or vectored
through the airspace,
which is standard procedure,
according to a spokesman
for the FAA.
The eight-seat King Air 350
was a charter flight operating
out of Saint George, Utah,
bound for Amarillo, Texas.
It sounded like hail.
Like heavy hailstones.
It was just...
bump-bump-bump
all over the neighborhood.
... indicating that the final
death toll now stands at 167.
... 167.
This mid-air collision
has left many wondering
how such an accident
could take place
in a system with so many safeguards.
Allegations continue that the collision
which brought down Flight 515
was caused by improper
air traffic control.
The bombshell confirmation
out of Oklahoma City today,
as the FAA confirmed,
it was, indeed,
a lone air traffic controller's
fateful mistake...
... is Donald Margolis,
a 19-year veteran of the FAA's
Air Route Traffic Control Center
in Albuquerque.
... Margolis recently
returned to work
after a five-week absence,
which was due to,
quote, "a personal loss".
While it's now known
that Margolis had recently
lost a daughter...
... to a drug overdose
a month before.
His troubled daughter
Jane Margolis, aged 26,
apparently had a long history
of substance abuse.
Friends of the family say
the death of his only child
hit Margolis particularly hard.
Coming as it did little more
than a month before,
many are questioning
the timing of his return to work,
and are wondering
how much blame truly lies
with those who let
this grieving father...
I usually open
with "So sorry you're here."
Where would you like to begin?
I really just need this
quick and easy, you know?
As quick as...
something like this can be.
Is that mutual?
Does your husband go along with that?
Does he know?
I mean, he certainly knows
we're separated, so...
Has he moved out?
We're in the process of moving him out.
Yeah. Today, hopefully.
And in the meantime, my...
my son and my daughter
and I are staying with my sister.
So you've moved out?
Yes, just temporarily,
only so he could get his things.
That was supposed
to happen last week,
but then came the crash, and...
- God. You weren't one of the...
- Right...
Right beneath the flight path.
We had debris land in our yard
- and all of our neighborhood, so...
- Terrible.
Apparently, even...
you know,
parts of bodies, and so...
I certainly
couldn't bring myself to...
- So awful.
- I know.
Anyway, I was certainly
not ready to move back,
but it's time.
And...
I'm sure we're driving my sister
and her husband up a wall.
You definitely want
to maintain residency
in your actual home.
It just puts you in a better position
in regards to custody.
Two children?
Holly here, and then I have a son
in high school...
Walter Junior.
They need to stay with me.
- How long have you been married?
- Sixteen years.
And it's not an apartment.
It's a house that you live in?
Do you own outright?
Do you have a mortgage?
There's definitely a mortgage.
We have...
maybe 15 years on it.
What about other debts
or assets?
Do you feel
you have a good understanding
of you and your husband's
financial situation?
- Is your husband employed?
- Here's the thing.
I'm really not looking
for any, sort of...
loopholes or...
- I don't know... just...
- No.
No loopholes.
I just intend
that every one of my clients
get a full and honest accounting
of what it is they owe
and what it is they own.
To that end, I say
let's leave no stone unturned.
You'd be amazed what I've seen
partners hide from one another.
There you are.
Listen, I...
You know, well...
It's...
It's time.
The shittiest week since 9/11, okay?
Bar none. Yeah, this is it.
Hands down, we're living it.
I speak with some authority
because we had some shitty weeks
in the past few months.
But this here, call, you know...
call freakin' the Guinness
Book of World Records...
Call freakin'...
Am I talking too much?
I am, right? I am.
I know. Look.
But this situation
between you and...
I'm not asking, by the way.
It's none of my business.
I do not want to get in the middle.
I'm just saying...
Listen, okay?
You beat a little tactical retreat.
And regroup.
And then... bong.
Absence makes the...
I'm pulling for you.
- No heavy lifting. I got it.
- No, it's okay.
I got it.
Jesus.
What do you got in there,
cinder blocks?
Half a million in cash.
That's the spirit.
I got it. I got it.
Who's here for self-improvement?
Come on, give me a show of hands.
Who among you is here hoping
they can actively
improve who they are?
Right.
See, that's your first mistake.
You should be here
to learn self-acceptance.
Honey, you...
You want another waffle?
I still got the iron out.
I could cut up some bananas.
Hi, you're reached Walt,
Skyler, Flynn, and Holly.
Please leave us a message.
Hey. Hello, everybody.
Good morning.
I was just checking in
and thought I'd pass along
the current contact information.
I mean, certainly,
you can always reach me on my cell.
I've always got that on me.
But in terms of...
a mailing address,
I'm here at The Beachcomber.
And you know what?
It's actually very nice.
It's very pleasant.
Not as high end as the Oakwood,
but, you know, not as corporate...
Would you please just...
Hey, Dad. It's me.
No, I'm not okay.
I don't know
what the hell is going on.
Nobody's telling me jack shit.
Flynn.
Whatever.
I don't even care anymore.
Can you just give me
a ride to school?
I'll take you to school.
Yeah. No.
I'm ready now.
Flynn, I'm taking you to school.
All right. I'm here.
See you soon.
May I have your attention, please?
As all of you know,
last week our city suffered
a terrible tragedy,
one that none of us
will ever forget,
which is why today
we're going to take a little time
out of our schedule
to gather in the gym and talk.
I just find it,
you know, really...
really hard to concentrate
because of all the horrors,
you know, we perceived.
It just really gets
inside your brain, and...
In college they have
this thing where,
if your roommate kills himself...
like, if you come home
and find him hanging
in the closet or whatever...
it's basically, like,
an automatic "A"
for you.
And I just think that
that kind of compassion is...
- Okay.
- is something to...
Thank you, Barry.
Who wants to go next?
No judgments, guys.
Just feelings.
You can say anything and everything
that's on your mind.
Anyone?
There you go, honey.
I just keep asking myself...
Honey, could you please stand up?
Just keep asking myself,
"Why did this happen?"
I mean, if there's a God and all,
why does he allow all those innocent
people to die for no reason?
Can we just keep it secular, honey?
Anyhow, I haven't really
been sleeping much.
Does anyone else have that?
I just keep hearing that...
that sound.
That... boom.
It just plays over
and over in my head
like it won't ever stop.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Is there anyone else?
Over here.
My neighbor,
he heard the crash,
and he ran outside,
and he found, like, this seat...
like an airline seat.
Like one you have on an airliner?
Anyway, the seat was standing
perfectly upright in his front yard,
right next to his Sea-Doos...
because, like,
he has Sea-Doos... But...
there was still a pair of legs
buckled into them.
Human legs.
Jesus H. Christ.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Sorry.
I was just moved.
Maybe we should hear
from the faculty.
Certainly this tragedy
didn't only affect our students.
Mr. White, would you
like to say something?
And by the way,
welcome back.
It's so good to have you back.
I guess what I would...
Sorry. Sorry.
I guess what I would
want to say is...
to look on the bright side.
First of all, nobody
on the ground was killed.
And that...
An incident like this
over a populated urban center...
That right there,
that's just gotta be
some minor miracle, so...
Plus...
neither plane was full.
You know, the 737 was...
Was what? Maybe two-thirds full,
I believe. Right? Yes?
Or maybe even three-quarters full.
At any rate,
what you're left with
casualty-wise is
just the 50th worst air disaster.
Actually, tied for 50th.
There are, in truth,
fifty-three
crashes throughout history
that are just as bad
or worse...
Tenerife?
Has anybody hear of Tenerife?
In 1977,
two fully loaded 747s
crashed into each other on Tenerife.
Does anybody know how big a 747 is?
It's way bigger than a 737.
And we're talking about two of them.
Nearly 600 people died
on Tenerife.
Doesn't any of you
even remember it at all?
Any of you? I doubt it.
You know why?
It's because...
people move on.
They just move on.
And we will, too. We will move on,
and we will get past this
because that is
what human beings do.
We survive.
And...
We survive, and we...
We overcome.
We survive.
We survive, and...
Thank you.
Good.
How's your Aunt Marie doing?
Fine,
I guess.
You make sure you say hello
to her for me, will you?
Why don't you just come inside?
It's your house.
No, I...
He's gone.
Hey, Flynn!
- How's tricks?
- What?
Tricks.
It's an expression.
How are you?
Why do you gotta
treat him like this?
Why you gotta be like this?
Why can't you just talk, even?
Cool down.
Out of the mouths of babes.
Try not to hold it against him.
I mean,
the poor kid, he's probably just
dying of curiosity.
And I guess it would be natural
for him to wonder.
He's probably just wondering
what is it that could
have gone so wrong...
- Marie.
- ... that my mother would leave...
I can't help you get
through this, Skyler,
you know, if you won't tell me
what it is that Walt did.
You know what?
I don't remember
asking you, all right?
So if you want to be supportive,
you could be supportive without prying,
that would be really great...
and so...
helpful.
It's that...
voice inside your head.
It's that sneaky,
rat-bastard, 24/7 voice.
You guys know what I'm talking about.
It tells you you're not good enough.
Not good enough for what?
Not good enough to...
be what,
President of the United States?
Okay, so maybe you're not that good.
But now,
are you good enough
to deserve your share
of basic human happiness?
Are you good enough to be okay
with who and what you are?
I say yes.
But it doesn't matter what I say.
It's your voice, which means
you're the only one that hears it,
which means that you're
the only one that can fight it.
Right?
Jesse...
we never hear from you.
What's going on?
You can tell me I'm full of shit.
It's okay. I don't mind.
Just... Come on.
Let us in on it.
So, like,
what makes you the expert?
I don't think
I ever said I was that.
Yeah, but you're the one
sitting here, right?
Telling us thus and so,
be happy, forgive yourself,
Have you ever really hurt anybody?
I don't just mean disappointed
your mother or whatever,
but did you...
ever really...
hurt someone?
I killed my daughter.
It was July 18th...
which is my birthday.
July 18th,
1992.
I was...
high on cocaine, and I was drunk.
Cocaine wasn't an issue
because I had bought myself 2 grams
the night before as a birthday present.
I had plenty left.
But I was out of vodka.
And this is in Portsmouth, Virginia,
where instead of selling
liquor in the supermarkets,
they have these ABC stores
which close at 5 p.m.
And right then it was, like, 4:42.
So I'm arguing with my wife...
"Come on, go to the ABC for me.
"It's my birthday.
"Come on.
"They're not gonna sell it to me."
She's saying, "No, no."
So I'm pissed,
and the clock is ticking,
so I jump in my truck.
She's...
my 6-year-old daughter...
She's playing at the end
of the driveway.
How do you not hate yourself?
I did hate myself...
for a long time.
But it didn't stop me from...
drinking and getting high.
It just made it that much worse.
Self-hatred, guilt,
it accomplishes nothing.
It just stands in the way.
Stands in the way of what?
True change.
Is this a good time to talk?
Yeah. Come in, please.
Do you want to start?
Why are you doing this?
Why are you even thinking this way?
Is it to punish me?
- I am not punishing you, Walt.
- This is punitive
is what this is.
We are happily married.
I am happily married.
I am happy.
We're just...
I love you,
and I would do anything for you.
Would you even consider...
I mean, Jesus!
You come in here,
and you wave these papers in my face,
when there's a whole other
entire side to this thing.
There's your side,
and there's my side.
And you haven't heard my side yet.
- You haven't heard any of it at all.
- You're a drug dealer.
How else could you possibly
make that kind of money?
Marijuana.
That Pinkman kid.
Cocaine?
It's methamphetamine.
But I'm...
I manufacture.
I am not a dealer.
Per se.
It doesn't mean...
No, Skyler.
Listen to me.
There are a lot of angles to this, okay?
It's complicated.
All right?
So please, let's... Please,
let's just sit back down,
and we'll talk it through.
I'm gonna make you a deal, Walt.
I won't tell Hank,
and I won't tell your children
or anybody else.
Nobody will hear it from me,
but only
if you grant me this divorce
and stay out of our lives.
I mean it.
Now let me out of here
before I throw up.
Your windshield's broken.
Yep.
A little friction
in the marriage right now.
Strictly temporary.
We're just...
just taking a little break.
That's you over there.
Listen,
money.
Saul has got it for you,
- so as soon as you're feeling better...
- I'm better.
You're better.
Really?
What? The rehab?
It helped?
Yeah.
I'm done using.
That's excellent. That's...
That's very good, Jesse.
Boy...
Very good.
You know, um...
in spite of how bad things got,
it really could be looked at
like a wake-up call for both of us.
You know, just to get our...
our lives back together again
and on the straight and narrow.
You been following
this airplane crash?
Yeah.
You know it was
Jane's dad who accidentally
crashed them together?
Because he was so torn up?
Let me stop you
right there, all right?
You are not responsible for this...
not in any way, shape,
or form, all right?
Now, I am very up-to-date
on this thing,
probably far more than you are,
and there are... there are...
many factors at play there.
Yeah?
For instance,
there's some sort of collision radar
on the jet that may not
have been working properly.
That's public record.
You can look that up.
And the whole system is run on...
on 1960s technology.
No.
No, really...
I blame the government.
You either run from things,
or you face them, Mr. White.
And what exactly does that mean?
I learned it in rehab.
It's all about accepting
who you really are.
I accept who I am.
And who are you?
I'm the bad guy.
Is the food to your satisfaction?
Very much.
It's good to see you again.
May I?
I have an offer that I think
will be of interest to you.
I actually...
am not here to...
I'm here
because I owe you
the courtesy and respect
to tell you this personally.
I'm done.
It has nothing to do
with you personally.
I find you extraordinarily
professional,
and I appreciate
the way you do business.
I'm just...
making a change in my life
is what it is, and I'm...
I'm at some...
something of a crossroads.
It has...
brought me to a realization.
I am not a criminal.
No offense to any people who are.
But...
this is not me.
I'd like you to hear my offer,
notwithstanding.
It won't change my mind.
I'm sorry.
$3 million
for three months of your time.
Three months,
then out.
3 million?
May I take this as a yes?
I have money.
I have more money
than I know how to spend.
What I don't have is my family.
The answer is still no.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
What the hell is going on?