Previously on Breaking Bad...
If you're gonna launder the money,
at least do it right.
- Be my guest.
- You sure?
I can cook, I can watch.
We're looking for someone trustworthy.
Who knows about laundering.
What about me?
I know I owe you my life.
They got Tomás slinging,
then, they made him kill somebody.
Are you Tomás?
- Yeah. What you want?
- Crystal.
Hey, guys.
Subtitles:
Michvanilly
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
So if it's okay, I was thinking
about using this one for the test.
Mom's brakes are very sticky...
and you barely press down on them,
and it's like a screech.
Sure.
But I'm good?
Yeah, you're great.
Why?
Are my feet okay?
I looked it up.
New Mexico says all I need
is a note from a doctor.
I mean, I know it's
not the right way and all,
but once I get my provisional,
I can keep working at it.
As long as it gets you
safely from point A to point B,
then who am I to argue?
Hi.
You're a sweet girl.
Yes, you are.
I know.
There you go.
Here you go.
All right.
Thank you.
Got it?
Okay. All right.
So...
9 a.m. Saturday?
9 a.m. Saturday.
So, which means pick me up
about 8:30.
I'll be here with bells on.
What?
Just a saying.
Don't worry.
I won't be wearing bells.
Hey, Mom.
Hi. Do you have a minute?
- Could you keep an eye on your sister?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
- See you, Dad.
- Bye, son. Good work today.
- Thank you.
Have you thought anymore
about about what we discussed?
"Thought any more,"
meaning reconsidered?
So show me the flaw in it.
"Flaws," Skyler.
"Flaws," plural, not singular.
Where do you want me to start?
I don't love
this situation, all right,
that you put me in.
However, let's just stick
with what makes sense here.
You took the seed money.
You went gambling.
You invested it in the car wash
that you helped run for four years.
You hired your wife as a bookkeeper.
Because guess what?
She's actually a bookkeeper.
Now, that is a story an auditor can
believe, so what am I missing?
You're missing that you should just
take this money that I give you
and not look too closely at it,
so
if, God forbid, I get caught,
you maintain plausible deniability.
Okay, my estranged husband
who, when he was working,
made $43,000 a year,
starts shoveling money at me,
and when the police come,
I'm supposed to say, "Gee,
"I never thought about it, Officers.
Made sense to me."
Really?
That, in your mind,
is plausible deniability?
I'll tell you what, Walt.
I'd rather have them think
I'm Bonnie what's-her-name
than some complete idiot.
So you're
promoting caution here.
And you want a believable story.
That, it seems to me,
is the safest way to make the best
out of a very bad situation, yes.
But I'm noting
a little hole in your plot, though.
Why would your estranged husband
be doing all this for you?
Because he loves his family
and desperately wants
a reconciliation,
though it may be
hopeless and futile.
Then again,
he'd try anything.
I'm just not buying it.
No, I think it would be better
if the husband were
no longer estranged.
You know, maybe if he were back
sleeping in his own bed.
It's suddenly a fantasy story.
I am at least going to be
a part of this household.
Dinner with the family
every night of the week.
Not every night, no.
Six nights a week.
You'll get one night off.
Dinner two nights, not weekends,
with 24-hours' notice.
Five nights a week with no notice.
Three, six-hours' notice.
Five nights a week
with two hours' notice.
Four.
Don't push it.
And I want my own key to the house.
For emergencies
and appearances, yes.
I am going to babysit
my own daughter.
I'll help my son with his homework.
I am going to be
a part of this family,
and that is how we'll sell
your little fiction.
How about we stop somewhere
afterward and get a beer?
No. Thanks, though.
Maybe some other time.
No, seriously.
Get a beer with me.
What?
What the hell are you doing?
That's ours, right?
Look at it and tell me
if that's ours.
Yes, it's ours.
Now put it away.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Where did you get that?
Did you take it from the lab?
I bought it from the two guys
who killed Combo.
They had Combo shot down
in the street,
and now it's our product
they're selling.
Which means they work
for our guy. Right?
What is that?
That's hearsay.
- Do you have any proof?
- I heard it from the sister of the kid
who shot him.
Hear how I just said "kid"?
This kid...
he's 11 years old...
shot Combo on orders.
These two scumbags,
they got him dealing.
They got him...
And you know he's not the first.
They use kids 'cause, hey, why not?
Easy to control, easy to fool.
All they get is juvie
if they ever get caught.
Hearts and minds, right?
Get them young,
and they're yours forever.
These guys killed Combo.
They used this little kid
like some puppet.
They used him to shoot my friend.
So why are you telling me this?
I need your help.
How?
I need ricin.
My God.
God.
These two...
They got to go.
All right?
I've got the entire
thing figured out...
a delivery method, everything.
All I need from you
is the poison, that's all.
Look,
otherwise, you don't have to...
lift a finger.
Listen, you don't even know
what you're talking about.
Look, you
don't get how right this is?
You don't get how the whole
entire world
- would be better off...
- We're not even talking about this.
I know a woman
who buys from the
these two once or twice a week.
She brings them hamburgers 'cause
they sit in their car all day,
and they get hungry,
so she brings them food,
and they knock
a few bucks off her price.
There's your delivery system
right there.
- I can be a mile away.
- Jesus.
A meth-head
you're trusting to do this?
You know what? That meth-head
stood up to your brother-in-law.
All right?
He questioned her for five hours.
She didn't give it up.
You know how it is you know?
Because you're not
in prison right now.
I know I would be
in prison after this.
Prison or worse, and I'd
be right alongside you.
You cannot be serious.
Listen, this is a ridiculous idea.
It's ridiculous?
What, so you're saying
it's not going to work?
How about back
when it was your plan?
Back when you were
going to use it on Tuco?
Apples and oranges.
Guy eats ricin. Two or three days later,
he gets the flu
or a heart attack or something,
and he keels over.
That's what you said.
Untraceable back to us.
To me.
Not even that other scumbag we work for
is ever going to figure it out.
It was a good plan
back when it was Tuco,
and it's a good plan now.
Tuco wanted to murder us.
These guys don't.
Apples and oranges.
Do I really have to sit here
and explain the difference to you?
Combo
was us,
man.
He was one of us.
Does that mean nothing?
Why didn't you go after these guys
- two or three months ago?
- Because I just found out about them.
What's to find out?
It's a dispute over turf, right?
how hard could it have been
for you to track them down
on their turf
and kill them months ago?
Because back then
you were too busy getting high,
feeling sorry.
Now,
murder...
is not part of your 12-step program.
This is not some amends
that you have to make.
What you are talking
about here is pointless.
This achieves nothing.
It accomplishes nothing.
If you don't see
what it accomplishes,
then there's no way
I can explain it to you.
Jesse, listen to me.
You are not a murderer.
I'm not, and you're not.
It's as simple as that.
I'm doing it...
with or without you.
Knock, knock.
Christ sakes, Marie,
you don't say "knock, knock." You...
- Like that.
- Well, I like saying it.
That's not the rules.
Listen, you knock your way, Groucho.
I'll knock mine.
But, look, see?
I win.
Not so fast.
Christ, again?
That's three in a row.
Frickin' Paul Newman over here?
Do you play cards with your dad?{\Have you been playing cards
with your dad?}
No, why?
How is your old man?
- He back teaching?
- No,
I don't think either
of them are working right...
right now.
How they swinging that?
Did you know
that the doctor has told your Uncle
Hank that he can get out of here
- any time he wants to.
- Yeah?
That's great.
Yeah, well,
we're not so sure about that.
Why not?
What? That's what they said.
That's what they said
because they want the room.
They hit the sheets with Lysol,
re-set the meter,
and wheel the next slob in here.
We went over this.
Drop it.
Are you not well enough?
Jesus, kid, you, too?
Do I look well enough?
I'm shitting in pants,
peeing in pitchers.
Can't move my legs.
Got it?
So people in wheelchairs
should be in hospitals?
What about people on crutches?
Maybe I should be in here, too.
- Is that what you're trying to say?
- Yeah, that's exactly what I'm saying.
Deal, you little prick.
Bitch.
You know I'm hourly, right?
He promised me he'd be here.
Oh, he promised, huh?
Well, why didn't you tell me?
Let's wait, then.
That's a joke.
The kid ain't coming.
Okay, so what's Plan B?
I don't know.
I really don't.
Well, let's brainstorm.
- You really think he's serious?
- That's why I'm here, Saul.
The way he was talking,
he is going to do it.
Or try, at least.
Okay, so, what, we pay him off.
No. No, it's not about money.
It's about getting him
off the streets,
getting him to calm down.
Maybe...
What if we...
maybe...
Could you get him arrested?
You want your criminal associate
taken into police custody?
No, now, listen.
I know it sounds risky,
but it wouldn't be anything
that would get him into real trouble
and nothing that could lead
back to our business.
Just some minor offense.
Pinkman in jail... I don't know.
- I'm picturing it and...
- No, not in jail
as in...
"jail" jail.
I'm talking about one of those
situations where you're
in an orange jumpsuit
picking up litter along the highway.
That's jail.
You're talking
about a level-two joint.
Something that keeps him off
the street for, say,
30 days.
Then by the time he gets out,
tempers have cooled
and hopefully we can move on.
Roswell Correctional's
pretty low impact.
In the past
I've recommended Springer, but
hearing chancy things
about their bathrooms
since they renovated,
so...
So it's possible, right?
It falls under
my premium-services package,
but you can afford that.
I'll call my P.I.
You understand what you have to do?
You can
never talk to anyone.
Right?
I mean, ever.
Understand?
Yeah.
I found this stuff on the Internet.
Takes days to kick in.
Just keep quiet,
and this won't ever come back to you.
You're okay with this, right?
Just think of it like
it's the same thing as always.
You're just delivering
some hamburgers.
It's not just delivering hamburgers.
You got a kid.
Right?
What's his name?
Patrick.
Imagine these two guys
and Patrick working as a mule,
making him kill people.
Wouldn't you do anything
to protect your kid?
Of course I would.
I do all kinds of things for him.
Okay, so...
these guys using kids like that,
they got to go.
Right?
Good.
Tomorrow.
I'll be in touch.
Bet that tastes good, huh?
Come here.
Here we go.
What are you doing?
If you need to talk, use the phone.
This isn't a phone talk, Walter.
Your wife's out, right?
Isn't she something?
I got a granddaughter
a few years older.
What can I do for you?
Have a seat, Walter.
I spoke to Goodman about Pinkman
and this plan of yours.
- And?
- I'm not going to do it.
Why?
Because it's moronic.
Saul said you've done things
like this before.
That's not the moronic part.
Okay, so what's the problem?
The problem is
the boss wouldn't like it.
Saul?
My boss.
Your boss.
This is a professional courtesy.
No one knows I'm here.
Understand?
But our employer would
find out, like always,
and if Pinkman were arrested,
he'd take it as a problem.
You got a good thing going here.
We all do.
You want to risk it all
on one junkie?
Now, I realize you two
have a history,
but this kid's been
on the bubble a while now.
It's a long time coming.
What is?
I used to be a beat cop,
long time ago,
and I'd get called out on
domestic disputes all the time.
Hundreds, probably, over the years.
But there was this one guy, this one
piece of shit that I will never forget.
Gordie.
He looked like Bo Svenson.
You remember him?
Walking Tall?
You don't remember?
Anyway...
big boy...
270, 280,
but his wife...
or whatever she was... his lady
was real small,
like a bird,
wrists like little branches.
Anyway, my partner and I get
called out there every weekend,
and one of us would pull her
aside and we'd say,
"Come on, tonight's the night
we press charges."
And this wasn't one of those "deep
down he really loves me" set-ups.
We got a lot of those, but not this.
This girl was scared.
She wasn't going to cross him
no way, no how.
Nothing we could do
but pass her off to the Emts,
put him in the car,
drive him downtown,
throw him in the drunk tank.
He sleeps it off.
Next morning, out he goes...
back home.
But one night
my partner's out sick,
and it's just me.
And the call comes in,
and it's the usual crap...
broken-nose-in-the-shower
kind of thing.
So I cuff him, put him in the car,
and away we go.
Only that night...
we're driving into town,
and this sideways asshole
is in my back seat
humming "Danny Boy."
And it just rubbed me wrong.
So instead of left,
I go right, out into nowhere.
And I kneel him down,
and I put my revolver in his mouth,
and I told him,
"This is it.
This is how it ends."
And he's crying,
going to the bathroom all over himself,
swearing to God
he's going to leave her alone,
screaming...
as much as you can
with a gun in your mouth.
And I told him to be quiet...
'cause I need to think about
what I was gong to do here.
And of course he got quiet.
Goes still.
And real quiet.
Like a dog waiting
for dinner scraps.
Then we just stood there
for a while.
Me acting
like I'm thinking things over,
and Prince Charming
kneeling in the dirt
with shit in his pants.
And after a few minutes I took
the gun out of his mouth,
and I say, "So help me,
if you ever touch her again,
"I will such and such
and such and such
and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah."
Just a warning?
Of course.
Just trying to do the right thing.
But two weeks later he killed her.
Of course.
Caved her head in with the
base of a Waring blender.
We got there, there was so much
blood, you could taste the metal.
The moral of the story is...
I chose a half measure
when I should have gone all the way.
I'll never make that mistake again.
No more half measures, Walter.
Man, I don't get this.
I don't get this at all.
All I'm seeing is the kid.
So where are they?
I don't know.
They're always around.
Burgers are getting cold.
So is it, like, fast?
Don't sweat it, all right?
You're just doing what you do.
Nobody's going to know anything.
Can I have another bump?
You had your bump.
We get this thing done.
Then you can have all you want.
Going to need you to come with me.
Take a walk.
Where are we going?
Sit down.
I understand that you have a
problem with two of my employees.
It is true that they killed
one of your associates.
It is possible they acted rashly,
but, on the other hand,
there was provocation.
A man was selling
on their territory.
There is blame on both sides.
This will go no further.
It will be settled right here,
right now.
You told him.
Wait outside.
Listen to me.
You have one friend in this room.
This man.
Those men outside
are my trusted employees,
and when I learned
what you intended to do...
If it wasn't for this man
and the respect I have for him,
I would be dealing with this
in a very different way.
You don't look at him.
You look at me.
This is what happens now.
My men will come back inside,
and you will shake their hands
and you will make peace.
And that will be the end of this.
Pardon me?
They use kids.
These assholes of yours,
they got an 11-year-old kid
doing their killing for them.
You're supposed to be some kind
of reasonable businessman.
This how you do business?
You okay with this?
You got anything to say here?
Bring them back.
No more children.
Understand?
And you.
You keep the peace.
Say it.
I'll keep the peace.
Shake hands.
Jesse, your actions...
they affect other people.
And sometimes
compromises have to be made...
for the best of reasons.
Let the people who get
paid to do this, do this.
The people who get paid to
do this, do a lousy job.
So I guess this is
what you want, huh?
Just lying in a hospital bed,
getting sponge baths from nurses.
It's time to go home, Hank.
How many times I got to tell you?
Not till I'm well.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm just seeing.
Seeing what?
Seeing what I see.
I'm not at my best here, Marie.
We'll see.
Nothing's going to happen.
I say it will.
I'm in this bed for a reason.
It's a waste of time.
Besides, what if someone comes in?
Let them. I don't care.
What's wrong with you?
I'll tell you what.
If I can get the groundhog
to see his shadow...
- It's not going to happen. I'm sorry.
- I'm betting it will, and if he does,
you check out of here.
I'm not going to bet
on whether I get a boner.
It's not bet.
There's no bet here. No bet.
You afraid you'll lose?
You know what?
You're just...
You're just being foolish, you know?
Come on.
What's the point?
The point is...
you're not completely hopeless.
We have a bet?
You know what?
If it'll get you
out of here quicker,
- you got one minute.
- One minute?
All right.
That's a cakewalk.
Yeah, this is just...
It's just sad.
I mean...
I really feel sorry for
you, Marie, you know?
I really do.
It's just... It's...
pathetic.
That's okay.
Keep talking.
Protest.
Struggle.
Marie, give up.
I mean, seriously, it's...
not...
going to happen.
Bad day?
I don't even know.
Anyway,
it's better now.
Tell them you're busy.
Hello.
Grandma?
Slow down.
Slow down. I can't...
God.
Tomas!
You have to let me in!
Please!
Hey, it's me.
Wait for the thing.
You are now 42 minutes late.
I'm starting without you.
- What is wasabi?
- Wasabi. Right you are.
"Four-letter Word" for 1,200.
Pilots and musicians
know this word...
Dinner's almost ready, okay?
- What is "solo"?
- That's the word.
This guy is good.
- "Four-letter Word," 2,000.
- "A loud"...
harsh cry.
Walt Whitman's was "barbaric".
- Yell.
- What is "yawp"?
- Kevin.
- "Yawp."
- "Tokyo," 1,200.
What the heck's a "yawp"?
"Yawp" is a yell.
I'll be right back.
That's what I said.
Hey, it's me.
Wait for the thing.
Look, I hope you're not waiting
for an apology,
because I did not rat you out.
I was looking out for your best
interest as well as my own,
and I stand by my decision 100%,
so we'll just have to agree
to disagree.
Anyway, just call me back.
So the TV turns itself off?
I'll get it.
Where's the remote?
On the murder of a young boy
in the South Valley.
Police have yet to release
a statement,
but sources indicate
that 11-year-old Tomas Cantillo
may have been the victim
of a gang-related execution.
An anonymous tip brought police
to a playground
on the 4700 block
of 8th Avenue late last night.
Paramedics were called to the scene
but were unable to revive the boy.
A gruesome crime...
Can you turn that off?
And yet another casualty
in what appears to be
the city's ongoing struggle against
drugs and the gangs that peddle them.
We'll be passing along detail...
Give me your dad...
I'm sorry. It's just,
they've been talking about
that all day, and it's just...
Did you know your dad and I
are thinking about maybe
starting a business together?
Seriously?
- What kind of business?
- I don't know.
We're thinking maybe a car wash.
What do you mean?
Like...
I'm sorry.
I... I have to go.
Run.