Flight 2570, New York,
JFK, now boarding all rows.
Okay, well,
there you go, young lady.
Off into the wild blue yonder.
Great. Maybe I'll get lucky
and my plane will explode in mid-air.
I don't get it, Becks.
What could possibly be so awful
about visiting the woman who pushed you
through her magnificent vagina?
In New York.
In the fall, no less.
You're gonna be stepping off
that plane into a Woody Allen film.
And not recent Woody Allen,
old Woody Allen.
Annie Hall, Manhattan Woody Allen.
I'm pretty jealous right now.
Chelsea has Lakers tickets.
- So what? You hate basketball.
- You're missing the point.
It's a killer scene.
I know you're in there somewhere,
baby girl.
My sweet little partner in crime.
And you're having a good laugh about
this, even if it's only on the inside.
Have a nice trip.
Kiss mama bear for me.
I love you.
Stay.
Stay?
Stay. Stay.
Come on, turn around, just once.
Then I'll know you still love me.
God, send me a sign from on high.
Come on.
Oh, yeah,
that's what I'm talking about.
All right, well,
she's up, up and away.
I'm so excited. I can't wait
to squeeze that little peanut.
I wouldn't get too excited.
She hasn't been very pleasant lately.
Kind of a little shit, actually.
Hey, come on.
Don't poison the well.
I know we're gonna have a great time,
she and I. I can feel it.
Okus-dokus.
I'm just warning you,
something post-pubescent
and wicked your way comes.
- I wish you could come with.
- Yeah, me too.
- I'm not anticipating this W/E much.
- Come on, Hank.
- He's your best friend.
- Once upon a time, in long island.
He calls me up after many years
saying he's got something to tell me.
Whatever.
Just have fun, you know?
Call me when she lands. Give her a kiss
for me. Give yourself a kiss for me too.
- Talk to you later.
- Bye.
You handsome motherfucker. I just
have to have me a piece of that ass.
- Fuckin'...
- Wait, I'm not through.
Zloz, shit.
- What's up, buddy?
- Where'd that plane come from, 1987?
You look exactly the same.
And that smell.
What is that, booze, cigarettes,
and Drakkar Noir? Takes me right back.
Yeah, what about you? You look like
half a fag in this smoking jacket.
You smell pretty much the same...
Like a cock dipped in shit.
It's good to see you, man.
Yeah, it's been a long time.
Whose fault is that?
Who never comes back to the island?
Fuckin' fancy book writer Hank Moody,
that's who.
Well, you know,
they won't let me back.
I divulged too many
small town secrets.
Named too many names.
Well, here I finally am, man, in LA.
L-fuckin'-A.
Yeah, well, what's up? You sounded
pretty mysterious on the phone.
Yeah, later. Later for that, man.
There's a lot of time to shoot the shit.
First, I want to see
Britney's vertical smile.
I don't know if she's showing this week.
I'll have to check the schedule.
All right, then,
I want to act like a millionaire
and get properly faced with my best
buddy in the whole world, Hank Moody.
What do you say?
I say we do it.
Let's shoot the moon.
If we only get halfway there,
so be it.
- It's better than working for the man.
- Or dying 5 miles from your birthplace.
Mr. Amato.
11th grade english.
Words to live by.
You know, come on,
let's get fuckin' ossified.
How many kids now?
Three, which is...
Three too fuckin' many.
I made you come with one finger.
You imagine what
I could do with the rest.
Jesus Christ, Zloz,
that old chestnut?
Stand down, charm school.
I apologize for my friend.
He's sick in the head.
Just two days out of the asylum.
He's doing okay, having said that.
We'd like another round, my lady,
if you don't mind. Thank you.
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- What? What?
I'm sorry.
There's smokin' hot bitches
everywhere you look, you know?
- What's the move here?
- The move?
I mean, they all seem like
a bunch of stuck up cunts.
That's the move. That's the line.
Try that one out. See where it gets you.
- You still pulling a ton of ass?
- I do all right.
I got my dick wet first.
Remember that shit.
You guys ready to settle up?
- No, fuck you.
- No, let me. Let me.
- Look at you.
- Look at me.
I'm... you know...
I feel a little
underdressed in this joint.
That's because you are underdressed.
- You look like a fuckin' landscaper.
- I am a fuckin' landscaper.
- I own my own business now.
- That's terrific. Good for you.
Not quite as nice as getting
paid to make shit up.
- That is much harder than it looks.
- Right.
I'd love to have her sit on my face
before I die.
Like you'd ever cheat on Kim.
How is she?
That's what I meant
to tell you, man.
- What?
- We're through.
What?
We called it quits, man.
It's over.
- What happened?
- We get in a fight.
Words were spoken.
Household appliances were thrown.
I got in a cab.
Hopped on a plane for LA.
You don't mind if I crash on your couch
for a couple of weeks, do you?
Yeah, I mind. I'm trying
to raise a daughter, numb nuts.
Becca. How's she doing?
- What is she now?
- You won't do any better than Kim.
She's beautiful. I used to jerk off
to that girl every night in HS, almost.
You were my hero
when you nailed her.
Yeah, well, how does the saying go?
For every beautiful woman, there's
a guy who's bored of fucking her.
Let's get out of here, man.
Where's the party?
What party?
Party, there's a party
out there somewhere.
And a blonde with big tits waiting
for me to bang her stupid, all right?
Call your agent.
Isn't that what he gets paid to do?
You don't know my agent.
Great, so we'll see you there.
Looking forward to it.
Any friend of yours.
I'll see what I can do
about the blonde.
With big tits, right?
I'll make a note of that.
See you, Hank.
Hey, you.
Hey there, porn star.
Your boobs, they're really... big.
I know, right?
So that's what my last
ten grand looks like?
You can touch them.
- Really?
- Sure.
You paid for 'em.
Feel me up, citizen.
I knew you'd be back,
you know, sooner or later.
- Yeah? You did?
- Sure, I said so, didn't i?
This one's heavier.
Yeah, you did.
Yeah, when I broke up with you.
You were all: "you'll be back".
"They all come back
sooner or later".
Exactly, the thing is,
though, Daisy, see,
as much as I look back fondly
on our little afternoon in the sun...
I don't think I can go back there.
I'm trying to mend fences
with the missus.
You two are great together.
Good luck with that.
Well, thank you.
I have something I need to tell you.
I'm all ears.
Eyes, Charlie.
I've been making the rounds,
informing my partners
of the various STDs I've contracted.
Nothing crazy, mind you.
Nothing life-threatening
or anything like that.
But you might want
to get to a doctor
and have him whip up
some kind of cocktail.
Help fight it off.
'cause let me tell you,
this is some really pernicious shit.
My vagina looks like
downtown Baghdad right now.
- Charlie, are you okay?
- Yeah, I think so.
I'm just... I'm a little dizzy.
And... And clammy too.
Do I feel clammy to you?
Is that how it starts?
This is some serious
Scarface shit here.
It's the boys.
This here is the almighty zloz,
my oldest friend
from the island of long.
- Mr. Almighty, pleasure to meet you.
- You too.
Mike Zlozowski.
Very nice to meet you guys.
You've known him a long time.
Was he always such a prick?
Always!
He's always been a ball buster.
I spent half my life making sure
he didn't get his teeth kicked in.
True. He's my bodyguard.
Welcome, boys...
And girl.
You must be Runkle.
In fact, I am.
I see what you mean.
Great head for helming.
This is my husband, Ricardo Collini.
Call me Dickie.
Have fun, cap'n.
You too.
Hold on a minute there.
You're married?
Yeah, 25 years and countin'.
I had no idea.
You never asked.
I feel very strange about this.
Runkle, don't worry.
Dickie and I have a very...
A very open relationship.
But, as you can see,
he has some limitations.
He is, however,
a master of the oral arts.
You ought to try him
sometime, honey.
There's no place like home.
Is your father a lumberjack?
Because every time I look at you,
I get serious wood in my pants.
Do you think you're better than me?
Nice one, Shecky Greene.
To the city of angels
and its stuck-up snatch.
Can't we do better?
Let's drink to Levittown,
from whence we came.
I don't know, Moody.
I think I could get used to this.
I got a few screenplay ideas.
What's... What's stopping me
from taking this town by storm?
Me. Just me.
I won't let you.
You gonna get in my way?
You gonna keep it all for yourself?
That? That out there?
That's a fuckin' mirage.
That doesn't exist, behind me.
You got everything
you ever want or need home.
Trust me.
What do you know about home?
You got out years ago.
Now, it's easy for you to spout
some working class hero,
springsteen bullshit
about the sanctity of small towns
when you're driving a porsche.
- You got it all wrong, man.
- I got it all wrong? Listen.
You see that...
You see that girl over there?
I'm gonna go talk to her.
Maybe she's warm for my form,
maybe not, but...
You know, I'm no marky mark,
but I'm going down swinging tonight.
- Wish me luck.
- Good luck.
What are you doing?
This is...
Look...
All this erotica, got me all...
Grande.
I'm all sexed up and shit.
And you know how I am.
- The more I gets, the more I wants.
- Yeah, but not tonight, maybe.
Maybe we just take a break,
you know.
What? Why don't you want to fuck me?
'cause this is my boss's house.
That's why.
Yeah, baby,
and your boss is a stone freak.
I think she would very much approve
of a quickie happening
right under her own roof.
Really, I'm sore still.
I mean, chafed, really.
Okay, what the fuck is going on?
Nothing, I'm just...
I'm, you know, I guess a little,
overwhelmed by the whiplash
nature of our relationship...
Bullshit!
You fucked someone else, didn't you?
No, never.
I am done with that behavior.
Something's going on with you.
Daisy... came to see me.
I knew it!
I fucking knew it.
A woman knows that shit.
So, what, you want to get
back together with her now?
You're gonna have some
skanky little porno babies?
Why don't you make up
your fucking mind already?
No, I told her
I want to be with you,
only you...
My one true love.
Really?
What'd she say, that little tramp?
Actually...
And this is interesting...
She said that she had contracted
a few STDs.
Nothing crazy. Nothing a bolus
of antibiotics wouldn't cure.
Just... Knock it out.
No, I seriously think
I'm gonna throw up right now.
That is exactly what I said! Right?
Or, I don't know.
Maybe I said, I was dizzy.
But it's the same difference, really.
I'm taking your little
fucking girl car, Charlie.
And don't you dare
bother coming home tonight!
Fucking hell.
She's got a cock!
Really?
Sure it wasn't just
an oversized clit?
I know a cock when I touch one.
I... We were messing around,
okay, in the hot tub.
I was getting ready to close.
She says she wants to tell me something.
Like she had a boyfriend.
Next thing I know, she's guiding
my hand down to her thin, bent dong.
- Then what, you gave her a handy?
- Fuck you, man.
- I fuckin' clocked her.
- There's laws.
You can't do that.
That's a human being.
You can't just be throwing
punches at people.
What the fuck is
wrong with you, Moody?
Have you been in LA so long
that a tranny means nothing to you?
Your friend's
a closeted fucking homo!
That's what I've been telling him
for years. I have, really.
See, them's fightin' words.
- Asshole... I thought you knew.
- You'll hit me now?
When I realized you didn't,
I tried to break it to you gently.
Well, for what it's worth,
I think you're beautiful.
I think you could
totally pass for a lady.
- Thank you, sweetie.
- Anytime.
Why don't you guys get a room, maybe,
and suck each other's dicks?
I think he knew, deep down.
- He was looking for a little meat.
- Possibi...
Shit.
Pause!
Boys, enough!
Up.
- There'll be no fighting in this house.
- This place is made for love.
The Collinis are open to all sizes,
shapes, and sexual preferences.
- Ignorance will not be tolerated.
- You're absolutely right, Sue.
We are deeply ashamed. Deeply.
- Right, Zloz?
- Maybe you are...
I am deeply ashamed...
- That I touched a tranny's cock.
- All right, all right!
Now that we've got
that cleared away...
You boys wanna go skiing with me?
Yeah, okay.
You see the mams on this broad?
This guy was your BFF?
I don't see it.
You wouldn't know it to look at him now,
but he was the coolest kid in HS.
Not the smartest, but the funniest.
A regular fuckin' riot.
He had the hottest girlfriend.
We all wanted to be him.
I worshipped the guy.
I like you like this.
Like what?
Like my new boyfriend.
Be careful, ladies.
I think I might have an STD.
You don't happen to have a dick,
do you? No offense.
None taken.
Nope! No dick.
No pubic hair, either.
Dig that shit.
I'm sorry I doubted you, sweetheart.
Bad boy. I'm gonna punish you.
You're my bitch. You my bitch?
That's right. Oh, yeah.
What... Dude. Wait.
Stop it! Asshole! Get off!
Hey, fucker!
You're out of here!
What happened?
What'd he do?
He was sucking on her titty,
and that ain't cool.
That is not cool.
What the fuck are you thinking?
Did you see those things?
They were epic, man.
It was like Pamela Anderso
meets Samantha Fox.
- Remember her?
- Shut up.
- Tits for days!
- I apologize... Shut up!
I'm throwing
working class out on his ass.
Working class?
Watch it!
You with me, compadre?
Good morning, teach.
Our very first sleepover.
I wish I remembered more of it.
Did we take a bubble bath?
There is evidence to
support that theory, yes.
Can I ask you a favor?
Good morning.
Did we... Did we...
Fuck, yeah.
- Was I any good?
- Oh, the best.
You've got a great cock.
Fuckin'- a.
Good times.
Morning, kids.
- Dude.
- Buddy?
This place is beautiful, man.
Takes your breath away, sometimes.
That's one of the perks.
That and in-n-out burger.
- I got a question for you.
- Shoot.
How come you never made
it to my wedding, man?
Man.
I don't know.
I guess I was pissed.
You know...
I didn't want to see
you ruin your life.
We had a plan.
Right, and I fucked it up.
Well...
We were gonna get out of there,
together.
You were gonna be a rock star.
I was gonna be a famous write
that's the way I thought back then.
Black and white.
I was a fuckin' idiot.
Couldn't have been more wrong.
You did a beautiful thing.
You stepped up,
married that girl, had a family.
Don't fuck it up.
Don't chase these...
girls with fake titties
and half-baked screenplay ideas.
Dude...
I'm sorry about your father, man.
Thank you.
Thanks for the flowers.
Did you hear about Mr. Amato?
- He passed away last year.
- Did he?
I guess that really proves his theory,
that you...
You really do die less than five
miles from where you were born.
- Now, that might happen to me now.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- I get these nosebleeds.
What do you mean nosebleeds?
What are you talking about?
I never thought much about them,
but...
Kim finally made me
go to the doctor.
And it turns out I'm sick, dude.
What do you mean sick?
What kind of sick?
Sick like I gotta...
Like I got something
I gotta deal with sick.
I got to get a whole
shitload of tests.
I keep putting it off.
And that's why kim and I had
that big fuckin' blowout, man.
It's not a good time right now.
At least I got to see all this,
though, man.
You're not gonna die.
Maybe, you know.
Maybe not.
Whatever happens,
it's got me thinking
about a lot of things,
About fuckin' short it all is.
How you and I, once upon a time,
we were thick as thieves.
I don't know what happened.
I wish I knew the moment
where it all changed,
- 'Cause I would do things differently.
- You didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't mean to let things
slide with you, Zloz.
I guess I did.
You were my best friend, Hank.
I'll never forget.
Some of the greatest times of my life,
you know?
Maybe that mak m me a big,
pathetic fuckin' loser,
but, once upon a time
has got to count for something.
- Right?
- Course it does.
I just...
I didn't belong there anymore.
Fuck, I don't belong here, either.
It doesn't change
the fact that I love you, man.
Look at you, Moody.
I can't believe...
I haven't seen you cry
since Thurman Munson died.
You got to bring up Thurman Munson?
- You fucking asshole.
- I had to go there because...
- You were crying, I was crying.
- It was beautiful.
You were crying about Andy Gibb.
I got to pick up the little monster.
No worries.
Gives me plenty of time to get
loaded and piss myself on the plane.
It was good to see you, Zloz.
Yeah, you too, man.
Thanks for showing me a good time.
You know, what happens in LA...
- Right, brother?
- Yes, it stays in the vault.
You think you're gonna be able to
patch things up with the old lady?
To tell you the truth,
she doesn't even know I'm gone.
She was so pissed at me,
she took off with a couple of
her girlfriends to Atlantic City.
For all I know, she could have
been making out with a tranny too.
- You're a colossal pussy.
- You better come visit.
I got a bunch of kids with
Hank Moody stories.
They don't have a face
to put to the name.
- That's not good.
- No, it's not.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- Fuckin' homo.
- OK, faggot. Go.
Made you look...
At my cock.
Look who's here.
Not even a hello.
Good times.
Good times, good times.
What are you doing?
What am I, your limo driver?
Come on. You get in the front.
What? Were you just
gonna leave me behind?
Merry fucking Christmas.
Can we go home already?
Shut up.