Previously on californication
I think we should
go into business together.
To be honest, i'm interviewing
for jobs in new york.
So, how do you two
know each other?
Hank is the father.
Alleged father.
I'll raise the child,
and i'll love it as my own.
Oh, my god.
Look, look, look...
damien and becca.
Because isn't that
the becca right there?
Oh! Bec!
I don't want to do
any more porn.
Really?
I'd like the last person i had
on-Screen sex with to be you.
Charlie:
all right, marcy.
After all the shit
we've been through,
I want to get a divorce.
I'm gonna be with daisy.
You fucked my man.
Marcy,
i didn't mean...
She's here.
She who?
"She who"?
Janie, you asshole!
Come on!
What?
Lew. Shit, lew.
Lew!
Lew?
You got yourself
a bit of a ritual there, huh?
Yep.
Every time i finish a book,
whiskey, weed, and warren zevon.
It's the little things.
Yeah.
How'd it turn out?
Hard to say.
You would know better than i.
You lived the motherfucker.
Yeah,
but living it right
Means you don't remember
much of it at all.
Well, you can
read all about it here...
Your dirty life and times.
What's next?
I suppose i try to get my life
back in order in some fashion.
Yeah, you...
You do that.
Remember,
at the end of the day,
It's all about her.
Who?
You know.
I'll miss seeing you
around here, man.
Gonna miss you, too.
And it's true
what they say, you know.
They got
one hell of a band.
What up, buttercup?
Oh, i just thought
i'd pay my last respects
Before i hit the road.
Where you headed?
Oh, didn't you get
the memo?
Mnh-Mnh.
I'm taking
"fucking & punching"
All over this fair country
of ours.
Coming soon to a supersized
bookstore near you.
Mothers,
lock up your sons.
And husbands.
I'm gonna miss him...
Way more than i thought.
Yeah,
i know the feeling.
At first,
fucking him was...
Was just a way
of yanking your chain.
Really?
You don't say?
Yeah, but then he just had to
win me over, you know?
Like some sweet,
mangy little puppy
Who just wanted someone
to pet him
And tell him
he was a good boy.
Then he'd shit the rug.
Or hump your leg.
Mm.
Where's your first stop?
Uh, borders in tacoma.
Know it. There's a great
coffee shop down the street.
Around the block,
there's this old record store,
Sells used vinyl, tons of it...
fantastic.
Great...  old guy's guide
to tacoma. Good to know.
Well, just be gentle with
our retarded love child.
I will.
Be good out there,
psycho.
Tell 'em who sent you.
Well, if it isn't
the madre of my bambino.
What's shakin', sweet duck?
I got a job.
A good job?
A great job.
I mean, my dream job.
Wow,
way to go, fancy pants.
Yeah.
It's, um...
It's in new york.
Even better.
Right.
I start monday.
No time
like the present.
Oh, my god. You're taking this
much better than i thought.
Why shouldn't i?
I've been trying to get
back to new york for years now.
Hank.
Karen.
I got a job.
You got a job.
That's what you just said.
Not you.
No. Not...
i'm not following.
No, you're not following.
I mean, you're not invited.
That is fucked up.
Well, this is not about
you or us, okay.
This is about me and becca.
But you can't
just whisk her away
And expect me to sit here in
l.A. With a dry thumb up my ass.
Well, you know what?
You do have some serious shit
to deal with here.
Karen,
i can write anywhere...
Or not, as the case may be,
which is not the case.
I just finished
the ashby book
This morning,
as a matter of fact.
Good.
Honey, i'm on fire...
good for you.
... which is why
we should be together,
Or, at the very least,
why i should be your manny.
Do you laugh?
My manny?
Yeah!
You're a high-Powered
career gal now.
You need somebody
to hold down the fort.
Right.
A majordomo.
Thank you.
I'm your man, woman.
I'm not talking about your
writing or lack thereof, okay?
I was talking about
the impending arrival
of your latest mistake.
D-Did you forget?
Uh, sir francis drake
said he was totally down
With raising
the little bastard as his own.
You heard
the bearded woman.
Y-You're okay with that?
I'm not entirely convinced
it's mine.
You know,
i never came inside her.
I don't...
i don't think i did.
I mean,
when she broncoed me,
I spasmed out
a little dog water, you know.
Thank you.
I'm still
holding out the hope
That she banged some dude
in the p.F. Chang's parking lot
While she was looking for
mr. Goodbar.
I think that's
an entirely plausible scenario.
There is something wrong
with you.
Well, i'm special.
I think i'm special.
I really do.
What does jeff becca think about
you tearing our family apart?
Well, no...  right now...
she's heartbroken right now.
Yeah, of course
she's heartbroken.
You rip her away
from her old man,
You don't invite him
to come with.
That shit is harsh!
She's heartbroken
about damien.
What about damien?
Well,
she saw him making out
With someone else
at mia's party, so...
Welcome to all american burger.
May i take your order?
Can i get a jumbo "what the fuck
were you thinking?"
That's the problem...
i wasn't thinking.
I mean,
she fucking kissed me, dude.
That kind of shit just doesn't
just happen to me a lot...
Like ever.
W...  w...  yo.
Be that as it may,
on the flip side,
What i've got is a young girl
whose heart is broken.
Yeah, i know.
I know, and i feel all sorts
of awful about it.
But, you know,
i've been thinking about it,
And given the opportunity
to...  to do it again,
I don't think it would go
any differently, honestly.
I mean, a beautiful girl
is kind enough to kiss you...
Fuck,
you kiss her right back.
'Cause...
You know,
who...  who knows
Where that kiss
is gonna take you?
I went there
to kick his ass,
And i stayed
to soak up his wisdom.
They know more than we do...
the children. We forget.
Which is why we end up
in these fucked-Up situations.
Yeah. Selling bmws
in the valley...
What the fuck, dude?
Don't kid yourself, pal.
I always was.
Selling writers, actors,
directors...
It's all the same shit.
Have you talked to
the marce?
Through the lawyers.
She's a little feral
right now...
Wants to take me
for all i'm worth.
Oh, no.
All four figures?
I don't even care, really.
I just want to be happy,
you know.
That's all that matters now...
the big happy.
Right...  pimping rides,
living in a studio apartment
In the valley
with a porno chick.
Hey, hey, hey...
retired porno chick.
She's taking
some groundlings classes.
She's really quite funny.
I am sure she's a deep-Throating
lucille ball.
Bully for her,
but what about you?
Does this work for you,
give you the big happy?
More than you know, pal.
I feel like i'm 23 again.
You know, life is simple.
It's good.
Money's a little tight,
you know.
I think i'm gonna have to use
the office xerox
To copy your manuscript.
I'm so happy
i stayed with you.
Me too. Good for us.
We're making shit happen.
Let's go, runkle.
You got to be on that
sales floor at all times.
A.B.C., baby...
"always be closing."
Yes, sir!
"A.B.C., baby...
'always be closing'".
These fucking guys...
They all think
they're the only one
Who ever saw
"glengarry glen ross."
Hey, if you want,
I'll take you out back
and shoot you.
I will let you know.
That number, my friend,
Puts you in a beautiful
'07 convertible with navigation.
Oh, you're good.
How we doing over here?
Chuck runkle.
Man:
nice to meet you.
There goes my agent.
I'm sick to my stomach.
It's gonna get better.
I promise.
Maybe it does,
maybe it doesn't.
Well...
Either way, dad,
words don't help.
Yeah.
I suddenly understand the appeal
of cigarettes and alcohol.
Here's an idea...  why don't you
hang behind with me
And nurse
your broken heart?
We could, uh,
smoke some cigarettes,
Pass the bottle,
listen to some blues.
It'll be fun.
Hank, that is
very manipulative.
No! It's not.
It's not manipulative.
Dad...
it's a suggestion.
... i'm going with mom.
I need a change of scenery.
I don't want to be
driving down the street
And be reminded of all
the places we kissed.
"All the places"?!
What kind of an operation
are you... running here?
What the hell?
Hey, no, don't answer that.
It's rude.
No, it's sonja.
It could be important.
Well, really
don't answer it.
No! It's around
the due date, right?
Right to voicemail...
that's what it's for.
No, no.
Excuse me, sweetie.
Hey, sonja.
You are?
Drugs!
I want some fucking drugs!
Fuck! Can't you hippies
make this shit stop?!
Breathe, mommy.
It's all about transc...
Okay, you know what? Fuck you,
you stupid fucking doula!
Hey.
Oh, god.
Hey. Hi, guys.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming.
And by the way, hank,
fuck you
For putting this goddamn monster
in my stomach.
I'm not entirely sure it's mine.
There will be some genetic...
Hank,
do not be an asshole!
You're right, and when
you're right, you're right.
Let's get the little fucker out
first, then we're gonna test.
Oh, hey, look at you.
Look who showed up.
I'm back.
The man's back.
Have you been drinking?
Just a little tequila
for the pain.
You bearded fucking lunatic.
Who do you think you are?!
You're stressed out,
huh?!
You need a drink?!
Shh.
You know what?
Don't come near me.
I'll rip his fucking handlebars
right off your fucking face!
I'll do it.
Fucking drunk.
Come on. You got to get
your shit together.
It's time to stand up
and extract that little
artist within. Come on.
I'm just a fraud,
hank.
I know,
but it's time to stand up.
No.
Take the dress off
already.
Oh, stop.
I am.
Don't. Don't.
No, actually, actually,
that's good. That's good.
You march over there
with those tears,
And you tell her
those are tears of joy, okay?
She will swoon.
Trust me. Go.
Okay.
You go.
Thank you.
Yes, you're welcome.
You're beautiful.
Just go.
No,
you got to go alone.
Okay,
i'm just gonna...
What the fuck, julian?
I'm crying.
Are you crying?
Yeah.
What the fuck?!
I'm the one fucking pushing out
a goddamn bowling ball
Out of my pussy...
my sweet, beautiful pussy
That is never gonna
look the same again!
I should be crying!
You are crying.
I did have a pretty pussy,
didn't i, hank?
Oh, my god, yes.
I mean, a beautiful pussy.
I would put it in
the top 10 of pussies.
I love
your pussy, too.
Your p...  you know, not...
no disrespect to yours.
Karen...  number-One pussy
in the world, with a bullet.
Fuck you.
Lover!
You home?
Oh, yeah.
Charlie.
Oh, shit.
I know that look.
He's gonna blow.
Slow it down, runkle.
Forget it, jake.
It's vaginatown!
I know.
That's the only way...
Charlie,
what are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Can you just wait outside
for a second?
Sure thing, babe.
I'm sorry, baby.
I just...
I thought i was gonna be
by myself for a while, you know?
I...  who's that?
Oh, just a guy
from my groundlings class.
We were gonna work on
a sketch.
Oh, okay.
Wow. I'm really sorry.
I just...  i thought i was gonna
have a few minutes to myself.
Oh, it's okay.
You know i'm totally fine
with you masturbating.
It's just kind of weird
when you bring somebody over.
I understand, and it's important
that we set these ground rules.
Gus?
Oh.
Um, gus, this is
my lover, charlie.
Gus, chuck runkle.
Hey, charlie.
Uh, should we start?
Oh, fuck.
Here it comes.
Woman: okay.
Fuck.
Okay, it's time.
Oh, yeah.
Breathe, breathe.
Okay, go, sonja.
Go! Yes!
Fuck!
Push. Push!
Oh, my god!
Oh, look.
What the fuck?!
Boooooo-Ya!
Baby is black!
Karen!
Damn it, the baby's black.
You see that shit?!
Goddamn it!
I didn't knock her up.
I know!
I love you.
Ohh.
Congratulations, mommy.
Bathe the child,
and bring him to me.
I forgot about
that fucking barista.
He was so hot.
He looked like lenny kravitz.
Fuck.
I said, bathe the infant,
and bring him to me.
Coming. Coming.
Fuck, i forgot.
I'm sorry, hank.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
I will raise...
This black baby
as my own.
Before you drop him,
you fucking drunk, come here.
I will raise this black baby
as my own.
As my own.
Yeah.
Oh.
He's beautiful.
Congratulations.
He looks like me.
He doesn't
look like you.
Hey, lover.
Hey!
How'd it go?
Good.
I think it's gonna be
really funny.
Good. Good.
I had sex with gus.
What?
I got confused.
You got confused?
What the fuck does that mean?
Well, i've never
done a scene like that before,
And we got to the kissing part,
and i got all confused.
My autopilot kicked in,
and i kissed him for real,
And the next thing you know,
he was inside me.
That sounds like rape.
No, not really...
Unless he wants to
press charges.
It felt good.
He had a really nice cock.
Jesus christ, daisy!
I'm sorry.
Does that
make you feel bad?
Yeah, it makes me feel bad!
It makes me want to throw up!
Do you want me
to suck your dick?
No!
Yes.
I don't know.
Now i'm confused.
See?!
This is confusing stuff!
Maybe we should
take a break.
"Take a break"?!
I just left my wife for you!
I didn't ask you to,
charlie!
I know!
It just... seemed incredibly
romantic at the time.
It was.
Maybe we should have some sex,
just fuck through the pain.
O... kay.
Okay, citizen,
fuck the gus out of me.
Why didn't you
pinch me?
Jesus! Woman!
Uhh,
i'm tapping out.
You had me looking for
the fucking rodeo clown.
Really?
Hey, you know what?
I think you should come
to new york.
Well.
Why the change of heart?
I can't live
without this.
I thought
maybe it was 'cause
You wanted to make
a black baby with me.
No,
i just need a manny.
Oh, i have
excellent references.
Plus, my vagina's become
really attached to you.
Not your heart?
Just your vag?
Well,
it's tough if, you know,
The heart and the vag
are not on the same page.
But, you know what?
In this instance, they are.
Well, that's terrific
because i am all about
Improving heart/vag
relations, you know?
It's my thing.
So we're in sync.
Mm-Hmm.
Should we
take advantage of that?
Could...  could we...
Round two?
Yeah.
I'm answering
the bell.
You got five minutes,
runkle.
You look beautiful.
That's right,
motherfucker, i do.
I've always
looked beautiful.
That's true.
You have.
Then why the fuck
did you have to go
And stick your dick
into some skanky porno chick?
I don't know.
I got confused.
You could've stayed
with me.
You were number 19.
There were 18 cocks
before you, charlie...
Not a ton,
not a rogues gallery,
But enough to know
that i liked yours the best.
Not the longest,
not the thickest,
Little bit of english on it,
but it was mine...  all mine.
And now you
and your cock
Have betrayed me
for the last time.
Don't go, marce.
I'm already gone, baby.
I was gone the moment
That you said
you wanted to be with daisy.
You said it out loud!
You can't take it back.
Oh, and, uh... your friend
ronny praeger called.
He said something about
intense video wanting to
"Buy 'vaginatown'
For a shitload of money."
Really?
That's good news.
Oh, hells yeah.
It's great news... for me.
What? You said
i could have everything.
But don't worry your
pretty little head about it.
We'll let my lawyer
figure it out.
He's really good.
Later, runkle.
Where's my ipod?
I can't find my fucking ipod!
Bec...
It's gonna be
a long trip.
Yeah.
What?
Something pubescent
this way comes.
Okay, i know
you hate me right now.
I do.
Okay, but i figured
i'd hate myself even more
If i didn't, you know,
at least say goodbye.
That's it?
That's the best
you can do?
Here,
i got you something.
I put a playlist
on there...
Our playlist...
the one we made out to...
All 17 songs.
What?! 17 songs?
That's a lot
of making out.
Hank,
could you shut up?
He said 17 songs.
I still
loathe you.
I know. I know.
And you have every right.
I do feel like
i was unjustly seduced,
But i know that doesn't
make it okay.
Anyway, i just wish
you weren't leaving 'cause...
'Cause i...  i love you...
becca moody.
You're like the only
post-Punk, heavy-Metal chick
Who's ever
truly rocked my world.
Is it okay if we go upstairs
for a minute?
Of course...
no fucking way.
No, no, no.
You take it out on the strand
Where there are people,
and i'm watching you...
Eyes in the back
of my head.
As always.
Hey, damien.
Well played.
Big ups.
You know, that was
a nice parental move.
I...  yeah.
I kind of...
I like the way
you handled that shit.
That's right,
mothafuckah!
I feel kind of bad
splitting them up right now.
Well, then don't.
What do you mean?
You go. I stay.
Are you crazy?
What, you think
i'd leave becca behind?
Well, i'm not gonna break her.
I promise.
Well, hold on a second.
What about you?
I mean,
you'd give up new york?
For her, yeah.
At the end of the day,
it's all about her.
It's always been about her.
What happens between us,
i can't fucking control.
Lord knows
i've tried every which way.
But what i can do
Is be the absolute best
i can be for her.
If i followed you
to new york,
I'd just be
hoping against hope
That we lived
happily ever after.
Maybe we do.
Maybe we don't.
But you got some shit
you got to do, lady.
I think you should do it.
I'll hold down the fort...
Keep her off the pole.
Oh, jesus.
I wish you hadn't
just said all that.
Why?
I don't know.
'Cause, you know, it just
makes me love you even more.
Yeah, well...
that really can't be helped.
I am me, after all.
A quick one
while they're away?
You're disgusting.
Mm.
Look, just because
it's you and me now, alone,
Doesn't mean i'm gonna let you
get away with stuff.
It's good.
'Cause i'm not gonna let you
get away with stuff either.
Oh, really? What are...
what are you gonna do?
I'm not scared of you.
You're...  you're...
you're very diminutive,
You know,
and i know jujitsu.
I can still
kick your ass.
Yeah,
at "guitar hero," maybe.
Hey.
Hey, yourself.
Is this
your offspring?
Yes, this is, uh,
this is becca, my daughter,
And this is...
This is surfer girl.
Hello,
surfer girl.
It's michelle.
My name
is michelle.
Okay.
I'm gonna go check out
that head shop.
I'll be watching.
N...
Eyes in back
of my head.
Head shop.
Oh, boy.
Cute kid.
She has her moments.
So, michelle, huh?
That's...  that's interesting.
You're disappointed,
aren't you?
Well, you know,
i did kind of like not knowing.
It was...  it was cool
In a "last tango in paris"
kind of way.
I think you mythologize me
just a little too much.
You know,
i'm just a normal girl...
With normal wants
and needs.
You know, i have been around
the block a time or two, lady,
And there ain't
nothing normal about you.
Aw, you're still the sweetest
guy i ever fucked and robbed.
You know, i'd like nothing more
than to get high,
Fuck you goofy, and indulge
your larcenous tendencies,
But i have a, uh,
serious child-Raising...
Problem here.
Look at that.
I think she's...
she's looking for a bong.
And the dance
continues.
So it does.
She seems nice.
I don't know if "nice"
is exactly the word.
Have you been intimate
with her?
Why do you got to
talk to me like that?!
What?
You're always up in my grill
about boys.
Well, and up in your grill
i always will be. Count on it.
Don't stop, okay?
Even if i curse your name
on a semi-Daily basis.
I wouldn't dream of it.
He gig.
Hey.
Oh.
What's this for?
For staying.
You're stuck
on the island now.
And you did it for me.
What are you
talking about?
I like it here.
It's nice.
The sun is chirping.
The birds are shining.
The water's wet.
Life is good, sweetheart.
Life is good.