Previously on Californication...
- Did you two come together?
- No. We just came in together.
I've never stepped outside
of my marriage before.
But I'm guessing
that you feel like you're...
owed one.
Come on. You're coming in.
I want to take a look at you.
This is so not fair.
Daisy... came to see me.
What'd she say, that little tramp?
She said that she had contracted
a few STDs.
No, I seriously think
I'm gonna throw up right now.
What could possibly be so awful
about visiting the woman
who pushed you through
her magnificent vagina?
Chelsea has Lakers tickets.
I'm so excited. I can't wait
to squeeze that little peanut.
I wouldn't get too excited.
She hasn't been very pleasant lately.
Look who's here.
Not even a hello. Oh, good times.
What? Were you just
gonna leave me behind?
Chelsea.
I need to take this.
What do you mean? What,
are you with the organ transplant team?
Shut that shit down.
Tell your old man about your weekend.
Start by telling me
how much you missed me.
We had a grand old time.
Soaked up some culture, did you?
Museums, shopping, girl talk?
Some dirty-water hot dogs maybe?
What?
Where you going?
I'm still allowed to pee, aren't I?
Remember this?
Remember when you thought
that was a good idea?
It's awful.
I don't recognize her anymore.
I told you.
She's changed, right?
She's a miserable little bitch
all the time now.
- I guess at least we know why, right?
- We do?
Chelsea.
It's all she cares about anymore.
It's better than her
caring about a boy, right?
'cause you can't get
pregnant from your bff.
At least not without the aid of
a turkey baster.
- This isn't working anymore.
- What isn't working?
- Don't say that.
- This arrangement.
She need to be living
with me right now, okay?
I know she hates me.
And I know she wants
to live here with you.
But fuck it. We're the parents.
We get to decide.
- We?
- Yes, we.
So you're saying we just pack up
and leave LA?
The three of us,
move back to NY together?
Well, soon, yeah.
End of the semester, whatever.
This place is toxic.
LA is no place to raise a daughter.
That's my line.
You're stealing my shit.
To our beautiful family...
Our black president,
and my magnificent dong.
I'm not even a part
of this fucking family anymore?
She gets to decide?
How is that fair?
I don't think
we were shooting for fair.
For the 1st time in my life,
I'm actually happy, now
I must go someplace
I have no friends?
NY doesn't mean shit to me.
It isn't the answer to anything!
Telling her together... I guess
that didn't work out so well, did it?
You know what? It kind of came up
while the narcissist in the family
was deep-conditioning.
I can't believe
you didn't fight for me.
There's nothing to fight about, honey.
This was always the plan.
You're gonna be late
to school, okay?
We will talk about it later.
I love you.
So, well, the worst is over.
You think the french Revolution was over
when they stormed the Bastille?
No, no. They had a little thing called
the Terror. It happened years later.
She will get used to the idea.
Who doesn't want to live in New York?
Anyway, professor...
- Get dressed or you're gonna be late.
- Not that late.
It's a very progressive school.
The students almost teach themselves.
- Stop!
- Why?
Because.
For a start,
I don't know where you've been.
I'm freshly showered, right?
That should count.
- I don't know where you've been either.
- You do.
I do?
What is that, like a riddle?
You getting all sphinx-like on me?
I slept with Bill.
I ran into him at NYU
when he was visiting Mia.
She says hi, by the way.
Are you okay?
You look a little sick in your stomach.
Shit, you're totally not
joking about this, are you?
Come on, Hank.
It's not that big a deal.
I kind of felt like I owed him one.
I did, you know,
ruin his life and all.
I mean, that night that I married him,
and then I jumped in the car with you.
God, it feels good
to tell the truth.
Come on, professor.
Come out of there. Get dressed.
I'm so excited
to go to class with you!
"Eva lifts her head from her book
"and regards the curious figure
striding her way.
"The faint hint of a smile
appears on her face.
"Adam slows down,
reaching her table.
"Their eyes meet, and it seems Adam
will do it. But what do you know, folks?
"He averts his eyes
and keeps right on walking,
"jamming his hands in his pockets.
So what can we learn from this early
execrable work from a major...
And I do mean major...
american author?
And don't be shy.
Rip him a new asshole
or three or four.
Go. Dig in.
I think "execrable"
is a little harsh.
I mean,
I didn't think it was so bad.
And I think those that are auditing
this class really shouldn't participate.
- Others?
- You should let the woman speak.
What did you say your name was?
She didn't.
Next.
"Their eyes meet"?
That's a little hokey, don't you think?
Eva's whole introduction,
really, is just...
Stupid, you know? We know she's pretty.
We get it.
And we're out of time. Look at that.
Class has now ended.
Go in peace and love
to serve the word.
Here's the papers on last week's
- poetry of Jagger and Richards.
- Thank you.
Well, then, I'll see you next week.
You are unbelievable.
- What?
- So, Adam...
Which one are you sleeping with?
- Excuse me?
- My bets are...
on the young, voluptuous student.
She's a definite...
Eva prototype.
Please.
There's only one Eva.
It's against the rules
to sleep with students.
Of course. Yes.
Though when I was in college...
- I slept with...
- "slept with my professor. "
I've heard quite enough about
your sexual goings-on for one day.
I can't believe you kept
this ridiculous story.
You wrote this when you were,
like, 23?
I save everything I write...
All parts of the buffalo.
Especially the stuff about you.
Yeah, one-act plays, haikus,
grocery lists.
I'm sorry, I was just wondering
if you were picking up...
The girls from school.
Not... Not the Karen?
The mamacita of my bambina. Si.
I'm Becca's mom.
- It's nice to meet you.
- I'm Chelsea's mum.
Lovely to meet you finally.
Becca must be delighted
to have you back.
Well, she's not back back.
It's just a quick visit.
You know,
my work keeps me in New York, so...
I know.
It's so awful, isn't it?
The whole working-mum thing.
I'm so lucky
with my teaching schedule.
I'm not working this afternoon,
so I could pick them up if you'd like.
No, you know what?
That's OK.
I kind of... I kind of like it.
I miss it, actually.
Who doesn't love a carpool line?
Well, then, problem solved, I guess.
So, lovely to meet you.
And you.
Yes. Yeah, bye.
Oh, my god,
can you believe that woman?
She's real classy-like, right?
- What?
- No, and that ridiculous accent.
- I mean, what the fuck?
- It's pleasant.
She was like, you know,
"so lovely to meet you.
- "My schedule".
- She taught to speak like that.
She's not making it...
I think you're jealous.
- Are you being jealous?
- No.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you were.
She is definitely not your type.
There you are,
you V.D.-riddled sack of shit.
Ten days' worth of antibiotics
I have to take,
just in case, mind you.
I'm taking them too, you know,
and I'm getting tested tomorrow.
Yes, dear, but the delicate balance
of yeast in your vagina
isn't as likely to be compromised
by all this shit, now, is it?
Just, you know, eat more yogurt.
Hey, I'll make you a smoothy.
Do I look like I want
a fuking smoothy?
- Whose Corvette is that?
- Rick Springfield.
And a smoothy can be very
refreshing on a hot day.
- Now you got to be fucking with me.
- What fucking with you?
I said, whose car is that
blocking the driveway?
And I said Rick Springfield.
He's got a audition tomorrow,
and we're running lines here.
He is running lines with you
in my house right now?
Yes, he's a new client.
I've told you this before.
Now, listen to me. I'm gonna be late
coming back from his audition,
so I got everything prepped
for our dinner with Hank and Karen.
It's gonna be gumbo. Everything going
in the pressure cooker.
All you have to do is remember
to start the rice, please.
Rick fucking Springfield is here
in my house right fucking now?
He's upstairs having a nap,
- sort of.
- Or wait.
I spoke too soon.
Here's Rick now.
Dude, don't you have anything raunchier
than back issues of Gent Magazine?
You're really...
Rick Springfield in my house right now.
You're...
You're very tall and...
And dark and handsome and, uh...
No. Charlie doesn't have
anything raunchier than that,
because he likes to, you know,
kick it old school with the pornography.
- Know what I'm saying?
- Church.
Are these my beta-blockers?
- I get real nervous before...
- No, that's just a...
Lip gloss.
Back in the old days,
Sue used to blow me.
But these days,
she likes them younger...
And balder.
Don't you need to be running
along somewhere, little one?
Appointments and such?
No, I'm OK.
I just want to stay here talk to Rick.
Not on my watch, OK?
We got work to do.
Lots of it.
No time for distractions.
But come on!
One more word out of you, and I'm gonna
tell him what those pills are for.
When I was a kid,
you spoke when you were spoken to,
or else you were chased around
a kitchen with a wooden.
Sorry, we weren't put
on this planet to entertain you.
Untrue...
Entertainment for the poor.
That's what my mother
always called children. Clearly,
she was wrong.
Maybe if you weren't poor...
- Excuse me?
- Poor? Are we?
- I didn't get that memo. Are we poor?
- No offense, Karen, but
Becca showed me a picture
of where you live,
I've been in dorm rooms
that are bigger than that.
I think that it would be best
for Becca if she could stay in LA.
And have at least some
shot at a normal life.
She did say "no offense. "
She returns!
Yes, in!
On the fucking line!
I'm gonna take you down, mommy.
Is there any sport for which your father
does not have the proper attire?
I bet he swims in a Speedo.
Does he?
Take that, you lazy motherfucker!
All right...
You just caught us
getting some exercise.
- Honey, game's not over.
- That was just a point?
And when you win a whole match,
sacrifice a calf?
- He doesn't...
- Cheers.
Actually mean it,
all that trash talking and such.
That's just his way.
Stacy, this is Becca's mum.
So nice to meet you.
Heard so much about you.
Delighted.
You should stay for dinner.
Just you, not him.
OK, give me that racket.
The dean has just requested a heaping
helping of my backhand for dinner.
Yes, of course, you must stay.
Oh, well, you know,
that's really kind, but we have plans.
We're meeting some friends, so...
Their friends, not mine.
Yes. But the point is
we're going as a family.
Tout ensemble...
So that's the point.
I'd rather stay here
with this family.
Isn't she sweet?
- You know you're always welcome here.
- Yes. Always.
Your mom is visiting from New York.
Have you met your mom?
She's not gonna be here long time
You want to spend time with her, no?
Once you drag me back to New York,
all I'm going to be doing
is spending time with my mother.
I certainly won't have any friends.
Apologize to your mother.
- It's really fine.
- You know what?
It seems like you have an open
invitation here, so it's...
Of course!
It's no problem if you want to stay.
And that way, you two can have
a time with your friends.
Yes. Thank you, Felicia.
Karen couldn't make it.
Not feeling well.
- Oh, look at you.
- Look at you.
- I miss you.
- Is this for me?
- What, my muumuu?
- Looks like America's next top smurf.
It's just the schmata
I wear around the house. What?
In with you!
Where's the Runkle-ator?
He's stuck in...
traffic on his way
over from the Valley.
That man is dead to me, by the way.
Do you see this?
This hideous vd-type pustule
on my face?
- No, not really.
- That is disgusting.
- You see it, right?
- Yeah, it's deep in there.
Guess what?
He gave it to me.
Thanks.
And he tried to rape me, by the way.
- But how are you?
- I'm good.
You know, Becca, she's...
I know.
Make way for the victors.
- Victory.
- He got the part?
You got the part?
Congratulations...
Is that Rick Springfield?
I believe it is.
And who are you, pretty lady?
Rick Springfield
and Andy Gibb on solid gold...
This means nothing to you?
I remember.
Everybody loved
Rick Springfield, right?
She just didn't have the poster
over her bed. You...
I'm guessing you practiced
your she-bopping to that?
You know what always
used to start my motor?
Mannix.
That tall Armenian
with a great head of hair...
Just thinking of him
still gets my juices flowing.
Teen fantasies are great.
I've had some of my own.
What, you?
Duran Duran?
Boy George?
Cheryl Tiegs, thank you very much.
My point is, you have to remember...
Musicians, actors, models...
These are people with flaws and such.
There's no way
they could possibly live up
to the excitement, the mystery
that our tortured teen psyches
choose to project upon them.
That's my point.
I made a girl come seven times once.
Over the course
of an entire relationship?
All in a row?
Sweet Jesus.
Who's ready for dessert?
I know I am.
Cheers to you, Rick Springfield.
Hold on a second.
What are you doing moping in the fridge?
Rick Springfield is stealing your girl,
not Jessie's girl,
your girl, Runkle's girl.
I'm well aware of this fact.
- So get in there and make her jealous.
- With what? You gonna loan me Karen?
- Disgusting. What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong with you?
Shit, really?
We'll be right over.
We got to go.
Little problem with the offspring.
Don't panic. They just...
It seems Becca and Chelsea staged
a raid on the Dean's wine cellar.
I knew that Chelsea was trouble.
Honey, I...
Call me later.
I hope she's okay.
- Bye, Rick Springfield.
- Bye, guys.
Do you want to...
Go up to my room
and listen to some records?
- Only if they're mine.
- Church.
What are you serving for dessert?
I know what I want.
Tube steak.
Yes, I know.
Listen, Sue, this is...
a really difficult time
for me right now,
and besides,
I should probably let you know,
- I think I have V.D.
- No worries.
Just slap a bag on it,
and I'm good to go.
Welcome.
Glass of Cab?
I forget what fucking year this is.
- She's drunk.
- No.
- She can't walk in a straight line.
- Felicia, are you drunk?
Just a tiny bit.
Seems such a shame to let all
that perfectly good wine go to waste.
They opened about $3,000 worth.
Which is the one you were saving
for our 20th anniversary?
Not that we're gonna get there,
at this point.
Darling, you should slow down
a little bit.
Karen, may I get you a glass?
I've got an '82 Petrus,
an '86 Chateau Margaux,
and a '92 screaming Eagle Cab
that'll blow your mind.
- What can I get you?
- This is not some social occasion!
I have come here
to collect my daughter!
Okay, so where is she?
I understand your concern, but...
is profanity really warranted?
- Where the fuck is she?
- The kids are chained in the basement.
She's not as scary as she seems.
She has some anger-management issues.
- Thank you.
- Excellent.
A whole family of sociopaths.
OK, in this case, maybe she's right.
We should just get Becca and leave.
If you like.
I don't see why we can't just sit down
as adults and talk this thing through.
What? Your idea of shitty parenting?
I don't think we should comment,
even though you're absolutely right.
Let's all just try to keep cool heads,
shall we?
The girls are just testing
our boundaries.
's's all perfectly normal
for their age range.
Normal for Chelsea, maybe.
Are you implying
that this is Chelsea's fault?
I'm not implying anything.
I'm just saying it flat out.
- You've got a lot of nerve.
- Now you've angered the dean.
Fuck it, Stacy.
She's right.
This is obviously Chelsea's fault.
Becca doesn't have the gumption
to get in any kind of serious trouble.
- She's a follower.
- Excuse me?
I meant it in a nice way.
You know, teenagers suck.
They're all bloody awful,
Chelsea in particular.
I just hope she makes it
to 17 without getting pregnant.
Honey!
That's not fair.
You're all such fucking hypocrites.
We are the way we are
because you made us this way.
Okay, sweetie, come on.
Let's go home.
I don't want to go home.
I want you all
to listen to me for once!
Sweetie, we're here.
We're listening.
We're all ears.
What do you want to say?
I fucking love this part!
Hi. What took you so long, Runkle?
You know, they've been at it
for a while over there. Sounds good too.
I almost started without you.
I'm just finishing up some dishes.
- I thought I'd let a few things soak.
- Runkle, are you...
Were you crying?
Maybe... a little.
- Yes.
- Oh, please!
Over that?
That's kids' stuff. Ignore it.
Destroy me, Rick Springfield!
Listen to that, will you?
I don't know
how to compete with that!
I only made Marcy squeal like that
when I put the ring on her finger!
Harry Winston?
- Tiffany.
- Oh, Runkle.
You are the saddest sack
I have ever seen!
To you, the glass is
always half empty?
Never half full?
Right now my wife is half
full of Rick Springfield!
That's exactly what I mean. Men.
I mean, you are the biggest bunch
of pussies there ever was.
- You're leaving?
- Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna let you
off the hook this time.
But before I go...
I'm gonna a give you a little tip
on how to get your little wifey back.
Sex is supposed to be about joy,
Runkle.
Pure joy.
And if you've forgotten what
that sounds like...
Don't stop!
Runkle, no! Don't...
Stop! Oh, god!
You are good!
That is perfect!
That is...
perfect!
Collini...
Out.
Come on, take this.
Now, you may wake up
in the middle of the night...
Possibly craving an egg McMuffin.
You should not get off the ride
at that point,
but remain in your seat
with your seatbelt securely fastened.
Okay, sweetie?
Good night, sweetie.
I promise,
everything will be better tomorrow.
Except for your head.
That'll feel much worse.
Stay.
What's up, sweetie?
We don't have to do what she says,
you know.
What who says?
Her.
The enemy.
Your mom is not the enemy.
She loves you.
She wants what's best for you.
Mom doesn't understand.
She never will.
This is it, okay?
I'm not just gonna wake up
one day and be like her...
Six feet tall and beautiful.
You already are beautiful.
Chelsea's
the only friend I've ever had...
the only one
who accepts me for who I really am.
- That is not true.
- It is.
Do you know what it's like
to have no one and nothing...
how totally awful that feels?
Yes, I think I do. I...
Once upon a time, I felt like that.
Now I have you.
Yet, somehow...
I still have nothing.
So...
I guess you're on her side,
like you guys are th t team right now.
We're a team, all right.
Just not a very good one...
not without our captain.
You're right. L.A. Is no place
to raise a daughter or a dad.
We need your guidance.
We need you, mommy dearest...
Really...
Even though sometimes
we may take you for granted and...
throw embarrassing
hissy fits and get drunk...
and generally act like
we don't give a shit about anything.
So you're just both adolescent
girls at heart, right?
Yes, we are, the both of us.
I like you like this.
What, all defeated and shit?
Yes. You're like...
You're like putty in my hands.
- Oh, yeah?
- Really.
Do with me what you will.
- Anything?
- Yeah, anything at all.
You know what I said about bill...
- this morning?
- Yes.
Got ya.
You fucker.