the tudors s03ep01
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync:FRS@ÓîÒâ ×··çÓê¿´²Êºç
???
- Jane.
- Your majesty.
We are come here together
Before god and these witnesses
To join in holy matrimony henry viii,
King of england and france,
Defender of the faith, Supreme
head of the church of england,
And the lady jane seymour.
And if there be any among you
Who may imagine some impediments
As to why they should not be married,
Let them now speak out,
Or forever hold their tongue.
Thank you for my gift,
it's so very beautiful.
I soon trust to thank you for mine.
Shall we join in the dance.
Music.
- I feel guilty.
- Why.
Because sometimes i forget
about how beautiful you are.
I think she'll make him happy.
God's help, we'll all be happy now.
I don't recognize you, my lady.
- Are you new at court?
- Yes, sir.
I am to be a maid to her majesty.
What's your name?
Lady ursula misseldon.
You know who i am?
You're sir francis bryan.
I've heard about you.
What have you heard?
You like to board other man's boats.
I trust that i shall be seeing
A lot more of you, lady misseldon.
Since both the king's daughters Have
been declared illegimate and unfit to rule,
We must trust the queen
to conceive a child quickly.
I still fear, with anne's death,
We've lost a great friend
and a powerful supporter.
If the new queen favors
the catholic religion,
As she is rumored to do,
Then our whole reformation
is surely in jeopardy.
What a suprise, You have
such little faith in the king.
Unless we press ahead the
dissalution of those brothels
And slaughter whores of the conscience.
The monasteries.
In nomine patris,
- et filii,et spiritus sancti. Amen
- Almighty and everlasting god
give onto us the increase of faith
- Hope and charity.???
- and that we may obtain
that which thou dost promise,
Make us to love that which thou dost
command Through jesus christ, our lord.
Amen.
Madam,
if i may, I have a
wedding gift for your majesty.
It once belonged to queen katherine.
Thank you.
His majesty, the king.
Wife.
Husband.
I don't think we need
to proceed in public.
Not this time.
- Majesty.
Yorkshire Northern England
Make way!
Sawley Abbey
Make way, the king's commissioners.
- Be assure everything is accounted for.
- Yes, dr. Frankish.
Dr. Frankish, here's a wealthy madonna.
Here is a fine one.
Coat of silk, ton of
jewels, wealth property.
Well, lady,
Are you stripped now?
Mr. Aske.
Look what they've done, john.
Just look.
It's all cromwell's doing.
Cromwell and that sect of
heretics in london, That bustard.
I'll tell you this mr. Aske, people,
They're no longer willing to stand by,
And watch their faith, And
everything that they care for,
Being stripped away.
I heard just yesterday,
That two of cromwell's commisioners
were attacked In lincolnshire.
And here in yorkshire,
And a man of the commons
Stood up in his own church
And said go away to follow the crosses.
For what they've taken from us,
We can follow them no more.
What am i supposed to do, john?
The commons here,
in lincolnshire, everywhere.
They're prepared to fight,
To save what they love.
But they need captains,
They need clever,
educated man to lead them.
- I'm no leader, john.
- Don't decide now.
We'll call a meeting,
Then decide.
For the love of god.
Take a look at that.
Our commisioners found it in sawly abbey.
How was it done?
See it yourself.
People thought the
saint's bones were alive
Use it work for benedictions.
If they pay a little money
they had to the church
and to rome. How do
our reforms progress?
As you know, my lord.
Parliament has now voted for the suppression
Of all the small monastery houses
And the commisioners are upon
and about their businesses
In nearly every county in england...
much opposition?
Not as much as we might have expected.
Why should we have expected it?
People conceive for themselves
That all these houses should be condemned
For their manifest sin:
carnal and abundable living.
I was told, one anecdote among many.
When our commisioners entered the
london houses of the crossed friars
They found the prayer himself,
in babel disorder.
Both stunned and naked.
They often bribes to go away.
It is true that ordinary people
are so greedy Upon these houses
when they are suppressed.
They scavenge in the night
and day untill nothing is left.
They even take the books, to use
for paper in their houses of easement.
How about the gains of king's treasure?
So far, by my reckoning,We have
already doubled the king's income
And taken in possesion of the monastic
lands Worth many millions of pounds.
Millions?
Yes, mr. Secretary.
Sir edward seymour.
Sir edward,
As the brother of his
majesty's beloved wife, jane,
It is his majesty's
pleasure today to creat you
Viscount beauchamp of hache in somerset,
Also to appoint you a governor of jersy
And chancellor of north wales.
Your majesty, i'm deeply honoured.
And i assure your majesty
that i would labor Unremittingly
in your majesty's interest,
In the hope of repaying the
great trust you've shown in me.
My lord,
here are your letters patent.
May i congratulate you on your elevation.
Mr. Secratary.
Thomas, what are the businesses there?
Your majesty has received
a letter from the emperor,
Congratulating your new marriage.
Since he's no further impediment,
He's very anxious to
become a new accommodation.
Good. What else?
The lady mary has also
written to you, majesty.
What does she want?
She writes, that it is time now
to forget the unhappy past,
She begs to be taken by
your majesty's forgiveness
And humbly beseeches you to remember
That i am a humbled woman and your child.
I'll never take her back.
Not until she first submit herself to me
The subject of his mother's
marriage and surprint.
You'll send the delegation
If she trully wants to
forget the unhappy past,
Then she can stop by signing it.
- Majesty.
- Groom.
Ah, sir francis.
I have some good news for you.
His majesty has agreed to your appointment
As a gentleman of the privy chamber.
I'm sure i know. Thanks for that.
I may have a small job for you, soon.
- Excellency.
- Your majesty.
Come with me.
There's someone i wish to present you to.
Queen jane.
Allow me to introduce his
excellency eustace chapuys,
Ambassador to the emperor
charles v, spain.
Excellency.
I leave you to talk in private.
Your majesty,
may i congratulate on your marriage.
Wish you good health and prosperity.
Although the device of the lady
who proceeded you On the
throne was the most happy.
I have no doubt that it is you,
yourself who will realise that mortal.
Thank you, excellency.
I know that the emperor will
rejoice of Such a virtual ascent
and amiable queen on the throne.
I must tell you it would be impossible
for me to overstate the joy
And happiness which each englsih men
that i have met Have expressed
to me on hearing of your marriage.
Especially, as it is said,
that you're a peace-Maker
who'll be continually Trying to persuade his
majesty to restore his daughter mary to favor.
I promise you, excellency.
That i would continue to
show favor to the lady mary.
And do my best to deserve
the title of peace-Maker
You so gallantly have given me.
If you do so,
i think you'll find madam that Without
the pain of labour, and childbirth,
You'll gain a treasure of the daughter
Who may please you even more
Than your own children by the king.
I can only say again, excellency.
That i will do my best to restore the peace
Between the king and his eldest daughter.
- Ambassordor.
- Madam.
Madam.
You're the first ambassordor she's received.
She is not yet used to see such audiences.
But it is true what they say.
She is kind and amiable,
And much inclined towards peace.
I swear, for example,
She would strive to prevent me
taking part in a foreign war.
If only to avoid the fear
and pain of separation.
If you are on war, your
majesty, against whom?
I was talking hypothetically.
Surely you'll do that
youself, your excellency.
Thanks for coming.
Thank you.
Friends! Friends.
We've come here, so you
can listen to and talk to
This good man, mr. Robert aske.
Now some of you have already known him,
He is the duke of
northampton's legal man.
He's always been honest and fair minded
In these dealings with the commons so...
mr. Aske can speak for himself.
- Ladies and(evening???) gentlmen.
- evening.
Now, tell me what is your want.
Mr aske,
all of our faith days
were abolished and gone.
Should it pleased the king's grace
that we might have our holy days back.
We want our abbeyes restored.
And demand that this
advance of heresy be halted.
We want this new heretic bishop
like cranmer be casted off.
Even cromwell to besurplanted
by man of noble birth.
We hear rumors, mr. Aske,
that new taxes levy's against us
On our cattle, and our christenings
On our marriages, and our births.
Aske,they even destroy our perish
churches and steal our treasures.
All right, gentlemen.
What do you reckon you
can do to stop them.
Mr. Aske,
before our lands,
our good to their houses
Are taken from by the church
commissioners. We'll fight.
And we'll die,
die after full ultimate, mr. Aske.
I know you are angry.
The destruction of the abbeys
is a terrible and criminal thing.
Since that represents by that very
presence and exotic ideal to of all of us.
But gentlemen, this call to arms,
to rebellion against the king's grace
Is something which are my
conscience i cannot agree to.
Since the king is our body and soul.
Then an attack upon him is an attack
upon the commonwealth and upon god himself.
Did you hear that, my mates
The gentry doesn't care for us.
Christ die for the poor.
Do you remember that, mr. Aske?
Lady misseldon, your majesty.
Lady misseldon.
Your majesty.
Do your duties honournably and virtuesly?
And remember, you are
all bound to serve and obey.
Lady rochford.
Your majesty.
Please.
I ask to see you.
I know that the things
have not gone well for you
since your husband was executed.
I have been utterly abandoned.
I feel i was condemed
because of what george did.
Even mr cromwell has
refused to answer my letters.
Nothing was your fault.
George bolyen was his own keeper.
I want you to come back to court.
And i'd like to appoint you
my principal lady in waiting.
I hope you'll accept this position.
Thank you, your majesty.
Well then, lady rochford.
All is well again.
All is mended up.
HUNSDOND HOUSE
HERTFORDSHIRE
Sir francis bryan, my lady.
- Lady mary.
- my lord.
I'm very glad you've come to see me.
I've written a letter congratulating
the king on his marriage.
And begging leave to
wait upon queen jane.
Or do her grace such services
would please her to command me.
I'm afraid, lady mary. I've not
come here to discuss pleasentaries.
His majesty urged
you to sign this.
What is it?
A list of articles.
Recognising the king
as head of the church,
And your mother's marriage
just incestuous and unlawful.
You must also renounce rome
and free acknowledged
of your illegitamacy.
If you not sign,
i'm afraid mr secretary cromwell
can not guarantee your safety.
However much i love
my father, your grace.
And would do anything to please
and satisfy him, i still cannot
risk my mortal soul for
the favor of an unearthly king.
You're an unfitlial daughter.
Since you're not submit
to your father.
He may yet procceed
against you for treason.
No, no he would not.
I cannot believe it.
Listen to me.
I tell you
If you're my daugher,
I would smash your
head against the wall,
until it is soft
as a boiled apple.
Do you understand?
Lady mary.
I've been discussing plans for
your coronation with mr. Holbein.
Have you ever heard
of the centre of Venice?
No, your majesty.
It's a ship.
In which the doge travels out
Into the lagoon every year
to renew its marriage while the sea.
It's a magnificant thing.
The dawn will gold and bronze, statues,
meptune, sea lions and
other fantastic sea creatures...
and i'm going to build it.
And you're going go travel in it,
from greenwich to the city,
Where you'll be crowned,
queen jane of england.
Your majesty,
i... i don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
It will be the most
fabulous coronation
Any english queen has ever had
That i promise you.
Your majesty.
Forgive me.
But i've heard your majesty Make
some proceedings against the lady mary.
With all my heart
i beg you not to.
Are you out of your senses?
Don't talk of such matters again.
Jane,
I have another wedding gift for you.
I hope you like it.
Thank you your majesty.
Oh i love him,
he's so pretty.
Lady misseldon.
Sir francis.
I hope i didn't alarm you.
No sir.
You left me a note that
you wanted to see me?
Yes, i did.
About what.
I was wondering
If you'd like to become my mistress.
Sir, i'm already
engage to be married.
To whom?
Sir robert tavistock.
Can he afford to buy you gifts-
like this?
I didn't think so.
But if it's more important to you
to keep your virgin then
keep it for what it's worth.
And i swear i wouldn't bother you
or your conscience ever again.
I haven't decided yet.
How can i renounce rome?
Or my mother's marriage.
After all of my mother's sufferings.
I understand.
But may i suggest that
you could sign the document.
And then make what is
called a protestation apart.
That is secretly foresware
your submission before witnesses.
Is that not hypocrisy?
Surely the emperor's against
my signing such a document.
And the holy father.
Lady mary,
I must tell you in honesty that-
that the emperor's no longer inclined
to Interfere any further in this matter.
After all,
you are not his subject and-
and since he is seeking
a new alliance with the king,
He would in truth be most reluctant
to offend him in any way.
Then,
i'm on my own?
What if i do not sign it?
It is very possible that
the king would put you to death.
Well,
- Do you...do you not want to read it first?
- No.
Only i ask if you can pray
for absolution for what i've done.
So long as i live,
I will never forgive myself.
CASTLE GANDOLPHO
POPE'S SUMMER RESODEMCE. ITALY
Father pole.
Yes your eminence.
I'm cardinal von waldburg.
How long have you been as
the servant adhere in rome, father pole?
Almost a year your eminence.
I left england when
to became clear that
the king meant to break his obedience
to see of roman, our holy father.
The death of whore anne
boleyn is perhaps providential.
And his holiness prays
that king henry would
grasp this divine opportunity
for reconciliation.
Just one gesture,
Of he sounds to see
of rome, however small,
Will allow him to leave
the threat of excommunication.
Your eminence believe me,
That is something that the faithful
of england are praying for.
My mother, lady salisbury
has written to me,
expressing her hope
that the new queen is
in her heart a true catholic.
Perhaps your mother
could do more than hope.
And perhaps you
yourself father pole
might've considering returning
to england.
In order to influence events there.
You see, father pole,
I know who you really are.
Here is the real danae
She would kindle
your lust even higher.
One touch,
one mere touch of her body,
And your limbs will
melt in the fire.
The necklace suits you,
And you're adored.
YORKSHIRE
In nomine patris, et filii,
et spiritus sancti. Amen.
Ave maria, gratia plena,
dominus tecum.
Your majesty has received
a letter from lady bryan,
Governors to the lady elizabeth.
Apparently the child has
outgrown her clothes.
Lady bryan asks if your majesty
would permit Her to purchase new ones.
Why should i-
i don't believe she is my child.
The whole world knows their father's a traitor
henry norris and their mother was a whore.
What else?
There's letters,
the submission of the lady mary.
You will make arrangements for myself
and the queen to meet with her.
Not here and not publicly.
We will go to her residence.
There're rumors
of plague in the city.
Coronation would have
to be postponed.
Your majesty.
Thomas.
Mr.Richard showed me the figures.
I'm very pleased with you tom.
I will shortly prove it.
Lady rochford.
Yes, your majesty.
Take this to lady bryan,
Tell her to use it buy clothes
for the lady elisabeth.
Yes, madam.
And you must think of
a gift for the lady mary.
I'm looking so forward
to meeting her.
Your majesty is very kind.
Lady rochford,
it's not your fault that
your husband betrayed you.
Nor is it mary's fault or elizabeth's
fault to be born of a king.
Women are much put
upon in this world.
It's my desire as much as
i can to promote their interests.
I must do it quietly.
But i will do it all the same.
And i trust you'd help me.
Yes, your majesty.
What's your name, man.
Charlie, sir.
Charlie roll.
Trade?
Shepherd.
Mr. Secretary cromwell.
Kneel.
Do you know well about it,
charlie?
Yes, captain aske.
We're not rebels,
We're pilgrimages
And we have a pilgrimage to go on.
If you want to join us then you shall
swear to be true to our mighty god.
To christ catholic church.
To our sovereign lord, the king.
And to the commons of this realm,
so help you god.
I do swear.
Wear this badge.
It show the five wounds of christ.
To prove that the commons
will fight in christ cause.
Yes, captain.
God bless you, charlie.
Sir.
Arise, sir thomas cromwell,
Also baron cromwell of wimbledon.
And from this day forth,
Lord privy seal.
Majesty.
Your grace. Your grace.
May i, son?
God be with you lad.
Your majesty is too kind.
Mary,
gifts like these are easy compared
with gifts of a heart.
It gives more pleasure than i can say
to see you reconcile with your father.
Mary.
Your majesty.
Here is enough
for a thousand crowns.
If you need anything
else you need only ask.
Thank you, your majesty.
Father.
Yes, father.
Mary's so sweet and affectional.
She's everything i heard should be.
It seems to be no wonder
she's so marvelous and beloved
for her virtue and goodness
in the hearts of the people.
Your majesty must invite her
to the court, show her off.
Your majesty,
Why were you not speak to me?
Because i'm disappointed.
Why?
I'm disappointed because
you're not yet with child.
Lord,
my lord, my lord.
We have come here in great haste
to tell you that
the great part of the north
as well as part of lincolnshire have risen
in sudden rebellion against his majesty.
There are master
of commons everywhere.
The beacons of rebellion burning
heir own light to cross the hills.
Just four days ago,
While we're collecting
taxes and hectinsome
We were set upon by an angry mob.
They captured one of the
commissioners call nicolas bello.
Pull him down from his hourse
and beat him to death
with their stave.
Among them, my lord,
we saw armed priests.
Urging on these rebellion's names
And cries 'kill them, kill them'.
Then we heard another man,
william lichie,
Who is known to be
your servant mr. Cromwell
have been hanged from a tree.
And what these rebels
said they want?
so far i can tell you,
they want to keep their holy days.
They want monasteries restored
and their church unelested, and...
no more taxed.
I heard they declared
they prospaid with their journey.
They intend to kill you,
my lord crownwell.
454 or 5 bishops,
and chancellor richie
as deviced taken church goods,
and tearing down churches.
Why dont the local gentry intervince
and serpress these traitors and wait.
Surely they want to protect
their lands than holy days.
They tried,
but the rebels then
come back even greater.
Some say, my lord crownwell,
they are not hundreds but thousands religion
rebelions against the king's church reforms
Why did you know,
you are suposed to know
everything that goes on here?
You told me there was little
opposition, on the contrary.
You told me that most people was
glad to see such places dissolved.
You were wrong.
You didn't know anything,
knave.
Sit down, write this.
We take it as greatest unkindness,
that our common unfearist objects
should rise agasint without any grounds.
As for taking the goods from
perish church which is never intended.
Yet even it had been intended.
True subjects would
have not dealt with me,
their princess in such violence.
But would petition me for that purpose.
Now,
i command you rebels to go home,
and say no more.
And remember your allegiance,
you are duly bound to to obey me,
your king.
Both by god's commoments,
and by the law of nature.
(LINCOLNSHIRE)
All commands, stick together
Now it's the time to arise,
for else ever
So forwards,
forwrds to york.
Forwards in pain of death.
Forwards in god's name,
forwards.
Writing to the gentry of yorkshire
Reminding them of their duties
to suppress these traitors,
penalties in not doing so...
so any case,
for suspending the work
of church commisioners,
- until rebels...
- no,
the only way to beat the king's
Authority into the hands
of rude people of north
Is to show them king's intend
to continue with reformation
And correction religion
whatever they say.
What ever they do
Yes
My lord
The rebels have taken lincoln
The rebels flag flies
over city gate
and more of them are
now marching on york.
My god, help us
when i was 5,
my mother and i were taken
accross london, into the tower.
There was a rebelion
against my father.
The cornish rebels
reached the city walls,
And inside everything was
panic, fear.
With no news at all,
nor army of my father.
My mother tried to remain calm,
she was terrified.
So was i,
I was sure we were
both going to be killed.
I'm appointing you command
of the royal forces,
You will arrive north
as soon as possible,
You will find guns and ordnances
of hunger, but don't tarry there
No, your majesty,
i will do all your majesty
commands and more
These rebels are
our traitors, charles.
Full of wretched
and devilish intense.
They must be punished,
For their detestable and unmature sin
of rebellion against their sirvior
Just as my father,
punish the cornishmen.
Charles, what is going on?
- Leave us.
- Yes your grace.
His majesty has charged me
would lead his army
against north rebels.
You are not to worry,
i will have my back enough men
and arms to subdue them.
Easily, i have his majesty's promise.
I hope to god, he keeps it.
I'm happy to accept this charge
Crownwell is being
blamed for everything,
And the rebels is demanding
his head with god's help.
I may will be able to deliver it.
The lord privy seal
I'll despatch duke of
surffolk to the royal army.
If we need to send the second
army to destroy the rebels.
Yes, your mejesty.
Unless they disperse
and said 100 of their ringleaders
to the duke of surffolk
of with halters around their necks.
Then he has our permission to burn
to destroy all their goods.
And make a fearful example
of them to all of our subjects.
Yes, majesty.
If still they do not submit,
mr. Cromwell,
then i promise the utter
destruction of them.
Their wives and their children.
Do you understand me?
i will destroy them all.
And then i'll destroy you, cromwell.
welcome to www.1000fr.com