Previously on Tudors...
In this ippery world you represent
for me all that is innocent.
- Everything that is good.
- What is that?
- Let me see it.
- Ah!
We have come so far. No one is
going to be allowed to destroy us.
Do you understand?
In the question of
legitimizing the Lady Mary,
there remains one great obstacle.
We must find a way around it.
There are some rumors about
the Queen's behavior. It seems,
she entertains men in her room at
night and behaves intimately with them.
It's true that some men came
into the Queen's chambers.
- What are their names?
- The King's groom, Brereton...
- And Sir Henry Norris,
and Mark Smeaton - And?!
Well I saw her hugging
and kissing her brother.
You are both arrested for
High Treason, and having...
- ...carnal knowledge of her
Majesty the Queen. - What?
For the love of Elizabeth!
Have mercy!
You lied to me! You've always lied
to me. You are not what you seem!
This is the warrant for your arrest. You
are charged with committing adultery.
We are come at the King's command
to conduct you to the Tower.
She's humiliated me,
Charles! I hate her!
For such awful adultery, there
should be only one punishment.
The Queen was tried yesterday.
She was sentenced to
death either by burning
or decapitation according
to the King's pleasure.
Most people think I've changed.
At heart, I'm still a humanist.
I promise you that I shall
be remembered eternally.
I have no doubt whatsoever that your
Majesty's reign will always be remembered.
The Tudors
Season 2 -  Episode 10
I will give glory to thee O Lord:
for you have saved me
from injustice, from slanderous
tongues and an unjust king.
My soul shall praise thee
even to the last to my death,
for thou deliveries
those that wait for thee.
ENOUGH!
Make way for Princess Elizabeth.
Make way there.
Make way for her Grace.
- Master Kingston.
- My Lady.
My Lady, I can now tell you
that the King has decreed
that you will not be burned,
but suffer a quicker death
by decapitation.
In his mercy, the King has
also acceded to your plea
to use the services of
the Executioner of Calais,
who is even now on his
way here from Dover.
- When am I to die?
- At nine o'clock.
I am content.
Will you please send
for Archbishop Cranmer,
so he may hear my last confession
and administer Holy Communion?
My Lady.
"To the Emperor. Nephew.
"This day will
bring you, I think,
"news of great satisfaction.
"Let us put all
quarrels behind us.
"And work for an accommodation
that will increase the trade
"and prosperity between us.
"And unite us against that
bastard, the King of France.
"Above all, I love the
prospect of change."
Master Kingston, tell
me, how is the Lady?
Truthfully, in the early
days of her captivity
she often spoke rather wildly.
For example, that it would not
rain until she was released.
But now, according
to her almoner,
preparations for death have
increasingly occupied her thoughts,
and so I believe she
is reconciled to it.
I am glad.
Although...
it grieves that I must
cause her further pain.
My Lady, I am
obliged to tell you
that your marriage to the King
has been declared null and void.
On what grounds?
On the grounds of your close
and forbidden degree of affinity
to another woman known
carnally by the King.
My sister...
- Then my daughter is...?
- Yes.
Elizabeth is to be
declared a bastard.
Madam, I swear to you I will
do everything within my power
to protect and support her,
and keep her always
in the King's good
and kind graces.
Thank you.
And now, since my
time approaches,
I beg your Grace to
hear my confession.
Also, I should like
the Constable present
when I receive the good Lord.
Madam.
My child, do you
have a confession?
Yes.
I confess my
innocence before God.
I solemnly swear,
on the damnation of my soul,
that I have never been
unfaithful to my lord and husband,
nor ever offended with
my body against him.
I do not say that I have
always borne towards him
the humility which I owed him,
considering his kindness and
the great honor he showed me
and the great respect
he always paid me.
I admit, too, that I have
often taken it into my head
to be jealous of him.
But God knows,
and is my witness,
I have not sinned against
him in any other way.
Think not I say this in
the hope to prolong my life.
God has taught me how to die,
and He will strengthen my faith.
As for my brother...
...and those others who
were unjustly condemned,
I would willingly have suffered
many deaths to deliver them,
but since I see it
pleases the King,
I will willingly
accompany them in death.
With this assurance:
that I shall lead an endless
life with them in peace.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Master Kingston.
Please go and make sure to report
my Lady's true and last confession,
so the world will know it.
I will.
Mr. Cranmer, I do not suppose
that, even at this last hour,
the evangelical bishops that we
put in place might intervene for me?
Your Majesty, I...
No, I understand.
How could they? Forgive me.
Gaudeamus omnes in Domino, per
omnia saecula saeculorum. Amen.
Is it done? Is
the harlot dead?
I don't know. But, certainly,
she will be dead before very long.
The Lord is good.
Tell me: why is
she really to die?
They say that her child, Elizabeth,
was not conceived
with the King at all,
but with one of her
countless lovers.
How many lovers was
she supposed to have?
According to Mr. Cromwell,
over a hundred men,
including her brother, Rochford.
But I'm told she also blames
me for what has befallen her,
and holds me
accountable for her doom.
Naturally I am flattered
by the compliment,
since she would have thrown
me to the dogs if she could.
Tell me about this other Lady,
this Jane Seymour?
I have been told in confidence
that she is of our faith,
and that the King loves her,
and means to marry her.
And that she means to restore
your grace to the succession.
And Elizabeth will
become a bastard now?
- As I have been a bastard?
- Yes, Princess.
The brat is now
officially a bastard.
Tell them to ready the horses.
- But tell no one of our destination.
- Yes, Majesty.
To every thing
there is a season,
and a time to every
purpose under heaven.
A time to be born,
and a time to die.
A time to plant and a time to
pluck up that which is planted.
A time to weep,
and a time to laugh.
A time to cast away stones,
and a time to gather
stones together.
A time to mourn,
and a time to dance.
That which hath been is now.
And that which is to
be has already been...
A time to get,
and a time to lose.
A time to keep,
and a time to cast away.
A time to rend,
and a time to sew.
A time to keep silence,
and a time to speak.
I said in my heart, God shall judge
the righteous and the wicked,
for there is a time for
every purpose under the sun.
Am I to go now? I thought...
My Lady, forgive me...
The executioner has been
delayed on the road from Dover
and your execution is
postponed until twelve o'clock.
I wanted to tell you,
in good time, in case...
Master Kingston.
I hear you say I will
not die before noon,
and I'm sorry for it,
for I thought to be dead by
that time, and past my pain.
Madam, there will be no pain.
The blow will be so subtle.
Yes, I heard the
executioner was very good.
And in any case,
I have only a little neck.
- Edward!
- Ah!
- Ha!
Father?
Sir?
- HA!
- Ah!
My God.
Edward, this is not a toy.
Yes, sir.
So, have you ever
killed someone?
Yes. In battle.
What did it feel like?
He was my enemy.
I didn't care.
I would really like
to see someone die.
Can I go to the
execution with you?
How much did they
charge for the scaffold?
Twenty- three pounds, six shillings
and eight pence, Mr. Secretary.
Daylight robbery.
And what is the Headsman to
be paid, if he ever arrives?
Fifteen pounds.
Fifteen pounds?
For one stroke?
My God, he makes
a damn good living!
Allons, vas- y. Allons- y.
On y va. Viens!
-  Well, is it done?
- Uh...
Is it?
No, your Majesty.
Uh... Unfortunately,
we must postpone
the execution again.
- What?
- The Executioner was delayed.
Then you fetch somebody
else! Do you hear?
Fetch back the axman
who did the others!
He was good enough wasn't he?
He didn't botch the thing.
Your Majesty made a promise.
Why should I care about my
promises to that whore?!
Your Majesty's promise is
public knowledge. That is all...
I still don't care!
I ordered you to get someone
else! I want her dead!
I want it over with! Finished!
Go and do it or by God's
blood you will join her!
I said!
Postpone it!
Majesty.
Let's go.
Master Kingston, I am ready.
My Lady, you must
forgive me once again.
But the Executioner
is still not arrived.
What do you say?
Madam, your execution is put off
until nine o'clock tomorrow morning.
No...
No. It cannot be.
It is not that I
desire death, but I...
I thought myself prepared
to die... I was prepared.
I fear... I fear that of further
delay it may weaken my resolve.
Please... If it...
If it were possible...
No, Madam. It is the
King's express command.
No! Wait! Perhaps
I'm not meant to die.
These postponements
they mean something.
Perhaps the King
is testing me.
I'll be sent to a nunnery.
Hiya! Whou!
I am sure you
are aware, Sir John,
that my marriage has been
declared null and void.
I have been made aware of the
circumstances, your Majesty.
And, like everyone else,
I have been shocked
and utterly amazed
by what I've heard.
I am grateful.
But I must tell you...
The Privy Council,
despite these recent hurts,
have pleaded with me to venture
once more into matrimony,
in the hope that my bride
will produce a legitimate heir.
I think you know my choice
has fallen upon your daughter.
I do.
Tomorrow you will all travel
by barge to Hampton Court,
where our betrothal
will be announced.
I swear to you, Sir John, from tomorrow,
everything will be different.
We will be young and
merry as we used to be.
- Lady Jane.
- Your Majesty.
Lady Jane!
I won't wear it!
You can't make me!
No! No! I'm not going!
Lady Elizabeth, you must do
as you are told! Now hush!
Or I will hit you.
Don't look like that, girl!
We are ordered to remove the child so
she can be kept out of sight of the King.
- Little Princess.
- She is no longer a Princess.
She is a bastard. And Master Cromwell
has asked for her accounts to be settled.
Also in respect of necessities
provided for her mother in the Tower.
You mean, the child should pay
for her mother's imprisonment?
Yes. Out of the money the
King pays for her household.
Exactly.
The world is a
slippery place, my Lady.
If you would take my advice,
for what it's worth,
find a rich man to marry who is too
stupid to know anything about politics.
Then, perhaps, unless you die
in childbirth, which is likely,
or the plague, which
is almost inevitable...
then you will be happy.
What would you like to
talk about, sweetheart?
If your Majesty would allow, I should
like to talk about your daughter Mary.
When I am Queen I would hope to
see her reinstated as heir apparent.
Jane, you're a fool to hope so.
You ought to solicit
the advancement
of the children we're going
to have, not any others.
But, Your Majesty, I thought
I was asking not so much
for the good of others, as
for the good, of the repose
and tranquility of yourself,
as well as the children
we may have ourselves.
And for the tranquility
of your Majesty's kingdom.
Forgive me.
It's just that I so much
want a new beginning.
A renaissance.
Sometimes it is hard to be reminded
of things. Do you understand?
You are so pure.
I just don't want you to be affected
by things that have gone before.
May I kiss you, Jane?
Aren't you the King of England?
Everything will change for her.
That kiss is her destiny,
and her fortune.
And ours.
You know, when I was a girl, I served
at the court of Margaret of Austria.
It was a wonderful time.
Pageants and dances.
So many dances.
I once appeared as the
Queen of the Amazons,
with a naked sword in my hand,
and a crimson headdress
with a great plume!
But Margaret was wise, too.
She said to us: "Trust in
those who offer you service,
"and in the end, my maidens,
"you will find
yourself in the ranks
of those who have
been deceived."
Am I...
Am I to be tried?
No. You are to be released.
But, his Majesty commands,
that since you no longer
enjoy his trust or affection,
you are to be
stripped forthwith
of all your official
posts and titles.
You will no longer serve
on the Privy Council,
you will relinquish the
role of Lord Privy Seal,
and all its privileges.
His Majesty also desires
that you leave court.
And that you never show
yourself in his presence again
On pain of death.
So I am to keep my earldom?
Did you watch your son die?
What about your daughter?
Will you watch her suffer?
Will you watch her die?
Tell me, Boleyn:
was it all worth it?
Halt!
Do see this?
Do you know what this is?
It's the Fountain of Youth.
Look!
I am re- born!
This way, Monsieur.
I deeply regret
you were delayed.
May I see it?
Si vous voulez, Monsieur.
It's beautiful, no?
The execution is
ordered for nine o'clock.
You will be awoken two hours before,
in order for you to have breakfast.
- So, if that is all?
- No, Monsieur.
I must say a few words.
The lady must not to be
restrained in any way.
But, it is very
important that the lady
doesn't look back like this
for the fear of the sword.
Alors first, I hide the
sword so she cannot see it.
It is totally normal
they want to look around
and see where your death
come from. No? Ha! Ha!
So, when she has finished her
prayers, and is ready to go...
I say, to boy in front
of her, "Fetch my sword".
Of course the
lady looks at man.
And this is just the
perfect angle for me.
When she looks at man.
Then I strike.
Then, "Chuck!"
You understand?
I think so, yes.
Oh, it's very quick.
She feel no pain.
Monsieur?
You will be not disappointed.
I'm sure.
Thou knowest whether
I deserve this death.
Not my will O Lord,
but thine be done.
I will give glory to thy name,
for thou art my help
and my protection.
Thou hast protected
me and preserved me...
Anne!
He'll get you!
Madam, the hour approaches,
you must make ready.
Acquit yourself of your charge,
for I have been long prepared.
The King asks that
you take this purse.
It has twenty pounds in it,
to pay the headsman
for his services
and distribute
alms to the poor.
Thank you.
Will you and your
ladies follow me.
Master Kingston, I pray
you not to give the signal
for my death until I have spoken
what I have the mind to speak.
Madam.
Good Christian people,
I have come here to die,
according to the law,
and thus yield myself to
the will of the King, my lord.
Long live the King!
And if, in my life, I ever
did offend the King's Grace,
then surely with my
death I do now atone...
I pray and beseech you all,
to pray for the
life of the King.
God save the King!
My sovereign lord and yours,
who is one of the best princes
on the face of the earth,
who has always
treated me so well,
wherefore I submit to
death with a good will,
humbly asking pardon
of all the world.
If anyone should
take up my case,
I ask them only
to judge it kindly.
Thank you... Thank you.
Madame, forgive me
for what I must do.
Gladly.
And here is your purse.
Thus I take my
leave of the world...
- ...and of you.
- Bless you...
And I heartily desire
you all to pray for me.
Lord have mercy on you.
The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not be in want.
He makes me lie down
in green pastures.
He leads me beside
quiet waters...
Jesus, receive my soul.
O Lord God, have
pity on my soul.
To Christ I commend my soul.
Jesus Christ receive my soul!
O Lord God have pity on my soul.
Jesus receive my soul.
O God have pity on
my soul, Jesus Christ.
O Lord God have
pity on my soul.
Jesus Christ receive my soul.
Thank you.
Christ receive my soul.
Jesus Christ receive my soul.
O Lord God have
pity on my soul.
To Christ I commend myself.
Jesus receive my soul.
O Lord God have pity on my soul.
To Christ I commend myself.
Boy! Fetch my sword!
Make way for the
King's household.
Make way.
Make way for the
King's household.
May the Lord Jesus
be drink and food.