Previously...
The annulment of my marriage
must be declared immediately.
The King of England asks your approval
to appoint an Archbishop of Canterbury.
- What is the name of the candidate?
- Thomas Cranmer, a nobody.
What harm can a nobody inflict
on our Holy Church?
That the union between
King Henry of England
and Katherine of Aragon
is declared null and void.
Regal supremacy over our Holy Church
would represent a tearing asunder
of the seamless coat of Christ.
There are rumours that
the King has married Anne
and that she's already with child.
I want the people to love
their new Queen. And if I can love her,
why shouldn't they?
If you succeed
in killing the King's whore,
you will be the beloved of God,
and of the faithful people of England.
- Unfortunately, Holy Father, I failed.
- Who knows, my son?
God works in mysterious ways.
I come to offer my resignation
from my post as Chancellor.
I can't. Not now, while the baby...
Exquisite, isn't she?
Lady Eleanor Luke.
Shall I talk to her on your behalf?
I fear for the Queen. Anne Boleyn
hates her. And her daughter, too.
Your mother must now accept
the title of Dowager Princess,
just as you have no right
to call yourself Princess.
You are forbidden to communicate
with your mother from this day forward.
The Pope threatens to excommunicate me
if I do not return to Katherine.
He's too late.
I want you to organise jousts,
banquets and masques
to celebrate the birth of my son.
Your Majesty has given birth
to a very healthy baby girl.
I'm so sorry.
[ www.seriessub.com ]
Presente:
THE TUDORS
Season 2 - Episode 4
Transcript: www.yyets.net
Synchronisation VO: dmbmh
[ www.seriessub.com ]
Abrenuntias satanae
(Do you renounce Satan)
Abrenuntio.
(I do renounce him.)
Ego te baptizo,
(I baptize you)
in nomine Patris
(in the name of the Father, )
et Filii,
(and of the Son)
et Spiritus Sancti.
(and of the Holy Spirit)
Vade in pace,
(Go in peace)
et Dominus vobiscum.
(and the Lord be with you.)
Amen.
God, of infinite goodness,
send prosperous life and long
to the high and mighty
Princess of England,
Elizabeth!
There can be no question
of illegitimacy.
You will prepare a bill
to put before Parliament.
It will state that the succession
is now firmly vested in our children...
and no others.
I shall do as Your Majesty commands.
I am mindful, Mr. Cromwell,
that there are some people
some wrong-headed, some biased people
who are still unwilling
to accept the validity of my marriage.
In view of that, I think...
some sanction
should be made against them.
Everyone will be given their opportunity
to demonstrate their loyalty.
I am told that the Lady
is much dismayed
at having given birth to a daughter
and not the son she promised.
To my mind, it is sure proof
that God has abandoned her.
How is my mother, the Queen?
Alas, I cannot visit or speak to her.
I have little communications
with her ladies,
and they tell me she is still strong...
but always begs the King, your father,
of his mercy, to be allowed to see you.
I am sure His Majesty
will one day relent,
for I think...
I believe with all my heart
that he still loves and cares for me.
I am sure that he does.
Bishop Tunstall.
Sir Thomas.
Thank you.
To what do I owe this honour?
We have known each other
a long time, Sir Thomas.
But now you have retired
from public life
and I never see you.
Naturally I was concerned
about your welfare.
I am very well, thank you.
But I am...
I am exorcised by the fact
that one of our old acquaintances
is still under house arrest.
You mean Bishop Fisher?
Yes, the outcome is regrettable.
The "outcome" of what?
His intransigence.
I see.
Tell me,
has the King sent you here to see me?
His Majesty wondered
why you did not attend
the Queen's Coronation,
as you were invited to do.
Well...
in answer to that, let me...
let me show my poor mind to you.
There's a story
about the Emperor Tiberius.
He had enacted a law which exacted death
for a certain crime... unless
the offender was a virgin.
Now, when a virgin eventually
appeared on the charge,
the Emperor didn't know exactly
how to proceed,
so one of his council
proposed the perfect solution:
Let her first be deflowered,
so she then can be
... devoured.
There are some...
and no, I won't name them...
who first procure you
for the coronation,
next to preach at it,
and then to write books defending it.
Thus they deflower you,
and will not fail soon afterwards to
... devour you.
But they shall never deflower me.
That was beautiful.
Do you play?
All the time.
- Majesty.
- Lady Eleanor.
Never mind.
More like this. Watch.
Fingers like so.
Don't squeeze the arrow.
Draw...
and release.
I'll never do that.
Yes, you will.
Your Grace. I have it.
- Mr. Secretary.
- Your Grace.
- And your son?
- Yes.
I'm teaching him to sport
before I get too old for it.
- Do you shoot, Cromwell?
- Sometimes, Your Grace.
My Lord.
Shall we walk?
What does the King want?
His Majesty would like
to see you back at court.
With your wife.
He misses Your Grace's company.
And?
His Majesty is aware
that you favour the Imperialist cause
you say so openly in Council
and have, perhaps, a great sympathy
for the Dowager Princess?
Don't you?
Actually, I do.
I'm not heartless,
whatever some people think.
Quite the contrary.
But I serve the King.
His Majesty intends
to vest the succession
with the children he will have
with Queen Anne.
A bill will go before Parliament.
He wants to know
if he'll have your support.
Hungry?
What are you doing?
Your Majesty.
May I not feed her from my own breast?
Queens don't do that...
especially not for a daughter.
Give her back to her wet-nurse.
The Princess will shortly be given
her own establishment at Hatfield.
Among others, the Lady Mary
will attend and wait on her.
Katherine's daughter?
Yes.
It is well that she knows her new place.
Secretary Cromwell is arranging it.
I will still give you a son.
Come soon, my darling,
to my hot bed.
- Ladies.
- Majesty.
Alice, children...
My dear family,
I have something to say to you.
My income is now
so greatly reduced, that...
that we can no longer go on living
as we are accustomed.
I am no longer the recipient
of the King's bounty.
And so,
I must live frugally
and... reduce my household.
Those of you who can must
live in your own houses
and eat at your own tables.
- But, Father...
- No. Come on.
Things inevitably must change.
You can't all be supported forever.
Life is not like that.
Real life is raw
and difficult.
And you must face up to that fact.
If not to even worse things.
Come on. Let us eat.
Give me a little wine, please.
Yes, mother.
The Lady Mary, Lady Bryan.
Lady Mary.
Welcome to Hatfield, your new home.
I am Lady Margaret Bryan,
the Princess's Governess.
These other Ladies, are also here
to attend the Princess.
Lady Mary, may I present you
to her Highness the Princess Elizabeth.
You will be shown to your room.
You will begin your duties
in the mornings, after prayers.
I shall say my prayers alone.
sThis is your room, my Lady.
Christmas.
Why is it that as you get older,
it always seems to be Christmas?
Of course, it is always
Christmas for you, isn't it, my Lord?
A Baron in your own right now,
and some new titles.
Remind me.
Master of Buckhounds.
Lord Warden of the Cinque Ports.
Was there not another one?
Master of the Bedlam Hospital
for the insane?
Yes.
Do you plan to visit it?
I don't mean as an inmate.
I read one of your satires
about life here at court.
If I were you,
I'd be more careful about poking fun
at those who have the power to hurt you.
That's just friendly advice.
Here, my love.
I have a gift for you.
It's fantastic!
Who made this?
Master Holbein.
The man's a genius.
As are you,
my beautiful Queen.
Happy Christmas.
I could still do it.
- I could find a way to poison her.
- No!
- But I thought that was...
- It would be blamed on my master.
At the moment, he doesn't need that.
He has a war with the Turks
to contend with.
- But why should anyone ever know?
- Don't be stupid, Brereton.
They would find you and torture you,
- and you would tell them everything.
- No, I wouldn't.
I'd die a martyr's death.
You've never seen a man being tortured.
Now do you understand?
You don't act alone.
Charles.
- Happy Christmas.
- And to Your Majesty.
- I have a gift for you.
- Where is it?
You'll have to wait
the new session of Parliament.
For it's my vote.
How could I have ever doubted you?
Eleanor Luke.
You see the way the King looks at her?
She's his mistress.
Get rid of her.
Mary. Majesty.
We must find you a new husband.
I have another gift for you.
I am with child again.
Majesty, Councillors...
here is the new Act,
the Act of Succession,
which I am commanded to present shortly
to the Houses of Parliament.
The Act nominates the children born
of His Majesty and Queen Anne
as first rightful heirs.
By so doing, it protects
the nation from the divisions
it has suffered in the past,
when several different titles
have pretended to the throne.
The Act warns
that anyone saying or writing
anything to the prejudice or slander
of the lawful matrimony between the King
and his most dear
and entirely beloved wife Queen Anne,
or against his heirs,
would be guilty of high treason,
for which the penalty is death,
and forfeiture of goods to the Crown.
"The new Act requires
all the King's subjects,
"if so commanded, to swear an oath
"that they shall truly, firmly,
constantly, without fraud and guile,
"observe, fulfil, maintain,
defend and keep
"the whole contents
and effect of the Bill."
This oath will also require recognition
of the King's supremacy in all matters,
spiritual and temporal.
Those who refuse to take it...
will be accounted guilty of treason
and sent to prison.
That is all well done, Mr. Secretary.
I am pleased.
So it must be sworn by oath, after all.
God save us.
Et unam sanctam
catholicam
et apostolicam ecclesian.
In nomine Patris et Fillii
et Spiritu Sancti.
Amen.
Does the King remain obdurate?
Yes, Holy Father.
He refuses to listen to advice,
and he forces all true believers
to perjure their immortal souls.
How so?
They must all swear an oath
that the King is head
of the English church.
Those who refuse are put in prison.
Like our brother in Christ,
Bishop Fisher.
Yes, Holy Father.
This is unacceptable.
The shepherd cannot stand idly by
while the wolf enters the fold
and threatens his flock.
I have decided
to make Fisher a Cardinal.
You will send his hat to England.
Let's see if the King is still prepared
to prosecute and torture
a Prince of the Church.
Mistress Bryan.
A very good morning to you.
I'm on Progress.
I've come to see my daughter.
How is she?
She is a credit to Your Majesty
in every way.
My Elizabeth.
Who knows, Mistress Bryan,
perhaps one day this little girl
will preside over empires.
Please forgive me...
I don't have much time.
Thank you
for all your care toward
our beloved Princess.
Your Majesty.
Lady Eleanor.
My Lord.
How did you suppose
no one would find out your secret?
- I...
- Your chamber was searched today.
- My Lord...?
- The jewels were found.
You did not hide them well enough.
- Jewels...? I don't...
- Her Majesty's jewels.
The ones you stole.
- It's not true!
- And I say it is true.
And if your crimes were ever reported,
who do you suppose would believe you?
After all,
Lady Eleanor,
no one could accuse you
of being innocent...
could they?
What am I to do?
Leave court.
Go back to your family.
See if they will have you.
Cousin Madge!
Lady Sheldon, what are you reading?
Nothing, my Lady.
Just some... poetry.
By Sir Thomas Wyatt.
Give it here.
You should not be wasting
your time on such trifles.
If you must read, when you are supposed
to be attending on me,
then you should read that book!
You will learn
a great deal more from it,
perhaps even some wisdom.
Yes, Madam.
Now go about your business.
The Earl of Wiltshire, Your Majesty.
Papa.
Your Majesty.
You look well.
And I believe you're already showing.
A little.
How was your trip to Paris?
It was...
King Francis is not
the easiest man to deal with.
He sends you wedding presents,
but he can't officially
recognize you as Queen.
As long as Katherine remains alive.
How is the King?
He must be pleased at your condition.
He is.
But...?
Everything is fine.
But when I was last with child,
the King took a mistress.
And now...
now I fear he will take another,
since I must be careful
for the sake of the child
and not let him enjoy
his conjugal rights.
It is natural for a man,
when his wife is big with child
and not willing to lie with him, to...
find some temporary
consolation... elsewhere.
And for Kings,
it is properly expected.
Sweetheart,
listen to me.
The danger to you, and to us,
is not that the King takes a mistress...
but that he takes the wrong one.
Someone we can't control,
or who would seek to control the King.
But... if you suppose
the King is sure to take a mistress,
then make sure
she is your... choice,
and not... his.
I must make my report to the King.
I'll see you later.
- Mr. Secretary.
- Reverend Fisher.
I just came to see
if you were being well treated.
As to that, my... aged stomach
cannot cope with the rank food
the jailor brings.
But that is nothing, since it pertains
to my body and not my soul.
You have not taken the Oath.
No.
Why not?
Do you refuse to accept that
the King's marriage is proper and legal?
I believe His Majesty thinks it so.
But you don't?
No.
I believe what I have always believed...
that the King's marriage
to Queen Katherine is still valid,
and can be undone
by no man, not even...
Archbishop Cranmer.
And...
do you dispute that the King is
Supreme Head of the Church in England?
Yes, I do. Most emphatically.
The King our Sovereign Lord
is not the Supreme Head on earth
of the Church of England.
Tell me,
how is Sir Thomas More?
Jailor!
I will...
see if the quality of your food
can be improved.
Thank you.
Why did you get rid of Lady Eleanor?
She stole something precious from me.
- Are you sure she stole it?
- Yes.
I had the evidence. I had no choice.
I hope Your Majesty is not
too disappointed?
In any case,
I have something for you.
Your Majesty.
Elizabeth.
Thank you.
What's this?
Majesty, there are a number
of small monastic institutions
I have had cause to investigate.
The monks there refuse to take the Oath.
They'd rather serve
the Vicar of Rome than you.
This is a bill for their dissolution.
The very considerable wealth
of these houses
will thus be transferred
to Your Majesty's exchequer.
Well?
Majesty, I have just heard
that the Pope intends
to make Reverend Fisher a Cardinal.
Apparently he has already
dispatched a Cardinal's hat.
Then Fisher will have to wear it
upon his shoulders!
For by the time it gets here,
he won't have a head to put it on!
And what of More?
I want to know!
Will he take the oath?
How is she? Does she feed well?
She's good in every way, Majesty.
And hardly cries at all,
as if she already knows
that she's a Princess.
I love you, Elizabeth.
I love you with all my heart
and I bid you never forget it.
Your Majesty.
Before I leave, I wish to say
something to the Lady Mary.
Lady Mary...
Lady Mary, I am here in kindness.
I would welcome you back to court,
and reconcile you with your father,
if you will only accept me as Queen.
I recognize no Queen but my mother.
But if the King's mistress
would intercede
with the King on my behalf...
then I would be grateful.
Sir Thomas More.
Sir Thomas.
Mr. Secretary.
Please be seated.
This is but an informal occasion.
A little ale, perhaps?
No, thank you.
I'm sure we both know the object
which has brought us together.
It is very widely rumoured, Sir Thomas,
that you will refuse to take
the Oath of Succession.
I say this to you
very openly and sincerely,
that I wish no harm
to come to a great man
who has for years enjoyed and deserved
His Majesty's good graces.
I would rather lose my own son
than see any hurt come to you.
May I ask your opinion
of the King's new marriage?
I have no opinion.
I neither murmur at it,
nor dispute upon it.
I never did...
and never will.
Then what of His Majesty's claim
to Supremacy
over the Church in England?
I was unsure about this matter...
until I re-read
His Majesty's own pamphlet:
the "Assertio septum Sacramentorum."
In fact, I have...
I have a copy of it here.
Of course, in the pamphlet,
the King asserts
the divine origin of the papacy.
The Pope's supremacy descends directly
from the Rock of St. Peter.
I think you'll find
His Majesty's arguments are as...
persuasive and powerful now
as they were when he first wrote them.
Will you take the Oath?
I need hardly remind you
of the consequences of not doing so.
Mr. Secretary,
I am the King's loyal subject.
I say no harm,
I think no harm,
but I wish everybody good.
And if this be not enough
to keep a man alive, in good faith,
- I long not to live.
- Sir Thomas...
You should know that
the King himself has no mind
to coerce you.
He simply asks you to relent
and condescend to his request
that you take the Oath.
Mr. Cromwell, please impart to the King
my utter faithfulness,
truthfulness, and loyalty to him.
Cousin Madge.
Yes, Madam?
Come and talk to me.
I suppose you have many admirers?
Yes,
but I always remember
what Your Majesty told us,
about not being lewd
and setting a standard.
I'm sure you do.
But would it surprise you to learn
that one of your admirers
is the King?
- It's not true!
- It is true.
Now, would it surprise you even more
if I told you that
you would have my blessing
to become his mistress?
- Madam!
- While I am with child,
His Majesty needs to be able to lie
with another woman.
He is a passionate man.
But she must be someone I can trust.
Whose family I can trust,
like yours.
After all,
we are family.
And you are reformers.
Yes, Your Majesty.
We all gladly took the oath.
And now will you gladly
take the King to your bed?
His Excellency, the Imperial Ambassador.
- Excellency.
- Your Majesty.
Forgive me, but I come here
upon a mission of mercy.
- Mercy?
- Very much so.
Your daughter, the Lady Mary,
has fallen ill,
even to the concern of her doctors.
I have a letter written by her mother.
She would like to nurse her child.
She writes... if I may?
"A little comfort and mirth with me
would be a half health to her."
"I could care for her with my own hands
"and put her in my own bed
"and watch with her when needful."
I will send my personal physician
to examine and help her.
But I cannot allow Mary
and her mother to be together.
But, Your Majesty... it is just the cry
- of any mother for any daughter.
- But that's just it!
They are not just
any mother or daughter.
Do you not suppose
they would conspire to plot against me?
- I cannot believe it.
- Of course you can believe it!
You know it happens.
And that sometimes illness
is used for political purpose.
Do you not believe that Katherine
wants Mary to be Queen above all else?
Mr. Chapuys,
Lady Katherine is a very proud
stubborn woman
of very great and high courage.
She could muster an army, take the field
and wage a war against me
as fierce as any her mother Isabella
ever waged in Spain.
Is that not true?
I've been handed a summons
to appear at Lambeth Palace
to take the oath.
I imagine I shall be
imprisoned afterwards.
- No!
- Father!
You must be good to each other
and to everyone else.
Or, if you cannot be good,
be the least bad you can be.
Darling, no...
Ah! Lady Sheldon.
- Where's the Queen?
- Your Majesty,
the Queen is feeling indisposed
and asks you to forgive her
not riding this morning.
Of course.
She...
She wondered if Your Majesty
would be pleased if...
if I took her place.
Riding, I mean.
If the Queen gives her permission,
then why not?
Lady Sheldon.
What's your name, Lady Sheldon?
Margaret, Your Majesty.
Though people call me Madge.
Then I shall call you Madge,
if you'll allow me?
Of course, Your Majesty.
Sir Thomas.
Are you now ready to swear the oath?
May I see it?
Thank you.
Well?
I don't mean to put at fault
this oath or its makers
or any man who swears to it.
And I will never condemn
the conscience of any other man.
But for myself, in good faith,
my own conscience
so moves me that I will swear
to the validity of the succession,
yet not the rest of it,
without jeopardizing my soul
to perpetual damnation.
We are very sorry to hear you say this.
You are almost the first to refuse it
and your refusal will cause
the King's highness to be both
indignant and suspicious of you.
Here are all the members
of the Commons and the Lords
who have sworn to take the oath.
- The clergy too.
- I myself cannot swear.
But I do not blame any other man
who has sworn.
Sir Thomas, we have come
to the conclusion
that, far from being a true and loyal
servant to His Majesty,
there never was a servant so villainous,
so traitorous to his prince as you.
If you refuse to take the oath,
not only will you be imprisoned,
but the most horrid things imaginable
will be done to you.
My Lords, these threats
are for children, not for me.
Do you deny...
that you bullied and persuaded the King,
against his conscience,
to write this pamphlet against Luther?
Of course I deny it.
In the first place I never ask anyone,
be he ever so high or so low,
to act against his conscience.
And secondly,
I remember it was His Majesty
who rather persuaded me
of the paramount importance
of the papacy.
I ask you a final time,
before the awful penalties
are exacted upon you.
Why will you not swear?
Madge!
What? Madge!
I don't know. It's funny.
Madge.
I like your dimples
when you laugh, Madge.
Madge.
Your Majesty.
Come here.
Let me...
examine your dimples
a little more closely.
Sir Thomas.
Thank you.
Oh, and... your Highness might like
to know that the Reverend Fisher
is lodged in the room down below.
Good day to you, sir.
Synchronisation VO: dmbmh
[ www.seriessub.com ]