The Henrys Team
La Fabrique
www.seriessub.com
aspirat, od_Od, Funi, HelenScott, karim,
kiry, khillaree, neuceu, mytom, olaola.
Cheerleader: Blek L'Andouille.
Guest Star: ricorod.
- Master Holbein!
- My Lord.
I've... I've a commission for you.
The Duke of Cleves has given
you permission
to paint his daughter, Anne.
You should leave at once.
There're so many pressing things and
you've time to talk about a painting?
This is no ordinary painting,
A great many things hang upon it.
To that effect, however
you should find the lady,
whatever her actual appearance,
I pray you use your art and give her
at least a pleasing countent
Even if she is as ugly as sin?
I truly hope she is not so.
But still, you wish me,
if necessary to lie?
Surely, all art is a lie,
master Holbein.
My Lords, since the signing
of the Treaty of Toledo
Between the French king
and the Emperor
There've been vital
and unavoidable signs
of their mutual preparations for war
Against this realm.
You know in this how much they've
been urged on by the Vicar of Rome
and now we hear competent
reports of fleets
Gathering at Antwerp and Bologna.
And of an army of the Netherlands.
Furthermore, the French and Imperial
ambassadors
Have been recalled by their masters.
My Lords,
we've not been idle
under such provocations
Defence forces have been mastered
and beacon set along the coast
for warning.
Work has also begun building
artillery forts facing
the English Channel.
In the North, we have strengthen
our borders against the Scots.
And His Majesty's fleet warships
has been provisioned.
Foreign vessels are being forbidden
to leave these shores
without Royal permission.
My Lords.
How can anyone doubt that the
Pope, that pestilent idol,
that enemy of truth,
the usurper of all princes,
is now conspiring
to corrupt England's religion
and strip her of her wealth.
My Lords, at such a time,
it is good for me to be amongst
my people.
I'll visit all the places
where the barricades
and the defences
of the realm are being built
for the encouragement of my troops.
And to my enemies' terror.
My Lords.
Your Majesty.
It seems we are threatened
from everywhere, Sir Francis.
Scotland, Spain, the Low Countries.
We are like a morsel among
these choppers.
I'll tell you something else.
According to Cromwell's agents,
Just two weeks ago, Cardinal Pole
left Rome in a secret mission.
Shall we be after him again? As soon
as we've more news of his whereabouts,
we shall.
Sharpen your knives.
Your Grace.
- My Lord.
- Can we talk?
- In private?
- Sometime. Not now.
Mr. Holbein has sent this portrait
of Anne de Cleves,
your Majesty.
She is pleasing.
Has our ambassador been able
to see her properly?
Yes, Sir John has written to me in
great praise of the princesses person.
He writes, "she's incomparable
and excels the Duchess of Milan
as the golden sun excels
the silver moon".
Majesty,
if I may.
Marriage to the Duchess of Milan
is no longer an option.
Nor since the Emperor and the French
are in league against us.
Or any of the French women.
Your Majesty is beset by enemies.
Marriage to Anne of Cleves
would bring with it the military
and financial support
of the Protestant League.
What?
- What's it?
- Enemy ships,
flying the Black Eagle.
Give it a look.
It's appeared on the ships.
For Lord's sake!
Light the beacon!
Hurry!
Light it!
God save us!
Duke William,
his Majesty is much taken
by the portrait of your sister, Anne.
He encourages you to send ambassadors
to England
to conclude the negociations
including the question of your
sister's dowry and so on.
Once again,
his Majesty is premature.
But surely, your highness...
I think the king should come to me
publicly
And on bended knee
to beg for my sister's hand.
And for the protection
of the League.
In any case,
Anne was already promised, formerly
to the Duke of Lorraine's son.
And I don't see how I can break
that promise
- or keep my honor.
- Your highness,
if true, this is most unexpected
and unwelcome news.
That is because you expected
from the start to have your way
with Cleves and my sister.
But my country is not a brothel
and my sister is not a whore.
Well...
If your master truly desires
to have an alliance,
then he must demonstrate his respect
for my country...
and put a better price
on my sister's virginity.
Make way!
Thank you.
Come on.
Message for His Majesty!
Majesty.
From Sir Thomas Chaining,
warden of the Sank Ports.
Your Majesty, Lords of the Council,
this morning we counted
68 Imperial ships in the Channel.
I sent out two ships and afterwards
my bowmen
were taken aboard
the Imperial flagship
and shown every courtesy
by the Admiral.
He said his fleet was bound
for Spain,
and not England.
That he meant no harm to either us
or our coast.
If they doubt this word,
they ought to see
How poorly armed the ships were.
Quick more like merchantmen,
That hold both the provisions for
Emperor's voyage to Constantinople.
The Imperial ambassador,
your majesty.
I thought you'd been recalled.
There was some talk, your majesty.
But I had no desire to leave here,
Not that I think
there was any cause.
Of course.
But your master and the French king
have formed an alliance against me.
There appears to have been preparations
for an invasion encouraged
by the Vicar of Rome.
Your Majesty, I've been in this job
for a long time,
I know when to believe what I am told,
and when not to.
Which is most of the time.
Although the Emperor publicly embraced
the French king,
And even gave him the Order of
the Golden Fleece from around his neck,
He still continues to hate him.
More than any other enemy,
my master fears the Turks.
And yet the French are
in league with them.
How is such behavior from another
Christian Monarch to be forgiven?
Then they are no longer
in the alliance?
The accord has already broken down.
Which means that
the Duchess of Milan is
once more available for your
Majesties bed.
It's to late, Mr. Chapuys.
Tell me,
am I to be relived that once more,
I've been used as a pawn in a game
between your master and
the French King?
I tell you this here and now,
I've had enough, Mr. Chapuys.
I've had enough.
You may leave.
I'm surprised to see you back
so soon, Excellences.
We have good news, your Highness.
How so?
His Majesty so desires
to marry your sister, Anne,
That he is willing to forfeit
the requirements of a dowry.
- He wants nothing?
- Only his new bride,
in the shorter time as possible.
His Majesty will also pay
your Highness
a considerable stipend
for introducing him to the League.
However, we recall that your sister
is already promised to the son
of the Duke of Lorraine.
Yes, that was indeed
a great obstacle.
However, on closer consideration
we have discovered that
the contract was never ratified.
And so is not binding in law
or any other way.
So your sister is free
to marry the king?
I will send my ambassadors to England
to conclude the negociations.
Gentlemen.
What's this?
Cromwell's agents, finally intercepted
a letter from Cardinal Pole.
He was on his way to Rome.
I have managed to decode it.
May I see?
To Cardinal Von Waldburg.
Supposed to travel to Paris,
to meet King Francis.
Have already written,
telling him I found the Emperor
very sympathetic to my mission.
But fear it is not so.
The Emperor fears the Turk
more than king Henry,
so I believe he will not act
against him.
So, postpone journey.
Will go instead to papal city
of Carpentras.
I wait further instructions
from his Holiness.
Have you ever been to Carpentras?
No...
but I'm dying to go.
The Duke of Sufolk, My Lord.
Your Grace.
To what do I owe this honor?
I'm here to congratulate you.
The king has made you Earl of Hartford.
And I believe it is time to patch up
our past quarrels and difficulties.
We have better quarrels to be added.
I am happy to agree with your grace.
- Drink?
- Please.
Please.
I am commanded to meet
the Princess at Calais.
Great, many things hang up
on this marriage, do they not?
The King's happiness, for one.
And my Lord Cromwell's reputation.
What a pity if all should go awry.
I would have pity for the King.
But on the other hand?
- Salut!
So, he is marrying
a Lutheran heretic?
- So it seems.
- And I shall marry no one?!
- My lady... I...
- No, I prefer it.
Do you suppose I'd like
to be married off to the Dukes brother,
or some heretic cousin of his?
I would prefer to live in a nunnery.
Like, you don't know
what to think of the King,
He burns one Lucifer,
and then marries another?
If God so wills it,
she might drown at sea.
Chequers, Calais
English Occupied France.
Gentlemen,
we bid you welcome to Calais
on this most auspicious occasion.
"Danke."
May I present to you, His Grace,
the Duke of Suffolk.
Your Grace, I'm honored.
I am Herr Hoghesten,
and this is Count Olisleger.
"Hallo!"
And here, is she,
Her Highness Princess Anne.
After a long time, my God!
Your Highness.
Good day, your Grace.
I'm afraid the bad weather will prevent
our sailing for a few days.
I understand.
Perhaps your Grace could...
help me to explain
how the English are eating?
Of course.
And maybe...
show me some things
the king likes to do?
His Majesty likes to play cards
and gamble.
- Do you play?
- No.
I think, only the men play the cards
in my country.
And, is it not bad to gamble?
Only if you can afford to lose.
We'll play Piquet,
it's not hard to learn.
Das ist gut.
There are 4 suits of cards.
Spades, clubs,
diamonds and hearts.
Hearts? You play with hearts?
Sometimes.
And here we have aces, kings,
queens and knaves.
Then all the Court is here, ja?
Does the king always win?
His Majesty does not like losing.
What have they told you
about the king?
Why?
What is it I should know?
Carpentras
Papal Enclave of Venaissin
- You are Francis Bryan?
- You can take us to the Cardinal?
Si. Yes. Come quickly.
He is with us.
Where is the bastard?
Sorry senor.
Prego,
go with God my sons.
We'll never catch him.
It's a waste of time.
Perhaps not.
Holy Mary pray for us...
and deliver me from my ennemies
Amen.
- You didn't see her face?
- No Your Majesty.
But she plays cards as pleasantly
and with as good a grace
as any other noble woman.
She's come to Rochester.
I'm due to meet her
in three days time.
I tell you I'm more impatient
than ever to see her.
What of Sir Francis Bryan?
He and Sir Thomas Seymour are now
to Carpentras.
Where Cardinal Pole is supposed
to be hiding.
It appears he has grown fearful
of assassination.
He's every right to be so.
I swear that man should be flamed alive
and I should wear his skin as a shirt.
He will doom the day he allowed the Pope
to use and to threaten me.
I tell you,
I cannot abide this waiting.
It's been a long time.
I need to nourish love.
- I can understand.
- Can you?
I want to possess this woman
And I haven't even seen her.
She's a complete stranger to me.
What if I can't?
What if you can't... what?
Broom.
- Majesty.
- Fetch the master of the horse,
I live for Rochester immediately.
Go!
Make way!
Dismount!
Tell the lady a gentleman has come
to see her, bearing a New Year's gift.
I'm here to welcome you to my realm.
I trust you are comfortable here?
Before your journey to London.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I'll see you in London.
I should have taken more
lessons from the Duke.
English manners are very
different from ours.
I like her not!
Do you understand me?
Call a meeting of the Council.
It seems, that Princes in marriage
suffer more then poor men.
Since they have to take
what is brought to them,
while poor man are
at liberty to choose.
I have been deceived
about Anne of Cleves.
She is nothing like
what was reported to me. Nothing!
She looks like a horse!
A furless mare!
Your Majesty will remember
that it was Sir John
who described her as being like a...
I never saw her properly,
which was not my fault.
I carried out my commission
as best I could,
and I told you I was no good
with women.
My Lord Cromwell.
Do you deny
that you spoke to me of her beauty?
Of the desirability
of my marriage to her?
No. Your Majesty.
And if I had misled your Majesty
and His Council
by commendations based on false reports,
then, I am truly sorry for them.
If I had known what I know now,
she would never have been brought here!
What remedy Mr. Cromwell?
Your Majesty have to say
that there is none.
That's the case, you've been following
the Cleves agenda since the beginning.
Go on.
Today, the Emperor is the guest
of the King of France.
They have renewed their alliance.
If we now reject our German allies,
then England will remain alone
and friendless and at the mercy
of the King and Emperor.
Your Majesty, if you break this
marriage contract now
you risk the possibility that even
Duke William himself
might retaliate against us.
I am sorry that your Majesty has
no better contempt.
I'm not well handled, Sir Cromwell.
Majesty.
Milady.
I am here to welcome you
to what is yours.
Your Majesty is very gracious
and I am very happy.
My daughters, Princess Mary...
The Princess Elizabeth.
For you... I think they are pretty.
Thank you Princess.
I think you are pretty too.
I shall love them both.
I like her not.
But it seems
Your Majesty must marry her.
Who says I must? Cromwell?
I have my lawyers working on it.
The betrothed can be prevented
on two grounds:
Either the German envoy fails to bring
the commission from the Duke
authorizing them to conclude
the legalities of the marriage,
Or they can't provide
written evidence
that her betrothed was formerly
revoked. Either way I can get out of it.
I wish in my heart that your majesty
is successful.
It seems to me that my lord Cromwell
is to keen to stress there's no remedy.
The marriage was his idea.
There were other candidates.
The Duchess of Milan is supposed to be
the most desirable woman in the world!
Instead of which...
Perhaps, in this matter,
Lord Cromwell...
has overreached himself.
Perhaps.
Oh God!
If there is no remedy I must put
my neck into this yoke.
I'm sorry Lord Cromwell,
I didn't see you, I...
I was talking to God.
But surely say you have to go
to church for that.
Do you understand nothing
about Reforms?
God is not just in church, he is...
everywhere.
We do not need priests
to speak for us.
We can... speak to Him ourselves,
and He will listen.
There's no need for bells,
and books and candles.
All you need is... your soul.
Now go away. Think.
Wait!
Today is the fifth of the Epiphany,
and my wedding day.
So, there is no legal remedy?
None that it was possible to discover,
Your Majesty.
I am not well handled.
I think when Your Majesty gets to know
the lady better...
I don't want to know
the lady better Mr Cromwell!
The notion of it repulses me.
My Lord, if it were not to satisfy
the world and my realm,
I would not do what I must do this day
for no earthly thing!
Shall we to bed?
Majesty.
How does
Your Majesty like the Queen?
My Lord, I didn't like her very much
before, I like her much worse now.
She is nothing fair
and has evil smells about her.
She's no maid because of the looseness
of her breasts and other tokens.
So I had neither the will
nor the courage to prove the rest.
I have no appetite
for unpleasant airs.
I left her as good a maid
as I found her.
And now my Lord, leave me.
I'm very busy.
Speak out!
- I couldn't sleep. Who is there?
- No one.
Go back to bed.
Should I come to you later?
If you could still be
my sweet Charles.
I am as good as I may be.
Can't you take me as I am?
I love you Catherine.
I have drained to the pus
from Your Majesty's wound.
Your Majesty should feel
no more pain.
I expede to God.
Forgive me,
but is Your Majesty troubled by...
other things?
I have been unabled to consumate
my marriage with Lady Anne.
I find her body in such a sort,
disordered and indisposed,
that it doesn't excite me
or provoke any lust in me.
Have you heard any rumors of it?
Not at all, Your Majesty.
It has not anything to do
with my virility.
Indeed, these last nights,
I have had
pollutione and nocturne in somno.
Two nocturnal emissions...
You see, I know myself perfectly able
to... perform the act with others,
just not with her.
With her I have no appetite to do
what a man should do with his wife.
- My Lord Cromwell?
- Majesty.
May we speak alone?
Alone?
Oh, yeah. Of course.
My Lord.
Madam, I've come on a delicate matter,
forgive me.
I... must warn you
againt antagonizing the King.
I must remind you
of the expediency of doing your utmost
to make yourself agreable... to him.
Sir...
I am not sure
how I given His Majesty offence.
It is in your interest and in mine
to make your marriage to the King
a sucess.
If for example, you were...
to find yourself,
quick with child...
I'm sorry to talk
in such intimate matters, but...
You are the Queen of England, you have
nothing private anymore.
How am I to become quick with child
when the king leaves me a maid?
I am not the Virgin Mary!
You say I have nothing private,
Then I say you
it is not all pleasing.
I would do anything the King wants,
but sometimes,
The score on his leg is bad.
It oczes blood and pus.
And it smells.
It stinks. It smells, yeah?
You understand?
Now, I am sorry, My Lord.
I will go on,
doing all that I can to make myself
agreable to His Majesty.
He is always gracious and kind.
Majesty.
Madam, how do you find the king?
Why,
he is most kind and solicitousness,
Lady Bryan.
When he comes to bed, he kisses me.
Takes my hand,
bids me "good night sweetheart".
Then, in the morning,
he kisses me again.
And says: farewell darling.
My lady,
we all hope you'll be with child soon.
I know very well, I am not.
But, how do you know you are not?
I know it well, I am not.
I think
your Majesty is a maid still.
He must put his member inside you
and stir it.
Or else we'll not have a Duke of York,
which is all this realm desires.
I am contented Lady Bryan.
I received as much
of the king's attention as I wish.
I know no more!
Lady Bryan?
Yes, Your Majesty.
If I don't please the king...
will he kill me?