Previously on
"moonlight"...
I saw coraline last night.
Coraline is dead.
You look just like
someone i used to know.
Ex-girlfriend, maybe?
- Ex-Wife.
She's found a cure.
There is no cure
for vampirism, mick.
One of these days you're gonna
have to stop hating what you are.
What could be
the downside?
Missing all of the things
that you once loved.
Turn me.
If she is back, what does she want?
She's back for mick.
She's been lying
to us, stalking us.
No!
She's not a vampire! She's human.
She has a cure.
The object missed her heart but punctured her
left lung and partially tore the pericardium.
Is she going to live?
It's a deep wound, and
infection has already set in.
That's our biggest
concern right now--
That and a buildup of
fluid around the heart.
You know, it's a
very unusual wound.
I understand she told the e.r.doctor
that it was some sort of accident.
Do either of you
know what happened?
No. We don't know what happened.
Well, all we can do
now is monitor her.
I'll let you know
if there's any change.
Thank you very much.
Why did she lie for me?
Why didn't she
tell them i did it?
She wouldn't want
the police involved.
I can't believe i
almost killed her.
I-i thought for
sure she was a vampire.
You couldn't have known.
I didn't even know.
You still care
for her, don't you?
She was my wife.
You really think there's
some kind of cure?
Coraline was a
vampire for 500 years.
Now she's as human as you are.
Something changed her
back, and if she dies,
I'll never know
what that was...
Or how she did it.
NEW YORK
Did you find him?
That's him.
Where is he?
He's living in los angeles
using the name josef kostan.
What do you want me to do?
What i hired you
to do-- kill him.
I'll take the
next flight out.
It has to be done with fire.
Fire's impractical.
Long-range single shot
to the head would-- . - no
It has to be fire.
Why fire?
Because i said so.
Burn him to death, and
you'll get your money.
Consider it done.
LOS ANGELES
Oh, trust me on
this one, fellas.
When you get mixed up with
mortal girls, it never ends well.
You can always
turn 'em******
Nah, it's too much commitment.
- Come on.
So you're sayin
never turn a girl ever?
All i'm saying is
forever is a long time.
I know what you're saying.
All right, bets.
I'm in with three a.b.-negs.
i'm out.
What do you got?
Two pa...
Two pair.That's it?
- Yeah.
My flush beats that.
Of fives.
I guess tonight's my night, boys.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Moonlight
Season01 Episode10
Glad to see you're here, mr. St.john.
What happened, tom?
We're still putting
the pieces together.
There aren't many pieces left.
Josef?
Forensics haven't found
any remains yet, just ash.
Whoever did this brought an awful lot
of firepower to take out just one man.
How did they get in?
Hato be real pros.
I've been the head of security
for mr. Kostan for five years.
I'm tellg you, there's no way anyone should
have been able to get near this office.
Oh, great. You're still here.
That's why i love you.
I just have to
finish up some copy.
I spent the afternoon in the hospital.
Oh, yeah, morgan.
How is she doing?
She's in pretty bad shape.
Does anyone know
how she hurt herself?
No she's s-still unconscious.
Cheer up.
I've got something to
ta your mind off morgan.
Explosion in a downtown office
building took out the top floor.
Terrorists?
- No.
Apparently the
target was this, uh...
Big shot hedge fund trader.
Oh, my god. That's josef kostan.
He's a friend of mick's.
Okay, i take it back.
This is why i love you.
Was he there?
Afraid so.
No survivors.
Uh, have a cameraman
meet you down there.
I wanna know the
who, what and why.
I can't cover this story.
This guy's a really
good friend of mick's.
Great.
Use that to show
some vulnerability.
Tracking says women 18 to
34 find you a little hars
it was poker night.
I was supposed to be here.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah. Me, too.
Who could have done this?
I mean, they used fire.
They must have
known he was a vampire.
Josef had enemies, but this...
Who could hate him this much?
- Yeah.
You brought your camera guy?
That's why you're
here? You're on a story?
Look, maureen
sent me-- just--
beth, just go away.
Listen, they were gonna send
someone here to cover this story.
Wouldn't you rather it was me?
My friend just died.
I dot really wanna
talk to you right now.
No, actually, you
stay and get your story.
You do your job. I'll do mine.
Josef had cameras
installed in every office?
Top of the line--
offices, hallways, elevators,
Parking structure, the
basement, even the boiler room.
He even wanted infrared
cameras installed.
I don't know why, but he insisted.
I know why.
Vampires don't
give off body heat.
Josef wanted to know exactly
who his visitors were.
Here. This is him.
A heatignature.
Josef's killer is a human.
He must have come in with the
maintenance crew for the night shift.
As soon as i saw him go into mr. Kostan's
office,  i headed up there, but it was too late.
Wait. Stop.Stop right there.
Can you zoom in
on the incendiaries?
Those look military grade.
I need a copy of this footage.
- Sure.
Anything i can do
to help get this guy.
Yeah.
Mr. St.john?
- Yes.
This is dr. Duffy.
You should come down to the
hospital. Miss vincent's awake.
How's she doing? Is she okay?
Her wound shows
some signs of healing.
She's been in and
out of consciousness.
Can i talk to her?
Just a few minutes. She needs to rest.
Okay. Thanks.
Hey, coraline.
U look like someone just died.
Someone did.
It's josef.
God.
I remember introducing you two.
You thout he was a pompous jerk,
and he thought you weren't
cut out to be a vampire.
We were both probably right.
But you were best friends anyways.
Ye, we were, and
now he's gone.
But i'm back.
You have to tell me how.
How i survived the fire
thatou thought killed me?
How you became human.
It always comes back to this.
You're so desperate
to be mortal again...
To experience
death for yourself. Why?
It's beth, isn't it?
You think you love her.
This is not about beth okay?
I came back for you.
I became human for you.
Doesn't that mean anything?
How, coraline?
For you...
You have to tell me how.
Look, i know-- -
Look, i'm really sor--
I overreacted.
I shouldn't have brought a
camera into josef's office.
I'm so sorry.
This is just really
hard for me-- all of it.
Coraline's in the
hospital, josef's dead...
I know he meant a lot to you.
I've outlived so many
of my human friends,
you'd think i'd be used
to losing people by now.
Yeah, but losing
josef's different.
He survived 400 years.
400 years.
He saw so ch, so much history.
He was history.
And now he's gone.
And that loss to me...
Is so enormous...
That i'm not even sure if
i know how to mourn him.
I need a drink.
Yeah, me, too.
Well, are you just gonna
stand there all day,
Or are you gonna help me
find out who killed me?
Recognize that guy?
No, never seen him before.
Is he a vampire?
No, he showed up as
human on your infrareds.
Does he know josef's a vampire?
Well, he did use fire.
The other people he killed-- your
friends-- were they vampires, too?
Well, remind me to donate a little
something to charity in theiname.
Oh, wait. I can't.
I have no money.
I have no office.
I have no anything, because some janitor
decided to whack me in a very public,
Very-hard-to-explain how- i'm-still-alive
kind of y, so everyone thinks i'm dead.
Yeah, and it has
to stay that way.
This janitor of yours is a professional
assassin with access to military-grade weaponry.
Somebody hired him, and you're only gonna
be safe so long as he thinks he succeeded.
So find him and whack him so
i can carry on with business.
Ere are you going?
Well, your assassin
may be ex-military.
I'm gonna see if your hack buddy rider
england can get me into their files.
He can't.
Oh, he can't hack the military?
Oh, he can.
He did.
That's why he's on a sabbatical
in south america right now.
I know somebody.
Sam does some computer
work at "buzzwire."
Okay, let's go.
You... Stay.
You do not leave this apartment.
is this the ly time we get
a clear look at his face?
Uh, yeah.
Is there a problem?
No, i just-- when beth said she
knew a hacker named sam, i thought--
You thought
i was a guy--
Overweight, living in my parent's basement
wearing a t-shirt with yoda on it?
Yeah.
Mick's kinda old school.
Okay, if this guy was special
ops, he wenthrough basic training,
Which means that he had his
picture taken for his military i.d.
I'm using facial recognition software to cross-reference
your image with the pentagon's i.d.database.
Hodo you have
atcess to th?
Don't ask, don't tell.
Ralf Martan
He was training at Fort Bragg.
Ex-military*** special ops
He has been in
Afghanistan and then went to Iraq
He was discharged when he back
to work in Darkwatch associates
He's a machine
looks like he got
some trouble over there
went solo and disappeared
from the radar about six month ago
Are you sure you
wanna find this guy?
hey, you're back.
sorry.
Party's over.
Excuse me.
but they, uh...
They just got here.
What did i tell you?
Well, you told me not to
go out, so i ordered in.
What do you got, a death wish?
Get 'em out of here now.
I'm sorry, ladies.
Daddy's a little grumpy.
We're gonna have to
pick this up later.
Bye josef
I love your place
I love you
Bye
I don't believe this.
What if they tell
someone you're alive?
You want this guy throwing a firebomb
in here, too-- wreck my place, huh?
Burn me up like
he did tim and dan?
What's the matter with you?
You didn't even
think about it, did you?
Did you even think
about it for one second?
You know what? You don't
care about yourself.
Can you at least care
about not getting me killed?
Listen, i wasn't like...
Look, i get lonely, man. You know that.
Yeah. I'm beginning to see why.
The hacker got
the assassin's name.
Ralf martan--
do you know him?
Martan, martan...
Oh--nope.
Apparently some born killer.
Special ops, darkwatch, afghanistan...
Oh, you know, last time i was
there, the british were inving
And i need to
go to my office.
Are you-- are
you kidding?
No. I have a fireproof
safe.I need to get some cash.
You--what do you want?
You don't needash.
No, i gotta get it.
Okay, i can't drink your
store-bought blood anymore.
I need some fresh a.b.-negative.
Your office is--your office
is not a safe place. This...
I'm going to bed.
And what am i
supposed to do?
Why don't you tidy up?
Are you sure these vitals are right?
I checked them myself.
So our patient has a raging
infection, but instead of spiking a fever,
Her temperature's dropped 2
degrees in the past six hours?
I don't know what to tell you.
Try again. This
can't be right.
It's okay. I'm just
checking your vitals.
I'm dying.
Calm down now.
It's so strange.
I'm nosupposed to.
There you go.
Nice and comfy.
Stop right there.
Mr. Kostan?
Hi, tom.
I can't believe it.
Yeah, well, i thought
about calling first,
But i didn't want to make
a big deal out of this.
You're alive, but how?
It's a long story.
You're the only one who knows i'm still
alive, and we need to keep this between us.
Josef?
I called you as
soon as he showed.
Figured there might be a little
something extra in it for me.
There is.
You've already died once
this week. Isn't that enough?
Who are you working for?
Answer me! Who hired you?
Now... I don't
like repeating myself.
Whitley.
Whitley?
John whitley.
He's a real estate guy in new york.
You know that
name? Whitley?
I don't think so.
Don't lie to me, josef.
He certainly seemed to know you.
Give me a hand
lifting this guy, will ya?
Josef!
What's your connection to all this, mick?
I'm investigating the
death of josef kostan.
You think this guy's the one
that firebombed the building?
I'm pretty sure.
He looks like the same guy i
saw in the surveillance tapes.
What did he come back for?
- I don't know.
Security guy's dead.
Maybe he was a loose end.
We'll look into it. Good job.
Listen, be careful with this guy.
He's dangerous.
Hey, we do this for a living.
So i checked out
that name you got.
I found a john
whitley in new york.
He's 93, a wealthy
real estate developer.
At one point, he owned
half the upper east side.
That must be our guy.
No family.
His wife died
two years ago.
He had a daughter who
disappeared in 1955.
You think josef's after him?
Josef's sense of justice is
pretty much an eyeor an eye.
Where are you going?
New york.
I have to stop josef before
he does something stupid.
I'm going with you.
- Why?
To stop you from
doing something stupid.
All********
josh.
Oh, god. I-i completely forgot.
It's movie night, isn't it?
We need to talk.
Come in.
Are you...
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, to new york.
You know, the, uh, the
josef kostan story.
I thought that was wrapped up.
- No.
So are you going alone?
You and mick, i bet, huh?
When were you
gonna tell me?
I was gonna call you
from the air... Airport.
Look...
This isn't working.
It's just a case.
- A case?
A story.Whatever. Work.It's...
Look me in the eye right now and tell
me you don't have feelings for him.
Look me in the eye...
And tell me that.
You ready?
Oh, i'll--i can--
i'll come back.
No.
- No.
I was just leaving.
You two have fun in new york.
If you need
to stay--
no, it's okay.Let's go.
How did you get in here?
I work for you, remember?
What are you doing?
Josef kostan--
tell me about him.
Is he dead?
No, he's not.
He walked aw from an explosion no
one could possibly have survived.
His friend dangled me off
a balcony with only one arm.
Now you're gonna tell me
how any of this is possible,
Or i'm gonna put an air
bubble into your bloodstream
and you're gonna stroke out
without having gotten your revenge.
He's aampire.
That's not funny, old man.
No, it's not.
Now tell me everything about them.
Tell me...
How to kill them.
Mr. Kostan, we've
been expecting you.
Yes, sir, i will.
Sorry. Mr. Whitley
isn't receiving visitors.
Oh, please, can
you ask him again?
He was very clear.
This is really important.
- I'm sure it is.
Now is there anything
else i can do for you?
Yes, can you tell him it's
regarding josef kostan?
No way.
Hey, we asked nicely.
They said no.
After you.
Mr. Whitley, there are people here.
I'm not sure how they got in.
Should i call the police?
Mr. Whitley, we think
you might be in danger.
No, leave us.
You hired a hit man
to kill sef kostan.
No...
Sir, we have
evidence--
I hired him to kill
charles fitzgerald.
Who?
That was his name when he
took my daughter from me...
When he murdered her.
Sara was 21 when
that picture was taken.
That was 1955.
In a few months, she was gone.
You ink josef is responsible
for the death of your daughter?
I ow what he is.
He's a monster.
He took my daughter from me.
Well, you better
tell me all about josef,
so i can find him
before he finds you.
there...
In that drawer.
Bring me that diary.
This was my sara.
My wife kept it from me
until she died two years ago.
My daughter was a
beautiful, innocent, trusting young woman.
Her only mistake was falling
in love with fitzgerald.
He exploited her love.
He seduced sara, and
then he killed her.
I couldn't protect her then...
But i can avenge her now.
So is that all in the diary?
Read for yourself.
So you hired someone to kill him.
It took me two
years to find fitzgerald.
I can't die knowing that
monster still walks this earth.
You're gonna have to leave now.
Thank you.
Listen
to this--
"it doesn't matter to me
what he is.I love him."
"i want to be with him, even though
he tells me it's impossible."
"i know our love can
overcome any obstacle."
"i want him to turn
me into what he is."
"he says it's
dangerous, but i don't care."
"i'm not afraid."
"it's the ly way we can
be together forever."
"I'm ready."
That was the last entry.
So josef never
mentioned any of this?
Never told you about sara?
- No.
I knew he lived here in new york
before he moved to los angeles.
Vamps tend to move around. We
can't stay in one spot for too long.
You have. You
stayed in l.a.
I like the weather.
Really?
It's sam.
Hey, what did you find out?
Josef was picked up at the
terminal by an h & g limo.
I'll text you the
drop-off address.
Okay, thanks.
301 Waverly Place
Can i help you?
Yes, we're looking
for josef kostan.
No one by that name is here.
Are you sure?
A limo service just dropped
him off at this address.
I don't know what to tell you.
What about charles
fitzgerald? Do you know him?
It's okay, paula.
You can let 'em in.
Well, you can run, but you can't hide, huh?
Not from me... Charles.
So we had a pretty interesting
talk with john whitley.
You wanna tell
me what's going on?
Mick, beth...
This is sara...********
You can take your dinner break.
I'll watch her.
What's wrong with her?
Uh, she's been in a
coma... Since 1955.
Oh, my god. She hasn't aged.
You know, i met her at grand central
station, and we were both waiting for a train.
She asked me for a light, and the
moment i looked into her eyes,
i knew that she
was somethin' special.
I knew better than to
get involved with a human.
I knew it was a
mistake, but i did it anyway.
And for months, i thought i
was keeping my secret from her,
but then i discovered that she knew.
She knew...
And she didn't care.
That was the happiest day of my life.
So you were in
love with her.
I wasn't looking
for it, believe me.
The longer we were together, the
more i began to think that
The whole reason that
i became a vampire was...
You know, so i could live
long enough to meet her.
You know, it took me over
350 years to find her.
And only a year to lose her...
Forever.
So what happened to her?
He tried to turn her.
Ye.
And she'd been begging
me to do it for months.
I didn't want to, but
she wouldn't let it go.
You know, she knew that was the
only way we could be together.
So i tried.
I drained her, and i...
Fed her my blood, but it didn't work.
She never came out of it.
She got lost somewhe in between.
Josef...
This... L this...
It's not your fault.
I know, but
it--it is.
I'm the one who
did this to her.
You've been looking
after her ever since.
I couldn't let her go.
Oh, maybe someday medicine or...
A miracle or something
will bring her back.
Stay down, okay?
Die, vampire.
Why won't you die?
It doesn't always work like that.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
What are you using back
there, barbecue tongs?
Will you hold still?
I'm trying to get
the second bullet.
You know, for a 400-year old vampire, you
sure have a low threshold for pain.
Well, giving is
different than receiving.
Done.
How's your stake wound?
Well, nothing a little
blood wouldn't help.
All these years, you ranting about how it
could never work between us and humans.
Well, what happened to sara
is proof that i'm right.
Josef kostan in love?
That's proof that
anything is possible.
Love can show you a part of
yourself you never knew existed.
Or a part that you
thought you lost forever.
And then this happened.
I guess the universe had
a different plan for me.
I guess who i am is
who i'm supposed to be.
You gonna try to make
your thing with beth work?
I hope the universe is on your side.
Are you okay?
I will be.
That bastard staked me.
Are you coming
back to l.a. With us?
I'm gonna stay
here a few more days.
You should have this.
She really loved you.
You all right?
Yeah.
I just can't stop
thinking about sara.
She was so in
love with him.
Yeah, it's terrible.
Do you really
think there's a cure?
Coraline made
herself human.
Is that a cure? I don't know.
I can't say.
Taxi!
Come on. Let's
go do something.
Like what?
I don't know.
Something fun.
Something quintessentially new york.
We'll catch a set at
the village vanguard.
We'll... A couple of martinis.
A steak for the lady.
Just you and me on
the town. Come on.
I don't know, but our flight
leaves in a couple hours.
So we'll take
a later flight.
Look, i-i don't know. I...
I didn't leave things
very well with josh.
I do think i need to get home.
Yeah, of course.
But i'll drop you.
No, it's okay. I'll walk.
It's a good town for it.
Okay.
Mick?
Code blue.