previously on "moonlight"...
being on the hunt with you is kind of fun.
It's a giant thrill ride that never ends.
silver's like poison to you.
You've been avoiding me ever since...
so how does it work anyway--the sex thing?
You parents never told you?
They skipped the part involving vampires.
I saw the way you two looked at each other.
what we want doesn't always matter,
but then again,sometimes it's all that does.
gorgeous, renee. Yes!
We're here with photographer nigel hart,
shooting a sneak peek of the exciting new collection of hot young designer
ghislaine tavares...
outfits only a broomstick would wear.
???
Watch the platter hand.
????
show me sexy, babe. Let's go.
Steve, hello.
I'm over here.
Can I say something?
I think you got the wrong attitude about this assignment.
Well, I'm a crime reporter.
We should be covering a trial
or a riot, not this fluff.
Beats corpses in an alley, right?
I mean, at least everyone here is alive.
Barely.
(Muffled) get up!
Up!
(Muffled) okay! Okay!
oh, god.
Tell me it's not 12:00.
No.
I'm looking for somebody.
What, do you think they're in here?
I need your help.
You need my help.
Don't make me say it again.
Dolores maxford whitaker.
"Lola" to her friends.
Nice.
Is she a vampire?
Of course she's a vampire.
She's the vampire--
oldest one I've ever met.
And we've had this on again/off again thing for a hundred years or so,
but she came back into town a couple weeks ago, so it's on again,
until she disappears.
(Laughs) that's what you get for dating older women.
Well, it's better than dating a human.
Beth and I are not--
what's this about?
I told you. She's vanished,
okay, and I haven't found her in any of her usual haunts.
And believe me,I've been looking.
You got a phone number?
No, she usually calls me.
So you guys are, uh,
really close, huh?
Yeah, in our own way.
She's always been sort of unpredictable, exciting.
You know, traits you'll come to value when you hit the 400-year mark.
Yeah, yeah,
so she's been calling you.
Yeah.
Cell phone.
So let me get this straight.
Oh. She stood you up.
So instead of moving on,
you became so worried
that you immediately came over here and woke me up.
How much does she owe you?
Just see what you can find out.
Thanks.
Hey.
The theme for ghislaine's collection is celestial bodies,and this outfit is the focal point,
the linchpin that holds it all together.
Was that better?
Uh, there was just a tinge of condescension, just a tinge.
beautiful.
?????
No so high fashion, sweetheart.
(Man) renee!
(Woman) aah! Help! Help!
Someone get an ambulance.
(Man) come on. Just breathe.
Come on.
(Man) go call 9-1-1. Go.
no!
????
(Whispers) did you get that?
yeah. Yeah, I got it all.
I wouldn't call that fluff.
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
Moonlight 第1季第6集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
时间轴：Gino
no heartbeat. She's dead.
Excuse me.
You're with the camera guy.
Go away.
You were her friend,obviously.
Don't pretend you're all concerned.
You don't even know her name.
Renee. Renee beresford.
Moved here from shreveport last year.
I didn't know her,but I do know her name.
I've done my homework.
I really should go call her mom.
So you were friends.
Do you have any idea what just happened?
Not really.
We went out last night to two clubs.
then around 11:00,
she wants to go to this other place,
but I really needed to go home.
Where did she go?
Club valis. It just opened.
She never came back home...
just showed up today wearing what she had on last night.
She said none of this mattered anymore and that she was gonna quit.
(Voice breaks) I r--
I really should go find out if someone called her mom.
Okay.
beth.
What are you doing here?
Covering a story that just got way more interesting.
You get any video of what happened here?
Yeah.
I'm gonna need that tape.
I'm gonna need it back.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave the crime scene.
(Scoffs) a girl just convulsed and died.
Since when did this become a crime scene?
I'm not gonna discuss an ongoing investigation with you.
Ongoing? Since when?
What's going on?
I'm gonna have to ask you not to follow the story.
You're not gonna give me anything?
This is our third O.D.In two weeks from a drug we can't even identify.
How about I owe you dinner?
You owe me dinner anyway.
Um, ahem.
Yeah, give him the tape.
All right.
Here you go, big guy.
Thank you.
Hey, josh.
I'll call you later.
What was that all about?
Do you know of club valis?
Mnh-mnh.
I love the way the camera cut the light on her cheekbones.
You could dance on those.
Digital photography--what a boon for the tribe, huh?
Remember the old film days--no image?
It was like you didn't even exist.
Okay, okay,
so did you find her?
Before I tell you that,
I just have to know.
Is there any chance that you hired me to find beautiful lola
so you could cut off her very photogenic head?
Why would I want to do that?
You tell me.
I tracked the cell that she called you from.
I wanted to see who else she was talking to.
And?
She bought a metric ton of silver from a place called allied metals.
A ton of silver?
Yeah, quite an arsenal.
She got a vampire problem that you know about?
I can't think of any vamp who'd want to go up against her.
All those centuries she's lived--with that kind of age comes power.
I'm beginning to see why you're so attracted to her.
You know, when I met her,
she was building a pirate army.
Pirate army?
You know, back in the day,you could do that kind of thing.
Okay, so what aren't you telling me?
Oh, your vamp sense must be off.
I'm telling you all I know.
No, it's actually my detective sense at work here, josef.
What's going on?
it's embarrassing, okay?
Mm.
She stole money from me.
I knew it. How much?
A million bucks.
Siphoned it from one of my accounts right before she disappeared.
What, did you give her your password or something?
You gave her your pardsswo?
Not on purpose.
I don't even want to know.
And I can't let this happen.
On principle alone, I can't let her cheat me like this.
It'll ruin my reputation.
So what, this is just about money?
There's no hurt feelings about being stood up?
No, of course not.
I got the address of where they shipped the silver.
It's a storage facility downtown.
Well, don't forget.
She's powerful,
and you can't just confront her.
Thanks to your once-a-decade booty call,
a dangerous vampire now possesses a large quantity of a lethal substance.
I kind of have to check it out.
hi.
Right hand.
thank you
you're gonna hate that.
The drinks suck here.
Oh, I'm not here for the drinks.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm not here for that either.
Right.
Ah, the upstairs V.I.P. Room.
You can forget about that
unless you've been preapproved.
What do you mean?
it's qualified buyers only.
How do you get to be one?
No offense, but if I knew, would I be out here talking to you?
???
sorry.
What? I got a stamp.
A stamp doesn't get you into the V.I.P. Room.
What will?
Being a V.I.P.
There's a list.
How do I get on it?
You talk to the owner.
Who is where?
In the V.I.P. Room.
sorry.
I'm a friend of renee's, and she said it wouldn't be a problem,me getting upstairs.
Well, it's not a problem if you know how, but you don't, so...
If you're human,
a metric ton of silver is
maybe a good inflation hedge...
or a lot of jewelry.
If you're a vampire,
it has a different meaning.
Lola had bought enough silver to paralyze every vamp in L.A.
it kind of made me wonder what she was planning.
Silver.
Terrance.
Where's guillermo?
A straight flush won me a week's worth of his night shifts.
Please tell me that's just lunch in there.
Not this time.
Oh!
This is L.A. County morgue,
not help-u-autopsy.
You can't just bring in your own bodies.
I need to know what killed him.
I'm thinking fire.
Well, not just.
Silver?
Yeah, a lot of it.
Silver should show up in the blood.
Blood should show up in the blood.
What do you mean?
This vamp's been drained.
Someone soaked him in silver and drained his blood?
Then set him on fire.
It's kind of excessive.
The silver would paralyze the vamp.
So would a simple stake.
Yeah, but with a stake,
there'd be blood loss, right?
With silver, you can paralyze e vathmp with no leakage.
Whoever did this wanted the vampire's blood.
But why?
I got a list three pages long of vamps who want human blood.
I've never heard of anyone wanting vampire blood.
You think some freak is out there feeding on his own kind?
Actually, her own kind.
I'll let you know when I find out.
Can--
I could so lose my job over this.
You're happy to risk it,though.
What am I buying you this time anyway? An iphone?
Iphone.
Okay,I just want to see her hand.
What is she?Some friend of yours?
No, she's a model.
That explains it.
What?
She is really hot.
(Scoffs) do you mind?
Knock yourself out.
Just make it quick.
what's the "v"?
Oh, nothing.It's what I have.
That's not what got her in.
Got her in where?
The V.I.P room at a club.
There was a bouncer checking people's hands and letting 'em in.
What's that incision?
There was something under her skin. We removed it.
What?
A microchip.
A microchip?
What, like james bond?
Uh... no.
Uh, like "find my lost cat."
People get 'em put in their pets.
Any vet can do it.
Do you read those with a scanner?
Shyeah, elters do,
but I've never seen one in a human before.
Wow. So club valis uses a microchip and a scanner.
How 21st century.
This V.I.P. Room--
do they serve silver there?
Silver? What do you mean?
The other weird thing about your pal here is that she had silver in her blood.
What? How much?
Oh, more than you'd get if you used it as an herbal supplement.
The silver was pure. My guess--
it's what did her in.
you really gotta go.
hey. What you got for me?
hey.
Hey.
So, uh, this isn't awkward or anything,
running into each other in the middle of the night in a morgue.
Again.
Look, I didn't want to invade your privacy,
uh, whatever you do here.
Oh, no, I'm--
I'm working on a case. It's--
oh, me, too. A-a story.
Oh, how's it going?
Great.
Good. That's--that's good.
Listen, I'm trying to get into this club.
You don't know a good vet,do you?
Me? No.
Uh, vampires can't really be trusted with pets. It'S...
of course. (Chuckles)
exactly what kind of club is it that you're going to that you need to go to a vet?
I, uh...
I need this microchip inserted in my hand.
Well, of course you do.
They scan them.
Can't you just hold it?
No,they check pretty carefully.
Okay.
They found it in this model who collapsed.
The morgue guy thinks it's from traces of silver found in her blood.
Silver?
Any more than trace amounts,and you got yourself an overdose.
Any idea how it got in there?
No idea, but she was fine before she went to club valis.
Uh, I don't have a vet,
but, um, I have something else.
Come on.
Don't worry. It's sterile.
Honestly, I was more worried about the size.
Why do you even have that anyway?
Oh, right.
Stupid question.
Okay.
This may hurt a little bit.
Okay, but I'll be fine, right?
Won't I?
Let's hope.
By the way, the, uh,the whole kiss thing?
Yeah, the kiss.
I was thinking that maybe that was like an accident.
Oh, okay.
Tell me when.
All done.
Hold your finger there.
So I want to go with you...
to club valis.
Oh, I'll be okay.
I'm actually looking for someone.
The silver makes me think that maybe she's there.
she?
Yeah.
I'll see you there in two hours.
I can't believe this double standard.
I had to spend two hours getting myself up to club admissionability,
and you're just wearing the same thing you always wear.
Yes, well, perpetual coolness is the vampire's curse.
by the way, how do you get away with silver?
I thought it was poison for vampires.
It's gold. And where's this V.I.P. Room?
Upstairs in the back.
Good.
you're gonna do that vampire jumping thing, aren't you?
I don't have a chip.
Just being human is so lame.
I know,but you wear it well.
I'll see you inside.
???
thank you.
Don't let anybody else in.
???
that girl that just came up?
The scanner said renee beresford.
Your model friend.
You want me to pull her out?
I'll handle it.
black crystal?
Thank you.
thank you.
We prefer you consume it on the premises.
Uh, I was just waiting for a friend.We were gonna share.
Why are you wasting your time?
She's not even supposed to be here.
Calvin, go get me a drink.
You're not renee beresford.
How did you get her chip?
Oh, renee gave it to me.
I just wanted to try whatever it was she was doing.
Then try iT.
It's all for you.
I'm gonna wait for my friend.
Sorry I'm late.
I knew I should've closed the window.
You must be lola.
And you are?
We have a mutual friend.
He's been worried about you.
If it's the friend I'm thinking of, he's not worried.
Trust me. This little thing here helping you track me down?
She's got nothing to do with this.
Oh, I think she does.
Your friend and I have
something in common.
But you can see that,can't you?
And you two--don't tell me.
Just friends?
Leave her alone.
He lets you know what we are
and then leads you on the edge of our world, looking in.
Don't you want to do more then just look?
What is that?
It's what she came here for.
It's, uh, black crystal.
Well, you found it.You should go.
He cares about you,but he hasn't turned you.
Nobody's turning anyone.
I don't want that.
You say that now.
You're young,but in a year or two,
when he stops coming around,
and you look in the mirror,
I knowlo've  youoked at him and wondered,
what does it feel like to move
through the night so powerful,
nothing can touch you?
I can give you that...
I said leave her alone.
Without turning you.
Taste it.
Just once, and you'll see.
(man) this is the police.
We need everybody to move against the far wall.
Cops!
Get rid of everything!
Remember, darling,
half the world is night.
Bag that.
You've got to be kidding me.
???
Josh--
don'T.
Pat everyone down,
starting with him.
Hey.
????
???
come on
Thanks for taking me home.
Look...
I asked you not to follow that story.
Fine.
Be angry if you want to.
I don't want to,
but what do you expect when I walk into a club we're raiding
and see you there with mick st. John?
Oh,that's what this is about.
How do you think that looks?
I think it looks like
I'm a good reporter who got to a drug source
before the D.A.'S office,
and I wasn't there with mick.
Not really.
Look, I'm--I'm gonna go.
I'll call you later, okay?
Okay.
(josef) so?
Got somethin' for you.
Yeah?
Black crystal.
Oh, so I'm financing a drug operation?
Not just.
This is vampire blood.
Yes,apparently the high... is us.
Where's she getting the blood?
I found one vamp drained.
I'll bet there's more.
Preying on her own kind.
I should have known.
She stole a million bucks from you.
How could you know?
She didn't steal it.
She didn't steal it?
She asked,and I gave it to her.
I can't help myself,
but I thought she had,you know, uh, limits.
The vampire used to make this survived maybe for hundreds of years.
This used to be someone,
and lola exterminated him,
reduced him down to a vial of party drugs,fed him to humans.
Yeah,some of those are dying, too.
Look, I know this isn't what you signed up for,
but you can't let the cops solve this case.
Lola won't hide what she is.
The cops find her--
they find us.
Yeah.
Don't worry about that.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
P.C.P.--Bitter chemical taste.
Heroin's bitter, too.
what does it feel like?
Just once, and you'll see.
Okay.
Ooh.
Oh, my god.
Hey.
(Carl) we got no drug.
What do you mean we have no drug? We have 5 ounces.
Toxicology ran it four times.
I mean, they can't identify anything illegal in it.
It's just filler.
Traces of silver.
Take too much of that,and it'll kill you.
People are paying a lot for this stuff.
We must be missing something.
Well, we got one guy that might talk.
You just gotta ask him.
Look, I'm a damn doorman is all, okay?
I just--
I create a cool factor.
Let's think how a jury will see it.
First...
they'll see three people...
dead from a drug bought in your club.
Three innocents who bought your marketing--
the best high ever.
They'd hear all about your--
your cool factor,
where kids line up outside,
just so you can tell them
they're not good-looking enough to get in.
You see how this looks?
You're a predator.
These kids are your victims.
I want a deal.
Immunity,and I'll give you lola.
She makes the drugs.
I can tell you where she is.
How about this?
You wear a wire and say exactly what we tell you to.
You're not worried about the cops, right?
They've got nothing.
We're gonna have to distribute somewhere else.
The new location will be even better.
And we'll have a fresh supply of vamps to choose from.
If we take any more from here,
someone's gonna start noticing,
and we've already drawn enough attention...
thanks to you and your human girlfriend renee.
Lola-- (chokes)
did you forget something?
Hey.
Can I come in?
Yeah, of course.
Is everything okay?
Everything's great.
I feel fine.
I walked all the way here.
Why?
I wanted to feel the night.
Did you take some of that drug?
It was research for my story.
It tasted really weird.
Yeah, that's because it's vampire blood.
Do you feel like this all the time?
I don't know.
I doubt it.
I feel everything.
When I was walking,the breeze felt like individual molecules brushing against my skin.
I felt people in their houses.
I could feel their lives.
Can you do that?
Do you feel me?
Or is it more of a-a scent?
You have no idea what you're doing.
I feel close to everything.
Do you?
There's no space between us.
Okay, there's space.
There's space.
You saved me twice.
There are no barriers
between us.
You just think there aren'T.
This is the drug. It's not you.
No, no, no. Shh.
This is me.
I just didn't know it,and I like it...
(whispers) and I wanna be close to you.
Come on, mick.
Join me.
???
Turn me. Turn me.
Do it!
No, beth.
do it
It's just the drug.
what time is it?
It's early.
Is this yours?
Yeah. Your clothes were wet,
but they're dry now.
So do you remember much?
No.
Yes.
The drug made me feel
invincible,
like I was more than human.
I felt like the hottest thing on the planet,
like no one could resist me.
Wow. It sounds like this drug really gives you
all the highs of being a vampire without the lows.
What could be the downside of feeling like that
and living forever?
The scrounging, the hiding,
missing all of the things that you once loved,
like sunbathing, food.
I used to love that prime rib at musso'S.
Now I can't even remember what it tastes like.
And they say it gets easier the longer you live,
but I hope that's not true.
Really? I'd think you'd hope for the opposite.
To forget what it's like to be human?
No way.
Never.
I was wearing that?
Yeah.
That is not like me at all.
Actually, you said it was the real you.
oh. I better get going.
I have some apologies to make.
rough night?
You could say that.
I'm, uh...
I'm glad you're here.
Look, I'm sorry if I was insensitive about your case.
I know it's important to you.
I don't know what I was thinking,
trying to order you off a story.
The fact that I was in the club--
it was just work. I'm sorry if I embarrassed you.
I shouldn't have made such a big deal out of it.
It's just...
this case is driving me crazy.
I really messed it up.
The drug evidence vanished.
It's gone?
We seized the drug,but there's--there's nothing illegal about it.
Toxicology couldn't even get a read on it.
The guy we got from the club is giving us the manufacturer.
It's some woman named lola.
hey. He's wired.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's a little scared,
but, uh, he'll do it.
Uh, warehouse is at 5th and alameda.
Hey. Uh, I got the officers ready.
Okay.
All right.
hey, look, I'd better go.
Okay.Good luck.
mick, it's beth.
Listen, the police are about to raid lola's warehouse at 5th and alameda.
If there's anything there you don't want them to find,
you should get there first.
Okay.
Where's lola?
I don't know. Oh!
She's in the back.
Get out.
It finally made sense--
the silver, the vampire blood.
Oh, my god.
Lola had made her own little factory--
immobilize, extract and eventually dispose.
(Lola) I wouldn't do that.
It'll kill him.
They're vampires.
You're preying on your own kind.
(Lola) don't get all sanctimonious on me.
Humans kill each other every day. No one even blinks.
It's evil.
"Evil" is a word that gets tossed around a lot,
like "great" or "awesome."
you're actually enjoying this.
Everyone should enjoy their work, don't you think?
You're done here.
You're done everywhere.
So self-righteous,
like josef.
Both of you with your rules and laws.
We're above all that.
But you...
still trying to be human,
hanging on to your little freshie friend,
being all tragic and dark.
You can't go through eternity that way.
You'll understand when you're older.
I don't need to be old.
ErI understand now.
There's nothing I could do for the others.
With that much silver in their bodies, they're dead already.
I need you three.
Go around that side.
Come in the back entrance.
You three, take the east door.
You two, come with me.
Believe me,
I'm ding them a favor.
(beth) the explosion happened just after midnight.
Police believe this is the site of the drug manufacturing facility
that's responsible for the black crystal overdoses.
They currently have no leads as to the whereabouts of the people involved.
This is beth turner for "buzzwire."
So you got your story.
Yeah.
this fire...
anybody can see how convenient it is.
It's lola covering her tracks.
I would think that somebody obsessed with mysteries,
like you...
would seize on that.
And get in the middle of your investigation?
No, thanks.
Investigation's over.
The D.A.'S just happy black crystal's disappeared from the scene.
So has lola.
She won't be back.
I don't want to know.
The warehouse is tedorch.
Everything's taken care of.
What about, uh...
she's dead.
well, you know, lola never told me exactly how old she was,
but you know how women are.
Yeah.
She was at least 500 years old.
500?
Yeah.
Wow.
Imagine everything she must have seen.
Yeah.
All the history.
Lola said she thought you and I were alike.
(Scoffs) alike?
You and me?
Yeah.
Self-righteous,following human rules and laws,moral principles,that kind of thing.
But don't worry.
She was wrong.
You're 100% vampire.
Only, you know,when you live as long as lola,
it tricks you into thinking you're above it all,
that you really are immortal.
Yeah.
Then it ends.
beth, dinner's ready.
Okay, I'll be just a minute.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入