Previously on "moonlight"...
I saw coraline
last night.
You look just like
someone i used to know.
- Ex-Girlfriend, maybe?
- Ex-Wife.
Coraline is dead.
You saw her die with your own eyes.
I was kidnapped when i was 4.
I don't remember much.
But the man who rescued me--
He was fearless.
As long as i was in his arms,
i knew i was safe.
I know who saved me
when i was a little girl.
I found my guardian angel.
Memories can be fragile...
Mick!
Fleeting as a whisper
one moment,
Powerful as a scream the next.
I got the proof.
She's been lying to us,
stalking us.
Morgan is coraline.
- I know she is.
- You know?
I spent so long
hiding from my past...
Hi, beth.
Ignoring the whispers.
How could you?
This is not what you think.
But i remember everything now.
And the screams are
the only thing i can hear.
Hey.
- I got your message.
- Get in.
You want to tell me
what you're doing here?
Get in.
Ok
Does it seem ?? To you?
Morgan is quite the exhibition here, isn't she?
See? I got your attention.
So tell me about her.
Who?
Your ex-Wife.
What do you want to know?
Well, we got time, so whdon'mo
n' you start from the beginning?
Hñt1 how did she
become a
Raline was turned
in the early 1700s in france.
- She was a courtesan.
- Oh, she was a hooker.
No, more like a friend
of the court.
- She's still got the moves.
- Beth, that's not her.
- Was the sex good?
- You understand that, right?
So you were on and off
for, like, 33 years.
Was it the sex that
kept you coming back?
What is this?
She kidnapped me
when i was 4--
Took me from my bed,
Terrorized me,
Almost killed me.
Yeah, coraline did that,
Not the woman that you
are currently stalking.
You're sure, 100%?
No room for doubt?
Get down. Get down.
Look, if that's the same woman
who destroyed my childhood,
I've gotta know.
Are you telling me
you can't understand that?
All right.
What do you want me to do?
If coraline reinvented
herself as morgan,
There must be something
she forgot to cover up,
Some piece of evidence
left behind.
You're the one who told me
that her story checked out.
On the surface.
But now i want to dig deeper.
You've got
to keep her occupied.
How am i supposed to do that?
Just turn on
the mick st. John charm.
What girl could resist?
All right, listen to me.
If morgan is coraline--
And i'm not saying she is--
If--
And she realizes
that you suspect her,
I don't know what she'll do.
I'll be careful.
But one way or another,
I will finally find out the truth.
We both will.
www.1000fr.Com present
Moonlight s01e09
capture:óåñåµä±ù
sync:óêäì@frs
Pretty.
My wife tina.
I want you to follow her.
I want to know where she goes
and who she sees.
So what makes you think
she's cheating on you?
I didn't say she was.
I've been doing this job
for a while now, mr. Haggans.
A man wants his wife followed,
He thinks
she's having an affair.
Tina's my second wife,
Obviously much younger.
I've given her
financial stability,
social status,
And what i expect in return is fidelity.
Lately, she's been distant,
secretive.
If she were an employee,
I'd suspect that she was
interviewing for another job.
But she's not an employee.
She's your wife.
Principle's the same.
I'm the c.E.O.
Of a forbes 500 company.
If my trophy wife
is stepping out,
I want to know about it before
my board of directors does,
And i want someone
with no ties to me
To be looking into it.
$25,000 now,
Another $25,000
upon delivery
Of all audio
and photo surveillance.
I know a photographer who will
be perfect for this job.
I hope he knows how
to keep his mouth shut.
You're the only person
that knows about this.
Anything shows up
on the internet,
I'll know who leaked it,
And there will be
severe consequences.
Do i make myself clear?
Crystal.
She's leaving my office building
on bunker hill today
Around 1:00 p.M.
Just one more question,
mr. Haggans.
You obviously
don't trust your wife.
Do you love her?
I own her, mr. St. John.
That's all you need to know.
I wasn't sure
that you'd show up.
Yeah, me either.
You'll notice i chose
a public place.
You're buying, right?
Yes, of course.
Ready to order?
I'm gonna have
the carpaccio plate
With some french fries
and, um,
This burgundy here--
The romanée-Conti richbourg.
Excellent choice.
And for you, sir?
Oh, nothing for me.
I'm on a special diet.
Yeah, you and everybody else
in this town.
Body image freaks.
Okay, so if you're not
here to break bread,
Then what's this about?
I want to apologize.
I would think so.
The other night,
i was completely out of line.
That's an understatement.
There's absolutely no excuse
for the way i acted.
Now are you talking about when
you ripped off my clothes
Or threw me to the ground
Or just generally
scaring the crap out of me--
Which one?
Pretty much all of the above.
It's just you look so much...
Like someone i know...
Knew...
a long time ago.
If that's the way that
you acted towards her, too,
I gather it didn't end
very well.
No. No, it didn't.
But i want
to make it up to you.
I have a surveillance case.
I need a photographer.
It's gonna be $10,000
for a couple of days' work.
$10,000?$1
Yeah.
The romanée-Conti richbourg.
Apology accepted.
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
French fry?
No, thanks.
You sure?
Why don't you
enjoy them for me?
So what's this case about?
Husband thinks his wife's
having an affair.
He wants proof
before he confronts her.
Sordid.
You can't always judge.
No, i meant that
in a good way.
About this, um, ex-Girlfriend
that i remind you so much of,
What happened?
Did she cheat on you or--
Ex-Wife, actually,
And, no, fidelity
wasn't our problem.
It was just
a very complicated relationship.
It's probably best
if we leave it there.
That sounds like a story.
So do you want
the job or not?
Let me see--
$10,000 to follow people around
And take picture
of them having sex?
I'm in.
Digging into a person's
background these days d
Is pretty simple--
Google search here,
credit check there...
Morgan took the job. She'll be
with me the rest of the day.
But when
thground goes back
More than 300 years...
Journalism 101--
Begin at the beginning.
Go back
to where it all started.
No!
What's that?
Oh, um, a fleur-De-Lis.
Did you know
that french courtesans
Were branded with them
back in the 18th century?
It's like a permanent
scarlet letter.
Oh, does this have something
to do with paris hilton?
Uh... no.
Oh, then i don't care.
Do you have a story you're working on?
I do, actually. I'm off
to do some research now.
Bring me something sexy
that i can lead with.
Sex, betrayal, murder--
This one's got it all.
Oh, she's pretty.
But for 6 grand ?? A new model
There's a lot of people around,
h t of cell phones.
That means a lot
of interference.
I'm gonna have to stay close if
haggans wants all this on tape.
I'll keep moving
and try to get clean shots.
Okay. This is for you.
Keep the line open.
You let me know if you see
anything that i don't, okay?
This is so "bourne identity."
I love it.
Okay.
Target entering plaza
from northeast corner.
I'm on her.
I think we got something.
I see him.
... we take a walk
What are they saying?
There's too much interference.
I'm gonna have to get closer.
Ok. So i know you're going
to the office tonight,
Look don't worry. I've got it all worked out.
I don't know. Sometimes i feel
like we waited too long.
No, baby, i told you.
No one else knows. It's just us.
How can you be sure
that he doesn't kn?
What?
Move. She sees you.Mick!
What's matter?
What is it?
Nothing. I'm just being paranoid.
??
???
What are they saying?
The microphone's
not picking up anything.
That was the money shot.
All right, you go.
Listen, when you go home,
act natural...
All right? If he finds out...
i know...
He'll kill us.
Talk to you later.
Mick, i got it.
It's full frame,l he kiss.
I'm amazing.
What's your problem?We can go up to haggans
right now with this photo.
It'll be, like,
the easiest 10 grand ever.
Yeah, i don't think
we should do that.
Why?
I just heard tina say that haggen's gonna kill her.
I know you're going
to the office tonight.
But what about me?
Look, don't worry.
I've got it all worked out.
You know, after the kiss i heard
what tina and owen were saying.
Wow, you were right
about the interference.
-Cell phones,traffic noise...
- Don't worry. I've got it all worked out.
- It's gonna take a while to sort this out.
- No one else knows.It's just us.
How can you be sure
that he doesn't know?
'Cause i know him.
No, that's not it.
It was right around here.
Talk to you later.
When you go home,
act natural.
I heard it. I heard it.
The man said,
"but if he finds out,"
And then tina responded,
"you know he'll kill us."
I swear to you i heard it.
I mean, it could be
a figure of speech, you know?
Like "i'd kill
for a burger right now."
You're not gonna really kill somebody for the hamburger.
Well, it didn't sound
like that to me.
And you're sure
it was them talking?
I'm positive.
Maybe the mike missed it.
And you think your ears
can pick up something
- That a $5,000 digital unidirectional
microphone can't? - Look
What if haggans
isn't thinking about divorce?
What if he's actually
gonna use this evidence
As an excuse
to murder his wife?
Wouldn't divorce be easier?
Yeah, and it'd also
be more public.
Haggans doesn't strike me
as the kind of man
Who wants his personal life
on display.
Well, you met him.
Does he strike you
as the kind of man
That would be capable
of murder?
Anybody is capable
of murder...
G-Given
the right circumstances.
Haggans hired you
to get information.
You're not responsible
for what he does with it, okay?
I'm not gonna get
those people killed.
No info, no paycheck.
Alright. I'll talk
to haggans again, okay?
Are you gonna ask him if he's
planning on murdering his wife?
You know what?
I might try something
a little more subtle than that.
Well, on the way we can
stop by "buzzwire."
I'm friendly with one
of the sound guys,
And maybe he can help us
clean up some of this audio.
I had a boyfriend in college
Who taught me
how to pick locks.
Thought it was
a cool party trick.
He also taught me how
to chug a beer in one gulp.
Not really as useful
as an adult.
It's one thing to be
in someone's space
When they invite you in.
They make the bed,
clean the dishes,
Hide the bong.
! T when they're
not expecting company,
That's when you see
how someone really lives.
Let's w morgan
really lives.
I need to see mr. Haggans.
Mr. Haggans isn't here.
I can see him.
Well, yes,
he's here technically,
But i've been given strict
orders not to disturb him.
Okay, why don't you just tell him
mick st. John is here to see him?
When mr. Haggans gives me an order,
i take it very seriously.
You tell him,
or i'm gonna tell him myself.
What is it about "i don't
want to be disturbed"...
Mr. Haggans wants to know
If you have the surveillance
he requested.
If so, i've been instructed
to give you your final payment.
I'm not giving the surveillance
to anybody but mr. Haggans...personally.
You tell your boss
when he's ready to see me,
He can have his surveillance--
Not before.
How'd that go?
Haggans wouldn't see me.
Okay. It doesn't mean
he's a murderer, though.
Doesn't mean he's not.
I'm gonna keep following tina
until we know for sure.
Biltmore hotel, room 713.
One hour.
We should follow them.
They're gonna be
at the biltmore in an hour.
Wait.
How did you know that?
Trust me.
Don't know what
i was expecting to find.
Impressive shoes, though...
Prada, y3, manolos...
I'm in the wrong line of work.
Guess immortals
don't shop at shoe barn.
On our way to morgan's loft? Where are you?
I know i know
It just only takes one minute
Or maybe just 2 minutes
I have one thing i ...
I have the perfect rig
for this...
And a long lens that'll
pick up a bead of sweat
From, like, a hundred yards.
You're enjoying this
way too much.
You know that, right?
Beth?
Hi.
Did you say something?
Yeah, i said,
come on, hurry up. Let's go!
Okay. I'm just...
Just making sure i...
have everything.
Always something...
Are you okay?
What you've got is good.
We don't have much time.
Come on, we don't want
to miss anything. Let's go.
Wow. Someone's sure
getting into the spirit.
I still don't know how you heard
them talking about this.
You must have ears
like a bat.
Uh, not like a bat,
exactly.
You know what? Be grateful.
I used to date a lot of musicians,
and after a few years on stage,
They're just, like,
deaf as doornails.
- Musicians, huh?
- Yeah.
Hey.
Hey, can you talk?
Not really. Where are you?
Still at morgan's.
That was close.
Yeah, it was way too close.
Oh, hurry up. The clothes are
starting to hit the floor.
Where are you?
I'm at a hotel.
Whose clothes
are hitting the floor?
You know something?I -I uh
I can't really
get into this right now.
Oh!
My god, this is gonna be hot!
Seriously,
what are you guys doing?
We're working the case.
Sounds like you're
working something.
You have to hurry up or i'm
just gonna start without you,
- 'Cause this is hot.
- Mick!
I gotta go. I...
i gotta go.
Mick?
Are they saying anything?
Not unless they're using deep
breathing and moaning as code.
Listen to this.
What would your father
think about this?
You're his wife.
Ask him yourself.
Haggans' wife is having
an affair with his son--
Her stepson.
Like that wouldn't be
the final nail in our coffin.
That's kinky...
And a pretty good motive
for murder.
Yeah.
Hey!
How's thcase going?
There's nothing like spending the
afternoon
Cuddled up in a hotel room
watching family members gettin' it on.
They're--They're not even actually
related biologically, so...
It was like pay-Per-View,
but more hair.
Do you want to see
their photos? They're so hot.
I think--No.
They're confidential.
You're not blushing right now,
but i think you're actually embarrassed.
You're so cute.
You're so old-Shioned.
No, i'm not.
You weren't so shy
when it was happening.
Seems like you make
quite the team.
I was thinking maybe we could make this
a permanent arrangement.
I tend to work alone.
I mean, there's gotta be
something for beth to do, right?
We could make it
a threesome or something.
I would love that, but i've got
my own investigation going on--
Research on this new story.
You know maureen--Relentless.
But, um...
you two have fun.
Hey, listen, beth,
Morgan and i are gonna be
here for a couple of hours.
So, uh, maybe, uh, maybe i'll
see you when you get back.
Maybe.
I'll call you
when i'm wrapping up.
Hey.
About what happened
at the hotel...
Which part?
The kiss.
That was nice, huh?
Well, sure, but...
Don't be all weird.
It was--
Doesn't mean anything.
Unless you want it to.
No. Of course not. I mean...
Oh, i get it.
You don't want me to tell beth.
You've got it bad for her,
don't you?
Which i gotta say,
i don't think she's your type.
- Really?
- Uh-Huh.
Well, what do you
think my type is?
Well, that would be me...
Looking so much like
the ex and all.
Mick st. John.
This is mr. Haggans' assistant.
Mr. Haggans wants to know if you're ready
To hand over the materials he requested.
Well, that depends.
Is he ready to meet with me?
Mr. Haggans will meet with you
if you have the surveillance.
Okay, you tell him one hour,
the ca va restaurant.
We can discuss my terms of
handing over the surveillance.
You're meeting
with haggans?
Maybe i can find out if he suspects
that his son is the one involved with tina.
I'm taking everything back to my office
on my way to the restaurant.
I'm not giving haggans anything
until i know what he's up to.
Let me have your memory card.
Well, this is unexpected.
Thank you.
Sell that.
I need to talk to you
about mick.
I know you're his friend.
Is he in trouble?
I don't know.
I think so.
It's his ex-Wife coraline.
Coraline died
a long time ago.
I don't think she did.
I think she survived
and became human
And is masquerading
as morgan vincent.
I don't know what mick
has told you about me.
Not much, but i know
you're a... vampire,
Vampire
And i know he trusts you.
And what do you want?
The truth.
I'm sorry, sir,but you can't
just keep sitting here
Without ordering something.
I'm waiting for someone.
Have a sandwich while you wait.
- No, thank you.
- Something off the dessert menu?
I'm not hungry.
Then why do you keep meeting people at restaurants?
Fine, but at this point,
maybe you should consider...?
Your date's not showing.
How did it go with haggans?
He never showed.
He never intended to.
It was a ruse to get me
out of my office
So he could steal
the surveillance!
Well, let's go to his office
and confront him then.
No. I have to get
to haggans' son.
Haggans now knows about
his relationship with tina.
All right. I'm gonna look up
his address for you right now.
Let's see...
All right, here we go.
Owen haggans...
- "22 wedgewood lane, bel air."
- I'm on my way.
- Be careful.
- Yeah, yeah.
Thought you were
a photographer.
Yeah, i am.
You can still think that.
Then why did
one of my sound guys
Give me this jump drive
to give to you?
Because i asked him
to clean up some audio for me.
That's why.
What story is this for?
It's, uh, it's still
in the concept stages,
But i think you're
really gonna love it.
Mm.
I met morgan.
And sure, she looks like
coraline--
A lot like coraline.
But it's not her.
Morgan is not a vampire.
What if coraline found a way
to become human again?
Oy. First mick, now you.
There is no cure for vampirism--
No magic pill,
No click your ruby slippers
together
And rejoin the mortal coil.
Becoming a vampire
is a one-Way street.
There has to be a way.
I think mick--
Look,
when it comes to coraline,
Mick doesn't think
with his big head.
You have to understand,
Mick and coraline's relationship
Was one of those terrifying,
completely self-Destructive freak shows
That you spend
your whole life searching for
Knowing it can only end
in one or both of you dead.
That's your idea of love?
What can i tell you?
I'm a romantic.
This was coraline's house
in hollywood,
Where they first met.
Yeah, it was quite
the scene back then.
She could really
throw a party.
So you knew her?
Met her for the first time
in new york.
Lincoln was president.
Mick said she was
a courtesan.
Yeah?
Well, coraline was a lot
of things to a lot of people--
- Most of them men.
- But mick was different?
Yeah.
She wanted him and got him...
And then really
worked him over.
But eventually,
the crazy got to be too much,
And mick wanted out.
You know, he'd break it off,
But, uh, coraline was
like a bad drug habit.
He kept going back to her.
Until she took me?
Mick couldn't stand the thought
of a child dying because of him.
Finally, one happy family.
It was too much.
It gave him the strength
to break away once and for all.
I remember the fire.
I watched her burn.
I haven't been able
to ask mick this.
I know he feels guilty enough
as it is,
But why did coraline
choose me?
Maybe she thought she could
put a little family together and settle down,
Like the woman who gets pregnant
to save a bad marriage.
Why you specifically?
You were probably
Just in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
But it didn't work.
She didn't get him back.
Look, i think you know mick
better than that.
And you knew coraline
for a long time.
So if she is back,
what does she want?
If coraline is back,
And that's a big "if,"
She's back for mick.
I made up my mind
To see coraline's party house
for myself.
It's one thing
to want to know the truth,
It's another
to confront it head-On.
My mind has spent so long
trying to protect me...
Shieldg me
from what happened.
It was the only way
i could feel safe.
Even now, something inside me
is screaming "stop,"
But i can't,
And i'm beginning to wonder
if i'll ever feel safe again.
Yeah?
My name's mick st. John.
I'm a private investigator
hired by your father.
Come on in.
Thanks.
I told you.
No one else knows, just us.
Hey, listen. When you
go home, act natural, okay?
It's planned out,
But if he finds out
we're trying to kill him--
Hey, listen.
When you go home, act natural.
It's planned out,
but if he finds out
- We're trying to kill him...
- I know.
He'll kill us first.
So, uh, why would my fathe
hire a private investigator?
To follow tina.
He suspected
she was having an affair,
But he didn't know with whom.
It was you?
You broke into my office?
We can't take the chance
that anyone else knows.
We'll never get to my father
if he suspects.
So we kill him tonight.
Mick?
Come on. Pick up, mick.
Mick.
Here.
Oh, my god.
They must have hit me
from behind.
Oh, my god. Here.
Thank you.
All right, let's get you
to a hospital.
No, no, i'm fine.
It's just a scalp laceration.
They're always worse
than they look.
What?
Uh, look, they look worse
than they are.
That's what i meant.
Haggans wasn't the one
planning the murder.
I know that.
Haggans
is the intended victim.
They're going after haggans now.
We have to get to him first.
Oh, my god.
Hi, honey.
It's okay.
You have to go to bed now,
okay?
There, there.
This is the she kept me,
alone,
Locked in this room,
Waiting to bring me
to the cabin to meet mick,
To lure him back.
To make us a family
in her deranged mind.
Okay, there we go.
You need to get some sleep
tonight. You know why?
Because tomorrow's a big day.
You're gonna meet
your new daddy tomorrow.
I'm gonna take you
to meet your new daddy.
Hey.
- Mr. Haggans isn't here.
- Where is he?
- Gone for the day.
- Where'd he go?
I'm not at liberty to say.
Tell me where haggans is,
Or you better hope this job
has a good dental plan.
He just left two minutes ago
with his son.
You take the elevator.
Tina's waiting in the car
for us.
You're not gonna tell me what
the plan is, where we're going?
No. Come on, dad.
You'll ruin the surprise.
Surprise.
Mr. St. John.
Hey! What the hell are you--
That's my son!
Yeah, it's your son.
That's also your wife's lover.
These two have been conspiring
to kill you.
That's impossible.
Call the police.
Now! Now!
Morgan!
Holy crap.
What was that?
And they said jordan
had air.
The son and the stepmom
have an affair,
Conspire to kill
the husband/father?
They probably figured
with him out of the way,
They could have both the company
and each other.
Remind me to have kids.
Listen, haggans' assistant,
a guy named tucker,
Lured me out of my office
for owen.
- He had to have been working with him.
- I'll send a car.
You do have evidence
to back all this up?
Audio and visual.
We're gonna need
those photographs.
Morgan.
Sorry.
Sorry. I'm just still
a little freaked out.
I've never been
almost killed.
You got everything
you need?
Yeah. Go home
and get cleaned up.
You can bring everything
down to the station tomorrow.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Do you want something,
mick?
Coraline.
Are you really surprised?
How many clues
did i have to give you?
The proust book,
our old song.
I even ordered
my favorite glass of wine.
You really thought
you killed me, didn't you?
How have you done this, huh?
How have you done...
Become human?
Yeah.
I thought it would
get your attention.
You seemed to like
the human girls.
You're telling me
there's a way back, hmm?
there's a cure?
Tell me. Tell me.
- Mick!
- Wait.
Mick!
I got the proof.
She's been lying to us,
stalking us.
Morgan is coraline.
- I know she is.
- You know?
Hi, beth.
How could you?
This isn't what you think.
No! No! No!
What are you doing?
Oh, my god.
Try not to move.
What have you done?
Listen to me, coraline.
Try not to move.
We have to get her
to a hospital.
Stakes don't kill vampires.
They just paralyze them.
She's not a vampire.
She's coraline!
You just said so herself!
She's coraline,
but she's not a vampire!
Not anymore.
She's human.
There is a cure.
She has a cure.
welcome to www.1000fr.Com