Time traval, it's sounds so excited ???
but in a way,we travelha
through time every day.
a childhood memory can
instantly pull you into the past.
a wish can send you zooming into the future.
what's actually hard is to stay
planted in the present,
to be here,in the now.
i want to go home now.
calm down. you're fine.
mom,a brain doctor does not call
and say that he has to see you
unless there is something seriously wrong,okay?
you're not dying. you're not even warm.
if i slip into a coma again,do
not unplug anything,okay?
not a machine,not a radio. nothing.
oh. there's my favorite patient.
- hi.
- i bet your earyo n burning.
huh? um,yeah,they kinda--
they have,uh,maybe,sort of.
- is that bad?
- oh,no,no,no.
it just means people have
been talking about you.
okay,now the reason i called you here...
uh,it's strange not having our
weekly appointments,isn't it?
- they were like little dates for me.
- doctor,please,do you mind?
- i can't stand this. is she dying or not?
- oh,no,no,no,no,no,no.
no,no. we want her to be
part of a clinical trial. hmm?
we are close to getting
f.d.a. approval for a new drug
that will help people with
various forms of memory loss.
oh! oh,wow. that--that's it?
wow. i mean,you know,you could
have just le jhat on the machine.
oh,he did. i forgot.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:Evelyn~zx
Sync:Dear.Ryan
Samantha Who S2 ep03
see,this is the side of the brain
where the memory is.
it's a--it's--it's a very-- it's a
very exclusive study,
because apparently,
i am one of very few
high-functioning amnesiacs
in the entire country.
said the girl wearing black
shoes and brown pants.
okay. you know what? sometimes
einstein left the house naked.
how much are you getting paid for this anyway?
there's a guy in texas who got paid 25 grand
to have his foot cut off and reattached.
ooh,i'd do that for $13,500.
it's not about money,guys,
i just want to help people,
you know,and i want to
know that i helped people,
and i kind of want people
to know that i helped people.
oh,did i mention that they might
call it the "newly report"?
so what's it feel like?
well,it feels like nothing right now
'cause i only took the pill about an hour ago.
maybe you're the placebo.
no. no,i don't want to be the placebo.
you're not supposed to
remember anything that they--
aah! jeez.
what are you crying about?
you scared the crap out of me.
nope. not the placebo.
you just had one. what
was it? was it about me?
no. no. it--it was just,uh,
it was about kids and balloons
and stuff. it was really nice.
oh,dr. andy wants me to write this stuff down.
- free notebook. score.
- yeah.
- um,sam?
- yeah?
the guy we hate is parked over there.
oh,well. i'm sure this guy
did something wrong.
oh. okeydoke.
these are coming on a little strong,
so i think i'm gonna
just go lay down for a little.
- okay. well,feel better.
- thanks. bye,you guys.
oh,that poor bird.
well,hello there.
hello,yourself.
and who do you belong to?
- they're mine. they belong to me.
- they're mine.
they're mine,mine,mine,mine,mine. i love them.
lucky dogs. you have two
mommies fighting over you.
ah!
he thinks we're a couple.
- that's so funny.
- that's not funny,
it's a little funny,yeah.
maybe you should be mom,
and i-i should be mommy.
i don't want to confuse them.
hey,frank.
miss newly.
morning,ma'am. i'm frank,the new doorman.
i just want to say what a
pleasure it is to meet you.
shh. okay,here's what i need.
hold the door for me,hail my cabs,
and i don't like guys who send flowers,
so you can just throw those about.
you do all that,hank,and you might keep your job.
yes,miss newly.
i'm sorry,frank.
what's wrong?y.
nothing. oh,i lucked out.
i got to be part of this,um,this
study for memory recovery.
- you have crazy eyes. is that part of the study?
- i don't know. i'm not a scientist,so...
will you be okay alone?
because i was gonna head
out and look at an apartment.
what? oh. what happened
to the one from yesterday?
- it had a view.
- well,it also had a smell.
it turns out there was a goat's
head in the refrigerator.
- plus,somebody beat me to it,so...
- well,i hope you get this one.
i mean,for you.
i mean,i know it's been really
weird living here,you know,
for you and me.
for us.
mostly for you.
and me.
- i'll let you know.
- okay.
good-bye.
almost there.
okay. almost there.
mommy,can i come home tonight?
well,what time is your dinner party over?
and for youself ,???
you got your notebook and your...
your pills.
- thank you.
- and a wave machine.
i got this for your father on his last birthday,
but it made him have to tinkle all night.
i'm sorry i'm being such a baby about this.
it's just that these memories
are so vivid,you know?
like stepping off the curb,
and i was crying for some reason,
and these brakes--oh!
and i was wearing this very bright green jacket.
i know. it's probably a blessing in disguise.
that jacket never looked good on you.
anyway,um,maybe i'm just--
i'm--i'm--i'm skimming the bad
ones off the top,you know,
so i can get down to the good ones,
kind of like that skin that
forms on the top of pudding,
you know,and underneath there's just--
there's just chocolaty goodness.
ah,there are memories i'd love to have back,
like that summer before i had you.
yeah,thanks.
mom!
i had a great body that summer.
fine. but you know what?
don't come crying to me when,yoknow,
- y-you come crying to me,okay?
- all right,all right.all right,all right. fine.
good night. sleep tight.
the pill's working already.
i just remembered-- todd called,
and he said that he's got a new apartment.
really? he found an apartment? wow.
that's what you wanted,right?
yeah. yeah. no,it's just that he did it.
it's just... so not todd.
- oh,cute.
- well,you look nice.
thanks. do you have anyplace special in mind?
um,yeah,actually.
there's this cute place off i-90 west.
i-90?
wait. so our first date is really
me giving you a ride to the airport?
we have three hours. you're
lucky there's fog in new york.
what are you doing?
there must be men who actually
put up with this stuff,
or you wouldn't even try. good night.
don't be a jerk.
you know what? your not
giving a girl a ride to the airport
says something about your manners.
can you believe that todd guy hasn't called me?
i mean,who is he to not call me?
- i mean,i'm the one who doesn't call him.
- what do you care? forget about him.
- no,you're right. you're right. i'm done.
- wanna go to the bar?
do you know what he drives?
i was just rejected by a guy
whose windows zipper.
well,that guy over there owns a jet,
two buildings and three senators.
i mean,i practically apologized
to him,and he ignores me?
oh,nuh-unh. no. no,no,no,no.
no,he does not get to choose.
hello,todd.
- you.
- mm-hmm.
i thought i was hired to
photograph a kids' party.
well,what was i supposed to do?
you wouldn't return my phone calls.
oh,man. i should have gotten it
when i saw it was this building.
you're... "mrs. butterworth"?
yeah,well,i don't know anybody named "missus."
and so what?
you can take pictures of me
now,naked or whatever.
i'm very cooperative.
- wow.
- what?
well,you went to a lot of
trouble to get me here.
- you're really into me.
- shut up.
you are. why don't you put on some clothes,
and we'll go get some food?
i mean,unless you've never
done it in that order before.
jerk.
just let me put on some jeans.
ooh,bad night?
ugh. awful.
just all night long,just more
bad things that i did.
bad,bad,bad,then i had to get up to pee,
and more bad and bad,pee,
turned off that wave machine
and just bad.
- montpelier.
- i'm sorry?
capital of vermont. i can never remember that one.
these pills are great.
oh,yeah. they're like a party in my head.
u know what it does to me
when you wear that skirt.
she's kidding.
stop it. why are you doing this?
because you actually hate that
people think you're gay.it's too fun.
i don't care if someone thinks i'm gay.
i re if they think i'm with you.
- no offense.
- in what world is that no offense?
i'm just saying,if i were gay,i
would be with someone else.
like who? i haven't thought about it.
- like,for instance?
- i don't know. carol in payroll.
oh! not in a million years
could you get hot lesbian carol from payroll.
hey,i can get anyone i want.
i am the hottest lesbian that's not
a lesbian in the entire world.
i don't know how much longer i can do this,mom.
i want to help people and all,but i just--
- i feel like such a loser.
- sweetie,listen to me.
listen. i saw this article...
oh,lord. that was five years ago.
i'm a genius!
- anyway...
- mm-hmm.
about how the mind protects us
and only allows us to recall
as much as we can handle.
so if you're remembering really
bad things about yourself,
just imagine how truly awful
the things you're not remembering are.
yeah. i'm all better.
thanks. that's great.
hello?
samantha? oh,it's nic to hear your voice.
how did you,uh,do last night?
actually,doctor,i had a really rough time.
um,these--these pills are really somethin'.
aren't they?
why don't you go ahead and throw those away?
- just toss 'em.
- uh,well,if you're sure...
the drug company is suspending the trial. it's...
it's no biggie,just--just a few people
reporting some tiny side effects.
oh,gosh. yoknow,i just feel terrible.
i mean,i guess i'm just gonna have
to do good for people some other time.
i feel terrible,too.
maybe we could,uh,make our own memory?
yeah. okay. bye.
bye.
what was that?
no,no,no. what was that?
oh,no. that was a good one.
that was a good one. i
need another pill. oh,no!
I just need one more pill.
you gotta hook me up,doc.
- samantha,there are no more pills.
- don't tell me that,man!
i need a slam. i need a bang. i need a pop.
uh-huh. i think you might be making up slang.
i just need one more,okay?
i-i-i started to get pieces of
this really,really cool memory
about--of--of... oh,no. shoot.
- of us? was it us?
- no. damn it! what's going on?
- am i losing my memories now?
- no. that's a funny story.
yes. you are,but only the new memories--
the ones that were brought on by the drug.
so all these new memories that i'm having
are just gonna be gone,like,forever?
as soon as the drug leaves your system,yes. oh.
but if there's any changes
in the trial,i will call you.
in fact,i-i'd like to call you anyway.
yeah,but it was something
really important,though,
and i-i need to know what.
come here. come here.
what? oh. thank you. oh,there we--oh!
i-i gotta run. i have a thousand
meetings to get to.
-i'll see you later,okay?
- okay.
- bye.
what are you doing?
no,i'm not letting go until
you give me a real hug.
ugh. my god,you are such a girl. here.
- no.
- what? oh.
look at your shoulders.
they're way up here. drop 'em.
drop 'em more.there you go.
i hate you.
i just had another one,about todd.
todd? yay!
oh,but it's just gonna go away,isn't it? oh.
nope? we can do it later.
carol.
oh,hey!
oh,hey. oh,dena. hi.
just bringing chase some lunch and checking in.
his new assistant sounds a
little too pretty on the phone.
people tell me i have a beautiful phone voice.
oh,joan didion. i love her.
- andrea belladona's office.
- yeah,so di. you know,
i just finished reading "slouching
towards bethlehem"... oh.
and now i'm going back to
reread "play it as it lays." oh!
i love your blouse.
mine's kind of tight.
it keeps opening. see,it's open.
it's open.
okay.
that shirt thing worked three
times last christmas party.
these things work. they work.
hey. this is sam. and todd.
what--what are you doing?
i live here. i get my name on
the answering machine.
- no,no. that's not part of the deal.
- our phone line,our machine.
oh,my god. why don't you just
stamp "property of todd"on my ass?
or better yet,why don't you go ahead
and absorb me like an evil twin?
what?
what,did you not pay the electric bill?
todd,i ask you to do one thing.
what are you doing? get up.
sam...
he proposed.
cut it out,all right? things are
good the way they are.
they are. it's why i want more.
we live together,todd.
i mean,that's more than i've given to anyone.
you should just say thanks.
that should be a thank you ring.
wait. and this is where you push
me away because you're scared.
- do not tell me how i'm feeling.
- i'm trying to tell you i love you.
yeah,well,if you did,you wouldn't do this.
you're right. forget it.
big mistake.
there. never happened. better?
so now you're just gonna try to
make me feel bad about it?
feel however you want,sam. you alwa do. good-bye!
nice! very romantic!
hey. give me a pen. give me a pen.
please,please,please.
i don't have a pen.
- no,you have to have a pen.
- wait. wait. here. i have a lipstick.
okay. oh,god. oh,my god.
it was me! i was the scaredy-cat.
and now i'm pushing him away again?
oh,my god. i have to stop him.
what is this,tangerine? it's nice.
keep it.
thanks. okay.
Hey,Todd,it's me ,pick up,pick up
listen,i'm on my way back to the apartment.
i remember the proposal,so please don't go.
we really have to talk. proposal. proposal.
okay. proposal. proposal. proposal. proposal.
do not talk to me,frank. proposal.
always my first choice.
i-i tried. i did everything i
could,and it's not enough.
you do not get to choose when we break up.
i just did.
yeah,i just cut it all off.
todd loved my hair long.
that'll teach him.
- oh,hey. hey. listen--
- did your mom tell you i found a place?
- as soon as they process the application,i'm in.
- shh. shh. listen to me,okay?
it's not big. it's a little dark,
but there's zero goat heads,
- and i'm feeling pretty good about that.
- listen. listen. we need to talk.
i-i justeed you to know
that i am so sorry that i...
that i what?
oh. oh. it's here. it's here.
um,i'm--i'm,uh,for the pro--prof--
p... p...
um,pro-- it--it--it smeared.
pom--pomnip--uh,does
that-- any of that ring a bell?
you know what? hold on. there's a message.
hey,todd. it's me. pick up. pick up.
listen,i'm on my way--
well,you're here now. what was it?
- i don't know. it's gone.
- well,i'm sure it'll come back.
no. it won't.
maybe it was nothing.
oh,hi.
just reading a little didion,like usual.
there's nothing like a "'poignant and
trenchant look "at marriage in the 21st century,'
says the new york--" me.
why are you stalking me?
- what? i-i'm--i'm not.
- i know that you keep calling me and hanging up.
your extension shows up on my phone.
it does?
i call everyone in the office just to say hi.
okay,why don't you like me?
excuse me?
kiss me. kiss me. just do it.
okay,that's it.
you just bought yourself a
sit-down with human resources.
no. ooh. ooh. wait. wait,carol,okay?
you know,just go easy on her,okay?
she's not right. i think we
both--we both know that.
you know what i mean?
for you.
okay.
why is she not attracted to me?
i think she's stupid. i hate her.
well,maybe she's not into looks.
you know,maybe-- maybe she dislikes you...
for who you are.
you think?
andrea,life has a way of evening things out,
and pretty on the outside
usually doesn't get to be pretty on the inside,
and,andrea,you are very... very...
pretty on the outside.
thank you.
i just checked my voice mail.
i was turned down for the apartment.
it was a done deal.
it was my place--a crappy
place--but it was mine.
you know,um...
you could always just stay here.
excuse me?
well,you know,until you--
you find exactly what you want.
okay...
when did we ever worry about what i wanted?
i know. i know. i--it just--
i-i can't explain it entirely,
i just know,that looking over these notes,
everything ends with a "bad to todd,"
or "apologize to todd" or "buy todd a new bird."
that was you.
i just think i would feel a lot better
if i could just make it up to you.
so i'd be doing you a favor?
if you wouldn't mind.
- no rent then?
- a favor,not a charity.
but as just... friends,right?
yeah,of course. just as--
just as... friends,you know?
or not friends if you don't want to do that.
we could,you know,just be roommates.
no,no,no. friends would be nice.
you know,because i'll probably
slide on the rent a few times,
and my roommate might not understand.
navigating through memories can be quite a trip.
and maybe it's true,
maybe the mind,like any smart traveler,
does know where it's safe
to go and where it's not.
at least,until the time is right.
welcome to www.1000fr.com