Emergency personnel
would like to reiterate
that the mudslide in question
is a natural disaster,
not a giant alcoholic beverage.
They ask that citizens
please stop driving toward it.
And in lighter news,
it's time to turn our spotlight
on a local loony.
Let's meet Joy Turner,
Camden's Loser of the Week.
There was a reason why Joy was
on the Camden Loser of the Week segment,
and it was all my fault.
It started a few years back
when Joy was making
an audition tape for Fear Factor.
Unfortunately, I was responsible
for sending the tape in and...
it didn't quite make it there.
So I got her another shot
at being famous
on a game show where people can
challenge Erik Estrada to anything,
but instead of becoming famous,
she looked like a psycho,
and even worse,
I wound up blowing Darnell's cover
in the witness protection program,
which meant the family had to pack,
except for one member.
As you all know
from the fliers I put up,
Mr. Turtle remains lost.
The good news is:
I gave him plenty of survival training,
so I expect his imminent return.
So here's his food,
his favorite scarf,
and his lip balm for the dry season.
Next thing we knew,
the government snatched
Joy, Darnell and the boys away.
And even though me and Randy were woozy
from the needles stuck in our necks,
I still knew what I had to do.
I promised Joy
I'd make her dream come true.
We got to find them.
Which wasn't going to be easy
'cause the Turner family was already
in a witness relocation facility.
I know it's small,
but it was good enough for Tupac.
You didn't hear that.
DARNELL OUTED (PART 2)
Joy, Darnell and the kids
were waiting to start their new lives.
We have been locked for hours...
No idea where we are
or what happens next...
and I still don't know what you did to
get in the program in the first place.
Nobody does, except for Mr. Turtle,
and it's not
like he's telling anybody,
for one, because he's lost,
and for two,
you know, he's a turtle.
Mr. and Mrs. Turner,
sorry to keep you waiting so long.
Inside this packet you will find
your new family identity.
I'll give you a little time
to look it over.
The Rosensteins?
I do speak Hebrew.
We're from Columbus... We bowl.
Other hobbies include
designing clothes for our pet collie.
We got to get
something better than this.
We're trailer park underachievers
with two hyperactive, pre-diabetic kids.
How is this not better?
Since we didn't know where to start,
we combed the trailer park,
looking for any clue we could find.
Then, one walked right by us.
Sorry, I didn't see you over there.
You're on my bad side.
Bad side? No way.
The side with the eye patch
kicks ass.
Any mail for the Turners?
They must have moved because
all their mail is being forwarded.
- Any idea where their mail's going?
- Don't know.
Just know it's being forwarded.
That got me thinking.
If Joy and Darnell's mail
was finding them, I could, too.
You know, you spend years
hoping for an excuse
to mail yourself somewhere
in a cool wooden crate,
but when you actually get in the crate,
it's not so glamorous.
All this complaining,
and you guys are in a first-class box.
Americans are so spoiled.
While me and Randy
were trying to get to Joy,
Joy was trying to get
to the life she wanted.
So you're not happy
with the name you've been given.
That's right.
You'd like your name to be
Goldie Crystal.
My full name would be Goldilocks,
it's pronounced "Cristal"
like what Diddy drinks.
Sorry. New identities are worked out
in a top secret wing of the Pentagon.
The names are the result
of complicated mathematical algorithms.
Phyllis and Marty Rosenstein?
Look at this face.
Do I look like a Phyllis to you?
No, I look like the woman
Marty leaves Phyllis for.
I'm just trying to help.
They don't have this in Columbus.
I got to be from some place classy
like Panama City Beach, Florida.
And one more thing: a lady like me
don't make clothes for dogs.
Only thing I ever sewed was
my stab wound on prom night.
With all due respect,
Mrs. Rosenstein,
things don't work that way.
This is who you are now.
Give it some time.
You'll get used to it.
Not now.
He wouldn't let me change
one mouse-farting thing.
I guess I'm really going to be
Phyllis Rosenstein
for the rest of my life.
It's just a name.
We're still the same people,
except we're Jewish
and they're considering
changing my blood type.
O positive.
Mommy, did you get
our new names changed?
Ira, Lenny,
I did all I could.
This is exciting.
Yeah, it kind of is, Randy.
We haven't taken a trip
together in a long time.
That's if you don't count
my dreams every night
where we visit
all the great places in the world.
Last night we were on a safari.
You made love to a hippo.
You always make love in my dreams.
Someone's coming.
If that's you in there,
have a good vacation.
We were on our way
to get to Joy and Darnell,
and we weren't the only ones
looking for 'em.
While we were heading out
to find the Turners,
the Turners were turning
into the Rosensteins.
Dag, I can't believe
it took me into my 30s
to find out
I look this good in tweed.
Shalom, Dad.
Shalom, boys.
Baby, come out. Let's see who
Marty gets to cuddle with tonight.
Oh, man.
Perfect. No one will pay
any attention to you,
especially men.
I know.
How could you do this to me?
It's like you took an episode
of The Swan and ran it backwards.
Oh, my God. I'm a before.
We all got to sacrifice.
They're going to surgically take
my hair off and graft it to my face.
It's a new process,
we're very proud of it.
Here's a picture
of what he'll look like.
And we plan
on you gaining 30 pounds.
Double-stuffed tater skins?
You're trying
to turn me into a fatty.
You're trying to mess with this?
Hell, no.
Where is she going?
Does she know we're in a bunker
half a mile under the Mall of America?
Baby, you in here?
It's hard to track her
when she's not chewing gum.
I usually just follow the scent
of strawberry-kiwi Hubba Bubba.
Listen, you got
to get her under control.
She's a risk, Harry.
That's why you were advised
to leave Camden,
so you wouldn't get mixed up
with people like her.
That's my wife.
You were only supposed
to be in Camden for six months.
Now, if you'd taken that job
we had for you in Tokyo,
you would have been the one
who invented Dance Dance Revolution,
but you wanted to waste your life
in a trailer park.
That wasn't a waste.
That was the best decision of my life.
You could have left Camden?
They wanted you to leave Camden
and go off to the glamorous beaches
of Tokyo, and you didn't do it?
I couldn't leave my baby.
I love you, Marty Rosenstein.
I'll hold up my end of the deal,
no matter how much it hurts.
I hear you.
They're going to snip off
the tip of my penis tomorrow.
Being in that box was fun at first,
but 6 hours
and 3 truck changes later,
the fun was wearing off.
This is horrible.
I'm starving, and I already ate
the emergency jerky I keep in my cheek.
All right, I was going
to save this for later, but...
I caught a cricket.
- You want to split it?
- Yes, please.
What do you want...
breast or thigh?
Breast.
This must be a female one.
I taste a little milk.
I got to taste something else
to make the flavor go away.
You're not licking me.
Don't you see what's happening?
Getting shocked, eating bugs.
These are things Joy did
on her Fear Factor tape.
Karma's punishing us
for ruining her dream.
We're stopping.
- I think we're here.
- What do we do now?
Wait for them to open us.
Knowing all Darnell
sacrificed for her,
Joy decided to be
the best Phyllis Rosenstein ever.
We're going to start
with a grocery store.
Excuse me, Miss,
you look so familiar.
Do I know you from somewhere?
I don't know.
See if any of this rings a bell.
I was raised in Columbus, Ohio,
but I was born in Sandusky.
I was bat-mitzvahed
at Temple Beth Torah.
What a party.
Had my first dance
with Shmokey Bernstein.
He grabbed my tucchus.
So she memorized
everything about Phyllis.
I've been designing for 8 years.
My company is called
"Collie want a cracker."
I have to say my signature piece
is the puppy peacoat.
She even learned to speak Jewish.
That cricket breast isn't settling
very well in my stomach.
Joy threw up, so Karma's going
to make you throw up, too.
Don't worry, Earl.
I'm not going to thr...
Damn it, Randy,
now I'm going to throw...
What the hell?
We're in a dumpster.
We covered Joy in garbage
on her audition tape.
This one's to Peter Dick Johnson,
that guy who used to live
in the trailer park.
Remember how much we used
to make fun of his name?
Those were some fun times.
I heard he jumped
in front of a train.
All this stuff
has been stamped, "Forward."
Must be mailed for people who moved.
The post office isn't forwarding it.
Oh, man, and there are
so many letters in here
for Santa Claus and God.
They're gonna be pissed
when they find out
they didn't get their mail.
And those are two guys
you do not want to piss off.
I can't believe Karma would put us
through all this just to punish us.
I mean, the bugs and the box
and the throw-up.
And all for nothing?
What the hell is going on?
Son of a bitch.
It's a letter from Estrada or Nada.
Joy could get another chance
to be on the show. Listen.
"Send in this application,
"a check for $50 made out
to Erik Estrada,
"and get your friends to text
message their vote for you."
That's it, Randy.
That's why Karma brought us here.
If we can get Joy
on that show again,
she'll come back from anywhere
in the world to be on it.
That's great, Earl.
Where can we find a check
that's already made out
to Erik Estrada?
In order to get to Joy,
we started at Jasper's.
Somebody left a tooth
in this retainer.
Yeah, that's a nice tooth.
It's nicer than yours.
If you pulled out your front tooth,
that thing would fit perfect.
Good idea.
- I'll take these.
- Why you need all my cell phones?
For text voting.
One of the Camden contestants
on Estrada or Nada
had some bad mayonnaise
and died for three minutes.
He's alive now,
but in no shape to compete.
Now they're having a contest
to see who's gonna replace him.
That's messed up.
Your one shot at fame
undone by a condiment.
I feel smarter already.
I'll be right back.
My money's in the car.
Oh, buddy.
I passed out the cell phones
to everyone I knew
and asked them
to text their vote for Joy
to get a chance to compete
against Erik Estrada.
Sure, I'll text for Joy.
Maybe if she comes out of hiding,
the bad guys will kill her.
Everybody spent the next two days
texting votes
and crank-calling each other.
By the time
they announced the winner,
we had the whole Crab Shack
rooting for Joy.
Now it's time for the results
of the text-in vote
to see who will replace the victim
of the mayonnaise tragedy,
go head-to-head with me
and find out if they're...
Estrada or Nada.
And the winner is...
Joy Turner.
And we weren't
the only ones watching.
Joy Turner.
Did you hear that?
America has spoken,
and they've spoken for me.
Baby, I feel terrible.
I always wanted to make you happy,
and I'm keeping you from your chance
to be famous and possibly
be in Parade magazine.
Are you kidding me?
I'd rather becPhyllis Rosenstein,
keep wearing these granny panties
and have my family
than to whup Erik Estrada
and have nobody to share it with.
Besides, we ain't allowed
to work today anyway.
It's Shabbat.
Marty, time to change
your blood type.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I love you, baby.
What the hell?
You got the rest of your life
to be Phyllis Rosenstein.
You deserve one more chance
to be Joy Turner.
Time to find out
if you're Estrada or Nada.
Where the hell is Joy?
Maybe she didn't see the commercial.
Maybe she's here, but we don't know it
because they changed her identity.
She could be anyone.
She could be a Chinese dude.
She could be that Chinese dude.
It's not her.
I'm out of ideas.
I was starting to think
this whole thing was a waste of time,
but at least I wasn't on stage
getting humiliated.
Alas, poor Yorick.
I knew him, Horatio.
A man of infinite jest
and excellent fancy.
To be... or nada to be!
Coming up next was supposed
to be Camden's Joy Turner
going head-to-head
against Erik Estrada
to see who has the better
circus variety act,
but unfortunately,
it looks like Joy is a no-show.
- I guess that means that Erik...
- Does this look like a no-show to you?
Erik Estrada, your ass is mine!
It is on now, people.
It is on!
And it was on.
Joy did a weird stretchy,
sing-y thing.
But Erik Estrada matched
Joy's amazing musical circus
stunt with one of his own.
They were both so good,
the judges decided
it would go into a...
Tiebreaker!
Joy got to pick
the first tiebreaker,
so she chose the body part
she used to win every fight:
her mouth.
But to her surprise,
Erik Estrada's nickname
wasn't Hot Tongue
just 'cause he was a good kisser.
And when breathing fire
didn't break the tie,
Erik Estrada chose
his secret weapon:
playing music on wineglasses.
But it turns out,
Joy was just as good.
They're going again!
That's when Joy came up
with the one thing she knew
no one else could beat her at:
a combination of all her new skills.
She called it dressing a dog
while talking Hebrew
with a follow-up trivia
question about Ohio.
Okay, here we go
with our trivia question
about the great state of Ohio.
Everyone knows
that East 105th Street and
Euclid Avenue in Cleveland
was the location of the first
pedestrian button
for the control of a traffic light.
Name the boy chosen
for the 1948 newsreel
to demonstrate its operation.
Okay, time's up.
Your answers, please.
The correct answer is...
L-O-
U- I-S. Oh, my God!
I can't believe this!
Joy is right!
The great one has fallen.
Congratulations, Joy Turner.
I gotta tell you.
You remind me of a young me.
Full of drive and passion.
And an esoteric knowledge of Ohio.
Get ready, Joy Turner.
You're about to be famous.
You made this happen, didn't you?
I knew you weren't a nada,
and I wanted to make sure
everybody else knew it, too.
We better go.
Soon thousands of agents
will be swarming down on us.
While it's cool in movies,
it's not so cool when you're
the one being swarmed up on.
I guess this is it.
I know I might have divorced you,
and kicked you out
of your own house,
and tried to kill you,
multiple times...
but it all came out of love.
I know, Joy.
I'm gonna miss you, guys.
We've had a good run, Randy.
Some of the stuff you've said
will stay with me forever.
Like "What if dogs had legs
like shrimps."
- Shrogs.
- Or drimps.
Shrogs.
- Shrogs!
Let's not do this again.
Good-bye, Randy.
Bye, Darnell.
Good-bye, Earl.
After everything me and Joy
had been through,
and after all the things we'd yelled and
screamed at each other over the years,
I was surprised to find
there was one thing I couldn't say.
You didn't say good-bye.
I'll tell them next time.
Subtitles:
Jarick & loky