Earl, I need you
to drive over to joy's
And punch her in the face.
I don't think
that's a good idea, randy.
Are you saying that
because it's a great idea?
She did it again,
Didn't she?
Uh-huh.
And it was a real fancy bird.
(sam the sham and the pharaohs'
"wooly bully" begins)
Earl:
randy had invested a lot
Of his time and my money into
the crab shack claw machine.
I won a horse!
Who won a horse?
But, thanks to joy,
He didn't have much
to show for it.
I won a spider!
I will take that.
Thank you.
¶ and a wooly jaw,
wool bully... ¶
I won a bird dressed up
for a wedding!
And you're not getting it.
¶ wooly bully ¶
Catch.
(gasps)
(toy squeaks, joy laughs)
¶ watch it now, watch it ¶
¶ you got it, you got it. ¶
(sobbing)
Randy, you're 32 years old.
I can't protect you
from your bullies forever.
You need to learn
to stick up for yourself.
Joy's not going anywhere.
She's a part of our lives.
Man!
I'm always going to regret
giving her that heimlich.
I mean, first she sued me
and now this?!
Look, I know I go overboard
looking out for you,
But I'm not doing it anymore.
And while we're at it,
I'm not kissing your boo-boos
anymore, either.
It's getting awkward.
Even when we're alone?
Especially when we're alone.
You know the kind of guy
who does nothing
But bad things and then wonders
why his life sucks?
Well, that was me.
(shutter clicks)
Every time something good
happened to me,
Something bad was always
waiting around the corner.
Karma.
That's when I realized
I had to change.
So I made a list of everything
bad I've ever done,
And one by one, I'm going
To make up
for all my mistakes.
I'm just trying to be
a better person.
Captioning sponsored by
20th century fox television
And volkswagen.
It's what the people want.
Earl:
while randy was bummed
Because joy kept taking
his claw machine toys,
I was kind of happy
(sighs loudly)
'cause it reminded me
of something on my list.
(hums loudly)
Randy, this tantrum
is getting out of control.
Here we go.
"#32: bullied wally panzer."
When I was in the eighth grade,
My parents made a last-ditch
effort to fix me:
Catholic school.
I knew that the new kid
at school usually got picked on
Unless there was someone lower
on the totem pole than him.
So I decided
to make that happen.
(screams)
That kid loves butterflies.
And he hates when they die!
(continues screaming)
wally panzer.
More like wally pansy.
And once I smelled blood
in the water, I didn't let up.
Hey, everyone, look.
It's pant-less pansy.
But, like most things in life,
I pushed it too far.
Even thought I got kicked out,
my legacy lived on.
Wally wasn't hard to find,
Since if you hadn't left camden
by grade school,
Odds are you weren't leaving
camden at all.
Okay, the way I remember it,
This guy was
pretty delicate as a kid,
So try to be as friendly
as possible.
I don't want to spook him.
(sighs)
What do you want?
Uh, are you,
uh, w-wally panzer?
Yeah. Who are you?
Cliff.
You here about my ad
in the penny saver?
Mm-hmm.
Awesome!
I hope you're ready
for some pain.
I'm going to get my belt.
Man, you must be scared.
You forgot your name.
I didn't forget my name, randy.
I just don't want him
to know who I am.
Why is he getting his belt?
That's what dad used to say.
Are we going to get spanked?!
I guess it depends
on what's in his ad.
Why didn't you just tell him
why you're here?
Because, if I tell him who I am,
he'll probably kill me.
I'm going to have to try
to cross him of the list
Without him ever knowing
who I am.
We're just going to have
to take our chances with the ad.
What if his ad is sex?
I hope it's not sex.
(door opens)
All right.
You guys ready to pump?
Oh, god!
He does want to have
sex with us.
"us"? You.
Cliff answered the ad.
Come on.
Let's hit the gym.
(sighs)
We're going to work
out together.
Awesome.
I hope this gym
has group showers
Like the ones we had at school.
I want to show everybody
I have hair now.
I wasn't sure how karma was
going to feel about me lying.
But it turns out, karma already
had a plan in motion.
To torture me the way
I'd tortured wally.
What the hell'd
you do that for?!
To get us pumped!
Come on, cliff. Hit me back.
Go ahead.
Good.
(grunts)
Wally was so hard-core,
He'd already broken
three partners before me.
Come on, cliff. Push it!
You can do it.
Two more!
It's all you.
How about a little less me
and a little more you?
Here we go.
It slipped.
I'll get it.
Come on.
What do you say
we take a quick break?
So I figured
if I got big and strong,
My bully would leave me alone.
How long do I have
to bounce on this thing
Before I look like you guys?
If you want to
really get ripped,
You got to work with
some free weights.
Good, 'cause I don't have
any money.
Don't worry, man.
We'll buff you out.
So, uh, how big
is your bully?
About this tall,
This wide and...
About a 32c.
Wait. Your bully's a girl?
A really tough girl.
32c.
Dude, if your
bully's a girl,
It's not about
how big you are.
It's about confidence.
What you need
Is 100% pure shark adrenaline.
It'll turn you into a beast!
You'll destroy
Everyone and everything
that gets in your way.
Especially baby seals.
Mmm, man, what I wouldn't give
For a baby seal right now.
(both grunt)
cool.
So what's it taste like?
The drugs,
not the baby seal.
I know what those taste like.
Oh, you don't
Drink this;
you inject it into your scrotum.
Yeah...
(screams)
Oh, my god!
That's my scrotum?!
(screams)
(groans, grunts)
Mr. Camden, huh?
Pretty big deal.
I was there when mr. Camden 1998
cut the ribbon
At the opening ceremony
of the new welfare office.
Me and my brother
were third in line.
Eh, the mr. Camden competition
is stupid.
"stupid"? Really?
Look at all this stuff
you could win.
You could get
a month's worth
Of something
called "dvd rentals,
"an office-quality
paper shredder,
"and a gift certificate
for all-you-can eat sushi
From sensei yum-yums."
Okay, fine.
Yes, of course I want to win.
It's always been
a dream of mine.
But there's just some stuff
I'm not willing to do.
Wally told me competing
in mr. Camden
Involved a lot of things
other than just muscles.
You were expected
to shave everything
That wasn't covered
by tiny pants,
Have a head-to-toe tan
And oil yourself
like a catcher's mitt.
And wally wasn't
into that stuff.
(grunting)
I don't care if that contest
comes with a talking pet monkey.
It ain't worth
turning myself into a pansy!
I knew something was wrong
'cause no man would turn down
a talking pet monkey.
Then I realized
me calling wally a "pansy"
When we were kids
was stopping him
From trying to be mr. Camden.
Randy, you're not going
to believe what just happened.
I was just going to say
the same thing.
I know how I can cross
wally off my list.
I'm going to help him
get over his fear,
So he can win
the mr. Camden competition.
See you later, buddy.
I just got a shot in my balls.
Look, I've been thinking,
You're the biggest,
strongest guy I've ever seen.
You should be mr. Camden.
It just makes sense,
like how the biggest,
Strongest peanut
became mr. Peanut.
What?
It's true.
Don't you ever read the jar?
Cliff, dudes like me and you,
We don't do all
that pansy stuff.
We wear flannel.
We have body hair.
We really like soups that are so
hearty you eat them with a fork.
Are you kidding?
I'm totally going to do
All that bodybuilder stuff,
as soon as I'm ripped like you.
Why do you think I was looking
for a training partner?
I don't know, cliff.
Come on.
We'll do it together.
Two men shaving, tanning,
Oiling each other up...
We won't talk about it.
We'll just do it.
All right.
If a man's man like you
can do it,
Then I guess I can, too.
Hot damn!
I'm going to be
mr. Camden.
Let's get psyched.
(screams)
Good. Good.
Uh, could we work out, uh,
some kind of signal
Before you do that?
Just like marcus and kyle
had promised,
That shark adrenaline
was starting
To affect randy's attitude.
Hand over
the floppy puppy.
You're not getting
my floppy puppy.
Give me the floppy puppy.
No! Mine! Mine!
Kill her! Kill her!
I know a guy who can make
any death look like a suicide.
(growls)
Keep the stupid dog.
Big baby.
I did it! Victory!
I got my floppy puppy!
But I had to burn through
my week's supply
Of that shark's adrenaline.
I'm going to need more.
Well, kyle should be
back from...
Now!
To help wally win
the mr. Camden title,
I was going to have
to do some things
That made me uncomfortable.
Smooth, but uncomfortable.
I don't know.
This doesn't feel right.
Come on.
It's perfectly manly to do this.
And these lady razors
are exactly like the men's.
They're just a little
more flexible
To move with the contours
of our legs.
Okay.
It looked like
I had wally on the road
to becoming mr. Camden.
I just didn't know trouble
was coming around the corner.
Bros, what the hell?!
Relax, randy, we're just
shaving for the competition.
What are you competing for,
who gets to be on the bottom?
Pansies.
What's he talking about?
Tell him, cliff.
We're not pansies!
"cliff"?
You still sticking
With that name?
You haven't told him
Who you really are?
What are you talking
about, randy?
I-I-I am who I am.
I'm cliff.
Man, I don't know
Which one of you's
a bigger pansy:
Wally, for actually
being a pansy,
Or you for being too afraid
to tell him
Your real name... Earl.
Wait a minute.
"earl"?
"pansy"?
Earl hickey?
I-I-I-I guess cliff
is more of a nickname.
But-but look, I can explain.
I always dreamed
I'd run into you again.
Earl hickey.
I-I dream about stuff, too.
(yelps)
I'm glad you're here.
You can clean up
my splatter, lady legs.
Randy, what the hell's
gotten into you?
Shark adrenaline--
that's what's gotten into me
And I love it!
(knocking)
(screams)
(screaming)
Damn it, earl!
Open this door!
J-just give me a second.
Let me at least
get my jeans on.
I don't want to die
in my underpants!
Unlock it, earl.
Take the medicine like a man.
No way!
Why is your pee blue?
(screams):
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
(crashing)
(grunting)
I'm really sorry!
I got a list!
It's a karma list.
It's really hard
to explain.
I was just trying to help.
By making me look like a pansy?
No!
(wally grunts)
(groans)
Eh, fella, you
want to party?
I'm not sharing mine.
Randy:
what the hell
Are you doing, jerk?!
This was my favorite wall!
Randy, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
I wanted to get things
under control
Before they got too crazy.
¶ keep your eyes
on the road... ¶
(grunting)
(both grunting)
You take back what you said!
(grunts):
thanks!
You just released more
shark juice from my scrote!
No, no, no! No, randy!
(screams)
Randy, you got to stop this
Before you get...
Wally, hold on!
I'm trying to...
(screams)
Cut it out!
¶ all night long... ¶
It was no fun being
In the middle
of two monsters.
But they were monsters
I had created.
Randy!
I created one by telling him
to stand up for himself
And the other
by pushing him down.
(honking)
Sam, I'm going around back
to grab some ice.
You mind watching the bar
for a second?
Who's a pansy now? Huh?
(grunting)
(thudding)
¶ all night long. ¶
What the...?
There was only one thing
that could distract randy
From fighting with wally.
The return
of his original bully, joy.
She got my babies!
Sam, may we have a word?
It took me 20 minutes
to get to my car,
But I knew I had to do
whatever it took
To stop randy
before he killed somebody.
And I wasn't the only one
looking for him.
Wally was also following
the path to destruction.
Hey! Where's the guy
who did this?
(grunting)
I should've guessed that path
to destruction would only
Lead to one place.
So I told that teacher,
"I'm glad my son's
flunking spanish."
Frankly, I'd be disappointed
if he wasn't.
Oh, god.
I want my claw machine toys!
All of 'em!
Including the ones
you took today!
Eugenia, call the police
right now.
I'm at...
I'll get you a bag.
Randy was happy
he got all of his toys.
Well, except for one.
(penguin squeaks)
Give me that bird
dressed for a wedding.
Hey, uncle randy.
I said I want
my dressed-up birdie, punk.
But it's mine.
Mommy got it for me yesterday.
Give me that dressed-up birdie!
(squeaking)
Though nothing had stopped
this monster so far,
There was one thing
he wasn't prepared for.
(sobbing)
Even though
the shark adrenaline
Had completely taken over
his brain, there was still
One thing that could get
through to the old randy:
The cry of a bullied child,
Especially since this time,
he was the bully.
(sobbing)
Oh, my god,
what am I doing?
But when I came around
that corner,
All I saw was
a juiced-up maniac
Heading right for a kid.
(randy screaming)
(grunts, toy squeaks)
Sorry, buddy.
You turned into a monster.
But it wasn't
your fault, though.
I pushed you to be a tough guy
and stand up to joy,
But you're not a tough guy.
You're a sweet,
gentle, sensitive guy.
I shouldn't have
made you change.
Being sweet and sensitive
is a good thing.
Randy?
Randy didn't hear me
Since his brain
was kind of swollen
At the time, but my words
did have an effect on someone.
You know what, earl?
I used to be sensitive, too.
Wally had been sensitive,
But I made him ashamed of it
back when we were kids.
I'm sorry, wally.
I should've never bullied that
out of you.
Something about what I said
Made wally realize
that you might be able
To change how you look
on the outside,
But you can't change
who you are on the inside.
No matter
how big and strong
Wally made his outer shell,
he couldn't change
The sweetness inside
he was trying to protect.
And wally was finally ready
to embrace
Both of those people:
the bodybuilder
And the little kid
who loves butterflies.
And like a butterfly,
wally finally came out
Of his cocoon and became
the person he was meant to be.
(cheering and applause)
¶ ¶
(grunting)
Sorry again.
For what?
Oh, hitting me
with the car?
That's okay.
Hey, earl?
Yeah, randy?
You think kryptonite works
on people who aren't superman?
I don't know.
Probably not.
What about garlic?
That only works on vampires.
Apples?
I'm pretty sure
that's only for doctors.
What are you trying
to keep away?
Joy.
Try hummus.
Thanks, earl.
Good night, randy.
Good night, earl.
Captioned by
apit9
www.tvsubtitles.net