Good morning, Earl.
Good morning, Randy.
You know what team
I've always wanted to join?
The debate team.
- No, you haven't.
- Yes, I have.
No offense, but I don't think
you'd be very good at that.
Yes, I would.
I think debating
is more than just saying the opposite
of what the other person says.
No, it isn't.
- Yes, it is.
- No, it isn't.
This is stupid.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
I win.
EARL AND JOY'S ANNIVERSARY
There were a few things on my list that
I'd actually done to the Crab Shack.
One of them people had gotten used
to working around.
Beer coming.
But it was still something
I wanted to fix.
I'm fixing the dent, Darnell.
That's good to hear.
I tried to build a ramp over it
with disastrous results.
Why would you slide it to me?
Who slides wine?
There was a reason
why I was fixing this today.
'Cause it was the anniversary
of the day I dented it,
which was also the anniversary
of the day I married Joy.
Joy's situation forced her to be
a new wife and mother all at once.
Damn it, baby!
You keep kicking my kidney,
and I'm gonna hold my breath again!
All right, you asked for it.
- What's your name again?
- Joy.
You got a baby in there?
That my brother's baby?
It is now.
Mrs. Hickey,
I believe you requested
I steal one of these?
Oh, Earl, you did it!
I knew we were meant for each other
the first time I met you
the other night.
Where'd you get it?
You walk into a bakery
wearing a hairnet,
you can walk out with
pretty much anything you want.
Randy?
I got you a bag of sprinkles.
Shut up!
It's going in the freezer.
If you eat it
on the one year anniversary,
you'll have good luck.
Saw it on Oprah.
She don't know much about marriage,
but she sure knows something about cake.
That first year didn't go
the way Joy had hoped.
And a few days before our anniversary,
she hit rock bottom.
Our belly button fuzz balls
are about the same size.
How do we pick a winner?
That's it.
I can't wait to eat that cake.
I need my luck now.
Is that skin or a piece
of Frosted Flake in yours?
- Skin.
- What the hell?
Somebody switched my cake
with a pile of dog turds.
Either one of you
know anything about this?
Actually, they're cat turds.
But I don't know anything about it.
A couple days
after I stole that cake,
me and Randy had
a drinking contest at the Crab Shack.
I never made it home,
but unfortunately for Joy,
Randy did.
Here comes the stomach...
Don't think I don't hear you
out there, Sasquatch!
You better not be getting
into my food in the fridge!
I hate you, too,
you bitchy old screech owl.
Randy knew he couldn't just put
empty foil back in the freezer,
and that's when he realized
he could have the best of both worlds:
eat Joy's cake and feed her poo.
You think this is funny?
Why are you getting so mad
over a little thing like this?
So, my brother replaced
our wedding cake with cat poo.
I'm sure it happens
in a lot of marriages.
It's not a little thing.
That cake was a symbol.
Of what?
I don't know. Something!
Like, that you cared about me.
And then dummy ruins it,
and you just sit there and laugh.
That means something, too.
I'm really sorry
I made Joy mad at you, Earl.
If you need a place to sleep tonight,
my couch is your couch.
Your couch is my couch, Randy.
So, we agree.
Randy felt guilty for days.
So, on our actual anniversary,
he did something
to put an end to it.
"Dear Earl and Joy,
"I'm sorry for eating your cake
"so I'm going to kill myself
"at the Crab Shack at 3:00.
"I'll probably shoot myself
in the face.
"Stay cool. Love, Randy."
Surprise!
Happy Anniversary!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, Randy,
did you do all this?
Are you kidding me?
Earl's been planning this for weeks.
Why do you think
he's been such a jerk lately?
He was setting you up for this.
You did this?
I did this.
Me.
Thanks, Earl.
I really needed a lift right now.
I thought I might get it
from Randy killing himself,
but this is even better.
Thanks, Randy.
You made life better for both of us.
You're welcome, Earl.
I felt bad.
When this marriage ends,
I want it to be
because you and Joy hate each other,
not because of me.
It's been fun chatting.
You want to get out and go have sex?
'Cause I do. Real bad.
No, Donny.
Quit staring at me
with your crazy eyes.
I'll put a bag over my head
like you made me do last time we banged.
The reason you got lucky that night
was 'cause I had cramps,
and sometimes that helps,
And no hard feelings,
but when you're naked, you look
like you got kneecaps everywhere.
Oh, my God.
Mr. Stevens!
I haven't seen you
since Missy's wedding.
What's that, like, five years ago?
Seven.
And aside from my daughter,
you were the most beautiful girl there.
You are so sweet.
You didn't tell anybody
that we slept together that night?
Hell, no.
I wasn't in a rush to tell my friends
about humping someone's red-faced,
baldheaded, out-of-breath dad
in the back of a catering truck.
I'll tell Missy you said hi.
Looking good, Joy.
Pickup's out back, Joy.
- Long time, sweet cheeks.
- Shake that thing!
Hey, babe!
Who exactly
did you invite to this party?
Randy was more in charge
of the guest list.
Who'd we invite?
People me and you know.
Plus all of Joy's friends.
From her address book.
"Guys I've phoned."
Randy, it says "Guys I've boned."
That's a "B"?
- I thought it was an "F."
- How could you let this happen?
I didn't.
I didn't have anything to do
with this stupid party.
Wait. Yes, I did.
I did everything.
No, I did nothing!
What are you more mad about?
You didn't throw this party.
Dummy did.
I know.
I'm a terrible husband who never...
You're no prize, either.
What kind of wife keeps an address book
full of guys she banged?
The kind of wife that wants to keep
her options open for the future.
What? You think you're going
to find someone better than me?
Go for it, baby.
But keep in mind, this is Camden.
I own my own car.
I almost graduated high school,
and I have a huge collection
of cassette tapes.
So, good luck to you.
Back then, Mr. Turtle was still young
and need to take walks,
and since Darnell
hadn't met Joy yet,
he had plenty of free time.
But that day,
thanks to some hateful bees,
their leisurely walk
turned into a run for cover.
And Darnell wasn't
the only new Camdenite
that the bees decided to pester.
Quick! In here!
I just got to this country, and already
I'm invited into someone's house.
You must be rich.
You have a phone.
This is Phil.
He does mortgages down at the bank.
You know, 30-year balloon loans.
Has a gold pinky ring,
white shoes, brand name socks.
I know Phil.
We went high school together.
How's it going, buddy?
Oh, God!
How did I not notice that
when we slept together?
No wonder he didn't want to cuddle.
All the ladies
in the house say, "Ho!"
And that's right about
when the fun ended for me.
Blake was my cousin,
and I'd hated him
since we were kids.
It all started
when our moms took us to audition
for a local backpack catalog.
I knew I could make
the Little Explorer look good,
but I just couldn't
keep my eyes open.
From that day on,
I've never measured up to cousin Blake.
Cousin Blake?
That's right, Earl.
Blake's here 'cause he's in my book.
For a while there, I didn't think
Joy could do better than me,
and now I knew she could.
You want to know what she wrote
next to his name?
Absolutely not.
Gimungo!
You look a little surprised
to see me.
You must have just found out
I boned your wife.
It's a look I get a lot.
Still a loser and a thief,
I'll assume.
And I'm still rocking
the model thing.
Blake was better than me
at everything,
so I had to do something fast.
Back then my motto was,
"When in doubt,
set something on fire."
Oh, my God!
Fire! Run for your lives!
The whole place is going up!
Nothing can keep people in a bar
when it's on fire.
Killer bees! Killer bees!
Don't go out there!
Except killer bees.
Don't worry, Joy.
I'll protect you.
So, while killer bees
were invading Camden,
I was stuck inside
having to watch my wife
canoodle with my cousin
and his backpack that was worth
more than my car.
Nobody worry.
I come prepared like a Boy Scout.
A Boy Scout, that's...
a handsome, professional
backpack model with his own condo.
You worry about everyone else.
I'll take care of my wife.
All of a sudden
you care about me.
- Looks like you're jealous.
- I'm not jealous.
I'm just doing what a husband does,
protecting his family.
So, what you going
to protect me with?
I got a piece of gum
and a corn dog stick.
Why the hell are you carrying around
a corn dog stick?
There's still a little
corn dog on it.
Sometimes, if you wait,
it loosens up.
It's not ready.
I've been working at Club Chubby
for a couple of weeks now.
So, I'm trying to figure out
my signature move.
Cinnamon slaps her ass
with a ruler.
Chantelle lets people
put gum in her hair.
I just need something to...
help me stand out.
Have you ever thought
of jumping?
That'll work.
Hey, bees just swarmed me
and my John.
I didn't have time to untie him
from the tree.
I hope he's okay.
If they're swarming people,
it means these bees are Africanized.
Those brothers mean business.
I don't know who you are,
but you better not be hooking
because you are
much prettier than me
and I got a teenage son to put
through hairdressing school.
We're inside a phone booth
trapped by killer bees.
If that's Clarence,
ask him how his ma is.
I call emergency nine times a day.
It comes with the job.
They got me on hold.
There's a lot of callers.
Good!
Barry got his ropes untied.
I got nothing on this guy, Randy.
He's beaten me again.
Just like he did with modeling
and staying cavity free.
I'm sorry about all this, Earl.
I didn't even get a chance
to show the anniversary video
I made for you guys.
You made a video
about me and Joy?
About our love
and crap like that?
Yeah.
I hid the camera
around the trailer for a while.
I got the idea off that show
where the guy catches perverts
in his kitchen every week.
He should really move.
Anyway, I took the tape
to that lady
that makes wedding videos
and breeds Taco Bell puppies.
Randy, that's perfect.
Put it on.
Excuse me, everyone.
I made a little video I think
some of you would like to see.
It's called "Earl and Joy",
high dot, low dot,
"A Love Story."
Honey, this is for you.
Blake,
one of these fingers is for you.
Oh, my God!
What happened?
Just 'cause
you leave me a note
saying I got to do something
with a bird in a freezer
doesn't mean I gotta drop everything
that's important to me and do it.
Is my name "note-reader"?
Is my name "bird-defroster"?
No, my name...
That was, uh,
- clearly the blooper reel.
- Hey, cousin.
It looks like you're gonna need
a place to crash for a while.
You can stay at my pad.
I won't be there.
'Cause even though
we're 4 months from Christmas,
it looks like I'm gonna
be busy spreading Joy.
Son of a bitch!
Wait, you're from La Paz?
Near the river of blood?
I did my Peace Corps year
down there.
- Small world.
Let me in!
Thank you.
Those bees are such bitches.
You laugh,
but that statement is factual.
Most of the colony
are actually female.
There're a few males
and their job is
to have sex with the queen.
Ick!
Worst job ever.
If we're the only 4 survivors
left on the planet,
I call the black guy.
Cut it out!
You're gonna break the bar.
That's right.
You might know "fujitsu,"
but my head can break things.
What do you think of that,
Mr. I'm-Better-Than-Earl-At-Everything?
Bet you can't do this.
Son of a bitch!
Oh, God.
Blake, go get me some cigarettes
from the vending machine.
Yeah, sure.
I'll just be... over there,
at the vending machine.
And I'll be waiting right here.
Excuse me.
Earl, this isn't right.
Isn't this what you wanted?
For me to get jealous?
You're jealous of your cousin.
It ain't got nothing
to do with me
or else you'd be jealous of
all these other guys, too.
I don't know
what you want from me.
Look, I'm not trying
to criticize you,
but jealousy,
throwing me a party,
making me a nice video,
those are all ways
to show you care.
And you don't do stuff like that.
Well, I pretended
to do all those things.
Doesn't that count
for something?
Who are we kidding?
You saw the video.
This isn't a marriage.
What did I expect, I mean,
I tricked you into marrying me.
You didn't care about me
when you agreed to that,
and I don't think you ever will.
I wouldn't.
I'm sorry, Earl.
I think it's time we just end it.
In a whole year, I had never
stopped to think about
whether or not
I cared about my wife.
In those days, I never really
stopped to care about anything.
While I was facing
the end of my marriage,
everyone else was facing
the end of their lives.
They're gonna get in!
I can't believe
I'm gonna die today.
I have four outstanding books
from the library.
What if that's all
it says in the paper?
I can't believe
I'm gonna die a virgin.
I was saving myself
for marriage.
I hope you're impressed!
And that you exist!
I can't believe I'm gonna die
without giving it up for free.
Just once
I should've done that.
I've always wanted
to try a threesome.
I've never kissed a man
and I want to.
Bad.
What kind of man doesn't know
if he cares about his wife?
A man in a coma.
Or a man who got married
over the Internet
and he hasn't met his wife yet 'cause
she's being shipped here on a boat.
The only person
I've ever really cared about is you,
and you're my brother.
I don't have a choice.
What if I'm just a lazy jerk
who's gonna live his life
never caring
about anybody else?
Bee!
Before my list,
when I didn't have time
to think,
it always ended
with me doing the wrong thing,
like stealing
or peeing in public.
But not on that day,
not in that moment.
You okay?
I can't say that moment turned me
into a perfect husband,
or that Joy didn't have
to drive my drunk ass home
later that night,
but that was the day I knew
I could care about someone else.
I did care about someone else
and she knew it, too.
I guess you learn
what you're capable of
when you stare death
in the face.
It's all okay!
They are gone.
The bees are on their way
to Texas.
This never happened.
And when you have history
with people,
you'll always remember
those meaningful days.
I think it's ready, Darnell.
Give it a shot.
Beer coming.
I'm sorry, Darnell.
I just got so excited, I forgot
I was supposed to catch it.
Happy Anniversary.
That was two dollars and tax.
You don't have to pay me back.
I just wanted you to know.
You're welcome.
I know this sounds crazy,
but of all your wives,
I think Joy was my favorite.
Mine, too.
Subtitles:
Jarick & loky