Subtitles by Loky and Jarick
Transcript by SadGeezer.com
For me, prison was like
a long car vacation with my parents.
The more I slept, the shorter the trip.
Wakey, wakey, hands off penis.
It's for protection.
There's a new guy here
who thinks it's funny
to pull on your junk
while you're sleeping.
The principal wants to see you.
You mean the warden?
Did I say "landlord" again?
Good.
- You wanted to see me, sir?
- Yeah, Hickey, come on in.
You don't mind if I multitask, do you?
Not at all, sir.
Vinny's here to shave
some guy for the electric chair.
Oh, I hate execution days.
Especially if they die with a funny face
and then you start giggling.
And suddenly you're the jerk
who's laughing at an execution.
Anyway,
I am getting ready to start
a program called "Scared Straight".
Not into the ladies, huh?
Well, it worked for a guy
at my parents' church.
The program I'm talking about
is where we go into schools
and we try to scare kids
out of a life of crime.
We used to bring 'em here.
Didn't work out too well.
Remember. Be scared, stay straight.
Excuse me.
He wasn't my buddy when we came in.
We finally found the real kid
in a washing machine.
2 months later, he's still dizzy.
What do you say?
Are you in?
I'll give you a certificate
that knocks another 5 weeks
off your prison sentence.
If it keeps me out of trouble and
gets me out of here 5 weeks sooner,
I guess scaring kids is a good thing.
Great. You're gonna be putting
on a presentation
at the school in a couple of days.
You just pick any three prisoners
you want to help you.
Just, if you pick a black guy,
make sure he's a doctor or lawyer
we don't want to perpetuate
negative stereotypes.
Season 3 - Episode 9
Randy In Charge
I was really excited to get started
on my Scared Straight project.
But first, I had to look after Randy.
You okay, Randy?
I'm great.
I found a shady spot in the yard
where no other guards could see me,
and I took a nap.
Because as great as it was
to see Randy every day,
he really wasn't the best prison guard.
Elvis, great. How was your weekend?
Sometimes I got there
in the nick of time.
And sometimes I didn't.
Meal time.
Hello? Dinner.
That tickles.
And sometimes,
he wasn't just a danger to himself.
Everyone, this is Fred.
It's his first time in prison
and he's a little nervous.
He used to be a police officer
and then he molested a little boy.
So, make him feel welcome.
Really?
They wrote "Best Guard" on my forehead?
They sure did.
I realized if I wanted
to keep Randy out of trouble,
I needed to keep him close.
And I figured the warden wouldn't mind.
Good news, Randy.
The warden thinks you should be the one
to escort us on the project.
I was worried he thought I was an idiot
when he saw me fall out
of that guard tower.
I guess when I said,
"I meant to do that," he believed me.
While I was trying to help
Randy stay out of trouble,
a very pregnant Joy
was trying to get out of bed.
Thank God, you're here.
I'm stuck again.
This mattress is pressing
against me like a creepy uncle.
Recently, Joy had found out
that Liberty, her lifelong enemy,
was also her lifelong half-sister.
And after putting aside
their differences,
Joy agreed to be Liberty
and Ray Ray's surrogate mom.
Baby, I told you
you needed to stay in the middle.
I was in the middle.
That damn monster truck
pulled in next door
and created a wave
that pushed me into the crack.
Get me out of here.
I'm-a go sleep on the couch.
You know you're not allowed
to sleep on any furniture
with exposed rusty springs.
We don't know it was the couch
that gave Earl Jr lockjaw.
Besides, when I agreed
to be their surrogate,
I didn't realize they were part
of the nazi gazpacho.
Being new to parenting,
Liberty and Ray Ray
had a lot of baby rules.
No fried foods, no transfat,
no alcohol, no tobacco...
You first-timers are way overprotective.
I was that way with Dodge.
I switched to Marlboro Lights
and he still came out with asthma.
Earl Jr, she smoked cloves.
That's why he likes spicy food.
Also, no soft cheeses,
no canned cheeses,
no antiperspirants,
no hair dye, no G-strings.
No G-strings or canned cheese?
How the hell am I supposed
to celebrate new year's?
And even though
she agreed to all those demands,
9 months and 2 weeks later,
her patience was running thin.
Even though Joy was not
at a very good place,
Randy was, by my side,
where he'd be safe
while I have my auditions.
Our first two auditioners
are Frank and Paco.
Frank's new to performing,
but Paco did once stab a guy
in front of a big crowd.
Thanks for coming in.
Frank, why don't you go first.
Scare me straight.
Okay. All right. Yo, yo.
When you get in here,
first, I'm gonna mess you up.
And then...
I'm sorry, I blanked out.
You know,
I had it perfectly back in my cell.
You know what? My fault...
Paco should have gone first.
Go in the hall and collect yourself.
Go for it, Paco.
It's not too bad in here.
I mean, I made some new friends,
and I even took a computer course.
And last week,
I googled myself... Paco,
and I found out
I have unclaimed money in Tejas.
That's "Texas" for you.
Next!
I like to cuddle.
Do you like to cuddle?
You're in.
Did you really think
this could possibly work?
I gave it a shot.
This is you.
This is you in prison.
- Any questions?
- It was confusing, but...
I like your voice. You're in.
Watch this.
This will freak the kids out.
That was impressive, Wilson.
I wish he would have saved that
for the show.
And then I'm gonna kick in your teeth
and wrench you out of your cigarettes.
And then when I get 100 cigarettes,
I'm gonna stuff 'em all up in your mouth
and make you smoke 'em,
like that dude from the Guinness Book.
You know why?
Cause prison is boring.
I knew you had it in you.
So, did I get the part?
I had my scared straight team together
and was excited to show the warden.
Okay, kids.
The scariest thing about prison
is that there's violence everywhere.
Everywhere, yeah.
Everyone's always trying
to get over on you.
And when you think you're safe...
You're walking along by yourself
because you might be walking around...
that is such nice work.
- You like that?
- That is so scary.
Just had another thought.
What if the scared straight show
had a green message, too?
I don't follow.
Green.
It means environmentally friendly.
The thing is, sir,...
going green doesn't fit
with the rest of the show.
Work your magic. Make it fit.
Well, I'd just be wedging it in.
But if I told you you had to do
it because I'm your boss...
Then I would say I could take
the shower-killing story
and turn it into something about
the importance of conserving water.
That's good.
And how about if we start the show
when the guy bends over
to pick up the phosphate-free soap?
I wasn't the only one dealing
with other people's crazy ideas.
PBS?
Ray Ray, how the hell would I get PBS
when I'm pregnant?
Oh. It's a channel?
Oh. Hold on.
Okay, I found it.
He's listening.
Dipstick and Dum Dum
wanting the baby to listen
to some stupid show
about the moon landing.
Alleged moon landing.
Keep the receiver covered while I give
this baby the opposing point of view.
Consider this, little man.
In the footage, you'll notice
shadows from divergent sources.
This baby's already smart, Darnell.
He just turned around,
so you're talking to his butt.
That baby still had a chance
to come out smart.
But it was too late for Randy,
who had just been outsmarted
by a pair of handcuffs.
These things close so fast.
Sit down, Randy.
I think we need to have a little talk.
I'm wondering if...
you wouldn't be happier working...
in some place like...
the cafeteria.
No way.
Cafeteria guys don't get
night sticks or cool uniforms.
Where is your nightstick?
Oh, I lost it.
I didn't lose it...
I know which prisoner has it,
but he won't give it back, so...
Come on. Working in the cafeteria,
they'll let you use the big spoon.
That is a big spoon they got in there.
Wait.
Do you think I'm a bad guard?
No. Not, not bad. Just...
too trusting,
and I can't look after you in here,
like I can on the outside.
What are you talking about?
I look after you.
Randy, that's ridiculous.
Is it?
Who got your new mattress
when hepatitis Bob had sex with yours?
If I hadn't a been here,
you'd have
whatever disease hepatitis Bob has.
Face it, Randy,
you only took this job
because you couldn't exist
out there without me.
Or maybe I knew
you couldn't exist in here without me.
Or maybe you're getting defensive
and saying everything I say
back at me.
Or maybe you're just saying what
I'm gonna say before I say it.
What?
I don't know.
Why don't you tell me?
Randy, the point is,
you're not cut out
for positions of authority.
I see what's happening here.
You can't handle me being in charge.
- What?
- Yeah.
You've been bossing me around
so long,
you can't stand
that I'm top dog.
Oh, really?
You think you're top dog?
- Come here, top dog.
- Give it.
Come get it, top dog.
Randy, look.
It doesn't matter that
you're a guard and I'm a prisoner
'cause when it comes to us,
I'm always gonna be in charge.
Code pink.
You'll get your stuff back
at the end of the day.
Now get out in the yard.
It's time for mandatory volleyball.
I was trying to get Randy
for my Scared Straight presentation,
but me and Randy were still fighting
over which one of us was in charge.
- "Not jail."
- No pointers.
- Anyway, not jail...
- No pointing.
I was surprised to see
Randy was staying so mad.
But I guess being the little brother,
these feelings had been building up
inside him for years.
Randy, I told you, it's too weird.
We can't both have mustaches.
And I had mine first.
In fact, I was in charge for as long as
either of us could remember.
Randy didn't just mess
with my rehearsal time,
he also started messing
with my meals.
Half portion.
Who's in charge now?
Kosher meal.
Enjoy your muslim food.
Regular meal.
Upside down.
- Damn it, you're acting like...
- Code pink.
Turns out, me and Joy were both dealing
with uncooperative babies.
And your great-great-great
great-great great grandfather
was sent to asia by a tobacco company
to get the chinese hooked on smoking.
And if you ever go there, little one,
you'll see
what a first-rate job he done.
Damn it, Ray-Ray,
the baby can't see you.
You want to show him pictures,
let me induce.
Absolutely not.
Inducing's not a part
of our natural childbirth plan.
Your body will tell us when it's time.
My mouth speaks for my body,
and it's saying it's go time.
My daddy always said
"Don't do business with family."
I told you we should've gotten
a written contract.
Good luck with that.
Before we were married,
I asked for a prenuptial agreement,
and she burned all my stuff.
But then she did sign it.
We don't need a written contract.
Joy and I have a verbal agreement,
between sisters.
Look, I agreed to carry this baby
for nine months.
So, technically,
our agreement expired
two weeks ago.
The only reason I haven't cut
this baby out myself
is because a cesarean scar
and my prom scar
would make a weird little crucifix
right above my landing strip.
Yo, man, I mean, things were going
from worse to even worser.
And not only did the cops have
my footprint from the casino vault,
but my carbon footprint
was off the charts.
Great job, guys.
We're leaving in five minutes.
Scooby, when you tell that story
about dumping a body in the woods,
say you felt bad about littering.
I did. That was the only part
I did feel bad about.
You can go back
to your bunk now,
you're not involved
in the show anymore.
What?
Your fieldtrip privileges
have been canceled.
I'm only taking these three.
I can do that 'cause I'm in charge.
Well, I'll talk to the warden.
The warden's not here.
We're leaving.
You're getting way out of control.
You know what's getting
way out of control?
My taser.
My taser hand's way out of control.
You know I hate tasers.
Come on, guys, we're going.
Do me a favor.
My brother gets a little mixed up and...
Don't worry, I'll look after him.
Hey, but, Earl...
about my performance,
am I doing good or am I pushing?
- Yeah, it's good.
- All right.
Carbon footprint.
Frank didn't want to push, but...
Joy did.
She was trying everything she could
to get that baby out.
Cause while she promised
not to induce at the hospital,
she never promised
not to try and induce at home.
Get out!
Great show, guys.
I heard one kid say
"I'll never stab anyone,
"or order chilean sea bass."
They are dangerously over fished.
Bob, that was really something
how you got the teacher's phone number,
even after telling that story
about killing a teacher.
I dig chicks who want to fix me.
You know what, you guys did
such an awesome job,
we're gonna stop for ice cream.
This is the last time I'll bring it up,
but frozen yogurt would be
a lot healthier than ice cream.
Damn.
There's no parking spots.
I don't want to double park.
If I get a ticket in this van,
I'll get in big trouble.
We can run in for you.
Okay, I'm trusting you.
I want half french vanilla,
half rocky road.
Sprinkles, not too many,
only rainbow color.
One scoop, chopped nuts,
whipped cream.
Don't screw me on this.
Yeah, but what about Frank?
Just let him sleep.
But get him something.
Nothing too fancy.
He hates snobs.
Get him a working man's flavor
like rum raisin.
- Or brown.
- Okay.
Baby, you've been squatting
for five and a half hours.
That's like five hours longer
than any human should squat.
That's it.
I don't care what I promised.
We're going to the hospital
and inducing right now.
Get your keys.
I'm all cramped up.
I feel like B.J. and the bear.
Whichever one of you pregnant bitches
thinks you're going next, you are wrong.
I need to get some drugs
to kick-start this delivery.
I forgot you were back there.
Where is everyone?
Silly sleepyhead, did you forget?
Ice cream.
- What?
- Don't worry,
they're getting you something.
You can't just let a couple of criminals
go into an ice cream store.
That's like letting a bull loose
in a chinese shop.
That's nuts.
How would you even get
a bull into a store?
The door would have to be huge
and then once he was in there,
he'd just go crazy with...
Oh, crap.
Can't believe you didn't trust us.
Although now that i think about it,
that was a wasted opportunity.
I'm sorry, guys.
I should've known better than to think
one of you would try and run away.
An escaped convict
and a parking ticket
on a state vehicle?
Not the kind of thing that's gonna
get me laid at home, fellas.
It's not my fault, sir.
Captain Jackass was in charge.
You actually took prisoners
for ice cream?
Yes, sir.
But I got a receipt.
So if I could just get my 8 $ back...
Moron.
I hold you both responsible
for this mess.
Look, sir,
I knew frank on the outside.
Maybe I can help the troopers
figure out where he's hiding.
No! No, no! No troopers, no press.
And the governor
can never hear about this.
There was a good reason the warden
didn't want the governor to find out.
She was also his wife.
So you're trying scared straight again?
Yes.
And this time,
you're going to the school?
That's what I said.
With actual prisoners?
I know what I'm doing!
I'm a grown man!
You like your job, fella?
Yes.
Do you like your brother?
Not at the moment, sir, no.
Too bad.
You're both gonna go out there,
you're gonna find Frank
and you're gonna bring him back.
- Fine, we'll do it.
- Great.
You've got 46 hours.
And nobody better find out about it.
Before we go,
which one of us is in charge?
Will you two figure it out?