You think Adam's okay?
Doubt it.
Cass either.
The cage you sprung Lucifer from.
You can shove his ass back in.
Key to the cage.
Four rings from the horsemen.
We got War's. We nicked Famine's.
That's two rings down.
Collect all four.
I can give you Pestilence.
Do you want the horsemen rings or not?
- What are we dealing with?
- Croatoan.
Virus of plague and pestilence.
More like demonic germ warfare.
They want our vaccine.
They need our vaccine.
It's called demand, people.
Now, supply!
Sir, great news.
The vaccine trials...
the results have been...
... really quite grotesque.
I think you'll be pleased.
Hello, Death.
You make a wish.
I can give you anything you want, mate.
Up to and including
Death's coordinates.
- All I need is...
- My soul.
Say we can open the cage.
But then what?
What if you guys lead the devil
to the edge and I jump in?
Dr. Green, how was your trip?
Very productive.
And how are we tonight, Celeste,
my favorite patient?
The nurse says you can't sleep.
I just feel worse and worse.
That's because you're suffering
from a combination of the common cold...
Dengue fever and a nasty,
nasty case of Japanese encephalitis.
What are you...
- I'm sorry. I...
- You heard me.
Oh, and look at that.
You never had chicken pox
as a child.
This is gonna be fascinating.
But I...
How could I...
Have all those diseases at once?
Well, it's a proprietary blend.
I mix it up in a petri dish...
The petri dish being... you.
Try and relax. It'll be all right.
Are you gonna cure me?
No, you're going to die.
In four, three, two...
Interesting.
= 521 =
= Supernatural Team =
What is wrong with you?
Don't "Dean" me.
You have had
some stupid ideas in the past,
but this... Did you know about this?
- What?
- About Sam's genius plan
to say yes to the devil.
- Thanks for the heads up!
- This ain't about me.
- You can't do this.
- That's the consensus.
All right, awesome.
End of discussion.
This isn't over.
- Dean?
- Cass?
Is he okay?
We thought you were dead.
Where are you?
- A hospital.
- Are you okay?
You wanna elaborate?
I just woke up here.
The doctors were fairly surprised.
They thought I was brain-dead.
So, a hospital?
Apparently, after Van Nuys,
I suddenly appeared,
bloody and unconscious,
on a shrimping boat off Delacroix.
I'm told it upset the sailors.
I gotta tell you.
You're just in time.
We figured out a way
to pop Satan's box.
- How?
- It's a long story, but, look...
We're going after Pestilence now.
So if you want to zap over here...
- I can't "zap" anywhere.
- What do you mean?
You could say
my batteries are drained.
You're out of angel mojo?
I'm saying that I am thirsty
and my head aches.
I have a bug bite that itches
no matter how much I scratch it,
and I'm saying
that I'm just incredibly...
Human.
Sorry.
My point is I can't go anywhere
without money for...
An airplane ride.
And food.
And more pain medication, ideally.
No worries.
Bobby's here. He'll wire you the cash.
I will?
You said no to Michael.
I owe you an apology.
It's okay.
You are not the burnt and broken
shell of a man I believed you to be.
Thank you.
- I appreciate that.
- You're welcome.
Be careful.
So this is Dr. Evil's lair?
It's more depressing than evil.
It's like a four-color brochure
for dying young.
Of course, to Pestilence,
it's probably Dollywood in there.
Great.
A whole building full of people.
We don't know who's human,
who's demon, and who's Pestilence.
So what do we do?
Hang on.
I'm looking for my Nana.
Her name is Eunice Kennedy.
Go around front and see the nurse.
You mind just helping me out, sir?
She's about that small
and gray hair, wears diapers.
Eunice Kennedy?
That's the beauty about improv.
You never know
what's gonna come out.
What are we looking for?
He's Pestilence,
so he probably looks sick.
Everybody looks sick.
Now we're talking.
Dr. Green, how was your trip?
Very productive.
And how are we tonight, Celeste,
my favorite patient?
Sir...
The Winchesters are here.
We should go.
Are you kidding me?
They have a track record
with horsemen.
You mean my brothers.
What they did to my brothers.
The only reasonable thing to do here
is to...
Take it out
of their healthy young asses.
We're under strict orders
not to kill the vessels.
If Satan wants them so bad,
he can glue them back together!
Come, come.
Now then.
- Page me if she's dying.
- Yes, doctor.
Must be getting close.
You think?
The doctor will see you now.
Come right in.
You boys don't look well.
It might be the Scarlet fever.
Or the meningitis.
Or the syphilis.
That's no fun.
However you feel right now?
It's gonna get so very,
very much worse.
Questions?
Disease gets a bad rap,
don't you think?
For being filthy. Chaotic.
But, really, that just describes
people who get sick.
Disease itself...
Very...
Pure...
Single-minded.
Bacteria have one purpose...
Divide and conquer.
That's why, in the end...
It always wins.
So, you've got to wonder
why God pours all his love
into something so messy...
And weak.
It's ridiculous.
All I can do is show him he's wrong,
one epidemic
at a time.
On a scale of 1 to 10,
how's your pain?
- How'd you get here?
- I took a bus. Don't worry, I...
Well, look at that.
An occupied vessel, but...
Powerless.
That's fascinating.
There's not a speck of angel in you,
is there?
Maybe just a speck.
It doesn't matter.
It's too late.
Well,
it's nice to actually score a home run
for once, ain't it?
- What?
- Last thing Pestilence said.
"It's too late."
He get specific?
We're a little freaked out
he might have left a bomb somewhere.
So, please tell us
you have actual good news.
Chicago
is about to be wiped off the map.
Storm of the millennium.
Sets off a Daisy chain
of natural disasters.
Three million people are gonna die.
I don't understand
your definition of good news.
Well...
Death, the horseman,
he's gonna be there.
And if we can stop him
before he kick-starts this storm,
get his ring back...
- You make it sound so easy.
- I'm just trying to put a spin on it.
Well...
Bobby, how'd you put all this together,
anyways?
I had, you know... Help.
Don't be so modest.
I barely helped at all.
Hello, boys.
Pleasure, et cetera.
Go ahead. Tell them.
There's no shame in it.
Tell us what?
World's gonna end.
Seems stupid to get all precious
over one little soul.
You sold your soul?
- Pawned it. I intend to give it back.
- Then give it back!
- I will.
- Now!
Did you kiss him? Just wondering!
Why'd you take a picture?
Why do you have to use tongue?
You know what? I'm sick of this.
Give him his soul back now.
- I'm sorry. I can't.
- Can't or won't?
I won't, all right? It's insurance.
- What are you talking about?
- You kill demons.
Gigantor over there
has a temper issue about it.
But you won't kill me...
As long as I have that soul
in the deposit box.
You son of a bitch.
I'll return it.
After all this is over,
and I can walk safely away.
Do we all understand each other?
Let me guess.
We're about to have a talk.
For the record...
I agree with you.
About me.
You think I'm too weak
to take on Lucifer.
So do I.
Believe me, I know exactly
how screwed up I am.
You, Bobby, Cass...
I'm the least of any of you.
It's true, it is. But...
I'm also all we got.
If there was another way...
But I don't think there is.
There's just me.
So I don't know what else to do.
Except just try
to do what's got to be done.
And...
Scene.
Something you need to see.
Niveus pharmaceuticals
is rushing delivery of its new
swine-flu vaccine to
"stem the tide
of the unprecedented outbreak."
- Shipments leave Wednesday.
- Niveus pharmaceuticals.
Get it?
You two are lucky
you have your looks.
Your demon lover, Brady?
VP of distribution, Niveus.
Yes, that sound
of the abacus clacking?
We all caught up?
- Pestilence was spreading swine flu.
- But not just for giggles.
That was step one.
Step two is the vaccine.
- And you think...
- I know.
I'll stake my reputation.
That vaccine
is chock-full of grade-A,
farm-fresh Croatoan virus.
Simultaneous,
countrywide distribution.
It's quite a plan.
They don't get to be horsemen
for nothing.
So, you boys better stock up on...
Well, everything.
This time next Thursday,
we'll all be living in Zombieland.
Watch where you're walking, pal.
What's your problem?
This is what they mean
by "the 11th hour," right?
Pretty much.
Well, it's the 11th hour,
and I am useless.
All I have is this.
What am I supposed to do?
Point it and shoot.
- What I used to be...
- Are you really gonna bitch to me?
Quit pining for the varsity years...
And load the damn truck.
All right, well...
Good luck stopping
the whole zombie apocalypse.
Good luck killing Death.
Remember when we used to just...
Hunt wendigos?
How simple things were?
Not really.
You might need this.
Keep it. Dean's covered.
Death's own.
Kills, golly, demons
and angels and reapers
and, rumor has it,
the very thing itself.
How did you get that?
Hello!
King of the crossroads.
So, shall we?
Bobby, you just gonna sit there?
No, I'm gonna riverdance.
I suppose
if you wanna impress the ladies.
Really wasted that crossroads deal.
Fact... You get more
if you phrase it properly.
So, I took the liberty
of adding
a teeny little sub-a clause
on your behalf.
What can I say?
I'm an altruist.
Just gonna sit there?
Son of a bitch.
Yes, I know.
Completely worth your soul.
I'm a hell of a guy.
This is getting maudlin.
Can we go?
Yes to Lucifer.
Then jump in the hole.
It's an interesting plan.
That's a word for it.
So, go ahead and tell me
it's the worst plan you ever heard.
Of course.
I am happy to say that
if that's what you wanna hear.
But it's not what I think.
Really?
You and Dean have a habit
of exceeding my expectations.
He resisted Michael.
Maybe you could resist Lucifer.
But there are things
you would need to know.
- Like?
- Michael has found another vessel.
What?
It's your brother Adam.
- You must have considered it.
- We were trying not to.
If you say yes to Lucifer
and then fail...
This fight will happen.
And the collateral...
It'll be immense.
- There's also the demon blood.
- What are you talking about?
To take in Lucifer, it would be
more than you've ever drunk.
- Why?
- It strengthens the vessel.
- Keeps it from exploding.
- The guy he's in now...
Is drinking gallons.
And how is that not
the worst plan you ever heard?
They're loading up hotshots
of Croatoan in the trucks.
Okay.
First truck don't leave for an hour.
We get in,
we plant the C4 every 25 feet,
- Then we pull the fire alarm.
- That truck is leaving.
Balls!
Okay, new plan.
It's the Winchesters.
Let's bake them up a little treat.
Side door!
Get back!
Help me!
There's still people here.
Wait here.
Damn.
Let's stop for pizza.
- Are you kidding?
- Just heard it was good, that's all.
Up ahead. Big, ugly building.
Ground zero.
Horseman's stable, if you will.
- He's in there.
- How do you know?
Have you met me? Cause I know.
Also, the block is
squirming with reapers.
I'll be right back.
Boy, is my face red.
Death's not in there.
Cut the cute
and tell me where he is.
Sorry. I don't know.
Wait a minute. You don't know?
Signs pointed.
I'm just as shocked as you.
Bobby sold his soul for this!
Relax.
All deals are soul back or store credit.
We'll catch Death
in the next doomed city.
Millions, Crowley.
Millions are about to die any minute.
True.
So I strongly suggest
we get out of here.
You okay?
So, what?
Call in a bomb threat?
1,000 bomb threats?
How am I supposed to get three million
people out of Chicago in 10 minutes?
Come on!
What?
- I can't hear you!
- I said I found him.
Death, he's in there.
You coming or...
Not.
All clear.
Actually,
these things can be useful.
Can we commit our act
of domestic terrorism already?
Let's go.
Thanks for returning that.
Join me, Dean.
The pizza's delicious.
Sit down.
Took you long enough to find me.
I've been wanting to talk to you.
I gotta say...
Mixed feelings about that.
So is this the part where...
Where you kill me?
You have an inflated sense
of your importance.
To a thing like me,
a thing like you...
Well...
Think how you'd feel
if a bacterium sat at your table
and started to get snarky.
This is one little planet
in one tiny solar system
in a galaxy
that's barely out of its diapers.
I'm old, Dean.
Very old.
So invite you to contemplate
how insignificant I find you.
Eat.
Good, isn't it?
Well, I got to ask.
- How old are you?
- As old as God.
Maybe older.
Neither of us can remember anymore.
Life, death, chicken, egg.
Regardless.
At the end, I'll reap Him, too.
God?
You'll reap God?
God will die, too, Dean.
Well, this is way above
my pay grade.
Just a bit.
Then why am I still breathing,
sitting here with you?
- What do you want?
- The leash around my neck off.
Lucifer has me
bound to him.
Some unseemly little spell.
He has me where he wants,
when he wants.
That's why I couldn't go to you.
I had to wait for you to catch up.
He made me his weapon.
Hurricanes, floods,
raising the dead.
I'm more powerful
than you can process,
and I'm enslaved to a bratty child
having a tantrum.
And you think...
I can unbind you?
There's your ridiculous
bravado again.
Of course you can't.
But you can help me
take the bullets
out of Lucifer's gun.
I understand
you want this.
I'm inclined to give it to you.
- To give it to me?
- That's what I said.
But what about...
Chicago?
I suppose it can stay.
I like the pizza.
There are conditions.
Okay. Like?
You have to do whatever it takes
to put Lucifer in his cell.
- Of course.
- Whatever it takes.
- That's the plan.
- No. No plan. Not yet.
Your brother.
He's the one that can stop Lucifer.
The only one.
- What, you think...
- I know.
So, I need a promise.
You're going to let your brother
jump right into that fiery pit.
Well, do I have your word?
That had better be yes.
You know you can't cheat Death.
Now...
Would you like
the instruction manual?
How'd it go at the Rockets audition?
High kicks, fair.
Boobs need work.
I walked up and down stairs
all night for no damn reason.
I'm sore.
Feels so good,
I'm scared it's a dream.
But then I remember that
the world's dying bloody, so...
Drink?
Check it out.
Death told you how to operate?
- The whole deal?
- Yeah. It's nuts.
Of course,
I got bigger problems now.
Really? Like?
What do you think Death does
to people who lie to his face?
Nothing good.
What'd you say?
That I was cool with Sam
driving the bus
on the whole Lucifer plan.
So Death thinks Sam
ought to say yes,?
I don't know.
But of course he'd say that.
He works for Lucifer.
Against his will, I thought he said.
I'd say, take his sob story
with a fat grain of salt.
I mean, he is Death.
Exactly. He's Death.
Think of the kind of
bird's-eye view.
- Seriously?
- I'm just saying.
Don't. I mean,
what happened to you being against this?
I'm not saying Sam
ain't an ass-full of character defects.
- But...
- But what?
Back at Niveus?
I watched that kid pull
one civilian out after another.
He must have saved 10 people.
Never stopped. Never slowed down.
We're hard on him, Dean.
We've always been.
But in the meantime...
He's been running
into burning buildings
since he was, what, 12?
Pretty much.
Look, Sam's got a...
Darkness in him.
I'm not saying he don't.
But he's got a hell
of a lot of good in him, too.
I know.
Then you know
Sam will beat the devil.
Or die trying.
That's the best we can ask for.
So I got to ask, Dean.
What exactly are you afraid of?
Losing?
Or losing your brother?