- Dean!
- Lisa.
You know
how I never mentioned my job?
This is my job.
Ben wouldn't be alive
if it wasn't for you.
- You're welcome to stay.
- I can't. It's not my life.
There is someone besides Michael
strong enough to take on Lucifer.
- Who's that?
- God.
- I'm gonna find God.
- I'm Joshua.
- You talk to God?
- He knows the apocalypse has begun.
He just doesn't think
it's His problem.
- Not His problem?
- He's finished.
Just another deadbeat dad
with a bunch of excuses, right?
Maybe Joshua was lying.
I don't think he was.
You son of a bitch.
I believed in...
We'll find another way.
We can still stop all this, Dean.
- How?
- I don't know, but we'll find it.
You and me.
We'll find it.
- Drive faster.
- I can't!
- Are you okay?
- I'm amazing.
- You ever seen that many?
- No way. Not in one place.
What the hell?
Damn it!
That's something
you don't see every day.
You two all right?
- Peachy.
- Be careful.
- It's dangerous around here.
- Wait!
- No need to thank us.
- No, hold up a sec!
- Who are you?
- We're the sacrament lutheran militia.
- Sorry, what?
- Those were demons,
and this is the apocalypse.
So... buckle up.
- We're in the same line of business.
- And among colleagues.
That's a police-issued shotgun.
That truck is inspired.
Where'd you pick up this crap?
You know, you...
Pick things up along the way.
Guys, come on. This whole corner
of the State is nuts with demon omens.
- We just wanna help.
- We're on the same team here.
Just talk to us.
Follow us.
- Dylan, it's a church. Headphones off.
- Yes, ma'am.
Who would've thought the
apocalypse could be so romantic?
Marriage,
family, it's a blessing.
Especially in times like this.
So hold on to that.
Wedding?
Seriously?
We've had eight so far this week.
So, Rob tells me
you boys hunt demons.
Yes, sir.
You missed a few.
Tell us about it.
- Any idea why they're here?
- They sure seem to like us, though.
Follow me.
- So, you're a preacher.
- Not what you expected?
Dude, you're packing.
Strange times.
Is that a 12-year-old
packing salt rounds?
Everybody pitches in.
- The whole church?
- The whole town.
A town full of hunters? I don't know
whether to run or buy a condo.
The demons were killing us.
We had to do something.
- Why not call the national guard?
- We were told not to.
By who?
You're as locked and loaded
as we've ever seen.
And that exorcism was enochian.
Someone's telling you something.
Look, I'm sorry. I can't discuss it.
- Dad, it's okay.
- Leah!
It's Sam and Dean Winchester.
They're safe.
I know all about them.
You do?
Sure. From the angels.
The angels. Awesome.
Don't worry.
They can't see you here.
The marks on your ribs, right?
So, you know all about us
because angels told you?
- Among other things.
- Like the exorcism spell.
And they show me where the demons
are gonna be before it happens.
- How to fight back.
- Never been wrong.
Not once.
She's very special.
Let me guess.
Before you see something,
you get a really bad migraine,
you see flashing lights?
- How'd you know?
- You're not our first prophet.
But you are the cutest.
I mean that with total respect.
You've reached the voice mail of...
I don't understand.
Why do you want me to say my name?
Cass, it's me.
So, we are in Blue Earth, Minnesota,
and we could use a little help.
I hope you get this.
- Busy night.
- I'm telling you,
since the end started,
it's been like one long last call.
- That round's on me.
- Thanks.
So, did you get a hold of Cass?
I left him a message... I think.
So, what's your theory?
Why all the demon hits?
I don't know.
Gank the girl prophet, maybe?
What?
Just, these angels are sending
these people to do their dirty work.
And?
And they could get ripped to shreds.
We're all gonna die,
in like a month.
Maybe two. I mean it.
This is the end of the world.
But these people
aren't freaking out.
In fact, they're running
to the exits in an orderly fashion.
I don't know that
that's such a bad thing.
Who says they're all gonna die?
Whatever happened to us saving them?
Something I said?
- Paul, what's going on?
- Leah's had another vision.
Wanna go to church?
You know me.
Downright pious.
3 miles off Talmadge road.
5 miles.
There are demons gathered.
I don't know how many, but a lot.
Who's gonna join me?
Wouldn't miss it.
Someone's got to cover Rob's ass.
We're in, padre.
I'd like to offer a prayer.
Our Father in heaven...
Not so much.
Help us to fight in Your name.
We ask that You protect us
from all servants of evil.
Guide our hands in defeating them.
Deliver us *
Thank you. Amen.
I guess that's what it's like.
What?
Having backup.
Is that cool if I get a ride
back with you guys?
You saved my ass twice.
One more time, you can drive.
Get a beer.
- You earned it. Don't tell your mom.
- Believe me, I will not.
Ma'am, we're just very sorry.
You know...
This is your fault.
I wish I knew what to say.
But I don't.
I'm so sorry, Jane.
Rob.
There are no words.
Dylan...
I don't know why this happened.
I don't know why any of this
is happening.
I got no easy answers.
What I do know is...
Leah, honey?
It's okay, sweetie, it's okay.
- Dad, it's Dylan.
- Just rest a minute,
No, listen.
Dylan's coming back.
Jane, Rob...
It's going to be okay.
You'll see Dylan again.
When the final day comes,
judgment day,
he'll be resurrected,
and you'll be together again.
We'll all be together.
With all our loved ones.
We've been chosen.
The angels have chosen us.
And we will be given
paradise on earth.
All we have to do
is follow the angels' commandments.
No drinking, no gambling,
no premarital sex?
They basically just outlawed
90% of your personality.
Well, whatever. When in Rome...
- You're cool with it?
- I'm not cool.
I'm not not cool...
Look, man, I'm not a prophet.
We're not locals. It's not my call.
I'll catch up with you.
Bad time?
In general.
But now's okay.
Angel stuff
really takes it out of you?
Can't complain.
I know you have it worse.
So, what's on your mind, Dean?
Don't take this the wrong way,
but...
Are you on the level?
About what?
About paradise.
What about it?
I wanna know
what the angels are telling you.
Everything.
Well...
And you can skip the rainbows.
There's gonna be a prizefight,
and...
It's gonna get bad.
But after we win,
and we will,
The planet gets handed over
to the chosen,
and...
It's finally peaceful.
No monsters,
no disease, no death.
You're just...
With the people you love.
If you can get past the velvet rope.
Must be nice.
Being chosen.
Well, Dean, you're chosen.
More like cursed.
Must be hard.
Being the vessel of heaven
and having no hope.
So, what happened to,
"the apocalypse is good for business"?
Right up until Leah's angel pals
banned the good stuff.
- Help me kill some inventory?
- Sure.
Don't get me wrong.
I grew up here. I love this town.
These holy rollers...
I noticed
you're not the praying type.
Between you and me,
neither are half those guys.
Couple of months back, they were here,
getting wasted, banging the nanny.
Now they're all warriors of God.
- Cheers.
There's sure as hell demons.
And maybe there is a God.
I don't know. Fine.
But I'm not a hypocrite.
I never prayed before, I ain't starting.
If I go to hell, I'm going honest.
How about you?
- What about me?
- Not a true believer, I take it?
I believe.
I do. I'm just...
Pretty sure God stopped caring
a long time ago.
Where you been?
Drinkin'.
- You rebel.
- I'd have had more...
But it was curfew.
You hear they shut down
the cell towers?
That's news to me.
No cable, Internet.
Total cutoff from the "corruption
of the outside world."
Don't you get it?
They're turning this place into
some kind of fundamentalist compound.
- No, I get it.
- And all you got's a "hmm"?
- What's wrong?
- I get it. I just don't care.
What?
- What difference does it make?
- It makes a hell of a...
At what point does this become
too far for you?
Stoning? Poisoned kool-aid?
The angels are toying
with these people.
- Angel world, angel rules.
- Since when is that okay with you?
Since the angels got the only
lifeboats on the Titanic.
Who is supposed to come along
and save these people?
It was supposed to be us.
We can't do it.
So, what, you want to just
stop fighting, roll over?
I don't know. Maybe.
- Don't say that.
- Why not?
- Cause you can't do this.
- Actually, I can.
No, you can't.
You can't do this tome.
I got one thing.
One thing keeping me going.
You think you're the only one
white-knuckling it here?
I can't count on anyone else.
And I can't do this alone.
I got to clear my head.
It's past curfew.
Leah, what's wrong?
Daddy, can I talk to you
for a second?
Of course.
- Leah, honey, what is it?
- I'm sorry. They're just so angry.
- Who is?
- The angels.
- Why are they angry?
- They said...
They said that
we can't go to paradise.
What?
- We're doing everything they say!
- They gave clear commandments.
But some people aren't listening.
Who, Leah?
I got your message.
It was long, your message.
And I find the sound of your voice
grating.
What's wrong?
Are you...
Drunk?
What happened to you?
- I found a liquor store.
- And?
I drank it.
Why'd you call me?
There you go. Easy.
Are you okay?
Don't ask stupid questions.
Tell me what you need.
There have been these demon attacks,
massive, on the edge of town,
and we can't figure out why...
- Any sign of angels?
- Sort of.
They've been speaking
to this prophet.
- Who?
- This girl, Leah Gideon.
- She's not a prophet.
- Pretty sure she is.
Visions, headaches...
The whole package.
The names of all the prophets,
they're seared into my brain.
Leah Gideon is not one of them.
Then what is she?
Take a breath!
You come on my property,
spouting some...
Sorry, Paul! There's no other way!
What country is this?
- Need a hand, padre?
- Everybody cool down for a minute!
My friends
are trying to run me out of town.
- I should cool down?
- It is not our choice.
- Come on, that's bull.
- Go!
- For everyone's sake!
- We grew up together.
- I stood up at your wedding!
- You did, but that was then.
- Now you're standing against the flock.
- That's not true. I fight with you.
This is a town of believers.
- You are not a believer.
- Don't make this hard for us.
Hard for you?
This is my home.
You want me out of here?
Drag me out.
You don't wanna do this.
No one's gonna stop me
from seeing my son again.
We went out looking for...
You all right?
It's not my blood.
- Paul's dead.
- What?
- Jane shot him.
- It's starting.
What's starting?
Where have you been?
On a bender.
- Did you say on a bender?
- He's still pretty smashed.
It is not of import.
We need to talk
about what's happening here.
I'm all ears.
For starters...
Leah is not a real prophet.
- What is she, exactly?
- The whore.
Cass, tell us what you really think.
She rises
when Lucifer walks the earth.
"And she shall come,
bearing false prophecy."
This creature has the power
to take a human's form, read minds.
Book of revelation calls her
"the whore of Babylon."
That's catchy.
Leah was probably killed months ago.
- What about the demons?
- They're under her control.
- And the enochian exorcism?
- Fake.
It actually means
"you breed
with the mouth of a goat."
It's funnier in enochian.
The demons smoking out,
that's just a con?
- Why? What's the endgame?
- What you just saw.
- Innocent blood spilt in God's name.
- You heard that heaven talk.
She manipulates people.
To slaughter and kill
and sing peppy little hymns.
Awesome.
Her goal is to condemn
as many souls to hell as possible.
And it's just beginning.
She's well on her way to dragging
this whole town into the pit.
All right.
So, then, how do we go
pimp of Babylon all over this bitch?
I only wanted to...
Did I make it worse?
Did I make the angels angry?
The angels...
They understand.
What you did
was for the greater good.
We all liked Paul.
But he was a sinner,
and would have
taken us down with him.
- You saved us.
- Thank you.
How can that be okay?
She killed him.
- That sin is so much greater...
- It's not a sin to strike down evil.
- How can the angels...
- You always taught me
we have to have faith.
The whore can be killed with that.
It's a stake
made from a cypress tree in Babylon.
- Great. Let's ventilate her.
- It's not that easy.
Course not.
The whore can only be killed
by a true servant of heaven.
- Servant, like...
- Not you.
Or me.
Sam, of course, is an abomination.
We'll have to find someone else.
The angels...
I don't know why they've chosen us.
But they have.
And today...
They told me
the most important thing yet.
Tonight, at midnight...
I'm sorry.
It's just that we knew
this day would come,
and it's here.
The final judgment.
Now, we need to do this right.
We don't have much time.
We're not ready.
There are still a few elements
that need to be taken care of.
Sinners.
Everybody calm down.
Hold on.
- You're scaring these people.
- I don't want us to panic.
- But we have to hurry.
- Stop it.
I've been given instructions, names.
What are you doing? Stop it!
- You're gonna get somebody killed.
- Let me go.
Or the next sinner I name
will be you.
Pastor David Gideon?
Who are you?
- I'm an angel of the Lord.
- Yeah, sure.
What was that?
He wasn't lying
about the angel thing.
Have a seat, padre.
We got to have a chat.
- She's my daughter.
- I'm sorry, but she's not.
- She killed your daughter.
- That's impossible.
But it's true.
And deep down, you know it.
Look, we get it. It's too much.
But if you don't do this,
she's going to kill a lot of people
and damn the rest to hell.
Why does it have to be me?
You're a servant of heaven.
- And you're an angel.
- Poor example of one.
Heads up.
- How many should I take?
- You?
Down the whole bottle.
Don't mention it.
I've been there.
I'm a big expert on deadbeat dads,
so...
I get it.
I know how you feel.
How do you manage it?
On a good day,
you get to kill a whore.
Rob, Jane, please!
Come on, it's me! It's Elise!
Sorry. Really.
But you know we have to do this.
We're putting them
in the storage unit.
Jane, is that everyone?
Get the kerosene.
What?
There are kids in there.
The angels named them for a reason.
Your son needs you to do this.
- Daddy! Don't hurt me!
- Gideon, now!
Pizin noco iad.
Wait! No!
Help me! He's a demon!
Light the kerosene.
Please.
Like you're a servant of heaven.
Let me go!
This is why my team's gonna win.
You're the great vessel?
You're pathetic,
self-hating, and faithless.
It's the end of the world.
And you're just gonna sit back
and watch it happen.
Don't be so sure, whore.
I don't understand.
How are we supposed
to get to paradise now?
I'm sorry.
Pretty sure you're headed
in a different direction.
Gotcha.
- How did you do that?
- What?
- Kill her.
- Long run of luck held out, I guess.
Last I checked, she could only be ganked
by a servant of heaven.
What do you want me to tell you?
I saw a shot, I went for it.
- Are you gonna do something stupid?
- Like what?
Like Michael stupid.
Come on, Sam. Give me a break.
- How's the head?
- I'm seeing double.
But that may be the painkillers.
You'll be okay.
Where you going?
Grab some clean bandages
out of the trunk. Relax.
Damn it! Dean!
Hi, Lisa.
I didn't have your number, so...
It's okay, I'm...
I'm just surprised.
- How's Ben?
- Good.
Good. He's at baseball.
You moved. It's a...
Nice house.
You didn't come here
to talk about real estate.
You all right?
Not really.
What is it?
Look, I have no illusions.
I know the life that I live.
I know how that's gonna end for me.
Whatever, I'm okay with that.
But I wanted you to know...
When I do picture myself happy...
It's with you.
And the kid.
- You don't have to say anything.
- I mean, I know. I know.
I want to.
- Come inside, let me get you a beer.
- I wish I could.
Take care of yourself, Lisa.
You can't just drop a bombshell
like that and then leave.
I know. I'm sorry.
- But I don't have a choice.
- You do.
You can come inside
and let me get you a beer.
Wait a minute.
Things are about to get really bad.
Like how?
- Like your kind of bad?
- Worse.
Next few days,
it's gonna be downright trippy.
Scary.
But don't worry, because
I'm making arrangements for you and Ben.
- Arrangements?
- You're gonna be okay.
What do you mean?
The people I'm gonna see
won't get anything from me
without agreeing
to a few conditions.
Just come inside. Please.
And whatever you're thinking of doing,
don't.
I have to.
Just stay an hour.
At least say bye to Ben.
It's better if I don't.
Bye, Lisa.