I remember now.
I'm an angel.
I have a death sentence on my head.
- Why?
- I disobeyed.
You really shouldn't have come.
- You have to stop it.
- Stop what?
1973?
- Mom?
- John Winchester.
My parents are
Mary and John Winchester.
And I am your grandson.
Mary gets killed
by a yellow-eyed demon in 1983.
Now, if we don't catch this thing now
and kill it and it gets away...
Then Mary dies.
I couldn't stop any of it.
She still made the deal.
- She still died in the nursery?
- Destiny can't be changed, Dean.
All roads lead
to the Same destination.
I take it all back.
I love the devil.
That's what I call peace on earth.
I was just working on a case.
This is what you dream about.
This is awkward.
Why are you gate-crashing my head?
Why don't you just swing by the motel?
I can't find you.
Cass did this thing.
Cass. Right.
Now, there's a friend
you can count on.
What?
He didn't tell you?
- Tell me what?
- Where I've been.
Of course not.
Why would he?
Where have you been?
Prison.
Upstairs.
All the torture,
twice the self-righteousness.
Why wouldn't he have told us
where you were?
'cause he's the one who turned me in.
Don't look so shocked.
He was always a good little soldier.
- Did anything under orders.
- I didn't know.
Are you okay?
No.
And I don't have long.
I broke out...
Barely.
They're looking for me.
If they find me...
- What do you need?
- Meet me. 225 industrial.
And, please, just hurry.
Hello?
Who's there?
Hello, Anna.
Well...
If I didn't know any better...
I'd say the Winchesters
don't trust me.
They do.
I don't.
I wouldn't let them come.
And why is that?
If you're out of prison,
it's because they let you out.
And they sent you here to do
their dirty work.
And what makes you so sure?
Because I've experienced...
- Heaven's persuasion.
- You mean when you gave me to them.
That was a mistake.
Whatever they sent you here to do...
They didn't send me.
- I escaped.
- No one escapes.
All these centuries
and you're underestimating me now?
If you're not one of them,
then what do you want?
I want to help.
You want to help?
Then what are doing with that knife?
- I'm not allowed to defend myself?
- Against whom?
That blade doesn't work against angels.
It's not like this one.
Maybe you're not working for heaven.
But there's something
you're not telling me.
Sam Winchester has to die.
= 513 =
= Supernatural Team =
I am sorry.
But we have no choice.
He's lucifer's vessel.
- He's not the only one.
- What? That guy Nick?
He's burning away as we speak.
Sam is the only vessel that matters.
You know what that means.
If lucifer can't take Sam,
his whole plan short-circuits.
No fight with Michael,
no croatoan virus,
the horsemen go back
to their day jobs.
Even if you could...
Kill Sam, Satan would just
bring him back to life.
Not after I scatter his cells
across the universe.
They'll never find him...
Not all of him.
We'll find another way.
How's that going?
How's The Colt working out?
Or the search for god?
Is anything working?
If you want to stop
the devil, this is how.
The answer is still no.
Because Sam is my friend.
You've changed.
Maybe too late.
But I have.
Anna, we've been
through much together.
But you come near Sam Winchester
and I'll kill you.
Oh, my god.
You okay?
We have to get her to a hospital.
Come on.
Really? Anna?
- I don't believe it.
- It's true.
So she's gone all Glenn Close?
That's awesome.
Who's Glenn Close?
No one. Just this psycho bitch
who likes to boil rabbits.
So, the plan to kill me
would it actually stop Satan?
No, Sam, come on.
Cass, what do you think?
Does Anna have a point?
No.
She's a "Glenn Close."
I don't get it. We're looking
for the chick that wants to gank Sam?
- Why poke the bear?
- Anna will keep trying.
She won't give up until Sam is dead.
So we kill her first.
- I found her.
- Where is she?
Not where.
When.
It's 1978.
What?
Why 1978?
I wasn't even born yet.
You won't be...
If she kills your parents.
What?
Anna can't get to you because of me.
- So she's going after them.
- Take us back right now.
And deliver you right to Anna?
I should go alone.
They're our parents, Cass.
We're going.
It's not that easy.
Why not?
Time travel was difficult even with
the powers of heaven at my disposal.
But you're cut off.
So, what? You're like a delorean
without enough plutonium.
I don't understand that reference.
But I'm telling you, taking this trip,
with passengers, no less...
... it'll weaken me.
They're our mom and dad.
If we can save them
and not just from Anna...
I mean,
if we can set things right...
We have to try.
Ready?
- Not really.
- Bend your knees.
Did we make it?
Unless they're bringing pintos back
into production, I'd say yes.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
You all right?
I'm fine.
I'm much better than I expected.
He's breathing...
Sort of.
What do we do?
I mean, the mustaches alone...
So I paid for Cass for five nights up
in the honeymoon suite.
I told the manager:
"Do not disturb no matter what".
You know what he said to me?
"Yeah. Don't sweat it.
Want to buy some dope?"
Dope.
We ought to stick around here,
buy some stock in Microsoft.
We might have to
if Cass doesn't recover.
Is he all right?
What do I look like
Dr. Angel, medicine woman?
He'll wake up.
He's tough for a little nerdy dude
with wings.
If he landed like that,
hopefully, so did Anna.
- Should buy us some time.
- So, did you find 'em?
The Winchesters.
485 Tobin Tree.
Let's go pop in on the folks.
Wait, wait.
Anna could be here any second.
What exactly are we gonna
march up there and tell 'em?
The truth.
That their sons are back from the future
to save them from an angel
gone "terminator"?
Those movies haven't even
come out yet.
Then tell her demons are after'em.
She thinks you're a hunter?
A hunter who disappeared right
when her dad died.
She's gonna love me.
Just follow my lead.
How was work?
It was great.
Not until you wash up.
I love when you get bossy.
Hi, Mary.
You can't be here.
- I'm sorry if this is a bad time.
- You don't understand. I'm not...
I don't do that anymore.
I have a normal life now.
You have to go.
I'm sorry,
but this is important, okay?
Sorry, sweetie, they're just...
Mary's cousins.
We couldn't stop through town
without swinging by
and saying "hey," now, could we?
Dean.
You look familiar.
Really?
You do, too, actually, you know?
We must have met sometime.
Small towns, right?
- Got to love 'em.
- I'm John.
This is Sam.
Sam.
Mary's father was a Sam.
It's a family name.
You okay, pal?
You look a little spooked.
Just a long trip.
Sam and Dean
were just on their way out.
What?
They just got here.
Real happy to meet folks
from Mary's side.
Please come on in for a beer.
Twist my arm.
Are you sure you're okay, Sam?
I'm just...
You are so beautiful.
He means that in a non-weird,
wholesome, family kind of a way.
Right.
We haven't seen Mary
in quite some time and...
See, she's the spitting image
of our mom.
- I mean, it's...
- Eerie.
So, how are you guys related?
You know, distantly.
- So you knew Mary's parents?
- Yeah, yeah.
Mary's dad was...
Pretty much like a grandpa to us.
That was tragic...
That heart attack.
Yes, it was.
So what are you guys
doing in town, anyway?
Business, you know.
What line of work?
- Plumbing.
- Scrap metal.
It's almost 7:00.
I hate to be rude,
but I got to get dinner ready.
- Maybe they could stay.
- I'm sure they have to leave.
Look, please stay.
You know, it would mean a lot to me.
I haven't met much
of Mary's side of the family.
Look, Mr. Woodson,
I'm begging you to reconsider.
I'd like to, John.
You're a great mechanic.
But times ain't exactly rosy.
Even just part time.
I really need this job.
All right, look.
Come on in right now, let's talk.
Maybe we can figure something out.
You serious?
I'll see you in 10 minutes.
Don't keep me waiting.
You have to leave.
Now.
- Just listen...
- No, you listen.
Last time I saw you,
a demon killed my parents.
Now you waltz
in here like you're family?
Whatever you want... no.
- Leave me alone.
- You and John are in danger.
- What are you talking about?
- Something's coming for you.
Demon?
Not exactly.
What, then?
- It's kind of hard to explain. It's...
- An angel.
What?
- There's no such thing.
- I wish.
But they're twice as strong
as demons and bigger dicks.
Why would an angel want to kill us?
It's a long story
and we'll tell you the whole thing,
but right now, you've got to trust us
and we got to go.
Look at my face
and tell me if I'm lying to you.
Okay.
Where do we go?
Out of here.
We got to move now, though.
- But what do I tell John?
- Just tell him...
John?
Mr. Woodson?
You still here?
I wish I could say
it's good to see you.
You too, Dean.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
It's not that easy to kill an angel.
No.
But you can distract 'em.
Monsters.
Monsters?
Yes.
- Monsters are real.
- I'm sorry, I didn't know how...
And you fight them?
- All of you?
- Yeah.
How long?
All my life.
John, just try to understand...
Shut up, all of you!
Not another word, or so help me,
I will turn this car around!
Wow. Awkward family road trip.
No kidding.
Place has been
in the family for years.
Devil's trap.
Pure iron fixtures, of course.
There should be salt and holy water
in the pantry, knives, guns.
All that stuff will
do is piss it off.
So, what will kill it?
Or slow it down, at least?
- Not much.
- Great.
He said not much, not nothing.
We packed.
If we put this up
and she comes close,
we beam her right off the starship.
This is holy oil.
It's kind of like a devil's trap
for angels.
I'll show you how it works.
What's the deal
with the thing on the paper?
It's a sigil.
- That means...
- I don't care.
Where does it go?
On a wall or a door.
How big should I make it?
- John...
- What?
Y'all might have treated me
like a fool, but I am not useless.
I can draw
a damn... Whatever it is...
A sigil.
Go help Sam out.
Cause this has got to be done in...
In human blood.
So, how big?
I'll show you.
What?
All of a sudden,
you really remind me of my dad.
That's really good.
You come to check on me?
I wanted to say I'm sorry
about all this.
I know it's a lot.
How long have you known
about this hunting stuff?
Pretty much forever.
- My dad raised me in it.
- You're serious?
Who the hell does that to a kid?
For the record, Mary's parents did.
I don't care.
What kind of irresponsible bastard
lets a child
anywhere near...
You could've been killed!
Came kind of close.
The number it must've done
on your head.
Your father
was supposed to protect you.
He was trying.
He died trying.
Believe me...
I used to be mad at him,
I used to...
I used to hate the guy.
But now I...
I get it.
He was...
Doing his best.
And he was trying
to keep it together
in this impossible situation.
See...
My mom...
She was amazing, beautiful, and...
She was the love of his life.
And she got killed.
I think he would have gone crazy
if he didn't do something.
Truth is...
My dad died
before I got to tell him that...
I understand...
Why he did what he did.
And I forgive him
for what it did to us. I do.
And I just...
I love him.
Uriel.
- You look well.
- You shouldn't have called.
We're under strict orders
not to come down here.
Much less take a vessel.
You're not the Anna of now.
But 30 years from now,
I'm still your superior.
I need you to kill some humans.
Always happy to do some smiting.
What's going on?
In the future, these people
are going to kill you, Uriel.
I'm giving you the chance
to kill them first.
Thank you.
You said you'd explain everything
when we had a minute.
We have a minute.
Why does an angel want me dead?
Cause they're dicks.
Not good enough.
I didn't even know they existed
and now I'm a target?
It's complicated.
Fine.
All ears.
Trust me, okay?
I've been trusting you all day.
- It's kinda hard to believe.
- All right, then.
- I'm walking out.
- I'm your son.
What?
I'm your son.
I don't know how else to say it.
We're from the year 2010.
An angel zapped us back here.
Not the one that attacked you.
Friendlier.
You can't expect me to believe that.
Our names
are Dean and Sam Winchester.
We're named after your parents.
When I would get sick,
you would make me tomato-rice soup,
because that's what your mom
made you.
And instead of a lullaby,
you would sing Hey Jude.
Cause that's your favorite
Beatles song.
I don't believe it.
It's true.
I raised my kids to be hunters?
- No, you didn't.
- How could I do that to you?
You didn't.
Because you're dead.
What?
What happened?
Yellow-eyed demon.
He killed you, and...
John became a hunter to get revenge.
He raised us in this life.
Listen to me.
A demon comes into Sam's nursery
exactly six months after he's born.
November 2, 1983.
Remember that date.
And whatever you do...
Do not go in there.
That morning,
you take Sam and you run.
That's not good enough.
Wherever she goes,
the demon's gonna find her.
Find me.
Well, then what?
She can leave dad.
That's what.
You gotta leave john.
When this is over,
walk away and never look back.
So we're never born.
- He's right.
- I can't.
You're saying you're my children,
and now...
You have no choice.
There's a big difference
between dying and never being born.
And trust me, we're okay with it,
I promise you that.
I'm not.
You think you can have that normal life
you want so bad.
But you can't, I'm sorry.
It's gonna go rotten.
You are gonna die,
and your children will be cursed.
- There has to be a way.
- This is the way.
- Leave John.
- I can't.
This is bigger than us.
- There are so many more lives at stake.
- You don't understand.
I can't.
It's too late.
I'm pregnant.
We got a problem.
The sigils, they're gone.
- Gone as in...
- I drew one the door, I turned around.
When I looked again,
it was a smudge.
He's right.
There's no more holy oil.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm Uriel.
Come on...
Go.
Here goes nothin'.
I'm really sorry.
Anna...
Michael.
I didn't know.
Goodbye, Uriel.
- What did you do to John?
- John is fine.
Who... What are you?
Well, I'd say this conversation
is long overdue,
wouldn't you?
- Fix him.
- First...
We talk.
Then
I fix your darling little Sammy.
How'd you get in my dad?
I told him I could save his wife,
and he said yes.
I guess they oversold me
being your one and only vessel.
You're my true vessel
but not my only one.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- It's a bloodline.
- A bloodline?
- Stretching back to Cain and Abel.
It's in your blood, your father's blood,
your family's blood.
Awesome.
Six degrees of heaven bacon.
What do you want with me?
You really don't know?
I ain't gonna say yes,
so why are you here?
- What do you want with me?
- I just want you to understand
what you and I have to do.
I get it.
You got beef with your brother.
Well, get some therapy, pal,
don't take it out on my planet!
You're wrong.
Lucifer defied our Father,
and he betrayed me, but still...
I don't want this any more
than you would want to kill Sam.
You know, my brother...
I practically raised him.
I took care of him
in a way most people
could never understand,
and I still love him.
But I am going to kill him
because it is right
and I have to.
- Because God says so?
- Yes.
From the beginning, He knew
this was how it was going to end.
- And you're gonna do whatever God says.
- Yes, because I am a good son.
Well, trust me, pal,
take it from someone who knows,
- that is a dead-end street.
- Think you know better than my father?
One unimportant little man.
What makes you think
you get to choose?
Because I got to believe
that I can choose what I do
with my...
Unimportant little life.
You're wrong.
You know how I know?
Think of a million
random acts of chance
that let John and Mary be born,
to meet, to fall in love,
to have the two of you.
Think of the million random choices
that you make,
and yet how each
and every one of them
brings you closer to your destiny.
Do you know why that is?
Because it's not random.
It's not chance.
It's a plan
that is playing itself out perfectly.
Free will's an illusion, Dean.
That's why you're going to say yes.
Buck up.
It could be worse.
Unlike my brothers,
I won't leave you a drooling mess
when I'm done.
- What about my dad?
- Better than new.
In fact, I'm gonna do your mom
and your dad a favor.
- What?
- Scrub their minds.
They won't rember me
or you.
- You can't do that.
- I'm giving your mother what she wants.
She can go back to her husband,
her family.
She's gonna walk
right into that nursery!
Obviously.
And you always knew
that was going to play out
one way
or another.
You can't fight city hall.
He's home.
Safe and sound.
Your turn.
I'll see you soon, Dean.
- We got you.
- You son of a bitch, you made it.
I did?
I'm very surprised.
- You're okay.
- Bed?
Well, I could use that drink now.
- This is it.
- This is what?
Team free will.
One ex-blood junkie,
one dropout
with 6 bucks to his name,
and Mr. Comatose over there.
It's awesome.
It's not funny.
I'm not laughing.
- They all say we'll say yes.
- I know, it's getting annoying.
- What if they're right?
- They're not.
I mean, why would we, either of us?
I've been weak before.
- Michael got dad to say yes.
- That was different.
Anna was about to kill mom.
And if you could save mom,
what would you say?
- Where'd you even get it?
- Garage sale.
25 cents.
Well, I'm glad to hear that, anyway.
I mean, you really don't think
it's just a little cheesy?
I think it's sweet.
Can't even put my finger
on why I like it.
I just...
Like it.
Well, then, I love it.
Quite a kick there.
Troublemaker already.
It's okay, baby.
It's all okay.
Angels are watching over you.