- Who are you?
- Castiel.
- What are you?
- I'm an angel of the lord.
- Some angel you are.
- My true form
It can be overwhelming to humans
And so can my real voice...
But you already knew that.
Certain people... special people...
- Can perceive my true visage.
- What visage are you in now, huh?
This? This is...
- a vessel.
- You're possessing some poor bastard?
He's a devout man.
He actually prayed for this.
Something major must have
happened while I was downstairs,
'cause I can't back and
and you're bff with a demon?
- Why do you trust her so much?
- Because... she saved my life.
Sucking blood?
You got to know that's wrong.
I wish to god I could stop.
We need to talk.
I'm dreaming, aren't I?
It's not safe here.
- Someplace more private.
- More private? We're inside my head.
Exactly.
Someone could be listening.
Cass, what's wrong?
Meet me here.
Go... now.
What'd he say, Dean?
What was so important?
If I knew, would I be here?
What the hell?
Looks like a bomb went off.
There was a fight here.
Between who?
Check it out.
Look familiar?
Yeah, it does.
Anna used something like that
To wish the angels
back to the cornfield.
So, what? Cass was fighting angels?
I don't know.
Sam.
Cass?
Cass! Hey! Cass!
What's... what's going on?
Just take it easy. Take it easy.
Cass, you okay?
Castiel?
I'm not Castiel.
It's me.
- Who's "me"?
- Jimmy.
My name's Jimmy.
Where the hell is Castiel?
He's gone.
Mind slowing down?
You're gonna give me angina.
I'm hungry.
When's the last time you ate?
I don't know... months.
What the hell happened back there?
It looked like
an angel battle royal.
All I remember is there was
a flash of light, and I...
I woke up, and I was just,
you know, like, me again.
So, what Cass just ditched
out of your meat suit?
I really don't know.
You remember anything
about being possessed?
Anything at all?
Yeah, bits and pieces.
I mean, angel inside of you...
It's kind of like being
chained to a comet.
Well, that doesn't
sound like much fun.
Understatement.
Cass said he wanted
to tell us something.
Please tell me you remember that.
Sorry.
Come on. What do you know?
My name is Jimmy Novak.
I'm from Pontiac, Illinois.
And I have a family.
Claire.
Bless this food, O lord,
And ourselves to thy loving service,
That we may always continue
in thy faith and fear
To the honor and glory of thy name.
- Amen.
I can see my head sticking out
From underneath the front bumper.
My eyes were closed.
My head was turned
to the right side.
And on each side
of me is an angel, and...
blank.
So, what do we do?
The guy's got a family.
We buy him a bus ticket,
send him home.
I don't know about that.
Dean, he's the only lead we got.
- He doesn't know anything.
- Are you 100% about that?
You think he's lying?
You want to go
guantanamo on the guy?
Dean, maybe he doesn't
even know what he knows.
I say at least
we get him to Bobby's.
Maybe all he needs is...
is hypnosis or a psychic,
maybe Cass will just
drop back into him.
- I don't know.
- Back there, that was
angel-on-angel violence.
I don't know what's going on,
but it's big,
and we can't just let the only
lead we've got just skip out.
What?
Remember when our job
was helping people...
- Getting them back to their family?
- You think I don't want to help him?
I'm just being realistic.
We're doing him a favor.
- How?!
- Dean, if we want to question the guy,
You can damn well bet
the demons do, too.
What the hell are you talking about,
I can't go home?
You have a bull's-eye on your back.
What? From who?
- Demons.
- Come on. That's crazy.
- What do they want with me?
- I don't know. Information, maybe.
I don't know anything!
- I know, but...
- Look, I'm done, okay?
With demons, angels, all of it.
- I just want to go home.
- We understand.
I don't think
that you do understand.
I've been shot, stabbed and healed,
my body's been dragged
all over the earth.
By some miracle,
I'm out, and I am done.
I've given enough, okay?
All we're saying is
that until we figure this out,
The safest place is with us.
How long?
We'll cross that bridge
when we get to it.
- Where you going?
- To see my wife and daughter, okay?
No, you're not.
You're just gonna put
those people in danger.
So, what... now I'm a prisoner?
Harsh way to put it.
Dean!
Would you hurry up?
Sorry... this is funny to you?
Mr. Big bad prison guard,
and Jimmy Mcmook gives you the slip?
It's pretty funny.
What were you doing, anyway?
I was getting a coke.
Was it a refreshing coke?
Can we just go, please?
- What the hell are you doing?
- It's okay.
- I'm okay.
- Jimmy.
Look.
- What's wrong with you?
- Nothing's wrong.
He asked me to do it.
Who asked you to do it?
Castiel.
To prove my faith. Look.
I'm fine.
It's a miracle.
Who's Castiel?
Hey, guys.
Geez!
- Smooth.
- You ever try calling ahead?
I like the element of surprise.
You look terrific.
Not the most appropriate time, Dean.
You let Jimmy get away?
Talk to ginormo here.
Sam...
You seem... different.
Me?
I don't know. Haircut?
That's not what I'm talking about.
So, what'd Jimmy tell you?
- He remember anything?
- Why? What's going on?
It's Cass. He got sent back home.
- Well, more like dragged back.
- To heaven?
- That's not a good thing?
- No.
That's a very bad thing.
Painfully, awfully bad.
He must have seriously
pissed someone off.
Cass said he had something
to tell me, something important.
- What?
- I don't know.
- Does Jimmy know?
- I don't think so.
You don't think so?
Whatever it is, it's huge.
- You got to find out for sure.
- That's why we're going after Jimmy.
That's why you shouldn't have
let him go in the first place.
He's... probably dead already.
Take the pills.
- I'm not sick.
- Jimmy, take the pills.
I know that this is
hard to understand...
But he chose me.
- Castiel the angel?
- He's spoken to me now, Ames
A dozen times.
You believe in god, don't you?
What kind of question is that?
Of course.
- And angels?
- Yes, Jimmy.
So, why is it, then,
so hard for you to believe
- That they're talking to me?
- You sell
- ad time for a. m Radio.
- No, he said that
I'm special, it's in my blood.
It's in your blood?
He didn't say.
He just said that god has chosen me
- for a higher purpose.
- To do what?
You know, it's god's will.
Not really my place to question it.
Hey, come here.
This is a blessing.
This is the most important thing
to ever happen to me.
I thought we were the most
important things to ever happen to you.
- Have faith.
- Jimmy... you're scaring me.
God will provide.
If you won't take your pills
and if you won't get help...
... then I'm gonna take Claire
to my mother's in the morning.
So, I want to help you.
I'm about to lose my family here
If you don't tell me how.
Please, Castiel, just talk to me.
What do you want from me?
Yes, I understand.
Promise my family will be okay
and I'll do it.
Then...
Daddy?
I am not your father.
We...
- We stopped looking for you.
- I'm so sorry.
You were dead.
We... we thought you were dead.
I'm okay.
Claire, room, now.
Can I see her?
No.
I don't know yet.
- It's been almost a year, you know?
- I know.
Think your daughter would have
wanted to know you were okay.
I was in a psych clinic.
I just wanted to get myself
straight before seeing you.
- And no telephones, or...
- No. I know. You're right. I'm...
I'm so sorry.
But it's all, it's all over now.
- I mean, I'm really okay.
- What does that mean?
I was, I was confused, Amelia.
I was completely delusional.
And I thought, I thought god was
calling me to something,
And I thought that it was important.
And...
I was wrong.
I was such an idiot.
Heaven, hell...
None of that matters.
The only thing that's important
to me is you and Claire.
And I...
I can't undo what I've done.
But I just want to come home again.
I don't know if I can do that.
Not yet.
I mean, whatever...
you're comfortable with.
Maybe we could start
with something smaller?
Like what?
I don't know. Dinner?
Where the hell are you, Ruby?
This isn't funny anymore.
I'm all out.
Stop whatever you're doing.
Call me.
I need more.
- Hi, daddy.
- Hi, baby.
We have turkey and roast beef.
- Better be okay. It's all we have.
- It's fine.
It's more than fine.
- Shall we sit?
- Yeah.
It's perfect.
Daddy aren't you gonna say grace?
No, honey, I don't think I am.
Why are you crying?
'cause I'm happy.
Am I crazy, or did I just see
your husband wander in here
about half an hour ago?
Yeah, you did. But...
- Roger, now's not a good time.
- Hey. There he is.
Son of a bitch.
What the hell happened to you?
Long story. But it's over.
Yeah?
- I'm good.
- Can I talk to you?
Can I get you a beer?
- That'd be good.
- Thanks.
Get in here.
Buddy, you scared the hell out
of a lot of people.
I know, I know.
So, really, what happened?
Honestly?
Worst year of my life
and you wouldn't believe a word of it.
But... it's all okay now.
Swear.
Actually, no, it's not.
What do you mean?
I'm gonna gut your daughter
while you watch.
Here you go.
What are you doing!
- He's a demon!
- Jimmy, stop!
- Run! Run!
- Stop it!
- Where is it?
- Roger was your best friend.
Roger was a demon.
- Don't cross this line.
- You thought you were better.
But you are so sick.
- I'm not crazy.
- Stay the hell away from us!
- This is very, very real.
Claire! No! Run!
Leave her alone!
Stay there! Claire!
Damn it!
Hey, pal.
- Told you I'd gut the bitch.
- Roger.
- Daddy?
- Just let her go, okay?
Now, me... I would.
But the missus...
she has other ideas.
Daddy!
Oh, my god.
No!
Go! Get them out of here!
Go! Go!
Can't get it up, can you, Sam?
No, but I can.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh, my god.
- Where's your wife?
- Right here.
Let's go!
You were right.
Sorry we were.
But I'm telling you...
I don't know anything.
I don't think they're
inclined to believe you.
And even if they did,
you're a vessel.
They're still gonna want to
know what makes you tick.
Which means vivisection...
if they're feeling generous.
I'm gonna tell you once again...
You're putting
your family in danger.
You have to come with us.
How long?
And don't give me that "cross
that bridge when we get to it" crap.
Don't you get it?
Forever.
The demons will never stop.
You can never be with your family.
So, you either get as far
away from them as possible
Or you put a bullet in your head,
And that's how you
keep your family safe,
But there's no getting out
and there's no going home.
Don't sugarcoat it, Sam.
I'm just telling
him the truth, Dean.
Someone has to.
I pretty much owe you
the biggest apology ever.
- No, you don't.
- Yes. I do.
I'm so sorry, Jimmy.
And I will never,
ever forgive myself
for letting you walk out that door.
Well, you did what any rational
person would have done.
I mean, hell,
I thought I was crazy half the time.
So... demons, huh?
Yeah.
Can we...
Can we even go home, or...?
What are we gonna do?
These boys are gonna get you a car.
Don't ask me how.
And you're gonna take
Claire to Carl and Sally's
As fast as you can.
Wait. What about you?
No. I'm not going
anywhere without you, Jimmy.
Listen to me.
Every moment that I'm with you.
You and Claire are in danger.
I don't care.
We are not splitting up again.
We don't have a choice.
For how long?
We'll... cross
that bridge when we get to it.
- We're family.
- They will kill you, Amelia.
And they'll kill Claire.
You just have to get as far
away from me as you can.
Okay, so... here's your car.
Take care of your mom, okay, bub?
Why is he leaving again?
This is just not my day, is it?
You little bitch.
What the hell happened back there?
What?
You practically fainted
trying to gank a demon.
Okay, I didn't faint.
- I got a little dizzy.
- You can call it whatever you want.
Point is, you used to be
strong enough to kill alastair.
Now you can't even kill
stunt demon number three?
What do you want me to say about it?
For starters,
what's going on with your mojo?
It's yo-yo'ing all over the place.
I'm not trying to pick a fight here.
you're scaring me, man.
I'm scaring myself.
Hello?
Who is this?
It's your wife.
Amelia?
Oh, my god.
They're expecting you to come alone.
That's exactly what you're gonna do.
We'll work our way
through the catwalks.
We'll be right behind you.
All you got to do is stay calm
and stall and let us do our job.
You want me to stay calm?
This is my family we're talking about.
Listen to me, this will work.
You understand?
Nobody's gonna get hurt.
Whatever.
Give me a minute, okay?
There's no way they're expecting
him to come alone, Dean.
You know this is probably a trap.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I have a plan.
Castiel, you son of a bitch!
You promised me
my family would be okay!
You promised you were
gonna take care of them!
I've gave you everything
you asked me to give!
I gave you more!
This is the thanks I get?
This is what you do?
Your heaven?!
Help me, please!
You promised, Cass!
Just help me!
Typical.
Hi, honey. You're home.
Listen, I'm...
I'm begging you here.
You do whatever you want with me...
But my wife and daughter,
they're just...
- They're not a part of this.
- They're a big part of this, Jimmy.
And p.s, you should have come alone.
- I am alone.
- Oh, you're such a liar.
Like I didn't think you'd
bring Heckle and Jeckle.
- Nice plan, Dean.
- Well, nobody bats a thousand.
Got the knife?
- And you know what's funny?
- You wearing a soccer mom?
Is I was actually bummed
to get this detail.
Picking up an empty vessel?
Sort of like a milk run.
- Now look who landed in my lap.
- Yeah, well...
You got us, okay?
- Let these people go.
- Oh, Sam.
It's easy to act chivalrous
When your wonder girl
powers aren't working, huh?
Now for the punch line...
Everybody dies.
Waste little orphan annie.
Castiel.
Of course we keep our promises.
Of course you have our gratitude.
You served us well.
Your work is done.
It's time to go home now...
your real home.
You'll rest forever in
the fields of the lord.
Rest now, Jimmy.
She's with me now.
She's chosen.
It's in her blood,
as it was in yours.
Please, Castiel.
I mean, just... just take me.
Take me, please.
I want to make sure you understand.
You won't die... or age.
If this last year
was painful for you,
Picture a hundred...
a thousand more like it.
Doesn't matter.
You take me.
Just take me.
As you wish.
Cass, hold up.
What were you gonna tell me?
I learned my lesson
while I was away, Dean.
I serve heaven. I don't serve man.
And I certainly don't serve you.
All right. Let's hear it.
- What?
- Drop the bomb, man.
You saw what I did. Come on.
Stop the car. Take a swing.
- I'm not gonna take a swing.
- Then scream. Chew me out.
- I'm not mad, Sam.
- Come on. You're not mad?
Right. Look,
at least let me explain myself.
Don't.
I don't care.
You don't care?
What do you want me to say
that I'm disappointed?
Yeah, I am.
But mostly, I'm just tired, man.
And I'm done.
I am just done.
Hey, Bobby.
You and your brother better
shag ass to my place asap.
- What's going on?
- The apocalypse,
genius. Now, get your
asses over here.
What'd he say?
Well, thanks for shaking a tail.
Glad you got here.
Go on inside.
I want to show you something.
All right.
So... what's the big demon problem?
You are.
This is for your own good.
Guys?
Hey. Guys!
This isn't funny!
Guys!
I'm not drinking
the demon blood for kicks.
I'm getting strong
enough to kill Lilith.
All the seals falling.
Except one.
You give yourself over holy to
the serves of the god and his angels.
- Yes. I swear.
- I will wait on... time.
I'm not gonna give him demon blood.
I won't do it.
I won't let my brother
turnning into a monster.
Guys, help
- Sam looks last... st worker.
- We are killing him.
This poison I hope is Ruby.
***
She is poison, Sam.
You are gonna out door,
don't you ever come back
I've been waiting this
- For a very long time.
- Then give me your best shoot.