You know how I feel
about Halloween?
- Who are you?
- Castiel.
- I mean what are you?
- I'm an angel of the lord.
The rising of the witnesses
is one of the 66 seals.
Those seals are being
broken by lilith.
- Last one opens and...
- Lucifer walks free.
So, you been using your,
- freaky E.S.P. stuff?
- No.
Yeah, well, let's keep it that way.
- I'm just exorcising demons.
- with your mind!
I can send them back to hell.
- But try to see the other side here.
- The other side?!
I'm pulling demons
out of innocent people.
- Use the knife!
- The knife kills the victim.
What I do, most of them survive!
You should show me some respect.
I dragged you out of hell.
I can throw you back in.
- How was the store?
- Oh, madness.
Everyone in town was stocking up.
Did, uh, you get enough?
I had to arm-wrestle
norma bleaker for these.
Honey, she's 74.
And a lot stronger than she looks.
Remember last year?
We ran out at 6:30.
It's just one piece.
You can have as much as you want...
After halloween.
No.
Oh, who needs a bath?
Oh, there we go!
- You coming?
- I'll, uh, i'll be up in a minute.
Okay.
Luke, what's taking you so long?
Oh, my god!
Synchro VO: IceFre@k
Now, how many razor
blades did they find?
Two on the floor,
one in his stomach, and...
one was stuck in his throat.
He swallowed four of them.
How is that even possible?
The candy was never in the oven.
We just have to be thorough, mrs.
Wallace.
Did the police find any
razors in the rest of the candy?
No.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't think so.
I just...
I can't believe it.
You hear urban legends about this stuff,
but it actually happens?
More than you might imagine.
Mrs. Wallace,
did luke have any enemies?
Enemies?
Anyone who might have
held a grudge against him?
- What do you mean?
- Co-workers.
Neighbors.
Maybe a woman.
Are you suggesting an affair?
- Is it possible?
- No!
No, luke would nev--
I'm very sorry.
We just have to consider
all possibilities.
If someone wanted
to kill my husband,
don't you think they'd find
a better way than a razor
in a piece of candy he might eat?
Really?
After that guy choked
down all those razor blades?
It's halloween, man.
Yeah.
For us, every day is halloween.
Don't be a downer.
Anything interesting?
We're on a witch-hunt,
that's for sure.
But this isn't your typical hex bag.
No?
Goldthread... An herb that's
been extinct for 200 years.
And this is celtic,
and I don't mean some new age knock-off.
Looks like the real deal.
Like...
600-years-old real.
And, uh...
That is the charred metacarpal
bone of a newborn baby.
Oh, gross.
Relax, man.
It's, like, at least 100 years old.
Oh, right,
like that makes it better?
Witches, man.
They're so freaking skeevy.
Well, it takes a pretty powerful
one to put a bag like this together.
More juice than we've ever
dealt with before, that's for sure.
What about you...
Find anything on the victim?
This luke wallace --
He was so vanilla that
he made vanilla seem spicy.
I can't find any reason why
somebody would want this guy dead.
This party blows.
We should just go t. P. Somebody.
- Uh, hey, justin.
- Yo.
You break into the booze yet?
Uh, it's triple-locked.
So, you guys going to the
mausoleum party tomorrow night?
Are you gonna be there?
It's gonna be rad.
I'm gonna get so baked.
Well, it's got to be better
than this g-rated assfest.
Oh, come on, it's not that bad.
Oh, check it out.
Okay, bobbing for apples is lame.
Oh, come on, it's halloween.
Uh... lame.
I stand corrected.
Well, I want to try.
She can really hold her breath.
Jenny?
Help me!
Jenny, what's wrong?
Help!
Come on, let's go!
What is happening?
Jenny, come on!
Help! Jenny!
Oh, my god.
Yes.
I got this one.
Two words... Jail bait.
I would never.
You know, it's just so weird.
I mean, the water in the tub...
It wasn't hot.
I had just been in there myself.
You friend didn't happen
to know a man named luke wallace?
Agent seger... FBI.
Um, who's luke wallace?
He died yesterday.
I don't know who that is.
I'm telling you,
both of these vics are squeaky-clean.
There was no reason
for wicked-bitch payback.
Maybe 'cause it's not about that.
Wow. Insightful.
Maybe this witch
isn't working a grudge.
Maybe they're working a spell.
Check this out.
"Three blood sacrifices
over three days...
The last before midnight on
the final day of the final harvest."
Celtic calendar... The final day
of the final harvest
is october 31st.
- Halloween?
- Exactly.
What exactly are the,
uh, blood sacrifices for?
Uh, if I'm right,
this witch is summoning a demon.
And not just any demon --
Samhain.
Am I supposed to be impressed?
Dean, samhain is the
damn origin of halloween.
The celts believed that october 31st
was the one night of
the year when the veil was thinnest
between the living and the dead.
And it was samhain's night.
Masks were put on to hide from him,
sweets left on doorsteps
to appease him,
faces carved into pumpkins
to worship him.
He was exorcised centuries ago.
So even though samhain took
a trip downstairs, the tradition stuck.
Exactly.
Only now, instead of demons
and blood orgies, halloween is all about
kids, candy, and costumes.
Okay, so some witch wants to
raise samhain and take back the night?
- Dean, this is serious.
- I am serious.
We're talking
heavyweight witchcraft.
This ritual can only
be performed every 600 years.
And the 600-year
marker rolls around...
- Tomorrow night.
- Naturally.
It sure is a lot of death
and destruction for one demon.
That's 'cause he likes company.
Once he's raised, Samhain
- can do some raising of his own.
- Raising what, exactly?
Dark, evil crap and lots of it.
They follow him around
like the friggin' pied piper.
So we're talking ghosts.
Zombies?
- Leprechauns?
- Dean.
Those little dudes are scary.
Small hands.
It just starts with
ghosts and ghouls.
This sucker keeps on going, by night's
end, we are talking every awful
thing we've ever seen,
everything we fight
all in one place.
It's gonna be a slaughterhouse.
How's it going?
Awesome.
Yeah, I talked with mrs.
Razor blade again.
I've been sitting out
in front of her house for hours,
and I've got a big,
steamy pile of nothing.
Someone planted those hex bags,
someone with access to both houses.
- There's got to be some connection.
- Yeah, well, I hope we find him soon
'cause I'm starting to cramp like a...
Son of a bitch.
Quit whining.
No, sam, I mean "son of a bitch."
So?
Our apple-bobbing cheerleader?
Tracy?
The wallaces' babysitter.
She told me she'd never
even heard of luke wallace.
Interesting look for
a centuries-old witch.
If you were a 600-year-old hag
and you could pick any costume
to come back in,
wouldn't you go
for a hot cheerleader?
I would.
Well, tracy's not as
wholesome as she looks.
Did some digging.
Apparently, she got into a violent
altercation with one of her teachers.
Got suspended from school.
Bring back memories?
What do you mean?
Being a teenager, all that angst.
Oh.
What'd you think I meant?
Nothing.
Now, that brings back memories.
Dude, I need a bigger kiln.
You gentlemen wanted to talk to me?
Ah, Mr. Harding.
Oh, please. Don.
- Okay, don.
- Even my students call me don.
Yeah, we get it, don.
Uh, I'm agent geddy.
This is agent lee.
We just had a few questions about,
uh, tracy davis.
Uh, yeah, tracy.
Uh, bright kid, loads of talent.
It's a shame she got suspended.
You two had a,
uh, violent altercation.
Yeah, she exploded.
Uh, if principal murrow
hadn't walked by when he did,
- Tacy would have clawed my eyes out.
- Why?
You know, I was only trying
to rap with her about her work.
It had gotten inappropriate
and disturbing.
More disturbing than --
Than, uh, those guys?
She would cover page after page
with these bizarre cryptic symbols.
And then there were the drawings...
Detailed images of killings,
gory, primitive.
She would depict herself in
the middle of them, participating.
Symbols?
What kind of symbols?
Uh, anything like this?
Yeah. Yeah, I think that
might have been one of them.
- You know where tracy is now?
- I would imagine her apartment.
- Her apartment?
- Yeah.
She got here about a year ago alone,
as I understood it,
as an emancipated teen.
God only knows what
her parents were like.
So?
Tracy was nowhere I could find.
Any luck with her friends?
Luck is not our style.
Friends don't know where she is.
It's like the bitch hopped a broom.
She could be making the
third sacrifice any time.
Yes, thank you, sam.
Trick or treat.
This is a motel.
So?
So we don't have any candy.
- No, we have a ton in the, uh --
- We did, but it's gone.
Sorry, kid, we can't help you.
I want candy.
Well, I think you've had enough.
Who are you?!
Sam, sam, wait!
It's castiel...
The angel.
Him, I don't know.
Hello, sam.
Oh, my god.
Er, uh, I didn't mean to --
Sorry.
It's an honor.
Really,
I-I've heard a lot about you.
And i, you.
Sam winchester --
The boy with the demon blood.
Glad to hear you've ceased
your extracurricular activities.
Let's keep it that way.
Yeah, okay, chuckles.
- Who's your friend?
- This raising of samhain --
Have you stopped it?
Why?
Dean, have you located the witch?
- Yes, we've located the witch.
- And is the witch dead?
- No, but...
- We know who it is.
Apparently,
the witch knows who you are, too.
This was inside
the wall of your room.
If we hadn't found it,
surely one or both of you would be dead.
Do you know where the witch is now?
- We're working on it.
- That's unfortunate.
What do you care?
The raising of samhain
is one of the 66 seals.
So this is about your buddy lucifer.
Lucifer is no friend of ours.
It's just an expression.
Lucifer cannot rise.
The breaking of the seal
must be prevented at all costs.
Okay. Great. Now that you're here, why
don't you tell us where the witch is?
- We'll gank her, everybody goes home.
- We are not omniscient.
This witch is very powerful.
She's cloaked, even to our methods.
Okay, well,
we already know who she is.
- So, if we work together --
- Enough of this.
Who are you, and why should I care?
This is uriel.
He's what you might call...
A specialist.
What kind of a specialist?
What are you gonna do?
You -- both of you,
you need to leave this town immediately.
Why?
Because we're about to destroy it.
So this is your plan, you're
gonna smack the whole freakin' town.
We're out of time.
This witch has to die.
The seal must be saved.
- There are a thousand people here.
- 1,214.
And you're willing to kill them all?
This isn't the first time I've...
Purified a city.
Look, I understand
this is regrettable.
- Regrettable?
- We have to hold the line.
Too many seals have broken already.
So you screwed the pooch on some seals,
and now this town has to pay the price?
It's the lives of 1,000
against the lives of 6 billion.
- There's a bigger picture here.
- Right...
'cause, uh,
you're bigger-picture kind of guys.
Lucifer cannot rise.
He does, and hell rises with him.
Is that something that
you're willing to risk?
We'll stop this witch
before she summons anyone.
Your seal won't be broken,
and no one has to die.
We're wasting time
with these mud monkeys.
I'm sorry.
- But we have our orders.
- No, you can't do this.
You -- you're angels.
I mean, aren't you supposed to --
You're supposed to show mercy.
Says who?
We have no choice.
Of course you have a choice.
I mean, come on, what, you've never...
Never questioned a crap order?
What are you both,
just a couple of hammers?
Look, even if you
can't understand it,
have faith the plan is just.
- How can you even say that?
- Because it comes from heaven.
That makes it just.
It must be nice
to be so sure of yourselves.
Tell me something.
When your father gave you an order,
didn't you obey?
Sorry, boys,
it looks like the plans have changed.
You think you can stop us?
No.
But if you're gonna
smite this whole town...
Then you're gonna have to smite
us with it because we are not leaving.
You went to the trouble
of busting me out of hell.
I figure I'm worth something
to the man upstairs.
You want to waste me?
Go ahead.
See how he digs that.
I will drag you out of here myself.
Yeah, but you'll have to kill me.
Then we're back to the same problem.
I mean, come on.
You're gonna wipe out a
whole town for one little witch?
Sounds to me like you're
compensating for something.
We can do this.
We will find that witch.
We will stop the summoning.
- Castiel, I will not let these --
- Enough.
I suggest you move quickly.
Astronaut!
What?
Nothing.
I thought they'd be different.
- Who, the angels?
- Yeah.
Well, I tried to tell you.
I just --
I mean, I thought
they'd be righteous.
Well, they are righteous.
I mean, that's kind of the problem.
Of course, there's nothing
more dangerous than some a-hole
who thinks he's on a holy mission.
But, I mean, this is god and heaven?
This is what I've been praying to?
Look, man, I know you're into
the whole god thing
and jesus on a tortilla
and stuff like that.
But just because there's
a couple of bad apples
doesn't mean the
whole barrel is rotten.
I mean, for all we know,
god hates these jerks.
Don't give up on the
stuff is all I'm saying.
Babe ruth was a dick,
but baseball's still a beautiful game.
Are you gonna figure out
a way to find this witch,
or are you just gonna sit there
fingering your bone?
You know how much heat it would
take to char a bone like this, dean?
No.
A lot.
I mean, more than a
fire or some kitchen oven.
Okay, betty crocker,
what does that mean?
It means we make a stop.
So, tracy used a
kiln to char the bone?
What's the big deal?
That hex bag turned up in
our room not after we talked to tracy...
After we talked to the teacher.
Oh, my god.
Those are all from children.
I'm guessing he's not
saving them for the dog.
The decision's been made.
By a mud monkey.
You shouldn't call them that.
Oh, That's what they are --
Savages, just plumbing on two legs.
You're close to blasphemy.
There's a reason we
were sent to save him.
He has potential.
He may succeed here.
At any rate...
It's out of our hands.
It doesn't have to be.
And what would you suggest?
That we drag dean winchester
out of here,
then we blow this insignificant
pinprick off the map.
You know our true orders.
Are you prepared to disobey?
Thank you.
He was gonna kill me.
Ugh, that sick son of a bitch.
I mean, did you
see what he was doing?
Did you hear him...
How sloppy his incantation was?
My brother always was a little dim.
He was gonna make
me the final sacrifice.
His idea.
But now,
that honor goes to him.
Our master has returned.
This spellwork's a two-man job,
you understand?
So for 600 years, I had to
deal with that pompous son of a bitch.
Planning, preparing --
Unbearable.
The whole time,
I wanted to rip his face off.
And...
... you get him with a gun.
Oh, I love that.
You know, back in the day,
this was the one night you kept
your children inside.
Well, tonight,
you'll all see what halloween really is.
What -- what are you doing?
Just follow my lead.
My love.
You've aged.
This face...
I can't fool you.
Your beauty is beyond time.
Whore.
What the hell was that?
Halloween lore.
People used to wear masks to
hide from him,
so I gave it a shot.
You gave it a shot?
How are we gonna find this mook?
Where would you go to raise
all the dark forces of the night?
- A cemetery.
- Yeah.
- So, this demon's pretty powerful.
It might take more
than the usual weapons.
Sam, no.
You're not using your psychic whatever.
But --
Don't even think about it.
Ruby's knife is enough.
- Why?
- Because the angel said so, for one.
- You said they were fanatics.
- they happen to be right about this
I don't know. Doesn't seem
they're right about much.
- Forget the angels, okay?
- You said yourself, these powers --
It's like playing with fire.
Please.
Dude, i'm tripping balls.
Yo, shh.
Be quiet. It's the cops.
Mr. Harding?
I mean... don?
Uh, don, you, uh --
You locked us in.
Help them.
- Dude, you're not going off alone.
- Do it.
Stand back!
Come on, come on, get out!
Move!
Bring it on, stinky.
Yeah.
That demon-ray-gun stuff...
Doesn't work on me.
Zombie-ghost orgy, huh?
Well, that's it.
I'm torching everybody.
Tomorrow is november 2nd.
That's an anniversary
for you, right?
What are you doing here?
It's the day azazel
killed your mother,
and 22 years later,
your girlfriend, too.
It must be difficult to bear,
yet you brazenly use
the power he gave you,
his profane blood pumping
through your veins.
Excuse me?
You were told not
to use your abilities.
What was I supposed to do?
That demon would have killed me
and my brother and everyone.
You were told
not to.
If samhain had gotten
loose in this town --
Been warned twice now.
You know,
my brother was right about you.
You are dicks.
The only reason you're still alive,
Sam winchester,
is because you've been useful.
The moment that ceases to be true,
the second you become more trouble
than you're worth,
one word... One...
And I will turn you to dust.
As for your brother,
tell him that maybe he should
climb off that high horse of his.
Ask dean...
What he remembers from hell.
Let me guess.
You're here for the "i told you so."
No.
Well, good,
'cause I'm really not that interested.
I am not here to judge you, dean.
Then why are you here?
Our orders --
I've had enough of these
orders of yours.
Our orders...
Were not to stop the
summoning of samhain.
They were to do whatever
you told us to do.
Your orders were
to follow my orders?
It was a test...
To see how you would
perform under...
Battlefield conditions,
you might say.
It was a witch...
Not the tet offensive.
So, i, uh, failed your test, huh?
I get it.
But you know what?
If you were to waive that...
That magic
time-traveling wand of yours
and we had to do it all over again,
i'd make the same call...
'cause, see, I don't know what's gonna
happen when these seals are broken.
Hell, I don't know what's
gonna happen tomorrow.
But what I do know
is is that this here --
These kids,
the swings, the trees,
all of it...
Is still here because
of my brother and me.
You misunderstand me, dean.
I'm not like you think.
I was praying that you
would choose to save the town.
You were?
These people --
They're all my father's creations.
They're works of art.
And yet...
Even though you stopped samhain,
the seal was broken,
and we are one step closer
to hell on earth for all creation.
And that's not an expression, dean.
It's literal.
You of all people should...
Appreciate what that means.
I'll tell you something if
you promise not to tell another soul.
Okay.
I'm not, uh...
A hammer, as you say.
I have questions.
I...
I have doubts.
I don't know what is right
and what is wrong anymore...
And whether you
passed or failed here.
But in the coming months,
you will he more decisions to make.
I don't envy the weight
that's on your shoulders, dean.
I truly don't.