Good night, Love.
Sweet dreams, Sam.
Sammy, you're my favourite.
Does this mean I
have demon blood in me?
It's you.
Mary?
The goal in life has been
searching for this demon.
That thing killed Jess,
that thing killed mum.
- I'm sorry
- For what?
- Who are you?
- Castiello,
I'm the one who gripped you
tight and raised you from perdition.
- I mean, what are you?
- I'm an angel of the Lord.
Samuel Colt made a special gun,
this gun can kill anything.
Why would an angel rescue me from Hell?
Because God commanded it.
Because we have work for you.
Ready?
Definitely.
Hello, dean.
And what were you dreaming about?
You get your freak on
by watching other people sleep?
What do you want?
Listen to me.
You have to stop it.
Stop what?
Move it, buddy.
- You can't sleep here.
- Okay.
- Sleep where?
- Anywhere but here.
Perfect.
Where the hell am i?
Jay bird's diner.
Yeah, thanks.
I mean, uh, city and state.
Lawrence, Kansas.
Lawrence.
Are you okay, buddy?
Tough night.
Hey, uh, coffee here, reg.
Can you tell me where I can get
reception on this thing?
The U. S. S Enterprise?
Thanks.
Nice threads.
You know sonny and cher broke up, right?
Sonny and cher broke up?
Hey, winchester!
Son of a bitch!
How you doin', corporal?
- Hey, Mr. D.
- I heard you were back.
Yeah, a little while now.
Good to have you home,
john -- damn good.
- Dad?
- Say hello to your old man for me.
You got it, Mr. D.
Do we know each other?
I guess not.
Take it easy, pal.
Synchro : IceFre@k
www.seriessub.com
What is this?
- What does it look like?
- Is it real?
Very.
Okay, so, what, angels got
their hands on some deloreans?
How did I get here?
Time is fluid, dean.
It's not easy,
but we can bend it on occasion.
Bend it back.
Or tell me what the hell I'm doing here.
I told you.
You have to stop it.
Stop what? Huh?
What, is there something
nasty after my dad?
Come on.
What, are you allergic to straight
answers, you son of a bitch?!
Fine young man like
yourself just starting out.
How about I take off another $250?
Let's do it.
I'll get the paperwork.
That's not the one you want.
You following me?
No, no.
I was just passing by.
I never got to thank you
for that cup of coffee this morning.
- I was a little out of it.
- More than a little.
Let me repay the favor.
This is the car you want.
Oh, yeah? You know something about cars?
Yeah.
Yeah, my dad taught
me everything I know.
And this --
This is a great car.
327 four-barrel, 275 horses.
A little tlc, this thing is cherry.
You know, man...
You're right.
What are you buying that thing for?
Kind of promised someone I would.
Over a'67 chevy?
I mean, come on.
This is the car of a lifetime.
Trust me, this thing's still
gonna be badass when it's 40.
John winchester.
Thanks.
Dean van halen.
And thank you.
I was in pretty rough
shape this morning, huh?
No kidding.
I've been hung over before, but,
I was getting chills in that diner.
You didn't feel any of
those cold spots, did you?
Nope.
I swore I smelled something weird,
too, you know?
Like rotten eggs.
You didn't happen to smell any sulfur,
by chance?
- No.
Have there been any
cattle mutilations in town?
Okay, mister, stop it.
Yeah.
If only I knew what to stop.
Listen, uh...
Watch out for yourself, okay?
Yeah. Sure.
So?
I'll take this one.
What's this?
My car.
What happened to the van?
Mary, this is better than the van.
It's got a 327, a 4-barrel carburetor.
Mom.
Sammy, wherever you are...
Mom is a babe.
I'm going to hell.
Again.
I should just talk to him.
My dad's being my dad, john.
It's not you.
How is it not me?
He's been like this for how many years?
He's just protective over me,
that's all.
He's doesn't want me to...
Hook up with a mechanic
from a family of mechanics?
No.
I love you for exactly what you are.
I'll be right back.
Why are you following us?
Are you crazy?
You've been trailing us since my house.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, really?
- Okay, how about we talk about this?
- Let me go!
Are you a hunter?
- See you later.
- If you're lucky.
Dean, right?
I'm not sure you should come in.
You can trust me, I mean come on,
we're all hunters, right?
I mean, we're...
practically family.
The thing is,
my dad, he's a little, um...
Oh, I got to meet him.
You've heard of him?
Clearly, not enough.
So, you're a hunter?
Tell me something, Mr. Hunter,
You kill vampires with
wooden stakes or silver?
Neither.
You cut their heads off.
- So, do I pass your test?
- Yep.
- Now get out of my house.
- Dad!
I don't trust other hunters, Dean.
- Don't want their help.
- Don't want them around my family.
Knock it off, samuel.
He's a hunter.
Who passed your little pop quiz,
and now i'm inviting him to dinner.
- You hungry?
- Starving.
Good.
I'm deanna.
You've met my husband, samuel.
Now wash up.
Samuel and... deanna?
Really?
First time in lawrence, dean?
Been a while.
Things sure have changed...
I think.
You working a job?
- Yeah, maybe.
- What's that mean?
It means I don't trust
other hunters either, samuel.
So, why were you following me and john?
I thought something was
after your -- your boyfriend.
But, um, I don't think that anymore.
John winchester mixing
it up with spirits.
Can you imagine?
I saw that.
- What?
- That sour-lemon look.
Now, hold on.
John's a really, really nice...
... naive civilian.
So, what, would you rather
me be with a guy like this?
What? No, no.
Mary, of course not.
It's just that I --
That's enough, both of you.
We have company.
So, what about you, sam?
You, uh, working a job?
Might be.
He's working a job
on the whitshire farm.
Whitshire... why does
that name sound familiar to me?
It's been all over the papers.
Tom whitshire.
- Got tangled up in a combine.
- That kind of thing happens.
Except why was he on it in the
first place when his crops are all dead?
- Demonic omens?
- That's what I got to find out.
What about the rest of the town?
Did you find anything on the web?
Of... information
that you have assembled?
Electrical storms, maybe.
The weather service graphs
should be here on friday.
By mail?
No, we hired a jetliner
to fly them to us overnight.
You know, it sounds to me like
we might be hunting the same thing.
You know, if we go in there in numbers,
we'll take care of this real quick.
What part of "we work alone"
do you not understand, son?
- And I'm here because...
- Family business, mary.
Family.
What, you'd rather be waving
pom-poms at a bunch of dumb jocks?
Uh, where you going?
To do the job, dad.
Father.
I see you beat me here.
The lord is funny that way.
Beth whitshire...
This is my associate,
our senior senior priest,
Father Cheney.
Please accept our deepest condolences
on behalf of the county diocese.
Thank you.
Miss whitshire was just telling me
all about tom
and how normal and ordinary things
were on the day before his death.
I see.
So you didn't notice
anything unusual, ma'am?
You mean like my husband's
guts fertilizing the back 40?
Excuse me.
Charlie, would you like to tell
the father here what you just told me?
Dad drank sometimes.
Sometimes he got rough with mom.
And that's when the stranger came?
I just thought he was some
bible-thumper, like you-all.
He showed up about a week ago.
Saying what?
Did I want the beatings to stop?
I just thought he was crazy.
I didn't think...
And the next thing I know, dad's dead.
Am I going to jail?
You didn't do this, charlie.
Did the stranger want
something in return?
- He didn't want anything.
- Come on, chuck.
He wasn't just handing out freebies,
was he?
He did say something about coming
a-calling 10 years from now
- and maybe he'd want something then.
- Something like what?
I don't know, okay?
Look, I told you he was nuts.
What do you think?
I think he just pimped his soul
to a demon, and he doesn't even know it.
Charlie, do you remember
what the stranger looked like?
Yeah, uh...
He's about 5'10"...
White.
- He was kind of normal-looking, really.
- Anything else?
- There was one thing.
- What?
It's just, the light hit
his eyes in a weird way, and...
- For a moment, I could have sworn --
- What, that they were black?
Or red, maybe?
No.
They were yellow.
Pale yellow.
What do you say we just slow
down and talk this thing through?
- There's nothing to talk about.
- Except there's a demon
and none of us has ever heard
of demon with yellow eyes.
Yeah, well, ihave.
This thing killed my family.
- Just calm down, son.
- You don't get it, do you?
You are in danger.
We are all in danger.
You need to
get yourself someplace safe.
- Not til we know what we deal with.
- Sam's right...
It could be a demon, it could
be a shapeshifter, any number of things.
I know what this thing is!
And I'm gonna kill it.
That's all the talking I need to do.
You're gonna kill a demon?
How?
There's a hunter named Daniel Elkins.
He lives in colorado.
He has colt's gun.
The colt.
Yeah, I heard about the colt.
I used to tell it to
mary as a bedtime story.
Well, it's real.
All right, say that it is.
You got some kind of a crystal ball
telling you where this demon's gonna be?
Yeah, maybe I do.
- What's this?
- It's a list.
Of what?
My dad wrote down anyone he thought
ever came in contact
with the yellow-eyed demon.
Who, where, and when.
Why?
'cause the more he could learn
about the son of a bitch,
the more he could figure out
why it killed my mom.
Look.
Whitshire farm.
I told you that name sounded familiar.
Whitshire farms --
That was two days ago.
How the hell is that on your dad's list?
My dad could see the future.
Look at this -- says he's
gonna hit here tomorrow night.
- Liddy walsh?
- Haleyville.
That's close.
Yeah, it's about 3 miles, but...
I know you guys think I'm crazy.
You seem like a really nice kid,
dean, but, yeah, you're crazy.
Yeah, maybe.
But I know where
this bastard's gonna be.
And I'm gonna stop it...
Once and for all.
I'm shoving off.
I just wanted to say "bye."
Really?
So soon?
Yeah, I have a job to do.
Hey, I wanted to tell you,
you know, for what it's worth, um...
It doesn't matter what your dad thinks.
I like that john kid.
You do?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think you two are meant to be.
- Hell, i'm depending on it.
- What?
Nothing.
Can I ask you a question?
What's he like?
John?
Why do you ask?
Just curious.
I don't know.
He's sweet...
Kind.
Even after the war,
after everything,
he still believes in
"happily ever after," you know?
He's everything a hunterisn't.
No offense.
No, none taken.
Can I tell you something?
He's gonna ask me to marry him.
Tomorrow, I think.
- Yeah?
- Oh, dad's gonna explode.
But I don't care.
I'll run away if I have to.
I just...
I love john.
And...
And what?
I want to get out.
This job, this...
life.
I hate it.
I want a family.
I want to be safe.
You know,
the worst thing I can think of...
The very worst thing...
Is for my children to
be raised into this, like I was.
Well, I won't let it happen.
Yeah.
You okay?
No, I'm -- I'm fine.
Hey, m--
Uh, mary...
Can I tell you something?
Sure.
Even if this sounds really weird,
will you promise me
that you will remember?
Okay.
On november 2, 1983...
... don't get out of bed.
No matter what you
hear or what you see...
promise me you won't get out of bed.
Okay.
So, what, god's my co-pilot?
Is that it?
Oh, you're a regular chatty cathy.
Tell me something --
Sam would have wanted in on this.
Why not bring him back?
You had to do this alone, dean.
And you don't care that he's tearing
up the future looking for me right now?
Sam's not looking for you.
All right, if I do this,
then the family curse breaks, right?
Mom and dad live happily ever after,
and sam and I grow up
playing little league and chasing tail?
You realize if you do alter the future,
your father, you, sam, you'll never
become hunters.
And all those people you saved,
they'll die.
I realize.
And you don't care?
Oh, I care.
I care a lot.
But these are my parents.
I'm not gonna let them die again.
I can't.
Not if I can stop it.
Hold it right there, friend.
Drop the gun.
Be on your way.
Can't do it, daniel.
Who the hell are you?
A hunter, just like yourself.
- "Thief" is more like it.
- I need it for a few days.
Not happening, mister.
Look, I have a chance
to save my family's lives.
My family.
But I need this gun to do it.
So if you want to stop me, kill me.
There's some hunters
in lawrence
The Campbells.
Never heard of them.
That's where she'll be.
Dean say where he was going?
He said he was gonna kill a demon.
Kill a demon?
- That's impossible.
- Yep.
Where?
- Oh, I don't know...
- Over in Haleyville.
Walshes, maybe.
Oh, wait --
Not liddy walsh?
Well, yeah, I- I think so.
Dad, she's a friend of mine!
We got to help her.
- What's wrong?
- I'll be in the car.
She wants to hunt,
she doesn't want to hunt.
Is this some female
"time of month" thing?
What?
I'm sorry, liddy.
It's metastasized.
- Where?
- His liver, his lungs.
It's time we talked about arrangements.
No, you have to do something, Dr. Brown.
There is one way --
A cure, actually.
But I'll need your help.
- What do I have to do?
- Nothing.
Just in 10 years, i'm going to
come to you and ask for something then.
- What?
- Nothing you'll miss.
Hold that thought.
You son of a bitch.
Well, hello, there.
Where the hell have
they been hiding you?
I like you.
You got a lot of spunk.
You let her go!
Where'd you get that gun?
- Mary, what else did he say to you?
- I told you...
Just that he liked me.
What did he mean by that?
- Liddy's a strong kid.
- She'll be fine.
- Are you okay?
- No, dad, i'm pretty far from okay.
Can we go?
- Nice job in there.
- I missed the shot.
Take the compliment, son.
I'm saying that I was wrong about you.
We need to talk alone.
We have to kill this thing now,
or Mary dies.
- What?
- How do you know that?
- I just do, okay?
- When?
Maybe today, probably years from now,
but it's happening. Trust me.
So, what, are you some
kind of a psychic now, too?
No.
All right, listen to me.
Now, this is gonna sound a little...
Actually, it's gonna sound massively,
massively crazy.
Okay.
- Mary is my mother.
- Excuse me?
And I am your grandson.
- I know what I'm talking about.
- You want to run that by me again, son?
My real name is dean winchester.
I was born january 24, 1979.
My parents are mary and john winchester.
I don't have to listen to this.
Mary gets killed by
a yellow-eyed demon in 1983.
Now, I think that this,
what happened tonight,
I think this is the moment
that he caught her scent.
Now, if we don't catch this thing
now and kill it and it gets away...
Then mary dies.
So I'm asking you...
Please.
Y- you okay?
You promised you'd take me away.
Of course I did.
Do it now.
How did I know about the colt, huh?
How did I know about the yellow-eyed
demon or where it would be?
I'm not making this up, samuel.
Every bone in my body is aching
to put you six feet under, but...
There's something about you --
I can't shake it.
Now, I may be crazier than you,
son, but I believe you.
Thank you.
How do we find this bastard?
Right here -- the list.
And with the colt?
Let me see it.
Sorry.
I don't let anybody hold it.
I'm your grandfather.
Nothing personal.
Sure it is.
Especially when it's
me you're trying to kill.
Future boy, huh?
I only know one thing that's got
the juice to swing something like that.
You must have friends in high places.
So, I kill your mommy?
That's why you came all
this way to see little ol'me?
Oh, I came here to kill you.
Wait a minute.
If that slug marries your mommy,
are you --
Are you one of my psychic kids?
No.
Not you.
Maybe you got a sis.
Or a bro.
That's terrific.
That means it all worked out.
After all, it's why I'm here.
- So that's what this is about...
- These deals you're making.
You don't want these people's souls.
No.
I just want their children.
I'm here to choose the perfect parents,
like your mommy.
Why her?
Why any of them?
Because they're strong.
They're pure.
They eat their wheaties.
My own little master race.
They're ideal breeders.
Oh, get your mind out of the gutter.
No one's breeding with me.
Though Mary...
Man, I'd like to make an exception.
So far, she's my favorite.
So, why make the deals?
I need permission.
I need to be invited into their houses.
I know, I know -- the
red tape will drive you nuts.
But in 10 short years,
it'll all be worth it.
'cause you know what
i'm gonna do to your sibling?
I'm gonna stand over their crib,
and I'm gonna bleed into their mouth.
Demon blood is better than ovaltine,
vitamins, minerals.
It makes you big and strong!
For what?
So they can lead your
discount demon army?
- Is that your big plan?
- Please.
My endgame's a hell of
a lot bigger than that, kid.
Endgame?
What endgame?
Like I'm gonna tell you.
Or those angels sitting
on your shoulder.
No.
I'm gonna cover my tracks good.
You can cover whatever
the hell you want.
I'm still gonna kill you.
Right.
Now, that, i'd like to see.
Maybe not today.
But you look into my eyes,
you son of a bitch.
'cause I'm the one that kills you.
So, you're gonna save everybody.
Is that right?
Is that it?
Well, I'll tell you one
person that you're not gonna save.
Your grandpappy.
No!
I guess it's no secret
why I brought you way out here.
- John...
- I just...
just let me get through this, okay?
Okay, wait.
There's things you
don't know about me, john.
So?
I will always love you
for exactly who you are.
- What did I tell you?
- Dad!
Sir, just listen!
Ow! Dad!
Stay away from her!
- You're hurting me!
- Hey, take it easy!
No.
You killed him.
Oh, not just john, sweetie pie.
Mommy and daddy, too.
They're all dead.
No.
Yep.'fraid so.
- You're little orphan mary now.
- You son of a bitch!
Oh, sticks and stones
may break my bones.
And they won't bring
your family back either.
I'll kill you.
I swear to god.
Oh, let's not get nasty.
Now, look,
we both said some things that we regret.
Let's, uh...
kiss and make up.
I'll tell you what --
i'll arrange to have lover
boy here brought back breathing.
My parents, too?
Nope.
Sorry, doll.
That's not on the table.
Think about it.
You could be done with hunting forever.
The white picket fence,
station wagon, couple of kids.
No more monsters or fear.
I'll make sure of it.
What?
And all it costs is my soul?
Oh, no.
You can keep your soul.
I just need permission.
For what?
In 10 year I need to swing by your House
for a little something, that's all.
For... what?
Relax.
As long as I'm not interrupted,
nobody gets hurt.
I promise.
Or you can spend the rest
of your life
desperate and alone.
Mary?
It's a good deal.
So, what do you say?
No!
I couldn't stop any of it.
She still made the deal.
She still died in the nursery,
didn't she?
Don't be too hard on yourself.
You couldn't have stopped it.
What?
Destiny can't be changed, dean.
All roads lead to the same destination.
Then why'd you send me back?
For the truth.
Now you know everythingwedo.
What the hell are you talking about?
Where's sam?
We know what azazel did to your brother.
What we don't know is why --
what his endgame is.
He went to great lengths
to cover that up.
- Where's sam?
- 425 waterman.
Your brother is headed
down a dangerous road, dean.
And we're not sure where it leads.
So stop it.
Or we will.