I was on the fast track once.
Employee of the month
every month... Forever.
And then they assigned me you.
I can't close the deal on a couple
of pathetic, flannel-wearing maggots?
Everybody's laughing at me.
- We're John Winchester's sons.
- I've got brothers?
- Adam doesn't have to be cursed.
- He's a Winchester.
He's already cursed.
You're not Adam.
You've never been Adam.
You're a ghoul.
You can't kill the devil,
and you're losing faith
In yourself, your brother.
God was your last hope.
- Are you gonna do something stupid?
- Like what?
Like Michael stupid.
Whatever you're thinking of doing,
don't do it.
I have to.
Let me guess.
- Pink-slipped?
- That obvious?
Takes one to know one.
"Outsourcing."
What was your crime
against humanity?
Deal of the millennum.
Couldn't even get the one
simple "yes" I needed.
Got to nail that bottom line, right?
Hear that.
All they care
about upstairs, ain't it?
Results, results, results.
They don't know.
They're not down on the ground,
in the mud,
Nose to nose
with all you pig-filthy humans.
Am I right?
Absolutely... filthy what?
I mean, whatever happened
to personal loyalty?
How long have I worked
for these guys?
Five millennia?
Six?
- Seems like it, don't it?
- Damn straight, it does.
Two more.
- Zach.
- Stuart.
What are you gonna do next, Stuart?
Hell, I don't know.
Maybe something to do
with the Internet.
Yeah?
Earthquake?
No.
My boss.
Go ahead.
Get it over with.
I'm ready.
Wait
What?
Yes!
Anything. Of course.
Just... put me back in.
You won't regret it.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Back in business, boys!
= 518 =
= Supernatural Team =
Sending someone a candygram?
How'd you find me?
You're gonna kill yourself, right?
It's not too hard to figure out
the stops on the farewell tour.
How's Lisa doing, anyway?
- I'm not gonna kill myself.
- No?
So, Michael's not about
to make you his muppet?
What the hell, man?
This is how it ends?
You just... Walk out?
- Yeah, I guess.
- How could you do that?
How could I?
All you've ever done is run away!
And I was wrong
every single time I did.
Just... Please...
Not now.
Bobby is working on something.
Oh, really?
What?
You got nothing, and you know it.
You know I have to stop you.
Yeah, well, you can try.
But just remember, you're not all
hopped up on demon blood this time.
Yeah, I know.
But I brought help.
Yeah, no, this is good, really.
Eight months of turned pages
and screwed pooches.
But tonight... tonight's
when the magic happens.
You ain't helping.
Why don't you let me
get out of your hair, then?
What the hell happened to you?
Reality happened.
Nuclear's the only option
we have left.
Michael can ice the devil,
save a boatload of people.
But not all of them.
We got to think of something else.
That's easy for you to say.
But if Lucifer burns this mother down
and I could have done
something about it.
Guess what... that's on me.
You can't give up, son.
You're not my father.
And you ain't in my shoes.
What is that?
That's the round
I mean to put through my skull.
Every morning, I look at it,
And I think...
"Maybe today's the day
I flip the lights out."
But I don't do it.
I never do it.
You know why?
Because I promised you
I wouldn't give up!
Cass, you okay?
No.
What's wrong?
Something's happening.
Where?
I'm gonna get a beer.
Do you mind?
Help.
Boys!
Who is it?
That's our brother.
Wait a minute.
Your brother? Adam?
Cass, what the hell?
Angels.
Angels? Why?
I know one thing for sure.
We need to hide him now.
Where am I?
It's okay.
- Just relax. You're safe.
- Who the hell are you?
You're gonna find this a little...
A lot crazy, but we're
actually your brothers.
It's the truth.
John Winchester was our father, too.
- See, I'm Sam.
- And I'm sure that's Dean.
I know who you are.
- How?
- They warned me about you.
- Who did?
- The angels.
Now, where the hell is Zachariah?!
So, why don't you just
tell us everything?
Start from the beginning.
Well, I was dead and in heaven...
Except it...
kind of looked like my prom.
And I was making out with this girl.
Her name was Kristin McGee.
That sounds like heaven.
Did you get to third base?
Just... Just keep going.
These angels,
they popped out of nowhere,
and they tell me that I'm chosen.
- For what?
- To save the world.
How you gonna do that?
Me and some archangel
are gonna kill the devil.
- What archangel?
- Michael.
I'm his sword or vessel or something.
I don't know.
That's insane.
Not necessarily.
How do you mean?
Maybe they're moving
on from you, Dean.
That doesn't make sense.
He's John Winchester's bloodline,
Sam's brother.
- It's not perfect, but it's possible.
- You got to be kidding me.
- Why would they do this?
- Maybe they're desperate.
Maybey've wrongly assumed
Dean would be brave enough
to withstand them.
- You know what? Blow me, Cass.
- Look. No way.
After everything that's happened.
All that crap about destiny,
suddenly the angels have a plan "b"?
Does that smell right to anybody?
You know, tis has been
a really moving family reunion.
- But, I got a thing, so...
- Whoa, no. Sit down.
Just listen, okay?
Please.
It's unbelievable.
Now, Adam...
The angels are lying to you.
They're full of crap.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Really? Why not?
'cause they're angels.
They tell you they were gonna
roast half the planet?
They said the fight
might get pretty hairy
but it is the devil, right?
So, we got to stop him.
Yeah, but there's another way.
Great. What is it?
We're working on the power of love.
- How's that going?
- Not good.
Look, Adam...
You don't know me from a hole
in the wall, I know,
but I'm begging you.
Please, just trust me.
Give me some time.
Give me one good reason.
Because we're blood.
You got no right to say that to me.
You're still John's boy.
No, John Winchester was some guy
who took me to a baseball game
once a year.
I didn't have a dad.
So, we may be blood,
but we are not family.
My mom is my family,
and if I do my job,
I get to see her again.
So, no offense, but she's the one
I give a rat's ass about,
Not you.
Fair enough.
But if you have one good
memory of dad... just one...
Then you'll give us
a little more time.
Please.
Going somewhere?
Out for a beer.
Great. We got beer.
Have a seat.
Great.
You know, you pitch this whole
dewy-eyed bromance thing,
but the truh is,
I'm on lockdown, aren't I?
Adam...
You may not believe it,
but dad was trying to protect you,
keeping you from all this.
I guess the monster that ate me
didn't get that memo.
You remember that?
Oh, yeah.
Still, trust me,
the oning worse
than seeing dad once a year
was seeing him all year.
Do you know how full
of crap you are?
- What?
- Really.
You see, it was me,
and it was my mom, that's it.
She worked the graveyard shift
at the hospital.
I cooked my own dinners.
I put myself to bed.
So, you can say whatever
you want about our dad,
but the truth is,
I would have taken anything.
All right?
Look, if we had known
we had a brother...
- You didn't, so...
- ... we would have found you.
I can't change the past.
I wish I could.
- But from here on out...
- What?
We gonna hop
in the family truckster?
Pop on down to Wally world?
Tell you one thing...
Attitude like that,
you'd fit right in around here.
Cass, not for nothing,
but the last person
who looked at me like that...
I got laid.
Why don't you go keep
an eye on Adam?
Is this really necessary?
We got our hands full, Dean...
- A houseful of flight risks.
- I'm not letting him do it.
Who, Adam?
No, I'm... I'm not, either.
- No, you're not getting me.
- No, I "get" you perfectly.
But I'm not
letting you do it, either.
That kid's not
taking a bullet for me.
- Dean...
- I'm serious.
Think abouw many people
we've gotten killed, Sam.
Mom, dad...
Jess, jo, Ellen.
Should I keep going?
It's not like we pulled the trigger.
We might as well have.
I'm tired, man.
I'm tired of fighting
who I'm supposed to be.
Do you think maybe you could
take a half a second
and stop trying to sacrifice
yourself for a change?
Maybe we could actually
stick together?
- I don't think so.
- Why not?
Dean, seriously.
Tell me.
I want to know.
I just...
I don't believe.
In what?
In you.
I mean, I don't...
I don't know whether
it's gonna be demon blood
or some other demon chick
or what, but...
I do know they're gonna
find a way to turn you.
So, you're saying
I'm not strong enough.
You're angry, you're self-righteous.
Lucifer's gonna wear you
to the prom, man.
- It's just a matter of time.
- Don't say that to me.
Not you...
Of all people.
I don't want to.
But it's the truth.
And when Satan takes you over,
There's got to be
somebody there to fight him,
and it ain't gonna be that kid.
So, it's got to be me.
How's he doing?
How you doing?
Where's Cass?
Blown to Oz.
Look, I'll get Dean.
He couldn't have gone too far.
- Watch Adam.
- How?
He's got a slight height advantage.
Then cuff him to your chair.
I don't know. Just watch him.
Your mom's not coming, you know.
This is the park where your mom
took you on her day off, right?
She's not coming. Not yet.
But she will... Soon.
You're Zachariah, right?
I am.
You weren't
where you were supposed to be, kid.
- I know.
- Can't quite zero in on you, either.
So, let me take a wild guess.
You're with Sam and Dean?
Didn't we tell you about them?
So, you know you can't trust them?
You know Sam and Dean Winchester
are psychotically, irrationally,
erotically
codependent on each other?
I don't know.
They said a few things about you.
Really?
Trust me, when the heat gets hot,
theywon't give a flying crap
about you.
They'd rather save each other's
sweet bacon than save the planet.
They're not your family.
Understand?
Now...
You want to see your mom again
or not?
The end is nigh!
The apocalypse is upon us!
The angels talk to me,
and they asked me to talk to you!
The apocalypse...
- I'm Dean Winchester. Know who I am?
- Dear God!
I'll take that as a yes.
I need you to pray to your buddies
and let them know I'm here.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name.
You pray too loud.
- What, are you crazy?
- I rebelled for this?
So that you could surrender to them?
Cass! Please!
I gave everything for you.
And this is what you give to me!
Do it.
Just do it!
Bobby, what do you mean,
Adam is gone?
- Should I say it in Spanish?
- He's gone how?
- What the hell, Bobby?
- Watch your tone, boy.
He was right in front of me,
and he disappeared into thin air.
Because the angels took him.
- What the hell happened to him?
- Me.
What do you mean,
the angels took Adam?
You branded his ribs, didn't you?
Yes. Adam must have tipped them.
- How?
- I don't know.
- Maybe in a dream.
- Well, where would they have taken him?
I see you and your brother
share the same refined palate.
We ready?
For what?
What do you mean? For Michael.
About that...
Look, this is never easy,
but I'm afraid...
We've had to terminate your position
at this time.
- Excuse me?
- Don't get me wrong,
you've been a hell of a sport...
Good stuff.
But the thing is, you're not so much
the "chosen one" as you are...
A clammy scrap of bait.
What about the stuff that you said?
I'm supposed to fight the devil.
If it's any consolation,
you happen to be the illegitimate half
brother of the guy we do care about.
That's not bad, is it?
So, you lied...
- About everything.
- We didn't lie.
We just avoided certain truths
to manipulate you.
You son of a bitch.
How do you think I feel?
I got to put up
with that dumb look on your face!
Kid, we didn't have a choice.
The Winchesters got one blind spot,
and it's family.
See, Sam and Dean, they're gonna
put aside their differences,
they're gonna come get you,
and that's gonna put Dean right...
Here.
Where I need him.
This is the night, kid!
Our night.
Michael's seen it.
The tumblers
finally click into place,
and it's all because of you.
- And me. But who's keeping score?
- I'm not gonna let you do this.
Cool your jets, Corky. Sit down.
We're doing it together.
Plus, you still get your severance.
You still get to see your mom, okay?
Why should I believe you?
You know what?
I keep hearing this.
But what I wanna be hearing is this.
That's better.
How you feeling?
Word to the wise...
Don't piss off the nerd angels.
So, how's it going?
Adam's gone.
- The angels have him.
- Where?
- The room where they took you.
- You sure?
- Cass did a recon.
- And?
The place is crawling with mooks.
Pretty much a no-shot-in-hell,
hail-Mary kind of thing.
So the usual.
What are you gonna do?
For starters...
I'm bringing you with.
Excuse me?
There are too many of them.
We can't do it alone,
and you're pretty much
the only game in town.
Isn't that a bad idea?
Cass and Bobby think so.
I'm not so sure.
Well, they're right.
Because either it's a trap
to get me there, to make me say yes,
or it's not a trap
and I'm gonna say yes anyway.
And I will.
I'll do it... Fair warning.
No, you won't.
When push shoves,
you'll make the right call.
You know, if tables were turned...
I'd let you rot in here.
Hell, I have let you rot in here.
I guess i'm not that smart.
I don't get it.
Sam, why are you doing this?
Because...
You're still my big brother.
- Where the hell are we?
- Van Nuys, California.
- Where's the beautiful room?
- In there.
The beautiful room is in an abandoned
muffler factory in Van Nuys?
- Where'd you think it was?
- I don't know. Jupiter?
A blade of grass? Not Van Nuys.
Why don't you just grab Adam
and shazam the hell out of there?
Because there are at least
five angels in there.
- So? You're fast.
- They're faster.
I'll clear them out.
You two grab the boy.
- This is our only chance.
- You're gonna take on five angels?
Yes.
- Isn't that suicide?
- Maybe it is.
But then
I won't have to watch you fail.
I'm sorry, Dean.
I don't have the same faith in you
that Sam does.
What are you gonna do with that?
What are you waiting for?
Come on.
You came for me.
- You're family.
- Dean, it's a trap.
I figured.
Did you really think
it would be that easy?
Did you?
You know what I've learned
from this experience, Dean?
Patience.
- Let him go, you son of a bitch.
- I thought I was downsized for sure,
And for us, a firing...
Pretty damn literal.
But I should have trusted
the boss man.
It's all playing out like he said...
You, me, your hemorrhaging brothers.
You're finally ready.
You know
there's never been a choice.
Stop it. Stop it right now!
In exchange for what?
Damn it, Zachariah.
Stop it, please.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry. What was that?
Okay, yes.
The answer is yes.
Do you hear me?
Call Michael down, you bastard!
- How do I know you're not lying?
- Do I look like I'm lying?
He's coming.
Of course, I have a few conditions.
A few people whose safety
you have to guarantee before I say yes.
- Sure, fine. Make a list.
- But most of all...
Michael can't have me
until he disintegrates you.
- What did you say?
- I said...
Before Michael gets one piece
of this sweet ass...
He has to turn you
into a piece of charcoal.
- You think Michael's gonna go for that?
- Who's more important to him now?
You...
Or me?
You listen to me.
You are nothing but a maggot
inside a worm's ass.
Do you know who I am...
After I deliver you to Michael?
Expendable.
- Michael's not gonna kill me.
- Maybe not.
But I am.
Can you walk?
Come on, move it!
Dean! Help!
Hold on! We'll get you out!
You think Adam's okay?
Doubt it.
Cass either. But we'll get 'em.
So?
So what?
I saw your eyes.
You were rockin' the yes back there.
So, what changed your mind?
Honestly?
The damndest thing.
I mean, the world's ending,
the walls are coming down on us,
and I look over to you
and all I can think about is,
"this stupid son of a bitch
brought me here."
I just didn't want to let you down.
You didn't.
You almost did.
But you didn't.
- I owe you an apology.
- No, man. No, you don't.
Let me say this.
I don't know if it's being a big brother
or what,
but to me you've always been this
snot-nosed kid
I've had to keep
on the straight and narrow.
We both know that's not you anymore.
I mean, hell, if you're grown-up enough
to find faith in me...
The least I can do
is return the favor.
So, screw destiny
right in the face.
I say we take the fight to them,
do it our way.
Sounds good.