Lilith is trying to break the 66 seals
to free lucifer from hell.
Lucifer will bring the apocalypse.
- Sam, I'm sorry.
- For what?
Does this mean I have
demon blood in me?
I don't want to be
the freak for once, Dean.
I want to be normal.
Your brother is headed
down a dangerous road, Dean.
Do you even know how far off
the reservation you've gone?
How far from normal, fromhuman?
If I didn't know you,
I would want to hunt you.
You want to know
if I know about the demon blood.
You didn't tell Dean?
Where the hell are you, Ruby?
I'm all out. Call me. I need more.
This is for your own good.
Guys?
Guys, this isn't funny!
- Let me out. This is not funny.
- Damn straight.
Come on, this is crazy.
Not until you dry out.
Look, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
Open the door.
You don't have to apologize.
It's not your fault.
It's not your fault that you
lied to me over and over again.
I get it now.
You couldn't help it.
- I'm not some junkie!
- Really?
I guess I've just imagined how
strung out you've been lately.
You're actually trying
to twist this into some kind
of ridiculous drug intervention?
- If it smells like a duck.
- I'm not drinking
the demon blood forkicks.
I'm getting strong
enough to kill Lilith.
- Strong?
- Yeah.
It's about as far away
from strong as you can get.
Try weak. Try desperate.
Pathetic.
Killing Lilith is what matters.
Or are you so busy being
self-righteous you forgot about her?
Lilith's gonna die.
Bobby and I will kill her.
- But not with you.
- You're not serious.
Congrats, Sammy.
You just bought yourself
a benchwarmer seat to the apocalypse.
Dean. No, wait.
Come back here!
Dean!
Let me out of here!
Guys! Get down here!
Something's coming!
Hello, Sam.
It's a pleasure to see you again.
And looks like I have
you all to myself here.
Goodness.
How will we pass the time?
No, no, don't.
Alastair...
Please!
Please.
So polite all of a sudden.
Very nice.
I appreciate that.
No, no. Alastair.
Please! Please!
How long is this gonna go on?
Here, let me look it up
in my demon-detox manual.
Oh, wait.
No one ever wrote one.
No telling how long it'll take.
Hell, or if Sam will
even live through it.
Hello?
Suck dirt and die, Rufus.
You call me again, i'll kill you.
- What's up with Rufus?
- He knows.
I'm busy, you sumbitch.
This better be important.
The answer's "yes."
You're hallucinating.
That's right. It's me.
Or, I mean, it's you.
I'm losing my mind.
Definitely.
- What do you want?
- An explanation.
How could you do this to me?
- I thought we were gonna be normal.
- I tried. I did.
It didn't pan out that way.
Sorry, kid.
"Sorry, kid"?
That's what you have to say?
It's all we ever wanted.
We were so close!
You got away from dad.
You quit hunting. You were gonna
become a lawyer and get married.
- Why did you blow it?!
- Look!
They killed Jessica.
If you hadn't run off with Dean,
if you'd been there
to protect her, she'd still be alive.
I know.
Think Jess would want
you to turn into this?
She loved you.
You think she would be happy
you using her as an excuse?
I'm sorry.
I am. But life doesn't
turn out the way you thought it
would when you were 14 years old.
We were never gonna be normal.
We were never gonna get away.
Grow up.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe there's...
No escape.
After all...
How can you run from
what's inside you?
The news.
And the news ain't good.
This is what Rufus called about?
"Key west sees
10 species go extinct"?
Yep. Plus, Alaska...
15-man fishing crew,
all stricken blind...
Cause unknown. New york...
Teacher goes postal, locks the door,
kills exactly 66 kids.
All this in a single day?
I looked them up.
There's no doubt about it.
They're all seals.
Breaking... fast.
- How many are left?
- Who knows?
Can't be many.
Where the hell are your angel pals?
You tell me.
I'm just wondering...
What?
With the apocalypse being
nigh and all,
is now really the right time to be
having this little domestic
drama of ours?
What do you mean?
Well, I don't like this any
more than you do, but...
Sam can kill demons.
He's got a shot
- at stopping armageddon.
- So, what,
sacrifice Sam's life,
his soul, for the greater good?
Is that what you're saying?
Times are bad,
so let's use Sam as a nuclear warhead?
I know you hate me for suggesting it.
I hate me for suggesting it.
I love that boy like a son.
All I'm saying is, maybe he's
here right now instead
of on the battlefield,
'cause we love him too much.
Poor baby.
Mom!
Sam.
You look just awful.
Let's hear it.
- Go ahead.
- What do you mean?
You're disappointed.
You never thought I'd...
turn out this way.
I'm a...
Pisspoor excuse for a son.
Your heart is broken.
Am I close?
Not at all.
You're doing the right thing.
What you're doing is brave.
You're not being crazy.
You're being practical.
Sam, I am so proud of you.
But...
But... Dean.
Your brother doesn't understand.
I was raised a hunter,
from a long line.
We understand that there
are gonna be hard choices.
And we do what we have
to to get the job done.
Yes, our family is cursed.
But you...
You have the power
to turn it into a gift.
You can use it against them.
For revenge?
No, for justice.
I know how scared you are.
What's...
In me...
Mom?
- It's...
- Evil.
And you know it.
What if it's stronger than me?
Look at me.
What if Dean's right?
Dean can never know
how strong you are...
because Dean is weak.
Look at what he's done to you.
Locking you in here?
He's terrified.
He's in over his head.
You have to go on without him.
You have what it takes.
- You have to kill Lilith.
- Even if it kills me.
Make my death mean something.
I'm counting on you, Sam.
Don't let anyone
or anything get in your way.
Not even Dean.
Well, it's about time.
I've been screaming myself hoarse
out here for about 21/2 hours now.
What do you want?
You can start with what
the hell happened in Illinois.
What do you mean?
Cut the crap.
You were gonna tell me something.
Well, nothing of import.
You got ass-reamed in heaven.
But it was not "of import"? Dean.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Get to the reason
you really called me.
It's about Sam, right?
Can he do it?
- Kill Lilith, stop the apocalypse?
- Possibly, yes.
But as you know,
he'd have to take certain steps.
Crank up the hell-blood regimen.
Consuming the amount of blood
it would take to kill Lilith
would change your brother forever.
Most likely, he would
become the next creature
that you would feel compelled to kill.
There's no reason this would
have to come to pass, Dean.
We believe it's you, Dean,
not your brother.
The only question for us is whether
you're willing to accept it.
Stand up and accept your role.
You are the one who will stop it.
If I do this...
Sammy doesn't have to?
If it gives you comfort
to see it that way.
God, you're a dick these days.
Fine. I'm in.
You give yourself over
wholly to the service
of god and his angels?
Yeah. Exactly.
Say it.
I give myself over wholly
to serve god...
and you guys.
You swear to follow his will
and his word as swiftly and
obediently as you did
your own father's?
Yes. I swear.
Now what?
Now you wait.
And we call on you when it's time.
Guys! Help!
Now, correct me if I'm wrong, but
you willingly signed up
to be the angels' bitch?
I'm sorry.
You prefer "sucker"?
After everything you said about them,
now you trust them?
Come on,
give me a little credit, Bobby.
I've never trusted them less.
I mean, they come on like shady
politicians from planet Vulcan!
- Well, then why in the hell...
- Because what other option do I have?!
It's either trust the angels,
or let Sammy trust a demon?!
I see your point.
Do you hear that?
That's a little too much nothing.
- What if he's faking?
- You really think he would?
I think he'd do anything.
That ain't faking.
We're gonna have to tie him
down for his own safety.
Dean? You with me?
- Before he has another fit!
- Let's just get it over with!
We had to.
The demon blood was flinging
you all over the room.
Tell me something, Sam.
Why did you do this to yourself?
You know why.
Right.
"Kill Lilith." The big excuse.
But why?
What, revenge? Right?
- Of course.
- Revenge forwhat?
For sending me to hell?
Did you happen to notice i'm back?
Alive and kicking.
- So what's the point?
- The point?
How about stop the damn apocalypse?
My gig! Not yours!
The angels said so, remember?
God picked me, man.
So, have you got any
other fantastic excuses?
I'm gonna ask one more time.
Are we absolutely sure
we're doing the right thing?
Bobby, you saw what was happening
to him down there.
The demon blood is killing him.
No, it isn't.
- We are.
- What?
I'm sorry.
I can't bite my tongue any longer.
We're killing him.
Keeping him locked up down there.
This "cold turkey"
thing isn't working.
If he doesn't get what he needs...
Soon...
Sam's not gonna last much longer.
No.
I'm not giving him demon blood.
I won't do it.
And if he dies?
Then at least he dies human!
I know why you really
drink that blood, Sam.
Just leave me alone.
Makes you feel strong.
Invincible.
A big bad wolf
in a world of little pigs.
No.
You're wrong, Dean.
It's more than that, isn't it?
It's because your whole life,
you felt different.
Am I right?
Stop.
I hit a little close to home?
Not different
because you were some...
lonely kid or because
of your weirdo family...
Stop it.
- Because you're a monster.
- Shut up!
Just shut the hell up!
You were always a monster.
And you only feel right when you're
sucking down more poison
and more evil!
I would die for him in a second.
But I won't let him
do this to himself.
I can't.
I guess I found my line.
I won't let my brother turn
into a monster.
Monster, Sam.
- You're a monster.
- Dean, no.
I tried so hard to pretend
that we were brothers,
that you weren't one
of the filthy things that we hunt.
But we're not even the same species.
You're nothing to me.
Don't say that to me.
Hello?
Someone here?
What did you do?
You shouldn't have come.
Why would you let out
Sam Winchester?
- Those were my orders.
- Orders?
Cass... you saw him.
He's drinking demonblood.
It's so much worse than we thought.
Dean was trying to stop him.
You really shouldn't have come.
The only place you're going
is back inside with me.
No.
Damn it, boy.
You won't shoot me, Bobby.
Don't test me.
You won't do it.
You can't do it.
We're trying to help you, Sam.
Then shoot.
How in the hell did he get out?
Maybe he had help.
Room full of busted devil's traps.
Demons?
Ruby.
That'd be my guess.
How did she even touch the door?
You think she's got the mojo?
I didn't think so.
I don't know, man.
What difference does it make?
How he got gone ain't as important
as where he got gone to.
I'll tell you one thing.
At this point, i hope he's with ruby.
Why?
'cause killing her's the next big item
on my to-do list.
I thought you were
on call for angel duty.
I am on call... In my car,
on my way to murder the bitch.
One thing.
What?
Sam don't want to be found.
Which means he's gonna be
damn near impossible to find.
Yeah, we'll see.
Honeymoon suite.
Really, I'm flattered.
Did you bust me out of that room?
How could I?
The whole thing's engineered
to bite me in the ass.
Then how did I get out of there?
I don't know.
I don't want to know.
You're out.
That's all that matters.
I'm glad you're here.
Yeah?
Where the hell have you been?
- I got here as quick as I could.
- I mean the past three weeks!
I've been calling you!
I've been pretty deep in it,
trying to dig out Lilith.
Sometimes I can't sit around
and check my voicemail.
I'm sorry you're hurting.
Really.
I had no idea
that Dean would do that to you.
You and me both.
You didn't book this joint just
to impress me, did you?
Dean's gonna come after me.
And he knows my habits,
my aliases, everything.
He know sexactly
which motel I'd pick.
Hence the room.
Whatever it takes to shake him.
It won't be easy.
He knows you better than anyone.
Not as well as he thinks.
You know, it's sad.
What?
That things have gotten
this bad between you two.
Police found my car.
Abandoned in an alley
in Jamestown, North Dakota.
He's switching up.
Any other cars stolen in Jamestown?
Two.
1999 Honda Civic...
Blue...
Nice and anonymous, like Sam likes.
What was the other one?
White'05 escalade with custom rims.
It's a neon sign.
You're right.
He'd never take that.
Which is exactly what he did.
You think?
I know that kid.
All right, I'll head
in that direction.
You stay here,
ride the police databases.
We got to find him quick.
Your appetite's gotten much bigger.
What's that supposed to mean?
Sam, relax. It's okay.
It's good.
It just means you're getting stronger.
That's all.
It means you're
strong enough to kill Lilith.
Just in time, too,
because the final seals are breaking.
How many are left?
- Three? Two?
- What?!
Where are the angles?
Screwing the pooch,
wherever they are.
It's looking more and more like we're
getting down to the final seal.
And I found out something big.
What?
Seal 66?
It can't be broken
by just any demon.
Apparently,
only Lucifer's first can do it.
"Lucifer's first"?
Demon sunday-school story.
God prefers humans to angels.
Lucifer gets jealous.
And then he gets creative.
And he twists and tempts a human soul
into the very first demon...
As a "screw you" to god.
It's what got him locked up
in the first place.
That was Lilith?
She's way older than she looks.
Wait, so...
If lilith is the only one
who can break the final seal,
if I get to her in time...
Then lucifer never busts out
of his cage... exactly.
Great.
You figure out where she is?
That bitch can hide.
Buti finally have a lead on someone
who might be able to help us.
I closed in on a member
of Lilith's entourage.
You might call her a...
Personal chef.
Chef? Seriously?
What does she eat?
You don't want to know.
Did you hear about
that horrible thing at St.Paul's?
No.
One of the neonatal nurses walked
right off the unit with two babies.
- You are kidding me.
- Swear to god.
Worked there 17 years, then one day,
out of the blue, she just does it.
That's just horrifying.
Now she's saying that she doesn't
even rember what happened.
Like she was possessed.
- Nuts.
- I know.
Who could ever lay a finger on them?
I know.
They're just delicious.
So, our demon gourmet nurse...
... you sure?
She'll be there.
Graveyard shift.
Tomorrow night.
In the meantime, if you're gonna be
strong enough to kill Lilith,
you're gonna need more
than I can give you now.
Sam.
Come on.
It's okay.
I know, I need more.
I get it.
I know it's okay.
I just...
I wish he'd trusted me, you know?
I'm sorry.
I just hope...
You know, when all this is over...
I hope we can fix things.
The cops found the escalade
in a ditch outside Elk River.
- How far away am I?
- Couple of hours.
I pulled up a weather map,
made some calls.
There's a town
not far from there, Coldspring,
lighting up with demon signs.
That's a good place to look.
- Hey, listen.
- What?
Us finding Sam?
That's got to be about getting him back,
not pushing him away.
Right.
- I know you're mad, Dean.
- I understand.
You got a right to be.
But...
I'm just saying...
Be good to him anyway.
You got to get through to him.
Let her go!
Just take it easy.
That must have been someparty
you two had going,
considering how hard you tried
to keep me from crashing it.
Well, solid try, but...
Here I am.
Dean, I'm glad you're here.
Look... let's just talk about this.
Soon as she's dead,
we can talk all you want.
- Ruby, get out of here.
- She's not going anywhere.
She's poison, Sam!
- It's not what you think, Dean.
- Look what she did to you!
She up and vanishes,
weeks at a time,
leaves you cracking out
for another hit!
She was looking for Lilith!
That is french for "manipulating
your ass 10 ways from sunday."
You're wrong, Dean.
Sam, you're lying to yourself.
I just...
Want you to be okay.
You would do the same for me.
You know you would.
Just listen.
Just listen for a second.
We got a lead
on a demon close to Lilith.
Come with us, Dean.
We'll do this together.
That sounds great.
As long as it's you and me.
Demon bitch is a deal breaker.
You kiss her goodbye,
we can go right now.
I can't.
Dean, I need her...
To help me kill Lilith.
I know you can't wrap
your head around it.
But maybe, one day...
You'll understand.
I'm the only one
who can do this, Dean.
No, you're not the one
who's gonna do this.
Right. That's right. I forgot.
The angels think it's you.
- You don't think I can?
- No.
You can't.
- You're not strong enough.
- And who the hell are you?
I'm being practical here.
I'm doing what needs to be done.
Yeah?
You're not gonna do
a single damn thing.
Stop bossing me around, Dean!
Look.
My whole life, you take the wheel,
you call the shots.
And I trust you
because you are my brother.
Now, I am asking you, for once...
Trust me.
No.
- You don't know what you're doing.
- Yes, I do.
- Then that's worse!
- Why?
I'm telling you...
Because it's not something that
you're doing! It's what you are!
It means...
What?
No.
Say it.
It means you're a monster.
You don't know me.
You never did.
And you never will.
You walk out that door...
Don't you ever come back.
= [ Supernatural Team ] =
on SeriesSub.com
= [ Thx for the transcript ] =
Sync: Jjbrqmz, Grîshnak