Lilith was the final seal.
I killed her,
and I set lucifer free.
You sons of bitches
jump-started judgment day!
- It's apocalypse now.
- Raphael, where is he?
- God?
- He's dead, Castiel.
- You know who I am.
- Lucifer.
- You're the one, Sam.
- You're my true vessel.
- That'll never happen.
- You're the michael sword.
-  I'm the sword?
- You're michael's weapon.
- I'm a vessel?
- You're The vessel.
You got a trickster on your hands.
- What is it, spirit, demon?
- More like demigod.
They're immortal, and they can
create things out of thin air,
usually with a sense of humor...
Deadly pranks.
Another thing Bobby mentioned was that
these suckers have a real sweet tooth.
So this is fun for you?
Killing Dean over and over again?
Sam, there's a lesson here.
- What lesson?
- Dean's your weakness.
The bad guys know it, too.
He's gonna be the death of you, Sam.
"Supernatural" is filmed
before a live studio audience.
I'm gonna need a bigger mouth.
Hey, there, Sam.
What's happening?
Oh, nothing.
Just the end of the world.
You're gonna need a bigger mouth.
Have you done your research yet?
All kinds of research.
All night.
We have some more "research" to do.
Son of a bitch!
= 508 =
= Supernatural Team =
Wellington, Ohio Two Days Earlier
- Doctor...
- What are you watching?
It's a hospital show.
"Dr. Sexy M.D."
I think it's based on a book.
When did you hit menopause?
It's called channel-surfing.
You ready?
Are you?
One more time...
The F.B.I. Is here why, exactly?
It might have something to do
with one of your locals
getting his head ripped off.
- Bill randolph died from a bear attack.
- How sure are you that it was a bear?
What else would it be?
Whatever it was,
it chased Mr.Randolph through the woods,
smashed through his front door,
followed him up the stairs,
and killed him in his bedroom.
Is that common...
A bear doing all that?
Depends how pissed off it is,
I guess.
The Randolphs lived way up
in high country.
You got trout runs
that'll make a grown man weep...
And bears.
Right.
Now, what about Mrs. Randolph?
The file says she saw
the whole thing.
Yes, she did.
My heart goes out to that poor woman.
She said bear?
Kathy randolph went through
a hell of a trauma.
She's confused.
What did she say?
No. It must have been a bear.
I mean,
what else could it have been?
Mrs. Randolph...
What did you think it was?
No. I remember clearly now.
It was definitely a bear.
We're sure it was.
But see,
it helps us to hear, every angle.
So, just tell us what you
thought you saw.
Well, it's impossible, but...
I could have sworn I saw...
The incredible Hulk.
The incredible Hulk?
I told you.
It's crazy.
Bana or Norton?
No, those movies were terrible.
The TV-Hulk.
- Lou Ferrigno?
- Yes.
- Spiky-hair Lou Ferrigno?
- Yes!
You think I'm crazy.
No.
No, it's just...
Is...
Is there...
Would there be any reason
that Lou Ferrigno,
the incredible Hulk would have
a grudge against your husband?
No.
Find anything?
I saw the house.
And?
And there is a giant 8-foot-wide hole
where the front door used to be.
- Almost like...
- A Hulk-sized hole.
- Maybe.
- What do you got?
It turns out that Bill Randolph
had quite the temper.
He's got two counts
of spousal battery, bar brawls,
and court-ordered
anger-management sessions.
You might say you
wouldn't like him when he's angry.
So, a hothead getting killed
by tv's greatest hothead.
Kind of sounds like just deserts,
doesn't it?
It's all starting to make sense.
How is it starting to make sense?
I found something else
at the crime scene.
Candy wrappers.
Lots of 'em.
Just deserts, sweet tooth,
screwing with people
before you kill them.
We're dealing
with the trickster, aren't we?
Sure looks like.
Good.
Been wanting to gank
that mother since mystery spot.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
No, are you sure you
want to kill him?
Son of a bitch didn't think twice
about icing me...
- A thousand times.
- No. I know.
- I'm just saying.
- What are you saying?
If you don't want to kill him,
then what?
- Talk to him.
- What?
Look, think about it, Dean.
He's one of the most powerful
creatures we've ever met.
- Maybe we can use him.
- For what?
Okay, trickster's like
a hugh hefner type, right?
Wine, women, song.
Maybe he doesn't want
the party to end.
Maybe he hates this "Angels and Demons"
stuff as much as we do.
Maybe he'll help us.
- You're serious?
- Yeah.
Ally with the trickster?
Yeah.
A bloody, violent monster...
And you want to be
facebook friends with him?
Nice, Sammy.
The world is gonna end, Dean.
We don't have the luxury
of a moral stand.
I'm just saying, it's worth a shot.
That's all.
If it doesn't work...
We'll kill him.
How we gonna find the guy, anyway?
He never takes
just one victim, right?
He'll show.
Dispatch?
I got a possible 187 out here
at the old paper mill on route 6.
Roger that.
What are you looking at, son?
Honestly, I wouldn't even know how
to begin to describe what I'm seeing.
Just, send everybody.
All right, stay calm, stay back
in your car. Help's on the way.
- That sounds weird.
- Weird enough to be our guy?
There was a murder here...
And there's no police cars...
There's nobody.
How does that look to you?
Crappy.
What the hell?
- Doctor.
Doctor?
Doctor.
- Seriously?
- What?
Seriously, you're brilliant,
you know that?
And a coward.
You're a brilliant coward.
What are you talking about?
As if you don't know.
I don't believe this.
- What?
- That was Dr. Piccolo.
Who?
Dr. Ellen Piccolo.
The sexy-yet-earnest doctor at...
Seattle Mercy Hospital.
What the hell are you talking about?
The doctor getups.
The sexy interns.
The "seriouslys."
- It all makes sense.
- What makes sense?
- What's going on?
- We're in "Dr. Sexy M. D"
Dude, what the hell?
- I don't know.
- No, seriously. What the hell?
I don't know.
One theory.
Any theory.
The trickster trapped us in TV land.
That's your theory?
That's stupid.
You're the one who said
we're on "Dr. Sexy M.D"
Yeah, but tv land isn't tv land.
There's actors and lights
and crew members.
- This looks real.
- It can't be.
Dean, how can this possibly be real?
I don't know.
All right?
But there goes Dr. Wang,
the sexy-but-arrogant heart surgeon.
And there's Johnny Drake.
He's not even alive.
He's a ghost in the mind of...
of her, the sexy-but-neurotic
doctor over there.
So, this show has ghosts?
Why?
I don't know.
It is compelling.
I thought you said you aren't a fan.
I'm not.
Oh, boy.
What?
- It's him.
- Who?
It's him.
It's Dr. Sexy.
Doctor.
You want to give me one good reason
why you defied my direct order
to do the experimental face transplant
on Mrs. Beale?
One reason?
Sure.
- You're not Dr. Sexy.
- You're crazy.
Really?
'cause I swore part of
what makes Dr. Sexy sexy
is the fact
that he wears cowboys boots...
Not tennis shoes.
Yeah, you're not a fan.
It's a guilty pleasure.
Call security.
Yeah, go ahead, pal.
See, we know what you are.
You guys are getting better.
Get us the hell out of here.
Or what?
Don't see your wooden stakes,
big guy.
That was you on the police scanner?
This is a trick.
Trickster?
Come on!
I heard you two yahoos were in town.
- How could I resist?
- Where the hell are we?
You like it?
It's all homemade.
My own sets, my own actors.
Call it my own little idiot box.
How do we get out?
That, my friend,
is the $64 question.
Whatever. We just...
We need to talk to you.
We need your help.
Let me guess.
You two muttonheads broke the world,
and you want me to sweep up your mess?
Please.
Just five minutes.
- Hear us out.
- Sure.
Tell you what.
Survive the 24 next hours,
we'll talk.
- Survive what?
- The game.
What game?
You're in it.
How do we play?
- You're playing it.
- What are the rules?
Son of a bitch.
Dr. Sexy?
Paging Dr. Sexy.
Report to the E.R.
By the way, talking with monsters?
Hell of a plan.
What do we do now?
You know what I'm doing?
Leaving.
Lady...
What the hell?
You are a brilliant, brilliant...
Yeah, a coward.
You already said that.
But I got news for you.
I am not a doctor.
Don't say that.
You are the finest cerebrovascular
neurosurgeon I have ever met...
And I have met plenty.
So that girl died on your table.
It wasn't your fault.
It wasn't anybody's fault.
Sometimes people just die.
I have no idea what
you're saying to me.
You're afraid.
You're afraid to operate again,
and you're afraid to love.
Yeah, we're getting out of here.
Hey, doctor.
Yes?
My wife needs that face transplant.
You know what, pal?
None of this is real, okay?
And your wife doesn't
need jack squat.
Real!
It's real!
We need a doctor!
B.P. Is 80 over 50 and dropping.
Doctor?
What?
Sam, do something.
Come on.
I don't know how to use
any of this crap.
Figure it out!
Sam!
Come on. I'm waiting.
I need a...
Penknife, some dental floss,
a sewing needle, and a fifth of whiskey.
Stat!
We okay?
- How's it looking?
- Yep. You'll be fine.
Let's play.
Nut-Cracker!
NUT-CRACKER
Sam winchester...
What was the name of the demon
you chose over your own brother?
Countdown.
What?
- What am I supposed to say?
- You think I know?
I don't understand japanese.
What was the name of the demon
you chose over your own brother?
Is he screwing with me?
I can't speak japanese...
The answer is...
Ruby.
I'm sorry, Sam winchester.
Sorry?
Sorry for what?
Nut-Cracker!
Hello, chikato-san?
Hai?
Have we discussed these
nutritious Shrimp Chips?
Lots of nutrition, tastes great...
and the more one eats,
the slimmer they get just like you.
You okay?
Now what?
Cass?
- Is this another trick?
- It's me.
- What are you doing here?
- Us? What about you?
Looking for you.
You've been missing for days.
Get us out of here.
Let's go.
Cass.
No, no, no, no.
Mr. Trickster does not like
pretty-boy angels.
Dean Winchester...
I don't want to get hit in the nuts.
- Countdown.
- What do I do?
- I don't wanna get hit in the nuts.
- I don't know.
Just...
- Wait.
- What?
- I played a doctor.
In Dr. Sexy.
I played a doctor, I operated.
- So?
- I did what the trickster wanted.
- We have to go along with it.
- With what?
With the game.
We're on a game show, right?
- Answer the question.
- In Japanese?
- I don't know Japanese!
- Try!
Damn it!
Dean Winchester...
Nuts-cracker champion!
How did you do that?
I have no idea.
So, that's it.
We play our roles, we survive.
Play our roles for how long?
Good question.
I've got genital herpes.
Seriously?
You're the one who said
play our roles.
I've got genital herpes.
I tried to be responsible.
Did I try.
But now I take twice-daily herpexia
to reduce my chances
of passing it on.
Ask your doctor
about using herpexia.
Patients should always consult
with a physician before using herpexia.
Possible side effects
include headache,
diarrhea,
permanent erectile dysfunction,
thoughts of suicide, and nausea.
I am doing all I can
to slightly lessen the spread of...
Of...
Genital herpes
And that's a good thing.
We now return to Supernatural.
Son of a bitch!
I am really, really very sorry,
but...
We've got some work to do.
But we did do work...
In depth.
How long
do we have to keep doing this?
I don't know.
Maybe forever?
We might die in here.
How is that funny?
Vultures.
- You okay?
- I don't have much time.
- What happened?
- I got out.
- From where?
- Listen to me.
This thing
is more powerful than it should be.
- What, the trickster?
- If it is a trickster.
What?
Hello!
Thank you.
Thank you!
Ladies... Stop!
Hi, Castiel.
- You know him?
- Where did you just him?
Relax. He'll live.
Maybe.
You know what...
I'm done with the monkey dance.
Okay? We get it.
Get what, hotshot?
Playing our roles, right?
That's your game?
- That's half the game.
- What's the other half?
Play your roles out there.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You know...
Sam, starring as Lucifer.
Dean, starring as Michael.
Your celebrity deathmatch.
Play your roles.
You want us to say yes
to those sons of bitches?
Hells, yeah.
Let's light this candle!
We do that, the world will end.
And whose fault is that?
Who popped Lucifer out of the box?
Look, it's started.
You started it.
It can't be stopped.
So, let's get it over with.
Heaven or hell...
Which side you on?
I'm not on either side.
Yeah, right.
You're grabbing ankle
for Michael or Lucifer. Which one?
You listen to me, you arrogant dick.
I don't work for either
of those S.O.B.S believe me.
You're somebody's bitch.
Don't you ever,
ever presume to know what I am.
Now, listen very closely.
Here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna suck it up,
accept your responsibilities,
and play the roles that destiny
has chosen for you.
And if we don't?
Then you'll stay here in TV land.
Forever.
300 channels and, nothing's on.
Come on.
- What do you think?
- What do I think?
Go screw yourself,
that's what I think.
Can you give us a sec, please?
Thanks.
- You got to calm down.
- Calm down?
I am wearing sunglasses at night.
You know who does that?
No-talent douche bags.
I hate this game.
I hate that we're in a procedural
cop show.
And you want to know why?
Because I hate procedural cop shows!
There's like 300 of them on television.
They're all the same.
It's, "Ooh, a plane crashed here".
Shut up!
What?
Check out sweet tooth over there.
Think that's him?
Just, follow my lead.
You okay?
What do we got?
Well...
Aside from the ligature marks
around his neck,
he has what appears to be a roll
of quarters jammed down his throat.
Well, I say...
Jackpot.
Also...
There was a stab wound
to the lower abdomen there.
Well, I say...
No guts, no glory.
Get that guy a...
Tums.
Gutter ball.
That's a good one, guys.
- You got the wrong guy, idiot.
- Did we?
I'm worried, man...
What that S.O.B. did to Cass.
You know, where is he?
Sam?
Where are you?
It's Sam.
Leave me a message.
Sam, it's me.
The hell did you go?
Where are you?
I don't know.
Crap.
I don't think
we killed the trickster.
Okay, stake didn't work.
So, what? This another trick?
I don't know.
Maybe the stake didn't work
because it's not a trickster.
- What do you mean?
- You heard Cass.
He said this thing was too powerful
to be a trickster.
D'you notice how he looked at Cass?
Like he knew him.
And how pissed he got
when you brought up Michael and Lucifer.
- Son of a bitch.
- What?
I know what we're dealing with.
What?
That feels really uncomfortable.
- You sure this is gonna work?
- No, but I have no other ideas.
All right, you son of a bitch!
Uncle!
We'll do it!
Should I honk?
Sam, get a load of the rims on you.
Eat me.
Okay, boys...
Ready to go quietly?
Not so fast.
Nobody's going anywhere
until Sam has opposable thumbs.
What's the difference?
Satan's gonna ride his ass
one way or another.
Happy?
Tell me one thing.
Why didn't the stake kill you?
- I am the trickster.
- But maybe you're not.
Maybe you've always been an angel.
A what?
Somebody slip a mickey
in your power shake, kid?
I'll tell you what.
You just jump out of the holy fire,
and we'll call it our mistake.
Well played, boys.
Well played.
Where'd you get the holy oil?
You might say
we pulled it out of Sam's ass.
- Where'd I screw up?
- You didn't.
But nobody gets the jump on Cass
like you did.
It was how you talked about
Armageddon.
- Meaning?
- Well, call it personal experience.
Nobody gets that angry
unless they're talking about
their own family.
So, which one are you?
Grumpy, Sneezy, or Douchey?
Gabriel, okay?
They call me Gabriel.
Gabriel?
The archangel?
Guilty.
Okay, Gabriel.
How does an archangel
become a trickster?
My own private witness protection.
I skipped out of Heaven,
had a face transplant,
carved out
my own little corner of the world
till you two screwed it all up.
And what did daddy say
when you ran off and joined the pagans?
Daddy doesn't say anything
about anything.
What happened?
- Why'd you ditch?
- You blame him?
His brothers
are heavyweight douche-nozzles.
Shut your cake hole.
You don't know anything
about my family.
I loved my father.
My brothers... loved them.
But watching them turn on each other?
Tear at each other's throats?
I couldn't bear it, okay?
So I left.
And now,
it's happening all over again.
Help us stop it.
It can't be stopped.
- You want to see the end of the world?
- I want it to be over!
I have to sit back
and watch my brothers
kill each other, thanks to you two!
Heaven, hell...
I don't care who wins!
I just want it to be over!
It doesn't have to be like that.
There has to be some way
to pull the plug.
You do not know my family.
What you guys call the apocalypse
I used to call Sunday dinner.
That's why there's no stopping this...
Because this isn't about a war.
It's about two brothers
that loved each other
and betrayed each other.
You think you'd be able to relate.
What are you talking about?
You sorry sons of bitches.
Why do you think
you two are the vessels?
Think about it.
Michael...
The big brother,
loyal to an absent father.
And Lucifer...
The little brother,
rebellious of daddy's plan.
You were born to this, boys.
It's your destiny!
It was always you!
As it is in heaven...
So it must be on earth.
One brother has to kill the other.
What the hell are you saying?
Why do you think I've always taken
such an interest in you?
Because from the moment
dad flipped on the lights around here,
we knew it was all gonna end
with you.
Always.
That's not gonna happen.
I'm sorry...
But it is.
Guys, I wish this were a TV show.
Easy answers,
endings wrapped up in a bow.
But this is real.
And it's gonna end bloody
for all of us.
That's just how it's got to be.
So, boys...
Now what?
Stare at each other
for the rest of eternity?
First, you're gonna bring Cass back
from wherever you stashed him.
Am I?
Or we're going to dunk you
in some holy oil
and deep-fry ourselves an archangel.
Cass, you okay?
I'm fine.
Hello, Gabriel.
Hey, bro.
How's the search for daddy going?
Let me guess.
Awful.
Okay, we're out of here.
Come on, Sam.
Guys?
So, what?
You're just gonna...
You're gonna leave me here forever?
We're not. We don't screw with people
the way you do.
And for the record...
This isn't about some prizefight
between your brothers
or some destiny that can't be stopped!
This is about you being too afraid
to stand up to your family!
Don't say
I never did anything for you.
That stuff he was spouting in there...
You think he was telling the truth?
I think he believes it.
So, what do we do?
I don't know.
I'll tell you one thing. Right now,
I wish I was on a TV show.
Yeah, me too.