Can i get you guys anything else
before i ???
As a matter
of fact, you can.
My partner,
trapeezius milkington,
Would like to see something
in a belgian waffle.
Shawn, it's 12:30.
I do not want waffles,
or eggs, or malt-O-Meal.
All right.
What would
you recommend?
Oh, my gosh.
If you're going to do this,
i'm going to the bathroom.
Excuse me.
Don't mind him.
His bladder is
probably smaller than yours.
Now, go ahead.
And take my taste buds
on a fantastical journey.
I don't know.
Um, i like the burgers.
'M sorry.
I should hav you.
Only rule,ly
it can't be something
That someone would order
for lunch.
Keep in mind,
we want to go off script here.
Okay, i see.
Well, in that case,
I would recommend
the pumpkin pancakes
With a side of lingcod.
-Does that work?
-Let's get married.
You don't even know me.
Oh, really? Allow me
to introduce yourself...
Jetta girl.
Maybe green,
Backseat loaded
with empty pinkberry cups.
Oh, my god!
Wrong.
I drive a jeep.
A black jeep.
But you're dead on
with the pinkberry.
So what do you think, should
we save a date, or what?
Mm.
I'll think about it.
-Fair enough.
-Okay.
Let me guess.
She's considering
your pposal of marriage.
How could you
possibly know that?
Shawn, you use
that same tight-Ass routine
On every other waitress
that serves us.
That is
categorically untrue.
You used it on a eighty-Year-Old
"fixins" attendant at fuddruckers.
What's your point, man?
My point is, you're going to be
eighty-Years-Old
And still shamelessly
hitting on waitress.
Is that what you want?
-Is that a trick question?
-What do you think?
All right, hitch.
You want me to take a chance?
Huh?
You want to see
some will hunting action?
Here we go.
Who you calling?
Juliet?
That routine is as tired
as the waitress bit.
Wait for it.
* wait for i-I-I-It *
Hello?
Abigail lytar?
Judd nelson.
Shawn, stop playing.
Is that really abigail?
Shawn, is that you?
Of course it is.
Don't be ridiculous.
Look, clearly we left some loose
ends at our high school  sunoon.
So i was thinking...
That maybe
we should get together.
Why on earth would you think
that's a good idea?
Oh, i don't know.
The last time i saw you,
we kissed for, like, 27 seconds.
Gord...
So just us?
Sitting ate ble?
Hofully a corner booth.
Abigail...
What's happening here is, uh...
I'm asking you out
on a proper date.
Shawn, are you sure?
Are you sure about this?
Yes, i believe i am.
?? Seven.
I'll be the one flaring
my nostrils uncontrollably.
Oh, god, no.
Done.
How do you lik
them apples?
I sincerely hope you didn't
just do that to prove a point.
She's a real person, shawn.
That's no atke.
She misses me already.
Oh... chief.
Get down here now.
I'm not asking.
That was weird.
We received the following
letter about an hour ago.
It has been authenticated.
It's from the yin yang killer.
Pay close attention.
"Hey everybody, i'm back.
For one night only.
"I'm going to kill someone tonight.
"Guess who, guess where,
guess how.
This is going to be so much fun."
Signed, "mr. Yang."
He's looking
for a new challenger.
That's what he does.
Chief, i believe
he's speaking to me.
Trust me.
I am ready.
Oh, come on, people.
He could be talking
about anybody.
Just last week,
Officer yankowitz
guessed my favorite variety
Of snack crackck tuscan wheatan
It's really obscure.
www.1000fr.Com presents
capture:frm@zx
sync:frs@Â±±Áˇ≥/Â∞èËç∏Ëç†
Psych s03 ep16
What do we have
on his description?
We don't.
We've never had any age, ethnicity,
or physical description.
The harsh truth is is that
this is his game.
And we just have to play along
with him.
That's a terrific plan.
Especially since it's worked out
so well in the past.
Chief...
-The mayor's on the phone.
-Oh, here we go.
Detective lassiter,
introduce shawn to our point person.
-Spencer, listen up.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm getting--
I'm getting something already.
What?
What is it?
I can see the killer.
-Already?
-Yes.
And i know exactly where he is.
Right there.
Come on, that's our guy.
Shawn.
Shawn,
that is mary lightly,
Our profiler
from the serial homicide
And abduction task force.
He is very familiar
with the patterns of our killer.
And how to make an attractive lamp
out of human skin.
Shawn, play nice.
He's a genius.
And we need him.
Mary...
-This is...
-Shawn spencer.
In the flesh.
See?
He said "flesh."
You know him?
I've done my research, okay?
Yeah, well,
i've googled myself too,
And there's a lot
of stuff missing.
This is my partner,
sterling cooper.
Hello.
So what's mary short for?
Marian?
No.
Great, we're all good friends.
Care to shed a little light
on this subject?
Mr. Yang is the most notorious killer
this city has never seen.
He claimed six victims
in the summer of 1995,
And has resurfaced twice,
Claiming a single victim
each instance.
He only resurfaces when he feels
there is a worthy opponent.
Now, his m.O.
Is to challenge us
with the opportunity
To save the victims
by solving his riddles.
Question.
-Regarding the whole mary thing.
-My father's name was mary.
His father before him
was named mary.
And his father before him
was named craig.
Fair enough.
Proceed.
Yin yang.
The origin of this chinese symbol
is the unity of opposites.
Two opposing, and at the same time,
complementary aspects.
Dark versus light, killer versus cop,
kramer versus kramer.
Just show him the riddle.
"She serves the general well today
whose soldiers wait to die--
"In a white river they shall pay
for them she will not cry--
Who is she?"
Now, this riddle came
with this stopwatch.
Already running.
One of his classic moves.
You've got one hour
and ten minutes, people.
"Generals and soldiers"--
She'd be in the military.
Mcnabb!
-Yes, sir!
-Damn it.
Want you to contact every military
base in an 80 mile radius.
Find out if any female personnel
have gone awol in the last 48 hours.
Now bear in mind,
It's the psychic
that he wants to play with.
Each riddle will relate
to him personally.
Do you have
any thoughts, shawn?
Yes, jules.
I do.
First of all,
His rhyming skills
are rudimentary at best.
Today, pay, die, and cry?
Come on.
That's bush league.
Yes.
I understand.
Thank you, sir.
Karen...
You are not going to use
my son as a pawn.
Oh, i'll advise you
to proceed with caution.
Need i remind you what happened
to the last detective
Who went head-To-Head
with this sick bastard?
He lost
and an innocent girl died.
Now, i will thank you
to go home and let us do our work.
Not going to happen.
Henry!
Your son is the only shot
that we have.
Period.
Yeah, well...
not my problem.
Shawn.
Excuse me.
Hey, did i miss the memo?
I thought "bring your daddy
to work" day was next week.
I forbid you
to be a part of this, shawn.
You're coming with me.
Wh--Wh--Whoa.
Forbid me?
I'm familiar with your hands-On
approach to parenting,
But i'm not 27 anymore
i can do whatever i want.
This guy knows about you,
He knows about everybody
you care about.
Think about that.
You don't catch
the son-Of-A-Bitch, kid,
You're never going
to sleep again.
Spencer.
???
Go home, dad.
I've got this.
Go home.
Sorry, guys.
?? My zodiac dvd.
??? , please?
"In a white river
they shall pay."
His im washed up
re, maybe there a--
No. There's never
a repeat performance.
Okay, each victim
is a new masterpiece,
And the first riddle
is always a gimme.
No, this guy is itching
to play the game.
Think about the last 24 hours.
Gus.
Gus, i got it!
I-I mean i know
who the general is.
His name is mills.
General mills?
The cereal manufacturer?
Exactly!
The white river is milk,
and the soldiers are cereal.
So who is "she?"
Hi, welcome to captain ron's.
Table for five?
There was a waitress
here earlier.
Long brown hair.
I haven't seen her in a while,
she must be on break.
-Where?
-In the back. By the lockers.
-How do you know this girl?
-We don't really know her.
She served us our lunch.
"All right, shawn.
So close.
"Too bad she has to die.
"But how? And when
and where?
Don't bother asking why."
Oh, he still owes us
a riddle.
This is just the amuse-Bouche.
He's taunting you.
I believe he's using the alphabits
to send a message.
That he, too,
believes that breakfast
For lunch
is way underrated.
Would anyone like to try to
write this message with a burrito?
Open challenge.
Take a shot.
Exactly.
I rest my case.
And now
i want a burrito.
Can i talk to you
for a second, please?
-Dude, what are you doing?
-What are you talking about?
A girl's life is at stake,
and you're acting like an ass?
Making jokes?
You haven't taken this thing
seriously from jump street.
-Exactly.
-Exactly?!
'Cause i have to work
like this, okay?
If that guy gets
in my head, we lose.
I have to do my thing.
I cannot show weakness.
And my fanciful rhetoric
helps diffuse a situation
That's very tense
for the group.
But, shawn,
nobody is laughing.
Trust me, they're laughing
on the inside.
Th how it works,
buy.
I need you  help me out here.
Do you thinkouu can d
-I'll try.
-All right.
???
?? Run,
we'll have more fun.
???
-Next location.
-How much time do we have?
17 minutes.
Wow.
I want pancakes.
Who wants some pancakes?
Whipped butter, maple syrup,
what?
"Make sure you beat the throw"
insinuates a close play.
You got to touch
home plate.
You got to touch home plate
to score a run.
That means the clue's back
at the police station.
Make a hole.
Mom?
Hey, goose.
-Hi, mrs. Spencer.
-Hey.
Spencer?
Let's go.
We need to talk.
I'll make it quick.
Sure, no problem.
Find the clue.
I'll be right there!
-Bye.
I'm not going to mince words.
Your father called me.
He's worried about you.
He wants me to convince you
not to do this.
So he calls you,
you hop on a plane,
-That's how it works, huh?
-No, shawn. I didn't fly down here.
I was at a conference
in ventura.
You're in town?
Would've been nice to know.
The truth is, i'm worried
t u too.
I did psych evals
of several officers
Who were involved in the first round
of this maniac's game.
It wasn't pretty.
All right, look.
First of all, mom...
I have a date tonight.
All right?
So i have to wrap this up
at a reasonable hour.
And secondly...
This guy has never gone up
against me.
If i can stand here
and tell you
That i will nail this guy, are you
really going to tell me to walk away?
-Shawn.
-Mom.
I can beat him.
I will...
Beat him.
Okay, goose.
Nail the son-Of-A-Bitch.
Okay, i got to go, mom.
Please be right.
-Spencer, conference room.
-Thanks.
Well, someone must've signed
for this.
It wasn't delivered.
Dobson found it outside the file room.
How in the hell can--
Okay, you know what,
people?
Eyes open.
Chief, lou sardocki from the s
phone.
?? You owe him
a statent.
Ah, i'll give him statemen
That's very clever.
"Meet my little buddy ben.
"Pitter patter is your hint.
"If you can't remember when,
Just read the fine print."
We have
less than one hour.
Shawn, can you...
Speak to it?
No, he
can't speak to it.
Yes, he can.
Just--Just give him
some room, back up.
Fine, knock yourself out,
doctor doolittle.
Doctor doolittle?
I know you can do
better than that, lassie.La
I know you can.
I don't--I don't know
what i'm supposed to remember.
Hey, everybody,
guess who i am.
Hee-Hee.
I'm michael jackson.
King of pop?
Shawn, i don't think
this is working.
Are you kidding me?
That was a home run.
Keep up the good work.
"Pitter patter"
is the hint.
Now, i don't think
we're speaking to the mouse.
I think the mouse
is speaking toak.
What d'you got, shawn?
Fine print.
Hello, my friend.
It's the fine print.
As walking on it.
Dude, this is crazy.
"Adam hornstock: selling black snake.
Will go fast."
"Mira gaffney:gagaseeks bruton
to love her tender."
All people from past cases.
How do you know that?
I told you,
i did my research.
And finding uchard's treasure
was extremely impressive.
-Thank you, willard.
-My pleasure.
"Snarky psychic: seeks ferroequinologist
To help with killer smile."
He's calling me "sna"
Ferroequinologist?
A ferroequinologist
is a train enthusiast.
How do you know that?
Because i'm a ferroequinologist.
I, too, am a ferroequinologist.
"Love her tender."
The tender is a small fuel car
right behind the locomotive.
And black snake is slang
for coal train.
There's only one coal train
that runs through santa barbara.
???
Train's right on time.
That is outstanding.
It's not going
to stop.
What?
It's not going to stop.
This is just
a pull through station.
What the hell
are we doing here?
-???
-??
Where the hell
are you going?
Come on, gus.
This is our fantasy, man.
It's like we're hobos.
I don't have
a hobo fantasy, shawn!
Abigail,
you called me back.
Yes, you left me
very specific instructions
In your message to do so.
-Is this a bad time?
-No, i can talk.
Look, we're still
totally on for tonight.
I might just have to push
the time a little bit.
Uh-Huh.
Let me guess, you're chasing
a serial killer or something.
Holy crap, yes.
Yes, that's actly
what i'm doing.
How did you--
I cannot believe that you
are bailing on me again.
Hold on.
Tell abigail
what we're doing.
Hello, abigail.
It's gus.
We're chasing a train
like hobos.
What?
She wants
to talk with you.
First of all,  his
"out-Of-Breath voice" is terrible.
He was bad in othello senior year,
he's bad now.
Look, i'm just--I'm flashing
back to high school.
And i have this image
of me standing alone
On a pier
looking like an idiot.
I swear
i'm telling the truth.
I'm going
to have to call you back.
By the way, you were beautiful
on that pier.
"A moving picture
is worth a thousand words.
"So read the story,
and follow the birds.
"Yes.
"Once you're there,
you'll hear a phone.
"You have eight rings
to pick up.
"Or the girl is dead
"Shame on me,
that didn't even rhyme."
We have 27 minutes
to solve this.
What do you see?
Nothing...
I don't see anything.
Not yet.
Oh, wait, i do see something.
What?
What is it?
I think you're going to want
to see this.
It's pretty good.
Let me on.
Mary, i'm surprised
it took you so long.
You seem so spry.
Ankle weights.
I always wear them,
even when i sleep.
Read about it in men's fitness.
Totally reinvigorated
ryan reynolds's career.
So what's the riddle?
How can i help?
"A moving picture--
A moving picture
Is worth a thousand words."
You got to be kidding me.
I got it.
I-I solved it.
Let's go.
"Calls of the birds."
There.
That'se thngs, sth.
Answer it!
-Shawn, what are you doing?
-No, don't you see?
It didn't start ringing
until we were three feet away.
Answer the phone, spencer.
He's watching us,
right now, from somewhere.
Answer the phone, shawn.
If that girl dies,
you're an accessory to murder.
Shawn, i hope to god
you know what you're doing.
Unbelievable.
He's been here.
He was here watching us the whole time!
Don't touch anything.
Let's get csi down here to dust for prints.
No need...
I'm sure he touched things.
He probably touched everything.
But you're not going to find any prints.
He's too good for that.
What is this sick, twisted admiration
you have for this whack job?
Now do you get how good he is?
This puppy's just warming up.
Hey, everybody, check it out.
See how big i am compared to this plane.
I'm king kong.
Guster, what the hell is going on with you?
Seriously, man, i need you
to pull yourself together.
Oh, my god.
I got it.
It's a message.
He says... you are a naughty, naughty boy.
But he's giving us another chance.
She's still alive.
Let's go back to the station,
wait for instructions.
Forget that, i'm not going.
- What do you mean?
- I'm nobody's puppet.
Okay?
I'm done--I'm done playing his little games.
I solved his puzzles, i talked to a rat,
I even chased a train. I'm--I'm finished.
But no one's ever gotten this far,
that's why he's still playing.
It's a sign of respect.
No, it isn't, mary.
You said it, man,
With your fey name and
your weird ken burns haircut.
He's too good.
Isn't that right? He's better than me.
We never had a chance.
He's going to kill that girl either way.
Maybe. Maybe not, shawn.
But i know this, you don't just give up.
Tell you what, jules. Uh,
the next time a serial killer
Calls you out, personally,
Uh, you can pick up your little pom-Poms,
And you can rally the troops
to never say "die." I'm out.
Now get out.
All three of you.
- I can't believe i'm hearing this.
- Should i say it again?!
Screw you, spencer. We don't need you.
We don't need him, o'hara.
We will find this sicko
on our own, come on.
We're running out of time.
Look... shawn.
I know you're upset.
- But if we give up now--
- Gus. Don't be the last of
The famous international playboys.
We're not giving up, okay. Far from it.
The only--Only chance we have to win the game
at this point is to change the rules, okay?
I took a risk out there
because i knew he wouldn't kill her.
I knew he wouldn't kill her
because he loves the game too much.
But that bought us time--
It bought us time to work by ourselves.
Okay, we're going--We're going
to drop off his radar,
We're still going to find the girl.
We're going to do it on our own.
That's our move.
All right, but where do we start?
We're gonna go e ginning. ???
Like what i did dwith the king kong?
You're on fire. You're even using props.
Just got this fax.
Traced it to a bogus 800 number.
"I'm no doubting thomas.
I pucker up to fights.
Were you to shake my hand,
you'd have to use your right.
Who am i?"
Well, if yang was watching,
he could know spencer flew the coop.
This could be directed at any one of us.
Probably not this guy.
It's me.
It's directed at me.
He must know i'm a civil war buff.
??? Confederate geer
omas stonewall jackson,
Shot and killed by his own troops
at the battle of chancellorsville.
He was known for sucking on lemons,
even durin ???
And while he is buried
in lexington, virginia,
His left arm is buried separately
near the battlefield.
Hey, you guys remember that pat
swayze miniseries, north and south?
Talk about civil war buff, huh?
Oh, my god... the stonewall
hotel and suites.
Probably room 1863.
We've got to get down there.
And you can count me in
For next year's reenactment, partner.
Copy that. Get my jacket.
Look, call me back, okay?
We're still on for tonight.
Gus and i are making
some serious progress here.
Call me back.
Straight to voicemail.
That's not a good sign.
Uh, wrong. I drive a jeep.
A black jeep.
Gus, there's no jeep.
I think he drove away in her car.
We find the car, we may find the girl.
Lassie, hold on.
Find the girl's car.
It's a black jeep.
We already did.
You got to get down here.
Where are you?
???
She's breathing.
I'll get the paramedics.
"Shawn no longer wants to pla
kes too low to make you stay."
He's--He's got her.
Gus.
He's got my mom.
??? Over to abigail lytar's apartment.
Now, she's fine.
But i'm posting them on a watch
until we can figure out what is going on.
Spencer, you need to get in here.
"You should be moving,
as most people do.
But instead you sit,
and enjoy the vu.
P.S. Mommy says, "hi."
And "bye."
Just in case."
V.U.
Why'd he spe way?
Maybe that'she hint.
Or maybe he ran out of lipstick.
Brendan vu.
From the spelling bee.
Od g ss.
But it's a misdirect.
I know exactly what he wants me to watch.
You do?
Morning, mr. Malone. Morning.
I want ten pounds of kumquats,
have 'em done in a hurry.
This is  a needle in a haystack...
Made completely out of needles.
Looks like we're at the end game.
All right, we know
he used the waitress' car.
- So there's a good chance it's--
- It's definitely a chance
What kind of car does your wife drive?
She rents when she's down here.
Do you know what company she rents from?
That can narrow it down to a few models.
It's blue. It's blue, gus.
We're looking for a blue car. It's a sedan.
People, we're looking
for a blue car. A sedan.
All right, split up.
S.W.A.T., cover the exits.
Hey, man,
watch where you're going.
What'd you say?
Hey, ma.
- ???
- Shhh-Hh-Hh. Dad t down, get down.
Oh, shit.
Mom, i'm going to take this off, okay?
- Mm.
- It's okay.
- Ah.
- It's just a decoy.
I know. I see that.
He's fine. He's breathing.
Yang must've knocked him out.
S.W.A.T. Call for a medic.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, my god.
Dad, she's strapped.
Oh, god, no!
??? Where is he?
Maddy...
Henry?
Yeah, it's me, sweetheart.
I'm right here.
I'm not going anywhere.
All right. Then i won't either.
Besides, i don't really have
anything better to do right now.
It's just a pen. It's just a pen.
What does this mean, mary?
- Tell us!
- I don't know.
This feels more like improvisation.
This isn't his game.
We got here in time,
maybe we won.
No, he's definitely going
to kill her dead.
I just don't know how.
He's been one step ahead
this whole time.
Where's shawn?
Hopefully one step ahead of us.
All right, be honest with me.
You're surprised, right?
I'm prettier than you'd thought i'd be.
It's the bone structure.
I won.
I beat you,
that was the deal.
Let my mom go.
You are just amazing.
My most--
Most admirable foe.
But then, see,
i knew you would be.
That's why i chose you.
Because i'm--I'm your yin.
Oh, that's sweet.
Thank you for that.
But you're completely surrounded.
There's no way out of this for you.
Now you know what i love
about this movie, shawn?
Its great resolution.
Okay, so call me old-Fashioned, but really.
Is there anything more
satisfying than a solid ending?
You call me a killer.
But the truth is...
I complete things.
And that is what people really want.
To feel complete.
That, and a corner booth.
And now...
Our story that we created so
beautifully together is going to end.
But how?
Do you want to know what it is?
Or do you want to be surprised?
???
Stand down! Stand down!
Let me guess.
You want to die. Right?
That's the perfect resolution.
Gee, that's original.
You're a cliche.
You're a knock-Off
of a knock-Off.
I could've killed your
mom hours ago, shawn.
This switch has such a light touch,
like pinching a baby's cheek.
And then boo!
She blows up.
How much fun would that be to see?
Ugh, it gives me shivers.
I want to do that so badly!
But then you wouldn't like me, shawn.
And i want you to like me.
Oh, god, i'm so torn.
I need you to like me.
Because we're going to be
working together again.
Ah, no, no, no, no.
You're going to rot in a cell
with four padded walls. The end.
No. The end of the beginning.
I'm going to write a book.
Our story.
It's going to be epic,
a best-Seller. And guess what?
I want you to write the foreword.
Pass.
Okay.
But think about it...
On your date tonight.
Clear!
??? Go! Go!
Okay, all right. You're okay.
Think about it on your date tonight.
She was there.
- Gus, she was there the whole time.
- You got her, shawn.
End of story.
Congratulations, spencer.
Don't be too excited there, mary.
It's not like we just apprehended santa
barbara's most notorious killer or anything.
You're right, gus.
I'm sorry to fly off the handle.
I've spent the last 13 years
of my life with this person.
Guess i have to find a new hobby.
Two words:
Racquetball.
That could work.
Thanks for your help, man.
I needed it.
- Gus, you play racquetball?
- Good-Bye, mary.
Till next time.
There we go.
Henry. I told him to go for it.
That doesn't matter.
What matters is
that you're both okay.
You two oe the most important people
in the world to me, you know.
??? Know.
Mom.
Let's get you outta here.
What do you need? What can i do?
Let's see, you already got me
kidnapped by a raging sociopath.
Right, check. What else?
Nothing. Nothing, goose.
I'm--I'm really fine.
Your father's been taking
very good care of me.
If i'm not mistaken...
You have a very important date tonight.
Oh, mom, please.
I can reschedule.
No, you won't.
I'm fine.
That crazy bitch snuck up from
behind me with chloroform.
Life is more than catching bad guys.
You did a good deed today.
Now it's time to go see about a girl.
It's time to go see about a girl.
How do you like them apples?
Mm.
- Well played,
- Mom. All right.
Hey.
Shawn, did you rlly just catch mr. Ya
Yes, i did. And he turned t to be a she.
- Curious.
- Yeah.
Hey, i'm sorry i didn't believe you earlier.
I just... really didn't.
Half apology accepted.
- Mm.
- Uh...
I cut a deal with the theatre manager.
So this is still happening in a big, big way.
How do you feel about popped corn?
I like it. I like it very much.
Jules.What're you doing here?
What i mean is, you know,
Who--Who's going to fit mr. Yang
with her straightjacket
And iron mask with face grill?
Something tells me there's an entire precinct
of officers bidding on that job right now.
Uh...
Can i interest you in a necco wafer?
Shawn, can you just not
talk for a few seconds?
Look...
I just wanted to tell you
that what you did today...
I mean...
I can't imagine being able to function
at that level while your mom was...
You know--
I am, uh...clearly
Not as good with words as you are.
And, um...
I know that things between us have been
A little complicated.
And there have probably been some
mixed signals, mostly from me.
With regards to the time that we spend
together outside of the line of duty...
- Look, jules--
- Shh!
Just please let me finish stumbling
through this. I'm almost done, i promise.
What i'm saying...
Is that i think maybe
The best things,
the richest things,
Aren't supposed to come easily.
And that sometimes the moments
that make the most sense
Happen when everything else doesn't.
And, well...
I think you deserve
more than popcorn tonight.
So w't you let me
take you to dinner?
Youyot on a dat ???
Am.
- Oper ???
- Wow.
I cannot believe this.
All this time, and...
Your timing is just awful.
- It is?
- Yeah.
It's just dreadful.
What?
I can't go to dinner
with you, jules.
I'm already on a date.
You are?
- What, here?
- Yeah, right now.
It's weird--
It's a little weird.
But, uh...
Yeah. With abigail.
The one that got away.
Yeah.
Get out there.
She's not going to wait forever.
Jules.
I'm so sorry...
For snapping at you earlier.
I know.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Why would you even ask that?
Mostly because you look like you got punched
In the stomach and stopped
breathing for a few seconds.
Wow.
I didn't realize
i was that transparent.
The truth-- The truth is,
abigail, everything's not okay.
I don't know exactly how to--
How to say this.
Try using words to form a sentence.
I'm so, so sorry, abigail.
They're all out of butter.
- Wait, what?
- I know, i'm sorry.
I'm sorry, i don't know
why i'm apologizing,
'Cause it's not my fault, really.
But, i mean, it's opening night.
And how do you run out of butter?
That's cardinal.
- What are we going to do?
- I don't know, exactly.
Uh...
As you can see, the kernels are
fluffy and salted quite nicely.
I tried--I tried one.
But we do have, uh, necco wafers.
Necco.
- And toblerone.
- I love toblerone.
Yes, i sensed that you might.
It's like a more sophisticated crkle.
Hey,'rhesure about this?
Absolutely.
Now, in with you.
This carriage.
Oh, god!
That's what i'm talking about.
Gus.
Hello, abigail.
The thing is, it's--It's his car.
It's a company car.
And he's very protectof it.
So just pretend like he isn't here.
Are those necco wafers up there?
Yes, they are. Pass them back, please.
www.tvsubtitles.net