Don't say a word.
- Fergulous.
- Shawn, I said no words.
I see how works.
Two weeks ago playing Scrabble
is not a word and actually...
It's a word
because it's convenient for you.
Oh, buddy.
Dude, you've got some peat moss
jammed behind your ear.
It could be infected with MAIDS.
MAIDS.
I lost a 200$ shoe.
Your dad almost got a skull fracture.
You're the one who got us into this.
- And nothing happened to you.
- Dudes, stop it.
I've been in the other side of
this table a thousand times.
You'll tell them only
what they need to know.
- What we'll say about Uncle Jack?
- He's not here. Is he, Shawn?
What about take care of ourselves?
We didn't do anything wrong.
We didn't break any laws.
Oh no.
Oh no, what?
- What did you do, Shawn?
- Nothing.
It's just the laws keep changing.
It's getting very challenges
to keep up with the move.
Do you know, for instance...
There is it now illegal
pretend to be other person?
Shawn. Did you
or did you not break any laws?
We impersonated priests.
What? We were professors.
We were priests, Shawn.
You, gentlemen, have
a lot of explaining to do.
You can bet sure I'm getting
to the bottom of this.
Do I get a phone call or something?
How about a text message?
I'll be quick.
I just need to respond, "OMG, LOL.”
Here's a question.
How do you make the face that's winking
with the tongue coming out one side?
Mr. Spencer, now, by my estimation,
you may be in
some serious trouble here.
So I am only going
to ask you this once.
Where's the gold?
It's not quite as simple as that.
Right, if we were to really
answer that question,
we'd have to go back quite a while.
How long?
About 20 years.
As the rain thundered down
from the dark night sky
and 30-foot waves
crashed over his ship,
the great pirate Bouchard
stood on his bow...
Pointed...
At the California coast,
and yelled,
"we shall take this land
as ours, men!"
Your dad's awesome.
I know.
I'm so glad my dad didn't come.
I mean, I don't even know
what a manager of debt
consolidation does, anyways.
Except drink.
Rumor has it that
Bouchard was obsessed
with searching for Spanish gold.
They also say
he may have had syphilis
and went crazy
searching for something
that never existed.
But I say...
The gold did exist!
Okay, my dad has to go now.
Thanks, dad. See you later. Bye.
Wh... Wh... What the heck's
going on here?
Officer, we're just
in the middle of a class.
Is there a problem with something?
Yes, there is a problem.
That's not Shawn's dad, 'cause
I'm Shawn Spencer's father.
You're not Shawn's dad?
You know technically.
Technically,
that is my brother Jack,
who technically didn't tell
me he was coming to town
and obviously cooked
up this ruse with Shawn
to fool his new teacher.
What were you thinking?
I don't know. I just thought
it'd be cooler if uncle Jack spoke.
Look, class, I'm sorry
to break this to you, but...
He's not a real
treasure hunter, and this...
Is not real gold.
Kids, my big brother
Henry is absolutely right.
This is not real gold.
But it is real chocolate!
What does this have to do
with the gold?
Relax, Lassidophilus,
we're getting there.
Last night...
What can I say?
The movie didn't make any sense.
Of course it didn't make any sense
to you. You came in 20 minutes late,
fell asleep for an hour, then woke up
and asked me what happened.
You always do this.
What can I say? The movie theater's
too damn dark. It makes me sleepy.
So basically I paid $10
for you to take a nap.
Basically, I paid...
Dad, someone's in the house.
Oh, my god. Let's call the cops.
We should call the cops.
You keep a stun gun
in the birdhouse?
What's under
the garden gnome, an M-80?
You want me to pok you
in the eyes on the roof?
We're calling the cops, right?
Why aren't we calling the cops?
Dad, wait.
Stop!
Uncle Jack!
I knew it was you
as soon as I saw the penny.
Ha ha ha! The kid!
Shawn, my boy.
And by the way,
that's a'59 penny.
It's the first year they used
the Lincoln memorial on it.
- I want you to keep it.
- Thanks, man.
Jack?
Dude. A hose? What were you gonna do,
give him a high colonic?
- Shut up, Shawn.
- No, no. I get it.
You bust in here,
you blind him with water,
and then you make your move, baby.
Come here, you!
Oh, boy.
It seems like only yesterday
I was bringing you kids
to the track,
and we were betting the ponies.
I was the only 8-year-old kid
who knew what a trifecta meant.
- Yeah.
- Uncle Jack, I haven't heard from you
since you sent that e-mail from
Prince Albert's boat in the Maldives.
Yeah, well, I had to sign a
confidentiality agreement there, guys.
Can't really talk about it.
By the way,
I got presents for everybody.
I got these when I was
excavating near Machu Picchu.
Dug them up myself.
It's been three years, Jack.
What are you doing here
besides breaking into my house?
Breaking in.
You gave me a key.
I didn't give you a key. I don't give
anyone keys, not even Shawn.
That's not true. I actually
made a copy a while back.
It was when I was hooked
on Wow Wow Wubbzy! On Noggin.
I didn't have cable.
I also stole your toilet paper
for about a year,
and a huge box of sporks.
I guess you are wondering
why I came back.
I want you to help me find
Bouchard's treasure.
Come on. Not that again, Jack.
I hate to break it to you,
little brother,
but Bouchard's treasure
does not, has not,
and will not ever exist.
It's a pipe dream.
Don't listen to him, uncle Jack.
He's a dream killer.
Ah, I understand his frustration.
All those years spent
listening to me drone on
about the whole "treasure" thing
without even a semblance of proof.
I get it.
One thing confuses me, though.
If it is just a figment
of my imagination...
Where'd I get this?
Psych 304: The Greatest Adventure
in the History of Basic Cable
Synchro : Flolo, Icefre@k
For SeriesSub.com
Why do I feel like he can see us?
No, it's impossible.
He can't see or hear a thing.
That's just weird.
So, what, we're just gonna let
this guy listens in on everything?
It's out of our hands, detective.
Now just get in there and
get to the bottom of this.
You got it.
When are we gonna find out the
deal with suit guy in there?
Let's just get back to the story.
I can't believe your uncle Jack
actually had a treasure map.
I can't believe you actually
pretended your uncle was your dad.
I wanted Gus' dad to do it,
but there was a genealogy
issue I just couldn't resolve.
- What else can you tell about Bouchard?
- We could only remember bits and pieces
of the Bouchard myth, but Jack...
filled us in on the rest.
November, 1818.
Bouchard sailed up and down
the California coast,
searching desperately
for the mythical Spanish gold.
He ravaged and looted
the mission in Monterrey,
was repelled
at san Juan Capistrano,
and finally made land here,
at Santa Barbara,
where he did battle with a small
Spanish garrison
and the Chumash Indians.
Yeah, I remember reading
about that.
They say he made off with
millions in Spanish gold coins,
but his boat sunk off the coast
north of here.
He disappeared, and years later
he showed up in Argentina.
Superior retention of
historic detail, Gus.
Bouchard was also fond
of hiding clues
to the treasure's whereabouts
in the map.
And I stumbled upon this one
while researching him in Argentina.
First you say you're
in Machu Picchu in Peru,
and all of a sudden,
now you're in Argentina.
- So which one is it?
- Dad, he's not a suspect.
He's suspect, all right.
Forget him. Forget him, okay?
My big brother's always been
just a little cynical.
And that's what I love about him.
You still haven't answered
my question.
What about it, boys?
- Want to be treasure hunters?
- You're kidding me?
That's like asking me
if I want my own jet pack
or if I've ever wanted
to be a koala bear.
Okay, I think he means,
yes, you can count him in.
And me too.
Superb. Mm.
You know, I've been, reading a
lot about that detective stuff you do,
and it seems to me that having a psychic
might be a real asset.
- Who knew I had one in my own family?
- Well, uncle Jack, I...
I don't know. I'm not really...
I wouldn't necessarily say psychic.
Stop that right now.
Don't you do that
to yourself, young man.
Do not sell yourself short.
Do not feel embarrassed
just 'cause you're a little different.
Didn't I always tell you
you'd be great? Didn't I?
Yeah, you did.
Okay, now, here's the plan.
Everything we find, we split 50/50.
That's after we donate most
of it to a museum, right?
- We are so gonna do that, Gus.
- Right.
You and I...
We're really, up here, in synch.
Okay, so the first thing
we need to do is...
Get matching fedoras?
"Get matching fedoras?"
You wanted the fedoras, not me.
Stop changing the story.
My mistake. He wanted
the yellow gauchos. I said no to that.
Would you please put me in a
separate room from these idiots?
- I will tell you everything.
- Just continue.
Jack had told us to meet him at
the front steps of the mission,
because that was the
first step on the map.
Gus and I could barely contain
our excitement.
I contained mine a little better.
Okay, just follow my lead.
Say yes to everything.
Welcome, welcome...
I'm Karen Raven,
head of the Santa Barbara
historical society.
We are delighted to have
such a distinguished professor
as yourself visiting us.
Ah, gracias, gracias.
I am Abner Espinoza, and these
are my compatriots,
Ernesto Agapito Garces con y a de Abelar
and Juan Priestly.
Now I see where you
got the priest thing.
- What does that mean?
- Nothing.
Well, welcome.
Please, come this way.
Now, as you know, most of
our prized collection pieces
are kept away from the public,
but, we're happy to open our doors
for visiting dignitaries
such as yourselves.
Yes.
Okay, then.
Um, take as much time as you need.
And, bill here
will be waiting just outside.
All right, boys, we got about 10 minutes
before the real Espinoza shows up.
There's a real Espinoza?
Well, technically speaking,
we used to be partners.
He's a great guy,
but we had a little falling out
when I had a small dalliance
with his wife...
And his sister...
And his housekeeper Debbie.
Uncle Jack,
what's really going on here?
My research has told me
there are clues
about the treasure's whereabouts
hidden somewhere in this room.
And it all has to do
with the number 152.
Why don't we just use the map?
Well, technically, there's...
Something I haven't told
you about the whole map.
Uncle Jack, this is a pretty
big thing to leave out.
Yeah, I know, I know, I know.
It's a long story...
A one-legged woman,
bottle of Cutty Sark.
The point is that
the missing part of the map
is the first step of the hunt.
Now, come on, kid,
use that psychic gift you got.
Come on.
Oh, boy.
I'm seeing letters swarming.
They're... They're zinging.
They're... They're forming...
They're forming words.
- "couleur. "
- C- couleur.
- Couleur.
- What does that mean?
French, color...
Paint! Painting!
That's it. Come on, let's go.
Hurry up, more.
There are paintings over there.
Wait. Go back. Go back.
Hello, Bouchard.
Let me see the map.
Where did you hide
that clue, you old syphilitic sea dog?
I know where the map starts.
And I know where the first clue is.
Wait. The map was actually real?
We couldn't believe it.
The lighthouse was the first clue.
What happened from there?
- We didn't make it to the second clue.
- Why not?
Because we weren't
the only ones who found the lighthouse.
All right, Spencer,
tell the chief what you just told us.
Okay, chief, here it goes.
We're so hungry.
I can't get the burrito place
on Cota street out of my mind.
They're open late.
Gus, children's burrito, no sauce.
Dad, I know you're a fan
of the carne asada.
All right, Mr. Spencer,
let me be frank.
As long as I can be Dean
and Gus Sammy.
- Why do I have to be Sammy?
- He's Sammy.
That makes you Joey Bishop.
Is that what you really want?
You want to be Joey Bishop?
I'm sorry, Jules. How often does someone
set you up with "let me be Frank"?
Don't forget that you are
in a lot of trouble here.
And I am probably the only person
in this room who cares
to see you get out of it.
Now, it's 2:30 in the morning.
We've been here for hours.
Enough with the jokes,
stop delaying,
and tell us what we want to hear!
My god. That was so hot.
Spencer, tell the chief what
you told us about the guys
who chased you away from
the lighthouse with the guns.
Not just chasing us,
they found us...
- Hiding in a cabin.
- Who were they?
Jack's partners.
'cause the one thing that you could
count on with my brother Jackie,
he always had partners.
Jack, what the hell are you doing?
Mark, calm down, will ya?
- It's all part of the plan.
- Wait a sec. You guys know each other?
Oh, yeah.
We were partners.
I thought We were partners.
Technically,
you're all my partners.
I don't know where you
guys went to partner college,
but I'm pretty sure you're not
supposed to shoot at your partners.
Should partners do this?
Maybe we shouldn't use the
word "partners" anymore.
It seems to make him mad.
Mark.
Kitten, listen.
This is my nephew Shawn, okay?
He's psychic, for real.
Works with the cops sometimes,
fully legitimate... Fully.
I brought him to help with the hunt.
I was just gonna pay him a finder's fee.
Finder's fee?
- Is that like 50%?
- Not even close.
No. Not buying it.
You were gonna sell us out.
Psychic things
are happening to me!
Running down my legs.
Welcome, welcome. I'm Karen Raven,
head of the Santa Barbara
historical society.
SAINT GERARD MAJELLA
PATRON SAINT OF PEGNANT WOMEN
You...
Don't worry about the pregnancy.
Your girlfriend's
gonna be just fine.
What did I tell you?
Now, why don't you just let us go?
We'll all find the treasure.
We'll be stinking, filthy
rich, and live fabulous lives.
No.
Give us the map.
We don't have the map.
Really?
That's too bad.
Okay, it's in the backpack.
Thanks.
It's in... It's in
the side pouch. Ssh!
Should we tell Mark
that there's a tear in the map?
Son of a bitch, Jack!
Hold it.
So you just gave them the map
and told them everything?
No, not everything.
Okay, everything.
So they found the treasure?
Not exactly.
Okay, I may...
have psychically led
them down the wrong path.
The spirit world is just one
of life's little mysteries,
like why the Oxygen Network
airs Goodfellas,
or why fools fall in love.
Here you go, Mr. Guster.
This is all they had in
lost-and-found in your size.
An UGG boot?
I can't wear an UGG boot with...
It'll be dope with my one puma.
Now, Mr. Spencer.
- Yes.
I meant the older...
- Sorry, not old, less...
- Handsome.
Less hair?
Less friends on facebook?
Less nose.
Henry.
Did you fill out a burglary
report on your house yesterday?
I did.
But nothing was taken.
And yet why do I feel this somehow
plays into this whole mess, doesn't it?
I was the one who picked them up.
Wait, wait, wait.
How did your dad know where to find you
if that Mark guy took
all your cell phones?
That is a good question.
I have to pee.
No. No way, Shawn.
- What am I supposed to do?
- Hold it like a man.
- I'll get a urinary tract infection.
- Like a man.
You know what? You can link
your legs underneath your chairs
and form a wheel
and roll to the bathroom.
I don't even want to project
how that's gonna happen.
I'm not rolling anywhere.
I don't know why I listen
to either one of you.
No one is gonna find us.
We're probably gonna die out here.
- Gus?
- What?
What is that on your leg?
Nothing.
Dude, you are strapped
with another cell phone?
Just call Henry. Come on.
No, we're not calling anyone.
That is my work phone, for work.
- This is work.
- My boss is watching everything I do.
Plus, you used up half my minutes
waiting on hold for concert tickets.
That was tony! Toni! Tone! And
Wet Wet Wet playing together.
You know I can't resist that.
The symmetry alone...
All right, Gus,
this is our only choice, man.
Fine.
Reach down and get it.
Me? I'm not gonna
reach down and... You get it.
With what hand?
Fine. I'll do it.
Hold still.
Stop it.
- You're wobbling!
- Hold on, now.
Stop flexing.
No, wait, it's ringing.
Fu's palace.
Want to place order?
You must have dialed the wrong number.
Hi. We're stuck out in
a cabin on tunnel road.
Can you send help?
For pickup or delivery?
This is Jack Spencer,
and I'm willing to offer you
a 50/50 split on pirate treasure.
- Hang up, shawn.
- Hold on.
While he's on the line,
you guys want anything?
Will you dial it again? And this time
try to dial the right number.
Look, man, I'm dialing with a
10-year-old erasermate in my mouth.
It's not an exact science.
You've reached Henry Spencer.
Leave your name and number.
But speak slowly, because people talk
too fast on these things,
and I can never understand it.
Dad, what's going on?
I got good news...
Great news...
The electric wrench you've been
wanting is in stock at home depot.
- what else?
- There was something else.
I know.
If you're not too busy,
Gus, Jack, and I are tied up
in a cabin about
100 yards off tunnel road,
right by where we had the pulled pork
sandwiches that one time.
Spencer, are you gonna answer
my question or not?
How did your dad know
where to find you?
With some people, I can communicate
through psychic wavelengths.
My father is one of them.
Val kilmer is another.
Here's something I don't understand.
Jack's partner wanted the map, right?
So why would they
trash your dad's house?
They know Jack wouldn't let
the map out of his sight.
Mark and his men,
they weren't looking for a map.
So what were they looking for?
You know you're my boy, shawn.
Why'd you have to go
and give mark the map?
Because I don't need it.
Uncle Jack, trust me.
I can re-create the map
psychically in my head.
Spare me, kid, okay?
You can't snow the snowman.
We were so close.
Stop!
I feel jittery!
It starts with beans.
Gus likes it in the morning.
Now he has gas.
- Something having to do with coffee?
- Yes! Coffee!
Coffee, coffee, coffee, coffee table!
Coffee table.
Mark and his goons weren't
looking for the map, were they?
No, no. They were looking
for something else.
A different piece of the puzzle.
Something you didn't want
connected to the map at all.
That is downright scary!
Maybe you really do have a gift, kid.
My bad for doubting it.
Now, this key is also from bouchard's
stuff, I found in argentina.
It was useless without that map,
but if shawn can actually
re-create that map,
that plus this key
means we are back on track!
Guys, I got to hit the head.
But when I come back,
we are finding us a treasure!
Hope he bought that.
With Jack, you never know.
But if that key is real...
Shawn, come on, take a look around.
Haven't you had enough? These guys,
they destroyed my living room.
Mark and his goons aren't gonna stop.
We gotta get back out there.
No!
No, shawn! No!
Just come with us.
Come with us.
- Why do you need me?
- It's not that we need you.
We want you.
Plus, we need you.
We need your truck because my car
is still at the lighthouse,
and mark has the key.
There you go.
Thank you very much.
Sorry. Count me out.
Shocker.
Okay, guys, ready?
Good.
All we got to do now
is borrow a car.
Now, technically,
the term is hot-wiring.
- However...
- I'm in, but I drive.
I'm the one who decides if and when
we go to the police.
I don't want any more surprises.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, dad!
Big bro, I knew you'd come around.
Okay, psychic...
What's the next step?
The key will guide us now.
I love this.
50/50 split between me and you guys!
- No more surprises, right, Jack?
- Of course.
Ya los tenemos.
Tell me this, shawn. How are we
supposed to find clues from a bell tower
that hasn't been around
for over 100 years?
The presidio was huge.
It would've taken up several blocks.
So what should we do now?
There's only one thing we can do.
Go back in time.
The bell tower is calling me!
Come on.
Shawn, wait up!
This is it.
This is where the bell tower stood.
What do we do now?
Let's buy some mufflers.
He doesn't even own a car.
I bet you I end up paying for this.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'll survive.
- What are we doing up here, shawn?
- I'm not sure yet.
That's part of the fun, isn't it?
We are good to go.
The manager said we can take
as much time as we need.
Alvin, good guy.
Filipino.
They love me.
And Jack offered him 50% of the
treasure. I also gave him an'82 penny.
It was the first year they used
zinc instead of copper.
What is the deal with you
and all these pennies?
Yeah, I don't get that either.
So Jack collects them
and then leaves them places?
What's that about?
Jack was always interested in history.
Collecting pennies was his way
of being a part of it.
But leaving the pennies was his own
personal philosophy.
See, uncle Jack always said...
I leave the penny
because it's good luck,
and lord knows the world
could use more good luck.
Are you for real?
All right, what are we doing up here?
You think that when bouchard
captured the fort,
he stood up here on the bell tower,
gazing out into the big blue ocean,
looking for a place
to hide the treasure?
If I were a french pirate
with a bad temper and at least
one venereal disease,
where would I be looking?
That's it.
That's it, right there.
We're so close!
Let's go!
How did he find us?
He's got the map.
He must've figured it out.
Come on, let's go!
I can't leave my puma, shawn.
I got it.
This is it.
This is the bluff on the map.
Uncle Jack!
I know this probably isn't
the right time to say this,
but, dude, I think we're gonna get
to ride in a helicopter.
You're obligated to let me speak...
I'm not obligated to make....
Chief, perhaps you should
see this one more time.
No, I don't need to see
the letter one more time.
Jules, lassie,
what's going on out there?
What's the deal with that guy?
He didn't say a word when he brought us.
His name is Andres Candelaria.
He works for the spanish government.
Apparently he's part of some
intergovernmental task force
on stolen antiquities.
Hello, Mr. Spencer.
I believe you know why you're here.
And I believe you know
I know why I'm here.
Now, why am I here?
To help us find the treasure
that rightly belongs to my government.
- But we didn't find anything.
- Si.
And my men have been searching the
bluffs all night as well with no luck.
That's because you stopped us
one step short.
Your treasure's not in the bluffs, che.
The spirits are guiding my man paw!
It's like... It's like
that movie idle hands,
except with no nudity,
which means I must be completely
unwatchable right now.
Do either of these words
mean anything to anyone?
It could be the clue
we're looking for.
- Cueva is spanish for "cave."
- Couleur could be french.
I think it means "paint."
I spent a semester in paris,
got salmonella poisoning,
and lost 20 pounds.
Best date ever.
Painted caves...
That's it!
Bouchard was french, but he was
fascinated with the chumash indians.
Chumash indians?
They used to paint caves
all over the area.
We used to roust punks in there
from drinking all the time.
"Roust punks"?
Thank you, Jack lord.
We will now lead you
to the treasure.
I know the cave.
Very well. Let's go.
Stop. You are not doing this.
The only reason I brought these
men here in the first place
was because Spencer would'nt talk
with us unless he was in the station.
I said we would cooperate with
you, but they are employees of the sbpd,
and they're not going anywhere
without my detectives.
We have been through this, no?
This is from your treasury department,
giving me full power to call the shots.
Now, I thank you for your help,
but it will no longer be needed.
Vamos.
Sorry Jules.
I can't believe we're actually
digging for buried treasure.
I know, dude... And you're getting
your pants totally dirty,
and you don't even care.
I'm so proud of you.
Keep digging!
H. b.
That could be
for hippolyte de bouchard.
Or harry belafonte.
- No.
- No, that doesn't make any sense.
Just get it out!
Oh, my god.
It's real.
Si.
Well done.
Buen trabajo.
You should know the spanish government
owes you a great debt of gratitude.
Now...
Could I please have the coins?
Before we do that...
I should tell you, I know three things
that you probably don't know.
Uno...
The secret of nimh
andthe secret of my success...
Same secret.
Dos...
I know that you don't work
for the spanish government.
And tres...
These caves are actually quite slippery.
- What are you doing?!
- Grab that, grab that! Right there!
What is going on?
Why are we running?
Why did we leave the caves?
What happened to your other puma?
You got to be kidding me!
I lost another shoe?
Come on.
This way!
Vamanos!
Jack! Jack!
Yes!
Hey guys.
I told you I'd come back.
I've been tracking you the whole time.
Do you... Do you have the treasure?
This is it.
I always believed in you, kid!
I always knew you were special!
No, no, no...
You can't come in here.
We gotta split up for safety.
Now, listen, they're not gonna hurt you
if you don't have the gold.
- I know what I'm talking about.
- What?
Come on, let's have it.
Remember the place on foothill
where I used to take you when you were
a kid, get you burgers and shakes?
- It's red robin. It's still there.
- That's the one.
I'll meet you there in an hour.
I'll be there.
Damn it! You gave him
the gold, didn't you?
That's my gold!
Who the hell are you?
If there were doves flying around,
we'd be in a john woo movie.
Son of a bitch!
I'm gonna kill Jack!
- What? You know Jack?
- He was my partner.
He was my partner.
Technically, iron giant guy,
he was all of our partners.
And the guy who answers
the phone at fu's palace.
- And the guy at the muffler shop.
- Good catch, Gus.
Look, we're just gonna roll on out
if that's cool, let you settle
your business here.
Not so fast.
Why don't we just take
the nephew here
and ransom his ass for the gold?
We have no other choice.
No, no...
You... You always have a choice.
You could ransom Gus's ass.
You could swirl it up.
You could ransom half my ass
and half his ass.
Drop it!
Hands in the air!
Shawn, you know
I don't curse very often.
So when I do, you know I mean it.
What the hell just happened?
I thought you weren't a big
fan of the wrap-up.
All right, i'll give it to you.
So, back at the station,
I realize andres' accent isn't spanish.
It's argentinean.
And that's where uncle Jack
just got back from,
- I figure he's one of Jack's partners.
- How did you know that?
You worked at that winery
in argentina for a year.
- I kept the postcards.
- You did?
I use 'em as beer coasters.
Okay, shawn, wh...
So that's why I called andresche,
to see if he'd react, which he did,
because in argentina, che
is slang for "buddy" or "pal,"
sort of like I call you "black star"
or "home skillet" or "big baby burton."
Don't ever call me "home skillet."
Right.
- But why didn't you tell anybody?
- I did.
She knew just what to do with it.
Sorry, Jules.
Doesn't matter what happened.
The important thing is you guys
are safe, and nobody got hurt.
Now, let's get out of here.
I'm too old to be staying up all night.
I can't believe I lost my other shoe.
Dude, I will buy you another pair.
Just tell me you didn't really
drop 200 bones on sneakers.
No, shawn.
I was making a point.
How much were they really?
80 bucks.
And I have $32 left
on my foot locker gift card.
- What am I looking at, like 30 bucks?
- 48.
I'm in for half.
We'll get some jerk chicken
on the way home.
Fine.
Strawberry?
You got to taste it.
I'd still go vanilla, but it's good.
Are you kidding me?
That is the best shake on the planet.
One part ice cream, two parts awesome.
It's been a long time
since you called me for a ride.
Yeah, Gus got tired of waiting
for someone who wasn't gonna show.
All right, look, shawn, here's the thing
about your uncle Jackie.
He'll always come back.
You're not the first to get duped.
You certainly won't be the last.
Welcome to the club, kid.
I guess I probably owe you an apology.
I can see now where uncle Jack
might not have been the best role model.
Yeah, maybe not.
Why didn't you say anything
when I was a kid?
Because I always wanted you to
have the... The fun uncle in your life.
I was only hard on you because
I didn't want your life to turn out
like the fun uncle.
It didn't...
Not totally.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
You know the penny thing?
Your grandpa taught me that,
and then I taught it to Jack
when we were kids.
He just took it to another whole level.
Yeah, he, he seems to do that a lot.
I still can't believe that
he got away with the gold.
I... You got to think that someday
all this stuff is gonna
catch up with him?
Yeah.
And that day might just be today.
- Does Gus know about this?
- yeah.
He's got the rest of it.
Don't worry, we're donating
it to the museum.
All of it?
"Ish." Wha...
I saw Jack following us.
I knew he was gonna show up
in the car.
I made the switch when we were
running through the forest.
So what does Jack have?
Well done, shawnie.
Well done.
For SeriesSub. Com