That's the highway
department's problem, Jerry, not mine.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
What are you three doing here?
Aren't you supposed to be in school?
We came to see that UFO you cleared
from that field this morning.
- You mean the weather balloon.
- They got to him.
- Who got to me, Dennis?
- The secret government agency
in charge of extraterrestrial
cover-ups.
- How much are they paying you?
- That's enough, guys.
Back to school now.
Do you think this is a game?
I assure you, it's not.
Inside that grounded
Cassiopeian death pod
sits an army of glornokian
mercenaries
intent on colonizing our planet
and propagating their evil species.
After they probe us.
We should go. He's packing.
There are no such things
as UFOs, Shawn.
So the plaintiff is entitled
to compensatory
and punitive damages,
per article 35-a,
section "j", which stip...
Are you okay?
Just came by to drop off
the Patterson file
and some refills.
Did you notice
any commotion a moment ago?
What kind of commotion
are we talking about?
Toby, where are you going?
Aren't you forgetting something?
We were supposed to let him
drive around with us.
We are not currently driving.
You need to stop taking your frustration
with Shawn out on Henry.
Better him than the neighbor's cat.
- I could have suffocated in there!
- Jeez, I cracked the window.
I'm glad that Shawn
peanut-buttered your phone.
I knew that was him.
I still have jif in my ear.
Mr. Kessler, I am detective O'Hara,
and this is detective Lassiter,
and this is Henry Spencer,
who helps us coordinate
our investigations.
So, sir, I understand
you witnessed a kidnapping last night.
I'd say it was more of an abduction.
Do you have any idea
who the perpetrator was?
An extraterrestrial.
How come the crazies
never live close by?
It sounds nuts, but I'm telling you,
I saw it with my own eyes.
An alien came down
and snatched a young lawyer
that works at my firm... Toby Shore.
No offense, but I think you're gonna
have a hard time finding anyone
to believe a story like that.
Was he tall and scaly,
or short, with a huge lollipop head?
Tall, I think.
- Reptilian.
- Probably hostile.
We're gonna need a speak & spell
and seven pounds of mashed potatoes.
Enough!
Mr. Kessler, if your co-worker
doesn't show up In the next eight hours,
feel free to file
a missing persons report.
Until then, stop wasting our time.
You owe me a new phone!
You have a very nice home.
This UFO, was it more like
a bright sphere,
or two soup bowls glued together?
No, it was a sphere, definitely.
Are you UFO chasers?
Nothing as ridiculous as that.
We're psychic detectives.
And we can help you get to the bottom
of what happened.
Fantastic. You're hired.
May I have a word?
You shouldn't take this case.
You shouldn't be dropping the dime
on my peanut butter pranks.
We all know there's 0% chance
you don't end up believing this kook.
- How do you figure that?
- You want to believe him.
Just like you wanted to believe
it wasn't a weather balloon,
and you wanted to believe that it was
aliens that abducted Joe Piscopo.
That remains my theory until someone can
pinpoint the man's whereabouts.
We will not let our interest in UFOs
affect our judgment.
Good. 'cause you run around town
telling everybody an alien did this,
you're gonna look like
a couple of nut jobs.
- I can't hire nut jobs.
- Dad, would you relax, please?
Obviously we don't think
aliens are responsible.
Good.
Hold your horses!
Because if aliens did do this,
there'd be signs
of electrical disruptions.
Exactly!
What else would we see?
There would most definitely be
a visible ground disturbance.
Right.
So where do you guys want to start?
How'bout your terrace?
"Not Even Close... Encounters"
Timing: Psych Team
www.sous-titres.eu
All those people
who gave you, Dennis, and I flak
for believing in aliens in school...
Jeff Garrett, and that female Russian
exchange student who stole my wallet...
They're gonna eat their words
when this goes public.
I've got news, Gus.
Toby Shore was not abducted
by an alien.
What? But what about
the lights and grass and stuff?
It's time we learned
it's never the crazy suspect.
It wasn't a mummy.
It wasn't the devil.
- It wasn't even Bigfoot.
- Bigfoot? When did we suspect Bigfoot?
Missing school bus case.
There were bite marks in cushion.
The driver's seat
was pushed back 6 feet.
You're probably
right that it's not an alien,
but why don't we keep
investigating just to be sure.
Because my dad actually makes
a valid point.
It's gonna be hard to beobjective
when we're hoping that it's an alien.
- We can rub it in Jeff Darrett's face.
- No, we have to let that go.
So what are you saying,
that we pass on the case?
You're $1,200 balance
on your J.C. penney card
is not gonna pay for itself.
We'll just have to acknowledge
our mutual tendency
to think unreasonably
about this topic,
police ourselves accordingly.
- How?
- All right...
If one of us starts leaning
towards this theory,
- other one flicks him in the ear.
- That's an incredibly stupid idea.
You have exactly 3 seconds to beat it.
Three, two, one...
Now, how is that fair?
Let's find out what, if anything,
happened here last night.
May I call you Phil?
- I'd rather you didn't.
- Fair enough.
- How many beers did you drink?
- Just one.
Are you implying that I beer-goggled
an alien abduction?
- Happened to Gus last new years.
- I hit the white zin hard.
I promise you,
I was sober as a judge.
Let me ask you this.
If Toby wasn't abducted last night,
what happened to him?
- He left when you weren't looking.
- His car's still in the driveway.
Listen. When I went out to move it
this morning, it wouldn't start.
- The car's brand-new!
- Really?
You know, cars often lose
battery power
when they come in contact
with UFOs...
- Have you tried calling him?
- About 50 times.
- Just goes straight to voice mail.
- Maybe he's out of range.
- What was that for?
- You were implying he's in space.
No, I wasn't.
Yes, you were.
Where are you going?
Maybe we should talk to your neighbors
to see if they saw anything.
Good luck with that. The nearest one's
about half a mile away.
You gotta believe me.
I was just sitting at the desk,
and the whole house started to shake.
And then there were these lights,
and then this...
I was hearing this weird sound.
It sounded like...
No, it sounded nothing like that.
Really. Sorry.
I was actually trying
to make this sound.
That's it! That's it!
That's the sound.
- You weren't even close.
- I struggle with tone deafness.
Now do you believe me?
Before we answer that question,
we'll need to consult an expert.
Hi, we're looking
for Dennis Gogolack.
Get the hell out of here.
I don't believe it!
What an awesome surprise!
What are you guys doing?
It's been forever!
We didn't even recognize you,
now that you're...
What, not fat and nerdy?
It's okay. It's the truth.
I credit my personal trainer and lasiks.
- Losing the wizard's cloak also helped.
- Get inside here!
That's interesting.
Yeah, my wife's into stuff
that dangles.
Looks like the software business
has been good to you, Dennis.
Very good.
I'm Dennis' wife, Molly.
That was the creepiest "very"
that I've ever heard.
Babe, this is Shawn and gus.
Two good friends in grade school.
And now they're psychic detectives.
- How cool is that?
- Really cool. Nice meeting you guys.
Why didn't you tell me
that we were having friends over?
Actually, we didn't give Denny
much of a heads up.
Here's the thing...
We're investigating a case that may
have involved an alien abduction!
And being that your husband is
one of the foremost experts
on the topic...
I'm sorry, guys, I'm afraid
I'm not much of an expert anymore.
It's been 20 years
since I was into that stuff.
- Same here, bro, I mean...
- Beer.
Yeah, Denny is a total jock.
Guilty.
I'm guilty as charged.
- They did, like, a little...
- Explosion.
But you don't have to take off yet.
We've got some catching up to do.
Actually, we're under
a bit of a time crunch.
Let me just give you
a tour of the place.
I was actually gonna go hang
with the girls, though. Is that okay?
- Nice meeting you guys.
- Very nice.
Stop it.
Come check out my office!
All right.
I gotta say, Dennis, I'm surprised
that you, of all people,
outgrew the whole nerd thing.
Come on, you were
a class-three dungeon master
with your own set of custom
12-sided dice.
Let's go.
Oh, my... You are a closet nerd!
Literally.
You have a replica
of captain Adama's helmet
from the original
Battlestar Galactica?
And Levar Burton's glasses
from Star Trek?
Those aren't replicas. I got those
for 15 grand a pop at auction.
I have never been so motivated
to make money.
Wait till I show you
where the magic happens.
And I mean that literally.
There's another hidden room downstairs
- where I practice my magic tricks.
- Why all the secrecy?
When I first met Molly, it was clear
she was only into guys' guys.
That's what I pretended to be.
She ended up buying it.
I guess I've been pretending
ever since.
- Sounds exhausting.
- You have no idea.
Every day is a new challenge.
Whether it's trying
to draw blanks during Jeopardy,
or having to sneak in here
every time I want to track
some UFO activity
or sew a new renaissance faire costume.
Excellent stitch work, my liege.
The worst is when I'm around
Molly's friends' husbands.
To say inane stuff, like "beer me",
or, "yeah, I'd totally hit that."
- What, exactly, am I hitting?
- Most likely an attractive lady.
That's horrible.
- Is it really worth it, Den?
- Have you seen my wife?
We need your opinion
on this recording.
Gus is convinced it's a UFO.
Let's hear it.
Based on my research,
i'd say that's a voyager pod
from the Serpens dwarf galaxy...
- or bad new age music.
- But if you had to choose?
Wait a second.
If you guys could give me the time
and location,
I could check the sky activity.
I hacked into the national weather
service's computer a few years back,
and can access
their radar database whenever I want.
All right.
He lives at 25 Buckskin drive.
And it happened
around 11:00 at night.
- Nothing.
- What do you know.
Wait a minute.
You better try 10:44,
just to be safe.
You've gotta be kidding me.
What is... What is that?
You all right there, buddy?
She doesn't even know
that you're asthmatic?
And she never will.
All right, gus, I can't believe
i'm about to say this.
- I think Toby got abducted.
- So do I.
You do?
Sweet.
- Why are we both covering our ears?
- I don't know.
- Don't call Jeff Garrett.
- Roy needs to know that we believe him.
Right, but make sure you
tell him to keep it on the QT.
I know.
I'm standing here
just outside the home
of prominent local attorney
Roy Kessler, who's joined me now,
and has a rather shocking
announcement to make.
Last night I witnessed
aliens abduct a fellow co-worker.
- People are gonna think he's nuts.
- I can prove it,
thanks to the fine investigative work
being done by psychic detectives
Shawn Spencer
and Gurton Buster.
Gurton what?
I look like K.D. Lang.
What kind of proof
are we talking about?
Yes, Dad, we'll be right there.
Before you go off on us,
answer me this question.
Does that picture of me on the news
makes me look like I should be
singing Constant craving?
What'd I tell you
about taking this case?
We have hard evidence on this one.
Not to mention the fact that Roy Kessler
is a respected attorney
- not some crazy conspiracy theorist.
- Are you kidding?
That's exactly what he is!
Shawn, have you ever heard
of Budding textiles?
The company that had to fork out
millions for the chemical spill.
It got hundreds of people sick.
And who thinks it was done on purpose?
- Erin Brockovich.
- Roy Kessler.
He's preparing a lawsuit
against them.
- We didn't know that.
- I suppose you also didn't know
he's being heavily medicated
for anxiety.
He misses a dose, and he's prone
to psychotic episodes.
Last year,
he claims to have seen a panda
in his company's kitchen.
That's not crazy at all.
Pandas are big eaters.
Ten years ago, Kessler claimed...
You got it... He saw a UFO
- while on vacation.
- Saucer or sphere?
You wouldn't have missed this stuff
if you hadn't been blinded,
First of all, the only thing
we were blinded by is...
- Science!
- That never gets old.
Tell me this...
If toby wasn't abducted,
where the hell is he?
Right in there.
- This morning.
- He really kind of...
He took a cab
to his parents' house that night
after his car wouldn't start.
Turned off his phone,
and he slept in.
Nice going, man.
I remember him muttering all this stuff
about lights and ships.
I thought it was just Roy being Roy.
And then I turned on the TV today
and heard his insane theory.
- I wouldn't call it insane.
- Let it go.
I tried everything I could
to get him to take his meds.
I would even pick them up
at the pharmacy for him
and bring them to him directly.
Man, he's gonna hear it
at the office on monday.
Actually, your firm just suspended him
until he completes a month's stay
in a mental health facility.
Who's gonna get all his cases?
We're available.
Isn't that right, Mr. Spencer?
Gus here is a whiz at legal zoom,
and my cousin has a personal injury
law firm called Accidentes.
- Heard of it?
- No, I haven't.
You will.
Good work, people.
Papa bear.
You know what, I really don't appreciate
being snickered at.
Never again are we
investigating something
related to one
of our childhood obsessions.
- What if there's a pop rocks murder?
- That is the exception.
Excuse me, Spencer.
Quick question.
How does it feel to be so wrong
that you are now...
a walking joke?
Just like you, minus the
kind boots and the soft eyes.
This is really a big moment for me.
I may even do a little dance.
Oh, yes, I will.
All right, that's it, Gus.
We are gonna find out what happened,
and we are gonna clear our good names.
Let me ask you something.
If you were an up and comer,
and you were abducted by aliens...
- Because that happens.
- Would you tell anyone?
I know I wouldn't,
because they would think I was nuts.
Like I do right now.
That dude was not abducted.
You have 3s to come up with a better
theory to explain all this weirdness.
- Three, two, one...
- That's my trick.
Explain the radar, the recording,
the indentation on the lawn.
It was a plane on the radar.
Someone cranking yanni on the recorder.
The indentation could be lots of things.
How do you explain the three strange
markings on Toby's arm?
- You saw those?
- Of course. I didn't have to do this.
Are you mocking my "it's a clue" face?
Do it again.
I don't look like that.
You're a bastard.
You know that abductees often have
strange markings on their skin.
So do I when I don't use
enough sunscreen... Now come here.
- Stand still, let me flick your ear.
- He was abducted.
- Was not.
- Yes, he was.
- Wasn't infinity!
If you're gonna act like a child,
we must bring in a 3d party to settle.
Fine. Who?
He was abducted. The markings and
the other details have me convinced.
Why would I tag in a guy
with a custom-made ewok costume?
What's the name
of that law firm he works at?
- Wilcox, Kessler, and something.
- Hold on. What are you doing?
Getting his work address
so you can spy on this guy.
You have to see if he's exhibiting
the other telltale abduction signs.
You know this.
Paranoia!
- Compulsion to travel to unknown areas.
- Suicidal tendencies.
Spewing nonsense with authority.
Wait, that's you guys.
You mock, but I'm still waiting
on a better theory from you.
All right.
It was Toby.
Why did he tilt his head and squint?
- It's his "I got a clue" face.
- Think at it, Gust.
Toby knew hewill inherit all of Roy's
cases if he got him out of the way.
So he arranged for him to have one
of his psychotic episodes.
How?
I would even pick the meds up from the
pharmacy and bring them to him directly.
By tampering with his meds.
And you know what,
it worked like a charm.
Roy goes nuts. The next day,
Toby's a major player at the firm.
- Let's go.
- Where?
Well, we're gonna take Dennis' advice,
do a little spying on our boy.
What can I do?
You could lend us
some sweet disguises.
Fellas, tell me what you need.
- I have never felt cooler.
- You've never looked cooler.
Dennis is gonna have to pry this helmet
of my cold, dead noggin.
There's Toby.
Dude, he's sweating and shaking.
Do you saw clues this time?
Paranoia is one of the
telltale signs of an abduction.
It's the sign of a guy
feeling guilty.
Stop saying stupid things.
You're a disgrace to those glasses.
He's bolting, Gus!
He's wandering to unknown areas.
This helmet is not made for running!
I should have borrowed Charlton Heston's
scarf from soylent green.
I can't see
out these glasses, Shawn.
Where'd he go?
We lost him.
Son of a...
Hello?
Is this Shawn Spencer?
Toby?
Help me. They're following me.
Whoa, whoa.
Calm down, man.
- Who's following you?
- I don't know.
it's the black dude from star trek and
some white guy in a ridiculous helmet.
Which is your opinion.
Where are you?
Listen to me.
Roy Kessler was telling the truth.
I told you!
- OK. You need to come meet us.
- I can't. It's too dangerous.
Meet me in an hour in front
of the Lansdowne hotel.
Lansdowne. Got it.
Dude, did you just break
Dennis' helmet?
Well, it clearly wasn't made
for running, Gus.
You...
Was that scarf worth
going back to Dennis'?
Is soylent green people?
- Let's go get this confession.
- The admission that he was abducted.
Let's start
with the non-batcrap angle.
You heard him say
Kessler was telling the truth.
Gus, you're really putting me
in a tough spot here.
You don't think I want to be the guy
riffing on how aliens abducted Toby,
and what they did to him
on board the mother ship?
They placed an embryo in his stomach
that will hatch out his ear in 12 days.
I can't do it! Someone has to hold
the sanity bag in this partnership, and
I miss the days
when it used to be you.
Shawn, he's exhibiting
all the telltale signs.
Paranoia, check!
Nervousness, check!
Suicidal tendencies.
Check.
Hey, Jules.
What's the word?
Well, we just found out
that Toby wired
all of the money from his bank account,
about 500 grand,
to a charity
an hour before his death.
We haven't found a note yet,
but it's looking like suicide.
I don't know about that.
Don't you find strange that a junior
lawyer has that kind of account balance?
Not to mention the fact he was
Roy Kessler's former co-worker.
Ooh, no, my senses are telling me
there is more to this.
- Much more.
- Settle.
Let me guess. You think
the Loch Ness monster did it.
What are you two doing here?
- Came to get going on the Shore case.
- Why? You're not being hired on it.
- You can't be serious.
- Shawn, I warned you.
I can't stick my neck out for 2 guys
viewed as the village idiots.
Village idiots?
Who here thinks that?
Dirty Larry!
Sorry.
Look, Gus and I might be
a lot of things. Handsome, chiseled.
- Smart.
- Urbane.
Whatever that means.
But not idiots!
I'm sorry, guys.
My bad.
That's all me. But
Who needs a fan this big?
- Leave now!
- Fine.
- Fine. We're audi.
- All right...
Smooth move!
Come on, give a brother some credit.
Let's see what we got here.
Nada.
Recipe for Juliet's weird cleanse.
- Preliminary coroner's report.
- What does it say?
Apparently they found
a strange object in Toby's...
Stomach.
- Embryo.
- Come on.
Woodrow!
Hey, boys.
You have got to try these French fries.
They're killer.
- We ate, thanks.
- For the last time.
We need to talk to you about the autopsy
you did on Toby Shore.
- What about it?
- We know you're hiding something.
Fine.
- I stole his watch.
- You did what?
Nothing.
Hey, how'bout some fried clams?
We want to know what
you found in his stomach.
Telling you that
will get me in trouble.
More or less than you'd get in
for looting corpses?
A flash drive.
Now, when you say flash drive,
is that coroner code for an alien embryo
- that hatches in the ear?
- No, that's "starfish".
This was a legitimate 4 gigabyte
flash drive. There were...
I take notes...
abrasions on his lungs,
which implied
he swallowed it
moments before his death.
Interesting.
And the markings on his left arm?
That was a birth mark.
Where is this flash drive now?
It's with Detective Lassiter.
Great. Thanks, Woody.
You stay creepy.
You know I will.
You know, Spencer,
the minute you refused to hire
that smarmy, fortune-telling kid
of yours,
you officially made it off
my crap list.
Here. See?
You actually have a crap list?
I like to keep track of people
who've wronged me over the years.
You know, people like
your son, my mother...
Olympia freakin' Dukakis!
You disturb me.
Do I?
Welcome back, Henry.
But I've gotta say it is really nice to
be able to do some real police work
without worrying about
your son interfering.
What the hell?
Can I get somebody
from I.T. Over here?
Dobson, come help me out!
I'm not comfortable
hacking a police computer.
It's his personal one. Which reminds me
to check the Internet search history.
All right.
Let's see.
"Grenadefancy.com,
squirrelassassins. Com."
And...
That's gross.
That man needs Jesus.
Let's see what's on
that flash drive, shall we?
Sorry, Gus, doesn't look like
a blueprint for an alien fertility lab.
Shocker!
It'sa bunch of legal documents
related to Budding textiles.
Kessler was working on that case.
He believed the chemical spill
was done on purpose.
That is crazy.
- I've got something.
- We know.
Damn, I've really gotta
stop doing that.
Denny, where are you?
Quick, get out of here! Go!
Denny? Denny?
One minute, babe.
What's going on in here?
- Uh, you know, guy stuff.
- Steak.
You can't host a football party
in your office.
Come on, Taylor just got a safety!
Sweet!
I'll be right there, babe.
Bye, Molly.
- What's a safety?
- Really?
Dennis, why don't you blow off
this party and come with us?
Where are we going?
I'm not sure, but it involves
a small town and some potential danger.
Oh, that sounds cool.
- How much danger?
- But I can't, man.
Molly would kill me!
Dennis, you're never gonna know what
it feels like to be a normal guy
as long as you're pretending
to be something that you're not.
Trust me, he knows.
Come on.
It's time for you to get out there
and experience some real-life,
non-virtual adventure.
He's right. It's time to
come out of the nerd closet.
I'm sorry, guys, I just can't.
I really like having sex
with my wife.
Don't say it.
What's wrong with you, man?
Now tell me
what the hell we're doing here.
Guess who's now
the owner of this home
along with the 700 similar ones
that make up this tiny town.
Shawn, if you say "us,"
I'm gonna punch you.
Budding textiles.
It's the last one they purchased.
Why would Budding want a bunch of
crappy houses on poisoned land?
Here's a better question... what is
the world's coolest truck doing here?
It's a decepticon.
It's not a decepticon, Gus.
It was made in Fresno.
Whatever it is, I highly suggest
we do not touch it.
- The keys were here. What should I do?
- Not start it.
- It's not that easy.
- Actually, it is.
When Toby said
that Roy Kessler was telling the truth,
he didn't mean an abduction.
He meant the lawsuit against Budding.
That makes no sense.
Why would they intentionally
spill chemicals?
- To get people to leave.
- What?
In all the ridiculous science classes
over the years,
did you ever learn about
hydrocarbons?
Of course I did. The organic compounds
found mainly in crude oil.
If there's a high percentage of them,
does that mean that there's oil?
You'd have to check using a machine
that sends vibrations
into the earth.
- We're in one of those machines!
- Why must you always touch stuff?
It stopped shaking.
I feel like a bobblehead.
- Idiot.
- Try it.
- No.
- Get in on the bit.
- I don't want to.
- It's fun!
you look ridiculous.
Think about it. It all makes sense.
Budding figured out that
this was a gold mine.
So what does he do? He orchestrates
a chemical spill to drive everyone away.
That way he wouldn't have to share.
Exactly. Which, I imagine, dwarfs the
cost of lawsuits and land purchases.
- And Kessler was onto all of this.
- Which sort of freaks me out.
Why?
Because it makes me wonder what else
he was telling the truth about.
I don't want to get probed, Gus!
What are you worried about?
You're the one who's less exotic!
Get in here!
Well, boys...
Start talking.
About what, exactly? How'bout a story?
Would you like to hear a story?
- Please. I always enjoy a good one.
- All right.
Once upon a time there was
this greedy ceo.
- Think, what, Stephen Lang?
- "Esque."
He wanted to kill this lawyer, because
the lawyer was on the verge of ruining
his plan. But he couldn't,
because the lawyer had
prepared a legitimate case against him.
Hot start.
Please continue.
He figured out that if he could
make the lawyer look wacko,
the case would be dismissed as
some nutty conspiracy theory. But how?
And ten years ago,
Kessler claimed to have seen,
you got it, a ufo!
Light bulb. He would convince the lawyer
he'd witnessed an abduction.
He already had this fancy copter,
so he add extra lighting, pump some
Enya b-sides through the sound system,
and figure out
how to trip the electricity.
- He most likely used an EMP device.
- What is that, a pregnancy test?
Doesn't make any sense.
Let me tell the story.
EMT, that's electrical pulses.
There's a fine line between being
knowledgeable and arrogant.
Enough!
I'm on the edge of my seat here.
Right. Well, it all worked like a charm,
with one exception.
See, the young lawyer that he paid
500 gs to to set up this guy,
had a change of heart once he came
across the dismissed-case file.
But it was still
just a minor mishap for our ceo
because he is a problem solver.
- I like his style.
- Yeah.
And he was in the clear
until he came across
two young go-getters,
and they were onto everything.
Who he then proceeded to let go
because they promised
not to tell a soul.
They swore.
Because that's stronger than a promise.
That's not gonna happen.
It's not?
And to think I only
picked you up for trespassing.
Take 'em out back.
Don't worry, I texted my dad.
The cops will be here any minute.
- Who is it?
- Messenger service.
I have a delivery
for you to sign.
- What's he doing here?
- I don't know.
- Let's see some I.D.
- Yeah, yeah. Sure.
Holy...
and he spent the rest
of his miserable life in jail. The end.
My lip!
- Dude, how'd you find us?
- I cloned Shawn's cell phone earlier.
I think I did some real damage
to my pre-molars.
It's OK.
You looked like a badass until you
clocked yourself in the face.
- You needed this, man!
- Hands in the air!
You, hands in the air!
Put those down!
Put 'em down!
No, Lassie, don't do it!
No, wait! Not him!
He didn't need that.
- I see it now.
- Right?
I look like I finished
a set at Lilith fair.
All right, let me have it.
I have better things to do with my time
than gloat about being a hero.
And the fact that you caused
one of our friends to whiz himself.
I'm here for police advice.
- Really?
- No, it's boogie time.
Is there ever
a high road between you guys?
Jerks.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't "ignore
your son's urgent text" man.
Good thing you told Juliet,
and she took it seriously.
I thought you were still goofing around.
Your credibility hasn't been too high.
That's no excuse.
You can make it up to us
by approving these expenses.
What? $7,000 in dental work
for Dennis Gogolack?
- And a new pair of underpants.
- 22 packs of razzles?
Season tickets to the Los Angeles sparks
of the WNBA?
Are you serious?
- As a Rebecca Lobo set shot.
- Glass!
I'll think about it.
In the meantime,
chief Vick wants you
take a look at this counterfeit thing.
Oh, look at that! Now you want us.
Well, guess what. It's gonna cost you.
How much?
- Two grand.
- 1,500.
Sorry, heroes don't work
for less than two large.
Fine.
Sweet.
Now can we see you make it official?
Yeah, just put it right in the old, uh,
bibbity-bobbity.
What? Thanks, dad.
We'll start tomorrow.
Why not now?
Because we've got to visit
some friends.
Oh, my God, Shawn,
you look like Billie Jean king.
- Detonate the pillar of Attu!
- I know how to play!
I've gotta say,
I can't thank you enough
for clearing my name.
I don't know how I'll ever repay you.
We do have a coroner buddy who's in
some hot water over a stolen watch.
- Consider him represented.
- Thanks.
This experience
has taught me a really important lesson
when it comes to
some of the crazy stuff
that I often see.
That there's an explanation?
No, it's that the eyes never lie.
Did I tell you guys I once saw bigfoot?
What?
- You think I'm nuts.
- Male or female?
- Was he driving a school bus?
- No...
babe... Hey.
Where am I standing right now?
Denny...
What's going on?
You know, it's dudes being dudes.
Cigars.
So listen...
There's something I need to tell you.
I'm not actually a jock.
I'm a giant nerd.
- I don't know what to say.
- Are you angry?
No, I'm pissed.
Do you know that I've seen
every single episode
of the original Battlestar Galactica,
like, 50 times?
I never told you 'cause I thought
you'd look down on that stuff.
You've gotta be kidding.
No. What do you think I was watching
while you went away
on that business conference?
I wasn't at a business conf...
I was at Comic-Con!
No way.
I wanted to go to that!
I love you.
She just got even hotter.
What?