The Honking
Notify his survivors.
B-E-N-D-E-R
Bender
B-E-N-D-E-R, Bender
Saying B-E-N-D!
Mail call!
Amy, your designer lingerie catalog.
Fry, Sadie's Bra Parade.
And Leela, Bulk Underpants Outlet.
You buy once,
you're on the list forever.
And for Bender. . . .
A black-bordered envelope.
Someone you know must have died.
I hope it was one of my enemies.
Those guys suck.
Oh, no! My uncle Vladimir!
I'm sorry.
When's the funeral?
Tomorrow, at the family castle.
Followed by the reading of his will.
Well, I'm rich. Goodbye, losers,
whom I've always hated!
Come on! It'll be fun.
Pardon me, my good simpleton.
Could you take us to yon castle?
Some say unholy things
happen up there.
For example, all of us say that.
Superstitious robot mumbo jumbo.
Mumbo, perhaps. Jumbo, perhaps not.
With your science,
are you closer to understanding. . .
. . .the mystery of how a robot
walks or talks?
Yes, you idiot! The circuit diagram
is here on the inside of your case.
I choose to believe what I was
programmed to believe.
I will go this far and no further.
And so we commend
Vladimir's remains to the earth.
Filings to filings. Rust to rust.
To my loyal butler, You There,
for decades of service. . .
. . .I leave a pittance to be paid
in 20 installments. . .
. . .of 1 /20th of a pittance each.
To my lazy, spoiled son, Tandy, who
never learned the value of a dollar. . .
. . .I leave my entire
$1 0 million fortune.
-Is that a lot?
-To my loving nephew, Bender. . .
. . .if he's not responsible
for my death, I leave my castle.
Let's stay there tonight!
On condition that he spend
one night in it.
Oh, man! There's always a catch.
I get a good vibe from this place.
Nice long dinner table. . .
. . .quiet, well-behaved spiders,
graveyard-adjacent.
Yep, it's gonna be--
-What is it?
-That painting's eyes are watching me!
Motor eye sensors attached
to motion detectors.
So does my butt, but I don't frame it
and put it on the wall. Although. . . .
-What's that?
-I don't know, but it's infectious.
No doubt about it.
This place is haunted.
Don't be silly, man.
The last ghost died 200 years ago.
The last human ghost.
But robot ghosts?
"01 01 1 001 01 . " What does it mean?
It's just gibberish.
" 1 01 001 1 01 0?! "
Uncle Vladimir!
Come, Bender. You'll like being dead.
They said that about being alive!
Join us.
Just as I suspected. These robots were
buried in improperly shielded coffins.
Their programs leaked into the wiring
through this old modem. . .
. . .allowing them to project themselves
as holograms.
Of course! It was so obvious!
That sequence of words I said
made perfect sense.
We really should tell Bender
there's nothing to be afraid of.
Bender, wake up!
He's okay!
Quick, does anyone have any liquor?
Bender, what happened?
Somebody ran me over!
And not with a normal hover car.
It crept along on round rubber feet,
like a wolf!
Poor Bender. Seeing things.
You've been drinking too much.
Or too little.
Anyway, not the right amount.
Maybe he has. Look at these tracks.
I think Bender may be
telling the truth.
Bender, you look awful.
I prescribe makeup.
Here! It just so happens I have
my Mary Kay sample case.
I just need sleep. I had nightmares
about cars running people over.
Many dream of a fresh new look.
And Mary Kay can make
those dreams come true.
Look! They found those same
rubbery tracks in New New York.
A hit-and-run
by the robot porno theater.
Robot porno theater?
I was in that general area last night.
Whoever ran me down out on the moors
followed me back here!
No one's trying to run you over.
Stop being a big hallucinating baby.
Yeah? Could a big hallucinating baby
do this?
I'm scared!
I don't know which I like more,
smashing cars or faces.
Lucky you won't decide tonight.
Come on. It's church tomorrow.
Did you hear something?
It was probably just
a golden marmoset.
Don't sound like no golden marmoset
I ever heard.
Made it.
So, what are you wearing tomorrow?
Where. . .? What the. . .?
Transmission fluid? Where have I been?
What happened?
Gets out of here, youse lousy bum!
-Please, I'm scared.
-We all are. It's the human condition.
That's why I put on this tough guy
facade. Now beat it!
I passed out around midnight,
much earlier than usual.
When I woke up, I found these
in my chest cabinet.
Relax. You were probably just
shooting big fuzzy craps.
No! I think I may have hurt someone.
Lord, I'm on the verge
of a nervous meltdown.
You're scaring me.
You're going wacko!
Right. I need professional help.
And damn the expense!
Damn the expense!
You have nothing to worry about.
Except a nightmarish life
of unremitting horror!
For you see, you are a were-car.
A were-car?
The car that ran you down
was a were-car.
It beamed the virus to you
through its demonic headlights!
That's crazy.
Yes. So crazy that it must be true!
Each midnight,
when your clock resets to 0. . .
. . .your hardware reconfigures
into a murderous car.
I can't keep running people over.
I'm not famous enough
to get away with it. Help me!
Yes. But you must be willing
to pay a terrible price.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Follow me.
Based on this ancient
"read me" file. . .
. . .your only hope is to destroy
the first were-car.
I'm with you.
In its death throes, the car will beam
out the virus' uninstall program. . .
. . .ridding you of the curse.
Otherwise, I can never die?
Sure you can die! You want to die?
No! There's still too many things
I don't own!
Then live on. Forever cursed!
Each night, your attacks will
become more gruesome. . .
. . .until one dark night you are doomed
to kill your dearest friend.
I wouldn't want to be me.
Now go. Go!
Could one of you just--?
Ah, forget it. I'll just sleep here.
There. No rampaging for you tonight.
What about welding everyone
except me to the wall?
Just relax. Tomorrow we'll pry
you down, have breakfast. . .
. . .and go hunt down
that ancient evil.
It'll be a rich, full day.
I'm gonna go make my dinners
for the next month and freeze them.
-Bender, no!
-Fry, stay back!
You jerk! I thought I was
your best friend!
What kind of two-timing kill-mobile
are you?
He's supposed to murder his closest
friend, which was me.
But he went for you, not even trying
to second-degree-murder me.
Could you help me?
Bender crushed my foot.
Stop rubbing it in!
Oh, God! Fry, I'm so glad to see you.
Did I hurt you?
Not physically. Why not ask
your new best friend Leela?
-I tried to run you over?
-It was very sweet of you.
It doesn't mean anything.
I have love enough for two.
Words. Nothing but sweet words turning
into bitter orange wax in my ears.
Enough with the feelings.
To cure Bender, we've got to hunt down
the original were-car.
-Cursed. Got it.
-Whatever.
-The tracks lead here.
-Thanks, eagle eye.
It's daylight.
He should be in robot form.
But be careful.
Many robots are stupid and violent.
I wish I was stupid and violent. We'd
see what's what. I'd pound him till--
Get ye to your houses,
ye ignorant villagers!
We aren't ignorant villagers.
We're sophisticated New New Yorkers.
Whup his butt!
Stop! What are ye doing?
Whaling on the original were-car,
which is you, jerk!
-Ye think me be he?
-Sl.
Nee. I mean no.
I was given the curse
many a year ago. . .
. . .while on a bird watching trip
to The Arctic.
I was attacked
by a vicious motorized sled.
The natives called it
the abominable snowmobile.
It's true. I ran over that
bird-watching jerk and 1 00 others.
Even my best friend
from aromatherapy school.
I once had a best friend who liked
to smell things with me.
Alas, I'm not the original were-car.
I got the curse while taking a class
from a famous robot actor.
You know him as...
... Calculon.
O fate most cruel,
would that my acting skills. . .
. . .might avail me a sword
to slay this wretched curse.
-Let's kick him!
-Let me explain.
It all began one fateful night
1 000 years ago.
Whoa, whoa! You're 1 000 years old?
Your bio says you're 27.
Lies! I change my identity
and appearance. . .
. . .every decade to avoid suspicion.
I was all of history's
great acting robots.
Acting Unit 0.8, Thespo-mat,
David Duchovny.
Are you the first were-car or not?
No. But you're near
the end of your search.
I was attacked
by the original were-car.
Give us a name, MacButt!
The year was 201 9, and I was just
a lowly roboton working. . .
...in an automotive research lab.
I was working on Project Satan...
...a savage car built from the evil
parts of the world's most evil cars.
The steering wheel from Hitler's car,
the signal from Charles Manson 's VW.
-Knight Rider's windshield wipers.
-Knight Rider wasn't evil.
His windshield wipers were.
It didn't come up in the show.
Only after finishing Project Satan...
...did they discover they had made
a horrible mistake.
For you see, it was pure evil.
What happened to Project Satan?
It's either in Paris
or much more likely...
...still in the abandoned
automotive lab.
Distract the were-car. . .
. . .and I'll kill it by plugging its
exhaust pipe with this silver potato.
There it is.
It looks so unhappy.
Excuse me, are you Project Satan?
Don't be afraid.
We know what you are.
You do?
Would you like us to put you
out of your misery?
Misery? What misery?
I love killing people!
Squishing them till their organs
squirt out like chunky mustard!
Look, everyone loves killing people,
but I don't wanna hurt my friends.
Oh, no! It's midnight!
Hey, this is starting
to feel pretty good.
Fry, distract him!
Hey, Project Satan! Over here!
I'm a blind pedestrian. 20 points!
Oh, no! There's no exhaust pipe!
That's right, thanks to
Ed Begley Jr.'s electric motor. . .
. . .the most evil propulsion system
ever conceived!
Take whichever one you want.
Oh, boy! I feel like a car
in a candy store!
Yes! He chose me!
He's trying to kill me!
Leela, I'm so happy!
Oh, thanks, Bender.
Too tight! Too tight!
Bender, you're cured!
But what happened to Fry?
I must have killed him!
He's my best friend and I killed him!
I never felt so empty inside.
Bender, I'm alive!
You didn't hurt me at all!
But I know you wanted to.
And that's what matters.
Here's to you.
That's my last beer, you bastard!
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you too, buddy.
I'll kill you too.
www.tvsubtitles.net