What are you doing?
The DJ is really good, huh?
Yeah. Too bad
she's not really good at P3.
Right. Sorry.
Focus, we are here
on business, not pleasure.
Okay. I know, I know.
But don't you think
you're overreacting a little?
No, I don't. This club has become
the hottest thing in town,
and I'd like to know
what they're doing that I am not.
Well, P3 is still doing great.
Not as great as it used to be,
thanks to me.
Well, Piper, you're having a baby.
Your priorities have changed.
Yeah, well, haven't you heard?
Women can have careers
and babies now.
It's been in all the papers.
Are those women trying
to save the world from demons too?
Oh, for God's sakes,
people, get a room.
- Piper.
- Paige.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, you know, just hanging out.
You couldn't hang out at our club?
What, and miss this DJ?
Come on.
This is my other sister, Piper,
and her husband, Leo. This is Dave.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah, you too, mate.
I didn't know there was a Dave.
Oh, we've only been hanging out
for, like, three weeks.
Weeks?
Here you go.
Oh, hi, Piper.
Hey. Hey. Wow, you're up late.
- What are you doing here?
- Right back at you.
- Dave, how about I buy you a drink?
- Yeah.
- I've got one, thanks.
- That's not gonna be enough.
I thought you were working tonight.
Yeah, well, I mean,
actually, I'm working here.
You know, I thought
that guys could help me
with my advice
to other guys, you know?
And that guy over there
with the dimples.
Hi. Yeah, huge help. Yeah.
See, yeah,
I don't know what bugs me more.
The fact that you guys are here,
or that you're here without me.
Oh, we just didn't think
it would be good for the baby.
You know, all the noise
and the people.
Yeah, I know. But sometimes
it's good for the mommy to get out.
Okay, so you would have
wanted to come?
No, but that is beside the point.
- You're a very confusing woman.
- It's all right. Hey, it's no big deal.
You guys, I'll see you at home.
Oh, Piper.
- Still think this is a good idea?
- Well, you know Piper.
She won't slow down
unless someone slows her down.
I just don't want to do anything
to add to her stress.
You seem stressed.
Arnon, you scared me.
What are you doing out here?
Door is locked, so I thought
I'd practice drawing while I waited.
Good.
Not really.
I don't know, I just can't seem
to make it work.
I've done everything you said,
tried to focus...
Then you're not trying hard enough.
You have a special gift, Kevin.
A very special gift.
And if you're to master it,
you have to believe in it fully.
You draw to see it better,
but it'll never be real,
not unless you make it real
in your mind's eye.
Make it real, Kevin.
Make it come to life.
Oh, my God, it worked.
Okay, how do we make it go away?
Now it's time to make
that hero of yours real too.
To take care of your little problem.
And then, take care of mine.
Yo.
What are you doing here, fool?
- I'm just trying to get home, Kaz.
- Listen.
We've had this conversation.
This is where I do my business.
All right?
And I don't like getting bothered.
Turn around.
It's gonna cost you.
Hey.
What is this?
Is this me?
Getting my ass kicked by you?
Catch you next time, little man.
All right, that's enough.
Let's get out of here.
What is this, Halloween?
Who the hell are you, fool?
I'm The Aggressor.
The Aggressor?
Well, whoever you are,
you just made a serious mistake.
Behind you.
- Morning.
- Did you just get home?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Pickles, hot fudge sauce and mustard?
Are you seriously eating that?
That was the plan.
Wait a minute,
you didn't come home all night?
No, Mom. Why?
I must be going nuts.
Because I could have sworn I saw you
when I walked past your room.
Was it about 2:30?
Was I half-naked?
Paige, what's going on?
- Nothing. I don't want to bother you.
- You're not bothering me.
Why does everybody think
they're bothering me?
I'm not bothered.
What's the matter?
Well, I was sort of
messing around with Dave, and...
- Messing around?
- Yeah, having "sex."
This is why I don't want to
talk to you about this.
It's weird talking to a pregnant lady
about sex anyway.
Well, Paige, how do you think
I got pregnant?
I don't want to know that either.
Anyway, so we were doing,
you know,
and I was about to, you know,
and suddenly I orbed out upstairs.
Oh, my God. You didn't?
- Did he notice?
- No, thank God.
I orbed back in
before the lights came back on.
- Talk about embarrassing.
- Forget embarrassing.
Paige, you could have had
some serious explaining to do.
Well, I didn't plan on
orbing out, Piper.
It wasn't exactly my particular goal
at the moment.
Okay, so why do you think
this is happening?
I mean, is he not
getting the job done?
No, he's getting the job done fine.
I think I like him a lot.
And, I mean, other than Glen,
he's the first guy I've been with
since I found out I was a witch.
I think I'm so busy protecting
this big old secret of ours that
I guess I can't really
let my guard down.
How'd you do it?
Marry an angel.
Leo?
Sorry. I'm sorry. Are you all right?
Been orbing long, have we?
Hey, I'm a little nervous.
Leo, what happened?
We heard a crash.
He missed.
Huh, who's the critic?
This is Ramus. He's an Elder.
An Elder? Really?
I thought you told us
he wasn't coming till tonight.
Told us? Nobody told me anything.
Leo?
We didn't want you
to worry about demonic threats
until it was absolutely necessary.
What threats?
Well, I suppose this will have to do.
Okay.
What are you two up to?
It was Phoebe's idea.
We were just trying to make things
a little easier, that's all.
- Relieve some stress.
- Well, stop it,
because it's pissing me off.
I'm pregnant, not terminal.
So, what...? What is he doing here?
Ramus is retiring.
He came down to pass on his powers
to a new Elder.
- So?
There isn't a demon alive
who wouldn't love to have his powers.
So the Elders want you to protect him
in case there's an attack.
Why couldn't he just orb out?
Because my powers are mental,
young lady, not physical.
You'd think a charge of yours would
know something as basic as that.
- Nothing wrong with his hearing.
- No, just his attitude.
Piper. Little respect.
For crying out loud.
So who is this new Elder,
and when does he get here?
We don't know who he is.
All we know is that the transfer
must take place
during tonight's equinox,
or else I will lose my powers forever.
So we're just supposed to
sit around here and wait?
Yes. Unfortunately.
Arnon?
- I was getting worried about you.
- Arnon, you scared me.
Sorry.
Where's The Aggressor?
He's...
He's gone.
- I ripped up the drawing.
- You what?
He killed a guy.
Arnon, he killed Kaz.
Isn't that why you wanted me
to help you create your superhero?
- No, not to kill. I never wanted that.
- He was a bad guy, wasn't he?
Just like Ramus is.
I'm not drawing him again.
Arnon, I'm sorry.
We had a deal.
I help you, you help me, remember?
Now, I need The Aggressor
to take out Ramus.
To rid him of his powers.
Why can't you just
take him out yourself?
I told you, I only have the ability to
sense great powers, not possess them.
That's how I found you,
that's how I'll find Ramus.
Now, help me
do the right thing, Kevin.
Bring your superhero back to life,
before somebody else loses theirs.
- Those are all life and death?
- Well, not literally.
At least, not most of them.
What am I supposed to do?
I can't keep up, they just keep coming.
What can you do?
Answer two or three a day,
ignore the rest.
- You can't help everybody.
- Yeah, that's the problem.
I got it. Thanks.
- Phoebe Halliwell.
- So, what do you say
to an overbearing younger sister
who's treating her pregnant
older sister like a porcelain doll?
- "Thank you"?
- How about, "knock it off"?
That's probably better advice.
Are you mad at me?
No, not if you come home
and babysit Ramus.
Oh, sweetie, I can't. I've got
a gazillion letters that I have to get to.
Well, "Bored in Berkeley" can wait.
I've got DJs to audition.
No, these are
a lot more serious than that.
You're not supposed to be
going to work, anyway.
- Phoebe.
- Can't I worry about my niece?
Okay, look, what about Paige?
Can she come?
Apparently not.
She's with Dave,
trying desperately not to orb.
Oh, for goodness' sakes, okay.
Well, what about...?
- Cole.
- Cole, watching an Elder?
I really don't think that's a good idea.
No. He...
Okay. I'll be home
as soon as I can, okay?
- Phoebe.
- Whatever it is, I don't have time.
No, you don't understand.
This isn't about us.
- I need your help.
- Yeah, who doesn't?
You ever heard of Edward Miller,
the slumlord?
He took millions from the city
in renovation moneys,
but instead of fixing the buildings,
he's kicking the tenants out?
Well, how is he able to do that?
I don't know, but that's why I'm trying
to get an injunction to stop him.
Oh, really? You?
What's with all the red tape?
Why don't you just
turn him into a fountain pen?
Believe me, I'm tempted.
But I've decided I'm not gonna
use my powers, no matter what.
- Since when?
- Since I tried strangling you with them.
I'll be working from home
for the rest of the day.
Phoebe. Listen to me,
this is legitimate.
These people are
gonna be evicted tonight
and I can't get an injunction
until tomorrow.
I mean, if you could just
threaten to expose him in your paper
or maybe even
leak it to a TV station...
I don't have enough time to help my
readers with their problems right now.
But we're talking about
whole families here.
Kids, babies, with nowhere to go.
Look.
It's great that you want to help.
I really do, but I can't.
I am powerless
to do anything right now.
You may be a lot of things,
but powerless isn't one of them.
Was he talking about Edward Miller,
the slumlord?
Actually, you did get some letters
from some of his tenants.
- Really? I haven't seen them.
- No, you haven't gotten to them.
Did you?
No.
I didn't think so.
It's not you, Dave.
Trust me, it's me.
You keep saying that, Paige,
but what does that mean?
It's complicated.
Well, you're in luck.
Because I happen to specialize
in complicated.
Come on, talk to me.
You won't scare me away.
Promise?
It's just that I'm...
...really different than other girls.
I know.
That's what I like about you.
No, I mean really different.
More than you
could possibly imagine.
Okay.
So you're all right with that?
All right with what?
- Forget it.
- Forget what?
Look, I'm not a freak.
It's not like I have a tail or something.
Paige, I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Just forget I said anything.
- But you didn't say anything.
You know, I think
I got closer that time.
You wanna try again?
Leo?
Leo!
- What are you doing?
- Would you mind?
My meditation
requires peace and quiet.
Well, then you're in
the wrong house, pal.
- Have you seen my husband?
- He's upstairs.
Okay, could you tell him
that I'll be at P3?
He can watch over you
until Phoebe shows up.
I'll tell him no such thing.
It is your job to protect me, not his.
Those are the rules.
Little history lesson:
I'm not a big fan of your rules.
In fact, I take pride
in breaking them.
I know, you've been
a real pain over the years.
Oh, you mean marrying Leo?
Yes, I know you Elders
were dead set against that.
Not all of us.
Some of us foresaw
the special baby you'd be carrying.
Still, that doesn't...
What do you mean, "special"?
- Hi.
- Wait, what do you mean?
Don't get excited,
I can't stay long.
- You'll see.
- Hi.
It is an honour and a pleasure
to meet an Elder, sir. Really.
Okay, but I gotta go.
I'm sorry, but if I don't
stop that dirt-bag landlord...
What's the matter?
Someone's coming.
For me.
- Ramus.
- Hurry, freeze him.
Paige!
Damn, I was so close.
I don't wanna hurt you.
I just want him.
Yeah, well, forget about it.
Ramus!
Who was that masked man?
Okay, we should look under...
Actually, I have no idea
what to look under.
Well, he had a great big giant
A on his chest, how about A?
I'm telling you, you're not gonna
find him in the Book of Shadows.
At a comic-book convention maybe.
- He could still be a demon.
- Paige, he was in tights.
Ramus is safe,
but he can't stay there long.
Otherwise he'll miss the equinox.
Oh, can't he just wait
for the next one?
No, he can't.
Otherwise he'll miss his chance to
pass on his powers to his successor.
But tonight's my only night
to help the families being evicted.
Otherwise they'll be on the streets.
Phoebe, I think super villains
trump slumlords.
Paige, where did you orb in from?
Just dealing
with some personal problems.
I'm your whitelighter,
so if you ever want to talk...
- No.
Can we please just concentrate
on the comic-book guy?
Well, comic books wouldn't be
a bad place to start.
- Remember the Demon of Illusion?
- No.
He was before you.
He literally hid in movies.
So this guy could be hiding in comics
or coming out of them somehow.
So we need to check
comic-book stores?
Oh, that's gonna take forever.
You just go deal with your slumlord.
I'll catch up with you later.
No, we should do it together.
No. If I see some dude in tights,
I'll just orb out.
Paige, it's dangerous.
You shouldn't do it alone.
Well, guess what. She won't have to.
Remember me, the invisible woman?
Now, you two have got to
cut this crap out, now.
Come on, let's go get you
into something less comfortable.
How could The Aggressor fail?
You told me you drew him invincible.
The equinox comes around
once in a lifetime.
And I don't plan on spending
the rest of that lifetime sensing power.
I want power. Ramus' power.
- I tried.
- Not hard enough.
You'll draw a new Aggressor.
Stronger. One that can handle
the witches when Ramus returns.
What if I turn The Aggressor
on to you?
I'd kill you before you could try.
And then I'd kill the rest of the people
in your life who still care about you.
I may not have much power,
but I have enough to do that.
Now...
...draw.
All right, come on. Move it.
Hey, let's get these people
cleared out, okay?
- Edward Miller?
- Yeah?
Phoebe Halliwell, Bay Mirror.
Could I ask you a few questions?
No. I don't think so.
Okay, so how does it feel to be
the most hated man in the city?
- Excuse me?
- Well, at least, not until tomorrow,
when the morning edition comes out,
and everyone reads that you're
forcing families out on the streets.
You print that, lady,
and I'll sue you for libel.
Now, I'm a little rusty on my law,
but how could it be libel,
when it's actually the truth?
- Get out of my way.
- Hey!
Look! You can run,
but you cannot hide, mister.
My newspaper's gonna do
a huge exposé on this.
- You won't get away with it.
- I already have.
Well, we have a few more stores
to check out.
Maybe we'll still find something.
Yeah, more Ionely superheroes
who have to hide their true identities,
which does not bode well
for my love life.
Paige, let me ask you a question.
Are you gonna marry Dave?
No, I just met him.
Well, then relax. Worry about it
when you gotta worry about it.
Okay, what just happened here?
See, I was kind of hoping
you could tell me.
Help! Somebody help me!
Please, help me!
No! No!
- Please don't shoot me.
- Hey!
Not exactly what I had in mind,
but it'll do.
Hi. How's it going?
- Are you all right?
- Who are you people?
Where did you come from?
That's a mighty good question, lady.
They don't have to move.
They can stay for a year.
Ten years.
What about the cockroaches? Are you
gonna do something about them?
First thing tomorrow. Just please,
don't drop me. Please!
Phoebe?
Cole? What are you doing here?
Well, I got a call
from one of the tenants
saying that Wonder Woman
was terrorizing the landlord.
What the hell are you doing?
Well, I'm teaching my buddy here
how important it is
to be a better person.
- Are you a better person yet?
- I'm slipping.
No, you're not slipping.
That's slipping.
- Honey...
- Don't call me "honey" anymore.
I don't know what's going on here,
but this is not you, literally.
Are you kidding?
This is better than me.
This is new-and-improved me.
Not only can I help my readers,
but I can help the entire city.
- Careful, he's got ears.
- Oh, please, relax.
The only thing he can hear right now
is the blood rushing to his brain.
One more slip-up, Edward,
and we'll end up right back up here.
Phoebe, are you out of your mind?
What if somebody sees you?
That's why we wear masks.
- We?
- Yeah, superheroes.
Cole, I gotta go. Because I have a lot
of loyal readers that need my help.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I want you to find out everything
you can about Cole Turner's wife.
- His wife? Why?
- Just do it.
Head rush.
- Let's do it again.
- No, what if somebody sees us?
Sees us? We're blurs.
Besides, who cares?
Okay, give me a sec
while my organs catch up.
- Nice outfit.
- Back at you, sis.
- Okay, but where did we get them?
- I don't know and I don't care.
All I know is I'm on a roll.
I've helped so many readers...
...today.
- What?
- I don't know, but suddenly,
I don't feel so good about this.
It's like the masks
are clouding our judgment,
making us feel like we're invincible.
- Yeah, see?
- Yeah, unfortunately.
I don't like it. I'm putting it back on.
No, Paige, we need to think clearly
so we can figure out who did this...
Phoebe.
Thank you.
What are you waiting for?
How do we know if we heal him
he's not gonna try and kill you again?
Leo, he's a kid.
Plus, killers don't usually thank you
for killing them.
He thanked you?
Just hurry up.
What happened?
Before or after
your alter ego tried to kill us?
Come on.
- What's your name?
- Kevin.
Well, Kevin, you have
some explaining to do.
Are you responsible
for these outfits?
I was hoping you'd be able
to stop The Aggressor.
- The Aggressor? Don't you mean you?
- Yeah.
We were gonna kill you.
We almost did.
Is that what you wanted?
I didn't know what else to do.
I didn't want to hurt anyone else.
And then after our first battle, I thought
maybe if I drew you with powers...
Hang on a second, mister.
What do you mean you drew us?
I've always been able
to imagine things,
and then make them come to life
through my drawings.
Like you guys, the Protectors.
I never told anybody
about what I could do.
I knew it would freak people out.
I mean, hey, it freaked me out at first.
Thought projection is a rare power.
It means he's a witch too.
Why did you
make yourself a superhero?
Because I got tired
of getting beaten up all the time.
Then Arnon came along and said
he'd teach me how to focus my power.
- Arnon. Who's that?
- Somebody I wish I'd never met.
He used me to get to Ramus.
Said he was a bad guy,
that we had to stop him.
But all Arnon wanted
were his powers.
The Elders, they want me
to bring Ramus back down.
No, you can't. Not until
we figure out a way to stop Arnon.
I don't have a choice.
The equinox is starting.
- He'll kill Ramus.
- He can't, not without The Aggressor.
We can't know that for sure.
You have to wait till we find him.
- Yeah, but how?
- I know how.
Arnon doesn't know
The Aggressor failed yet.
So all you have to do is
follow me back to his hideout.
No, that is too dangerous.
I won't be in danger
with you guys there.
With all your super powers
and your super hearing,
you'll easily be able
to overpower him. Trust me.
After all, I drew you, didn't I?
Okay, but you have to
do exactly what we say.
Promise.
- Is this it?
- Yeah, through that door.
Do you hear anything inside?
Rats.
Dripping water, cockroaches.
Might as well be my old apartment.
I don't hear any Arnon, though.
Well, at least
you didn't break anything this time.
- I think we'd be safer upstairs.
- No. Here is fine.
With all the doors,
if anybody attacks...
Anybody who attacks
doesn't need doors, Leo.
Relax.
There's nothing either of us can do
to change what's meant to be.
What is that supposed to mean?
- What aren't you telling me?
- Actually, quite a bit.
Look, Leo, you know as well as I do
that there is a reason for everything.
Which means
there is a reason for here, for now.
How the hell
am I supposed to protect you
if I don't know what the hell
is going on?
- Sorry.
- No, no, I like that.
You could stand to be
a little tougher sometimes.
Just because you're an angel
doesn't mean you can't
kick some ass now and again.
Leo, my fate is sealed.
Win or lose,
I'm right where I'm supposed to be.
Which means
that there is nothing more
either of us can do to change that.
There is, however, perhaps
something I can do for you.
What do you mean?
I am an Elder
and I can foresee the future.
Enough of it, anyway, to give you
a glimpse, if you're interested.
Isn't that against the rules?
I'm retiring. What do I care?
You can ask me one question,
and one question only.
Well, will our baby be healthy?
Yes, very healthy.
And more powerful
than you can even imagine.
Okay, listen. You're gonna go in there
and summon him, okay?
But when he comes, call for us
and we'll get you out of there.
The slightest peep, I'll hear it.
Okay.
You don't have to do this, you know.
No, I want to.
You okay?
Arnon. Arnon, it's me...
You betrayed me.
Now that I know you can draw powers
for others, you can draw some for me.
Stupid planes.
All I hear is ringing in my ears.
Okay, forget it.
We gotta get him out of there.
Kevin. Wake up. Come on.
What is this?
Another Aggressor?
That's right.
- Everybody still alive?
- I'm not sure yet.
Oh, no complaining.
You're the one that didn't want
to be pampered, remember?
I take it back, I take it back.
Hey, at least you have
a baby that can heal you.
Yeah, open wounds.
But apparently not aches and pains.
Oh, God. Oh, God,
I'm so sorry about this.
- It's okay, it's not your fault.
- I didn't have a choice.
Arnon threatened to kill me
if I didn't.
It doesn't matter.
All that matters is that you're fine.
For now, until he needs me
to draw him even more powers.
Well, he won't need any more powers
if he gets to Ramus before we do.
Okay, so how do we stop him?
We're not superheroes anymore.
I could make you superheroes again.
No, that'll take too long.
He'll have Ramus by then.
- So how do we stop him?
- As super witches.
But you couldn't stop
my superhero as witches.
How are you gonna stop Arnon's?
Okay. So we'll rip up his drawing
and turn him back into
the wimpy demon that he is.
You can't.
He took the drawing with him.
Will you just relax?
You're making me nervous.
Okay. Well, something isn't right.
I can sense it.
Leo, I've told you.
You've already done your job.
Now it's time
to let your charges do theirs.
I just don't understand
what's taking so long.
- They should be home by now.
- They will be.
They're just gonna be too late.
You know what,
I'm getting you out of here.
Oh, I'm afraid this is gonna hurt.
Looks like getting your powers
will be even easier than I thought.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
You're too late. Ramus is dead.
- Leo.
- Paige, now.
Boot.
Left. I meant left boot.
- Oh, for goodness' sakes.
- Left boot.
Yeah. Don't you just hate it
when that happens?
Fortunately,
since you have Ramus' powers,
you can foresee
what's gonna happen next.
It's gonna hurt, isn't it?
No!
What the hell is that?
What?
What just happened?
Looks like Ramus was able to pass
his powers to the new Elder after all.
An Elder? He's only 13.
Elders are like kings.
They can be any age.
I don't understand.
What does this mean?
Well, for one thing,
it means that nobody's gonna be
pushing you around anymore.
Are you Turner?
Yeah. Who are you?
Edward Miller.
But you can call me Ed.
I've got nothing to say to you.
Yeah? Well, I got something
to say to you,
as well as the little missus.
You know, there's just
a very certain, special way
that married people
talk to each other.
It's very distinctive to the ear,
even when you're
hanging upside down.
I haven't the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
Really?
Well, maybe this
will jog your memory.
Maybe we should go talk somewhere
a little more private, huh?
Looks like someone
needs to get a room.
Cute, very cute.
How's it going, Dave?
Never better, mate.
Never better.
Oh, really?
How about you guys
go get us girls some drinks?
- Sparkling or still?
- Sparkling, of course.
Right. Oh, by the way, congrats on the
club. It's great. And the DJ's wicked.
Thanks.
See, it's nice to know
you still got it in you.
Yeah. Although
I'm beginning to realize
that being number one in town
just isn't as important as it used to be.
And neither is fighting demons,
for that matter.
What, you didn't like
being a superhero?
Oh, no. Are you kidding?
It was awesome.
I mean, being a witch
is still awesome.
It's just that there's
a new number one in town.
- Good for you.
- Yeah.
And apparently, good for you.
Since you worked through
your issues with Dave, I gather.
Yes, I did, thank God.
I was just about to join a convent.
Must have been the pink leather,
broke you down.
Don't laugh, but I think
it might have been.
Something about leaping
over tall buildings in a single bound.
- I guess that will free any girl up.
- And let your guard down.
Yeah, I'm gonna take your advice,
and just, you know, relax.
If he's Mr. Right, I'll tell him
I fly around on broomsticks.
He may find out by himself.
- What?
- Cole just called.
He said the idiot slumlord
wants to meet Cole and me, now.
- Why?
- Oh, I don't know. Something about
having a tape of Cole's
superhero ex-wife in action.
Oh, no.
What do you want?
Well, your wife off my back,
for starters.
Then, maybe 50 grand a month.
- Fifty grand.
- Yeah.
And if they don't have it,
they can certainly get it.
Just put on those cute little outfits.
They don't have them anymore.
Well, they better find them.
I wouldn't try anything if I were you.
All right, this is just a copy.
I can find the original.
Oh, yeah? How?
Well, I have certain powers too.
But I'm trying very hard
not to use them.
Very hard.
I don't like what they do to me.
Yeah, okay. Whatever, pal.
Guess I'll just sell this
to the highest bidder.
- I can't let you do that.
- Try and stop me.
No!
- Is he here?
- Who?
Miller. Edward Miller.
You said he was coming.
Oh, yeah.
I took care of it.
What do you mean?
What does that mean?
Phoebe, he was gonna expose you.
What was I supposed to do?
Phoebe, wait.