Are you closing?
Not anymore.
Please, come in.
- I am Madame Theresa.
- I'm Phoebe.
Yes, I know.
Really? Did you read my mind?
No, I read your column.
You are not sure if you're a believer,
are you?
Oh, no. I'm a believer. Believe me.
That's why I'm here.
I didn't know where else to turn.
Sit.
Let's see what your hands tell us.
They're probably gonna tell you
that I need a manicure.
You have the gift of foresight.
- What?
- But don't worry.
Your secrets are safe here.
You are creative,
sensitive,
street-smart.
You have a strong family, close ties.
I am wondering why
you do not turn to them now.
I don't wanna worry them.
You see, I'm
having trouble with my gift.
And that's why I'm here.
I wanna try to figure out what's wrong.
These lines on your index finger,
they are saying
that you are overworked.
Yeah. Well, besides my column,
and my personal appearances,
my boss has me
giving advice on a radio show.
- And I love it, I do. It's just...
- Keeping that pace
has blocked out
other parts of yourself.
Including your gift.
Your gift must be honoured.
But so must your work.
So how do I find the balance?
Let's start by unblocking that energy.
Breathe with me.
I know that reaction.
You just had a premonition,
didn't you?
But I don't have premonitions.
Yeah, but I do.
Maybe you intercepted it for me?
The reading is over. You must go.
- No, but...
- I'm sorry.
Theresa. Theresa, wait.
I'm losing you. Say that again?
Orin, the gypsy hunter.
He's coming for me.
Theresa, that's impossible.
We blinded him decades ago.
Only gypsy magic can lift his curse.
I'm telling you,
it had to be him, Lydia.
The girl I was dukkering for,
she has a powerful gift for seeing.
And somehow I received her vision.
All right, where are you? I'll come.
No. You must leave town.
If he's hunting Shuvanis,
he could be after you next.
Expecting me, were you?
Theresa?
Theresa!
Orin?
You've heard of my father.
He'll be very pleased.
What do you want?
His revenge.
And of course,
your eyes.
- Maybe try a different yoga instructor.
- It wasn't the instructor.
It was all those women showing off
their sonogram pictures.
That was just working
on my last nerve.
Like, "Look, it's Jasper's first
photo and it's gonna go on the fridge
in a magnetic frame that says
'Jasper's first photo."'
Okay. I thought prenatal yoga
was supposed to help you relax.
How am I supposed to relax
when I can't even go to a doctor
like a normal person?
Honey, I thought we agreed that
a magical pregnancy was too risky.
Especially with a baby
that heals itself.
Okay, but she's not healing my
nauseousness. Every woman
in that class says it's supposed
to go away after the first trimester.
Well, according to this book,
every pregnancy is different.
- What book?
- This one.
The Joys of Home Birthing.
It also comes with this video.
I thought maybe we could
watch it together. It might make
you feel better about what's in store.
That sounds good.
I'll make some popcorn.
Since when are prenatal yoga
and home birthing videos
your idea of a good time?
Since I became a friendless loser
with no life.
- Paige, you have tons of friends.
- They're all employed.
And I'm a demon fighter
and I can't tell anyone about it.
So I basically just come off as
this big, dumb, fat, unemployed loser.
No, Paige. You're a big, fat, dumb,
unemployed loser who saves the world.
Oh, I hope that's leaded.
I didn't sleep very well last night.
- Cole problems?
- What?
No, he's soul-searching somewhere.
Or off searching for a soul.
I'm just a little overwhelmed
with work.
What's up with your hand?
I actually went to see
a gypsy fortune-teller.
Oh, look.
Work. Gotta go.
Hey. Hey there, Speedy.
Will you slow down and tell us
why you went to see a fortune-teller?
To get my fortune told.
Just don't freak out, all right? Because
I don't have time for a freak-out.
I went to find out
why I haven't gotten a premonition
in the last few months.
You've had premonitions.
Haven't you?
No, I haven't.
And check this out.
Hold this.
I can barely levitate.
- Do you think a demon...?
- No. I mean, I can still cast spells
and I still have
the power of three thing.
Whatever the problem is, it seems
more natural than supernatural.
Phoebe, why didn't you come to me?
I'm your whitelighter.
Well, because
you've been very busy.
- I've been busy?
- Okay. Well, I've been busy.
My work schedule's been really hectic.
But I'm coming to you guys now.
Okay, you guys yell at her.
I'm gonna check with the Elders
and see what they know.
I can't believe you went to a
fortune-teller instead of coming to us.
I'm really sorry, but I just
didn't want to worry you guys.
But now that we're on the subject...
What?
Something really weird happened
during my reading.
I felt like I was
getting a premonition
and then I think
Madame Theresa intercepted it.
Intercepted it? How?
She's a gypsy.
She probably channelled it.
Being that I have nothing to do,
I've actually been reading up
on a lot of gypsy magic lately.
Whatever she saw,
it must have been bad
because she closed up
shop very quickly.
Well, maybe you should swing by
and check up on her.
Yeah, I was going to, but...
Oh, that's work. I really have to go.
I'll go for you.
You know, I have no life and all.
Really? Oh, that would be great.
Let me just find the...
Here. Here's her card.
Thank you so much.
Find out what she saw.
I have a good feeling
about these eyes, Father.
I was glad to see the Shuvani
didn't put up much of a fight.
You saw that far?
Your mind's eye grows stronger.
I've had a long time to develop it.
But it's no replacement for
what those gypsies stole from me.
If these eyes work,
you'll have your revenge
and much more.
- Maybe we should stop trying.
- No!
The eyes I seek
are worth this pain.
Her Shuvani friend is near.
I can see her.
Yeah, we're almost done.
Yeah. I gave them
the heads up in there.
Phoebe Halliwell.
Hey, Phoebe, it's me.
I'm at the fortune-teller's.
Oh, really? What did you find out?
Nothing good.
Unfortunately, sweetie, she's dead.
What?
Yeah, she was murdered last night.
And from what I can gather,
it seems demonic.
She had her eyes gouged out.
I should have been able
to prevent this.
How do you figure?
Well, if my stupid powers
had been working, Paige...
They loved you over at Hot Line.
They want you to guest host
for the rest of the week.
This is not your fault, Phoebe. If you
were meant to stop Theresa's murder
you would have had
a premonition about this.
I know, I know. I can't.
Sorry, but I've already booked you.
- Can't what?
- I'm swamped.
Swamped? But, Phoebe, we have to
find this demon and stop him.
- Price of success, kiddo.
- Phoebe, hello?
I will meet you at home
and we'll get right on it. Okay?
Elise. Elise. Wait.
Is it possible that we could
postpone the radio show?
Because I barely have
time to write my column
let alone all the other stuff
that I have to do.
Dear Phoebe,
my career is on the fast track.
I'm wildly popular and the money is
pretty damn good. What should I do?
- Stop whining.
- Damn, you are good.
It's a very standard surgery.
You're gonna be just fine, I promise.
Excuse me.
Aunt Lydia,
what are you doing here?
No, in English.
I don't speak the language anymore.
I am in danger, Ava.
I am afraid you are too.
Orin is back and he is
seeking revenge on Shuvanis.
- Orin?
- The gypsy hunter.
You've heard the stories.
Aunt Lydia,
we've had this conversation.
I'm not interested in the stories.
- Ava, Madame Theresa was murdered.
- What?
I was talking to her on the phone
when it happened.
She had a vision of Orin
coming for her,
which means he'll be seeking
revenge on all Shuvanis, including you.
- I'm not a Shuvani, I am a doctor.
- Ava.
You cannot change
what you were born to be.
And Orin won't care that you rejected
your heritage. He'll sense you anyway.
Aunt Lydia,
I'm sorry about Theresa.
I know she meant a lot
to you and Mom.
I'll come to the funeral.
I'll pay my respects.
I'm not gonna run
from a fictional demon.
I gotta get back to work.
Ava, we have to trust
the gypsy magic.
Why? Because it did
such a great job saving Mom?
Your mother couldn't be helped,
chawi.
By the time she was sick,
it was too late.
You don't know that.
If she'd gotten chemo instead of
relying on herbs and spells...
Your mother believed in
herbs and spells, and so should you.
Yeah?
Well, if gypsy magic really worked,
then I'd be able to see her, right?
In the afterlife? Talk to her?
Like she promised me.
- Ava...
- I'm sorry, I don't have time for this.
Your friend was murdered.
Turn to the police, not superstition.
At full term, the baby's head
measures up to 38 centimetres.
Okay, see, I need an epidural
just to watch this.
Okay, let's
fast-forward to the part where
the parents get to meet the baby.
At this point, the birthing partner
will coach the mother's breathing.
Okay, give that to me.
Look, just tell me when the baby is out
and all wiped off.
But seriously though, I need a
sterile hospital, magical baby or not.
And medical people.
Lots of professional, medical people.
Gross. What are you guys watching?
Is that some horror movie?
No, it's the Joys of Home Birthing.
Strangely, I'm not feeling the joy.
Well, I'm sorry to cut
your entertainment short,
but we're on demon duty now. Turns
out Madame Theresa was murdered.
- The fortune-teller?
- Yeah, I checked with Darryl.
The third in a string of gypsy killings.
All had their eyes gouged out.
Now that video
doesn't seem so gruesome.
Speak for yourself.
Okay, let's go, people.
I've gotta fit this vanquish in between
two deadlines and three meetings.
Leo, what did you find out about my
powers? What's wrong with them?
Well, technically nothing.
Which means the disconnect
is tied to your emotions.
I think it's a case of
use them or lose them.
Hey, you know, if he's after gypsies,
we should stop by Theresa's funeral.
I know where it is.
Maybe you can get a premonition
that'll help us find the demon.
Prenatal yoga this morning, and now
you want to crash a stranger's funeral?
You really do need friends.
You're mean.
Well, I don't know what she's saying,
but the symbolism's beautiful.
It is. It's really beautiful.
Don't you guys think
Theresa looks a little crowded?
I think that's the gypsy custom,
to send their people off into the
next life with things they might need.
Okay, well, I need a cracker
in this lifetime.
Would it be bad if I grabbed
that box of saltines?
Probably.
May I join the choir invisible
of those immortal dead,
who live again in minds
made better by their presence.
Phoebe, enough with the work.
Sorry.
Well, go on. You're not gonna get
a premonition standing here.
Put a little shoulder into it.
Hi. Excuse me.
Pardon me. Hi.
Are you staying for the pomana?
I made stew.
Aren't you worried
about the gypsy hunter?
He won't attack in a crowd.
- Which means you'd be safer here...
- Please stop.
I have no interest in staying,
Aunt Lydia. This isn't my life.
Please accept that.
I have to get back to work.
Ava.
Ava, wait.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- Did you get anything?
- Kind of. Just bits and pieces.
Well, that's better than nothing.
What did you see?
I saw candles and lanterns
and Theresa in her coffin.
Okay, well, you don't need
a premonition for that. Anything else?
That woman. Her eyes.
Right.
Ava?
Ava!
Nice funeral.
Very touching.
But will there be any Shuvanis left
to throw you yours?
You're the one.
Hey!
He was supposed to blow up?
Why did he not blow up?
Oh, not good.
We gotta get out of here.
Thank you.
I have to go.
Wait, you don't have to be afraid.
I'm not afraid of you. We come from
sister traditions, witches and gypsies.
I appreciate everything you've done,
but I have to go.
But there's a demon after you.
I'm not the only one he's after.
Wait. Clearly you have powers,
but we face demons all the time.
Will you please at least
tell us what you know?
Maybe we're supposed to help.
Perhaps.
Years ago, my tribe threw a curse
on a gypsy hunter named Orin,
blinding him so he no longer
had the power to spot our people.
The demon we saw wasn't blind.
I think that was Orin's son, Cree.
I think he's killing Shuvanis
in the name of his father.
- Shuvanis?
- That's their form of a high priestess.
My niece Ava. She's a Shuvani too.
Only she's rejected her magic,
which is leaving her defenceless.
Well, can't you curse Cree
like you did his father?
There aren't enough Shuvanis left
to pool our power.
Because Ava chooses not to believe
anymore, she won't listen to me.
Maybe we can help.
Okay, I'll take care of that.
You know, sometimes it's easier
to hear the truth from a stranger
than it is to hear from family.
Her name is Ava Nicolae.
She's a doctor at
San Francisco Memorial.
Ob-gyn by any chance?
No, she's a surgeon.
- Close enough. I'll go.
- Why you?
Because I am done
with this nauseousness
and I can fight off Cree if he attacks.
So either you're orbing or I'm driving.
I'm sorry, Elise, I just can't make it.
Is it possible that we can move it?
Hey, we still have a book to check
and a vanquishing potion to make.
All right, all right.
I'll be there. I promise.
I'm sorry.
This is interrupting your lives.
No, no, no. This is our lives.
My sister just needed a little reminder.
Are you injured?
No.
- Did you see everything?
- I saw enough.
If only I would have been prepared
for her, I wouldn't have...
The search is over!
She has the power,
that's what matters.
Next time you'll be more prepared,
the way I taught you.
But how will I get to her?
She's protected by witches now.
They can't protect her heart.
I can see it yearns for
a wayward child, her niece.
Find her.
Shuvani will follow.
They even teach them to swaddle.
Come on, we have to find Ava.
I need to find some help.
Leo, I do not feel well.
And I don't think this is normal.
I need a doctor, a real doctor.
What happens when they check
the security camera footage
to find out why
the sonogram machine blew up
like it did with Phoebe's baby?
Phoebe's baby was a demon.
Ours is an angel, for crying out loud.
Thanks, Bill.
Ava?
Wait.
Do I know you?
No, you don't.
But we kind of know you.
We're friends of your Aunt Lydia.
Is something wrong?
Yeah, there kind of is.
See, there's this gypsy hunter...
Oh, please.
I don't mean to be rude.
You guys look like normal people.
My Aunt Lydia,
she's just very superstitious.
- She shouldn't be sending you...
- She's afraid for you.
People are dying.
Look around you.
That's why I'm here.
I save lives using medicine,
not magic.
But magic is part of who you are.
No, relying on magic
is what killed my mom.
Ava, I know what it's like
to lose your mom. Believe me, I do.
But still, you can't deny who you are.
Dr. Nicolae. Dr. Nicolae
to the emergency room, stat.
I've gotta go.
- Great. Now what do we do?
- Wait and try again.
- You okay?
- No, I am not.
Doctor. Any doctor, now.
All right, add ice to thicken.
I'd say we're done.
I wouldn't have thought to add
turmeric to anything but Indian food.
It's nice to finally have someone
to share my magic with.
Ava will come around.
Sometimes it takes longer for people
to embrace their magic. Right, Paige?
I hope you're right.
She's the last of our line.
If she doesn't carry on the tradition,
it dies with me.
Yeah. Well, that's
not gonna happen.
Being so hard on yourself won't
bring your powers back, you know.
- Okay, what can't you see?
- Maybe I can help.
Well, I think my stress level
is beyond chamomile tea at this point.
You're not gonna drink it.
You're gonna swirl it. Come.
Wait, you read tea leaves?
That's so amazing.
Now pour it out.
All right.
I see an X.
A thorn.
A broken spiral.
You're way out of balance,
just like your powers.
That's pretty much
what Madame Theresa said.
Well, that's what happens
when your brain overrides your heart.
If you want to regain your balance, to
reconnect, you'll have to find out why.
It's so crazy. I never would have seen
those shapes in there.
Just takes practice.
Here, read mine.
Okay.
What do you see?
I see an X.
And that looks kind of like
a lightning bolt.
Ava.
I can't put you in any more danger.
Lydia!
Well, that's an interesting
disappearing act.
I'll have to ask her
how she does that.
- What are you doing?
- I'm trying to see what Lydia saw.
Yeah. You can't read tea leaves.
No, but I get premonitions.
At least I'm supposed to.
Okay, come on.
Please let me see something.
- I saw Cree. He's after Ava.
- Where? When?
I don't know. It's still all in pieces.
But I saw cars, and a parking lot.
Maybe it's the hospital?
The hospital?
Why can't Piper and Leo stop him?
I wouldn't worry too much.
Some women are nauseous their
whole pregnancy. It's perfectly normal.
Yeah, I just...
First-time mom.
I wanted to make sure.
I'm getting paged.
- It's on vibrate.
- Don't you want to see who it is?
Oh, it's her sisters. They're the
only ones with the number, so...
Honey, I think we should hurry up.
Almost done.
Fast healer. Thanks.
Yeah.
Where's Ava?
She's in surgery.
What are you guys doing here?
Trying to find Lydia.
She ran out on us.
She's after Cree.
Surprised to see me again?
Hardly.
This time I was ready for you.
Lydia!
- I don't get a response.
- Clear.
Clear.
- Give me 200 joules.
- Two hundred charged.
Clear.
- Ava.
- Pressure's dropping.
Waffediyok, Ava.
Aunt Lydia?
Dr. Nicolae?
Are you all right?
No ventricular rhythm.
She's flat.
Let's call the code.
No.
Aunt Lydia.
- Oh, my God.
- Come on, sit down.
I saw her.
She came to me, a Mulo.
- Mulo?
- The living dead.
I never believed in it before.
It's okay. Just tell us
what happened.
It was a code blue.
My patient, she died.
And then it was Aunt Lydia.
Nobody else saw.
I thought I was going crazy.
I am so sorry.
No, it's my fault.
She tried to warn me this morning.
I didn't believe her.
No, it's not your fault.
You had your reasons to be sceptical.
Was she trying
to tell you something?
I don't know.
I don't remember much.
I do know a Mulo is a bad omen.
It means that something horrible
is about to happen.
Well, it shouldn't.
We vanquished Cree.
What about Orin?
It has to be him.
That's what she was trying
to tell me.
She was trying to warn me again.
My Romanian's weak,
but I think she was saying something
about him trying to take her power.
Well, how can he take her power
now that she's...?
I don't know.
I wish I knew what
waffediyok meant.
She kept saying that.
We should go to Lydia's apartment.
- Maybe you could get a prem...
- No.
We need more vanquishing potion.
I'm gonna go back to the house
and try to remember what she used.
But, Phoebe, we could
really use your powers.
Yeah. I know, Paige. I know.
Can you take me home?
Sure.
What should we do now?
Theresa would know.
Gypsy custom.
Covering the photos of the dead.
Looks like you're remembering
more and more of those customs.
Nobody knew more about them
than Theresa.
She was like the holy woman
of the tribe.
She always made sure
that traditions were passed down
from mother to daughter.
My mom tried to pass them
down to me, but I wouldn't listen.
Look at this. It's so beautiful.
Let me see that.
This is my mother's.
I can't believe Theresa kept it.
Yeah. Well, maybe she was
just saving it for a special kind of day.
My mother called it
her treasure chest.
It's where she kept precious things.
Is that you and your mom?
She made us matching dresses
for Christmas.
She worked so hard
to finish them in time.
I know it's hard.
My mom died 10 years ago and
there's still a lot of boxes I can't open.
These are recipes
and herbal remedies.
Would these be spells?
Maybe it's not too late to learn
after all.
Look at this.
It looks like Lydia's locket.
That's our family talisman.
The Evil Eye.
Your family symbol is evil?
Only to those
who would wish us harm.
Many feared the Evil Eye, but our
family was said to be protected by it.
The folklore said that
the keeper of the Eye
could use it to magnify
or channel her powers.
I don't think this is folklore.
Look at this inscription.
"Waffediyok."
That's the Evil Eye.
I think Lydia was the keeper.
I think she conjured up that dust storm
and I think this
is what Cree was after.
So he wasn't taking
Shuvanis' eyes just out of revenge.
He wanted the Evil Eye.
And Orin still wants it.
I'll have my revenge, son.
But not before I give you yours.
Who are you?
What are you doing in here?
Testing my new powers.
Okay, Piper. Just be careful.
They're going to the morgue.
- Done. Can you pass me the ice?
- Sure.
You know, maybe we should follow
and see if you can get a premonition.
It was my sorry excuse
for a premonition
that put Lydia in the
morgue in the first place.
Well, Phoebe, we lose innocents.
It's not your fault.
I think if anyone's to blame, it's Cole.
What? He's out of town.
For the first time,
he's actually not plaguing my life.
Which is what gave you
the time to find out
something was wrong with
your powers to begin with.
You dove into your work originally
to escape the pain
and you dealt with it fine.
But you haven't slowed down.
You went from one obsession
to another.
If you want to reach us,
you know the drill.
Phoebe, it's Elise.
Where are you?
Phoebe?
Elise?
Hey, just listen to me
for a second, okay?
Look, I'm sorry, but I have
a major family emergency.
More important than your career?
Of course my career is important to
me, but my family is more important.
Get your butt in here now!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
We were too late.
Orin got the Evil Eye.
- The Evil Eye?
- Yeah, Lydia's eyes have the power.
That's what she was
trying to tell me.
Wait, I hope you have the potion ready,
because we're gonna need it big-time.
Phoebe, are you okay?
Premonition.
Major premonition.
I'm in the future.
Let her go.
It's okay, it's okay.
What happened?
It's been so long since my powers
advanced. And boy, did they advance.
To the point it almost got you killed.
I don't get it.
How can you be at risk in the present
when you're witnessing
a future event?
All I know is it felt like
I was in two places at once.
Almost as if I astral-projected
into my future self.
Okay, it's really great
that your powers have advanced,
and we'll talk about that later. Right
after we make sure there is a later.
Now that Orin has the Evil Eye,
I'd say our best chance at survival
is to run and hide.
You said the vanquishing potion
had no effect?
He didn't even flinch.
So your new-and-improved
premonitions
are just a more vivid way
of telling us we're screwed?
Well, the premonitions
may have changed,
but the reason behind
getting them hasn't.
I mean, they show us the future,
so that we could change the outcome.
But how?
Isn't it a bit suicidal to be walking
into the room Phoebe saw us die in?
Yes, except for we have something
Phoebe's premonition didn't.
We have Ava.
How am I supposed
to make a difference?
Well, in the premonition, witchcraft
alone wasn't enough to vanquish Orin.
But we think witchcraft
plus gypsy magic will be.
But I don't know any gypsy magic.
Well, you have it inside you.
You were born with it.
Why else would you have received
your aunt's warning?
Even if you're right,
I can't defeat Orin on my own.
You won't need to.
You can just call upon your ancestors.
Here's a spell we've used before.
Just substitute these names
for those of
your gypsy family members.
Okay.
Here goes.
Nicolae gypsies
stand strong beside me
- Keep saying the spell.
- Marina, Theresa, Lydia.
Nicolae gypsies
Stand strong beside us
Vanquish this evil
From time and space
Nicolae gypsies
Stand strong beside us
Vanquish this evil
From time and space
Nicolae gypsies
Stand strong beside us
Vanquish this evil
From time and space
Nicolae gypsies
Stand strong beside us
Vanquish this evil
From time and space
Piper.
You did it.
My mother.
She was here. I felt her.
- Who's next?
- We are!
Well, not really.
But we'll make it super quick.
Hey, how you doing?
Fine. Hectic.
I can only make it here
after my hospital shift.
Hectic is good,
just as long as it's not too hectic.
Well, I think I have
my priorities in order.
Helping out gypsies who don't have
health care is definitely one of them.
Good for you.
Ava, did Mrs. Vasila
get her tetanus shot?
- Paige?
- Hey, guys.
- What are you doing?
- Oh, you know.
Just pitching in, helping out.
Did I ever mention that l...?
- Have no life. Yeah.
Paige has been great.
Quick study too.
You should see all the folk remedies
the gypsies have.
Some of them are even better
than Western medicine.
Really? Any of them help
with my nauseousness?
- Well, it's funny you should ask.
- Where are you going?
You don't want to be late
for your appointment, do you?
- What appointment?
- Your appointment with Ava.
Meet your new doctor.
She's also gonna teach us
how to be your midwives.
Midwives? No.
See, because I'm not
having this thing naturally.
No, I need lots and lots
of Western medicine.
- Piper...
- No offence.
Piper. You know, I trusted you
to carry on my heritage,
now you trust me to carry on yours.
Yeah, right. You're good.