[ Mulder ]
BEFORE THE EXPLORATION
OF SPACE,
OF THE MOON AND THE PLANETS,
MAN HELD THAT THE HEAVENS...
WERE THE HOME AND PROVINCE
OF POWERFUL GODS,
WHO CONTROLLED NOT JUST
THE VAST FIRMAMENT,
BUT THE EARTHLY FATE
OF MAN HIMSELF.
AND THAT THE PANTHEON
OF POWERFUL WARRING DEITIES...
WAS THE CAUSE AND REASON
FOR THE HUMAN CONDITION,
FOR THE PAST
AND THE FUTURE...
AND FOR WHICH GREAT MONUMENTS
WOULD BE CREATED ON EARTH,
AS IN HEAVEN.
BUT, IN TIME, MAN REPLACED
THESE GODS WITH NEW GODS
AND NEW RELIGIONS...
THAT PROVIDED NO MORE CERTAIN
OR GREATER ANSWERS...
THAN THOSE WORSHIPPED
BY HIS GREEK OR ROMAN
OR EGYPTIAN ANCESTORS.
AND WHILE WE'VE CHOSEN
NOW OUR MONOLITHIC
AND BENEVOLENT GODS...
AND FOUND OUR CERTAINTIES
IN SCIENCE,
BELIEVERS ALL, WE WAIT FOR
A SIGN, A REVELATION.
OUR EYES TURN SKYWARD,
READY TO ACCEPT
THE TRULY INCREDIBLE,
TO FIND OUR DESTINY
WRITTEN IN THE STARS.
BUT HOW DO WE BEST LOOK TO SEE ?
WITH NEW EYES OR OLD ?
[ Speaking Russian ]
[ Both Speaking Russian ]
[ In Russian ]
[ Fire Crackling ]
[ Glass Shatters ]
MAMA !
PAPA !
[ Continues In Russian ]
MAMA !
PAPA !
[ Shouts ]
[ Shouting In Russian ]
[ Man Screaming ]
AAH !
[ Shouting In Russian ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Boy Screaming ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
[ Door Creaking ]
[ Russian ]
DA.
TOO BAD FOR YOU.
IT-- IT'S LIKE
THE FLESH IS COOKED.
ALL THE WAY THROUGH.
[ Man Shouts In Russian ]
[ Russian ]
[ Chuckles ]
YOUR AUTHORITY
ISN'T RECOGNIZED HERE.
ONLY YOUR LIES.
THESE ARE U.N. PEACEKEEPERS.
THIS IS A MISSION OF MERCY.
THIS IS A MISSION OF FEAR.
YOURS AND THE MEN
YOU WORK FOR.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU GO BACK AND TELL THEM
WHAT YOU'VE SEEN HERE,
WHAT YOU'VE FOUND.
MY NAME IS
MARITA COVARRUBIAS.
I AM A SPECIAL REPRESENTATIVE
TO THE SECRETARY GENERAL
OF THE UNITED NATIONS.
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE,
AND I KNOW WHO YOU WORK FOR.
YOU GO BACK AND YOU TELL THEM--
TELL THEM WHAT ?
WHAT HAPPENED HERE ?
TELL THEM
IT'S ALL GOING TO HELL.
- [ Russian ]
- [ Groaning ]
DOES THE BOY KNOW ?
DID HE SEE ?
YOU TELL THEM TO KISS
MY AMERICAN ASS.
[ Spits ]
[ Woman ]
DURING MY LAST
SEVERAL ABDUCTIONS,
I HAVE EXPERIENCED
NO FEAR WHATSOEVER.
AND IT WAS THE ABSENCE OF FEAR
THAT ALLOWED ME...
TO COMMUNICATE WITH THEM,
AND THEM WITH ME.
THEY'VE TOLD ME
THAT I AM AN APOSTLE,
HERE TO SPREAD THE WORD
OF A DAWNING OF A NEW AGE
OF SUPERNATURAL ENLIGHTENMENT.
[ Murmuring, Applause ]
SENSIBLY, IT'S NOT A QUESTION
OF TRUTH VERSUS FICTION...
BUT OF TRUTHS WHICH ARE
INCOMPREHENSIBLE,
BECAUSE WE HAVE NO PHYSICS,
NO REAL LANGUAGE...
FOR EXPLAINING
PATIENT X'S STORY,
MUCH LESS THE EXISTENCE
OF EXTRATERRESTRIALS.
NOTHING TO PREPARE US
FOR THE ONTOLOGICAL SHOCK
THAT IS BOUND TO FOLLOW.
[ Woman ]
WE QUIBBLE AND WE JAW
ABOUT THE NEED FOR PROOF,
FOR EVIDENCE, AS IF IT
WOULD SERVE SOME PURPOSE,
AS IF IT WOULD MAKE
A DIFFERENCE.
WHEN WHAT WE SHOULD BE
SEEKING IS EXACTLY...
WHAT THIS WOMAN IS DESCRIBING--
NOT IF THEY ARE HERE
BUT WHY...
AND WHAT THEIR BUSINESS IS.
IN MY CONVERSATIONS WITH HER,
SHE BELIEVES THIS BUSINESS--
THE ABDUCTIONS
AND THE EXPERIMENTS--
ARE DUE TO THEIR PLANS
FOR US.
AND THAT WE ARE NOT SIMPLY
BREEDING COWS FOR THEM,
AS SOME HAVE SUGGESTED,
BUT SUBJECTS.
MUCH LIKE WE THINK
OF OUR RELATIONSHIP WITH GOD.
AND THAT THERE ARE SIGHTS...
WHAT SHE CALLS "LIGHTHOUSES"
AROUND WHICH WILL BE
GREAT ACTIVITY.
ALL-- ALL THIS CONJECTURE--
THE ONTOLOGICAL SHOCK
THAT YOU SPEAK OF--
FOR WHICH WE ARE SO
ILL-EQUIPPED IS, IN MY OPINION,
NOT ONLY FALSE BUT DANGEROUS.
THIS WOMAN--
THIS WOMAN PRESENTS NO GOOD
OR CREDIBLE TESTIMONY...
APART FROM THE FEEL-GOOD MESSAGE
THAT SHE PROMOTES.
YOU THINK SHE'S LYING ?
NO, I DON'T THINK
SHE'S LYING.
I THINK...
THAT IF YOU PREPARE PEOPLE
WELL ENOUGH TO BELIEVE A LIE,
THEY WILL BELIEVE IT
AS IF IT WERE TRUE.
AND IF YOU TELL THEM
A REALLY BIG LIE-- LIKE THERE
ARE ALIENS FROM OUTER SPACE--
MUCH MORE THAN A SMALL ONE,
THEY WILL BELIEVE IT.
AND IF YOU SUGGEST TO THEM
THAT THESE ALIENS ARE DOING
BAD THINGS TO THEM,
THE POWER OF THIS SUGGESTION
WILL BE TO MAKE
CERTAIN PEOPLE BELIEVE...
THAT CERTAIN
PSYCHOPATHOLOGIES AND NEUROSES
THAT THEY'RE SUFFERING FROM...
CAN NOW BE ATTRIBUTED
TO THAT.
MR. MULDER--  AGENT MULDER,
SHE HAS PHYSICAL AILMENTS.
ARE YOU DISCOUNTING
ANY BELIEF IN THE EXISTENCE
OF EXTRATERRESTRIALS ?
NO, I JUST QUESTION
MINDLESS BELIEF.
BUT YOU'VE CITED EVIDENCE.
YOU'VE MADE CLAIMS YOURSELF.
WHAT I'VE SEEN, I'VE SEEN
BECAUSE I WANTED TO BELIEVE.
I--  IF YOU LOOK TOO HARD,
YOU CAN GO MAD.
BUT IF YOU CONTINUE TO LOOK,
YOU BECOME LIBERATED
AND YOU COME AWAKE,
AS IF FROM A DREAM,
REALIZING THAT-- THAT
THE LIES ARE THERE...
SIMPLY TO PROTECT
WHAT THEY'RE ADVERTISING--
A GOVERNMENT WHICH KNOWS
THAT ITS GREATEST STRENGTH...
IS NOT IN DEFENSE
BUT IN ATTACK.
[ Murmuring ]
IT'S STRONGLY HELD BY BELIEVERS
IN U.F.O. PHENOMENA...
THAT THERE IS
MILITARY COMPLICITY
OR INVOLVEMENT IN ABDUCTIONS.
BUT WHAT IF THERE IS
NO COMPLICITY ?
WHAT IF THERE IS SIMPLY JUST
THE MILITARY SEEKING TO DEVELOP
AN ARSENAL OF WEAPONS...
AGAINST WHICH
THERE IS NO DEFENSE ?
BIOLOGICAL WARFARE,
WHICH JUSTIFIES IN THEIR EYES...
MAKING AN ASS
OUT OF THE NATION WITH
STORIES OF LITTLE GREEN MEN.
A CONSPIRACY WRAPPED IN A PLOT
INSIDE A GOVERNMENT AGENDA.
[ Murmuring ]
- DR. WERBER ?
- IT'S BEEN SOME TIME.
ALMOST FIVE YEARS.
I CAME DOWN
EXPECTING TO HEAR...
HOW YOUR WORK
HAD PROGRESSED.
I'M... SURPRISED,
TO SAY THE LEAST.
A LOT HAS CHANGED.
YOU SEEM TO HAVE ABANDONED
SOMETHING YOU BELIEVED
SO COMPLETELY.
IN SPITE OF WHAT
I KNOW ABOUT YOU,
FROM OUR WORK TOGETHER,
THE MEMORIES I HELPED YOU
RECOVER ABOUT THE EXPERIENCE
WITH YOUR SISTER.
WELL, I'VE COME TO DISTRUST
A LOT OF THINGS.
I'VE-- I'VE COME TO DISTRUST
THOSE MEMORIES.
I'M SORRY.
FOR WHAT ?
I'VE TAKEN A LOT OF CRITICISM
FOR MY WORK WITH ALIEN ABDUCTEES
AND IN THE FIELD ITSELF.
THE REGRESSION HYPNOSIS WORK
I DID WITH YOU--
NO, I'M NOT QUESTIONING
YOUR METHODS, DR. WERBER.
I'M QUESTIONING MYSELF
AND HOW I WAS TRICKED.
HOW I WAS LED TO BELIEVE,
THROUGH AN ELABORATE STAGING
OF EVENTS,
THAT MY SISTER
HAD BEEN ABDUCTED.
A MAN WITH FAITH
CAN INDULGE IN THE LUXURY
OF SKEPTICISM.
I DON'T THINK YOU UNDERSTAND.
THERE'S JUST TOO MUCH EVIDENCE
THAT IT'S ALL BEEN A LIE.
THE CONSPIRACY
IS NOT TO HIDE THE EXISTENCE
OF EXTRATERRESTRIALS.
IT'S TO MAKE PEOPLE
BELIEVE IN IT SO COMPLETELY
THAT THEY QUESTION NOTHING.
SO, YOU AND I
HAVE JUST BEEN ADVOCATES
OF INSANITY ALL ALONG ?
IS THIS
THE EXTREME POSSIBILITY
YOU BELIEVE IN NOW ?
YEAH.  IS PATIENT X
ANY MORE CREDIBLE ?
I HOPE SO.
I'M HER DOCTOR.
I THINK
YOU SHOULD MEET HER.
I THINK YOU MIGHT
CHANGE YOUR MIND.
[ Russian ]
CASSANDRA.
OH, HI.
- FOX MULDER.
- HI.
I AM SO GLAD
TO FINALLY MEET YOU.
YOU ARE A HERO OF MINE.
I AM ?
I READ ABOUT YOU IN THE NEWS
ABOUT THREE YEARS AGO.
HOW YOU HELPED THAT MAN
WHO ESCAPED FROM THE HOSPITAL.
UM, DUANE BARRY.
HOW HE HAD HELD THOSE PEOPLE
HOSTAGE AT THE TRAVEL AGENCY,
BECAUSE HE WAS BEING CALLED
BY ALIENS,
AND YOU WERE THE ONLY ONE
WHO BELIEVED HIM.
YOU MAY NOT LIKE ME
AS MUCH AS YOU LIKE
THAT STORY.
OH, THAT STORY
SAVED MY LIFE.
HOW'S THAT ?
I HAVE BEEN A MULTIPLE ABDUCTEE
FOR OVER 30 YEARS.
I HAD BEEN AFRAID
TO SEEK HELP.
NOBODY WOULD EVER
BELIEVE ME, REALLY,
UNTIL I READ ABOUT YOU.
THAT'S HOW I CAME
TO MEET DR. WERBER.
CASSANDRA--
HE TOLD ME THAT
YOU HAD BEEN THROUGH
HYPNOTIC REGRESSION YOURSELF.
THAT'S HOW YOU DISCOVERED
THAT YOUR SISTER
HAD BEEN ABDUCTED.
CASSANDRA.
YES.
ARE YOU HERE VOLUNTARILY ?
UM, YES,
UNDER DOCTOR'S SUPERVISION.
HMM.
WHATEVER IT IS
THAT YOU'RE AFRAID OF,
I SUGGEST YOU CHECK
YOURSELF OUT OF HERE
AS SOON AS YOU CAN...
AND START LIVING
YOUR LIFE, OKAY ?
UH, NOW'S NOT
A REAL GOOD TIME.
CASSANDRA IS EXPERIENCING
A SENSATION THAT SHE'S
ABOUT TO BE CALLED.
NOW IS A TIME OF WAR AND STRESS
AMONG THE ALIEN NATIONS.
THE-- THE DIFFERENT RACES,
THEY'RE IN UPHEAVAL.
I WILL BE SUMMONED TO A PLACE,
JUST LIKE DUANE BARRY.
THE MAN YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT DIED BECAUSE
OF WHAT HE BELIEVED IN.
HE DIED IN A ROOM
AFTER I'D BEEN
INTERROGATING HIM,
AFTER HE RECEIVED
A VISIT FROM SOME MEN
FROM OUR GOVERNMENT.
OH, I'M SURE
THE GOVERNMENT'S INVOLVED.
THEY DON'T WANT US
TO KNOW ABOUT IT ALL.
CASSANDRA.
THERE WAS A TIME WHEN
I WOULD HAVE BELIEVED WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING, WITHOUT A DOUBT.
THERE IS NO DOUBT,
MR. MULDER.
I KNOW WHAT I'VE EXPERIENCED.
I-I HAVE BEEN THROUGH THE TERROR
AND THE TESTS MORE TIMES
THAN I CAN COUNT.
I HAVE HAD AN UNBORN FETUS
TAKEN FROM ME.
BUT THEY'RE NOT HERE
FOR THE REASONS
THAT YOU MIGHT THINK.
THEY'RE HERE
TO DELIVER A MESSAGE.
EXCEPT SOMETHING
HAS GONE WRONG.
THERE ARE-- THERE ARE
OTHER FORCES AT WORK.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE
CALLING ME.  I CAN FEEL IT.
AND YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THIS...
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT CAN DO SOMETHING.
I'M NOT.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Door Unlocks ]
[ Russian ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Murmurs ]
[ Russian ]
WE'RE GONNA TAKE
GOOD CARE OF YOU.
AGENT SCULLY, MY NAME
IS JEFFREY SPENDER.
SPECIAL AGENT SPENDER.
IS THERE SOMETHING
I CAN HELP YOU WITH,
AGENT SPENDER ?
I FEEL KIND OF FUNNY
APPROACHING YOU LIKE THIS.
I JUST HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO REACH AGENT MULDER.
ABOUT WHAT ?
ABOUT SOMEBODY
HE'S BEEN TALKING TO.
SOMEBODY WHO CLAIMS
TO BE AN ALIEN ABDUCTEE,
WHO I'D REALLY PREFER
HE WEREN'T TALKING TO.
YOU GONNA TELL ME
WHO THIS IS ?
THIS IS GOING
TO SOUND WEIRD.
UH, IT'S MY MOTHER.
YOUR MOTHER.
IT'S A VERY LONG STORY.
SHE'S AN EXCEPTIONAL PERSON.
BUT FOR REASONS THAT ARE
PROBABLY KIND OF OBVIOUS,
I'D RATHER THIS
DIDN'T GET OUT.
APPEARANCES
BEING WHAT THEY ARE.
IS THIS PART OF A CASE ?
NO.
THEN WHY IS HE
TALKING TO HER ?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE JUST CALLED ME,
AND SHE'S--
SHE'S A VERY DISTURBED WOMAN.
THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT CAUSED A LOT OF PAIN
ABOUT 20 YEARS AGO.
I'M JUST TRYING TO SAVE MYSELF
ANY EXTRA HUMILIATION.
I'D LIKE TO BUILD
A REPUTATION HERE,
NOT BE GIVEN ONE.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND.
[ Covarrubias ]
WHATEVER HAPPENED IN KAZAKHSTAN,
THERE WAS NO ONE LEFT
TO GIVE AN ACCURATE ACCOUNT.
HOW MANY BODIES
WERE THERE ?
FORTY-ONE.  ALL BURNED
BEYOND RECOGNITION.
THE RESULT OF
SOME KIND OF INTENSE
BIOCHEMICAL REACTION,
NONE OF THE U.N. MEDICS
HAD EVER SEEN.
NOT IN THE GULF
OR ON ANY BATTLEFIELD.
THE CORPSES WERE LITERALLY
CARBONIZED FROM THE HEAT.
A NEW WEAPON BEING TESTED ?
THERE'S NO INTELLIGENCE
ON THAT.
THERE'S NO CLEAR DATA
ON THE VICTIMS
OR THEIR RELATIONSHIP,
BUT I FOUND AT LEAST
TWO OF THESE AMONG THE DEAD.
I THINK IT'S FAIRLY CERTAIN
THAT ALL THE VICTIMS HAD THEM--
THAT WHAT WAS TAKING PLACE
WAS A STAGING...
FOR A GROUP ABDUCTION.
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT ?
IN THE FINAL PHASES
BEFORE IT BEGINS,
THERE'LL MOST LIKELY
BE ASSEMBLIES.
WE'RE YEARS AWAY FROM THAT.
IF WE'RE TO BELIEVE
THEIR TIMETABLE.
UNLESS IT'S ALREADY BEGUN.
WE'RE 15 YEARS AWAY.
I DON'T THINK
THIS WAS PLANNED.
I THINK SOMETHING, OR SOMEONE,
SET THIS IN MOTION.
AN ACT OF WAR,
AGAINST US AND OUR PLANS.
KRYCEK WAS AT THE BURN SITE
WITH A UNIT OF RUSSIAN SOLDIERS.
ALEX KRYCEK DID THIS ?
HE WAS THERE.
PROBABLY ACTING
ON THE SAME DATA WE GOT.
WHETHER HE HAD ANY DIRECT
INVOLVEMENT IN WHAT HAPPENED,
HE KNOWS WHAT CAUSED IT.
KNOWS HOW ?
HE CAPTURED A BOY AT THE SITE.
A SURVIVOR.  SOMEONE WHO SAW.
WHAT DOES KRYCEK WANT ?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- HOW DO WE FIND OUT ?
[ Phone Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
YES.
WELL, LOOK WHO'S ANSWERING
THE BAT-PHONE.
ALEX KRYCEK.
[ Krycek ]
ARE THOSE GUYS TOO CHEAP
TO OFFER YOU A PENSION PLAN ?
- WHERE ARE YOU ?
- I'M IN TOWN, ACTUALLY.
- NEW YORK CITY.
- JUST TELL US WHAT YOU WANT.
YOU'VE BEEN WORKING
ON A VACCINE...
AGAINST THE BLACK OIL.
UNSUCCESSFULLY, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, WELL, I FIGURED
YOU AND YOUR BUDDIES MUST HAVE
BEEN BUSY WHILE I'VE BEEN GONE.
- OUR RESEARCH CONTINUES.
- I'LL TAKE EVERYTHING YOU GOT.
IN EXCHANGE FOR ?
THE BOY.
WHY IS THAT
IN OUR INTEREST ?
BECAUSE WITHOUT WHAT
HE KNOWS, YOU AIN'T GONNA
NEED ANY VACCINE.
WHAT DOES HE KNOW ?
THAT'S MY OPENING OFFER.
THE LONGER YOU WAIT,
THE SKINNIER THIS KID GETS.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Scully ]
SHOULDN'T THAT BE MY PICTURE
NEXT TO THAT HEADLINE ?
OR IS THAT JUST YOU
HAVING A LITTLE FUN ?
DO I LOOK LIKE
I'M HAVING FUN, SCULLY ?
YOU LOOK CONSTIPATED,
ACTUALLY.
THAT WOULD MAKE SENSE.
I'VE HAD MY HEAD UP MY REAR END
FOR THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
THIS WOULDN'T
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH CASSANDRA SPENDER.
CASSANDRA SPENDER
IS LIVING PROOF
THAT THE TRUTH...
I'VE SO BOLDLY BEEN SEEKING
FOR THE LAST FIVE YEARS...
IS THE TRUTH OF A MADMAN.
HOW'S THAT ?
ONE MORE ANAL-PROBING,
GYRO-PYRO,
LEVITATING, ECTOPLASM ALIEN
ANTIMATTER STORY...
AND I'M GONNA TAKE OUT
MY GUN AND SHOOT SOMEBODY.
WELL, I GUESS
I'M DONE HERE.
YOU SEEM TO HAVE INVALIDATED
YOUR OWN WORK.
HAVE A NICE LIFE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT CASSANDRA SPENDER ?
HER SON ACCOSTED ME
IN THE HALLWAY.
HE'S AN F.B.I. AGENT.
WHEW.  GREAT.
[ Chuckles ]
HE'S OF THE SAME OPINION
AS YOU, BY THE WAY,
THAT SHE'S NOT WELL.
YOU KNOW, YOU TRY TO
REVEAL WHAT'S HIDDEN,
YOU TRY TO INCITE PEOPLE
WITH THE FACTS,
BUT THEY'D RATHER BELIEVE
SOME INSANE NONSENSE,
REFUSING TO BELIEVE
WHAT OUR GOVERNMENT
IS CAPABLE OF.
YOU'VE COME
A LONG WAY, MULDER.
YEAH, AND STILL
NOBODY BELIEVES ME.
- [ Inhales ]
- WHAT ?
CASSANDRA SPENDER WAS ABDUCTED
AT SKYLAND MOUNTAIN.
THAT'S WHERE I WAS TAKEN.
WHERE DUANE BERRY TOOK ME.
THE WOMAN IS A NUT,
SCULLY.
IT SAYS HERE THAT
SHE HAS AN IMPLANT...
IN THE BASE OF HER NECK.
WHERE THE GOVERNMENT
NO DOUBT REMOVED HER BRAIN.
ISN'T THAT WHAT HER SON
STOPPED YOU TO SAY, SCULLY ?
OH, NO.  HE, UH,
HE ASKED IF YOU'D PLEASE NOT
TALK ABOUT THIS WITH ANYONE.
WISH GRANTED.
[ Engine Idling ]
[ Man ]
HI.  I'M LOOKING FOR A--
I'M-- I'M LOOKING FOR A--
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR WHAT ?
A MOUNTAIN, I THINK.
YOU AND EVERYBODY ELSE.
HOW'S THAT ?
OH, YOU'RE A LITTLE LATE
TO THE PARTY.
SIX DOLLARS.
I HOPE YOU FIND
SOME PARKING.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Scully ]
CASSANDRA ?
MS. SPENDER ?
OH.  YES ?
DO I KNOW YOU ?
OF COURSE I DO.
I DON'T THINK SO.
NO.  NO, I'M SURE OF IT.
ARE YOU A DOCTOR ?
AH, YES, BUT NOT
A PRACTICING ONE.
NO ?
MY NAME IS DANA SCULLY,
AND, UH, I'D LIKE TO
ASK YOU SOME QUESTIONS.
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHAT ?
MAY I ?
UM--
I THINK YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT I, UH,
I LEARNED ABOUT YOU
FROM YOUR SON.
JEFFREY ?
YES.
I'M AN F.B.I. AGENT,
AND HE ASKED THAT I PROTECT
AGAINST YOUR STORY GETTING OUT.
OH.
I GUESS I'M BETRAYING THAT
BY COMING HERE,
BUT, UM, I DON'T--
UH--
I'M HERE FOR MORE
PERSONAL REASONS, ACTUALLY.
I TOOK THE LIBERTY
OF READING YOUR MEDICAL FILE.
[ Exhales ]
YOU'RE FEELING IT, TOO,
AREN'T YOU ?
HERE.
YOU WAKE UP AT NIGHT,
KNOWING YOU NEED TO
BE SOMEWHERE,
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE IT IS.
LIKE YOU FORGOT
AN APPOINTMENT YOU
DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD.
THAT'S NOT WHY I'M HERE.
OH.
I'M HERE BECAUSE I, UH--
BECAUSE I WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT YOU SHOULD--
THAT YOU SHOULD NOT REMOVE
THE THING THAT YOU HAVE
IN YOUR NECK.
NOT WITHOUT
POSSIBLE CONSEQUENCES.
I BECAME VERY ILL.
I'D NEVER DREAM
OF REMOVING IT.
I WANNA GO.
WHEREVER IT IS.
OH, THEY HAVE...
SO MUCH TO TEACH US.
YOU, BEING A DOCTOR,
WOULD WANT TO KNOW...
THEY'RE GREAT HEALERS.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY
YOU WERE CHOSEN.
- OH, MY GOD !
- HELP ME !
HELP ME !  HELP ME !
PLEASE !
HELP ME !
[ Groans ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
[ Woman ]
AND THERE WAS NO INDICATION
BEFOREHAND ?
[ Mulder ]
ARE THERE ANY SURVIVORS ?
[ Scully ]
NO.  NOT AS OF THIS MOMENT.
THE SMELL.
THEY'VE ALL BEEN BURNED.
THERE ARE PLENTY MORE
WHO ARE STILL BEING BAGGED
AS WE SPEAK.
ANY PRELIMINARY THEORIES ?
WELL, IT APPEARS
THEY ALL CAME BY CAR.
MOST OF THE DEAD ARE
CONGREGATED IN A WOODED AREA
A SHORT DISTANCE OFF THE ROAD.
SELF-IMMOLATION ?
WELL, THERE'S NO EVIDENCE
OF THAT RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S NO ACCELERANTS,
NO INCENDIARY DEVICE.
WHAT WAS THE RELATIONSHIP
TO EACH OTHER ?
WERE THEY FAMILIES ?
WELL, THERE'S NO WAY TO I.D.
THEIR BODIES RIGHT NOW.
IT'S GONNA BE A PAINSTAKING
DENTAL PROCESS.
MULDER, WHY ARE YOU TIPTOEING
AROUND THE OBVIOUS FACT HERE ?
I MEAN,
THIS IS SKYLAND MOUNTAIN.
WE'RE RIGHT BACK HERE
ON SKYLAND MOUNTAIN.
AND YOU THINK IT'S RELATED
TO YOUR ABDUCTION
FROM THE SAME PLACE ?
WELL, YOU CAN'T DENY
THE CONNECTION.
YOU THINK THIS IS SOME KIND
OF ABDUCTION SCENARIO ?
NO, I'M NOT SAYING THAT.
DO YOU HAVE
ANY EVIDENCE OF THAT ?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "EVIDENCE" ?
THAT'S WHAT I'M ASKING YOU.
[ Sighs ]
WELL, ARE YOU GONNA
GIVE ME YOUR THEORY, THEN ?
NO.
I'M GONNA GIVE YOU
AN EXPLANATION.
THIS IS THE SAME SCENE
WE SAW IN KAZAKHSTAN.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON ?
THIS IS OUR OWN BACKYARD.
THIS IS NO GOOD.
I DON'T LIKE BEING KEPT
IN THE DARK ON THIS.
SOMEONE'S
GOING TO GREAT LENGTHS
TO SABOTAGE OUR WORK.
- WHO ?
- ONE WAY OR ANOTHER,
WE'D BETTER FIND OUT,
BEFORE IT'S DETERMINED
WE'RE UNABLE TO HANDLE
THIS OURSELVES.
TO PUT A STOP TO IT,
BEFORE THE COLONISTS INTERVENE.
[ Woman On TV ]
MORE ON OUR TOP STORY THIS HOUR.
IN THE NORTHERN PART
OF THE STATE, LAST NIGHT'S
MASS DEATH IN THE FOREST...
JUST INSIDE THE NATIONAL PARK
AT SKYLAND MOUNTAIN.
AGAIN, AUTHORITIES HAVE NOW
RELEASED A FAIRLY COMPLETE
LIST OF THE DEAD...
GATHERED FROM
VEHICLE REGISTRATIONS,
HOPING RELATIVES OR FRIENDS
WILL COME FORWARD...
AND HELP TO EXPLAIN THE CAUSE--
[ Woman On TV Continues,
Indistinct ]
[ Door Opens ]
CASSANDRA ?
YOU CALLED US ?
THIS IS NOT SUPPOSED TO
BE HAPPENING.
I KNEW THESE PEOPLE.
YOU KNEW THEM ?
TH-THEY WERE FRIENDS
OF MINE.
FRIENDS FROM WHERE ?
FROM A LONG TIME AGO.
IT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO
BE HAPPENING.
NOT LIKE THIS.
YOU HAVE TO
DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
[ Mulder ]
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO DO ?
[ Cassandra ]
YOU HAVE TO STOP IT.
[ Mulder ]
STOP WHO ?
[ Cassandra ]
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
AGENT MULDER,
MY NAME IS JEFFREY SPENDER.
OH, SON OF... THE PROPHET.
I ASKED YOU
TO LEAVE HER ALONE.
YOUR MOTHER CALLED US
ABOUT THE INCIDENT IN VIRGINIA.
SHE SAID THAT SHE KNEW
SOME OF THE DEAD.
OF COURSE SHE DID.
THEY WERE IN THE SAME
RIDICULOUS CULT
THAT SHE USED TO BE.
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
SHE WAS IN A CULT ?
A U.F.O. CULT WHO BELIEVED
THEY WERE GOING TO BE
CARRIED TO IMMORTALITY...
IN SOME KIND OF
FLYING MOTHER WHEEL.
[ Mulder ]
I'M SORRY.
WE WON'T BE BOTHERING
YOU OR YOUR MOTHER ANYMORE.
[ Liquid Pouring ]
YOU THINK YOU CAN
PULL THIS OFF, DON'T YOU ?
[ Moaning ]
IF THEY GIVE ME WHAT I WANT,
I'M GONNA RULE THE WORLD.
WE'VE GOT THEM
ON THEIR KNEES, ALEX.
YEAH.
LET'S GET OUT
OF THIS HOLE.
[ Door Creaks ]
WELL--
WHERE'S THE BOY ?
ARE YOU READY FOR THIS ?
I'VE BEEN GOING OVER
THE INITIAL FORENSICS
AND PATHOLOGY REPORTS...
FROM THE INCIDENT
AT SKYLAND MOUNTAIN.
AND WHILE THE EVENT ITSELF
REMAINS UNEXPLAINED,
I THINK IT'S LESS THAN
A MYSTERY WHO'S INVOLVED.
AT LEAST FOR ME.
AND CERTAINLY FOR YOU.
OUR PATHOLOGISTS HERE
HAVEN'T FINALIZED THEIR REPORTS,
BUT I WAS ABLE TO HAVE
THREE VICTIMS SELECTED
AT RANDOM FOR X RAYS.
THAT'S HOW I FOUND THESE--
SMALL PIECES OF WHAT
LOOKS LIKE METAL...
IN THE CHARRED
CERVICAL TISSUE HERE,
HERE AND HERE.
IMPLANTS.
I FOLLOWED UP
WITH THE FAMILIES
OF THE THREE VICTIMS,
AND I FOUND THAT NONE
HAD ANY CULT ASSOCIATIONS,
BUT TWO OUT OF THE THREE
BELONGED TO THE LOCAL
MUTUAL U.F.O. NETWORKS.
AND BOTH OF THEM CLAIMED
ABDUCTION EXPERIENCES,
AND BOTH OF THEM WERE BEING
TREATED BY A MEDICAL
HEALTH PRACTITIONER...
OVER THE PAST FEW MONTHS.
FOR WHAT ?
TAKE A LOOK.
"MAJOR DEPRESSIVE
DISORDER...
"CHARACTERIZED BY
PERIODS OF SUSTAINED
ANXIETY AND PARANOIA.
"PATIENT BELIEVES HE WILL
BE CONTACTED OR CALLED
TO AN UNDISCLOSED PLACE...
WHERE HE WILL BE
ABDUCTED BY ALIENS."
THE IMPLANTS TRIGGERED
THOSE RESPONSES.
THOSE PEOPLE WERE LED
TO SKYLAND MOUNTAIN.
BY WHOM ?
BY THE SAME GOVERNMENT
THAT PUT THE IMPLANT IN YOU,
TO FUNCTION AS
A HOMING MECHANISM.
MULDER, THAT
DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WHY NOT ?
A TRACKING SYSTEM USING MILITARY
APP. SATELLITE TECHNOLOGY
TO MONITOR TEST SUBJECTS,
OR TO STAGE WHAT PEOPLE
MIGHT OTHERWISE BELIEVE
ARE ALIEN ABDUCTIONS.
BUT THEY WEREN'T ABDUCTED.
THEY WERE LED TO THEIR DEATHS.
AND FOR WHAT PURPOSE ?
I DON'T KNOW THAT YET.
- YOU KNOW, MULDER,
- [ Phone Rings ]
MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T
BE SO QUICK...
[ Ringing Continues ]
TO RULE OUT WHAT
CASSANDRA SPENDER HAS TO SAY.
[ Ringing Continues ]
[ Ring ]
[ Picks Up Receiver ]
MULDER.
AGENT MULDER ?
YES.
THIS IS MARITA COVARRUBIAS.
IS THIS A SECURE LINE WE'RE ON ?
YES.
YOU WERE
AT SKYLAND MOUNTAIN.
ARE YOU AWARE OF A U.N. REPORT
ON A SIMILAR INCIDENT
IN THE FORMER SOVIET UNION ?
NO.
I WAS IN KAZAKHSTAN,
AGENT MULDER.
THERE IS A CONNECTION.
I HAVE SOMEONE WHO KNOWS IT.
I HAVE HIM WITH ME NOW.
WHERE ARE YOU ?
AT A PAY PHONE ON SCUDDER ROAD,
JUST OFF THE I-90.
COME HERE,
WAIT FOR MY CALL...
FOR DIRECTIONS.
[ Gasps ]
MARITA ?  M--
[ Receiver Clatters In Cradle ]
[ Ringing ]
HELLO ?
[ Mulder ]
WHO'S THIS ?
THIS IS SPECIAL AGENT SPENDER.
- THIS IS FOX MULDER.
- WHY ARE YOU CALLING HERE ?
I'M ACTUALLY LOOKING
FOR AGENT SCULLY.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO
REACH HER, AND SHE SAID--
SHE'S NOT HERE.
NOR IS MY MOTHER.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
SHE'S GONE FROM HER ROOM.
GONE WHERE ?
LOOK, SHE'S JUST GONE.
DON'T YOU GET IT ?
SHE'S GOT NOWHERE TO GO.
[ Woman ]
LOOK !
[ Man ]
THERE !  THERE IT IS !
[ Man Screaming ]
[ Man Continues Screaming ]
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !