[ Man ]
LET'S DO IT !
HEY, HOW YA DOIN' ?
QUITE A LITTLE PARTY.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ?
WE HAVE REPORTS OF AT LEAST
A DOZEN SHOTS FIRED.
DOOR LOOKS LIKE
IT'S BEEN JIMMIED,
BUT THE ALARM WASN'T TRIPPED.
YOU SEE ANYBODY COME OUT ?
NOT A SOUL.  WHOEVER IT IS,
THEY'RE STILL IN THERE.
MOVE !  MOVE !
GO.
LIEUTENANT, OVER HERE.
LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE GOT HIT.
SO WHERE'D HE GO ?
STAY LOW,
KEEP LOOKING.
[ Moaning ]
[ Lieutenant ]
DAVIS !
GONZALES !
[ Gonzales ]
YEAH !
[ Moaning ]
- [ Moaning ]
- EASY, BUDDY.
TAKE IT EASY.
YOU HURT ?
THEY'RE HERE.  THEY'RE HERE.
WHO'S HERE ?
[ Lieutenant ]
TALK TO US.
WHO'S HERE ?
COME ON.
[ Man ]
THEY'RE HERE.  THEY'RE HERE.
THEY'RE HERE.
- GET DOWN !  POLICE !
GET DOWN !  FREEZE !
- DON'T SHOOT !
DON'T SHOOT !
TURN AROUND,
SLOWLY !
- WE DIDN'T DO IT.
- DO WHAT ?
WHATEVER.
FACE DOWN
ON THE FLOOR.
NOW !  GET DOWN !
GET DOWN !  GET DOWN !
OKAY, CUFF 'EM !
SPREAD 'EM !
OH, MAN.
[ Grunting ]
[ Man ]
THEY'RE HERE !
[ People Chattering ]
I TOLD 'EM I WASN'T THERE.
YOU WAS DRIVIN',
THOUGH.
[ Man ]
WE'RE SCREWED.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR GETTING ME
INVOLVED IN THIS, DOOHICKEY.
FROHIKE,
YOU HIPPY JERK.
DOOHICKEY !
YOU KNOW, WITH THAT
LONG BLOND HAIR,
YOU'LL BE THE FIRST ONE
IN HERE THAT GETS
TRADED FOR CIGARETTES.
I'M GONNA BE
LAUGHIN' MY ASS OFF.
OH, YEAH ?
YOU WANNA CHA-CHA ?
[ Frohike ]
ANYTIME, ANYPLACE.
BOTH OF YOU, RELAX.
SHUT UP,
YOU NARC !
IT'S YOUR FAULT
WE'RE HERE.
[ Man ]
YOU, IN THE SUIT.
YOU FIRST.
DETECTIVE MUNCH,
BALTIMORE HOMICIDE.
DID THEY FIND HER ?
AND A GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
SORRY, NO SIGN OF
YOUR MYSTERY LADY.
SHE IS REAL.
THE F.B.I. AGENT SAW HER.
YEAH, WELL,
SPECIAL AGENT... MULDER...
IS CURRENTLY BEING HELD
IN FIVE-POINT RESTRAINTS
AND JABBERING LIKE A MONKEY,
AND THE F.B.I.'S
NOT TALKIN' EITHER.
SO WHAT I'M LOOKIN' AT HERE
IS A WAREHOUSE BREAK-IN
WITH NOTHING STOLEN,
A SHOOTOUT BUT NO GUNS,
LOTS OF BLOOD BUT NO BODIES...
AND AN F.B.I. AGENT WHO LIKES
TO TAKE OFF ALL HIS CLOTHES
AND TALK ABOUT SPACE ALIENS.
FILL ME IN.
FROM THE TOP.
START WITH YOUR NAME
AND BIRTH DATE.
JOHN FITZGERALD BYERS,
11/22 IN '63.
- SERIOUSLY.
- I WAS NAMED AFTER JFK.
BEFORE THE ASSASSINATION,
MY PARENTS WERE GONNA
CALL ME BERTRAM.
LUCKY YOU.  OCCUPATION ?
I WORK FOR THE GOVERNMENT,
FOR THE MOMENT.
-WHAT DO YOU DO FOR THE
GOVERNMENT, FOR THE MOMENT ?
-I'M A PUBLIC AFFAIRS OFFICER...
FOR THE FEDERAL
COMMUNICATIONS COMMISSION.
IT WAS IN THAT CAPACITY
THAT I WAS ATTENDING...
THE COMPUTER
AND ELECTRONICS SHOW AT THE
BALTIMORE CONVENTION CENTER.
[ Byers ]  IT WAS WHERE
THIS WHOLE THING STARTED,
JUST THIS MORNING.
WE AT THE F.C.C.
ENJOY FORGING...
POSITIVE TIES
WITH THE AMERICAN PUBLIC.
IT'S OUR WAY OF SAYING,
"COMMUNICATION IS JUST
ANOTHER WORD FOR SHARING."
HI, GUYS.
YOU LIKE A BUTTON ?
UP YOURS, NARC.
[ Byers Narrating ]
OF COURSE, SOME PEOPLE
DON'T SEE IT LIKE THAT.
AT ANY RATE, THAT WAS WHERE
I FIRST SAW HER.
WOULD YOU LIKE A BUT-BUTTON ?
UH--
[ Byers Narrating ]
I'M STILL NOT SURE WHY I DID
WHAT I DID NEXT.
IT WAS SO UNLIKE ME.
THERE WAS JUST
SOMETHING ABOUT HER.
KEN, I'M GONNA TAKE
A SHORT BREAK, OKAY ?
WHATEVER.
[ Beeping, Chirping ]
[ Man ]
HELLO, PRETTY LADY.
PICTURE THIS.
CRYSTAL-CLEAR TELEVISION.
THIRTY-THREE CHANNELS' WORTH,
WITH NO MONTHLY CABLE BILL.
EXCUSE ME ?
NOW, I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE THINKIN'.
"MELVIN, ARE YOU
OUTTA YOUR MIND ?
NO CABLE BILL ?"
BUT THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I'M SAYING, AND I'M TALKIN'
PREMIUM CHANNELS HERE TOO.
YOU GOT YOUR HBO,
YOU GOT YOUR CINEMAX,
YOU GOT YOUR SHOWTIME,
ALL COURTESY
OF THIS MODESTLY PRICED MARVEL,
DESIGNED AND BUILT...
BY THE FROHIKE
ELECTRONICS CORPORATION.
[ Man ]
THERE'S A NAME THAT INSPIRES
CONSUMER CONFIDENCE.
SHUT UP, PUNK.
WHERE WERE WE ?
IF YOU WANNA WATCHMATLOCK
WITH ANDY GRIFFITH ALL BLUE
AND SQUIGGLY, BUY FROM THIS GUY.
IF YOU WANT QUALITY
BOOTLEG CABLE, YOU TALK TO ME.
IF YOU WANT A CONVERTER
THAT'LL SHORT OUT
AND BURN YOUR HOUSE DOWN,
DEFINITELY
TALK TO THIS GUY.
THAT WAS A ONE-TIME FLUKE.
I HEAT-SINK EVERY BREADBOARD.
YEAH, WHAT ABOUT CO-AX LOSS ?
DO YOU USE THE RG-6U
OR THE 52-OHM RG-8 ?
[ Blond Man ]
TRICK QUESTION.
IT'S A 99-13.
BIG MAN.
[ Fake Cough ]
NARC !
OH !  AH--
OH, GOD.  SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
SHE'S VERY CUTE.
YES, SHE IS.
THANK YOU.
WAIT.
UM, UH--
YOU JUST LOOK LIKE
YOU COULD USE SOME HELP.
SO MY DAUGHTER TURNED
THREE YEARS OLD LAST WEEK.
LAST TUESDAY
WAS HER BIRTHDAY.
I HOPE
HE REMEMBERED THAT.
HER-- HER FATHER
TOOK HER FROM YOU ?
MY FORMER BOYFRIEND.
HE KIDNAPPED HER.
IT'S A LONG STORY.
BASICALLY, I GOT INVOLVED
WITH A MAN WHO TURNED OUT
TO BE A COMPLETE PSYCHOTIC.
YEAH ?
WE WERE ONLY TOGETHER
A FEW MONTHS.
I WAS ATTRACTED TO HIM
BECAUSE HE WAS
DARK AND MYSTERIOUS,
AND THEN HE JUST
KEPT GETTING DARKER
AND MORE MYSTERIOUS.
I GOT PREGNANT,
AND HE LEFT.
[ Sniffles ]
AND THEN HE SUDDENLY
CAME BACK...
AND TOOK HER
ABOUT SIX MONTHS AGO.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
DID YOU CALL THE POLICE ?
OF COURSE.
[ Sniffles ]
THE POLICE,
THEN PRIVATE INVESTIGATORS.
THEY WERE
SURPRISINGLY UNHELPFUL.
THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
YEAH.  WELL--
[ Sniffles ]
AT LEAST I MANAGED
TO GET A COUPLE OF LEADS.
I WAS TOLD HE'S IN
THE BALTIMORE AREA.
SO HERE I AM.
WELL, THAT'S A START.
YEAH.
EXCEPT HE NOW KNOWS
THAT I'M LOOKING FOR HIM...
AND THE CLOSER I GET,
THE MORE DANGEROUS HE BECOMES.
ARE YOU... WORRIED
HE MIGHT HARM YOUR DAUGHTER ?
LET'S JUST SAY I WANNA
FIND HER, NOT HIM.
[ Sniffles ]
THIS IS THE ONLY
OTHER LEAD I'VE GOT.
THAT'S WHY
I'M HERE TODAY.
THIS HAS SOMETHING TO DO
WITH COMPUTERS.  DOESN'T IT ?
WITH THE INTERNET ?
ACTUALLY, THE ARPANET.
IT'S A GOVERNMENT NETWORK
CREATED BY THE DEFENSE ADVANCED
RESEARCH PROJECTS AGENCY.
YOU CAN ACCESS IT
THROUGH THE INTERNET, THOUGH.
SOMEHOW THIS MEANS SOMETHING
TO MY EX-BOYFRIEND.
I WAS HOPING
IT MIGHT BE A MEANS
OF FINDING MY DAUGHTER.
IF YOU WANT,
I CAN GO ON-LINE,
TRY AND FIND OUT FOR YOU.
WOULD YOU ?  OH, THAT W--
I WOULD REALLY,
REALLY APPRECIATE THAT.
UH, BY THE WAY,
MY NAME'S JOHN.
HOLLY.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
JUST LIKE THE SUGAR.
[ Chuckles ]
YEAH.
JUST LIKE THE SUGAR.
FUNNY.
[ Beeping, Chirping ]
KEN, COULD YOU MAYBE
GO TAKE A SHORT BREAK ?
WHATEVER.
OKAY.
[ Sighs ]
LET'S SEE HERE.
SO YOUR EX-BOYFRIEND
IS INTO COMPUTERS ?
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
I KNOW VERY LITTLE
ABOUT HIM,
- EXCEPT THAT HE'S PSYCHOTIC.
-[ Computer Beeps ]
[ Keys Clicking ]
[ Beeps ]
SOMEHOW THIS KICKED US
INTO THE DEFENSE DATA NETWORK.
I'M SORRY.  I THINK THIS
IS THE END OF THE LINE.
ISN'T THERE SOMETHING
YOU COULD--
I MEAN,
HOW DO YOU SAY IT--
HACK INTO ?
"HACK INTO" ?  NO !
UM--  I MEAN, TECHNICALLY,
YES, I PROBABLY COULD,
BUT-- BUT THIS BELONGS TO
THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE.
THIS IS A SECURED SITE.
I MEAN, I WORK
FOR THE F.C.C.
THIS IS THE KIND OF THING
WE'RE TRYING TO STOP.
THANK YOU, JOHN.
I APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
WAIT.
YOU DIDN'T SEE THIS.
[ Keys Clicking ]
[ Computer Beeps ]
[ Holly ]
WHAT DID YOU DO ?
IT'S A GOVERNMENT SYSTEM.
I KNOW A COUPLE
OF LOG-IN/OUT TRICKS
WITH THE VMS VERSION FIVE.
NEVER MIND.
CAN YOU LOOK UP
SUSANNE MODESKI ?
THAT'S MY DAUGHTER.
I'LL TRY.
THERE'S JUST NO WAY
OF TELLING.
- [ Beeps ]
- WHEW.
[ Holly ]
WHAT IS THAT ?
IT'S AN ENCRYPTED FILE.
WHY WOULD YOUR THREE-YEAR-OLD
HAVE AN ENCRYPTED FILE...
IN A SECRET
DEFENSE DEPARTMENT DATABASE ?
CAN YOU DECODE IT ?
I'D NEED SOME HELP.
CAN YOU PRINT IT OUT
FOR ME ?
MY GOD !  HIDE.
WHAT ?
MY EX-BOYFRIEND
IS OUT THERE.
THE PSYCHOTIC ?
HE MUST HAVE TRACKED ME HERE.
H-HE'S LOOKING FOR ME.
DAMN IT !
THERE HE IS.
YOU LOOK LIKE A GENTLEMAN
WHO'D APPRECIATE 33 CHANNELS
OF CRYSTAL-CLEAR TELEVISION.
NO, THANKS, HANDSOME.
AH, A MAN OF DISTINCTION.
PUNK ASS.
[ Byers ]  IT WAS AT THIS POINT
WE ENLISTED THE HELP
OF ONE MELVIN FROHIKE...
COMPUTER HACKER.
OH, HELLO, PRETTY LADY.
OH, YEAH.
WHAT'S WITH THE NARC ?
WE PROCEEDED TO TELL HIM
THE ENTIRE STORY.
I HOPED HE COULD
ASSIST ME IN DECIPHERING
THE ENCRYPTED FILE.
[ Byers Narrating ]
IT WAS AT THIS POINT, HOWEVER,
THAT MR. FROHIKE RAISED...
AN INTERESTING QUESTION.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.  WHY DON'T
YOU JUST KICK THIS GUY'S ASS ?
WHAT ?
NO.  I JUST WANT
THESE PAGES DECODED.
CAN YOU DO THAT ?
SURE, BABY.
MY KUNG FU IS THE BEST,
BUT IT COULD TAKE HOURS.
I SAY,
CUT TO THE CHASE.
IF PRETTY BOY CAN TELL US
WHERE YOUR DAUGHTER IS,
WE JUST BEAT IT OUT OF HIM.
BAD IDEA.
HE'S VERY DANGEROUS.
LADY, I'M DANGEROUS.
ALL RIGHT.  SO WE'LL
JUST FOLLOW HIM.
FOR ALL WE KNOW, HE'S GOT
THE GIRL HERE SOMEWHERE.
HOLLY, IT MAKES SENSE.
NO.  JUST STAY
AWAY FROM HIM.
WE'LL STAY BACK A WAYS.
JUST WAIT FOR US HERE.
COME ON, F.C.C.
BUT--  UH-- UH--
[ Frohike ]
WHAT'S HE DOIN' ?
[ Byers ]  TALKING TO SOMEBODY.
THIS DUDE DOESN'T LOOK SO TOUGH.
ACT CASUAL.
[ Male Voice Over Loudspeaker ]
THEY'RE HERE.
ALIEN INVADERS ARE AMONG US.
DETECT THEIR PRESENCE
WITH HIGH-TECH,
MODERN ELECTRONICS.
[ Beeping ]
OH !  SORRY.
THEY'RE HERE.
ALIEN INVADERS...
[ Byers ]  HE'S MOVING.
ARE AMONG US.
DETECT THEIR PRESENCE WITH
HIGH-TECH, MODERN ELECTRONICS.
WHAT'S UP, FELLAS ?
YOU LOOKING FOR SOMEBODY ?
JUST, UM, THE BATHROOM.
I DON'T THINK IT'S DOWN HERE.
HEY, YOU WITH THE F.C.C. ?
WHAT'S IT TO YOU ?
I THINK WE SHARE
THE SAME CREDIT UNION.
SPECIAL AGENT FOX MULDER.
I'M WITH THE FEDERAL BUREAU
OF INVESTIGATION.
I WAS HOPING MAYBE
YOU COULD HELP ME.
I'M LOOKING FOR A GIRL.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU'D SEEN HER.
THIS IS HER HERE.
YOU SEEN HER ?
SORRY.
HMM ?
WHAT DID SHE DO ?
WHAT'S IT TO YOU ?
THANKS, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT ?
[ Phone Ringing ]
YEAH, MULDER.
OH, HEY, REGGIE.
WHAT'S UP ?
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT ?
HER EX-BOYFRIEND
IS WITH THE F.B.I. ?
WHERE'D SHE GO ?
[ Man #1 ]  OKAY,
STAND BACK, FOLKS !
[ Man #2 ]  HEY, GUYS,
JUST WAIT A MINUTE.
EXCUSE US HERE.
HEY, COME ON !
[ Man #1 ]
LET US THROUGH.
- KEN ?
- ALL I DID
WAS PLAY DIG DUG.
I DIDN'T HACK
INTO ANYBODY'S COMPUTER.
[ M.P. ]
EXCUSE US, PLEASE.
[ Ken ]  SERIOUSLY, GUYS,
I'VE GOT, LIKE,
A CIRCULATORY PROBLEM.
I HAVE A TENDENCY
TO FALL DOWN A LOT.
WAIT.  IT WAS ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
IHACKED
INTO THEIR COMPUTER.
SO YOU'RE GONNA
TURN YOURSELF IN ?
ARE YOU CRAZY ?
A HACKER
NEVER TURNS HIMSELF IN.
I AM NOT A HACKER.
LISTEN.  WE GOT
F.B.I. AGENTS RUNNING AROUND,
MILITARY POLICE.
WHATEVER THE HELL IS GOING ON
AROUND HERE, IT'S BIG,
AND YOUR LADY FRIEND IS SOMEHOW
AT THE CENTER OF IT ALL.
SHE NEEDS MY HELP.
HOW CAN WE LEARN
WHAT'S GOING ON ?
THE F.B.I.
ARE LOOKING FOR HER.
HACK INTO THE F.B.I. MAINFRAME.
I KNOW JUST THE GUY
WHO CAN DO IT.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
A PREMEDITATED CRIME...
AGAINST THE
UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT.
HEY.
YOUR SECOND ONE TODAY.
WELCOME TO
THE DARK SIDE.
[ Man ]
OKAY, LADIES,
WHO'S DOWN FOR 50 ?
FIFTY BUCKS.
ANYONE ?
OH, MAN.
MY DIAPER-WEARING GRANNY
WOULD BET 50.
COME ON.
[ Scoffs ]
THERE'S NO GAME HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
FIFTY.
ELRON THE DRUID BETS 50.
CASH ONLY, ELRON.
I DON'T TAKE NO PERSONAL CHECKS
FROM THE BANK OF MIDDLE EARTH.
COME ON, NATURAL 20.  DADDY
NEEDS A NEW SWORD OF WOUNDING.
[ Creaking ]
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA
BRINGIN' THE NARC IN HERE ?
ME AND THE NARC HAVE
A PROPOSITION FOR YOU.
WHAT PROPOSITION ?
THE COOLEST HACK
IN THE WORLD.
LORD MANHAMMER ?
SAY IT.
YOUR KUNG FU IS THE BEST.
[ Chuckling ]
HERE.
MAKE YOURSELF USEFUL.
- WHAT DOES THIS DO ?
- BESIDES OVERHEAT
AND BURN THE HOTEL DOWN ?
IT'S A LOOP-LINE SHUNT.
ANYONE WHO TRIES TO TRACE US
WILL GET BOUNCED AROUND...
BY C AND P'S
CALL-FORWARDING SOFTWARE.
MY PERSONAL INVENTION.
OH, GOD.
I'M GONNA GET FIRED.
I'M GONNA GO TO JAIL.
I DESERVE TO GO TO JAIL.
SHUT UP ALREADY.
WHAT DO YOU NEED ME TO DO ?
JUST WATCH AND LEARN.
BINGO.
GOVERNMENT HACK IS A SNAP.
LAST WEEK I GOT INTO
THE MARYLAND D.M.V.
CHANGED MY ENDORSEMENT
SO I COULD HANDICAP PARK.
I GOT TINNITUS.
[ Blond Man ]
WHAT NOW ?
LOOK UP THE F.B.I. AGENT.
WHAT'D HE SAY HIS NAME WAS ?
MULDER.
[ Beeps ]
IS THAT YOUR BOY ?
[ Frohike ]
"FOX WILLIAM MULDER,
BORN 10/13/61.
"DEGREE IN PSYCHOLOGY
FROM OXFORD UNIVERSITY,
TOP OF HIS CLASS AT QUANTICO."
COMMENDATIONS
OUT THE YING-YANG.
"CURRENTLY ATTACHED TO THE
VIOLENT CRIMES UNIT.  SINGLE."
THERE'S NOTHING IN HERE
ABOUT HIM BEING A PSYCHO
OR HAVING A DAUGHTER.
TRY, UNDER ACTIVE CASES,
HOLLY MODESKI.
[ Computer Beeps ]
NADA.  NO CASE FILE.
TRY THE DAUGHTER.
SUSANNE MODESKI.
SHE'S SUSANNE MODESKI ?
"EMPLOYEE AT THE ARMY
ADVANCED WEAPON FACILITY
AT WHITESTONE, NEW MEXICO."
- WHITECORPS.
- OH, MAN.  LOOK AT THIS.
SAYS HERE SHE BLEW UP
ONE OF THEIR LABS,
KILLED FOUR PEOPLE,
INCLUDING THE M.P. WHO TRIED
TO STOP HER AT THE GATE.
"SUBJECT MODESKI
IS CONSIDERED UNSTABLE
AND DELUSIONAL.
"INTELLECTUALLY BRILLIANT,
YET PRONE TO CONFABULATION...
AND FITS OF VIOLENT BEHAVIOR."
"PSYCHOTIC
AND PROFOUNDLY PARANOID."
[ Frohike ]
"ARMED AND EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
DO NOT APPROACH.
CALL IMMEDIATELY FOR BACKUP."
[ Clattering ]
[ Frohike ]
OH, NO !  OH.
YOU'VE BEEN READING
ABOUT ME.
[ Sighs ]
MY NAME IS
SUSANNE MODESKI,
NOT HOLLY.
I'M--
I WAS AN ORGANIC CHEMIST...
FOR THE ADVANCED
WEAPONS FACILITY,
BUT I NEVER BLEW UP ANY LAB,
AND I CERTAINLY
NEVER KILLED ANYBODY.
ALL I DID
WAS TRY TO QUIT.
I DON'T HAVE A JOB
YOU JUST QUIT.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER ?
I DON'T HAVE ONE.
I'M SORRY.
- THE PHOTO ?
- CAME WITH THE WALLET.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
BELIEVED THE TRUTH,
OBVIOUSLY,
AND I DESPERATELY
NEEDED YOUR HELP.
FOR WHAT, EXACTLY ?
TO GET THIS.
I STILL NEED IT DECIPHERED.
THIS HAS IN IT
EVERYTHING I NEED...
TO EXPOSE THE UNITED STATES
GOVERNMENT'S PLOT
AGAINST ITS OWN PEOPLE !
ONE I UNWITTINGLY...
HELPED TO FORWARD BY DEVELOPING
THE ERGOTAMINE-HISTAMINE GAS.
- ERGOTAMINE-HISTA--
- E-H, FOR SHORT.
IT'S AN AEROSOLIZED GAS
WHICH IN SMALL DOSES...
CAUSES ANXIETY AND PARANOIA
IN ITS SUBJECT.
PARANOIA ?
GOTCHA.
SECRET FORCES
WITHIN THE GOVERNMENT
PLAN TO TEST THIS GAS...
ON THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
RIGHT HERE IN BALTIMORE !
I AM NOT MAKING THIS UP.
DON'T YOU GET IT ?
NOBODY IS SAFE.
LOOK WHAT THEY DID TO JFK.
WHAT DID THEY DO TO JFK ?
DALLAS ?  1963 ?  HELLO !
THEY WANT TO CONTROL
EVERY ASPECT OF OUR LIVES,
FROM THE CRADLE TO THE GRAVE.
THEY PRACTICALLY DO ALREADY.
[ Panting ]
HOTEL BIBLE.
WHO DO YOU THINK
PUT THIS HERE ?
THE GOVERNMENT ?
ONE IN EVERY HOTEL ROOM
IN AMERICA.
IT'S THE PERFECT VESSEL
FOR ELECTRONIC SURVEILLANCE.
NO ONE EVER QUESTIONS
ITS PRESENCE.
NOW, I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT-- THE SAME GOVERNMENT
THAT GAVE US AMTRAK--
NOT TO MENTION
THE SUSAN B. ANTHONY DOLLAR.
IS BEHIND SOME OF THE DARKEST,
MOST FAR-REACHING CONSPIRACIES
ON THE PLANET ?
THAT'S JUST CRAZY !
I MEAN, LIKE, THIS GUY
WORKS FOR THE GOVERNMENT.
I'LL PROVE IT TO YOU.
JUST HELP ME
DECIPHER THIS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, GUYS ?
[ Byers Narrating ]
OF COURSE, AT THAT POINT,
WE DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE WE HAD MUCH CHOICE.
GET IT OFF ME !
LANGLY, WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG ?
SHOULD BE UP
ANY SECOND.
OH, YEAH.
HERE WE GO.
[ Frohike ]
FAR OUT.
THANK GOD FOR SUPERCOMPUTERS.
"THE SURPRISE DEFECTION
OF DR. SUSANNE MODESKI...
"IS A BLOW TO THE PROGRAM,
BUT NOT A FATAL ONE.
"THE TIMETABLE
REMAINS UNCHANGED.
"THE FIRST E.B.O.
WILL OCCUR...
IN THE
BALTIMORE-WASHINGTON CORRIDOR
WITHIN ONE WEEK'S TIME."
- WHAT'S AN E.B.O. ?
- ENGINEERED
BIOLOGICAL OPERATION.
TOXIC ORGANIC AGENTS
USED ON HUMANS.
"SECURITY RISKS
ARE BEING ATTENUATED.
"DR. MODESKI'S TEAM
HAS BEEN PROCESSED...
AND PLAUSIBLE DENIAL
CONSTRUCTED."
WHICH IS ANOTHER WAY
OF SAYING...
THAT THEY'VE MURDERED
MY RESEARCH ASSOCIATES
AND PLACED THE BLAME ON ME.
[ Susanne ]
NOW DO YOU UNDERSTAND ?
WAIT.  HERE IT IS.
[ Susanne ]
"E-H PRODUCT
IS PRESENTLY WAREHOUSED...
"AT 204 FELLS POINT ROAD.
LOT NUMBER A-9000,
AWAITING E.B.O."
- THIS IS IT.
- "SUBJECT MODESKI CURRENTLY
MONITORED AROUND THE CLOCK.
COVERT ELECTRONICS INSTALLED
PER DR. MICHAEL KILBOURNE,
11/6/88."
WHO'S DR. MICHAEL KILBOURNE ?
MY DENTIST.
EXCUSE ME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
THAT THING
ABOUT HER DENTIST.
[ Byers ]
DR. MODESKI ?
GET IN HERE !
MY GOD !
WHAT DID YOU DO ?
[ Muffled ]
LOOK AT IT.
LOOK AT IT !
AM I SEEING WHAT
I THINK I'M SEEING ?
WHAT'S THE ADDRESS
OF THAT WAREHOUSE ?
WHERE'S THE TOOTH ?
WE FLUSHED IT.
WE WERE AFRAID IT WOULD
GIVE AWAY OUR LOCATION.
SO, WE BROKE INTO
THE WAREHOUSE.
[ Langly ]
HERE IT IS !
A-9000, RIGHT ?
ASTHMA MEDICINE ?
THIS IS HOW THEY PLAN
ON DISTRIBUTING THE GAS.
IN ASTHMA INHALERS.
THIS IS THEIR
RANDOM TEST.
NOW WE'VE GOT PROOF.
[ Mulder ]
STAY WHERE YOU ARE !
I'M A FEDERAL AGENT !
SUSANNE MODESKI,
YOU ARE UNDER ARREST...
FOR THE MURDERS OF FOUR PEOPLE
AT WHITESTONE ARMY BASE.
SHE DIDN'T DO IT.
SHE'S INNOCENT.
YEAH.
YOU THREE ARE UNDER ARREST ALSO.
MA'AM, STAY WHERE YOU ARE.
JUST LISTEN.
THERE'S MORE GOING ON HERE
THAN MEETS THE EYE.
YOU THREE,
GET ON THE GROUND NOW !
MA'AM, STOP MOVING.
I'M NOT GONNA
ASK YOU AGAIN.
[ Footsteps
Approaching ]
DR. MODESKI,
PLEASE COME WITH US.
FEDERAL AGENT.
IDENTIFY YOURSELF.
- MA'AM, COME WITH US.
- STEP FORWARD
AND IDENTIFY YOURSELVES NOW !
[ Gasping ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Frohike ]
OH, MAN.
[ Mulder Gasps ]
SUSANNE !
SANITIZE IT.
KEEP IT COMING.
THAT'S IT.  COME ON.
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
- AHH !  [ Groaning ]
- [ Men Shouting,
Audio Distorted ]
- THEY'RE HERE.
[ Groaning ]
I'M ALIVE.
[ Gagging ]
[ Muffled ]
I'M ALIVE !
WHO ARE
YOU PEOPLE ?
[ Engine Rumbling ]
[ Frohike ]
WHOA !
WHAT AUTHORITY DO YOU
HAVE TO DO THIS ?
[ Langly ]  SHUT UP, BYERS.
BAG HIM ?
NO ONE TOUCHES
THIS MAN.
EXCUSE ME.
[ Langly ]
BYERS.
SIR.
WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS ?
YOU PEOPLE FRAMED
SUSANNE MODESKI,
YOU PLANNED TO TEST
THAT CHEMICAL
ON AN UNWITTING PUBLIC.
WHY ?  FOR WHAT
POSSIBLE REASON ?
BYERS, SHUT UP !
WHO GIVES YOU THE AUTHORITY ?
- NO BAGS.
- [ Byers Gasps ]
- WHOA !  WHOA, WHOA !  GUYS !
- [ Cylinder Clicking Rapidly ]
[ Clicks ]
[ Gasps ]
BEHAVE YOURSELVES.
THAT'S IT ?
YOU'RE JUST TRYING TO
INTIMIDATE US ?  TO SCARE US
SO WE'LL KEEP QUIET ?
BYERS, I SWEAR TO GOD,
I'LL SHOOT YOU MYSELF.
IT'S ALL TRUE WHAT SUSANNE SAID
ABOUT YOU PEOPLE, ISN'T IT ?
ABOUT JOHN F. KENNEDY ?
DALLAS ?
I HEARD IT WAS A LONE GUNMAN.
[ Sirens Wailing
In Distance ]
[ Byers Narrating ]
AND THAT WAS THE LAST
WE SAW OF HIM.
ALMOST IMMEDIATELY,
THE POLICE GOT THERE.
WE... PANICKED AND HID.
YOU KNOW THE REST.
DO I LOOK LIKE
GERALDO TO YOU ?
DON'T LIE TO ME
LIKE I'M GERALDO.
I'M NOT GERALDO !
[ Gasping, Exhaling ]
[ Langly ]
OH, MAN.  IT'S NOT
ALL A BAD DREAM.
[ Langly ]
I AM IN HELL.
OH.  WOMEN.
AIN'T IT THE TRUTH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"WOMEN" ?
YOU KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT HE MEANS.
YOUR MOLAR-PULLIN' GIRLFRIEND
ROPED US IN AND LEFT US
SWINGIN' IN THE BREEZE.
- IS THAT WHAT YOU MEANT ?
- LOOK.
SHEISHOT.
BUT YOU GOTTA ADMIT,
WE'RE HERE BECAUSE OF HER.
I'M HERE BECAUSE I WANTED
TO LEARN THE TRUTH.
I ASSUME THAT WAS
THE SAME FOR YOU.
SUSANNE OPENED MY EYES TO IT.
SHE DOESN'T OWE ME ANYTHING.
IF THERE WAS SOME WAY
I COULD HELP HER STILL,
I'D-- I'D DO IT IN A SECOND.
[ Door Opening ]
APPARENTLY AGENT MULDER
CAME TO AND VERIFIED
YOUR WAREHOUSE STORY,
AT LEAST WHAT LITTLE
HE SEEMS TO RECALL OF IT.
THREE CHEERS FOR THE F.B.I.
YOU GUYS ARE FREE TO GO.
COME ON.
LET'S GO.
HERE'S A TIP:
ALUMINUM FOIL
MAKES A LOVELY HAT...
AND IT BLOCKS OUT
THE GOVERNMENT'S
MIND-CONTROL RAYS.
KEEP YOU GUYS OUTTA TROUBLE.
ONE GREEN NYLON WALLET
CONTAINING $38 IN CASH.
ONE... WHATEVER
IN THE HELL THIS IS.
DETECTIVE ?
WE GOT A STOLEN CAR
THAT TURNED UP
AT THE TRAIN STATION.
-IT'S THE ONE THAT
THE F.B.I. AGENT WAS DRIVING.
- OKAY.
SUSANNE MUST HAVE TAKEN
MULDER'S CAR LAST NIGHT.
SHE LEFT IT
AT THE TRAIN STATION.
SO ?
SO MAYBE WE CAN
CATCH UP WITH HER.
WHERE ?
SHE TOOK A TRAIN.
NO.  SHE'S TOO SMART
FOR THAT.
DON'T YOU SEE ?
SHE JUST MEANT
TO THROW THEM OFF.
SHE SAID SHE WANTED
TO GO PUBLIC.
THEBALTIMORE GUARDIAN
IS ONLY A COUPLE OF BLOCKS
DOWN FROM THE TRAIN STATION.
SUSANNE !
[ Frohike ]
ARE YOU OKAY ?
JOHN.
THEY DIDN'T BELIEVE
MY STORY.
NOT A WORD OF IT.
WHO IN THEIR
RIGHT MIND WOULD ?
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO NOW ?
- TRY OTHER NEWSPAPERS,
TV STATIONS,
NOT GIVE UP.
KEEP TRYING TO FIND
PEOPLE WHO WILL LISTEN.
PEOPLE LIKE YOU.
I APPRECIATE
WHAT YOU DID FOR ME.
ALL THREE OF YOU.
WE STILL WANT TO HELP.
YOU ALREADY HAVE.
[ Phone Ringing ]
[ Ringing ]
GUYS ?
[ Ringing Continues ]
NO MATTER
HOW PARANOID YOU ARE,
YOU'RE NOT PARANOID ENOUGH.
[ Ringing
Continues ]
TELL THE TRUTH.
REACH AS MANY PEOPLE
AS YOU CAN WITH IT.
THAT'S YOUR WEAPON.
-[ Phone Ringing ]
-[ Tires Screeching ]
-[ Byers ]  SUSANNE ?
YOU FEELIN' BETTER ?
YEAH, I AM.  THANK YOU.
I JUST, UM--
I HAVE THESE WEIRD IDEAS
IN MY HEAD THAT I CAN'T
SEEM TO SHAKE.
WHAT KINDA IDEAS ?
- WEIRD ONES.
- Y-YOU GONNA BUST US ?
I'M NOT SURE.  I JUST SPOKE WITH
MY A.S.A.C., AND HE TELLS ME
THAT DR. SUSANNE MODESKI...
IS NO LONGER WANTED
BY THE F.B.I.
SHE'S STILL MISSING,
BUT THE CASE
IS SUDDENLY CLOSED.
WHAT I NEED FROM YOU GUYS
IS TO TELL ME WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
YOU WANT THE TRUTH ?
YEAH, I WANT THE TRUTH.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO SIT DOWN.
THIS IS GONNA TAKE A WHILE.
[ Byers ]
THE TRUTH IS
NONE OF US IS SAFE.
SECRET ELEMENTS WITHIN
THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT...
SEEK TO SURVEIL US
AND CONTROL OUR LIVES.
[ Mulder ]  WHAT ?
[ Langly ]  TELL HIM ABOUT
THE HOTEL ROOM BIBLES.
[ Byers ]
YEAH, I'M COMING TO THAT.
IT ALL STARTED
WITH SUSANNE MODESKI.
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !