[ Woman ]
HELLO ?
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
HELLO.  HI !
OH, MY GOD !
LOOK AT YOU !
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS ?
HOW AM I GONNA
PUT MY ARMS AROUND YOU ?
IT'S NOT GONNA
BE LONG NOW.
YOU'RE HUGE.
I KNOW.  HI.
HI.
WELCOME.  WELCOME.
HI, SWEETIE.
LET'S GET YOU TWO SETTLED.
SORRY ABOUT THE DIGS, MOM.
I KNOW YOU HOPED YOU'D
NEVER SPEND ANOTHER NIGHT
IN BASE HOUSING.
ARE YOU KIDDING ?
THIS IS WONDERFUL.
IT'S THE EXACT SAME LAYOUT
AS OUR OLD HOUSE.
THAT'S THE NAVY FOR YOU.
BILL TELLS ME, MOM,
THAT YOU'RE STAYING
IN YOUR OLD ROOM...
AND THE NURSERY IS
GOING TO BE IN DANA
AND MELISSA'S ROOM.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I GOT IT.
[ Bill ]
THANKS, TARA.
MOM...
YOU OKAY ?
OH, YEAH.
JUST THINKING
ABOUT YOUR DAD...
AND MELISSA
AND HOW MUCH I MISS THEM.
[ Phone Rings ]
BILL ?
[ Ringing Continues ]
SCULLY RESIDENCE.
[ Woman ]
DANA ?
YES.  WHO IS THIS ?
DANA, SHE NEEDS YOUR HELP.
SHE NEEDS YOU, DANA.
GO TO HER.
WHO IS THIS ?
[ Line Disconnects ]
[ Man ]
F.B.I., SAN DIEGO.
THIS IS
SPECIAL AGENT DANA SCULLY.
MY BADGE NUMBER
IS 2-3-1-7-6-1-6.
CAN YOU TRANSFER ME
TO YOUR SOUND AGENT, PLEASE ?
I'D LIKE TO TRACE
THE LAST NUMBER THAT WAS
DIALED INTO THIS PHONE.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHO ARE YOU ?
SCULLY, F.B.I.
COULD YOU TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE ?
WELL, NO OFFENSE,
SCULLY, F.B.I.
WHAT'S IT TO YOU ?
I RECEIVED A PHONE CALL
FROM THIS ADDRESS.
IT WAS A WOMAN'S VOICE.
SHE SAID THAT SOMEBODY
NEEDED HELP.
WHEN WAS THIS ?
ABOUT 20 MINUTES AGO.
I'VE BEEN HERE 30 MINUTES.
I GUARANTEE NO ONE'S
CALLED YOU OR ANYONE ELSE.
THE PHONE'S OFF THE HOOK.
PLEASE, CAN YOU TELL ME
WHAT HAPPENED HERE ?
THIS IS MRS. ROBERTA SIM,
AGE 40.
SUICIDE.
SHE'S BEEN DEAD
AT LEAST THREE HOURS.
YOU GOT A CALL FROM HER ?
SHE MUST HAVE DIALED
1-800-THE GREAT BEYOND.
[ Chattering ]
DANA, WHAT'S GOING ON ?
THEY'RE JOKING ABOUT
YOU GETTING A CALL
FROM A DEAD WOMAN.
I THOUGHT IT WAS A DEAD WOMAN,
JUST NOT THE ONE IN THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
I KNOW IT'S NOT POSSIBLE,
BUT IT SOUNDED JUST LIKE HER.
WHO ?
OUR SISTER.
MELISSA.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO TELL YOU.
PAC BELL DOES
CONFIRM THERE WAS
AN INCOMING CALL...
FROM THIS ADDRESS
TO YOUR BROTHER'S HOUSE.
BUT FROM THIS END,
THEY SHOW NO OUTGOING CALL.
PLUS, THEY CONFIRM THE PHONE
HERE HAS BEEN OFF THE HOOK
FOR THE LAST THREE HOURS.
WHAT WAS THEIR EXPLANATION ?
RECORDS MIX-UP,
SOFTWARE COLLISIONS.
IT'S JUST SOME KIND
OF MISTAKE.
ANYWAY, I GOTTA
WRAP THINGS UP,
TALK TO THE HUSBAND.
LISTEN, WEIRD PHONE CALLS
ASIDE, THIS IS LOOKING
PRETTY STRAIGHTFORWARD.
A LOT OF PEOPLE
CHECK THEMSELVES OUT
AROUND CHRISTMASTIME.
[ Chattering ]
EXCUSE ME.
[ Picks Up Receiver,
Dialing Phone ]
[ Line Ringing ]
[ Phone Ringing ]
HELLO ?  HELLO ?
HELLO ?
[ Hangs Up Receiver ]
- EXCUSE ME.
- EVERYTHING OKAY ?
YEAH.
OH !
OH, THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
IS HE KICKING ?
YEAH, HE WAS KICKING.
HE'S KICKBOXING.
YOU HAD BOYS AND GIRLS,
SO WHICH ONE KICKED MORE ?
OH, I HAD SOME PRETTY TOUGH
LITTLE GIRLS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M ABOUT TO SAY THIS...
AS BIG AND FAT
AS I AM RIGHT NOW,
BUT I CAN'T WAIT TO HAVE MORE.
THIS IS OUR BABY,
OUR SON.
IT KIND OF GIVES
EVERYTHING NEW MEANING.
I CAN'T HELP BUT THINK
THAT LIFE BEFORE NOW
WAS SOMEHOW... LESS,
JUST A PRELUDE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER ?
NOTHING.
MOM, I'VE VERY HAPPY
FOR BILL AND TARA.
YOU DON'T SEEM TO BE.
MOM--
SEVERAL MONTHS AGO,
I LEARNED THAT,
AS A RESULT OF MY ABDUCTION,
OF WHAT THEY DID TO ME,
THAT I CANNOT
CONCEIVE A CHILD.
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
I JUST NEVER REALIZED
HOW MUCH I WANTED IT
UNTIL I COULDN'T HAVE IT.
DANA, WHERE IS IT ?
WHERE IS THAT RABBIT ?
I'M NOT TELLING !
I'M GONNA FIND THAT RABBIT
AND COOK IT !  I'M GONNA
TURN IT INTO STEW !
NO, YOU'RE NOT !
RABBIT STEW, HERE I GO !
YOU'RE NOT GONNA FIND HIM !
BILL !
[ Phone Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
SCULLY.
[ Woman ]
SHE NEEDS YOUR HELP.
WHO IS THIS ?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS ?
GO TO HER.
[ Line Disconnects ]
[ Doorbell Rings ]
MR. SIM,
MY NAME IS DANA SCULLY.
I'M VERY SORRY FOR YOUR LOSS,
AND I'M SORRY TO DISTURB YOU
AT THIS HOUR.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ?
I RECEIVED A PHONE CALL
LESS THAN AN HOUR AGO.
I WAS ADDRESSED BY NAME,
AND TOLD THAT I NEEDED
TO HELP SOMEONE, A WOMAN.
I TRACED THE CALL,
AND IT CAME FROM YOUR HOUSE.
I HAVE NO EARTHLY IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THIS IS THE SECOND TIME TODAY
THIS HAS HAPPENED.  I'D LIKE
TO GET TO THE BOTTOM OF IT.
YOU WERE HERE EARLIER.
YES, THE DETECTIVE TOLD ME...
YES.
SOMETHING
ABOUT A SCREWUP
WITH THE PHONES.
I'M IN A MEETING.
NO ONE'S CALLED YOU
FROM HERE,
NOT EARLIER TODAY,
AND CERTAINLY NOT TONIGHT.
YOU CAN'T IMAGINE
HOW BAD A DAY THIS HAS BEEN
FOR MY DAUGHTER AND MYSELF.
I UNDERSTAND--
IF YOU UNDERSTAND,
THEN YOU'LL STOP COMING AROUND,
UPSETTING ME
WITH THIS... NONSENSE.
PLEASE.
SCULLY, F.B.I.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU
AT THIS UNGODLY HOUR ?
I'D LIKE TO SEE
EVERYTHING YOU HAVE
ON THE ROBERTA SIM CASE.
THE ROBERTA SIM CASE ?
THERE IS NO ROBERTA SIM CASE.
IT'S A SIMPLE SUICIDE.
WE WENT THROUGH THIS BEFORE,
YOU AND I, DIDN'T WE ?
WHATEVER YOU WISH TO CALL IT,
I'D APPRECIATE SEEING
EVERYTHING YOU HAVE.
IN THE SPIRIT
OF THE SEASON ?
SO, WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR ?
CAN YOU EVEN TELL ME ?
IT SAYS HERE YOUR PRECINCT
VISITED THE SIMS BEFORE,
TWO WEEKS AGO.
A DOMESTIC
DISTURBANCE CALL ?
WE SENT A UNIT
BECAUSE THE NEIGHBORS
WERE COMPLAINING.
THEY WERE SCREAMING
AT EACH OTHER.
WASN'T A HAPPY HOUSEHOLD.
HAPPY PEOPLE DON'T
KILL THEMSELVES.
- THEY RAN A TOX SCREEN ?
- YEAH, IT'S JUST PROCEDURE.
IT SAYS THEY TURNED UP
HIGH LEVELS OF DORITRIPTAN.
SOME KIND OF
NEW MIGRAINE MEDICINE.
APPARENTLY,
YOU TAKE ENOUGH OF IT, YOU'RE
WEARING A CLOUD FOR A HAT.
I FIGURE SHE
ANESTHETIZED HERSELF AND THEN--
FOUND A BUNCH OF EMPTY SAMPLE
PACKETS IN THE BATHROOM TRASH,
A COUPLE MORE IN HER PURSE.
I'D LIKE TO BORROW THIS.
[ Typing ]
SHE WAS ADOPTED.
DANNY, HI.
IT'S ME, DANA.
YEAH,
MERRY CHRISTMAS TO YOU TOO.
I'M WONDERING
IF YOU CAN DO ME A FAVOR.
UM, I NEED THE COMPLETE
CASE FILES...
ON MY SISTER,
MELISSA SCULLY.
YEAH, CRIME SCENE AND AUTOPSY,
ALONG WITH THE P.C.R.s
THAT WE RAN.
RIGHT, BUT I NEED YOU
TO SEND THEM TO THE SAN DIEGO
FIELD OFFICE...
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
OKAY.  THANKS, DANNY.
- DANA ?
- WHAT ?
IS THIS WHERE YOU
STAYED THE NIGHT ?
YEAH.
SOME OF IT.
IT'S A VACATION.
WHAT ARE YOU WORKING ON
THAT'S SO IMPORTANT ?
UH... SOME UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
SO, YOU UP FOR JOINING US
THIS MORNING ?
I'VE GOT A LITTLE WORK TO DO.
CAN I JOIN YOU GUYS LATER ?
HOW ARE YOU GONNA
GET AROUND ?
I'LL RENT A CAR.
ALL RIGHT.  LUNCH.
WE'LL HOLD YOU TO THAT.
AGENT SCULLY.
IT'S BEEN, WHAT, FOUR HOURS ?
I WAS GETTING WORRIED.
I'D LIKE TO ORDER AN AUTOPSY
ON ROBERTA SIM.
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY
SHE WAS MURDERED.
WHAT, YOU GOT
ANOTHER PHONE CALL ?
I THINK IT MAY HAVE
BEEN THE HUSBAND.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT IDEA ?
YOU WANT COFFEE ?
NO, THANKS.
HE'S GOT
AN IRONCLAD ALIBI.
MR. SIM WAS
AT THE DOCTOR'S OFFICE
WITH HIS DAUGHTER.
HE WAS THERE ALL MORNING.
I CHECKED.
I TOOK ANOTHER LOOK
AT THE POLICE PHOTOS
THIS MORNING.
THERE WERE
NO HESITATION CUTS
ON ROBERTA SIM'S WRISTS.
SUICIDE VICTIMS SELDOM
MAKE THE FATAL CUT
ON THE FIRST TRY.
SELDOM, BUT NOT ALWAYS.
IS THAT ALL YOU GOT ?
NO.
WHY WAS THE PHONE
OFF THE HOOK WHEN YOU GOT
TO THE SIMS' HOUSE ?
THE WIFE TOOK IT OFF.
I'M GUESSING SHE DIDN'T
WANT TO BE INTERRUPTED.
YOUR INCIDENT REPORT SAYS
THE HUSBAND CALLED THE POLICE...
- AFTER HE DISCOVERED
HIS WIFE DEAD.
- YEAH.
BUT IF THE PHONE WAS
OFF THE HOOK WHEN YOU ARRIVED,
HOW DID HE CALL YOU ?
DID HE FIND THE PHONE
OFF THE HOOK, CALL YOU...
AND THEN HAVE THE PRESENCE
OF MIND TO RETURN IT
TO THE WAY HE FOUND IT ?
- DOES THAT MAKE SENSE TO YOU ?
- WHAT ARE YOU SUGGESTING ?
I'M SUGGESTING THAT
THERE ARE QUESTIONS WHICH
BEG FURTHER INVESTIGATION.
ORDER AN AUTOPSY.
THE STOMACH CONTENTS
APPEAR TO INCLUDE COFFEE,
WHOLE WHEAT TOAST
AND CANTALOUPE.
NO MEDICINE TABLETS.
EMPTY SAMPLE PACKETS
OF DORITRIPTAN SUCCINATE
WERE FOUND,
BUT I SEE NO EVIDENCE THAT
THERE WERE ANY PILLS INGESTED.
WELL, OBVIOUSLY THERE WERE.
DORITRIPTAN SHOWED UP
ON THE TOX SCREEN.
THEN WHY DIDN'T IT SHOW UP
IN HER STOMACH ?
IT WAS ABSORBED
INTO THE BLOODSTREAM.
I DON'T BELIEVE THE ABSORPTION
WOULD BE THAT COMPLETE,
NOT THAT CLOSE TO HER DEATH.
THEN HOW DID THE DORITRIPTAN
GET IN HER SYSTEM, MS. SCULLY ?
- A NEEDLE PUNCTURE ?
- ON THE HEEL OF HER RIGHT FOOT.
EXTREMELY TINY AND EASY TO MISS.
IT WAS MEANT TO BE OVERLOOKED.
I BELIEVE THAT THIS WOMAN
WAS INJECTED,
ANESTHETIZED
SO SHE WOULDN'T FIGHT BACK,
THEN HER SUICIDE WAS STAGED.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
- IT'S A POSSIBILITY.
THEN AGAIN,
IT'S POSSIBLE THIS WOMAN
SIMPLY STEPPED ON A TACK,
AND THE REST IS
BLUE-SKY CONJECTURE.
I'D SAY IT JUSTIFIES
OPENING A MURDER INVESTIGATION.
THIS IS YOUR DOING, ISN'T IT ?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE THE DECENCY...
TO LEAVE ME
AND MY DAUGHTER ALONE.
MR. SIM, PLEASE.
NOW YOU'RE GONNA WANT
TO CALM DOWN AND LET US
DO OUR BUSINESS, OKAY ?
WHERE IS YOUR DAUGHTER
RIGHT NOW ?
WHY ?
SHE'S AT A FRIEND'S HOUSE.
THANK GOD, SHE'S NOT HERE
TO SEE THIS.
DETECTIVE, THIS WAS
IN THE TRASH OUT BACK.
YOU GOT AN EXPLANATION
FOR THIS ?
YES.  MY DAUGHTER HAS
A SEVERE FORM OF ANEMIA.
SHE REQUIRES
DAILY INJECTIONS.
WE'LL CHECK THAT OUT.
I WANT YOU TO ANALYZE THIS,
GET A P.C.R. ON THE BLOOD.
WE NEED TO IDENTIFY
WHOSE IT IS.
OKAY.
DANA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ?
IT'S 2:00 IN THE MORNING.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN ALL DAY ?
WE WERE EXPECTING YOU
FOR LUNCH.
MOM... SIT DOWN.
THE WOMAN WHO COMMITTED SUICIDE
HAS AN ADOPTED DAUGHTER.
A THREE-YEAR-OLD NAMED EMILY.
I GOT A SAMPLE
OF EMILY'S BLOOD,
AND I HAD THE LAB
RUN A TEST ON HER DNA.
IT'S CALLED A P.C.R. TEST.
THIS IS EMILY'S.
THIS... IS MELISSA'S...
WHICH WE RAN
DURING HER MURDER INVESTIGATION.
THEY MATCH.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN,
"THEY MATCH" ?
IT MEANS...
THAT THIS LITTLE GIRL, EMILY,
IS MELISSA'S DAUGHTER.
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
YOU CAN'T DENY THAT THERE'S
A REMARKABLE RESEMBLANCE.
MELISSA WAS THREE YEARS OLD
WHEN THIS PICTURE WAS TAKEN.
SHE WAS PRACTICALLY A BABY.
ALL KIDS CAN LOOK THE SAME
AT THAT AGE.
MOM, IT'S UNCANNY.
EMILY LOOKS EXACTLY
LIKE MELISSA.
THAT'S WHY I ORDERED
THE P.C.R. TEST;
BECAUSE HER FACE MAY CHANGE,
BUT HER DNA CAN'T.
AND THAT TEST IS ACCURATE ?
THERE IS A 60% CHANCE THAT
MELISSA IS EMILY'S MOTHER.
I'M GOING TO ORDER
A MORE COMPREHENSIVE TEST:
AN R.F.L.P.
IT'LL TAKE A COUPLE OF DAYS,
THEN WE'LL BE SURE.
I AM ALREADY SURE YOUR SISTER
DID NOT HAVE A BABY.
SHE WOULD HAVE TOLD ME.
MOM...
REMEMBER
ABOUT FOUR YEARS AGO,
MELISSA TOOK OFF ?
SHE TRAVELED UP AND DOWN
THE WEST COAST.
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHERE
SHE WAS HALF THE TIME.
YOU'RE SAYING SHE WAS PREGNANT,
AND SHE DIDN'T WANT US TO KNOW ?
THAT WAS 1994.
EMILY WAS BORN
THAT NOVEMBER.
SHE COULD HAVE GIVEN HER UP
FOR ADOPTION AND NONE OF US
WOULD HAVE EVER KNOWN.
DANA, LISTEN TO ME.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GOING THROUGH.
MOM, THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH ANYTHING I'M GOING THROUGH.
IT HAS HAPPENED TO ME.
WHEN YOUR FATHER DIED,
IT WAS A LONG TIME
BEFORE HE LEFT ME.
I SAW HIM IN MY DREAMS.
THE PHONE WOULD RING
AND, JUST FOR A MOMENT,
I WAS SURE IT WAS HIS VOICE.
AND YOU'RE DOING THE SAME THING
WITH MELISSA.
YOU'RE SEEING HER
IN THIS CHILD.
BUT THAT DOES NOT MAKE THIS
CHILD MY GRANDDAUGHTER.
WE'RE STILL CONNECTED
TO THEM, DANA,
EVEN AFTER THEY'RE GONE.
LOOK AT ALL THE PRESENTS.
[ Melissa ]
DANA, QUIET.
THEY'LL HEAR US.
THIS ONE'S FOR ME.
YOU WISH.
THAT'S FOR BILLY, YOU DOPE.
THIS HAS GOT TO BE IT !
IT'S GOTTA BE
"HOTEL CALIFORNIA."
SHH, YOU'LL WAKE EVERYBODY.
- I WONDER WHAT THIS IS ?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I GOT ONE TOO.
[ Mom ]
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SHAKE IT,
DANA.  YOU CAN OPEN THOSE NOW.
THANKS, MOM.
YOUR GRANDMOTHER GAVE ME A CROSS
JUST LIKE THAT WHEN I WAS
ABOUT YOUR AGE.
IT'S PRETTY.
IT MEANS GOD IS WITH YOU.
HE'LL WATCH OVER YOU
WHEREVER YOU GO.
[ Knocking ]
DANA ?
HI.
SORRY.
THERE'S A DETECTIVE
HERE TO SEE YOU.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
I KNOW IT'S EARLY.
NOT A PROBLEM.
INTERESTING TIDBIT
ON MR. SIM.
WHAT ?
BANK DEPOSITS,
LARGE ONES--
$30,000 A POP.
THREE IN THE LAST 18 MONTHS.
ALL THE CHECKS HAVE BEEN
MADE OUT TO HIS WIFE.
THE LAST ONE WAS DEPOSITED
YESTERDAY, APRES-MORT.
WHERE'D THE CHECKS COME FROM ?
A PHARMACEUTICAL FIRM
IN CHULA VISTA.
DR. CALDERON ?
YES ?
I'M AGENT DANA SCULLY
WITH THE F.B.I.,
AND THIS IS DETECTIVE KRESGE
WITH THE SAN DIEGO POLICE
DEPARTMENT.
- WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU ?
- WE'RE INVESTIGATING THE DEATH
OF ROBERTA SIM.
- WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN ?
- YOU KNEW MRS. SIM ?
HER DAUGHTER, EMILY,
IS A PATIENT HERE
AT OUR CLINIC.
WHAT WERE YOU
TREATING HER FOR ?
SHE'S A SUBJECT IN ONE
OF OUR CLINICAL TRIALS.
WE'RE DEVELOPING GENE THERAPIES
FOR SEVERAL BLOOD DISORDERS.
EMILY SUFFERS FROM A RARE TYPE
OF AUTOIMMUNE HEMOLYTIC ANEMIA.
SHE'S A VERY SICK LITTLE GIRL.
WHAT'S HER PROGNOSIS ?
[ Calderon ]
I REALLY COULDN'T SAY.
THESE ARE ONGOING
DOUBLE-BLIND TRIALS.
IT COULD BE YEARS
BEFORE WE HAVE ANY RESULTS.
YOU'VE BEEN
PAYING THE SIM FAMILY
SOME COMPENSATION FOR THIS ?
EMILY'S A VERY SPECIAL CASE.
WE WERE LUCKY TO FIND HER.
- HOW DID YOU FIND HER ?
- HER FATHER BROUGHT HER
TO OUR ATTENTION.
THEN WHY ARE THE CHECKS
MADE OUT TO HER MOTHER ?
HOW SHALL I PUT THIS ?
THESE PAYMENTS ARE A GESTURE
OF GOODWILL TOWARDS MRS. SIM.
SHE WASN'T COMPLETELY CONVINCED
THAT OUR EXPERIMENTAL TREATMENT
WAS THE WAY TO GO.
SHE WANTED TO PULL EMILY
FROM THE PROGRAM ?
SHE FILED THE PAPERWORK,
BUT HER HUSBAND
LATER WITHDREW IT.
DR. CALDERON,
DID YOU EVER PRESCRIBE...
DORITRIPTAN INJECTIONS
TO EMILY DURING THE COURSE
OF HER TREATMENT ?
NO, I PRESCRIBED THEM
FOR THE HUSBAND...
WHEN HE MENTIONED HE WAS
SUFFERING FROM MIGRAINES.
[ Knocking ]
MARSHALL SIM.  YOU'RE
UNDER ARREST FOR THE MURDER
OF ROBERTA SIM.
WHAT ?
WHERE'S EMILY ?
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND ?
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.
I DIDN'T KILL HER !
IF YOU REFUSE
TO REMAIN SILENT,
ANYTHING YOU SAY CAN AND WILL
BE USED AGAINST YOU
IN A COURT OF LAW.
[ Kresge Continues ]
WE'LL GET YOU RIGHT IN THERE.
OH.
WE'LL JUST GET YOU BUCKLED IN
HERE NICE AND SAFE, OKAY ?
YOU LIKE THAT, HUH ?
I'LL SEE YOU SOON, OKAY ?
[ Car Engine Starts ]
EVERY YEAR, MY HUSBAND
INSISTED ON PUTTING THE ANGEL
ON TOP OF THE TREE BY HIMSELF.
A MAN'S WORK.
YES.
DANA, CAN YOU GIVE ME A HAND
IN THE KITCHEN ?
YEAH.
WHAT'S UP ?
I NEED YOU TO TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
I'M HERE, DANA.
YOU'RE A MILLION MILES AWAY.
I THOUGHT YOU CAME
TO SEE THE FAMILY.
I DID.
I THOUGHT THIS OTHER THING
WAS RESOLVED.
I THOUGHT YOU CAUGHT THE GUY
THAT MURDERED THAT WOMAN.
WE DID.
THEN IT'S ABOUT THE GIRL,
ISN'T IT ?
MOM TOLD ME.
[ Closes Door ]
YOU REALLY THINK MELISSA
HAD A BABY ?
YES, I DO.
SHE CALLED YOU FROM BEYOND
THE GRAVE TO TELL YOU THAT ?
SOUNDS LIKE SOMETHING THAT
PARTNER OF YOURS WOULD SAY.
IT DOES NOT MATTER
WHERE THAT PHONE CALL
CAME FROM.
WHAT MATTERS IS THAT
THERE IS A LITTLE GIRL
WHO NEEDS MY HELP.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT
ANY LITTLE GIRL, DANA.
IT'S ABOUT YOU.
IT'S ABOUT SOME EMPTINESS,
SOME VOID INSIDE YOURSELF
THAT YOU'RE TRYING TO FILL.
I DON'T EXPECT YOU
TO UNDERSTAND, BUT I AM NOT
GONNA JUSTIFY MY MOTIVES--
DANA ?  THERE'S
A TELEPHONE CALL FOR YOU.
HELLO ?
[ Kresge ]
MERRY CHRISTMAS, AGENT SCULLY.
GOT A LITTLE PRESENT FOR YOU.
MARSHALL SIM JUST CONFESSED.
HE ADMITTED TO BEING
AT THE HOUSE THAT MORNING ?
I GOT A SIGNED STATEMENT
RIGHT HERE.
WHAT ABOUT THE WITNESSES
THAT PLACED HIM
AT THE DOCTOR'S OFFICE ?
- I GUESS THEY WERE MISTAKEN.
- MAYBE THEY WEREN'T.
- WHERE IS HE NOW ?
- COUNTY LOCKUP.
[ Scully's Voice ]
THEY IDENTIFIED THEMSELVES ?
THEY SAID THEY
WERE HIS LAWYERS.
HOW LONG WERE THEY HERE ?
TEN, FIFTEEN MINUTES
TOPS.
DAMN IT !
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
- WHEN DID YOU GET BACK ?
- JUST NOW.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
I WAS ON MY WAY
TO THE NEIGHBORS'.
MOM AND TARA
ARE ALREADY THERE.
WHAT HAPPENED ?
MARSHALL SIM,
EMILY'S ADOPTED FATHER, IS DEAD.
THEY MADE IT
LOOK LIKE A SUICIDE,
JUST LIKE HIS WIFE.
OH, MY GOD.
DO YOU KNOW WHO DID IT ?
NO.
DO YOU THINK
IT HAS SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THAT LITTLE GIRL ?
I THINK IT MIGHT.
DANA, I HAVE TO
SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
LOOK AT THE DATE
ON THE BACK.
DOES MELISSA LOOK PREGNANT
TO YOU IN THAT PICTURE ?
IT'S ABOUT FOUR WEEKS
BEFORE THE GIRL WAS BORN.
BILL, THAT DOESN'T
PROVE ANYTHING.
MELISSA DIDN'T
HAVE TO GET PREGNANT
TO HAVE A BABY.
THERE'S IN VITRO FERTILIZATION.
THERE'S SURROGATE MOTHERHOOD.
DANA, LISTEN TO YOURSELF.
YOU'RE CREATING
THIS WHOLE SCENARIO
TO FULFILL A DREAM.
- WHAT DREAM ?
- TO HAVE A CHILD.
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND.
I KNOW THE NEED.
GOD KNOWS TARA AND I
TRIED FOR YEARS.
BUT MAKING THIS GIRL
INTO MELISSA'S DAUGHTER
IS NOT THE WAY.
YOU'RE ONLY GOING TO END UP
HURTING YOURSELF.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
HI.
HI.  I'M HERE
TO SEE DANA SCULLY.
MAY I ASK--
I'M SUSAN CHAMBLISS
FROM THE COUNTY.
IT'S ABOUT THE ADOPTION.
HI.  THANKS FOR COMING IN
ON CHRISTMAS EVE.
NOT AT ALL.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, I THINK
I HAVE A RIGHT TO KNOW WHY
YOU'RE REJECTING MY APPLICATION.
IT'S NOT MINE TO ACCEPT
OR REJECT, DANA.
WE ONLY MAKE RECOMMENDATIONS
TO THE JUDGE.
BUT AT THIS POINT,
I'D ADVISE AGAINST YOU
BECOMING AN ADOPTIVE PARENT.
YOU'RE A SINGLE WOMAN
WHO'S NEVER BEEN MARRIED...
OR HAD A LONG-TERM
RELATIONSHIP.
YOU'RE IN A HIGH-STRESS,
TIME-INTENSIVE AND DANGEROUS
OCCUPATION.
ONE THAT I SENSE
YOU'RE DEEPLY COMMITTED TO,
AND ONE WHICH WOULD OVERNIGHT
BECOME THE SECONDARY PRIORITY...
TO THE CARE AND WELL-BEING
OF THIS CHILD.
I'M NOT SURE THIS IS A SACRIFICE
YOU'RE PREPARED TO MAKE.
WELL, IT'S ONE THAT I'VE GIVEN
A GREAT DEAL OF THOUGHT TO.
I MEAN, TO BE HONEST,
I'VE STARTED TO QUESTION
MY PRIORITIES SINCE I WAS
FIRST DIAGNOSED WITH CANCER,
AND I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN
GIVEN A SECOND CHANCE.
EVER SINCE
I WAS A CHILD,
I'VE NEVER ALLOWED MYSELF
TO GET TOO CLOSE TO PEOPLE.
I'VE AVOIDED
EMOTIONAL ATTACHMENTS.
PERHAPS
I'VE BEEN SO...
AFRAID OF DEATH AND DYING...
THAT ANY CONNECTION JUST
SEEMED LIKE A BAD THING.
SOMETHING
THAT WOULDN'T LAST.
BUT I DON'T FEEL THAT ANYMORE.
I KNOW YOU'RE
A TRAINED PHYSICIAN,
AND ARE AWARE OF EMILY'S
MEDICAL CONDITION.
I WANT TO
STRESS TO YOU, DANA,
EMILY IS
A SPECIAL-NEEDS CHILD.
ACCORDING TO HER DOCTORS,
HER CONDITION IS INCURABLE.
SHE REQUIRES CONSTANT CARE,
BOTH MEDICAL AND EMOTIONAL.
THE GOOD NEWS IS YOU HAVE
FIRSTHAND EXPERIENCE
OF GRAVE ILLNESS.
THE BAD NEWS IS...
YOU'D HAVE TO RELIVE IT
THROUGH THE EYES OF A CHILD.
I REALIZE THAT...
AND I FEEL LIKE I'M READY.
WE'LL REVIEW
YOUR FINAL APPLICATION...
AND MAKE OUR RECOMMENDATIONS.
OKAY.
I WISH YOU LUCK.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
I'LL SHOW MYSELF OUT.
DANA ?
MELISSA ?
I DIDN'T KNOW
ANYBODY ELSE WAS UP.
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
HOW COME ?
YOU WORRIED ABOUT QUANTICO,
OR WHO GETS THE MOST PRESENTS
THIS YEAR ?
I GUESS I'M AFRAID
I'M MAKING A BIG MISTAKE.
I COULD TELL DAD
SURE THINKS I AM.
OH, WELL,
IT'S NOT HIS LIFE, DANA.
YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
BUT WHEN I STARTED MED SCHOOL,
IT FELT SO RIGHT.
IT JUST SEEMED LIKE THAT'S
WHERE I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE.
THEN...
BY THE TIME I GRADUATED,
I JUST KNEW IT WAS WRONG.
BUT NOW THE F.B.I. FEELS RIGHT,
AND WHAT IF THAT'S WRONG TOO ?
THERE IS NO RIGHT OR WRONG.
LIFE IS JUST A PATH.
YOU FOLLOW YOUR HEART,
AND IT'LL TAKE YOU WHERE
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO GO.
GOD, YOU SOUND
LIKE A GREETING CARD.
I DON'T BELIEVE IN FATE.
I THINK WE HAVE TO
CHOOSE OUR OWN PATH.
JUST DON'T MISTAKE
THE PATH WITH WHAT'S
REALLY IMPORTANT IN LIFE.
WHICH IS WHAT ?
THE PEOPLE YOU'RE GONNA
MEET ALONG THE WAY.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU'RE GONNA MEET
WHEN YOU JOIN THE F.B.I.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW YOUR LIFE
IS GONNA CHANGE,
OR HOW YOU ARE GONNA
CHANGE THE LIFE OF OTHERS.
[ Tara ]
HEY !
GOOD MORNING.
HEY, SLEEPYHEAD.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
DID SANTA COME ?
SANTA'S STILL HERE.
SHE ALWAYS HAD TO BE FIRST UP.
COULDN'T WAIT TO GET
TO THOSE PRESENTS.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
ENOUGH PLEASANTRIES.
I'M DYING TO KNOW
WHAT'S IN THIS BOX.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR MONTHS !
LET ME OPEN IT.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
THIS ONE'S FROM CHARLES.
FROM CHARLES ?
DON'T OPEN ANYTHING.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
EXCUSE ME.
[ Man ]
F.B.I. COURIER
FOR AGENT DANA SCULLY, PLEASE.
I'M AFRAID I NEED AGENT SCULLY'S
SIGNATURE, SIR.
I NEED YOU TO SIGN HERE,
PLEASE.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
[ Mom ]
WHAT IS IT ?
IT'S THE DNA TESTS
ON EMILY SIM'S BLOOD.
WHAT DOES IT SAY ?
IT SAYS DEFINITIVELY THAT
MELISSA IS NOT EMILY'S MOTHER,
BUT THAT THEY FOUND
STRIKING GENETIC SIMILARITIES
BETWEEN EMILY AND MELISSA.
SO MANY
THAT THEY RAN A TEST...
AGAINST ANOTHER SAMPLE
THAT THEY ALREADY HAD.
- WHAT SAMPLE ?
- WHAT ARE THEY TRYING TO SAY ?
ACCORDING TO THIS...
I AM EMILY'S MOTHER.
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !