[ Chattering ]
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
[ Man On TV ]
NOW THIS-- THIS HERE'S
A SPECIAL NUMBER.
IT'S GONNA MAKE YOUR TONGUE
ROLL OUTTA YOUR HEAD
AND DIAL 911.
[ TV: Laughter ]
[ TV: Indistinct ]
[ Garbled Shouts ]
YOU ADD IN
ALL THAT NICE SHRIMP--
[ Gasps ]
[ Man On Police Radio ]
DISPATCH, THIS IS UNIT 7...
INVESTIGATING
A REPORT OF DISTURBANCE
AT 214 PROSPECT AVENUE, OVER.
[ Female Dispatcher ]
COPY THAT, UNIT 7.
JEEZ.
POLICE !  DON'T MOVE.
KEEP 'EM IN THE AIR.
CUFF HER, JIMMY.
DAMN, SHE'S GOT
BLOOD ALL OVER HER.
HEY, KEITH.
I THINK YOU MIGHT WANNA
CHECK THIS OUT.
I THINK SHE'S BLIND.
THE DECEASED IS PACO ORDONEZ,
A.K.A. LITTLE MONSTER--
STREET DEALER, LIKED TO USE
GRADE-SCHOOL KIDS AS COURIERS.
OUT ON BAIL FOR POSSESSION
WITH INTENT.
TWO-TIME LOSER
LOOKING AT LIFE.
I HAVE THE SAME
PAIR OF PANTS.
WHO EXTERMINATED HIM ?
THAT'S A SUBJECT
OF SOME DEBATE.
THE KILLER CARVED A SINGLE
C-SHAPED CUT UP THROUGH
THE RIGHT KIDNEY.
FATAL BLOOD LOSS CAME
IN UNDER 30 SECONDS.
I'M GOING TO ASSUME THE KILLER
KNEW WHAT HE WAS DOING, AND THAT
"C" WASN'T ONE OF HIS INITIALS.
YOUR ASSUMPTIONS ARE CORRECT,
ONLY THE KILLER ISN'T A HE.
MARTY GLENN, 28.
WE FOUND HER AT THE SCENE
DOING A FORMULA 409.
UNDER NORMAL CIRCUMSTANCES,
MY DEPARTMENT WOULD HAVE HER
DEAD TO RIGHTS.
THERE'S JUST
ONE LITTLE SNAG.
SHE'S BEEN
BLIND SINCE BIRTH.
BEFORE YOUR HEART
GOES OUT TO HER,
CHECK OUT HER RAP SHEET.
FRAUD, PETTY THEFT,
AGGRAVATED ASSAULT.
BELIEVE ME,
SHE'S A REAL PIECE OF WORK.
HER JUVENILE RECORDS ARE SEALED,
BUT DETECTIVE PENNOCK
HAS IT ON AUTHORITY...
THAT TWO OF THEM WERE
DRUG BUSTS-- POSSESSION
AND POSSESSION WITH INTENT.
SO DO YOU THINK THAT SHE CAUGHT
LITTLE MONSTER TRYING TO SNATCH
THE PEBBLE FROM HER HAND ?
NOTHING ELSE MAKES SENSE.
INCLUDING HOW A BLIND GIRL COULD
GET THE DROP ON AN EX-CON...
AND BLEED HIM OUT
WITH SURGICAL PRECISION.
MS. GLENN TOOK A $60 CAB RIDE
ALONE STRAIGHT TO THE MOTEL.
THE CABBIE INSTRUCTED HER TO
ROOM 10, WHICH SHE ASKED FOR
SPECIFICALLY...
AND THEN TOLD HIM
TO GET LOST.
THIRTY MINUTES LATER,
DEAD HEROIN DEALER.
ALL RIGHT, SO YOU REALLY BELIEVE
THAT SHE DID THIS,
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW HOW.
I GOT A THEORY
IF YOU WANT TO HEAR IT.
I THINK SHE'S GOT
SOME KINDA SIXTH SENSE--
LETS HER SEE IN THE DARK,
LIKE A BAT OR SOMETHING.
I GOT 48 HOURS
TO CONVINCE THE D.A.,
OR WAIT TILL SHE KILLS
SOMEBODY ELSE.
HOW SOON CAN I MEET HER ?
[ Cell Door Sliding ]
[ Footsteps ]
OH...
IT'S YOU.
SEE WHAT I MEAN ?
IT'S NOT MAGIC.
IT'S YOUR CRAPPY COLOGNE.
WHO'S THAT WITH YOU ?
- SPECIAL AGENT MULDER.
- AND THE LADY ?
UH, SPECIAL AGENT SCULLY.
WE'D LIKE TO ASK YOU
SOME QUESTIONS, MARTY.
YOU MUST BE HAVING TROUBLE
WITH YOUR CASE, DETECTIVE.
FINE.
SUIT YOURSELF.
WHAT ARE YOU STARING AT ?
AN INNOCENT WOMAN--
I HOPE.
SO, I'M ALL EARS.
I'M CURIOUS WHY YOU'VE
REFUSED YOUR RIGHT
TO AN ATTORNEY.
UNLESS YOU'RE GONNA CHARGE ME,
I DON'T PLAN ON NEEDING ONE.
WELL, YOU COULD BE
CHARGED RIGHT NOW,
WITH THE FACT THAT YOU'VE GIVEN
NO COMPELLING REASON WHY
YOU WERE IN THAT MOTEL ROOM.
WHAT WERE YOU
DOING THERE, MARTY ?
PUTTING MINTS
ON THE PILLOWS.
THE CABBIE HAS GIVEN A STATEMENT
THAT YOU ASKED SPECIFICALLY
FOR ROOM 10,
WHICH WOULD PUT YOU
AT THE MURDER SCENE
RIGHT ABOUT THE TIME OF DEATH.
IS THAT A CRIME ?
IF YOU WERE INVOLVED
IN ANY WAY.
YOU MEAN, LIKE,
AN EYEWITNESS ?
DID YOU INTEND TO BUY DRUGS
FROM PACO ORDONEZ ?
DID YOU KILL HIM ?
MAYBE IT WAS JUST
HIS TIME TO GO.
OTHER THAN THE STAB WOUND,
DID YOU CHECK HIS
CHOLESTEROL LEVEL OR ANYTHING ?
HOW DID YOU KNOW THERE WAS
JUST ONE STAB WOUND ?
DID I SAY THAT ?
MM-HMM.
I GUESSED.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE PROBLEM IS ?
YOU'VE GOT NO MURDER WEAPON.
AND I BET THAT'S DRIVIN'
STINKY BACK THERE CRAZY.
ISN'T IT, STINKY ?
WHY IS HE HIDING ?
IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN SEE HIM.
YOU KNOW WHAT I DID
WITH IT, DETECTIVE ?
I FED IT TO MY SEEING EYE DOG.
I'M CURIOUS, MARTY.
YEAH ?  ABOUT WHAT ?
IF YOU DIDN'T KILL HIM,
WHY YOU WERE AT THE CRIME SCENE
CLEANING UP...
AND DOING SUCH
A PISS-POOR JOB OF IT ?
WHY DON'T WE JUST STOP
PLAYING GAMES HERE, OKAY ?
I MEAN, YOU PROBABLY
DON'T KNOW A FEATHER DUSTER
FROM A DUCK'S ASS, DO YA ?
I MEAN, IT'S RIDICULOUS.
YOU'RE A BLIND WOMAN,
FOR GOD'S SAKE.
SO WHY DON'T YOU TELL US
WHO DID KILL PACO ORDONEZ,
AND AGENT SCULLY AND I
CAN GO ARREST HIM...
AND YOU CAN GO HOME AND WORK ON
YOUR "ANGRY YOUNG BLIND GIRL"
COMEDY ROUTINE.
OR WE CAN JUST STAY HERE
AND ENTERTAIN EACH OTHER
FOR THE NEXT 48 HOURS.
[ Glass Clatters ]
GO TO HELL.
[ Pennock ]
SEE WHAT I MEAN ?
PUT A KNIFE IN THAT HAND--
NO.
ALL I SEE IS A WOMAN
WHO'S ADAPTED TO HER
IMPAIRMENT ADMIRABLY.
SHE'S HONED ALL HER OTHER
SENSES AROUND HER BLINDNESS.
SHE'S TAUNTING YOU.
I DON'T KNOW.  I THINK SHE
JUST WANTS US TO THINK THAT
SHE'S STRONG, INDEPENDENT.
- IT'S IMPORTANT TO HER.
-SHE WANTS US TO KNOW
SHE DID IT.
- I DON'T THINK SHE DID DO IT.
- THEN WHY WON'T SHE HELP US ?
IT'S BEEN MY EXPERIENCE
THAT INNOCENT PEOPLE DON'T
ACT LIKE THAT, AGENT MULDER.
SHE WOULDN'T EXPLAIN
HER PRESENCE AT THE CRIME SCENE,
AND SHE AVOIDED ALL DISCUSSION
ABOUT THE MURDER WEAPON.
SHE KNEW THERE WAS
ONLY ONE STAB WOUND.
YOU CAUGHT THAT YOURSELF.
YEAH.
DETECTIVE, DID YOU SNAKE
ALL OF THE PLUMBING
IN THE BATHROOM ?
I TURNED THAT PLACE
UPSIDE DOWN AND INSIDE OUT.
WELL, IF WE FIND THE WEAPON
WITH HER FINGERPRINTS ON IT,
SHE'S AS GOOD AS CONVICTED.
SHORT OF THAT,
SHE'S GONNA WALK.
MAYBE I CAN GET YOU TO
COME OUT TO THE CRIME SCENE
ONE LAST TIME.
OKAY.
YOU GO AHEAD.  I WANNA--
I WANNA INVESTIGATE SOMETHING.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Door Closes ]
[ Man ]
I'M GOING TO ASK YOU
A SERIES OF QUESTIONS.
RESPOND ONLY WITH
A "YES" OR "NO."
DO NOT JUDGE THE CONTENT
OF THE QUESTIONS.
SIMPLY ANSWER TRUTHFULLY.
IS YOUR FULL NAME
MARTELL FRANCIS GLENN ?
YEAH.
ARE YOU A RESIDENT
OF THE STATE OF DELAWARE ?
LET'S CUT THROUGH THE BULL,
OR I'M GONNA DECIDE
NOT TO COOPERATE AT ALL.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S, UH, GET TO IT.
I NEED TO ESTABLISH
A BASELINE.
I'M A RESIDENT OF THE STATE
OF DELAWARE, OKAY ?
LET'S MOVE ON.
[ Sighs ]
IS IT YOUR INTENT TO LIE
DURING THE COURSE OF
THIS EXAMINATION ?
I'M SURE YOU'LL
TELL ME IF IT IS.
DID YOU STAB PACO ORDONEZ,
ALSO KNOWN AS LITTLE MONSTER ?
NOPE.
- DID YOU PLAN OR ARRANGE
THE MURDER OF PACO ORDONEZ ?
- NO.
HAVE YOU EVER MET
PACO ORDONEZ ?
NO.
WOULD YOU EVER HAVE OCCASION
TO SEE PACO ORDONEZ
OR KNOW HIM IN ANOTHER WAY ?
STRIKE THAT.
HAVE YOU EVER HAD OCCASION
TO INTERACT WITH PACO ORDONEZ
OR KNOW HIM IN ANOTHER WAY ?
NO.
-WERE YOU PRESENT DURING
THE MURDER OF PACO ORDONEZ ?
- NO.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
ASK ME YOURSELF ?
DID YOU SEE THE MURDER ?
- I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
-YES OR NO ONLY, PLEASE.
THEN, THE ANSWER IS NO.
[ Pennock ]
NO BLOOD TRAILS
LEADING OUT OF THE BATHROOM.
WINDOWS ARE PAINTED SHUT.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
NOT A LOT OF PLACES
SHE COULD'VE STASHED IT.
[ Cell Phone Rings ]
SCULLY.
SHE'S LYING.
ABOUT WHAT ?
SHE KNEW PACO ORDONEZ,
BUT I DON'T THINK
SHE MURDERED HIM.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
THAT SHE KNEW HIM ?
I MADE HER TAKE
A POLYGRAPH TEST.  SHE PASSED
ON EVERY QUESTION EXCEPT ONE:
DID SHE SEE THE MURDER ?
WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO
REMIND YOU WHY POLYGRAPHS
ARE INADMISSIBLE IN COURT ?
NO, SHE CRACKED, SCULLY.
SHE WAS LYING.  I'M SURE OF IT.
WELL, MAYBE SHE WAS, MULDER, BUT
DON'T MAKE ME STATE THE OBVIOUS.
SHE DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
NOT WITH HER EYES.
WELL, HOW ELSE
DID SHE SEE ?
BAT VISION ?
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, MULDER, WHEN YOU
FIGURE IT OUT, GIVE ME A CALL.
[ Beeps Off ]
DETECTIVE PENNOCK ?
[ Voice Garbled ]
[ Gasps ]
SOMEBODY, I NEED A PHONE.
I GET TO CALL A LAWYER !
SOMEBODY, I NEED A PHONE !
I GOT IT.
YOU KNOW, I'M SURE THE A.C.L.U.
IS GONNA BE VERY INTERESTED...
IN HOW YOU VIOLATED
A BLIND WOMAN'S RIGHTS...
BY EAVESDROPPING ON
HER PRIVATE PHONE CALL.
SAME TO YOU.
[ Ringing ]
dddd [ Blues ]
BLARNEY STONE.
UM, LET'S SEE--
THE GUY HITTIN' ON THE REDHEAD
AT THE END OF THE BAR.
- I TOLD YOU, STOP IT !
- YEAH, WE GOT SOMEBODY
MATCHING THAT DESCRIPTION.
POP, IT'S FOR YOU.
- YEAH ?
- LEAVE HER ALONE.
WHO IS THIS ?
YOU JUST LEAVE HER ALONE.
I'M WATCHING YOU.
[ Line Disconnects,
Dial Tone ]
LET ME GUESS.
YOUR KILLER IS O.J. SIMPSON.
THEY WERE FOUND
AT THE CRIME SCENE
WITH BLOOD ALL OVER THEM.
WE BELIEVE THEY WERE WORN
BY PACO ORDONEZ'S KILLER.
HMM.  YOU'RE GOOD.
WE THINK THEY
BELONG TO YOU.
WELL, THEY DON'T.
TRY ONE ON FOR US.
AND PUT MY PRINTS
ALL OVER THEM ?
YOUR PRINTS ARE ALREADY
ALL OVER THEM, MARTY.
[ Pennock ]
HOLD STILL.
ARE YOU HAPPY, DETECTIVE ?
LOOKS TO ME LIKE IT FITS.
SOMEWHERE MARCIA CLARK WEEPS.
BUT YOU STILL HAVEN'T
GOT A WEAPON.
OH, IT'S JUST
A MATTER OF TIME.
BUT YOU HAVEN'T GOT TIME.
HOPE YOU SAW WHAT
JUST HAPPENED IN THERE.
EVEN IF THE GLOVES DO FIT,
YOU CAN STILL ACQUIT.
I THINK IT'S ARROGANCE.  I THINK
IT'S THE SAME REASON SHE AGREED
TO TAKE THE POLYGRAPH TEST.
SHE KNOWS THAT
THE PREJUDICES IN THIS CASE
ARE ALL IN HER FAVOR.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
LOOK AT THIS.
SHE LIVES IN POVERTY,
BUT SHE'S NEVER
TAKEN ADVANTAGE...
OF THE DISABILITY BENEFITS
THAT ARE AVAILABLE TO HER--
NEVER ONCE.
IT'S POISON TO HER.
THE MERE SUGGESTION...
THAT SHE'S ANYTHING OTHER THAN
A WHOLE OR COMPLETE PERSON
IS OFFENSIVE TO HER.
IT'S NOT ARROGANCE,
IT'S PRIDE.
YOU THINK IT WAS PRIDE
THAT MADE HER DITCH
THE BLOODY GLOVES ?
HER PRINTS WERE
ALL OVER THEM, MULDER.
WHY WOULD SHE DO THAT ?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
OKAY, SO BY
YOUR REASONING,
THE KILLER TOOK OFF
WITH THE MURDER WEAPON
BUT NOT THE GLOVES,
LEAVING MARTY TO COME IN,
GO STRAIGHT TO THE GLOVES,
AND HIDE THEM IN THE ONE PLACE
THAT NOBODY WOULD EASILY THINK
TO FIND THEM.
I THINK THAT'S
THE MOST ACCURATE SCENARIO
AVAILABLE TO US RIGHT NOW.
WAIT A MINUTE.
MAYBE IT'S MUCH
SIMPLER THAN THAT.
WHAT ?
WHAT IF SHE'S NOT
REALLY BLIND ?
I MEAN, SHE HASN'T
APPLIED FOR ANY OF HER
DISABILITY BENEFITS.
MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE
SHE KNOWS SHE COULDN'T PASS
THE MEDICAL SCREENING.
- YOU THINK SHE'S FAKING IT ?
- NO.
NO, BUT POSSIBLY IT'S
A CONVERSION DISORDER...
OR A FORM OF BLIND SIGHT--
A SPLIT CONSCIOUSNESS,
WHEREBY A PERSON HAS...
A CERTAIN LEVEL OF VISUAL
ABILITY, BUT THEY'RE NOT AWARE
THEY'RE ACTUALLY SEEING.
I THINK IT'S WORTH
CHECKING OUT.
[ Man On Phone ]
YO, MAN, LITTLE MONSTER'S "H"
AIN'T GONNA BE EASY.
SEE, A LOT OF PEOPLE
RESPECTED HIM, YOU KNOW ?
YOU BUYIN' OR NOT ?
YOU'RE NOT BUYIN',
I CAN GO TO SOMEBODY ELSE.
[ Laughing ]
NO, YOU CAN'T.
BUT I'M FEELIN' MAGNANIMOUS.
SWING BY IN A COUPLE HOURS.
MAYBE WE CAN DO
SOME BUSINESS.
GOOD.
YEAH, THERE'S SOMETHIN'
I GOTTA LOOK INTO FIRST.
WHEN I'M DONE,
I'LL BE IN TOUCH.
[ Man ]
EYES WIDE, PLEASE, MARTY.
GOOD.
TRY NOT TO MOVE
AROUND TOO MUCH.
ARE YOU AWARE OF
ANY SENSATION AT ALL ?
[ Gasps ]
IT'S A MIRACLE !
ALL RIGHT, MARTY,
NOW WE'RE GOING TO INTRODUCE
SOME OPTICAL STIMULI.
TRY NOT TO BLINK.
JUST RELAX FOR A MOMENT.
I'M NOT GETTING ANYTHING.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANY ACTIVITY...
IN EITHER THE VISUAL CORTEX
OR THE SUPERIOR COLLICULUS.
THERE'S NO WAY
THAT SHE COULD FOOL
THE MACHINE ?
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WHOLLY
INVOLUNTARY PHYSICAL RESPONSES.
I WASN'T GETTING ANY READING.
THEN WHAT IS THAT ?
[ Garbled Chatter ]
WHAT IS IT, MARTY ?
WHAT DO YOU SEE ?
AGENTS.
THIS IS DANIEL COSTA
FROM THE D.A.'S OFFICE.
SO WHAT DID WE FIND ?
I HEAR THE GIRL CAN ACTUALLY
SEE WITH SOME LIMITED ABILITY.
NO, ACCORDING TO
HER EXAMINER,
SHE IS COMPLETELY
WITHOUT SIGHT OR ANY KIND
OF LIGHT SENSITIVITY.
BUT SHE IS STILL OUR BEST
AND ONLY SUSPECT.
- YOU SAID YOU WERE
MAKING PROGRESS.
- WE ARE.
I'M NOT GONNA
INDICT A BLIND GIRL
ON SOME LOUSY PRINTS.
SHE DOESN'T EXACTLY FIT
THE DEFINITION "BLIND GIRL."
COME ON, FOLKS.
EITHER SHE IS OR SHE ISN'T.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
- THERE IS EVIDENCE...
OF SOME KIND OF NEUROLOGICAL
ACTIVITY WHICH CAUSED
HER PUPILS TO DILATE.
- FROM WHAT ?
- TO ME IT INDICATES
SOME REACTION TO STIMULI,
SOME KIND OF PHYSICAL RESPONSE
TO IMAGES IN HER MIND'S EYE.
HOW DOES THAT MAKE HER
THE KILLER ?
I DIDN'T SAY IT DID.
KICK HER LOOSE.
-[ Pennock ]  DANNY--
- I GOT NO CASE, PENNOCK.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS !
I'M NOT TRYING HER,
NOT WITHOUT A MURDER WEAPON.
KICK HER LOOSE.
WONDERFUL.  THANKS.
THESE BETTER STILL BE 20s.
NO, I REPLACED THEM WITH 50s
SINCE YOU'RE SO DAMN SWEET.
WANNA HEAR THE LATEST ?
YES.
DETECTIVE PENNOCK
RAN THE GLOVES FOR BLOOD TYPING
AND FOUND TWO DIFFERENT SAMPLES,
ONE TYPE MATCHING
MARTY GLENN'S.
THERE WERE NO CUTS ON HER.
ALL THE SAME,
I'M GONNA HAND-DELIVER THEM
TO THE LAB IN WASHINGTON...
AND EXPEDITE A P.C.R.
TO SEE IF SHE'S A MATCH.
LOOK AT HER.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
SHE'S CAPABLE ?
I'LL LET YOU KNOW
AS SOON AS I GET
THE TEST BACK.
[ Garbled Screams ]
WHO CALLED ME LAST NIGHT ?
WHO'S WATCHIN' ME ?
WHAT ?
AAH !  I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT !
YOU A COP ?  HMM ?
YOU WEARIN' A WIRE ?
[ Screaming ]
NO !  I'M NOT A COP !
I NEED TO GET
TO SPRING STREET !
WHICH WAY IS SPRING STREET !
SOMEBODY ANSWER ME !
FOUR BLOCKS
TO THE LEFT.
[ Horns Honking ]
WHERE ?
[ Man ]  HERE, HERE.  THERE'S
AN ALLEY HERE.  RIGHT HERE.
OKAY, I'M FINE, THANKS.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
[ Marty ]
EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME, SOMEBODY.
- YEAH ?
- I KILLED 'EM.
I KILLED THEM BOTH.
[ Door Opens ]
I READ YOUR CONFESSION.
DETECTIVE PENNOCK IS
TYPING IT UP AS WE SPEAK
FOR YOU TO SIGN.
I'LL SIGN IT.
YOU'LL MAKE HIM
A VERY HAPPY MAN.
CAN'T HAVE EVERYTHING.
AS FOR ME, I'M A LITTLE PUZZLED
BY THIS SUDDEN CHANGE OF HEART.
PLEASE.
TOO MUCH CHARITY OF HEART,
AND I'LL WANNA PUKE.
I JUST--
WHY KILL THEM ?
PACO ORDONEZ.
SUSAN FORESTER.
DID YOU EVEN KNOW
THAT WAS HER NAME ?
SUSAN FORESTER.
SHE WAS 30 YEARS OLD.
NATIVE OF WILMINGTON.
SHE WAITRESSED PART-TIME.
SHE LIVED ALONE
WITH HER TWO CATS.
SHUT UP !
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS ?
I-I-- I'VE GIVEN YOU PEOPLE
EVERYTHING YOU WANT.
I LIKE YOU, MARTY.
I ADMIRE YOU.
AND I DON'T WANT TO SEE
YOU CONFESS TO CRIMES
YOU DIDN'T COMMIT.
YOU JUST FEEL SORRY FOR ME.
NO, I DON'T.
NOT THE WAY YOU THINK I DO.
READ THE CONFESSION.
I GOT IT ALL PERFECT.
EVERY DETAIL.
HOW COULD I DO THAT
IF I'M INNOCENT ?
I BELIEVE YOU
WITNESSED BOTH MURDERS.
YOU-YOU SAW THEM SOMEHOW.
BUT YOU WERE WAY ACROSS TOWN
WHEN THEY HAPPENED.
YOU WERE A $60 CAB RIDE AWAY.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
I THINK YOU TRIED
TO STOP THEM.
YOU TRIED TO, BUT YOU DIDN'T
GET THERE IN TIME.
I DON'T HAVE TO
TALK TO YOU ANYMORE.
MARTY, WHOEVER DID THIS,
THEY'RE GONNA KILL AGAIN,
AND YOU CAN HELP STOP THAT.
I CAN'T STOP ANYTHING.
I DON'T HAVE TO TALK
TO YOU ANYMORE, PERIOD.
OFFICER !  WE'RE DONE !
WHO'S WORTH PLEADING
GUILTY FOR, MARTY ?
OFFICER !  WE'RE DONE !
YOU DIDN'T DO IT.
AND I'M NOT GONNA
LET THIS HAPPEN.
DO YOU HEAR ME ?
MARTY ?
[ Man ]
SORRY, MAN, DEAL'S OFF.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"DEAL'S OFF" ?
YOU CAN'T BACK OUT.
I DO WHAT I GOT TO DO
TO STAY ON THE DOWN-LOW.
YOU'RE SHININ'
TOO MUCH LIGHT ON ME.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT ?
SOMEBODY'S GUNNIN' FOR YOU,
AND I AIN'T GETTIN'
IN THE MIDDLE OF IT.
WHO ?
WHO'S GUNNIN' FOR ME ?
SOME OLD GIRLFRIEND OF YOURS
CALLED LAST NIGHT AND TOLD ME
I SHOULD STEER CLEAR.
SHE CALLED YOU ?
YEAH.
SAID SHE WAS
PASSIN' THE WORD.
LISTEN TO ME.
LISTEN, MAN.
SHE'S NOBODY.
SHE KNOWS NOTHIN'.
UH-HUH.  YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU AND ME, MAN,
WE'RE STILL COOL.
TRUST ME.
IF SHE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING,
HOW'D SHE GET THIS NUMBER ?
LISTEN TO ME.
I GOT NOWHERE ELSE
TO TAKE THIS STUFF.
THAT'S NOT MY PROBLEM.
JUST DON'T YOU
CALL HERE AGAIN.
[ Line Disconnects ]
[ Door Opens ]
WELL, I APPRECIATE YOUR
HELP HERE, SUCH AS IT WAS,
BUT I'D SAY WE'RE
DOING ALL RIGHT.
SHE JUST SIGNED
HER CONFESSION.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I DON'T FEEL AS GOOD
AS YOU MIGHT THINK,
YOU KNOW.
ALL YOU GOT IS A SIGNATURE.
NO LAWYER'S GONNA LET HER
GO DOWN BASED ON THAT.
I'M AWARE OF THAT.
DOESN'T IT BOTHER YOU,
DETECTIVE, THAT YOU STILL
HAVE NO CLEAR MOTIVE ?
WELL, SHE JUST NOW
GAVE US THAT--
DRUGS.
JUST LIKE I THOUGHT.
SHE EVEN TOLD US
WHERE TO FIND THEM.
I'D THIS IS GONNA MAKE IT
A PRETTY SHORT TRIAL.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
DETECTIVE, IT ACTUALLY
PROVES NOTHING.
THERE IT IS,
JUST LIKE SHE SAID.
JUST LIKE SHE DESCRIBED.
YOU KNOW, THE THING
I FIND MOST SURPRISING
ABOUT THIS CASE IS YOU.
YOU ARE ONE SKEPTICAL GUY,
AGENT MULDER.
SKEPTICAL ?
OH, YEAH.
I'VE BEEN CALLED
A LOT OF THINGS.
"SKEPTICAL" IS NOT ONE.
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
YEAH, WELL, WHATEVER.
[ Scoffs ]
SKEPTICAL.
MULDER.
WHAT ?
I'VE GOT THE P.C.R. RESULTS
ON THE TWO BLOOD TYPES
FROM THE GLOVES.
NEITHER WAS MARTY'S.
YOU WERE RIGHT, MULDER.
SHE DIDN'T DO IT.
I KNOW THAT, YOU KNOW THAT
AND SO DOES WHOEVER
MARTY'S PROTECTING,
BUT PENNOCK IS
SALIVATING RIGHT NOW.
WHAT WE HAVE TO DO
IS CONVINCE MARTY.
I GOT AN IDEA.
I'LL GET BACK TO YOU.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
WHAT DO YOU WANT NOW ?
I KNOW WHO
YOU'RE PROTECTING, MARTY,
AND I THINK I KNOW WHY.
YOU'RE PROTECTING THE MAN
WHO MURDERED YOUR MOTHER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I READ THE ORIGINAL
POLICE REPORT FROM 1970.
YOUR MOTHER DIED FROM
A SINGLE STAB WOUND
TO THE RIGHT KIDNEY,
AS DID PACO ORDONEZ
AND SUSAN FORESTER.
DEAD AT THE HANDS OF
AN UNKNOWN ASSAILANT.
I NEVER KNEW MY MOTHER.
NO.
I KNOW.
BUT FOR ONCE YOU WERE
THERE WHEN IT HAPPENED.
SHE WAS PREGNANT
WITH YOU AT THE TIME.
SHE DIED ON THE OPERATING TABLE
AS DOCTORS WERE TRYING
TO SAVE HER.
YOU WERE BORN...
JUST BARELY.
BUT THE INTERRUPTION OF
BLOOD FLOW YOU SUFFERED MOST
LIKELY CAUSED YOUR BLINDNESS.
WHAT DOES THAT HAVE
TO DO WITH ANYTHING ?
I THINK THAT
DURING THAT TIME...
AS YOU LOST ONE SENSE...
YOU GAINED ANOTHER.
AND SOMEHOW...
A CONNECTION WAS FORMED
BETWEEN YOU AND YOUR
MOTHER'S KILLER.
WHAT CONNECTION ?
YOU SEE THROUGH HIS EYES.
YOU ALWAYS HAVE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO,
YOU JUST DO.
AND BECAUSE OF THAT YOU FEEL
RESPONSIBLE FOR HIS ACTIONS,
BUT YOU'RE NOT.
AND YOU'RE SITTING HERE
IN PRISON...
FOR CRIMES
YOU DIDN'T COMMIT.
IT ISN'T GOING TO
ACCOMPLISH ANYTHING, MARTY.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Pennock ]
EXCUSE ME, AGENT MULDER.
SHE'S BEING
TRANSFERRED NOW.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY NO POINT
TO YOU DOING THIS.
WE'RE GONNA FIND HIM
WITH OR WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
I'M SORRY.
[ Buzzing ]
[ Guard ]
ALL RIGHT.
[ Chattering ]
HI, MARTY.
WHAT'S GOING ON ?
DETECTIVE PENNOCK IS
WITH THE WARDEN RIGHT NOW
ARRANGING FOR YOUR RELEASE.
[ Groans ]
WHAT ?
CHARGES AGAINST YOU ARE BEING
DROPPED.  YOU'RE NO LONGER
A SUSPECT IN THIS CASE.
HOW CAN THEY DO THAT ?
I CONFESSED.
A CONFESSION IS WORTHLESS
IF IT'S A LIE,
AND YOURS WAS A LIE.
[ Sighs ]
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN
TELLING THEM ?
JUST THAT YOU'RE INNOCENT,
WHICH IS SOMETHING THEY WOULD'VE
FOUND OUT ON THEIR OWN ANYWAY.
THE LOCKER YOU SENT US TO ?
IT HAD PRINTS ON IT,
BUT THEY WEREN'T YOURS.
I WAS CAREFUL.
SOMEBODY ELSE
WASN'T SO CAREFUL.
CHARLES WESLEY GOTTS,
AN EX-CON.
CONVICTED IN 1970
OF AGGRAVATED ASSAULT.
HE WAS PAROLED
THREE WEEKS AGO, AND HE'S
BEEN MISSING EVER SINCE.
NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
I HAPPEN TO
BELIEVE THAT, MARTY.
P.C.R. TEST CONFIRMED
THAT IT WAS HIS BLOOD
ON THE GLOVE.
THE TEST CONFIRMED
SOMETHING ELSE, MARTY.
HE'S YOUR FATHER.
THAT WAS THE CONNECTION.
HMM.
[ Pennock ]
OKAY, WE'RE ALL SET.
THAT IS, IF EVERYTHING'S
TAKEN CARE OF ON THIS END.
WHAT'S HE TALKIN' ABOUT ?
DETECTIVE PENNOCK
HAS AGREED TO...
NOT PURSUE AIDING
AND ABETTING CHARGES IF
YOU AGREE TO HELP US--
IF YOU AGREE
TO HELP US FIND HIM.
WE NEED YOUR HELP,
MARTY.
YOU CAN END IT NOW.
I CAN END THIS.
I'M SURE THAT'S WHAT
YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED.
I NEVER WANTED TO SPEND MY LIFE
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
I HAD NO CHOICE.
HMM.
IF I HELP YOU,
WILL YOU PROTECT ME
UNTIL HE'S CAUGHT ?
I WILL PERSONALLY
GUARANTEE YOUR SAFETY.
HMM.
TAKE ME HOME.
[ Man On Police Radio ]
MOVING INTO POSITION
AT THE BACK EXIT.
- ALL RIGHT.  STAND BY.
-COPY THAT.
JUST IN TIME
FOR THE SURPRISE PARTY.
SHE TOLD YOU
HE'D BE IN THERE ?
YEAH.  SHE DESCRIBED
THIS PLACE PERFECTLY,
RIGHT DOWN TO THE MATCHBOOKS.
WHAT MADE HER
DECIDE TO COOPERATE ?
SHE WANTS TO STOP HIM.
ALL OF A SUDDEN ?
WHY DIDN'T SHE TELL US
HIS NAME BEFORE NOW ?
SHE DIDN'T KNOW HIS NAME.
THEY NEVER MET.  HE'S BEEN
IN PRISON HER ENTIRE LIFE.
YET ACCORDING TO YOU,
SHE'S BEEN SEEING THROUGH
HIS EYES THE WHOLE TIME.
I DON'T THINK SHE WAS SURE
EXACTLY WHAT SHE WAS SEEING.
IT WAS MORE LIKE A CONSTANT
IMAGE IN HER MIND SHE LEARNED
TO LIVE WITH OVER TIME--
UP UNTIL THREE WEEKS AGO.
WHEN THE MURDERS STARTED.
HE WAS PAROLED
AND EVERYTHING CHANGED.
WELL, IF ALL THIS IS TRUE,
LET'S GO GET HIM.
MULDER ?
EVERYTHING'S CHANGED
FOR HER, SCULLY.
I DON'T THINK WE'RE GONNA
FIND HIM IN THERE.
NEED SOME HELP
OVER THERE ?
NO.
SHOULDA KNOWN.
NOW, YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PACK
EVERYTHING YOU OWN.
I PROMISE YOU,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE IN
PROTECTIVE CUSTODY THAT LONG.
IT'S TOO LATE
FOR THAT ANYWAY.
WHY'S THAT ?
GOTTS IS ALREADY HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKIN' ABOUT ?
HE'S BEEN KEEPING TABS ON YOU
FOR ABOUT A DAY.
NOW HE KNOWS WHERE I LIVE.
HE'S READING THE NAMES
ON THE MAILBOXES RIGHT NOW.
WHAT ?
HOW COULD YOU--
[ Grunts ]
HOW DID YOU KNOW HE
WOULDN'T BE IN THERE ?
SHE MISDIRECTED US ON PURPOSE.
SHE'S STILL PROTECTING HIM ?
NO, SHE'S NOT.
SHE NEVER WAS.
PENNOCK'S NOT PICKING UP.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
IT'S NOT HIM SHE'S BEEN
PROTECTING.  IF HE GOES BACK
TO PRISON, SO DOES SHE.
UNTIL NOW,
SHE'S NEVER HAD A CHOICE.
[ Clicks ]
[ Whispers ]
I HATE THE WAY YOU SEE ME.
MULDER.
SHE DID THIS ONE.
TRUST ME.
NOT MUCH TO LOOK AT, IS IT ?
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT
THEY TELL ME.
YOU WERE AT THE SENTENCING,
AGENT MULDER.
IS IT MY COLOGNE ?
NO, I JUST KNEW
YOU'D BE THERE.
MARTY, LET ME SPEAK TO
THE JUDGE ON YOUR BEHALF.
NO.
WE FOUND WHERE
HE'D BEEN STAYING.
IT'S A MOTEL NOT FAR
FROM WHERE PACO ORDONEZ
HAD BEEN MURDERED.
AND BEFORE THAT,
ATLANTIC CITY.
HMM.  I'D NEVER SEEN
THE OCEAN BEFORE.
AND NOW,
WHEN I CLOSE MY EYES,
OR EVEN WHEN I OPEN THEM,
THAT'S ALL I SEE.
YOU'RE LUCKY HE WASN'T
A FAN OF THE ICE CAPADES.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Man On P.A. ]
LIGHTS OUT.
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !