-[ Announcer ]  LAST SEASON.
-WHAT WE HAVE IS THE CORPUS...
OF AN EXTRATERRESTRIAL
BIOLOGICAL ENTITY.
THE ICE CORE SAMPLES I TOOK,
THEY CAN'T BE FAKED.
[ Mulder ]
I REFUSE TO BELIEVE
THAT IT'S NOT TRUE.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
IT'S ALL BEEN ORCHESTRATED.
A HOAX.
WHICH YOU'VE BEEN USED
TO PERPETUATE.
-[ Gunshot ]
- HE SAID THE MEN
BEHIND THIS HOAX...
GAVE ME THIS DISEASE
TO MAKE YOU BELIEVE.
EARLY THIS MORNING
I GOT A CALL FROM THE POLICE...
ASKING ME TO COME
TO AGENT MULDER'S APARTMENT.
THE DETECTIVE ASKED ME--
HE NEEDED ME
TO IDENTIFY A BODY.
AGENT SCULLY--
AGENT MULDER DIED
LATE LAST NIGHT...
FROM AN APPARENT SELF-INFLICTED
GUNSHOT WOUND TO THE HEAD.
WHEN WE SPEAK OF LIFE
BEYOND THE EARTH,
WHAT WE GENERALLY MEAN...
IS, OF COURSE,
INTELLIGENT LIFE,
SOMETHING RESEMBLING
OUR NOBLE SELVES.
IT IS HIGHLY PROBABLE
THAT THERE ARE...
SUCH INTELLIGENT FORMS
OF LIFE...
IN OTHER GALAXIES
IN THE UNIVERSE.
[ Sighs ]
AND IT IS EVEN MORE PROBABLE...
THAT MANY OF THESE FORMS
ARE VASTLY MORE INTELLIGENT
THAN WE.
[ Mulder Narrating ]
I'VE HELD A TORCH
IN THE DARKNESS...
TO GLANCE UPON
A TRUTH UNKNOWN;
AN ACT OF FAITH BEGUN
WITH AN INELOQUENT CERTAINTY...
THAT MY JOURNEY
PROMISED THE CHANCE
NOT JUST OF UNDERSTANDING,
BUT OF RECOVERY;
THAT THE DISAPPEARANCE
OF MY SISTER 23 YEARS AGO...
WOULD COME TO BE EXPLAINED;
AND THAT THE PURSUIT
OF THESE GREATER TRUTHS...
ABOUT THE EXISTENCE
OF EXTRATERRESTRIAL LIFE...
MIGHT EVEN REUNITE US.
A BELIEF WHICH I NOW KNOW
TO BE FALSE AND UNINFORMED
IN THE EXTREME.
MY FOLLY REVEALED BY FACTS
WHICH ILLUMINATE...
BOTH MY ARROGANCE
AND SELF-DECEPTION.
IF ONLY THE TRAGEDY
HAD BEEN MINE ALONE,
MIGHT IT BE MORE EASY TONIGHT
TO BRING THIS JOURNEY
TO ITS END.
[ Phone Ringing ]
[ Man ]
AGENT MULDER ?
AGENT MULDER.
YEAH.
THERE'S A MATTER
OF SECURITY.  SOMETHING
I HADN'T ANTICIPATED.
JUST AFTER I LEFT
YOUR APARTMENT--
WHO ARE YOU ?
JUST AFTER OUR LAST
CONVERSATION, I WAS FOLLOWED--
WHO ARE YOU ?
ARE YOU LISTENING,
AGENT MULDER ?
ARE YOU HEARING ME ?
WE CAN'T SPEAK RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE REASON TO BELIEVE
THAT THESE--
DID THEY GIVE AGENT SCULLY
THIS DISEASE ?
DID THEY DO THIS TO HER
BECAUSE OF ME ?
THEY MAY BE LISTENING,
AGENT MULDER.
THEY MAY BE WATCHING YOU,
EVERYTHING YOU DO AND SAY.
ARE YOU LISTENING,
AGENT MULDER ?
[ Exhales ]
PUT THAT OUT !
BACK AWAY !
GET AWAY.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Machine Beeps ]
YOU HAVE NO NEW MESSAGES.
[ Beep ]
- [ Mulder ]
KEEP GOING, F.B.I. WOMAN.
- MULDER ?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
WHY ARE YOU SITTING
IN MY BEDROOM IN THE DARK ?
IT WAS TOO CROWDED IN MY
APARTMENT.  I COULDN'T SLEEP.
I'M NOT KIDDING,
MULDER.
GOOD.
'CAUSE NEITHER AM I.
THERE'S A DEAD MAN
ON THE FLOOR OF MY APARTMENT,
AND IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE HE STARTS TO STINK
THE PLACE UP.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, MULDER ?
WHAT'S GOING ON ?
APPARENTLY SOMEBODY THINKS
MY LIFE IS INTERESTING ENOUGH
TO PUT ON VIDEOTAPE.
MY APARTMENT'S BEEN UNDER
ELECTRONIC SURVEILLANCE
FOR AT LEAST TWO MONTHS.
LOOK AT THIS.  COURTESY
OF THE U.S. GOVERNMENT.
THAT'S THE DEAD MAN
IN YOUR APARTMENT ?
YEAH.  HE WORKS--
HE WORKED FOR THE
DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE.
HOW DID HE DIE, MULDER ?
GUNSHOT WOUND
TO THE FACE.
HAVE YOU CONTACTED ANYBODY
AT THE BUREAU ?
I CAN'T DO THAT, SCULLY.
I CAN'T GO TO THE AUTHORITIES
WITH THIS.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
- THIS MAN, OSTELHOFF,
WORKED FOR THE MILITARY.
ARE YOU BEGINNING TO GET
THE PICTURE ?  DO YOU SEE
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE ?
THAT THE HOAX IS CONNECTED
TO THE MILITARY, JUST LIKE
KRITSCHGAU SAID IT WAS.
THIS HOAX, YOUR CANCER,
EVERYTHING.
IT JUST DOESN'T LEAD BACK
TO THE MILITARY.
IT LEADS RIGHT BACK
TO THE F.B.I.
WHAT ?
THIS MAN OSTELHOFF WAS SET UP
IN THE APARTMENT DIRECTLY
ABOVE MINE.
I CAUGHT HIM TRYING TO DESTROY
PHONE RECORDS ON WHICH THE
SAME NUMBER WAS CALLED 17 TIMES.
THIS IS THE P.B.X. OPERATOR
AT THE BUREAU.
YEAH.
WHO WOULD HE BE CALLING
AT THE F.B.I. ?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- MULDER, HOW LONG
HAS THIS BEEN GOING ON ?
MAYBE SINCE THE BEGINNING, SINCE
YOU JOINED ME ON THE X-FILES.
THAT WOULD MEAN THAT FOR
FOUR YEARS WE'VE BEEN NOTHING
MORE THAN PAWNS IN A GAME;
THAT IT WAS A LIE
FROM THE BEGINNING.
MULDER, THESE MEN.
YOU GIVE THEM YOUR FAITH
AND YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
TRUST THEM WITH YOUR LIFE.
THERE ARE THOSE
WHO CAN BE TRUSTED.
WHAT I NEED TO KNOW IS
WHO AMONG THEM IS NOT.
I WILL NOT ALLOW THIS TREASON
TO PROSPER.  NOT IF THEY'VE
DONE THIS TO YOU.
MULDER, WE CAN'T GO TO THE
BUREAU MAKING THESE ACCUSATIONS.
BUT AS THEY LIE TO US,
WE CAN LIE TO THEM.
A LIE TO FIND THE TRUTH.
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
[ Mulder Narrating ]
LET THE TRUTH BE KNOWN
THOUGH THE HEAVENS FALL.
THE WEB OF LIES ENTANGLING US
CAN NOW BE CONNECTED...
BACK TO THE VERY INSTITUTION
WHICH BROUGHT US TOGETHER.
THE FACTS SUPPORTED
BY A BYZANTINE PLOT,
EXECUTED BY SOMEONE
INSIDE THE F.B.I.,
WHO, IF NAMED,
AGENT SCULLY ?
COULD BE TIED TO THE HOAX
MEANT TO DESTROY ME...
AND TO THE TERMINAL DISEASE
INFLICTED ON SCULLY.
IN FOUR YEARS I HAVE SHARED
MY PARTNER'S PASSIONATE SEARCH
FOR THE TRUTH.
AND IF MY PART HAS BEEN
A DECEPTION,
I HAVE NEVER SEEN HER INTEGRITY
WAVER OR HER HONOR COMPROMISED.
IS IT HIM ?
BUT NOW, I ASK HER TO LIE...
YEAH.
TO THE PEOPLE LYING TO US--
A DANGEROUS LIE
TO FIND THE TRUTH;
TO FIND THE MEN WHO WOULD BE
REVEALED AS ITS ENEMY,
AS OUR ENEMY.
AS THE ENEMY WITHIN.
AGENT SCULLY.
IS IT TRUE ?
YES, SIR.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ?
I'M, UH--
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
THEY ASKED ME TO COME DOWN
AND IDENTIFY THE BODY.
WELL, HOW'D YOU MAKE
THE I.D. ?
THE WORD FROM ALEXANDRIA P.D.
IS IT WAS SELF-INFLICTED.
A SHOTGUN BLAST TO THE FACE.
I SAW MULDER EARLIER
THIS MORNING.  HE WAS
WEARING THE SAME CLOTHES.
I'M VERY SORRY.
AGENT SCULLY.
SECTION CHIEF BLEVINS
WANTS YOU IN FOR QUESTIONING
ON THIS.
HE BELIEVES YOU HAVE INFORMATION
YOU HAVEN'T COME FORWARD WITH.
THE MILITARY CONNECTION
TO THE CONSPIRACY WE HAD PIERCED
WAS NOW UNDENIABLE.
THE MAN WHO LAY DEAD
IN MY APARTMENT WORKED
FOR THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE...
AT ITS ADVANCED RESEARCH
FACILITY.
WHAT I MIGHT FIND HERE,
I WAS UNCERTAIN OF,
BUT MY CRIME
HAD PROVIDED ME ACCESS.
AS LONG THEY BELIEVED
SCULLY'S LIE THAT IT WAS ME
LYING ON THAT FLOOR,
I MIGHT LEARN TRUTHS HERE.
BUT IF OUR LIES WERE DISCOVERED,
BOTH SCULLY AND I WOULD BE
DISCOVERED WITH THEM.
AGENT SCULLY,
PLEASE HAVE A SEAT.
SOME TIME HAS PASSED
SINCE YOU WERE FIRST
IN THIS OFFICE.
YES, SIR.
FOUR YEARS.
FROM ALL REPORTS, YOUR WORK
ON THE X-FILES BROUGHT YOU
VERY CLOSE TO AGENT MULDER.
YES, SIR.
WE'RE ALL SORRY ABOUT
WHAT'S HAPPENED, AGENT SCULLY.
BUT THAT'S NOT
WHY I'M HERE.
YOU'RE HERE BECAUSE
WE'VE BEEN INFORMED
BY THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE...
THAT PRIOR TO
AGENT MULDER'S ACCIDENT...
YOU MAY HAVE BEEN CONTACTED
BY A D.O.D. EMPLOYEE.
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THAT HE GAVE YOU
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
HE HAD INFORMATION ABOUT THE
DISCOVERY OF WHAT AGENT MULDER
BELIEVED TO BE AN ALIEN CORPSE.
HE, UH--  HE SAID THE BODY
WAS PART OF A HOAX.
HE PROVIDED EVIDENCE
OF THIS ?
N-NO HARD EVIDENCE, SIR.
NO.
AGENT SCULLY,
I SUGGEST YOU TELL US
EVERYTHING YOU KNOW.
IF YOU HAVE ANY KNOWLEDGE
OF THIS MAN, YOU SHOULD
SPEAK UP NOW.
WHAT KNOWLEDGE ?
HIS NAME.
WHATEVER YOU'RE WITHHOLDING,
YOU'LL BE ASKED TO EXPLAIN
YOURSELF TONIGHT...
AT A JOINT F.B.I. PANEL
I'VE ASKED ASSEMBLED
ON THIS MATTER.
IS THIS THE MAN ?
MICHAEL KRITSCHGAU ?
YES.
[ Man On P.A., Indistinct ]
HEY !
HOW'D YOU GET IN HERE ?
THROUGH THE FRONT DOOR.
YOU CAN'T BYPASS SECURITY.
YOU CAN WHEN YOU HAVE
THE CARD.
PUT THAT AWAY.
PUT IT AWAY.
YOU KNEW MY APARTMENT
WAS BEING SURVEILLED.
HOW ?
[ Chuckles ]
COME WITH ME.
[ Lock Clicks ]
I WAS FOLLOWED FROM YOUR
APARTMENT THE NIGHT WE SPOKE.
SOMEONE AT THE F.B.I.
IS INVOLVED.
THIS MAN OSTELHOFF
WAS IN CONTACT WITH SOMEBODY--
HOW'D YOU GET HIS CARD ?
I FOUND IT ON A DEAD MAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT IS,
WHAT YOU HAVE IN YOUR HAND ?
IT GIVES YOU
LEVEL FOUR CLEARANCE.
THAT MEANS I GET TO DINE
AT THE OFFICER'S CLUB ?
YOU HAVE ACCESS TO EVERYTHING.
THINGS I DON'T.  THINGS I CAN
ONLY TELL YOU ABOUT.
I NEED TO KNOW
WHO DID THIS TO SCULLY.
WHAT YOU CAN HAVE,
WHAT YOU MAY FIND,
- IS SO MUCH MORE THAN THAT.
- WHAT ?
WHAT YOU WANT
MOST DESPERATELY OF ALL.
THE CURE
FOR SCULLY'S CANCER ?
[ Woman ]
FEDERAL BUREAU OF INVESTIGATION.
HOW MAY I DIRECT YOUR CALL ?
COMMUNICATIONS CENTER,
PLEASE.
ONE MOMENT.
[ Line Ringing ]
- COMMUNICATIONS, HOLLY.
- HOLLY, DANA SCULLY.
DANA, I'M SO SORRY ABOUT
WHAT'S HAPPENED.  I JUST HEARD.
HOLLY, I NEED YOUR HELP
ON SOMETHING.
I WAS HOPING THAT YOU COULD
HELP ME WITH SOME INFORMATION.
WHAT DO YOU NEED ?
I HAVE SOME CALLS
PLACED AT THE BUREAU
ON CONSECUTIVE DATES.
ON THE SIXTH, SEVENTH, EIGHTH,
NINTH AND TENTH.
THEY CAME IN
TO THE P.B.X. OPERATOR.
THE FIRST WAS AT 11:21.
THE NEXT AT 11:14, 3:07,
2:02 AND 5:12.
THEY WOULD HAVE ALL
BEEN TRANSFERRED
TO THE SAME EXTENSION.
- AND YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR THAT EXTENSION ?
- YES.
I'VE GOT FIVE CALLS MATCHING
THOSE TIMES AND DATES...
TRANSFERRED TO
AN EXECUTIVE LEVEL EXTENSION.
- WHOSE ?
- IT'S A BRANCH EXTENSION.  IT
COULD BE ANYONE AT THAT LEVEL.
WOULD ASSISTANT DIRECTOR SKINNER
BE AT THAT EXTENSION ?
[ Keys Clacking ]
YES.
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
YOU TAKE CARE NOW, DANA.
[ Phone Rings ]
YES ?
[ Man ]
SPECIAL AGENT SCULLY ?
- YES.
- THIS IS DR. VITAGLIANO...
AT THE
PALEOCLIMATOLOGY DEPARTMENT
AT AMERICAN UNIVERSITY.
YOU ASKED ME TO LOOK INTO
THESE ICE CORE SAMPLES FOR YOU.
RIGHT.  I'M SORRY THAT
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN BACK TO YOU.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO COME
DOWN HERE TO THE LAB.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I KNOW YOU'RE GONNA
WANT TO SEE FOR YOURSELF.
WHAT AM I LOOKING FOR ?
LEVEL FOUR IS A BIOLOGICAL
QUARANTINE WING.
IT HOUSES A SERIES OF LABS
AND MEDICAL FACILITIES--
AN ELABORATE SYSTEM
FOR THE STORAGE OF
VAST QUANTITIES OF DNA.
DNA FROM WHOM ?
VIRTUALLY EVERY AMERICAN
BORN SINCE 1945.
EVERY IMMIGRANT,
EVERY INDIGENOUS PERSON...
WHO'S EVER GIVEN
BLOOD OR TISSUE
TO A GOVERNMENT DOCTOR.
THIS IS WHAT I WAS TELLING YOU,
AGENT MULDER.  THIS IS THE HOAX
INTO WHICH YOU'VE BEEN DRAWN.
THE ROOTS GO BACK 50 YEARS
TO THE END OF WORLD WAR II,
PLAYING ON A VIRULENT NATIONAL
APPETITE FOR BOGUS REVELATION...
AND A PUBLIC NEWLY FEARFUL
OF SOMETHING CALLED
THE ATOM BOMB,
THE U.S. MILITARY COMMAND BEGAN
TO FAN THE FLAMES OF WHAT WERE
CALLED "FLYING SAUCER STORIES."
THERE ARE TRUTHS
WHICH CAN KILL A NATION.
THE MILITARY NEEDED SOMETHING
TO DEFLECT ATTENTION AWAY FROM
ITS ARMS STRATEGY--
GLOBAL DOMINATION
THROUGH THE CAPABILITY
OF TOTAL ENEMY ANNIHILATION.
THE NUCLEAR CARD WAS FINE
AS LONG AS WE ALONE
COULD PLAY IT.
BUT THE GENERALS AND POLITICOS
KNEW THAT WHAT THEY COULD NOT
WIN WAS A PUBLIC RELATIONS WAR.
THOSE PHOTOS FROM NAGASAKI
AND HIROSHIMA...
WERE NOT FACES AMERICANS
WANTED TO SEE IN A MIRROR.
OPPENHEIMER KNEW IT,
BUT WE SILENCED HIM.
WHEN THE RUSSIANS
DEVELOPED THE BOMB,
THE FEAR IN THE MILITARY...
WAS NOT FOR SAFETY AT HOME,
BUT FOR ARMISTICE AND TREATY.
THE BUSINESS OF AMERICA
ISN'T BUSINESS, IT'S WAR.
SINCE ANTIETAM, NOTHING
HAS DRIVEN THE ECONOMY FASTER.
WE NEEDED A REASON
TO KEEP SPENDING MONEY.
WHEN THERE
WASN'T A WAR TO JUSTIFY IT,
WE CALLED IT WAR ANYWAY.
THE COLD WAR WAS ESSENTIALLY
A 50-YEAR PUBLIC RELATIONS
BATTLE,
A PITCHED GAME OF CHICKEN
AGAINST AN ENEMY WE NOT MUCH
MORE THAN CALLED NAMES.
THE COMMUNISTS CALLED US
A FEW NAMES TOO.
"WE WILL BURY YOU,"
KHRUSHCHEV SAID, AND THE PUBLIC
BELIEVED IT.
AFTER WHAT McCARTHY HAD DONE
THEY ATE IT WITH A BIG SPOON.
WE SQUARED OFF A FEW TIMES
IN CUBA, KOREA AND VIETNAM,
BUT NOBODY DROPPED THE BOMB,
NOBODY DARED.
WHAT DOES ANY OF THIS HAVE TO
DO WITH FLYING SAUCERS ?
[ Kritschgau ] THE U.S. MILITARY
SAW A GOOD THING IN '47
WHEN THE ROSWELL STORY BROKE.
THE MORE WE DENIED IT, THE MORE
PEOPLE BELIEVED IT WAS TRUE.
ALIENS HAD LANDED.
A MADE-TO-ORDER COVER STORY
FOR GENERALS LOOKING TO DEVELOP
THE NATIONAL WAR CHEST.
THEY OPENED OFFICIAL
INVESTIGATIONS WITH NAMES
LIKE GRUDGE, TWINKLE,
PROJECT BLUE BOOK,
MAJESTIC 12.
THEY BROUGHT IN COLLEGE
PROFESSORS AND CONGRESSMEN
AND FED THEM ENOUGH BOGUS FACT,
ENOUGH FUZZY PHOTOS
AND EYEWITNESS ACCOUNTS
THAT THEY BELIEVED IT TOO.
THEY EVEN HOOKED DOUG MacARTHUR,
FOR GOD'S SAKE.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW FORTUITOUS
THE TIMING OF IT ALL WAS.
DO YOU KNOW WHEN THE FIRST
SUPERSONIC FLIGHT WAS,
AGENT MULDER ?
1947.
SOON EVERY EXPERIMENTAL
AIRCRAFT BEING FLOWN
WAS A U.F.O. SIGHTING.
WHEN THE ABDUCTION STORIES
STARTED UP, IT WAS TOO PERFECT.
WE'D ALMOST GOTTEN CAUGHT
IN KOREA, AN AMBITIOUS MISSTEP.
CHINA AND THE SOVIETS KNEW IT.
THE U.N. GOT ALL HEATED UP
AT US.
GERM WARFARE.
WE WERE ACCUSED OF USING IT
ON THE KOREANS.
YEAH.
IT WAS DEVELOPMENTAL THEN,
NOTHING LIKE WHAT WE
AND THE RUSSIANS HAVE NOW.
THE BIOWEAPONS
USED IN THE GULF WAR
WERE SO INGENIOUS...
AS TO BE ALMOST UNDETECTABLE--
DEVELOPED RIGHT IN THIS
VERY BUILDING.
AND ALL THESE REPORTS
OF ABDUCTIONS, YOU'RE SAYING
THEY'VE ALL BEEN LIES.
NOT LIES, EXACTLY,
BUT CITIZENS TAKEN UNSUSPECTING
AND TESTED--
A CLASSIFIED MILITARY PROJECT
ABOVE TOP SECRET
AND STILL ONGOING.
YOU'VE HEARD THE RECENT
DENIALS ABOUT ROSWELL,
ABOUT THE MILITARY AND C.I.A. ?
WHAT'S BEEN THE EFFECT ?
EVEN WILDER AND MORE
WIDESPREAD BELIEF.
THE AMERICAN APPETITE
FOR BOGUS REVELATION,
AGENT MULDER.
BUT I'VE SEEN ALIENS.
I'VE WITNESSED THESE THINGS.
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
YOU'VE SEEN WHAT THEY WANTED
YOU TO SEE.
THE LINE BETWEEN SCIENCE
AND SCIENCE FICTION DOESN'T
EXIST ANYMORE.
WHAT THIS IS ABOUT IS CONTROL
OF THE VERY ELEMENTS
OF LIFE-- DNA.
YOURS, MINE, EVERYONE'S.
THEN WHY A HOAX ?
WHY CREATE HARD EVIDENCE,
AN ALIEN BODY THAT COULD
BE DISPROVED ?
THE BODY YOU FOUND
WAS SO GOOD,
SO BELIEVABLE,
THAT ONLY A DIRECTED
SCIENTIFIC EXAMINATION...
WOULD HAVE PROVEN
THE FRAUD.
SCULLY WOULD HAVE KNOWN.
THE TIMING
OF THE HOAX WAS PLANNED
SO THAT AGENT SCULLY...
WOULDN'T BE ALIVE
TO DO AN EXAMINATION.
YOU WENT ALONG WITH ALL THIS.
YOU LET THEM DO THIS TO SCULLY.
I PAID THE PRICE,
AGENT MULDER.
WHEN MY SON CAME BACK SICK
FROM THE GULF WAR,
THAT WAS MY RETRIBUTION.
I'M HELPING YOU NOW,
BUT NOT UNSELFISHLY.
YOU BELIEVE THERE'S A CURE
FOR HIM IN HERE TOO.
I HAVE TO THINK THERE IS.
MICHAEL KRITSCHGAU.
MAY WE TALK TO YOU ?
WHAT ABOUT ?
D.O.D. IS DETAINING YOU
FOR QUESTIONING.
WOULD YOU COME WITH US,
MR. KRITSCHGAU ?
SIR.
I WAS TOLD THAT YOU
NEEDED TO SEE ME,
THAT THERE WAS
SOME URGENCY.
IT SEEMS I'VE BEEN
LEFT OUT OF THE LOOP.
LEFT OUT ?
YOU WERE WATCHING MULDER.
YOU HAD A MAN ON HIM.
NO ONE BOTHERED
TO INFORM ME OF THIS.
I KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT A MAN.
I WILL NOT BE CUT OUT
LIKE THIS.
YOU NEED MY EXPERTISE.
IS THIS BEING RUN
FROM D.O.D. ?
IF IT IS,
I'M UNAWARE OF IT.
I'VE ALWAYS KEPT MULDER
IN CHECK.
I PUT THIS
WHOLE THING TOGETHER.
I CREATED MULDER.
AGENT MULDER IS DEAD.
OUR F.B.I. SOURCE
CONFIRMED IT THIS MORNING.
MULDER KILLED HIMSELF.
MULDER WAS AN ASSET.
WITHOUT HIS PARTNER,
WE MAY HAVE UNDERESTIMATED
HIS FRAGILITY.
I NEVER UNDERESTIMATED
MULDER.
I STILL DON'T.
AS YOU HAD ASKED, I'VE TESTED
SOME OF THE CELLULAR MATERIAL...
FOUND IN THE ICE CORE SAMPLE.
BECAUSE WE COULDN'T IDENTIFY IT
AS EITHER PLANT OR ANIMAL,
ONLY AS SOME KIND
OF CHIMERIC HYBRID,
I PUT SOME OF THE INDIVIDUAL
CELLS IN MEDIA...
CONTAINING FETAL BOVINE SERUM,
AND THE CELLS BEGAN TO DIVIDE.
WELL, THEN THEY WERE
ANIMAL CELLS THAT YOU FOUND.
THEY ARE NOT CLASSIFIABLE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
YOU SAID THERE WAS
MITOTIC CELL DIVISION.
WHEN THE CELLS BEGAN TO DIVIDE,
THEY DIDN'T JUST MULTIPLY.
THEY BEGAN TO GO THROUGH
THE STAGES OF MORULA,
BLASTULA, GASTRULA.
THEY BEGAN
SOMATIC DEVELOPMENT ?
THE BEGINNING OF A LIFE-FORM.
GROWING INTO WHAT,
I DON'T KNOW.
[ Mulder Narrating ]
I HAD COME HERE LOOKING
FOR ANSWERS,
HOPING NOT ONLY TO LAY BARE
THIS CONSPIRACY AGAINST THE
COUNTRY AND THE MEN BEHIND IT,
BUT TO FINALLY LEARN THE TRUTH
ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY...
OF INTELLIGENT
EXTRATERRESTRIAL LIFE.
NOW WITH WHAT I'VE HEARD,
MY BELIEFS SEEM
MORE AND MORE IMPROBABLE.
THE POSSIBILITY OF A CURE
FOR SCULLY SOMEWHERE
INSIDE THESE WALLS...
IS MY ONLY HOPE.
BUT IF I MIGHT FIND IT
AND SOMEHOW SAVE HER,
THE VERY EXISTENCE OF THIS CURE
WOULD MEAN WITH CERTAINTY...
THAT I HAVE BELIEVED IN A LIE
FROM THE START.
[ Scully Narrating ]
I HAD NO WAY TO REACH
AGENT MULDER...
TO TELL HIM
WHAT I HAD DISCOVERED--
AN UNIDENTIFIED
MICROSCOPIC LIFE-FORM
WHOSE VERY EXISTENCE...
HELD THE POSSIBILITY
OF REVELATION.
WAS THIS ORGANISM--
EXTRACTED FROM THE ICE...
WHICH HAD ENTOMBED
THE ALIEN CORPSE--
THE GERM CELL
THAT MIGHT GIVE PROOF
OF EXTRATERRESTRIAL LIFE ?
OR WAS IT JUST THE OPPOSITE ?
THE SCIENTIFICALLY ENGINEERED
CREATION OF A CHIMERA--
AN UNCLASSIFIABLE
BIOLOGICAL PRODUCT
DESIGNED TO SET UP A HOAX,
MANUFACTURED TO CREATE
THE FALSE BELIEFS...
THAT HAVE LONG DRIVEN
AGENT MULDER.
I NOW BEGAN TO REALIZE THAT
THE ANSWER TO THIS QUESTION...
MIGHT EXIST
WITHIN THE LIFE-FORM ITSELF--
BIOLOGICAL PROOF
OF ITS CONNECTION
TO THE CANCER INVADING MY BODY,
TO A VIRUS LIVING INSIDE
THIS ORGANISM...
TO WHICH I HAD BEEN EXPOSED
DURING MY ABDUCTION
THREE YEARS AGO.
I'M STILL NOT SURE WHAT
YOU'RE HOPING TO FIND HERE.
I NEED TO DO
A SOUTHERN BLOT...
TO RUN THE CULTURE
THAT YOU SHOWED ME
AGAINST MY OWN DNA.
YOU SAID THAT THE UNCLASSIFIED
CELLS YOU LOOKED AT UNDER THE
E.E.M. WERE FULL OF VIRUS.
RIGHT.  WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING FOR ?
A MATCH.  AND I NEED IT
BEFORE 7:00.
TONIGHT ?
NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
NOT UNLESS WE HAVE
A BLAZING HOT PROBE.
IT'S GOT TO HAPPEN.
EVERYTHING IN MY LIFE
DEPENDS ON IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
I WAS GONNA ASK YOU
THE SAME.
NO YOU WEREN'T.
YOU FOLLOWED ME HERE.
WHY ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME ?
IS THIS MORE DIRTY WORK
YOU'RE DOING FOR THE D.O.D. ?
WHY DON'T YOU
TELL ME SOMETHING ?
TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE DOING HERE.
I WANT AN ANSWER FROM YOU.
I WANT AN ANSWER FROM YOU !
THIS ISN'T YOUR JOB !
MY JOB IS TO DIRECT
THE AGENTS UNDER ME.
TO QUESTION THEIR MOTIVES
WHEN THEY'RE LYING
ABOUT INVESTIGATIONS.
TO TAKE STEPS TO CEASE
OR CENSURE THOSE ACTIONS.
YOUR LIE IS ON RECORD,
AGENT SCULLY.
AND WHAT ABOUT YOURS ?
ON MY DESK
I HAVE THE PATHOLOGY...
AND FORENSICS REPORTS
FOR THE BODY FOUND
IN MULDER'S APARTMENT.
NOW, YOU HAVE TO ANSWER
FOR YOURSELF IN FIVE HOURS.
AS YOU COMPOUND THE LIES,
YOU COMPOUND THE CONSEQUENCES
FOR THEM.
ALL LIES LEAD TO THE TRUTH.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT ?
AND WHAT ABOUT YOUR LIE,
AGENT SCULLY ?  WHAT DOES IT
LEAD TO ?
THE TRUTH ABOUT THE MEN
BEHIND WHAT HAPPENED TO ME;
ABOUT MY ABDUCTION
AND THE TESTS;
ABOUT BEING EXPOSED
TO SOMETHING AGAINST MY WILL;
ABOUT BEING PUT ON A TABLE
AND HAVING SOMETHING IMPLANTED
IN ME...
AND HAVING MY MEMORY STOLEN,
ONLY TO HAVE IT RETURNED...
ALONG WITH A DISEASE
THAT I WAS GIVEN.
IS THAT YOUR JUSTIFICATION ?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE GONNA
TELL THE JOINT PANEL ?
ARE YOU AFRAID OF THAT ?
WELL, CONSIDERING
THE DEAD MAN...
IN MULDER'S APARTMENT WAS
MURDERED IN COLD BLOOD...
AND YOU WILLFULLY MISIDENTIFIED
HIM, YES, I AM AFRAID.
BUT I'M ONLY AFRAID FOR YOU.
YOU'RE GONNA USE THAT
AGAINST ME, AREN'T YOU ?
YOU'RE GONNA USE ME
AS I'VE BEEN USED ALL ALONG,
TO PRESERVE THE LIES.
WHERE IS AGENT MULDER ?
YOUR SILENCE WON'T SAVE YOU.
NOT WITH THESE PEOPLE.
AND IF YOU LIE, I DON'T KNOW
IF ANYTHING CAN.
EXCEPT PROOF.
[ Scully Narrating ]
THE CRUELEST IRONIES
ARE THOSE CONSECRATED...
BY THE PASSAGE OF TIME,
CHANCED AND OCCASIONED
BY SHOCKING DISCOVERY.
I HAD JOINED AGENT MULDER ON THE
X-FILES BECAUSE OF MY BACKGROUND
IN THE MEDICAL SCIENCES.
MY ASSIGNMENT WAS
TO QUESTION HIS WORK,
TO DEBUNK
HIS INVESTIGATIONS...
AND REIN HIM BACK
INTO THE F.B.I. MAINSTREAM.
NOW, AS FATE WOULD HAVE IT,
I AM CALLING ON THESE
VERY SAME SKILLS...
TO PROVE THAT HE HAS BEEN
THE TARGET OF A SCHEME...
ORCHESTRATED BY SOMEONE
CLOSE TO US IN THE F.B.I.;
SOMEONE WE HAVE TRUSTED
ABOVE ALL OTHERS,
INVOLVED IN
A HIGHLY ORGANIZED PLOT...
TO KEEP A DANGEROUS SECRET
FROM THE LIGHT OF DAY.
I COULD ONLY GUESS AT WHAT
AGENT MULDER MAY HAVE UNCOVERED
ON HIS OWN;
WHAT HE MAY HAVE FOUND
TO CONFIRM OR DENY;
WHAT HE HAS LONG HELD
TO BE A CONSPIRACY TO CONTROL...
THE PUBLIC INQUIRY INTO
THE GOVERNMENT'S KNOWLEDGE...
AND CONTACT
WITH AN ALIEN RACE OR RACES.
IF HE HAD HOPED, AS I DO,
TO LEARN THE IDENTITY OF THOSE
WHO SOUGHT TO DESTROY US,
I HAD, WITH THE DISCOVERY OF
THIS UNIDENTIFIED MICROORGANISM,
WHAT COULD AMOUNT
TO FORENSIC EVIDENCE.
HARD AND UNDENIABLE
GENETIC EVIDENCE...
OF A CONNECTION
BETWEEN THE CONSPIRATORS...
AND THE CANCER WHICH HAS NOW
METASTASIZED IN MY BLOODSTREAM.
[ Scully Narrating ]
I HAVE FEW SHORT HOURS
TO CONDUCT THESE TESTS...
BEFORE I MUST APPEAR
BEFORE AN F.B.I. PANEL
TO EXPLAIN MYSELF.
AND AS I AM READY TO LIE
TO THEM ABOUT AGENT MULDER,
I AM ALSO READY
TO CONFRONT THEM WITH PROOF--
PROOF EXTRACTED FROM
THIS TINY ORGANISM...
THAT COULD BLOW OPEN
A CONSPIRACY
OF GLOBAL CONSEQUENCE.
[ Mulder Narrating ]
IF AGENT SCULLY AND I HAD BEEN
LED TO BELIEVE THE CONSPIRACY...
MEANT TO DESTROY US
HAS ITS ROOTS
IN THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE,
THAT FACT SEEMS
ALL BUT IRREFUTABLE NOW.
I HAVE GAINED ENTRY TO A LARGE
STORAGE FACILITY BY A HALLWAY...
CONNECTING UNDERGROUND
TO THE PENTAGON.
ON HUNDREDS OF ROWS OF SHELVES
ARE MATERIALS THAT REVEAL
NOTHING TO ME...
OF A CURE FOR SCULLY'S CANCER.
AND NOW, AS I HAVE REACHED
THE TERMINUS OF THIS SPACE,
WHAT APPEARS TO BE AN OLD
AND ANTIQUATED FILING SYSTEM
SEEMS MY ONLY HOPE...
OF FINDING
WHAT THIS MAN KRITSCHGAU
HAS ASSURED ME EXISTS.
IF HIS OWN DESPERATE SEARCH FOR
HIS SON'S CURE HAS ELUDED HIM,
I NOW SHARE HIS DESPERATION...
THAT AMONG THESE DRAWERS
IS A SIGN, A GLIMMER,
SOME SMALL CONFIRMATION
THAT THE JOURNEY
WHICH HAS BROUGHT ME HERE...
HAS NOT BEEN IN VAIN.
[ Ringing ]
- YES ?
- I HAD ORDERS TO CONTACT YOU...
IN THE EVENT SCOTT OSTELHOFF
ENTERED THE BUILDING.
IS HE THERE ?
HIS KEY CARD
WAS SCANNED THROUGH
THE LEVEL FOUR ENTRANCE.
HE USED THE SUBTERRANEAN ACCESS
TO BREACH THE PENTAGON.
ARE YOU SURE IT'S HIM ?
I CAN'T ASCERTAIN THAT.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO APPREHEND HIM ?
DON'T DO ANYTHING.
I'M ON MY WAY.
[ Scully Narrating ]
IF MY WORK WITH AGENT MULDER
HAS TESTED...
THE FOUNDATION OF MY BELIEFS,
SCIENCE HAS BEEN
AND CONTINUES TO BE
MY GUIDING LIGHT.
NOW I AM AGAIN
RELYING ON ITS FAMILIAR
AND SYSTEMATIC METHODS...
TO ARRIVE AT A TRUTH--
A FACT THAT MIGHT EXPLAIN
THE FATE THAT HAS BEFALLEN ME.
AN INVESTIGATION THAT BEGAN
WITHOUT, NOW TURNING WITHIN.
TAKING CELLULAR MATERIAL
FROM THE UNIDENTIFIED
LIFE-FORM...
AND ISOLATING A VIRUS
CONTAINED WITHIN IT,
THEN MATCHING THE DNA
FROM THIS VIRUS...
AGAINST THAT WHICH I BELIEVE
HAS CAUSED MY CANCER.
I HOPE A PICTURE
WILL DEVELOP.
A PICTURE THAT MIGHT CONFIRM
MY DARKEST SUSPICIONS...
ABOUT THE SOURCE OF THIS DISEASE
INVADING MY BODY,
IN HOPE OF PROVIDING EVIDENCE
THAT ITS CAUSE IS
NOT WITHOUT BLAME...
EVEN THOUGH ITS CURE
REMAINS UNKNOWN.
IF SCIENCE SERVES ME
TO THESE ENDS,
IT IS NOT LOST ON ME...
THAT THE TOOL WITH WHICH I'VE
COME TO DEPEND ON ABSOLUTELY...
CANNOT SAVE OR PROTECT ME,
BUT ONLY BRING INTO FOCUS
THE DARKNESS THAT LIES AHEAD.
THERE IT IS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
MY DNA HYBRIDIZED
WITH THE VIRAL DNA
FROM THE CELL CULTURE.
BUT THAT MEANS...
THE MATERIAL
FROM THE ICE CORE SAMPLE--
YOU'D HAVE TO HAVE DNA
FROM THE UNCLASSIFIED
CHIMERA CELLS...
IN YOUR OWN BODY.
I KNOW.
BUT HOW ?
AND HOW DID YOU KNOW ?
I BELIEVE THAT I WAS EXPOSED
TO THIS MATERIAL,
AND IT IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR GIVING ME A SERIOUS ILLNESS.
WHAT KIND OF ILLNESS ?
ONE WHICH CANNOT BE CURED.
[ Mulder Narrating ]
IF I DID INDEED HAVE THE CURE
FOR SCULLY'S CANCER,
I WAS NOW AS DEPENDENT ON HER
AS SHE WAS ON ME.
AS I HAD BREACHED THIS FACILITY,
I NEEDED TO FIND MY WAY OUT
TO SAFETY;
DEPENDING ON SCULLY
TO WEAVE HER STORY;
TO TELL HER TALE;
TO MAKE THEM BELIEVE THE LIE.
AGENT SCULLY,
PLEASE HAVE A SEAT.
THANK YOU.
AGENT SCULLY, WE'VE HAD
A BRIEF DISCUSSION,
BUT WILL YOU RESTATE
THE MATTER WE'RE HERE
TO PUT TO REST.
YES, SIR.
FOUR YEARS AGO,
SECTION CHIEF BLEVINS...
ASSIGNED ME TO A PROJECT
YOU ALL KNOW AS THE X-FILES.
AS I AM A MEDICAL DOCTOR WITH
A BACKGROUND IN HARD SCIENCE,
MY JOB WAS TO PROVIDE
AN ANALYTICAL PERSPECTIVE...
ON THE WORK
OF SPECIAL AGENT FOX MULDER,
WHOSE INVESTIGATIONS
INTO THE PARANORMAL...
WERE FUELED
BY A PERSONAL BELIEF...
THAT HIS SISTER HAD BEEN
ABDUCTED BY ALIENS
WHEN HE WAS 12.
I COME HERE TODAY,
FOUR YEARS LATER,
TO REPORT ON THE ILLEGITIMACY
OF AGENT MULDER'S WORK.
THAT IT IS
MY SCIENTIFIC OPINION...
THAT HE BECAME, THROUGH
THE COURSE OF THESE YEARS,
A VICTIM--
A VICTIM
OF HIS OWN FALSE HOPES...
AND OF HIS BELIEF
IN THE BIGGEST OF LIES.
YOU WERE CONTACTED BY A MAN
WHO CLAIMED HE WORKED FOR
THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE,
A MICHAEL KRITSCHGAU,
WHO TOLD YOU THAT MULDER
HAD BEEN TAKEN IN BY A HOAX.
- YES, SIR.
-[ Door Opening ]
HE TOLD ME A STORY WHICH
DETAILED POINT-BY-POINT...
THE SYSTEMATIC WAY
IN WHICH AGENT MULDER...
HAD BEEN DECEIVED AND USED,
AND HOW I AS HIS PARTNER
HAD BEEN LED DOWN
THE SAME PATH--
LOSING A FAMILY MEMBER
DUE TO MY ALLEGIANCE...
AND CONTRACTING A FATAL DISEASE
WHICH I WAS BEING TOLD
WAS ENGINEERED...
BY THE MEN WHO WERE RESPONSIBLE
FOR AGENT MULDER'S DECEPTION.
[ Blevins ]
WERE YOU ABLE TO CONVINCE
AGENT MULDER OF THESE FACTS ?
[ Scully ]
WHAT I COULDN'T TELL
AGENT MULDER--
WHAT I HAD ONLY
JUST LEARNED MYSELF--
WAS THAT THE CANCER WHICH
HAD BEEN DIAGNOSED IN ME...
SEVERAL MONTHS EARLIER
HAD METASTASIZED,
AND THE DOCTORS TOLD ME
SHORT OF A MIRACLE...
IT WOULD CONTINUE
TO AGGRESSIVELY
INVADE MY BODY...
ADVANCING FASTER EACH DAY
TOWARDS THE INEVITABLE.
I'LL HAVE SECURITY STOP HIM
AT THE ENTRANCE.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
LET HIM GO.
EARLY THIS MORNING...
I GOT A CALL
FROM THE POLICE...
ASKING ME TO COME
TO AGENT MULDER'S APARTMENT.
THE DETECTIVE ASKED ME--
HE NEEDED ME
TO IDENTIFY A BODY.
AGENT SCULLY--
AGENT MULDER DIED
LATE LAST NIGHT...
FROM AN APPARENT SELF-INFLICTED
GUNSHOT WOUND TO THE HEAD.
[ Door Opens ]
AGENT SCULLY,
THESE ACCUSATIONS
THAT YOU'VE MADE--
- YOU'VE BEEN GIVEN A DISEASE.
- YES, SIR.
THEY'RE EXTREMELY
SERIOUS CHARGES.
YES, SIR.
BUT I HAVE PROOF...
AGAINST THE MEN
BEHIND THIS...
OF THE LIES
THAT I BELIEVED.
WHAT I HAVE HERE IS PROOF
UNDENIABLE...
THAT THE MEN WHO GAVE ME
THIS DISEASE WERE ALSO
BEHIND THE HOAX,
A PLOT DESIGNED TO LEAD
TO AGENT MULDER'S DEMISE,
AND TO MY OWN,
PLANNED AND EXECUTED
BY SOMEONE IN THIS ROOM.
WHAT I HAVE HERE...
IS SCIENTIFIC EVIDENCE--
YOU.
SOMEBODY GET A DOCTOR.
[ Electronic Beep ]
WHAT ?
WHAT IS IT ?
IT'S DEIONIZED WATER.
IT'S NOTHING MORE THAN THAT.
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !