[ Gunfire, Explosions ]
dddd [ Rock ]
dddd [ Man Singing,
Indistinct ]
dddd
[ Owl Hooting ]
BOBBY ?
PHIL.
I'VE HAD IT
WITH THAT KID, PATTI.
I'VE ALREADY
TALKED TO HIM.
YEAH, LIKE
HE EVER LISTENS.
[ Video Game:
Explosions, Gunfire ]
[ Loudly ]
DID YOU HEAR ME
CALLING YOUR NAME ?
GET UP !
[ Pants ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN' ?
YOU THINK THIS IS WHY
I GO TO WORK EVERY DAY
SO YOU CAN SIT ON YOUR ASS ?
WHAT DID I DO ?
WHAT'D YOU DO ?
YOU NEVER DO ANYTHING.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
WHAT KIND OF A LOSER
ARE YOU GONNA
TURN OUT TO BE ?
PUT YOUR BOOTS ON.
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
YOU DON'T LEAVE MY TOOLS
OUT IN THE RAIN.
TOOLS ARE FOR WORK.
THEY COST MONEY.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL PUT IT AWAY.
AFTER YOU'VE FINISHED.
PICK IT UP.
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOUR MOTHER
WATCH YOU GROW UP TO BE
SOME KIND OF A JERK.
FINE.  I'LL PUT IT
AWAY... PHIL.
NO WAY.
YOU'LL FINISH THE JOB.
NOW.
[ Exhales ]
GET AWAY FROM ME !
- GET AWAY FROM ME NOW !
- BOBBY !
[ Grunts ]
BOBBY !
WHERE ARE YOU GOING ?
COME BACK HERE, BOBBY !
I'M CALLING YOU !
CAN'T YOU HEAR ME ?
BOBBY !  BOBBY !
[ Indistinct Shouting ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Shouting Continues ]
BOBBY !
BOBBY ?
[ Grunting ]
[ Thunderclap ]
BOBBY !
[ Grunting ]
NO.
TWELVE POUNDS,
NINE OUNCES.
ALL THAT CAME OUT
OF HIS STOMACH ?
MOST OF IT.  THE SMALL AMOUNT
IN HIS LUNGS IS WHAT KILLED HIM.
IS IT POSSIBLE THAT HE TOOK
THE TERM "MUD PIE" LITERALLY ?
I'M SURE IF MR. RICH
WERE ALIVE, HE WOULD FIND
SOME HUMOR IN THAT.
ACCORDING TO HIS POLICE REPORT,
MR. RICH WAS A MAN WHO COULD
TELL A JOKE.
HE GREW UP HERE, WORKED
THE SAME FIELDS FOR 20 YEARS.
WELL LIKED AROUND TOWN.
FUNNY HE SHOULD
TURN UP MURDERED.
IS THAT WHAT YOU CONCLUDED ?
I HAVE CONCLUDED
THAT THIS MAN'S HEAD
WAS HELD FORCIBLY...
DOWN IN THE MICHIGAN MUD
JUST A LITTLE TOO LONG,
MOST LIKELY BY HIS STEPSON
WHO WAS NAMED IN THE REPORT
AS BOBBY RICH, AGE 16.
ACCORDING TO THE SAME REPORT,
THE CORONER HAD TO HIRE
A BACKHOE...
TO REMOVE THE BODY,
WHICH WAS BURIED COMPLETELY
IN A STANDING VERTICAL POSITION.
THERE IS SOME INDICATION
THAT HIS STEPSON MAY HAVE DUG
THE HOLE...
AND THAT A RECENT RAINSTORM
MAY HAVE HELPED TURN IT
INTO A MUDDY TRAP.
- SOME RAINSTORM.
- THEY SAY IT RAINED
400 INCHES A DAY.
NOW, THAT SOUNDS LIKE AN
EXAGGERATION, DON'T YOU THINK ?
WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO SHOW
HOW HE MAY HAVE DONE IT ?
HOW A 6'4", 250-POUND MAN
WAS BURIED ALIVE...
IN LESS THAN FIVE MINUTES
BY A 16-YEAR-OLD KID...
WHOSE CLASSMATES LOVINGLY
REFER TO AS "DORK WEED" ?
HE MAY HAVE HAD
AN ACCOMPLICE.
"ICH BIN EIN AUSLANDER."
"I AM AN OUTSIDER."
WHEN KENNEDY TOLD THE GERMANS
"ICH BIN EIN BERLINER,"
HE WAS ACTUALLY SAYING
"I'M A COCKTAIL SAUSAGE."
WHO'S KENNEDY ?
I'M NOT HERE TO ACCUSE YOU
OF ANYTHING, BOBBY.
WHAT ARE YOU
HERE FOR, THEN ?
I WANT TO HEAR YOUR STORY.
I TRIED TO HELP.
I COULDN'T.
WELL, THE POLICE
AREN'T ENTIRELY CONVINCED
THAT THAT'S THE TRUTH.
SO, WHAT THE HELL AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO ABOUT IT ?
THEY WANT ME TO CONFESS
SO THEY HAVE SOMEONE TO BLAME.
RIGHT.
BUT, YOU SEE,
YOU'RE NOT MAKING IT VERY EASY
FOR THEM TO BELIEVE OTHERWISE.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT ?
[ Clears Throat ]
WHAT CAN I SAY ?
EVERYBODY KNOWS I HATED HIM.
THEY WERE REAL CLOSE
WHEN BOBBY WAS LITTLE.
ALWAYS KIDDING AROUND
AND STUFF.
BUT BOBBY SORT OF GOT INTO
THAT TEENAGE STAGE,
AND HE DON'T WANT
TO LISTEN TO NOBODY.
AND THAT CAME TO A HEAD
LAST NIGHT ?
PHIL WAS LATE COMIN' HOME.
HE'D BEEN STRESSED OUT
'CAUSE OF THE BLIGHT AND STUFF.
HOW DO YOU MEAN ?
THE HAZELNUT TREES
ALL GOT A DISEASE.
AND... BOBBY DON'T HELP THINGS
OUT WITH HIS ATTITUDE AND STUFF.
DID PHIL INSTIGATE
WHAT HAPPENED ?
IT'S HARD TO TELL
WHAT STARTS THESE THINGS.
PHIL COULD BE STERN,
JUST LIKE HIS OWN FATHER
WAS TO HIM...
BUT I NEVER SAW HIM
RAISE HIS HAND.
AND WHEN I SAW HIM
LYING IN THE MUD,
I HALF-EXPECTED HIM
TO PULL ME IN, LIKE HE
HAD PLANNED IT OR SOMETHING.
DID HE EVER HURT YOU ?
PHIL, HE USED TO GET OFF
SHOVING ME AROUND, YEAH.
DID YOU EVER SHOVE HIM BACK ?
[ Laughs ]
HE'S TWICE AS BIG AS ME.
THAT'S WHY SOME PEOPLE THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT HAVE DUG THE HOLE,
OR ATTACKED HIM
WHEN HE FELL IN THE HOLE,
'CAUSE HE WAS DOWN THERE.
THAT'S THEIR PROBLEM,
ISN'T IT ?
DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT WAS GOING
THROUGH YOUR HEAD AT THE TIME ?
I GUESS... I FELT
HE HAD IT COMIN'.
HE WAS KNEELING OVER PHIL,
STRUGGLING REAL HARD AND STUFF.
COULD YOU TELL
THAT HE WAS DEFINITELY
TRYING TO HELP HIM ?
IT SEEMED THAT WAY TO ME.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S
A STRONG CHANCE...
THE POLICE ARE GONNA
ARREST YOUR SON FOR MURDER.
I DON'T SEE HOW.
BUT IF THEY DO,
AND IF THERE'S EVIDENCE
OF ABUSE THAT YOU'RE
NOT COMING FORWARD WITH,
IT COULD HURT HIS CHANCES.
I KNOW EVERYTHING HAPPENS
FOR A REASON,
BUT I STILL DON'T SEE
NO REASON FOR THIS.
THEY'RE ALL DYING.
ACCORDING TO BOBBY'S MOTHER,
THAT'S THE BIG REASON
WHY HER HUSBAND BLEW UP.
HIS HAZELNUT ORCHARD
WAS HIT WITH A BLIGHT.
SO HE POUNDS THE KID ?
AND THE KID POUNDS BACK.
IS THAT WHAT SHE TOLD YOU ?
WELL, NOT IN SO MANY WORDS.
ACTUALLY, SHE WON'T ADMIT
TO ANY ABUSE IN THE HOUSE.
I SUSPECT SHE'S JUST
TRYING TO MOVE ON AND PROTECT
WHAT FAMILY SHE'S GOT LEFT.
THE KID SAYS HIS STEPFATHER
TEED OFF ON HIM REGULARLY.
IS THAT HIS EXCUSE ?
NO, THAT'S
HIS EXPLANATION.
HE SAYS HE'S INNOCENT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
I THINK HE'S
A HARD KID TO LOVE.
I'M STILL FINDING IT HARD
TO RECONCILE THE FACTS
WITH THE PHYSICAL EVIDENCE.
EVEN IF HE DIDN'T DIG THIS HOLE,
THE DISEASE COULD HAVE KILLED
ROOT SYSTEMS,
CREATING WEAKENED SOIL.
THEN HOW DID THE VICTIM
SWALLOW 12 POUNDS
OF THIS STUFF ?
WELL, WHEN YOU FIGHT FOR AIR,
A VACUUM IS CREATED.
AND MAYBE ONCE HE SUCKED DOWN
A MOUTHFUL OF MUD,
IT TURNED HIS ESOPHAGUS
INTO A SIPHON.
AND WITH HIS HEAD PUSHED DOWN,
IT FILLED ALL OF HIS PASSAGES
LIKE A GAS CAN.
WELL, YOU ASKED ME FOR ANSWERS.
THOSE ARE THE BEST ONES
I'VE GOT.
DID YOU ASK IF ANYBODY ELSE
MIGHT BE INVOLVED ?
HIS MOTHER SAYS THAT BOBBY
CAN'T MAKE FRIENDS.
HE'S BEEN IN THERAPY
FOR HIS ANGER SINCE 1995.
THAT COULD BE ME.
- WHAT IS IT ?
- SOMEONE'S WATCHING US.
SIR ?
HELLO ?
WHO WAS IT ?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S GONE.
[ School Bell Rings ]
[ Students Chattering ]
LISA.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
I CALLED YOU LAST NIGHT.
HOW COME YOU DIDN'T
CALL ME BACK ?
THEY'RE SAYING
YOU KILLED HIM, BOBBY.
I FINALLY STOOD UP TO HIM.
PSYCHO !  THINK FAST.
JUST GET AWAY
FROM ME, OKAY ?
OR WHAT ?
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO, HUH ?
MAYBE I'LL KILL
YOU TOO, HUH ?
[ Boy Chuckling ]
PSYCHO KILLER !
SEE ?  ALL YOU GOTTA
DO IS STAND UP.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER, THEN.
[ Knock At Door ]
[ Mulder ]
KARIN MATTHEWS ?
[ Door Opens ]
[ Woman ]
YES ?
[ Scully ]
WE'RE AGENTS MULDER
AND SCULLY FROM THE F.B.I.
I HOPE MY DIRECTIONS WERE CLEAR.
I'M A LITTLE TUCKED AWAY.
I FIRST WORKED WITH BOBBY
AFTER AN INCIDENT AT SCHOOL.
HE'S HAD DIFFICULTY
DEVELOPING RELATIONSHIPS,
AND THIS DIFFICULTY
HAS CAUSED HIM TO ACT OUT.
IN WHAT WAY ?
BY PUTTING ON CERTAIN AIRS,
AFFECTING AN ATTITUDE...
THAT HAS DRAWN
THE WRONG KIND OF
ATTENTION TO HIMSELF.
I'VE SEEN HIM COME IN HERE
PRETTY BEATEN UP.
PHYSICAL VIOLENCE ?
MORE THAN JUST KID STUFF.
WAS HIS STEPFATHER
EVER INVOLVED ?
I'M NOT FREE TO SPEAK WITH
PERFECT FRANKNESS, OF COURSE.
IF YOU KNOW THAT BOBBY
COMMITTED A CRIME, YOU'RE UNDER
LEGAL OBLIGATION TO TELL US.
BOBBY ONCE SPILLED
A GLASS OF MILK AT DINNER.
FOR THE NEXT TWO WEEKS,
HE WAS FORCED TO EAT
IN THE CELLAR.
NO TABLE, NO CHAIR,
NO LIGHT.
SOMETIMES HE WAS LEFT
DOWN THERE UNTIL
THE FOLLOWING MORNING.
YOU SEE, THERE ARE
ALL SORTS OF CRIMES,
NOT JUST THE ONES YOU MIGHT
FIND REASON TO INVESTIGATE.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
BOBBY WOULD HAVE GOOD REASON
TO KILL HIS FATHER ?
I'M SAYING THERE ARE SOME CRIMES
WHERE THERE ARE ONLY VICTIMS.
YOU'RE FREE NOT TO ANSWER,
MISS MATTHEWS,
OR YOU'RE FREE TO MAKE
THESE VAGUE ALLUSIONS,
BUT YOUR EVASIVENESS IS ONLY
GONNA LAND THIS KID IN JAIL
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
I'M NOT SURE I UNDERSTAND.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND
LIKE A JUSTIFICATION,
LIKE BOBBY DID IT,
AND I DON'T THINK HE DID.
dddd [ Car Stereo: Rock ]
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOIN' ?
GOING HOME.
WELL, I, UH--
I WAITED FOR YOU.
I THOUGHT, UH,
WE WERE GONNA TALK, SO--
YOU SCARED ME
TODAY, BOBBY.
WHY ?
WAS IT BECAUSE I STOOD UP
FOR MYSELF, OR, UM...
BECAUSE I DIDN'T LET THEM
BEAT ME UP LIKE USUAL ?
I GOTTA GO.
YOU GOTTA STAND UP, LISA.
YOU GOTTA TELL YOUR DAD
YOU'RE NOT GONNA PUT UP
WITH THIS CRAP.
THERE'S A WAY...
TO MAKE IT GO AWAY...
FOREVER.
[ Dog Barking
In The Distance ]
[ Door Opens ]
WHAT THE HELL BUSINESS
YOU GOT WITH HIM ?
NOTHING.
HE'S JUST A FRIEND.
[ Door Opens ]
I DON'T WANT YOU
SEEING THAT KID.
I DON'T WANT HIM
COMING ROUND HERE.
DO YOU HEAR ME ?
STOP IT, OKAY ?
I'M DOING WHAT'S
RIGHT FOR YOU.
JUST SHUT UP !
[ Muffled Yelling ]
[ Panting ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Bird Cawing ]
THE VICTIM'S NAME WAS...
EUGENE BAIOCCHI, 40s.
HE WAS A FOREMAN
FOR ONE OF THE LOCAL GROWERS,
A SINGLE PARENT.
DID YOU GET A LOOK
AT THE BODY ?
IT HAD ALREADY BEEN REMOVED.
I THINK IT'S PRETTY CLEAR
WHAT KILLED HIM, THOUGH.
FROM WHAT THEY PUT TOGETHER,
THEY'VE ALL BUT CONCLUDED
HE WAS PUSHED OUT THE WINDOW.
- PUSHED OUT ?
- HIS DAUGHTER LISA MADE
THE 9-1-1 CALL AT 8:08 P.M.
SHE SAYS SHE AND HER FATHER
HAD A FIGHT.
- ABOUT WHAT ?
- BOBBY.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO WORRY
ABOUT ANYTHING, ALL RIGHT ?
I'LL BE HERE FOR YOU
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
BUT THEY'RE GOING TO COME
AND ASK YOU SOME QUESTIONS,
AND THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
IS THAT YOU FEEL COMFORTABLE.
IF YOU DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
ANSWERING THEM, THEN I DON'T
WANT YOU TO ANSWER THEM.
CAN I HAVE A MOMENT
WITH LISA ?
WAS LISA ANOTHER
OF YOUR CLIENTS ?
LISA ?  YES,
FOR FOUR YEARS.
WHAT WERE YOU
TREATING HER FOR ?
AN EATING DISORDER.
HAVE YOU ASKED HER
WHAT HAPPENED ?
ISN'T THAT YOUR JOB ?
WE GATHER THAT SHE HAD
A FIGHT WITH HER FATHER
OVER BOBBY RICH.
WELL, IT DOESN'T
SURPRISE ME.
LISA'S FATHER
WAS VERY DISAPPROVING
OF HER GENERALLY,
WHICH STEMMED TO A LOT
OF HER PROBLEMS.
HAD YOU COUNSELED
HER FATHER ?
NO.
MY APPROACH IS
WITH THE VICTIMS SOLELY,
TO ALLOW THEM
TO EMPOWER THEMSELVES.
IN WHAT WAYS ?
BY BREAKING
THE CYCLE OF ABUSE,
BY OWNING IT,
BY CONFRONTING IT
AND BY STANDING UP AGAINST IT.
IT SEEMS TO BE WORKING.
WHEN I TOLD LISA
HER AUNT WAS COMING
TO PICK HER UP TOMORROW,
SHE STARTED TO CRY.
IT WASN'T OUT OF SORROW.
THREE GUESSES WHO FOLLOWED LISA
HOME LAST NIGHT...
AND WAS SITTING OUT FRONT
IN HIS FATHER'S TRUCK JUST
MINUTES BEFORE THIS HAPPENED.
- DOES SHE THINK BOBBY DID IT ?
- SHE THINKS HE'S QUITE CAPABLE.
I THINK WE'RE ALL
QUITE CAPABLE.
SHE SAYS THAT HE ALSO
THREATENED TO KILL A BOY
IN SCHOOL YESTERDAY.
COME HERE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
IF LISA'S FATHER WAS PUSHED OUT
THE WINDOW, THEN ALL THE GLASS
WOULD BE ON THE OUTSIDE.
THERE'S GLASS HERE
ON THE INSIDE.
THE PAINT ON THE MULLIONS
IS CRACKED ON THE OUTSIDE,
NOT ON THE INSIDE HERE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT SEEMS TO ME
LIKE SOME FACTS
HAVE BEEN ASSUMED.
IT LOOKS TO ME LIKE LISA'S
FATHER WAS PULLED OUT
THE WINDOW, NOT PUSHED.
HOW ?
THAT I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, THERE'S
NOWHERE TO STAND.
EVEN IF HE DID USE A LADDER,
THERE'D BE NO LEVERAGE.
I MEAN, ESPECIALLY
FOR A SCRAWNY 16-YEAR-OLD KID.
THAT'S MY POINT EXACTLY.
SODIUM HYDROXIDE
AND HYDROCHLORIC ACID.
ALL RIGHT, CLASS.
THERE WILL BE A QUIZ
ON THIS TOMORROW.
- MAY I HELP YOU ?
- I'M SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
I NEED TO ASK YOU
TO COME WITH US, PLEASE.
- WHAT FOR ?
- TO ANSWER SOME QUESTIONS.
ABOUT WHAT ?
I DON'T WANT TO
HAVE TO EMBARRASS YOU
IN FRONT OF YOUR CLASS.
WELL, I AIN'T EMBARRASSED.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Students Murmuring ]
I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN THIS MAN
DIED FROM A BROKEN NECK.
BUT THERE WAS A SUBSTANTIAL
AMOUNT OF BLOOD LOSS,
WASN'T THERE ?
YES, BUT THE CUTS ALL MISSED
THE ARTERY.  I HAVE X RAYS
IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME.
IT'S THE FOURTH
AND FIFTH VERTABRAE.
HAVE YOU DETERMINED
IF THE NECK INJURY
WAS CAUSED BY THE FALL ?
WELL, WHAT ELSE
WOULD IT HAVE BEEN ?
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS ?
WHAT DO YOU MAKE
OF THIS HERE ?
OH.
ARE YOU SATISFIED ?
[ Chuckles ]
NO, I'M NOT.
MM.
SCULLY.
- WHAT IS THAT ?
- EVIDENCE.
OF WHAT ?
ARE YOU JUST
TRYING TO SCARE HIM ?
NO, I THINK HE'S
SCARED ENOUGH AS IT IS.
OF WHAT ?
I'LL HELP GET THE REST
OF YOUR THINGS PACKED.
BUT I THINK IT'S BEST
YOU GO TO YOUR AUNT'S
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
WHEN DID SHE SAY
SHE WAS COMING ?
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING.
HEY.
FEEL IT.
IT'S OKAY.
COME ON.
[ Man ]
YOU NEVER LEARN.
[ Karin ]
I'M SORRY.  PLEASE--
PLEASE JUST DON'T YELL.
WHAT WILL YOU EVER
AMOUNT TO ?
STOP IT.
STOP IT !
WHERE ARE YOU GOING ?
UP TO MY ROOM.
[ Man ]
YOU'RE RUINING MY LIFE.
YOU HEAR ME ?
[ Footsteps ]
I WISH YOU'D
NEVER BEEN BORN.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR ?
THAT SPLINTER YOU'RE HOLDING
CAME FROM MR. BAIOCCHI'S NECK,
BUT IT DIDN'T COME
FROM THE BROKEN WINDOW.
WHERE DID IT COME FROM ?
IT'S GREENWOOD.
FRESH FROM A LIVING TREE.
WHAT ?
EXCUSE ME.
IT'S BEEN A FEW YEARS.
YOU THINK THAT BOBBY CLIMBED
THIS TREE TO PULL LISA'S FATHER
OUT OF THAT WINDOW ?
IT KINDA BEGS THE QUESTION,
DOESN'T IT ?
HEY, SCULLY,
IS THIS DEMONSTRATION...
OF BOYISH AGILITY
TURNING YOU ON AT ALL ?
[ Rustling ]
WHO ARE YOU ?
I TAKE CARE OF THE TREES.
SCULLY ?
I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU
TO BE STANDING
RIGHT THERE BEHIND ME.
YOU WERE WATCHING US
THE OTHER DAY IN THE ORCHARD.
THE TREES ARE DYING.
- SCULLY !
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD
COME DOWN HERE, MULDER.
DO YOU, UH, KNOW WHAT KIND
OF TREE THIS CAME FROM ?
SAME AS THIS TREE.
YOU, UH, SAID
THESE TREES WERE DYING.
THIS SPLINTER'S LIVE WOOD.
[ Man ]
TWENTY YEARS AGO
THIS HAPPENS.
WHAT CAUSES THIS ?
A VERY BAD MAN.
[ Door Creaking ]
[ Creaking ]
[ Ground Sloshes ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Woman ]
THE LITTLE SNOOP.
SHE'S JUST LIKE YOU.
WHERE IS SHE ?
[ Door Slams ]
[ Knocking,
Doorbell Rings ]
MS. MATTHEWS, WE'D LIKE
TO ASK YOU A FEW QUESTIONS.
ABOUT WHAT ?
YOUR FATHER'S DEATH.
WE NEED TO CLARIFY
A FEW DETAILS.
MY FATHER ?
HE DIED 20 YEARS AGO.
YEAH, UNDER RATHER
CURIOUS CIRCUMSTANCES.
HIS BODY WAS PULLED
FROM THE MUD OF AN ORCHARD ?
I-I'M SORRY.
I WAS JUST A YOUNG GIRL, UH--
I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU WANT TO TALK TO ME.
WE JUST THOUGHT
IT WAS STRANGE THAT YOU
DIDN'T BOTHER TO MENTION IT.
I DON'T SEE THAT IT MATTERS.
WE SPOKE TO SOMEONE
WHO THINKS IT DOES, SOMEONE
WHO WORKED FOR YOUR FATHER.
ACCORDING TO THE ORCHARD MAN,
YOUR FATHER'S DEATH
BROUGHT ABOUT...
THE END OF A BLIGHT
AFFECTING THE TREES.
MY FATHER WAS A POWERFUL MAN,
AND POWERFUL MEN ARE PRONE
TO INSPIRE THIS KIND OF FANTASY.
DON'T TELL ME YOU'VE
BEEN TAKEN IN BY IT TOO.
IS LISA STILL
STAYING WITH YOU ?
NO, SHE'S NOT.
SHE'S GONE TO HER AUNT'S.
LOOK, I'M SORRY I CAN'T HELP.
[ Engine Starts ]
HELP ME !
I'M DOWN HERE !  HELP !
LISA.
KARIN ?
KARIN !
KARIN.
LISA, YOU'VE GOT
TO BE QUIET,
QUIET AS A MOUSE, OR HE'S
GOING TO HEAR YOU DOWN THERE.
KARIN, I'M SCARED.
LET ME OUT, PLEASE.
I WILL, BUT NOT
UNTIL IT'S SAFE.
KARIN ?  KARIN, I DON'T
WANT TO STAY DOWN HERE.
PLEASE LET ME OUT !
[ Doorknob Jiggling ]
KARIN.
[ Departing Footsteps ]
[ Door Closes ]
MULDER, WHATEVER YOU'RE
HOPING WE FIND HERE,
WITHOUT A COURT ORDER
IT WON'T BE ADMISSIBLE.
I'M NOT EXPECTING IT TO BE.
[ Creaking ]
MULDER,
WHERE'S THE BODY ?
[ Knocking ]
YES ?
I'M LINDA BAIOCCHI.
LISA'S AUNT.
ARE YOU KARIN ?
YES.
- IS LISA HERE ?
- NO.  SHE WENT--
SHE'S GONE
TO THE BUS STATION.
SHE HAS ?
BUT IT WAS ALL ARRANGED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO TELL YOU.
I'M SORRY.  THERE MUST'VE
BEEN A MISUNDERSTANDING.
[ Glass Shatters ]
[ Lisa ]
HELP ME !  I'M DOWN HERE !
[ Sobbing ]
DON'T LEAVE !
I'M DOWN HERE !
AUNT LINDA, I'M DOWN HERE !
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
DOWN THERE ?
- JUST GET ME OUT, PLEASE !
OKAY.  I-IT'LL BE OKAY.
I'M GONNA CALL THE POLICE.
[ Gasps ]
[ Crunching Sound ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
MULDER, YOU STILL HAVEN'T
ANSWERED MY QUESTION.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
KARIN'S FATHER ?  WHY WOULD
ANYBODY STEAL HIS BODY ?
I DON'T THINK
THIS WAS AN ACT
OF GRAVE ROBBING, SCULLY.
NO, THAT'S WHAT
WE WERE DOING.
MORE LIKE AN ACT OF NATURE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
THE ORCHARD MAN SAID
THAT THE BLIGHT...
THAT PLAGUES THIS TOWN
WAS CAUSED BY A MAN,
IMPLYING A CONNECTION.
I'M A LITTLE AFRAID TO ASK
WHAT KIND OF CONNECTION.
BETWEEN THE PEOPLE
OF THIS VALLEY AND THEIR
LIVELIHOOD-- THE TREES.
LOOK AT THE VICTIMS, SCULLY.
BOBBY'S FATHER, LISA'S FATHER--
AND KARIN'S FATHER
20 YEARS AGO.
ALL MEN WHO WORKED
IN THESE ORCHARDS, THEIR LIVES
AND DEATHS TIED TO THESE TREES.
WE REMOVED THIS SLIVER
OF GREENWOOD FROM
LISA'S FATHER'S NECK.
AND THE BRUISE THAT YOU FOUND
ON BOBBY'S FATHER'S ANKLE
COULD'VE BEEN CAUSED BY A ROOT,
THE SAME ROOT SYSTEM THAT PULLED
KARIN'S FATHER FROM HIS GRAVE.
MULDER, THERE IS A CONNECTION
BETWEEN THESE DEATHS,
ONE THAT PROVIDES
A CLEAR MOTIVE AND INTENT.
THESE WERE ABUSED CHILDREN.
WHO COULDN'T
DEFEND THEMSELVES.
WHAT, SO NATURE
DID IT FOR THEM ?
SOMETHING DID IT FOR THEM,
OR SOMEONE CONTROLLING NATURE.
KARIN SAID SHE WAS COUNSELING
BOBBY AND LISA TO EMPOWER THEM.
I THINK WE SHOULD
TALK TO THEM.
I CALLED LISA AT
HER AUNT'S HOUSE 20 MINUTES AGO,
AND THERE WAS NO ANSWER.
- THEN WE SHOULD TALK TO BOBBY.
- MULDER, WE'VE ALREADY
QUESTIONED HIM TWICE.
MAYBE WE HAVEN'T ASKED HIM
THE RIGHT QUESTION.
[ Engine Starting ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YES, YOU DO.
MAYBE YOU HATED YOUR STEPFATHER,
BUT YOU DIDN'T KILL HIM.
YOU DON'T HAVE IT IN YOU.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
CAN I GO NOW ?
NO.  YOU CAN'T GO
UNTIL YOU TELL ME THE TRUTH.
FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN YOUR LIFE, PEOPLE
ARE TAKING YOU SERIOUSLY,
AND I THINK THEY
SHOULD TAKE YOU SERIOUSLY.
I THINK YOU'RE
A SERIOUS KID.
YOU'RE NOT AN OUTSIDER
ANYMORE, HUH ?
YEAH.  I'M THINKING ABOUT
RUNNING FOR A.S.B. PRESIDENT.
SO WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GIVE IT UP ?
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE IT UP ?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHAT HAPPENED THAT NIGHT ?
YOU TOOK THE SHOVEL TO HIM,
BUT YOU COULDN'T DO IT,
SO YOU RAN.
YOU RAN TO THE ORCHARD,
BUT NOT BECAUSE YOU DUG
A HOLE OR LAID A TRAP.
BECAUSE YOU WERE AFRAID.
NOT OF PHIL.
YOU WEREN'T AFRAID OF PHIL.
PHIL NEVER HIT YOU
OR HURT YOU IN THAT WAY.
IN FACT, I THINK
YOU WANTED TO HELP PHIL.
[ Screaming ]
YOU WANTED TO SAVE HIM.
YOU DIDN'T WANT PHIL
TO DIE, DID YOU ?
- [ Choking ]
- [ Sniffles ]
[ Grunting ]
WHAT WERE YOU AFRAID OF ?
I COULDN'T DO IT.
YOU COULDN'T DO WHAT ?
I COULDN'T STAND UP TO HIM...
BUT SHE MADE ME--
SHE WHO ?
KA-- KARIN.
KARIN, SHE--
SHE MADE ME, UH--
YOU'RE A LOSER !
YOU UNDERSTAND ME ?
I WISH YOU WOULD HAVE
NEVER BEEN BORN !
YOU'RE RUINING MY LIFE !
KARIN MADE YOU WHAT ?
SHE MADE ME SAY
THOSE THINGS.
SHE HAD ME PRETEND
THAT I WAS HIM,
THAT I WAS PHIL.
SHE MADE YOU BELIEVE
YOU WERE A VICTIM,
BUT YOU WEREN'T, WERE YOU ?
SHE SAID I HAVE
THE POWER...
TO-- TO MAKE IT
ALL GO AWAY.
BUT I-- BUT I DIDN'T MEAN
FOR HIM TO DIE.
IT'S OKAY.
[ Footsteps ]
[ Woman ]
YOU THINK YOU CAN HIDE
DOWN THERE ?
YOU THINK YOU'RE SAFE ?
[ Altered Voice ]
YOU'LL WISH YOU WERE DEAD.
KARIN ?
SCULLY, TAKE
A LOOK AT THIS.
MULDER.
TALK ABOUT
PUTTING DOWN ROOTS.
[ Scully ]
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON HERE ?
I THINK WE'RE LOOKING
AT KARIN MATTHEWS' FATHER.
BUT HOW DID HE GET HERE ?
THE SAME WAY BOBBY'S FATHER
GOT PULLED DOWN IN THAT MUD.
- MULDER, I--
- THIS HAS TO DO WITH KARIN,
WITH HER OWN FATHER'S ABUSE.
IT WAS NEVER BOBBY THAT
WAS LOCKED IN THE CELLAR.
IT WAS KARIN.
- KARIN CAUSED ALL THIS.
- YOU THINK KARIN
IS THE KILLER ?
I THINK SHE'S THE KILLER
AND THE VICTIM.
[ Lisa Groans, Shrieks ]
[ Sobbing ]
LISA.
WHERE'S KARIN ?
[ Indistinct Muttering ]
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
YOU STAY WITH HER, SCULLY.
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Pounding On Door ]
[ Latch Clicking ]
- I NEED TO SEE BOBBY.
- I'M SORRY, BOBBY'S NOT HERE.
HE'S IN DANGER !
GET AWAY FROM HERE, PLEASE.
BOBBY !
HE'S NOT HERE !
[ Groans, Shouts ]
WHERE IS HE ?
BOBBY !  BOBBY !
BOBBY !
- BOBBY !
- [ Panting, Grunting ]
STAY AWAY FROM ME !
I'M WARNING YOU.
[ Creaking ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Altered Voice ]
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
[ Grunting ]
[ Bobby Gasping ]
YOU LITTLE PIECE
OF GARBAGE.
KARIN, STOP !
- YOU STAY AWAY FROM HIM !
- STAND UP TO HIM !
KARIN DESERVES
WHAT SHE GETS.
[ Gasping ]
MAKE HIM STOP, KARIN !
TELL HIM WHAT YOU SHOULD'VE
TOLD HIM 20 YEARS AGO.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA
TAKE IT ANYMORE !
- KARIN'S DEAD.
IT'S DONE NOW.
NO MORE.
[ Mulder ]  COATS GROVE
AUTHORITIES CONDUCTED
A DETAILED EXAMINATION...
OF THE SOIL AND ROOT COMPOSITION
IN THE RICH FAMILY ORCHARD,
BUT COULD NOT EXPLAIN
WHAT PULLED KARIN MATTHEWS' BODY
INTO THE MICHIGAN MUD;
NOR COULD THE AUTHORITIES
DETERMINE HOW THE BODY
OF KARIN'S FATHER...
WAS PULLED FROM ITS GRAVE
INTO HER ROOT CELLAR
THREE YEARS EARLIER.
WHILE THE FORENSIC DATA
IS INCONCLUSIVE, I BELIEVE
THE EXPLANATION LIES...
IN HOSPITAL RECORDS DATING BACK
TO KARIN'S CHILDHOOD,
WHICH SUGGESTS SHE HERSELF
WAS A VICTIM OF ABUSE.
RAGE, UNCONFRONTED,
TAKES ITS OWN PATH.
I BELIEVE IT WAS
KARIN'S UNCONFRONTED RAGE...
THAT FORCED HER TO FACE
HER BURIED FATHER.
THIS SAME RAGE
MADE HER IMAGINE VICTIMS
IN THE CHILDREN AROUND HER,
TRYING TO INSTILL IN THEM
A STRENGTH SHE NEVER FOUND
IN HERSELF.
WHAT HAPPENED TO KARIN MATTHEWS
IN THE ORCHARD THAT NIGHT
WAS A RELEASE,
RELEASE FOR A VICTIM WHO,
UNABLE TO FACE UP
TO HER OWN PAST,
WAS FINALLY CONSUMED BY IT.
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !