ALL RIGHT,
LET'S SHOOT THIS, MARTY.
HOLD IT STILL.
[ Bug Buzzing ]
HOLD IT STILL, SLOAN.
I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU
HOLD IT STILL.
THE SOONER THEY PAVE OVER
THIS SWAMP, THE BETTER.
IT'S NOT A SWAMP.
YOU'RE STANDING IN A FOREST
WITH INDIGENOUS PLANT
AND ANIMAL SPECIES...
YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY
TOO IGNORANT TO APPRECIATE.
MARK IT.
GIVE ME ANOTHER POSITION.
LET'S SHOOT THIS ONE CAREFULLY.
THIS IS WHERE THEY'RE
GONNA PUT THE BLOCKBUSTER.
YOU'RE A REAL MORON, SLOAN.
YOU KNOW THAT ?
TREE HUGGER.
YOU SHOULD BE SAD TO SEE
THE DEMISE OF AN ECOSYSTEM
THAT'S LASTED A THOUSAND YEARS.
WE ALL SHOULD BE.
GIVE ME FOUR FEET
TO YOUR LEFT.
I CAN'T.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU CAN'T ?
I MEAN I CAN'T
BECAUSE IT'S STUCK.
THEN UNSTICK IT.
THIS IS WEIRD.
[ Screaming ]
SLOAN ?  SLOAN ?
[ Panting ]
[ Bug Buzzing ]
[ Screaming ]
LOUIS,
LET BO DO THE WORK.
HOW'S HE GONNA FIND
A POSSUM ?
SHH.
ANIMALS SENSE THINGS
THAT WE CAN'T.
THAT'S HOW THEY SURVIVE.
IS THAT HOW BO
KNOWS HOW TO HUNT ?
YEP.  OUR ANCESTORS WERE
HUNTERS TOO, BUT MOST OF US
HAVE LOST THOSE INSTINCTS.
THAT'S WHY WE NEED
A LITTLE HELP.
DAD, WHAT'S THAT ?
SURVEYOR'S EQUIPMENT.
SOMEONE LEFT HIS STUFF
OUT HERE.
[ Barking ]
[ Barking Continues ]
STAY CLOSE, LOUIS.
[ Dog Whimpering ]
WHAT IS IT, DAD ?
DAD ?
BO.  COME HERE, BO.
WHAT--
QUIET !
[ Rustling ]
LISTEN TO ME.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE BO
AND RUN STRAIGHT HOME.
WHAT'S THE MATTER ?
I WANT YOU TO RUN
STRAIGHT HOME,
AND I DON'T WANT YOU
TO STOP FOR ANYTHING.
-LOUIS, YOU UNDERSTAND ?
-I JUST--
ALL RIGHT, GO.
[ Rustling ]
COME ON, BO, COME ON !
[ Rifle Shot ]
BO, NO, NO !
COME ON, BO, COME ON !
[ Barking ]
COME ON !  COME ON !
[ Man ]
LAST YEAR WAS SOMETHING
OF A PERSONAL REVELATION.
WE WERE DOING AN EXERCISE
CALLED "TEAM BUILDERS,"
WHERE WE WERE GIVEN
TWO MINUTES TO BUILD A TOWER...
OUT OF ORDINARY
OFFICE FURNITURE.
WHEN I STOOD ON MIKE'S SHOULDERS
AND I PUT THAT ELECTRIC
PENCIL SHARPENER...
ON TOP OF THE PILE,
WE BOTH KNEW--
WE COULD NEVER
HAVE DONE IT ALONE.
KILL ME NOW.
YOU EVER BEEN TO ONE OF THESE
TEAM SEMINARS, AGENT SCULLY ?
UM, I THINK I WENT
TO A CONSTRUCTIVE
PROBLEM-SOLVING COURSE...
WHEN I FIRST JOINED
THE BUREAU.
DID YOU PLAY THAT GAME
WHERE YOU CAN'T USE
ANY NEGATIVE WORDS ?
I COULDN'T BELIEVE HOW HARD IT
WAS NOT TO USE THE WORD "BUT."
I'M HAVING THAT SAME PROBLEM
RIGHT NOW !
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO
A TEAM SEMINAR, AGENT MULDER ?
NO.  UNFORTUNATELY
AROUND THIS TIME OF YEAR...
I ALWAYS DEVELOP A SEVERE
HEMORRHOIDAL CONDITION.
WELL, IT BUILDS MUSCLES
YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW YOU HAD.
COMMUNICATION.
THAT'S THE KEY.
SORRY, FOLKS.
IT'LL BE A FEW MINUTES.
-WHAT'S GOING ON, OFFICER ?
- GOT A LITTLE SITUATION,
IS ALL.
THANK YOU, JESUS.
WHERE'S HE GOING ?
OH, EXCUSE ME !
ARE YOU FROM SEARCH AND RESCUE ?
NO, I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST STRETCHING
MY LEGS.
THEY SAID THEY'D HAVE WORD
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY HUSBAND.
I NEED SOMEBODY TO TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON.
JUST SLOW DOWN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
MY HUSBAND, MICHAEL, HE WAS
TEACHING OUR SON TO SHOOT.
HE SAID THE DOG GOT SPOOKED,
AND THEN HE HEARD GUNSHOTS.
NOW THEY'VE FOUND A JACKET
WITH BLOOD ON IT, BUT THEY
WON'T TELL ME ABOUT MY HUSBAND.
I'LL TRY TO FIND OUT
WHO'S IN CHARGE, ALL RIGHT ?
THANK YOU.
NOW WHERE'S HE GOING ?
HEY, STONECYPHER,
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
THIS TREE WAS HERE 20 YEARS
BEFORE PONCE de LEON LANDED.
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR THE WINE
AND CHEESE RECEPTION.
[ Man ]
OFFICER FAZEKAS ?
YES ?
- CAN I HELP YOU ?
- MY NAME IS FOX MULDER.
I'M AN AGENT WITH THE F.B.I.
F.B.I. ?
WHO CALLED YOU GUYS OUT ?
NOBODY.  WE GOT STOPPED
AT YOUR ROADBLOCK.  SOUNDS
LIKE YOU HAVE A SHOOTING.
SHOTS WERE REPORTED,
BUT WE HAVE NO EVIDENCE
OF ANYONE BEING SHOT.
WHAT DO YOU
HAVE EVIDENCE OF ?
A SURVEY TEAM WORKING
THESE WOODS DIDN'T REPORT IN
LAST NIGHT.
WE FOUND ONE MAN'S
BLOODY JACKET, PRETTY TORN UP.
AND THIS MORNING, A BOY
GOT SEPARATED FROM HIS FATHER.
SEPARATED BY WHAT ?
IT LOOKS MAYBE...
LIKE SOME KIND
OF ANIMAL ATTACK.
WHAT KIND OF ANIMAL ?
I'M NOT SURE YET.
I FOLLOWED GOOD TRACKS
FOR THE TWO SURVEYORS,
BUT THE TRAILS BECAME CONFUSED
AS THEY MOVED INTO THE BRUSH.
THERE WAS A THIRD SET OF TRACKS
LEADING AWAY...
I COULDN'T IDENTIFY.
COULDN'T IDENTIFY
AS THE SURVEYORS' ?
AS MAN OR ANIMAL.
-MULDER ?
- JUST, UH--
H-HOLD ON A SECOND.
WHAT ABOUT THE BOY'S FATHER ?
I TRACKED HIM ALL THE WAY DOWN
TO WHERE HE FIRED THE SHOT.
THE GROUND'S ROCKY,
BUT FROM THE DEPRESSIONS
IN THE UNDERLYING SOIL,
I CAN TELL YOU THAT HE ENTERED
THE BUSHES FROM OVER THERE...
WHERE I PICK UP
ANOTHER SET OF TRACKS,
TWO DISTINCTLY DIFFERENT SET
OF TRACKS THAT FROM THE WAY...
THE GROUND'S UPSET,
IS PROBABLY WHERE
THE MAN WAS ATTACKED.
BUT NO OTHER SIGN OF HIM ?
YOU HAVE PANTHER
IN THESE WOODS ?
THERE'S PANTHER, BEAR.
BUT THESE TRACKS LOOK LIKE
NEITHER OF THOSE.
NO, SIR.
YOU KNOW OF A GOOD MOTEL
IN THE AREA ?
EXCUSE ME.
I THINK WE CAN HANDLE THIS
VERY WELL ON OUR OWN.  THANKS.
MULDER ?
WE'VE GOT THIS CONFERENCE.
THEY'RE WAITING.
YEAH.
HOW DO I SAY THIS
WITHOUT USING
ANY NEGATIVE WORDS, SCULLY ?
YOU WANT ME TO TELL THEM
THAT YOU'RE NOT GONNA MAKE IT
TO THIS YEAR'S TEAMWORK SEMINAR.
SEE ?  WE DON'T NEED
THAT CONFERENCE.
WE HAVE COMMUNICATION
LIKE THAT UNSPOKEN.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M THINKING.
[ Laughing ]
LOOK !
HE'S ALL EATEN AWAY.
HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT, EH ?
[ TV Off ]
HE'S NOT COMING BACK, IS HE ?
NOW, WHY WOULD YOU
SAY THAT ?
DAD'S A GOOD SHOT.
IF HE HIT WHAT HE WAS AIMING AT,
HE'D BE HOME BY NOW.
YOU GOTTA BE BRAVE, LOUIS.
WE BOTH GOTTA BE BRAVE.
WE'LL FIND OUT MORE ABOUT IT
IN THE MORNING.
GET SOME SLEEP NOW.
[ Whimpering ]
[ Knocking On Door ]
IT'S OPEN.
WHO CUT THE CHEESE ?
SINCE YOU WON'T BE MAKING IT
TO THE CONFERENCE.
MMM !  PAR-TAY !
HOWEVER, I MUST REMIND YOU,
THIS GOES AGAINST
THE BUREAU'S POLICY...
OF MALE AND FEMALE AGENTS
CONSORTING IN THE SAME
MOTEL ROOM WHILE ON ASSIGNMENT.
TRY ANY OF THAT "TAILHOOK"
CRAP ON ME, SCULLY,
I'LL KICK YOUR ASS.
IT'S A POP QUIZ.
WHAT ANIMAL WILL ATTACK
THE STRONGEST, LEAVING
THE WEAKEST TO ESCAPE ?
THE ANSWER IS "NONE."
NOT ONE OF THE OVER
4,000 SPECIES NATIVE
TO NORTH AMERICA...
WILL ATTACK THE STRONGEST
WHEN THE WEAK IS VULNERABLE.
AND WHAT DOES THAT
HAVE TO DO WITH ANYTHING ?
IT MAKES ME THINK THAT WHAT
WE'RE DEALING WITH HERE
IS NO ORDINARY PREDATOR.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS A PLOY
TO GET OUT OF THE CONFERENCE.
I THINK WHAT WE'VE STUMBLED
UPON HERE IS SOMETHING MORE
THAN LOCAL AUTHORITIES REALIZE.
THE SCENARIO DESCRIBED
BY THAT BOY SOUNDS TO ME LIKE
A PRIMITIVE CULLING TECHNIQUE.
WE'RE IN WESTERN FLORIDA.
THE CLOSEST THING TO PRIMITIVE
DOWN HERE...
IS LIVING IN A BEACHFRONT
RETIREMENT CONDO.
THOSE WOODS ARE AS OLD
AS ANYTHING IN THE SOUTH.
THERE'S 800 SQUARE MILES OF IT.
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT'S ALIVE OUT THERE.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING ?
I'VE GOTTA CHECK
SOMETHING OUT.
SOMETIMES I THINK SOME WORK
ON YOUR COMMUNICATION SKILLS
WOULDN'T BE SUCH A BAD IDEA.
I'LL BE BACK SOON,
AND WE CAN BUILD A TOWER
OF FURNITURE.
OKAY ?
[ Barking ]
[ Whining, Barking ]
WHAT IS IT, BO ?
[ Barking ]
MOM ?
IT'S ALL RIGHT, LOUIS.
YOU GO BACK TO SLEEP NOW.
[ Barking ]
BO ?
BO, WHERE'D YOU GET TO ?
[ Rustling ]
BO, IS THAT YOU ?
- [ Growls ]
- [ Gasps ]
COME HOME, BOY.
LET'S GO BACK IN.
[ Growling ]
- [ Barking ]
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
STAY THERE THE NIGHT.
LOUIS ?
[ Pounding On Door ]
LOUIS !
LOUIS !  LOUIS !
MOM !
[ Screaming ]
WHAT IS IT, LOUIS ?
IT'S IN THE HOUSE.
HOW'S IT GOING ?
HE'S STILL FREAKED OUT.
I MIGHT HAVE SOME INSIGHT
INTO THIS INVISIBLE CREATURE
HE SAID WAS CHASING HIM.
THE INVISIBLE MAN
WAS INVISIBLE.
RIGHT.
HE SAID HE WAS CHASED
BY A CREATURE
WITH GLOWING RED EYES.
LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
MRS. ASEKOFF SAID SHE
WENT OUTSIDE WITH THE DOG.
WHEN SHE CAME BACK,
THE DOOR WAS LOCKED
FROM THE INSIDE.
AND ?
LOOK AT THIS.
WE GOT
SOME TRACKS HERE.
WHERE ?
HERE AND HERE.
DRIED MUD AGAINST THE TILE,
TRACKED IN
FROM THE OUTSIDE.
IT COULD'VE BEEN BROUGHT IN
BY THE DOG.
NO, NO.
YOU SEE THE BALL
OF THE FOOT HERE ?
A LARGE FOOT.
- AND I COUNT FIVE TOES.
- WAIT, I THOUGHT YOU SAID
IT WASN'T HUMAN.
I'M NOT SAYING IT IS.
THE WEIGHT DISTRIBUTION
IS ALL WRONG.
PEOPLE WALK HEEL TO TOE.
WHATEVER THIS THING IS,
WALKS ON THE BALL OF ITS FOOT.
YOU'RE PUTTING ME ON.
NO.  MY DAD AND I
WERE INDIAN GUIDES.
I KNOW THESE THINGS.
SO IF IT'S NOT MAN
AND IT'S NOT ANIMAL,
WHAT THE HELL IS IT ?
GUESS I'M A LITTLE LATE
TO THIS DANCE.
I FOUND SOME TRACKS...
RIGHT HERE.
SAME AS I SAW BEFORE.
WHERE WAS THAT ?
IN THE WOODS.
WEIGHT DISTRIBUTION'S STRANGE.
THEY APPEAR TO BE HUMAN,
BUT WHOEVER LEFT THESE
USES THE BALLS OF HIS FEET
MORE LIKE AN ANIMAL.
WHATEVER IT IS,
IT'S ATTACKED THREE GROWN MEN
PRESUMABLY IN BROAD DAYLIGHT,
DISPOSING OF ITS PREY
WITHOUT DETECTION.
AND IT WASN'T SHY LAST NIGHT
ABOUT COMING OUT
OF THE WOODS TO TRY AGAIN.
WHAT WE'VE GOT IS A PREDATOR
WITH LOW VISIBILITY AND
A HIGH DEGREE OF MOTIVATION.
IT'S GOT ONE ADVANTAGE
WE DON'T HAVE--
THE ENTIRE APPALACHICOLA
NATIONAL FOREST.
THEN HOW DO YOU STOP IT ?
BY IDENTIFYING IT.
FINDING IT BEFORE
IT FINDS SOMEBODY ELSE.
IT'S CALLED A "FLIR"
FOR FORWARD LOOKING INFRARED.
IT WAS DEVELOPED FOR
CHOPPER PILOTS IN VIETNAM.
DETECTS BODY HEAT
AT 300 YARDS.
THAT'S PRETTY SOPHISTICATED
FOR GOVERNMENT ISSUE.
I SEE YOU TWO HAVE MET.
JEFF'S OUR LOCAL TECH-HEAD.
SOME PEOPLE PREFER SEARCHING
WITH DOGS.
I PREFER AN EXTRA PAIR OF
HANDS IF I GET IN TROUBLE.
ARE WE READY TO GO ?
ONCE WE START IN, YOU CAN
PUT AWAY YOUR CELL PHONES.
THE ONLY COMMUNICATION
IN THESE WOODS
IS WITH SHORTWAVE RADIOS.
SO, STAY CLOSE,
MAINTAIN VISUAL CONTACT.
IF YOU GET LOST,
INITIATE ORAL CONTACT.
THAT MEANS HOLLER.
IF NOBODY RESPONDS, SIT DOWN,
DON'T MOVE.  I WILL FIND YOU.
DON'T GO LOOKING FOR ME.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS OBVIOUS,
BUT FOLKS STILL GET LOST.
OKAY.
I GOTCHA.  THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
LOCAL P.D.
HAS ALL THEIR RESOURCES
LOOKING OUT FOR A TRANSIENT,
A DRIFTER WHO'S WANTED
FOR A DOUBLE HOMICIDE
IN GASDEN, ALABAMA.
THEY WERE AMUSED WHEN
I TOLD THEM WHAT WE WERE DOING.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A DRIFTER.
WE MAY BE LOOKING
FOR TWO INDIVIDUALS.
WHY DO YOU SAY THAT ?
THAT THING LURED THAT WOMAN
OUT OF THE HOUSE...
TO SEPARATE HER
FROM HER SON.
FOR WHAT PURPOSE ?
DIVIDE AND CONQUER.
IF YOUR ENEMY HAS
GREATER NUMBERS THAN YOU...
YOU DIVIDE AND CONQUER
TO DIMINISH THOSE NUMBERS.
WHAT ENEMY WOULD THAT BE ?
ENCROACHING DEVELOPMENT.
THAT'S WHAT I SUSPECTED
WHEN I WENT TO CHECK
ON LOUIS AND HIS MOTHER.
THIS IS ABOUT A HOUSING TRACT ?
THAT SURVEY TEAM WAS STAKING OUT
A NEW 100,000 ACRE PLOT.
CIVILIZATION'S PUSHING
VERY HARD INTO THESE WOODS.
MAYBE SOMETHING IN
THESE WOODS IS PUSHING BACK.
ANYTHING ?
NO.
NOTHING AT ALL,
NOT EVEN WILDLIFE.
ISN'T THAT
A LITTLE STRANGE ?
YEAH.
THIS FOREST IS USUALLY
ALIVE WITH SOUND.
I'M NOT AN EXPERT,
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN IT
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
SURE IS BEAUTIFUL, THOUGH.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS.  PEOPLE GET
TO LOOKING AROUND, NEXT THING
THEY KNOW SOMETHING EATS THEM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
KILLED THOSE MEN ?
NATURE IS POPULATED BY CREATURES
EITHER TRYING TO KILL SOMETHING
THEY NEED TO SURVIVE,
OR TRYING TO AVOID BEING KILLED
BY SOMETHING THAT NEEDS THEM
TO SURVIVE.
IF WE BECOME BLINDED
BY THE BEAUTY OF NATURE,
WE MAY FAIL TO SEE...
ITS CRUELTY AND VIOLENCE.
WALT WHITMAN ?
NO. WHEN ANIMALS ATTACK
ON THE FOX NETWORK.
WAIT, I'VE GOT SOMETHING.
IT'S ABOUT 20 YARDS AHEAD.
WHERE ?
I DON'T SEE IT.
IT'S JUST SITTING THERE.
IT'S ON THE MOVE !
IT'S MOVING FAST !
IT'S-IT'S GOING TO THE RIGHT !
WAIT !  THERE'S TWO OF THEM NOW.
THEY'RE MOVING
IN OPPOSITE DIRECTIONS.
THERE AND THERE.
WHERE IS IT ?
ABOUT 40 YARDS AHEAD OF YOU.
I DON'T SEE IT.
NOW IT'S GONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT WENT.
WHAT IS IT ?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY'RE TRYING
TO SEPARATE US, PULL US
AWAY FROM THE OTHERS.
LET'S GO BACK.
[ Gasps ]
MICHELLE ?
[ Rustling ]
MULDER, I NEED HELP !
MULDER !
SCULLY !
OVER HERE !
SCULLY ?
OVER HERE.
WHAT HAPPENED ?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHERE'S FAZEKAS ?
SHE WAS WALKING AHEAD OF ME.
SHE WAS RIGHT HERE,
AND THEN SHE WAS JUST GONE.
I'M GETTING NO READING.
- WHAT THE HELL'S
HAPPENING HERE ?
- THEY SEPARATED US.
THAT WAS ON PURPOSE.
THEY DIVIDED US
SO THEY COULD GO AFTER HER.
SHE WAS IN THE LEAD,
AND PRESUMABLY
THE STRONGEST.
THEY TAKE
THE STRONGEST FIRST.
TAKE THEM WHERE ?
YOU CAN'T JUST
DISAPPEAR OUT HERE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE GOTTA FIND HER.
HOW ARE WE GONNA DO THAT ?
I DON'T KNOW !
FORM A LINE
AND BEAT THE BUSHES.
MAYBE YOU'LL PICK UP
A SIGNAL.
NO, WE NEED HELP.
WE NEED MANPOWER.
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK OUT HERE.
WE NEED TO GET OUTTA HERE !
LISTEN TO ME.
THE LONGER WE WAIT,
THE LESS CHANCE WE HAVE
OF FINDING HER.
THIS IS NUTS.
THIS IS LOONEY TUNE, MAN.
WE GOTTA GO BACK
OUT OF THESE WOODS
BEFORE IT GETS DARK.
OKAY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU GO BACK.
YOU LEAVE ME THE FLIR,
AND YOU GO BACK.
WE GOTTA GO TOGETHER.
WE HAVE TO FIND HER.
YEAH, WELL, IF WE STAY HERE,
THEY MAY NOT FIND ANY OF US.
MULDER, HE'S RIGHT.
WE WEREN'T PREPARED FOR THIS.
WE HAVE NO WAY OF TELLING THEM
WHERE WE ARE.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY FOOD.
MICHELLE HAD OUR ONLY WATER.
I'D LIKE TO FIND HER TOO,
BUT I THINK THE RISKS OF THAT
ARE WAY TOO FOOLISH.
ALL RIGHT, WE ALL GO THEN.
YOU LEAD THE WAY.
I DON'T HAVE MUCH FAITH
THAT THIS DEVICE
WILL DO US ANY GOOD.
SO FAR, ALL IT'S DONE
IS SPLIT US UP.
WHATEVER IT IS WE'RE CHASING,
DID SHOW UP ON THE SCREEN
AT FIRST.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU ?
NOTHING, EXCEPT WE'RE GOING
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
MAYBE IT CAN REGULATE
ITS TEMPERATURE.  YOU DON'T KNOW
OF ANY ANIMAL THAT CAN ?
TICKS.  I'VE HEARD THEY
CAN HALT THEIR METABOLISM...
FOR UP TO 18 YEARS,
ESSENTIALLY GOING
INTO SUSPENDED ANIMATION...
UNTIL SOMETHING
WARM-BLOODED COMES ALONG.
THAT'S INTERESTING.
WHY IS THAT INTERESTING ?
THIRTY YEARS AGO, THE TOWN OF
POINT PLEASANT, WEST VIRGINIA,
WAS TERRORIZED FOR OVER A YEAR
BY SOMETHING.
KILLING LIVESTOCK,
TERRORIZING THE PEOPLE.
WITNESSES DESCRIBED THEM
AS PRIMITIVE-LOOKING MEN
WITH RED-PIERCING EYES.
BECAME KNOWN AS THE "MOTH MEN."
I'VE GOT AN X-FILE DATING BACK
TO 1952 ON IT.
WHAT WOULD THAT BE FILED
NEXT TO ?  "THE COCKROACH
THAT ATE CINCINNATI" ?
THE COCKROACH THAT ATE
CINCINNATI IS IN THE "C's."
MOTH MEN'S OVER IN THE "M's."
THIS ISN'T THE WAY.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
MICHELLE ALWAYS MARKS HER ROUTE
WITH LITTLE WHITE STONES.
THIS IS THE SAME PATH.
THIS IS THE WAY WE CAME.
I HAVEN'T SEEN ONE OF HER STONES
FOR 20 MINUTES.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'VE HAD
YOUR NOSE GLUED TO
THAT SCREEN THE WHOLE TIME.
I'M TELLING YOU,
WE'RE ON THE WRONG TRAIL.
SOMEHOW WE GOT OFF TRACK.
OH, MAN,
THIS IS NOT HAPPENING.
EVERYBODY STAND STILL.
THERE'S SOMETHING OUT THERE.
WHERE ?
ABOUT 40 OR 50 YARDS OUT.
JEFF ?
NOTHING.
I SAW IT.
THE WOODS
HAVE GONE SILENT AGAIN.
[ Rustling ]
I GOT IT !
I GOT IT ON MY SCREEN.
WHERE ?  WHERE !
ABOUT 30 YARDS AHEAD.
IT'S JUST SITTING THERE.
WHAT IS HE DOING ?
[ Scully ]
TALK TO HIM.
THIS IS NOT A GOOD IDEA.
TALK TO HIM, JEFF !
GO TO YOUR RIGHT.
IT JUST DISAPPEARED.
[ Scully ]
MULDER, IT'S NOT ON THE SCREEN.
[ Mulder ]
SCULLY, I LOST IT.
[ Scully ]
I GOT IT !
- DID YOU HIT IT ?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST STOPPED.
WHERE'S GLASER ?
- HOW MANY SHOTS DID YOU FIRE ?
- SIX, MAYBE SEVEN.
THAT YOUR ONLY CLIP ?
YEP.
DON'T FIRE AGAIN UNLESS
YOU'RE SURE YOU'RE GONNA HIT IT.
IT MAY BE TRYING TO
SPEND OUR ADVANTAGE.
WHAT THE HELL IS IT,
MULDER ?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT WHATEVER IT IS,
IT'S SMARTER THAN US.
AT LEAST OUT HERE.
- [ Gasps ]
- MULDER ?  MULDER !
SCULLY !
MULDER ?
YOU OKAY ?
YOU WERE AN INDIAN GUIDE.
HELP ME OUT HERE.
INDIAN GUIDE SAYS MAYBE
YOU SHOULD RUN TO THE STORE
AND GET SOME MATCHES.
I WOULD, BUT I LEFT MY WALLET
IN THE CAR.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
TRYING TO OPEN MY GUN.
IF I CAN SEPARATE THE SHELL
FROM THE CASING, MAYBE I CAN GET
THE POWDER TO IGNITE.
AND MAYBE IT'LL START
RAINING WEENIES
AND MARSHMALLOWS.
DO I DETECT A HINT OF
NEGATIVITY ?
NO !  YES,
ACTUALLY.  YEAH.
MULDER, YOU NEED TO KEEP WARM.
YOUR BODY'S STILL IN SHOCK.
I WAS TOLD ONCE THAT
THE BEST WAY TO REGENERATE
BODY HEAT...
IS TO CRAWL NAKED INTO A
SLEEPING BAG WITH SOMEBODY ELSE
WHO WAS ALREADY NAKED.
MAYBE IF IT RAINED
SLEEPING BAGS,
YOU'LL GET LUCKY.
YOU EVER THOUGHT SERIOUSLY
ABOUT DYING ?
ONCE WHEN I WAS
AT THE ICE CAPADES.
WHEN I WAS FIGHTING
MY CANCER,
I WAS ANGRY
AT THE INJUSTICE OF IT...
AND ITS MEANINGLESSNESS.
THEN I REALIZED THAT
THAT WAS A STRUGGLE--
TO GIVE IT MEANING...
TO MAKE SENSE OF IT.
IT'S LIKE LIFE.
I THINK NATURE
IS SUPREMELY INDIFFERENT
TO WHETHER WE LIVE OR DIE.
I MEAN, IF YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU GET 75 YEARS, IF YOU'RE
REALLY LUCKY YOU GET 80.
IF YOU'RE EXTRAORDINARILY LUCKY,
YOU GET 50 OF THOSE YEARS
WITH A DECENT HEAD OF HAIR.
I GUESS IT IS LIKE LAS VEGAS.
THE HOUSE ALWAYS WINS.
OH !
dd TA-DA dddd
GO, GIRL.
[ Mulder ]
HEY, WHO DID YOU IDENTIFY WITH
WHEN YOU WERE A KID--
WILMA OR BETTY ?
I IDENTIFIED
WITH BETTY'S BUSTLINE.
YES !  I DID TOO.
I COULD NEVER HAVE BEEN MARRIED
TO BARNEY, THOUGH.
THE KIDS WERE CUTE.
YEAH, BUT WHERE
ARE THEY TODAY ?
"MOTH MEN" ?
REALLY ?
YEAH.  BUT THERE SEEM
TO BE ONLY TWO OF 'EM.
I DON'T WANNA WRESTLE.
GET OVER HERE.
I'M GONNA TRY
AND KEEP YOU WARM.
SORRY.
ONE OF US HAS GOT
TO STAY AWAKE, SCULLY.
YOU SLEEP, MULDER.
IF YOU GET TIRED,
YOU WAKE ME.
I'M NOT GONNA GET TIRED.
WHY DON'T YOU SING
SOMETHING ?
NO, MULDER.
IF YOU SING SOMETHING,
I'LL KNOW YOU'RE AWAKE.
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO SING.
I CAN'T CARRY A TUNE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
JUST SING ANYTHING.
d
dd JEREMIAH WAS A BULLFROG d
dd WAS A GOOD FRIEND
OF MINE dd
dd NEVER UNDERSTOOD
A SINGLE WORD HE SAID dd
dd BUT I HELPED HIM
DRINK HIS WINE dd
CHORUS.
dd JOY... TO THE WORLD dd
dd ALL THE BOYS AND GIRLS dd
d
dd JOY TO THE FISHES
IN THE DEEP BLUE SEA d
d
dd JOY TO YOU AND ME ddd
SCULLY ?
HERE.  OVER HERE !
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
LOOKING FOR FOOD.
I FOUND SOME WILD BERRIES.
I WOULDN'T GO FAR.
MULDER, YOU NEVER LEFT
MY SIGHT.
[ Groan ]
SCULLY ?
SCULLY !
DOWN HERE !
WHERE ?
I FELL DOWN A HOLE.
[ Coughing ]
YOU ALL RIGHT ?
YEAH.
I LANDED ON SOFT DIRT.
KIND OF.
WHAT'S DOWN THERE ?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S PRETTY DARK.
[ Gasps ]
SCULLY, WHAT'S GOING ON ?
YOU OKAY ?
- I FOUND MICHELLE.
- IS SHE ALIVE ?
NOT FOR MUCH LONGER.
MULDER, WE HAVE TO
GET HER OUT OF HERE.
- IS THERE A WAY OUT ?
- I DON'T KNOW.  I--
I'M IN SOME KIND OF A CHAMBER.
THERE'S--
IT'S LIKE...
SOME KIND OF NETWORK.
-MULDER ?
- YEAH ?
I'M NOT ALONE.
I DON'T HAVE MY WEAPON !
MULDER !
HOLD ON.  I'M GONNA
DROP MY GUN DOWN.
[ Rustling ]
- OW !
- JESUS !
-MULDER, ARE YOU OKAY ?
- DON'T MIND ME.
SCULLY !
MULDER, LOOK.
THERE HAS TO BE A SCIENTIFIC
EXPLANATION FOR THIS.
[ Groaning ]
TOO BAD WE DON'T HAVE
ANY OFFICE FURNITURE.
IF THEY COULD SEE US NOW.
GO, TEAM.
A HUNDRED MORE BODIES AND
WE'LL WIN THE HONEYBAKED HAM.
[ Man ]
AGENT MULDER !
WE'RE DOWN HERE !
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
DOWN THERE ?
WE'VE GOT INJURED PEOPLE
DOWN HERE.
WE NEED A LADDER.
RIGHT AWAY.
HEY, OVER HERE.
[ Siren Wailing ]
DAD'S GONNA BE OKAY.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
I'M JUST GONNA SAY GOOD-BYE.
[ Siren Wailing ]
WELL, WE JUST GOT
ALL THE THANKS
WHEN YOU DID ALL THE WORK.
ON THE CONTRARY, AGENT KINSLEY.
WE WOULD'VE NEVER GOTTEN
INVOLVED IN THIS IF NOT FOR YOU.
REALLY ?
YEAH.
YOU SEE THIS ?
YEAH, I POINTED THAT OUT
TO AGENT STONECYPHER
ON THE DRIVE DOWN.
THERE WAS SOMETHING
IN THE CAVE THAT SCULLY
FELL INTO, AN INSCRIPTION.
"AD NOCTUM."
THAT'S LATIN.
YEAH.  IT MEANS,
"INTO DARKNESS."
THE SPANISH CONQUISTADORS
USED TO CARVE IT
ON THE POST...
THAT THEY WOULD
LASH THE NATIVES TO
AS A WARNING.
SO, WHO ARE YOU SAYING
WROTE THIS ?
PONCE de LEON CAME HERE
450 YEARS AGO LOOKING FOR
THE FOUNTAIN OF YOUTH.
YOU MEAN,
YOU THINK THAT THAT BODY,
THE ONE THAT
AGENT SCULLY SHOT--
NO.
AFTER 400 YEARS
IN THE WOODS,
DON'T YOU THINK
THEY MIGHT HAVE ADAPTED
PERFECTLY TO THEIR ENVIRONMENT ?
YOU'RE MAKING THIS UP.
WHY DO YOU SAY THAT ?
'CAUSE YOU WORK ON THE X-FILES
AND YOU JUST WANT TO WRITE OFF
YOUR MOTEL.
SEARCH AND RESCUE
ARE STILL UNABLE
TO FIND JEFF GLASER...
OR THE SECOND PREDATOR
THAT YOU REPORTED.
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF THEY COULDN'T FIND
EITHER ONE OF THEM.
AGENT MULDER, I'M CONFUSED.
WHY WOULD THEY COME AFTER
THE BOY IN THE HOUSE
THAT NIGHT ?
THESE PREDATORS
HAVE BEEN IN THESE WOODS
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
THEY WOULD'VE PERCEIVED
ANY ENCROACHMENT ON
THEIR TERRITORY AS AN ENEMY,
EVEN A LITTLE KID LIKE THAT.
BUT THAT WOULD MEAN THAT THEY'D
COME AFTER ANY ONE OF US...
THAT HAD GONE INTO THE WOODS,
WOULDN'T IT ?
WHERE'S AGENT SCULLY ?
SHE GOT A LIFT BACK TO THE MOTEL
TO PACK UP BOTH YOUR THINGS.
SHE DID ?
EXCUSE ME.
MY JACKET'S IN THAT CAR.
SCULLY !  SCULLY !
MULDER, WHAT'S GOING ON ?
LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
OKAY.
YOU PACK EVERYTHING ?
YEAH.
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !