±¾׳צה»½צ¹©ס§ן°½»בק£¬סן½ףדףתילעµףדם¾
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
Criminal minds 320
-=ֶזאדנ׳צה»׳י=-
·­עכ: נ£¶פ:
ך±¼הצב:מע°®ך¨נהנ¡s walden
Taxi!
Spring street,
spring street station.
Spring street...
Excuse me.
Please.
Hotch.
Hey.
Uh, no, i'm actually still
at the office.
I'm just getting some things-
Whoa, hold on, hold on.
Start from the beginning.
No, we're all familiar
with the case.
When was the latest murder?
Is anything in the m.O. Changed?
So, what's your flight number?
No, i'm going to come pick you up.
Yeah, exactly.
I can't have you free
to pick out a crib without me.
Jj, will you get the team together?
We have a case.
Nothing's come across my desk.
This one came directly to me.
Uh, just don't head
to the airport just yet.
I'll call you as soon as i can.
Bye.
Don't get comfortable.
There'll be time to debrief
on the plane.
Where are we headed?
New york.
Five shooting's in two weeks,
It's about time we got the call.
I want to take garcia with us.
Hopefully we will get those access
to their surveillance systems.
What do we know?
All the killings are mid-Day.
Single gun shot to the head
with a.22.
Any witnesses?
No.
.22-Caliber pistol's only 152 decibels.
New york streets and subways
are routinely well over 100.
It could be people not even
registering the gunshot
Until the unsub's already
leaving the scene.
Sound like mob hits.
Except none of them
have ties to organized crime.
Do they have any connection
to each other?
None they've found.
How about communication with the police?
Does the unsub try
to make any contact?
Surveillance cameras have captured
video of three of the murders,
This is the latest.
That's the best image they have?
They are all the same.
He wears a hood and
keeps his head down.
This guy is bold.
Crowded areas, broad daylight.
So they're completely random?
It seems that way.
Son of sam all over again.
Voltaire said,
The man visited by
ecstasys and visions,
Who takes dreams for realities
Is an enthusiast.
The man who supports his madness
with murder
Is a fanatic.
How come i only get to travel
with you guys like once every two years?
Trust me, it can get old.
Oh right, like the way the spa treatments
and five star hotels gets old.
Remember the time we got on board
And they hadn't chilled the cristal?
Ooh. I almost quit the b.A.U. That day.
Okay, you know what?
You guys can joke all you want
Because i am never leaving the plane.
Victims?
Each killed in a completely
different neighbourhood.
Hell's kitchen, murray hill,
Lower side, china town,
East harlom.
Doesn't make any sense.
There's no common victimology.
No sexual component.
No robbery,
no geographical connection.
Do the police have any leads?
He's killing roughly every two days.
The press is having a field day.
And it sounds like the mood on the street's
getting pretty edgey.
It's a joint fbinypd task force?
Kate joyner heads up the new york field office.
She's running point on the case
And called me directly.
Jj, would you tell them
we're ready to go?
Right.
Kate's starting to butt heads
with the lead detectives
And wanted a fresh set of eyes.
Joyner, i know her.
She's a brit, right?
Well, dual citizenship.
Her father's british,
Her mother's american.
She was a big deal at scotland yard
before coming to the bureau.
I heard she can be
a little bit of a pain in the ass.
I didn't think so.
You know her?
We liaised when she was still
at scotland yard.
And she's good?
I think we're lucky to have her.
??? We're cleared for takeoff.
Please take your seats.
Can you have someone run to my flat,
Get me an extra set of clothes?
And tell forensics i don't want to just cross-Check
with conntticuec and new jersey.
I want interpol as well.
Has the b.A.U. Arrived yet?
They should be here soon.
Shelly, can you get me the commissioner?
Never mind. Hold the call.
Is it just me
or does she look exactly like haley?
Kate.
Aaron.
How have you been?
Well, thank you.
This is my team.
Kate joyner,
This is david rossi,
Emily prentiss,
Jennifer jareau,
Penelope garcia, derek morgan,
And spencer reid.
Thanks for being here.
Anything that you need,
just tell me.
Please don't stand on protocol.
What can you tell us about
the city's surveillance system?
Um, it's run by the nypd.
It's still in the infant stages.
It's been rather controversial.
American privacy laws.
Um, but they've had some success.
And i'll have complete access?
They're already expecting you.
Shelley?
I'd like to get a map of the borough.
I want to do a comprehensive
geographical profile of the area
In order to ascertain the unsub's mental map
Before it's clouded by our own linkage blindness.
I see you brought your own computer.
Detectives brustin and cooper.
I'll let you do the introductions.
You caught the first shooting?
They've all been in different precincts.
It wasn't until the third murder
that anyone even made the connection.
I guess this is where we play nice
And ask you what you need.
I'll let you all
figure out what that is.
I just ask that you run everything
back through me.
It's been my experience that
having one butt on the line is enough.
Yes, ma'am.
Can i have a word with you in private?
Sure.
Excuse me.
They, um...
Liaised when she was at scotland yard.
Of course.
So you're getting resistance from nypd?
It's nothing i wasn't expecting.
They're good detectives,
Just no self-Respecting cop
Wants to have his ass kicked
by some broad with a posh british accent.
So what's going on?
What can you tell me about derek morgan?
Hey, so, uh, what's your partner's problem?
Uh, well...
Well, by the fourth murder the fbi was brought in.
Good.
We can use all the help we can get.
But, uh, all of a sudden she's taking meetings
with the mayor
And calling in you all
without us knowing anything about it.
We're only here to help.
Think of us as a resource.
Ok.
Profile me.
What am i thinking?
It's never gonna happen.
No offense,
But we've had 5 murders.
Hope it gets better than that.
You must be fbi.
Lisa bartleby.
Penelope garcia.
May i?
I hardly ever get visitors.
You'll hardly know i'm here.
What's your operating system?
Um, linux os with 6 gigs of ram.
And a dual quad core 3 gigahertz processor
With a geforce 8800 ultra extreme vid card
And a cisco asa 5500 firewall.
Yeah.
Bitchin'.
How many cameras?
Uh, 4,468,
Not including the ones that only run
in the housing projects.
And all the footage is stored?
Catalogued and digitized.
Beautiful.
'Cause my boss man wants me
to send him a file
So he can run facial recognition software
On each of the crime scenes.
Um, i've already enhanced all of the photos
as much as i can.
No, i'm talking about using it
On the crowd
immediately after the shootings.
This is icky,  but these creeps,
They sometimes like to come back
And watch the police deal
with their handiwork.
And...
Voila.
Can i ask you a question?
When was the last time you went home
and got some sleep?
None of us are going to sleep
until this is over.
Who in the hell thinks they can
get away with murder
In the middle of the day
in new york city?
Someone patient
Who waits for the one
who gets separated from the flock.
Bang.
Is that the spot?
Yeah. Thereabouts.
Are we boring you?
Look, i know you don't like ssa joyner.
Fine. I get it.
But we're here to do a job.
Have any of your people ever been cops?
Chicago.
Then you'll understand.
I take it real personal
If something like this happens
in my city.
I was a beat cop during the son of sam.
This is worse.
He's not just going after one type.
He's going after everybody.
And i need everybody
working on this case,
Taking it personally.
You have that.
We'll see.
How long have you been doing this?
Uh, about 6 months.
I wish i could tell you
it gets easier.
Yeah, well, i'm used to
pulling footage up for muggings,
Maybe robberies.
Watching someone get shot in the head...
You know what helps me?
You make it your own.
You know? You...
Separate yourself
From what you see on the screen.
This isn't exactly, uh...
Regulation.
Well, then thank god it's only us in here.
Do you want to see a superfox?
What camera's on the last crime scene?
Derek morgan...
Lisa bartleby.
Lisa bartleby,
Derek morgan.
This guy's definitely
not afraid to get up close and personal.
Or be visible.
If you watch the tape,
He ducks his head the second
he steps off the train.
So he knows when he's being filmed.
Well, we've had glimpses, but the...
Descriptions have been sketchy.
Some people said
he's a light-Skinned black man,
Asian, puerto rican,
Basically every homeboy in the city.
Ballistics were the same for every shooting?
We checked the records back 10 years.
The gun's never been recycled.
22s aren't exactly the weapon of choice
these days.
Unless you're israeli intelligence.
That's what the mossad uses for
all their political assassinations.
All i know is this guy's organized.
He studies the cameras,
Carries a gun that's easy to conceal.
He knows what he's doing.
We're gonna need records
over the last 6 months
For any arrests on gun violence
or gun possession
In every borough except the ones
where the shootings have taken place.
Uh...i don't get it.
He won't strike near where he lives.
What makes you so sure?
It's anti-Geographical profiling.
Now it's anti-Geographical profiling?
Yeah, come on.
You wonder why we're so skeptical?
This unsub's organized.
He strikes at the same time of day.
He knows where the cameras are placed.
That means he's doing his own
pre-Surveillance.
A need-Motivated killer operates
within his own comfort zone.
An organized killer with some other motivation
Will make sure to strike outside that zone.
Not where he lives.
Exactly.
Unfortunately,
That means that every other neighborhood in the city
Has a reason to be terrified.
Excuse me.
Pretzel, no mustard.
Uniforms are rounding up witnesses.
It doesn't seem like
anyone got a clean look.
It's over in a flash.
He's probably gone before anyone even
realizes what's happening.
Is this what it felt like
during the son of sam?
First we realized that if the violence
was truly random,
There was almost no way of stopping it.
It seems like these people
have figured that out.
From the placement of that camera,
Odds are the only view
they're gonna get
Is the back of his head.
Let's not be too quick to decide
What we do or don't have.
Whoo!
The duchess of work has spoken.
You mind telling me why
i'm catching attitude from her?
Fbi brass has made it clear to her
That if she doesn't bring this case home,
She's gonna be reassigned.
And you are at the top
of the list to replace her.
You're kidding me.
Why should you be surprised?
You're good at your job.
People notice that.
What happened to the bureau
patting itself on the back
For stealing her away
from scotland yard?
I don't know.
Politics here are different.
And you can see she doesn't pull punches.
6 murders and he's finally
communicating with us.
What's that?
That's a tarot card.
Death.
Isn't that a little on the nose,
Even for a psycho?
So we think this guy's into spiritual garbage?
If he is, \he certainly doesn't know tarot.
The death card doesn't
actually signify physical death.
It's more of a transformation
from one place to another--
A job promotion
or a marriage.
So if he's not telling us
he's into fortune-Telling,
What's with the card?
The d.C. Sniper left the exact same card
At one of his scenes.
So this unsub must see himself in that role.
He's thriving off creating a panic.
More important,
he studies other cases.
He's telling us...
He knows we're here.
What have we got?
The latest shooting.
This was the previous murder.
Ok, do you see anything weird here?
He sprints off in one
and walks calmly in the other.
It's two entirely different demeanors.
6 kills in,
his behavior should be set.
Look at this.
Garcia, are you still there?
Would i ever leave you?
Ok, check it out.
I did a digital perspective analysis rendering
On the shootings where we have footage.
Now, the first two are inconclusive,
But the last two i found something
tres weird.
Your calm walking type,
He is about 6'1".
But your sprinter,
He's like 5'9",
5'10", tops.
We've got more than one unsub.
So, we have more than one unsub.
What does that tell us?
Most teams stick together.
Uh, ng and lake,
The krays.
Bittaker and norris.
They don't usually kill separately.
Could be some kind of gang initiation.
Gangs will kill you if they encroach
on your territory,
Not random people all over the city.
I'll coordinate with the gang taskforce,
Make sure we have an overview
by morning.
Do you think we have enough
for a working profile?
Broad strokes.
Dave, you and reid talk to the agents here.
Morgan and prentiss, brief the police
when each shift comes on duty tomorrow.
I think we should get out on the streets.
I brought you here to create a profile.
Which we can give in the morning,
And then they can share it
with the afternoon shift.
We've allocated every extra man we have.
This is new york city.
It's not like a few more people
is going to blanket the city.
I understand it's a long shot,
But these guys, they hit at mid-Day.
We could target ingress and egress
to particular neighborhoods.
Position us near express stops--
- 14th, 42nd, 59th--
- Morgan,
It's not your call.
I'd like to join you in the profile
If that's not stepping on your toes.
No problem.
Let's see it again.
Look at this.
Late edition doesn't miss a beat.
Jj.
Will.
Took a shot and flew to d.C.,
But that didn't work out.
I figured a train ride to new york
was only a few more hours.
Detective.
I'm sorry for showing up like this.
I know you're working.
But, um...
I can't stand you being on this case
And me not being there.
Not with what's going on.
Is there a problem?
I'm pregnant.
Oh my god, jj,
Congratulations!
I've asked jj to marry me.
Will.
We're working out some kinks.
We'll give you both some privacy.
Hotch
Jj, you could have told me.
I know.
I understand if you need to take some time.
No, i want to be here.
Okay.
???
Are you crazy?
I told you i couldn't get any personal time.
Come back to dc with me tomorrow.
You're not serious.
They know now.
They'd understand.
Will, we're covering a case
With six murders.
Exactly.
Your job's too dangerous now.
Yeah, exactly like yours.
Are you going to give up your shield?
Look, i love the gesture,
And i love the romance,
But we're both going to be parents, will.
Neither one of us has, exactly a typical job.
The first thing a cop does when she gets pregnant,
Is she takes herself out of the field.
Okay, you know what?
We only have until 7,
So can we just argue about names and cribs?
Only if you let me win.
Not a chance.
Okay, let's start with what we know.
For these unsubs, it's not personal.
It's not about sex, it's not about greed.
Which is why we think there's
something bigger at play here.
This isn't random.
There has to be a motive.
Now our first theory is that we are dealing with a team.
In the case of the d.C.Snipers,
There was actually one intended victim.
John mohamed wanted to kill his ex-Wife,
But he knew if he did,
He'd be the crime suspect.
So he created a spree in order to
mask his primary motivation.
What if the deaths got ott their scenes.
Just like this unsub.
We believe our unsubs have studyed that case.
They are opening a line of communication.
Hold on.
So now we have these guys playing games
Just because you are here.
We are just saying the unsubs are sophisticated enough
To study other crimes.
That doesn't answer the question.
Joe, easy.
Hear them out.
Hey, i got request for gun permits up 200% in my precinct.
This whole city is about to go up,
We all need to deal with that.
Hey, listen, you're right.
If the card was left because of us
Then yes, they are playing games.
But what that tells us is
At least one of them has some intelligence.
And like i said, they know about other cases.
He's also studyed the placement
of the surveillance systems
Well enough to avoid detection.
Most teams have a dominant and sub missive member.
Because of the relative intelligence of these unsubs
And the fact that they stick o a set time patternt ,
We believe at least one of them has a steady job.
We've asked the police to canvas their precincts.
Check businesses that open and close around the time of the shootings.
We're hoping someone will be able to identify a father/son
Or co-Workers that fit the dominant sub missive profile.
And what's the other theory?
It's less likely, but it could be some sort of gang i initiation.
We've asked the police to put every available undercover
On the streets.
These are all own gang members in manhattan.
Most of them are out of china town and clinton.
We'd like you to study these
And keep an eye out for anyone who looks suspicious.
Those i.D. Numbers stay behind
when the agents are finished,
I'll give you your assignments.
Like we said, we think there's something big art play here.
Talk to the people on your beats.
Save sparks and pray this thing ain't random.
Cameras aren't designed to prevent crime.
Supposed to help us catch the perp after the fact.
I got one.
Is there anyone nearby?
Negative.
This is a surveillance command centre.
We have a possible murder suspect
At the subway platform on 59th and lex.
Okay.
Hotchner.
It looked like it could be one of our guys.
What's going on?
We have eyes on one of them.
He is on the 59th and lex.
We could have been right there.
He's got a gun.
Oh my god.
He shot her.
Where the hell are the police?
This is kate joyner with the fbi.
We have a murder suspect
Subway platform 59 and this lex.
He is getting away.
Garcia. Can you get eyes on him aboveground?
He's heading west on 59th street.
If he makes it to the park,
We've lost him.
We've lost the visual.
Are the police on the scene?
Negative.
We could have had that guy.
Even if we were on that platform,
Odds are he wouldhave known he was isolated.
Maybe, but it was worth
taking a shot.
We had every available man
on the streets.
And i suggested to you that
you use this team.
Second guessing doesn't do us any good.
Hotch, how am i supposed to look
these cops in the eye
And tell them we are here to help them?
We are here to present a profile.
Let's we need to do.
I said put us in express stops.
14th, 42nd, 59th
- That's exactly where they hit.
- It's not your place
To have
this discussion.
My place?
You need to back off.
We got seven bodies, man.
Which is exactly why we need to stay focused.
Focused?
From where i'm standing, all you're focus is on her.
Take a walk, now.
I know.
I was out of line.
You get too emotionaly involved sometimes.
I know the feeling.
I just felt like hotch was taking her side.
There are no sides here.
I know.
The word is, they have an
eye on you
If jayner gets canned.
People talk.
If she were to get fired,
It would be because we didn't
solve this case.
Rossi, i hope you are not saying
You think i want her to fail.
Of course not.
I've never seen you push a
superior like that before.
So would you take the job?
I don't know.
It might be nice to finally be
the one making the calls.
And dealing with the
politics of running a field office?
That doesn't seem like you.
It wears people out, man.
Look at gideon.
That man was the best,
And in the end, he simply ran away.
I mean hotc hflt hasn't even
thought about cracking a smile in over a year.
That man has to take a personal day
Just so he can have a conversation with his own kid.
What about you?
How many times you been married?
I get it.
But i'll make you a deal.
If i think you're losing it,
I'll pull you out myself.
But right now,
I see someone
who wants to get back on the job.
Or is there another reason
Why you haven't even touched that beer?
Listen, um, about before.
You spoke your mind.
I respect that.
Jj reid and printess are at the crime scene
with the detectives.
It's the first time they've killed
two days in a row.
They are speeding up.
Your analyst went over
the latest footage.
This is a different shooter
from the last two.
There's three of them now?
Who the hell are these guys?
I want you all out on the
street tomorrow.
What are we missing?
When we first saw this case,
What did it remind us of?
Sam.
Same kind of unsung.
Random shootings.
Not need-Driven,
No sexual component.
Expect that berkowitz admitted that
he returns to the crimes scenes
Days later to masturbate.
Exactly.
So you're thinking
if the dominant unsub
has a similar m.O...
We get garcia to study
the footage and
We see if the same person keeps returning to the crime scene
In the days following the shootings.
All we've been looking at right now
Are the immediate aftermath of the crimes.
Worth a shot.
We'll hit the street tomorrow.
Dave will you grab reid and go over the profile
And make sure we didn't leave anything out?
Thanks.
Okay, people, talk to me.
Roll call, 59th street.
Check.
Carol square.
Chamber street.
Check.
72nd street.
Detectives.
Son of sam this case still pisses you off
Like it was yesterday.
Yeah, does.
There've been a lot of killers in the city.
Why him?
He was laughing at us,
and we couldn't catch him.
The only way we grabbed him
was through a parking ticket.
What are you thinking?
He hasn't contacted us again.
So-.
This doesn't fit.
These unsubs are organized.
They use presurveillance.
They strike in the heart of the day,
Yet they haven't done anything to seek out media attention.
And then this.
You said it was to tell you
they knew you were here.
We profiled opening a line of communication to create panic.
But if that was the case, his correspondence should escalate.
After they left their death card mohamed
And- Demanded an atm card a million dollars
And a bank account to taunt police.
Berko wits wrote letters about random hits in the city
Sdrooik himself as a monster.
They are more disciplined.
The fact they haven't contacted the press,
Tells me that this was private.
It's only for us.
So what does that mean?
They are wrapping up to something.
And they wanttous know that
they are watching us.
You saw both these traits
completely out of context,
What would be the first
profile to pop into your head?
Who do we have out on the streets?
Talk.
Garcia ,do you have eyes on
everyone on the team?
I can get them.
So we are on the cover,
Maybe we should, you know, act like a couple.
Are you still working this
tired sexual tension angle?
I don't know, you're the fortune teller,
you tell me.
You want to know what
profiling is, really?
Why do i have a feeling i'm
going to hear no matter what i say.
It's just noticing behaviour.
I'm about to hear about mine.
Is that the deal?
Okay.
When we first met, when your partner was sarcastic
And said yes, ma'am, you instinctively reached for your detective shield
As if you were protecting it.
That tells me you don't like
him disrespecting the chain of command,
But you are also loyal,
So you didn't say something to him.
I'd say you were military.
Probably an officer.
Public and sensor in public, right?
You're right-Handed,
But you have two different colour pen
marks on your left hand.
I guess you have a toddler at home
Just learning how to draw.
You don't wear a ring.
And you were quick to flirt with me.
So, you're happy to let people
think you are a player,
But if i took you up on it,
You would run for the hills.
Because you love your wife,
And you would never actually cheat on her.
You might just solve this case yet.
Okay. This is not good.
Why not?
I'm doing what you asked.
I'm looking at the footage to see
If i see the same person coming back to the crime scene
In the days after the shooting.
Right.
So i find the camera with
the widest angle on the scene.
So you have to sift
through hundreds.
Exactly. But-.
Someone's hacked in.
- Garcia.
- I'm on it.I'm on it
16 and this broadway,
he's running east on 16th.
He's headed our way.
Move, move!
Get out of the way!
Cooper?
Garcia!
We've got an officer down,
16th west of union square.
Let me see.
Okay, you're going to be okay.
Garcia, can you see us?
We have an officer down.
Stay with me.
It's going to be okay.
Cooper, stay with me
Are you okay?
Is he going to make it?
I don't know, he lost a lot of blood.
He's not going to live to
tell us anything.
Any o.D. On him?
Nothing.
This is not good.
I shouldn't have had to shoot him.
Emily, he shot a cop.
You did what you had to do.
No, not that.
I mean, he was ahead of us.
He would have gotten away,
But he stoped and waited.
So he felt trapped, figured
he'd shoot his way out?
I don't know.
Tell me about his behaviour.
Was he acting panicked?
Was he winded?
His hands were steady.
His eyes were dead calm.
I mean these guys have been
hyper individual lent,
Organized.
They do presurveillance what are the odds
They would shoot somebody two blocks
From where me and coop standing?
You think he deliberately shot someone
Where he could see cops?
What if he did?
What if they chose this spot
Because we were here.
What are you thinking?
He had no i.D. On him.
He waited until we caught up to him.
He was strangely calm.
It's almost like
suicide by cop.
Why?
Why would he do that?
I don't know.
Maybe to make us think
everything was finished.
We need to walk back
through this profile.
We think we might have a serious problem.
What is it?
We have multiple unsubs.
They are disciplined.
They are using cops and surveillance.
They know the fbi movements.
There's a hierarchy.
What does that usually equal?
Terrorism.
So how does this work?
The murderer simulate a bombing.
In order to gauge police response time.
Which case they know when
to bring in a second bomb.
First round of civilians
Followed by a second wave of
emergency responders.
It's crazy but ingenious.
They get a practice run and if someone catchs a shooter
They have a murderer that won't compromise.
It's lo-Fi.
Smartest way to plan for a terrorist event.
Creating panic ensures
That they see the most urgent
response time short of a bombing.
So there's been seven
different shooters?
Having followers
do the shootings would ensure
They're willing to kill or be killed for the cause.
Fits the profile.
There is something larger at play.
It simulates a gang i initiation.
Especially if they are home
grown they had a chance to prove themselves.
I think they are targeting
points of entry.
All the murders are taking
place near a bridge or tunnel.
Holland tunnel, midtown
tunnel manhattan bridge.
If bombs went off emergency response
would shut down
Any ability to get in or out of this city.
It would be like people are
trapped on the island.
Keep in mind still a theory
just like any profile.
Talktous garcia.
We got a problem.
I went through and checked off
4468 cameras.
They've hacked into the
surveillance system.
They have footage of every crime scene
They've been watching since the beginning.
How could we not have caught that?
They were smart not system wide
Had to check each camera individually.
This is from every crime scene?
I'm afraid so.
They hacked into one camera at every scene.
Thanks, garcia.
So much for theory.
We need to hit the ground running.
I'm going to head to the hospital
I'll check on cooper
and brief detective brustin.
Good. Dave, will you
go talk to the commissioner,
And morgan you brief online security?
Jj and i will talk to
the port authority police.
Kate and i will go talk to the mayor
and we'll meet back here as soon as possible.
One advantage
that we have right now
Is they don't we know they're watching.
Agent jareau.
Thank you.
Will?
He's going home to new orleans tonight.
You okay?
He doesn't want to be in the way.
He's quitting his job?
Do you need everyone in the field?
Reid, you can go brief port
authority police by yourself.
Jj you run point from the office.
Why don't you go back to the hotel,
Tell will what's going on then get back in line.
Yes, sir.
And jj,
Congratulations.
How's cooper doing?
He's still in surgery.
It doesn't look good.
We think we know what this is about.
-=±¾¼¾םך=-
¸ננ»ףנהד ·חףךם¬ננ
united we're strong!
»¶ף­²מףכדא¾חיחחרךגפצב×÷ןעוגפ »מ¶¯
¾לו»מ¶¯ןךחיחכ²מ¼זזאדנ¹שםר