Previously on criminal minds...
he came after me. He came to my home.
Sarah's dead. He butchered her.
Your team is in trouble.
Did you fly a disturbed college student to meet
with a man you believed to be a serial killer?
It was my decision.
Give me your badge.
You're suspended for 2 weeks
pending an investigation.
There's no satisfactory
explanation what I've done.
I just don't understand
it any of it anymore.
reid?
What are you doing here?
Gideon didn't answer his phone.
I called him twice.
Have you been here all night?
We were supposed to play chess.
Here?
Uh,he hasn't been back to
his apartment since,um...
right.
I need to brief the team,so...
is hotch here?
Uh,he's not due for a half hour.
- Thanks,honey.
- Yeah.
Are you sure you're ok?
Yeah,I'm fine.
You're doing the right thing.
I know.
Getting suspended was
a blessing in disguise.
We deserve a normal life.
- I love you.
- I love you,too.
What,no hotch,now no gideon?
No,not yet.
These guys have been out 2 weeks.
You'd think the least they
could do is be on time.
Yeah,'cause you're never late.
So where's prentiss?
Her phone keeps going
straight to voicemail.
Well,this room just keeps getting
smaller and smaller,doesn't it?
Should we wait 15 minutes?
We can just brief them on the plane.
Right now the police taskforce
in milwaukee needs our help.
They've had 4 murders over the past 3 weeks,and in
addition,another woman has been missing the last 2 days.
They've all the women are in
their 30s,married with children.
Any connection between these victims?
Just that they've all been
abducted from the area of wauwatosa,
all from very public
places,but there's no witnesses.
How are we even certain
it's the same killer?
Well,for starters...
all of the bodies have been
dumped in the city's third ward.
And there's this.
Is that what I think it is?
All the hearts have been
cut from their bodies.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Criminal Minds
Season03 Episode02 In Birth and Death
George washington said,let your heart feel
for the affliction and distress of everyone.
Hey,am I glad to see you.
Where you headed?
Milwaukee. Looks like another one.
I'll catch you up on the flight.
I'm meeting with the section chief.
Ok,so I'll wait.
I'm just glad you're back.
Trust me when I tell you things have
been a little bit shaky around here.
Morgan,I'm requesting a transfer.
Is that a joke?
No,it's not a joke.
Strauss has suspended me once
already. The writing's on the wall.
Hotch,we both know that
suspension was bogus.
You'll get a new unit chief.
What if we don't want a new unit chief?
Well,maybe the next one won't
be such a drill sergeant.
Look,man,are you a
pain in my ass? Yes,sir.
But wanting to hang out with you and needing you
to lead this team are two very different things.
It's been a privilege.
I was hoping you'd do the right thing.
Have you given any thought to
what department you'll request?
I was under the impression that if I left
the B.A.U. I'd have my choice of posts.
Well,I'll consider it after I
fully complete my investigation.
You were a prosecutor.
What about heading up a
white collar crime taskforce?
That'll get you home at
nights at a reasonable hour.
Sorry to interrupt.
Sir,I've decided to resign from
the fbi,effective immediately.
I don't understand.
I'm taking a foreign service exam.
With my connections,I stand a good
chance of landing in the state department.
Prentiss,I think that's a mistake.
Well,don't try to talk me out of it.
Garcia saw my name on the
list and she already tried.
If she can't talk someone out
of doing something,no one can.
Sorry for the interruption.
But,sir,it's good to see you back.
The team needs you. Ma'am.
I'll be overseeing this case
until I can assign a replacement.
You don't have any field experience.
My job is to protect the bureau.
If I have to hold the team's
hand for one case,so be it.
Ma'am,in order to function
effectively,this team needs stability.
The B.A.U. Has some very talented
people and they're bureau assets.
And I believe it's time that they were
out from underneath you and jason gideon.
You know,from this
angle,she almost looks human.
Has anyone talked to emily yet?
She was gone before I heard the news.
I told you,reid,now we're down
2 agents and gideon's M.I.A.
Doesn't strauss
ever do any--
correct me if I'm wrong,
but I believe it's protocol to brief
everyone before we arrive at the crime scene.
Yes,ma'am.
This unsub is abducting women from
very public places,with no witnesses.
He holds them 48 hours,with
no sexual assault,
and then he dumps their bodies with
their hearts carved out of their chests.
There's an obvious dichotomy in the skill
the unsub exhibits in abducting these women
and the fact that he cuts
their hearts out so crudely.
We're probably looking at
someone in a psychotic break.
Could be a butcher. Might be a hunter.
Somebody who's very comfortable
being around blood,but as you can see,
he obviously doesn't have
the skills of a surgeon.
So do we have a working theory?
Sure we do.
Somebody really doesn't like women.
Is it appropriate to ask whether
I could talk you out of it?
Heard you got a bigger office.
A swanky new map and everything.
It's the milwaukee file.
J.J.Wanted me to give it to you.
I'm not working it.
I'm just following orders.
They found a new body this morning.
The others are headed
straight to the scene.
You the fbi?
Derek morgan.
Spencer reid,jennifer
jareau,and section chief strauss.
Vic wolynski,milwaukee pd.
You worked the jeffrey dahmer case.
16 years ago.I've studied it.
And you remember my name?
He remembers everything.
'S it what he does.
What can you tell us?
Uh,local merchant noticed
her a few hours ago.
Uh,but considering he didn't see
her when he first came to work,uh,
we figure she was dumped
there between 7:50 and 8:05.
Same window as the others.
All the bodies were
found in this area,right?
Uh,wauwatosa is an upper-middle-class
suburb approximately 15 minutes from here.
All the women were abducted
from there in the afternoon
and turned up here in
the morning 2 days later.
All this foot traffic
and no one saw anything.
Well,he,up,wraps the bodies,uh,loosely
so they're not immediately recognizable.
Eventually the,uh,wrapping comes oNPe
my guess is he,uh,has a van or
a truck,something he can back up
so he's shielded when he makes the drop.
No prints on whatever he wraps them in?
There have been traces
of paint and wood stain,
but most of it's just common stuff
you'd get at any hardware store.
He's trying to demean
them,putting them out like trash.
This guy might work or live around here.
Gets off on the reaction
to his... handiwork.
What can you tell us about the victim?
She was taken from a supermarket.
Her husband says that most days she would
have been picking up her son at school,
but he was spending the
afternoon at a friend'S.
- This is your fifth victim,right?
- Yes.
You should have called us sooner.
I thought we had a handle on it.
- Apparently not.
- Ma'am.
Excuse me,sir.
We need to work with these detectives.
I'm sorry?
We don't generally criticize them.
It just really doesn't get us anything.
Are you saying it wouldn't be
helpful if he had contacted us sooner?
Well,of course.
- It's always,you know,the sooner the better.
- Right.
And agent jareau...
don't question me again.
Is jack still napping?
I thought this was over.
It is. I'm just curious.
Hello?
What did the section chief say?
She suggested that I transfer to
a white collar crime taskforce.
Would you have to travel?
No,I'd have a 9:00 to 5:00 life.
Then it's a no-brainer.
- Hey.
- How's it going?
Well,strauss just offended the lead detective
45 seconds into her first crime scene.
I'm not surprised.
This isn't about to
get any better,is it?
I doubt it.
Morgan,listen,I've been
looking at the file.
Milwaukee schools start at
8:10 and they get out at 3:10.
Every abduction has taken place within
15 minutes of school getting out.
And each body was dumped within
15 minutes of the first bell.
We could easily be looking at somebody
who works in the school system.
Ok. Thanks,man.
Any idea how's he's getting control of these
women? Is he blitzing them or coercing them?
- So far we're coming up blank.
- Ok.
Keep me posted.
You scared me.
I'm looking for my dad.
- Are you lost?
- I'm not lost.
I'm just not sure where I am.
Ok. Maybe I can help you?
Are you sure this is what your dad said?
He said if anything happened,to meet him on
the side because it wouldn't be so crowded.
Hey.Hey.
Hey,there you are.
Hey,guy,I was worried.
- Hi.
I'm sorry I tricked
you. My dad's just shy.
I want you to smile and ask if you can come home
with us,or I'm gonna gut the boy like a deer.
Would you mind if I came home with you?
I'd like that.
Well,then.
hey. What do we know?
Woman's name is claire thompson.
Husband tried to reach
her on the cell phone.
When she didn't pick up,he
drove to the department store.
Car's in the parking
lot,but she's not inside.
- Is that the husband?
- Yeah.
J.J.,Take strauss with you.
- I had the department store uplink the security footage to your analyst in quantico.
- perfect
My desk is over here.
Garcia,baby girl,please tell
me something I want to hear.
You're a statuesque god of
sculpted chocolate thunder.
How about something
I don't already know?
I have a sweet tooth?
Did you located the missing
girl on the security footage?
On it. It's coming
your way in 5,4,3,2...
I got it.
Keep me on speaker,will you?
She doesn't seem to
be on anyone's radar.
Look. Who's the kid?
Does claire thompson have a son?
No. 2-year-old
daughter.
It looks like the kid's lost.
- Garcia,this all you got?
- That's it.
Theyd urne tdown a hallway without
no security camera and we lose them.
I'll get a list of missing kids,see if we
can make out a resemblance to any of them.
- Oh,damn.
- What?
Something hotch said.
All the abductions and disposals
have been timed around school.
We thought the unsub
might work in the system.
What if this guy's actually using
his own son to lure his victims?
Detective wolynski told us you're
trying to single out trucks and vans.
That's smart.
The unsub is dumping his vic msti in the
business district,so I'd agree with you--
he's probably not driving
something that would stand out.
He may even have some type of company
logo on the side of his vehicle as well.
We know that he abducts
the women in wauwatosa
and dumps their bodies
somewhere in the third ward.
Most unsubs keep their area of
control-- where they kill their victims--
triangulated between the two points.
Which means that the unsub probably
lives in wauwatosa or the third ward.
Somewhere in that area.
And the people who live
there know the unsub.
There's no sexual
component to these crimes,
which means it's more about
the unsub making a point.
He's cutting their hearts out.
It might just be that this is the sickest way
the unsub knows to disfigure the women and...
throw them out like trash.
'T canwe really know.
The two most important
questions to ask ourselves are:
What is this guy doing with
these women for 48 hours?
And why is he willing to use
his own son to abduct them?
And if he is truly using his own son,then it's likely
that he has what we call borderline personality disorder.
Now,borderlines-- they think that all
relationships revolve entirely around them.
When they set their mind to
something,absolute-- there is no gray area.
It would also manifest in a way atth would
be visible to people around the unsub.
Intense bouts of anger and
depression,problems drinking.
He aould wlso be highly
sensitive to rejection.
And one last thing.
It is not easy to crack
clean into breastbone.
You're dealing with a guy who works with
his hands and he's used to hard labor.
At the very least,he's
not afraid to get dirty.
Now,I'm gonna take that out of your
mouth and you're gonna be really quiet.
Like a doll. Ok?
Oh,that's good.
Let's go on upstairs.
And you're gonna be
really,really nice to the boy.
Not like the little
bitch we all know you are.
You understand?
Say it!
I understand.
Lovely.
- Haley?Ok,mac and cheese.
- Got it
- Here you go.Good boy.
- Hello
- Mac and cheese.
- Ah,it's the best.
- It's morgan.
- Thanks.
Yeah,what's up?
You know I wouldn't be calling
you unless I was desperate.
Still no gideon?
No,not a word.
Reid's starting to worry about him.
We really need you out here,man.
Morgan,I've already put in for
the transfer. It's a done deal.
No,you didn'T. Not yet,anyway.
It's not in the system,hotch,not yet.
Come on. You know this case.
You could pitch in on just this one.
We think he might be using his
own kid to lure these women,man.
He just picked up another one.
- Hotch.
- I got to think.
What are you doing?
- Multiplication.
- That's hard.
- It's extra credit.
The rest of the class is
still on long division.
Maybe I could help you.
- It's ok.
- I'm really good at math.
The boy...
Has got to learn to
do things by himself.
No,of course.
But you can make me a sandwich.
- Ok.
- Come on.
Let's go clean up your room.
Help!
What the hell are you doing?
Keep your voice down.
Gideon didn't show in
milwaukee and the team needs me.
I don't believe this.
Don't worry,it won't affect my transfer.
I've been working on an existing case.
You're not working on this case.
I can't just switch
off my loyalty,haley.
They suspended you for 2 weeks.
Who are you being loyal to?
The team needs me.
No,they need gideon.
Do you know what this guy's doing to
women in milwaukee? I don't want to know.
He's using his son to lure them,he's holding
them,and then he's cutting their hearts out.
Aaron,stop!
Don't make me the monster here.
I feel sick about these women,but when
this case is over,there will be another one.
And another one and another one.
It is never going to stop.
This is who I am.
No...
this is what you do.
I'm trying to do the
right thing,here and there,
and I would really
appreciate a little support.
that's right.
'Cause you always need to be the hero.
- Don't give me that.
- No.
Obviously a happy life
isn't enough for you.
- ******
- I'll be back...
as soon as this case is over.
Yeah,well,make sure you give
your son a kiss before you leave.
can I come in?
the team needs us. They're
working on a case in milwaukee.
Gideon hasn't shown up,and don't tell
me you quit or I put in for a transfer.
You put in for a transfer?
They're both still hung up in the system,so technically
we're in dereliction of duty by not being there.
I'm sorry,I can't go.
Right. Sorry I barged in.
Wait. Wait.Can
I ask--
why are you really here?
I told you.
I think strauss came to you
and asked for dirt on me.
Why would she do that?
I think if you have your eyes
on top leadership at the fbi,
you want to know who
might stand in your way.
And... what could i have told her?
That one of my agents might have
murdered a suspect in cold blood.
Or another might have a serious
drug problem which I didn't report,
and if strauss had any
evidence,my career would be over.
I think she put you on our team
and expected something in return.
And to your credit,you quit.
Rather than whisper in her ear.
I told you.
I hate politics.
Come to milwaukee.
I'll make you a deal.
If your ready bag isn't
here,packed,I won't bug you anymore.
If it is,I want you on that
plane with me. One more case.
I already turned in my badge and my gun.
That's just hardware.
I have triple patrol in the area and I've
got every available unit recanvassing.
It's tough knowing they're out
there and we're still a step behind.
You know,it used to be a running joke that
if you told people you were from milwaukee,
all they wanted to talk
about was happy days reruns.
And then dahmer happens and they ask
you about it as if it's the same thing.
As if it's entertainment.
But I was in that apartment.
Gideon,one of our bosses,says that there
are things that attach to you that...
you can never wash off.
All righ it,t-- is it possible
we're looking at this the wrong way?
What do you mean?
Well,we're trying to
zero in on the unsub.
Now,you guys tell me,but...
if he really is using his son,wouldn't the
trauma manifest more clearly on the boy?
Can your analyst get a list of all the
children in the area that we're targeting?
Garcia can get you whatever you want.
Talk dirty to me.
I--
This is section chief erin strauss.
Ma'am,I think it goes without saying that
I was expecting it to be someone else.
I need a list of every grade school
in the third ward and wauwatosa.
Yes,ma'am.
the third ward has one
public grade school,
but there appears to be 4 private
schools that draw from that area.
And wauwatosa?
That would be 9,ma'am.
- And how many students?
- 3200
Can you also get me a list
of every guidance counselor
that deals directly with the
student body in that area?
Certainly,ma'am.
And again,I'd like to a...
You need to present these counselors
with a profile of a troubled kid.
The boy we're looking for is
possibly from a single-parent home.
He's sullen and withdrawn.
He may have been caught stealing
things from his female teachers.
He's more than likely clinging to maternal
figures in inappropriate settings--
hugging the female bus
driver,the woman in the lunchroom.
His classmates might notice this
inappropriate behavior and tease him,
which makes the boy incredibly angry.
- That many.
- I'm afraid so.
Well,thank you.
- How was school?
- Ok.
It was just ok?
- Is the lady still at home?
- Yeah.
- Is she gonna leave?
- I don't know.
I don't want her to.
Sometimes things
happen. Grown-up things.
- I don't want this
one to go. - But they--
they all leave.Ok?
- Maybe they all leave because of you.
- What?
I know you're old enough
to understand this.
I will not always be around!
They all leave. All of them.
They leave,they leave,they
leave. Do you understand me?
It's all right.
It's ok,all right?
I'm just trying to teach you something.
All right,the boy doesn't look
like he could be any older than 7.
Let's work youngest to oldest.
Start with the worbe sthavior.
Get the names of the
parents,send them over to garcia.
She can cross-check
for criminal records.
This guy's dumping bodies between
7:30 and 8:00. That gives us...
a little over 12 hours
to make something hit.
- Let's get it done.
- Look who's here.
Hey. Where do we start?
How fast can you get us up to speed?
How fast can you sit down?
We're only here to help.
We'll deal with this later.
It's impossible. There's too many.
Keep looking,reid.
We still have an hour.
Thank you,by the way,for giving
garcia that file to give to me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I didn't see garcia before I left.
- Did you sleep well?
- Yeah.
Do you mind if I have some cereal?
I guess not.
He's gonna kill you,you know.
Are you all right?
I st--I stepped
on her hair.
If you need a second,take a
second. This is what it is.
Just don't let the
public see you break down.
This is a different area from
the other dump sites,isn't it?
Reid: He's getting smart.
He knows where all of our manpower
will be so he's changing locations.
How long before he changes
when and where he abducts them?
He does that,we're back at zero.
Claire?
No,no,no,no. We gotta
keep him out of here.
Morgan says you're worried about gideon.
I keep on calling
him,he doesn't call back.
He's probably at his cabin.
That's where he goes when he...
needs to get away.
- Reid,I need your head in this.
- I know.
So what's around the dump site?
Here's the old printing press of
quad graphics,and the paving yard,
and then the concrete factory
where we found the body.
None of them visible from the highway.
You don't end up there by accident.
So we go back to the schools,we
eliminate the third ward,
and we target problem kids whose fathers have
held blue-collar jobs over the last 10 years.
- What if he's not a problem kid?
- What?
Forget it. It's off
the textbook profile.
What is it,reid?
Sometimes when a parent is unstable,especially
if the other one's out of the picture,
you'll do anything to
be the perfect child.
Like help your father abduct women?
They're never late for school.
Even with the abductions,the
disposal of the bodies,
it's always timed perfectly so
the kid will be on time to school.
I don't think the killer would
care. I think the kid would.
Fbi. Technical analyst
penelope garcia speaking.
Garcia,I need a list of parents
from the wauwatosa school district,
eliminating any two-parent households
or any fathers holding white collar
jobs that aren't labor management.
You'll see it flying over
the transom momentarily.
And one more thing-- the glitches in
the transfers and resignations stop now.
Uh--
yes,sir.
- And,garcia...
- yes?
Thank you.
He's a kid that's a model student.
Not just straight as,though.
It's someone who tries to please in a way that
the other teachers have probably talked about.
Inventing extra-credit projects,
volunteering to skip recess to help
clean the classroom,stuff like that.
David smith.
Do you know his father?
Oh,it's such a sad story.
The teachers all talk about it.
He was diagnosed with an inoperable tumor 6
months ago,and his wife left the two of them.
She just left?
Yeah. I don't know what's
gonna happen to david.
Thank you for driving me.
you know,I can't just leave you here.
I have to make sure your dad's home.
I know.
I can't imagine david's father
being someone you're looking for.
He's very involved.
He drops david off and
picks him up every day.
Do you happen to know
what kind of car he drives?
A van,maybe?
I can't say. Something big.
He makes hand-crafted furniture.
I know he does deliveries.
- Miss bennett.
- Just continue working.
We're looking for david smith.
You just missed him.
Do you know where he went?
He wasn't feeling well,so the nurse volunteered
to drive him home to help out david's father.
Thank you.
The boy's alone in the family room.
Where are your other agents?
Covering the other side.
They have an eye-line just in case
somebody tries to sneak out the back.
Is there any sign of
the nurse or the dad?
No.
Go ahead,you want to scream,scream.
Go ahead and scream!
- The school knows that I'm here!
- Yes,yes.
You dropped the boy off,I
thanked you,and then you left.
They'll find your car in the
parking lot of the mayfair mall.
I was trying to help your son.
So what are we doing here?
We call in S.W.A.T.,Secu trehe
perimeter,and wait for him to come out.
Ma'am,he's holding a woman inside.
We don't know that for certain.
We don't have probable cause.
She's right.
If he's got her,he waits 48 hours.
He's not gonna kill her yet.
He's changed the pattern of the dump
sites,and now he's changed how he abducts them.
Do we really want to gamble that he's
sticking to the rest of the model?
So let's pound on the door.
Maybe he'll panic.
But he could spook just
enough to kill her early.
Let me go in alone.
The boy's in the family room.
- He'll answer the door.
- No.
We need to get invited in that door.
He's looking for female
authority figures.
If he lets me in,I can signal as soon
as I see anything that gives us cause.
Technically,you're not even in the fbi.
All the better.
She's interfering with
a federal investigation.
Well,if I'm no longer in the fbi,then
you have no authority over me.
I'm just a civilian knocking
on a little boy's door.
- Prentiss.
- 3Q
- As soon as you have probable cause,give us a signal and get out of there.
- Ok.
Everybody knows what we need
to make this arrest legal.
hi.
Are you david?
Your dad asked me to come by.
He's busy.
Would it be ok if i came in and waited?
I guess.
Thank you.
My dad says it's unsafe to
leave your door unlocked.
Smart man.
Prentiss is in. We're waiting on her go.
So...
where is your dad?
He's working in there.
Is he alone
would it be ok if I just
let him know I was waiting?
He doesn't like me to go
down there when he's working.
Oh,no,you don't have to.
Um,I just gonna go and
see if he's to obusy.
And we can both be really
quiet,ok? Can you be quiet?
Who is this?
Where did she come from?
- She said she knew you.
- What?
She said she knew you.
- ****
- I can'T.
Take it.
It's ok.Just...
no.
Point it right here.
*******right thing
*********
Let's go!
Drop the weapon,son.
Give me the gun.
Here.
That's ok.
Do what they say.
Are you ok?
- Ah,I'll be fine.
- ******
You're dying,and this is what
you want to leave your son?
How's your head?
I'll live.
Is it weird I'm glad to be back?
I'll make sure it stays official.
- I'll be dead before I ever stand trial.
- Good.
You know,I never even told the
boy to bring me this last one.
How's she doing?
She's gonna be ok.
- You know,I can't officially approve of how this transpired,right?
- No.
The arrest was clean.
It would be a mistake
to break up this team.
None of you will ever move up the
chain of command. You know that.
Why would I ever want
to leave the B.A.U.
Hotch.
You mean that? You're
not gonna leave us?
I don't know. I gotta talk to haley.
haley?
Gideon?
Spencer,I knew it would be you who
came to the cabin to check on me.
I'm sorry the explanation
couldn't be better.
And I'm sorry it
doesn't make more sense.
But I've already told you,I just
don't understand any of it anymore.
you get enough to eat,honey?
Oh,yeah.
- You travelin'?
- Yeah
Where you headed?
Nowhere in particular.
How will you know when you get there?
That's a good question...
rose.
A very good question.
- Have a great day.
- You too
I guess I'm just looking for it again.
For the belief I had back in college.
The belief I had when I first met
sarah and it all seemed so right.
the belief in happy endings.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚