They said that storm
was coming,
And they weren't kidding.
oh...
How are we?
Well, you know, it's hard.
Just one foot
in front of the other.
Thanks.
It would have been
amy's birthday tomorrow.
Paul?
Hmm.
He's been a rock.
But you know how he is.
His glass is always full.
I think he's home.
Well, the kids are with
grandma tonight.
We have a night off.
Yeah.
God, we need it.
Thank you.
I appreciate the call, kate.
You know, I... I should go.
Yeah, ok.
Bye.
Paul?
Paul, i think the lightning
blew out the house.
Paul.
Honey? Paul?
Paul?
Paul.
Honey?
Paul, open the door.
Unlock the door!
Paul!
Aah...
Oh, my god!
Agent jennifer jareau?
A friend of mine
gave me your number,
Said you might be able
to help.
Ronnie baleman,
pittsburgh p.D.
There's something
going on in my town.
Something's not right.
Got a case.
So, you've either decided
we're taking the case
Or this bag is headed
for another destination?
I need a favor.
Of course.
I need some personal time,
no more than a day.
Take all the time
you need.
I need to talk to jack.
I've lost her,
but i'm not gonna lose him.
I need to try to...
Tell him what's going on.
I don't know how much
he's going to
understand, but...
All he needs to understand...
Is that you love him.
I'll join you when i can.
3 months ago a fire
in the shadyside rec center
Killed 14 children.
I remember that.
What does that
have to do with us?
Well, over the past
3 months there's been
5 suicides.
All of them lost a child
in the fire.
The last one
was paul baleman.
He was found electrocuted
in his bathtub yesterday.
I received a request
for our help.
Why do they need our help?
They're suicides.
All of the suicides
were within 2 weeks
of each other.
It could be
some kind of pattern.
Detective ronnie baleman,
pittsburgh, p.D.
Thinks that something's
going on.
Well, of course he does.
Why do you say that?
He's related
to that man, right?
His brother.
A cop who doesn't
believe his brother
committed suicide.
Come on, next case.
Now, wait a second.
5 suicides
in the same neighborhood
Within months?
That's a serious spike.
Suicides don't spike
after a tragedy.
Quite the opposite,
actually.
Following world war i and ii,
right after kennedy was shot,
And following 9/11,
Suicides plummeted.
Within a society,
external threats
Usually create group
integrations.
People come together.
So if there's
reason for doubt,
Which there obviously is,
Don't those families
left behind
Have a right to know?
Yes, they do.
Ok, sure,
they deserve to know,
But let somebody else
tell them,
like social services.
Contact detective baleman.
Let him know we're coming.
Http://www.Ragbear.Com
Rossi: "there is no refuge
from confession but suicide,
And suicide is confession."
Daniel webster.
Hotch would never
have taken this case.
And i say case
in the loosest sense.
We'll follow the facts
as they are without bias.
Isn't that what we do?
What facts, rossi?
Look at us.
We don't have a single file.
Ok, let me help you out.
Jump right in anytime.
Fact one...
There are no files,
So it seems no case.
But what if there is?
One fire, 14 deaths,
5 suicides.
All the suicides
Are connected
to the original fire.
And all exactly 2 weeks apart.
Come on, derek,
you can't tell me
That doesn't feel
a lot like a pattern.
Prentiss:
and a timeline.
Right?
A lot of people lost
their kids in that fire.
That's a whole
world of grief,
And for a few...
Suicide's their only way out.
Or someone decided it was.
And made it look this way?
What if they have?
Then we're looking for
one very smart unsub.
Who targets people
in grief.
And that would
make them what?
Someone who thinks
They're putting them
out of their misery.
An angel of death.
Agent jareau?
Hi. I'm detective
ronnie baleman.
Hi. This is ssa rossi,
Ssas morgan, prentiss,
and dr. Reid.
Thank you, all of you,
for coming.
Well, your colleagues don't
look all that happy to see us.
They didn't just
lose a brother.
I'd like to get started
on all the files.
We're gonna build what we
call psychological autopsies
To determine whether
the victims killed themselves.
Everything's
in those boxes.
We'd also like to take a look
at your brother's house.
I'll take you there.
I think it's better
if you stay here.
It's my case.
I brought you here.
Technically,
there is no case.
If there was,
you wouldn't be on it.
We need to profile
the scene without bias.
I could use your help
with these files.
It looks like
there's quite a few.
My brother kept a journal.
I found this on the desk
in his bedroom.
Read the last page.
They're not the words
of a suicidal man.
You seem pretty sure
that an unsub exists.
So are you.
You're here,
aren't you?
He wasn't on
antidepressants.
He wasn't depressed.
Do you mind if my colleagues
take a look upstairs?
Ronnie kept it
exactly as it was
Until you got here.
Tell me about the fire.
It's the annual fall dance
for the kids.
And it's really popular.
It's hard to get tickets.
But the kids love it.
Do you personally know
Any of the other families?
Who lost children?
And who recently
committed suicide as a result.
Just questions.
Ok?
He knows...
Paul wouldn't do this.
What?
Not after all
we've been through.
He would not leave us.
Not like that.
Go ahead.
Put it up.
This is a physical
representation
Of the 5 equivocal deaths.
Together with the profile
of each case,
We'll build psychological
autopsies of each person.
And this will tell us
if it was suicide
or murder.
Uh, suicide, yes,
murder, no.
And you think it's
a pretty good indicator.
Since its inception
in 1958,
It's proven to carry
a 92% accuracy rate
In cases that have
gone to trial.
Ok, so the door was locked
from the inside
And the wife
broke the door in.
But he could have
gotten out that window.
Well, it's a good
20-Foot drop.
It'd hurt,
but you could do it.
So a toaster was thrown
in the tub, right?
Space heater.
Toaster, space heater.
Did the job.
Hey. It's a 110 outlet
with no gfi.
Go on.
Well, it's a 1930s house,
but it's been remodeled,
With no ground fault
installation.
Yet there was a gfi unit
installed in the kitchen.
I put them
in all my properties,
Especially the bathroom
and the kitchen.
Any surge of electrical
current will shut the power down
At the source.
Properties?
Yeah.
How many properties?
4.
Whoever threw the space heater
in this tub
Knew that there was no gfi.
Mm-Hmm.
Come on.
Mrs. Baleman,
What did your husband do
for a living?
He was a contractor.
Well, if these autopsies
prove they weren't suicides,
Then i need to inform
the media right away.
I would err
on the side of caution.
What?
People need to know.
And they will, as soon as
we have absolute proof.
I think the town's been through
enough already, don't you?
Also keep in mind that
if these cases are related,
This unsub's probably
already aware
that we're onto him.
But the community
needs to know
If there's a serial
killer in its midst.
And they will,
as soon as we have proof.
Even if the proof
means another body.
He's right, you know.
He's also personally
motivated, though,
Which means he's likely
to react irrationally.
If this turns out to be
the work of a serial killer,
The whole town will, too.
You know what i think,
jakey?
Quarterback.
Yeah.
Maybe that's a little
too dangerous.
How about a kicker?
Yeah, a kicker.
Ooh! Looks like
we have a visitor.
Just a second!
Mommy will be right back.
Hey there. Come on in.
Thank you very much.
Say hi, jake.
Can you do that
for mommy, say "hi."
I've got your bag
in the other room.
You ok?
Yeah, i'm good.
Let's do this.
All right, you got a kid.
There's a bad guy
in the house.
What do you do
to protect your child?
Fight.
Not a single defensive
wound on her body.
Well...
I don't suppose she climbed
up there of her own free will.
Unless
she committed suicide.
She's got a baby
crying for her
in the other room.
Father found him
in the high chair.
Not a scratch.
Remember,
the unsub believes
He's on some kind
of a mission.
The child is of no
importance to him.
You find
a suicide note?
I haven't found one yet.
So what are you thinking?
In every case, there's no
evidence of a struggle.
Or breaking and entering.
I'm going to need
you and emily to contact
all of the families
Affected by the fire
and inform them
what's going on.
They need to be
warned immediately.
So she couldn't cope.
She snapped.
It happens.
It happens every day.
No, not here it didn't.
Emily...
Right now that's
exactly what happened.
Paul baleman's house...
That's what you'd expect
From someone who
was deeply depressed,
deeply traumatized.
Yeah, i know.
I saw it.
Everything past orderly,
everything present
disorderly.
The bookshelf,
the glass cabinet
All had order
when their lives had order,
had meaning.
Everything about beth's home
says she moved on.
Then how did she get up
there without a fight?
Whew... uh....
She was already dead.
Dead weight is a lot
heavier than alive.
Um...
Ok, well...
She can't believe
he's gonna spare the baby
If she does what she's told.
The question is,
How did he get in?
Beth must have let him in.
I mean, she had to.
They all let him in.
So she fixes them drinks,
he drugs her.
That's gotta be it.
Emily, the strange and great,
what can i do you for?
Hey, uh, i'm looking
for a drug
That would temporarily
paralyze or subdue someone,
Not kill them,
but give full control.
Well, i always use alcohol.
Less fuss, way cheaper.
Um, uh, look for something
that wouldn't show up
in a toxicology report.
Ok, got it.
Thank you.
Anything to tell us
Whether these are suicides
or not?
These are some samples
from diedre nollard,
the jumper.
See, we have
an insurance form,
A letter she wrote
to her neighbor
a month ago,
A birthday card she wrote
to her husband a week ago,
And her suicide note
as found on her body.
Suicide note matches,
right?
Definitely by her own hand,
But she's professing
regret. Look.
"Uh, i'm sorry i let you down.
Please forgive me.
I disappointed you." And so on.
But the handwriting,
The forensic analysis
is saying the exact
opposite.
What do you mean?
Um... well, you see
how the handwriting slants uphill?
It's a clear sign
of optimism.
The same with how
the spacing
is so consistent.
And these long t-Bars...
Those indicate
an enthusiastic person.
Not someone
who would take a swan dive
off a 5-Story walkup.
Look, even if we had
alerted the media...
Now we'll never know.
Like i said,
that's on me.
But, hey,
now we have the proof
That these aren't suicides.
Those notes,
were they coerced?
If you were to force someone
to write their own suicide note,
These are words
you generally wouldn't use.
I'll take that as a no.
And my brother's journal?
I haven't...
It's extensive. I haven't...
Another no.
Can we inform the media now?
I have.
I need you all outside.
This is ssa aaron hotchner.
He's just arrived.
What have we got?
Including extended families,
over 100 individuals
Within the pittsburgh area
were affected by that fire.
So this unsub
is targeting grief, eh?
Grief?
An event.
A single event
in this unsub's life
Led him to end the life
of someone he believes
had to die.
From that moment on,
he created his own sense of morality...
What is right
and what is wrong...
And he rationalizes
what he did,
That first kill
over and over again,
By targeting people
that he believes
can't be saved
By anyone
other than himself.
He decides who lives
and who dies,
And this gives him
an all-Consuming
sense of power.
So they're not gonna stop
anytime soon.
Well, that's assuming
there's someone
to actually stop.
And if there is,
He's convinced he's
on a mission of mercy,
And even after he's caught,
he'll maintain
he did nothing wrong.
He.
White male, mid to late 30s,
he's polite, forthcoming,
Doesn't stand out.
And we believe his victims,
these families,
Are all letting him in.
My brother and his wife
weren't letting anyone in.
If anything, they were
closing themselves off.
Well, this unsub
has found a way in,
One that's very hard to trace.
In every case
there was no evidence
of a struggle,
No attempt at escapes.
He finds
a personal connection
and uses it to buy time.
And my officers
need to know this.
We've found...
That angels of mercy
Are often people
in the medical profession,
Cops.
As well as law enforcement.
Which is why
we're meeting out here.
Now, we're only fishing.
We don't want to point
a finger.
Point it.
I don't give a damn.
If that's
what it's about,
Let us figure out
where to point it.
I asked garcia to check into
emergency responders
Around the scene of the fire.
Good. Prentiss?
He's smart. He knows
all about these
people's schedules,
Their routines.
Look, if this unsub
does exist,
This is a guy
who's all about control.
He chooses how they die,
when they die.
He even positions them exactly
how he wants them to die.
That makes him
hypervigilant,
A guy who's always
on the lookout,
risk averse, unseen.
The only way to stop him
Is to find out how
he's managed to get into
all of his victims' lives.
We find that out,
we've got our killer.
We can start
bringing people in,
Find the connection.
I haven't had a drink.
It's been 3 weeks...
4 days.
Some of you know
i lost my son... ben
In the fire.
A few of you
have pushed me
To go see
his little league games...
His old team.
He used to pitch.
But i gotta be honest,
I just haven't been
up for that.
I drive by every day.
I thought maybe today.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
Thank you for coming.
We're so sorry
about the loss of your son.
I'm sure you know
about the suicides
That have occurred
in shadyside over
the past 2 months.
We believe there's
a serial killer
Who is making it appear
as though his victims
were committing suicide.
Oh, my god.
And he's targeting
people
That were affected
by the fire.
Wh-What do you mean?
I mean, why would someone
do that?
He believes
he's an angel of mercy,
That he's actually
helping his victims move on.
Do you, uh, believe
we may know this person?
Yes, we do.
We just buried our daughter.
Yes, we know.
Whatever
his motivations are,
It's crucial we look into
every part of your life.
Oh, like he's done
or is doing, right?
Um, can you think of
anyone who might want...
Might want to kill us?
They're just
doing their job.
He's a white male,
mid-30s.
He comes across
as very concerned,
Friendly, charming.
No.
I'm sorry.
If you need our help...
For anything.
Thank you.
Did you see her
with her son?
What?
She couldn't hold him.
She couldn't look at him.
Mind if i sit here?
Help yourself.
So you made it.
Yeah, i did.
Face what you fear the most.
Step 10... Continue to take
personal inventory.
Go ahead, hot stuff,
talk to me.
Hey, so,
prentiss was looking
For some narcotics,
my burning love hunk,
And i scored humongously.
I ran every toxicological panel
known to man on the victims
And came up with zilch,
which means he must be
knocking them out
With a neuromuscular agent.
With a what?
A paralytic.
Yeah, yeah. Something like
succinylcholine
Or vecuromium, one of those ones
that would metabolize
in the body so quickly,
It wouldn't be detectable.
Plus, plus, also,
and i called me up mr. Coroner
And said, how would you
do this?
And he says, by injection.
So i say, hey, guy,
wouldn't that leave a mark?
And he's all, "hold up."
And then he goes and looks
at beth smoler's body
And finds the mark.
A hole,
right in her hairline.
Ok, so you have to be
in the medical profession
To get ahold
of those drugs, right?
Not necessarily.
You can get almost anything
online these days.
This drug leaves no trace?
None.
Even if a coroner
was looking for something,
The evidence was gone.
And beth smoler
didn't see anything coming.
No, sir.
She completely saw it coming.
They all saw it coming.
Neuromuscular blockers
paralyze the muscles temporarily
While you remain
very much awake.
He sedates them,
then quickly engineers
their suicide.
Well, if that's true,
it means this unsub's
Not looking for
the glory of the kill.
No, but unfortunately
for his victims,
They're wide awake
when he decides
It's time for them
to move on.
I know that feeling...
When is it ever
going to end?
The sadness,
it just goes on and on,
Every breathing moment.
And the pain,
it overwhelms you.
And if you could end it...
You would.
That's why when you
looked at me, curtis,
I knew in that moment
what you wanted of me.
What you wanted me to do.
I'm only sorry
it took me this long.
But i'm here now.
You can let go, curtis.
I think we're ready now.
Yeah.
We're ready.
Wo
the barrel was placed
right there,
Under the chin,
He shoots,
And the bullet
went up through
The small and hard
palate of his mouth,
And then it exited
out through his--
Cranium. Check
the back of his head,
His hairline.
There. See it?
Oh, a puncture wound.
Made by a...
Needle.
Did he leave a note?
All right, rossi, i'm in.
We got ourselves an unsub.
They all have
the same type of tone.
It's uncanny.
And you're saying that
they all wrote these willingly.
None of them are forced,
But even here
in curtis fackler's,
he never says goodbye.
It's like they're
not meant for anybody,
Not for a wife,
not for a kid.
Then who are they
writing them to?
They're amends,
to themselves, and i...
I believe they're written
as part of a program.
Program?
The five stages of grief...
In some self-Help groups
They ask you to write down
an amends to yourself.
Is that right?
And all of these groups
are anonymous, right?
Well, just to give you
an idea of what we're
dealing with here,
Just for alcoholic
support groups for tonight,
Monday, there are... 91
Around pittsburg proper.
You gotta be kidding me.
That many?
They have different meetings
all day and night,
Different locations,
different degrees
of participation,
Of religiousness.
Ok, i've sent you
a schedule of meetings
For the major grief staples...
Alcohol, drugs,
depression, and loss...
All within a 2-Mile radius
of shadyside. There are 11.
Can we get
a list of names?
Why not?
No.
They're anonymous. That's how
he's been getting away with it.
Let's gather the troops.
We're gonna need
all the people you can spare.
You got it.
Can you think of anybody
who sticks out?
He's confident, earnest.
Mm-Mmm.
Hell, i mean, we're addicts.
Everyone sticks out
and no one sticks out,
you know?
We're just checking
all the different groups
in the area.
This is a really
private group.
Honestly, i don't think
i can help you.
And if i could, i wouldn't.
Even if it means
that one of the members
of your group
Might get killed?
This person has
a specific background,
A tragic event.
He would have felt
compelled to tell his story
And maybe he told it
time and time again.
That's about
90% of the group.
He might have
brought up suicide.
There has been a lot
of suicide talk lately.
Anyone come to mind?
You know, there was a guy
Who talked about
his brother's suicide.
It was pretty intense.
This guy stood up
and told a story
about his brother.
His family was so poor...
They shared the same bedroom
till they were 15.
We heard
the same story.
He's moving
from group to group,
repeating it.
He said his name was peter
And that his dad was a...
Professor at brassard,
And we were just kids.
Slept in separate beds.
And my father, he'd be
coming up the stairway...
And we'd hear this...
This creaking sound.
It was awful.
And then he would...
He would get in the bed
with james and...
Molest him.
The worst part of it
is that he pretended
To be asleep
when it happened.
If it's true, it could be
what started our unsub
on his mission of mercy.
It certainly
didn't end well,
At least not for james,
the older brother.
Then one night, i, uh...
I came into our room and...
Well, james
had slashed his wrists.
The sheets were covered
in his blood.
It was... It was everywhere.
And then he looked me
in the eye...
And i knew...
In that moment...
I knew... that i just
had to let him go.
Ok, so we've got two names...
James and peter.
And the university...
Brassard.
Well, that'll make it
easier for you, garcia.
If the unsub's father
really taught at brassard,
Chances are he's local.
Reid?
Angels of mercy,
they repeat the same event
Over and over again.
What are you getting at?
Well, if as you said,
the story's true,
then he's leaving
One key piece
of information out.
The event that started it all.
His brother didn't
kill himself.
Peter did.
The fire caused
such grief and suffering
That it became the trigger.
And unable to stop himself,
He targets someone
he believes needs his help.
At first he keeps to
some kind of timeline,
A few weeks,
but the last two kills
were within days.
He's devolving.
I got it.
It's from 1984.
It's the brassard college
university newspaper.
Garcia, they lived on campus?
Yeah.
It says here james redding
was the youngest suicide
In pennsylvanian history.
And his father charles redding
was a professor. Creep.
Is there any possibility
That while
we've been talking,
You've been multitasking?
What, track down
his current address?
Ha ha. I love you,
penelope garcia.
Ha. Get in line.
Clear!
We're clear!
We need to work fast.
There's meetings taking place
all over the city.
At least
with your guys and ours,
His chances
are next to zero, right?
He's got away with it
this far.
Guys.
You might want
to take a look at this.
He's crossed off the names
of beth smoler
and curtis fackler,
The last two victims.
It's a grid
of all the support groups.
Times, dates.
Got a list of names
of all those in the meetings.
They all have a type.
Alcoholic, narcotic,
Depression, divorce.
Man, this guy
kept himself busy.
Hey. Laurie ann morris.
We spoke to her
and her husband.
Her name's not crossed off
like the others.
Hi, my name is laurie ann.
Hi, laurie ann.
She's not answering
her cell phone.
The husband's
already left for work.
I'm calling his cell now.
Jonathan, hello.
This is agent emily prentiss
from the fbi.
Is your wife laurie ann
with you?
Can you tell us where
she is right now?
Got it.
Rough day?
You don't have to
answer that.
Oh, tried to quit.
Can't quite
seem to do it.
Maybe now's not the time.
Right.
You'll know when it is.
You have good intuition.
And i can see that.
I'm late.
Nice to meet you.
You, too.
Oh...
Excuse me, sir.
We're looking for either one
of these people.
Have either of you
seen them?
You sure?
All right, let's split up
And search the building
and the surrounding area.
This way, guys.
Laurie ann morris.
Have you seen her?
Please, look close.
She was here.
Are you sure?
Excuse me.
Have either of you
seen these people?
All right, thank you.
Expired.
Triple-A?
I'll figure something out.
She was here
a minute ago.
Where'd she go?
Maybe the parking lot.
Was she alone?
She was talking
to some guy.
Thank you.
Parking lot?
Other side
of the building.
How many exits
does it have?
3. North, east,
and west side.
All right, split up
and cover each one.
Morgan,
you come with us.
Where are you going?
Please, it's no bother.
Where?
Main street.
I'm just going
to meet a friend.
Just hop in the back.
Blue chevy.
Do you know what kind
of car she has?
Wait.
I can help you.
Help me how?
With the pain of not even
being able to hold your son.
You think
you can help me?
Yes.
You just have to let go.
It's over there.
Is that what you did
for all those people?
Laurie ann!
Yes. I did
what they couldn't.
You think
you can help me?
Laurie ann!
You think
you can help me?
Yes.
Laurie ann!
What are you doing?
Morgan: put your hands
where i can see them!
I'm going around!
Show me your hands!
Ok. Don't move.
We've got help coming.
Morgan: do it now!
Yeah.
You got him?
I don't understand
what's going on.
Here.
Ow! Ow!
What's going on
Is you just took
your last breath
as a free man.
Shut up.
I've done nothing wrong.
Ow! Ow!
Ow. Uh...
Hi.
You're gonna be ok.
Am i?
Laurie ann...
A mother isn't supposed
to outlive her children.
Yeah.
But she's gone.
Allie's dead.
Please. I don't...
care anymore.
But your son does.
Don't lose him as well.
I wanted to thank you
for all you did
And for believing me
when no one else did.
Ron....
Thank you.
Paul's journal...
I read it.
Ronnie, your brother paul
wasn't murdered.
In peter's apartment,
Unlike all the other
victims,
Paul's name
was nowhere to be found.
I... I don't understand.
You said the psychological
autopsy was inconclusive.
Further analysis
of the journal concludes
it was suicide.
I'm sorry.
You're wrong.
But like i said,
thanks for coming.
"the most
authentic thing about us
"Is our capacity
to create, to overcome,
"To endure, to transform,
To love, and to be greater
than our suffering."
Ben okri.
How did it go with jack?
I just told him
that i wasn't going
to be around as much.
How did he take it?
He gave me a hug
and he said that everything
was gonna be all right.
Smart kid.
Like his dad.
So tell me,
Back at the house,
When we found beth smoler.
I don't know.
Sometimes i just wonder...
If we're actually
changing anything.
Do you know why
i have 4 properties?
Tell me.
If i'm not kicking down doors,
i'm smashing down walls.
At the end of the day,
They both make me feel
like i'm changing something.
For the better.
Good enough?
Good enough.
Http://www.Ragbear.Com