LITTLE CREEK RESERVIOR, VA
Go on, mudgie! Go on, boy.
Attaboy!
Go on, boy.
Come! Come!
Strauss, I'm coming in to
see you this afternoon.
Well, then cancel it.
I'll be there at 2:30.
That's it. Come on, boy!
Come on! Yeah.
I really don't understand this, david.
What's to understand, erin?
You've been retired for nearly 10 years.
B.A.U. Is a man down.
I'm offering to help.
You've written... how many books?
World tours.
Speaking engagements.
Big payday private consultations.
You've made quite a name for yourself.
Well, this is getting boring.
You know, you won't be in charge.
Agent hotchner's the S.A.C. And
I'll be seeking his endorsement.
I'm not looking for
anyone's permission here.
So you're coming in in
a subordinate position.
- Is that a question?
- The question is, why?
To help.
A completely selfless act.
Is that so hard to believe?
Yes.
I missed you too, erin.
You'll meet the team tomorrow.
CARROLLTON, TEXAS
HAVE YOU SEEN ME?
It was next to my front
door when I got home, frank.
God, I hate halloween.
- Here you go, sir.
- Halloween?
Less than a week away.
Police Department,
CARROLLTON, TEXAS
It's a prime time for stupid pranks.
So you think it's just a prank?
Well, you're obviously
not missing, michelle.
Where'd they get a picture of me?
It's probably one of your friends.
I don't know anybody
that'd think this is funny.
Molly didn't think it was funny.
She's the one who told me
to come right down here.
If my wife had just called, I
probably could have saved you the trip.
I'm sure it's nothing, really.
You sure?
Look...
I'll come by and check on you after
work and make sure you're safe.
I appreciate that, frank.
Hey. Serving and
protecting is what I do.
No, no, I didn't say it was funny, molly.
I said
someone might--
I--I know she's your best
friend. That's why I'm here.
No. No, I don't think it's
weird she didn't call--
look, I'm here already.
All the lights are out.
She--she probably
went to bed early.
I'll have her call you.
Yeah,20 minutes. I love you, too.
This wasn't funny the first time.
Michelle?
Michelle, it's frank!
Oh, my god.
www.ydy.com/bbs
Federal Bureau of Investigation
QUANTICO, VIRGINIA
Erasmus wrote, what else is the whole
life of mortals but a sort of comedy,
in which the various actors, disguised
by various costumes and masks,
walk on and play each one his part,
until the manager waves
them off the stage?
I'm waiting for you!
Reid...
happy all hallows eve, folks.
To paraphrase from celtic mythology,
tomorrow night all order is suspended,
and the barriers between the natural and
the supernatural are temporarily remooooved!
See, that right there is
why halloween creeps me out.
You're scared of halloween?
I didn't say I was scared, I
said I was creeped out.
There's a difference there, youngster.
You should look it up.
What creeps you out about it?
I don't know. People wearing masks.
I don't like folks in disguises.
That's the best thing about halloween.
You can be anyone you want to be.
Nah, I'm pretty good just being me.
Yeah, why is it that neither of
those points of view surprise me?
You know what, though? On the flip side,
it does provide a pretty good
reason to cozy up with a scary flick
and a little halloween honey.
Halloween honey. Now I'm creeped out.
Guys, he's here.
Agent hotchner.
- I'm sure you
remember-- - Dave.
how are you, aaron?
- I'm good. I'm great.
- I would say so.
Saw you on tv last week.
Can't believe you
want to come back here.
Well, I'll let the two of you catch up.
- If you need anything, I'm in my office.
- Thanks.
So how long's it been?
Dinner, almost 3 years ago.
But the last time I was in the B.A.U.
You were sharing a desk with 2 other
agents in that god-awful bunker we were in.
I remember.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Well, there's one just like this
next door if you're interested.
I'm ready to give the briefing.
Agent jareau, this is ssa david rossi.
Hi. Everyone calls me J.J.
It is such an honor to meet you, sir.
- I've heard a lot about you.
- Thank you.
And what's your function here?
I'm the communications
coordinator and liaison.
Pretty much the go-between for
the team and the rest of the world.
So I'll gather everyone.
We'll be right there.
- It is so nice to have you here, sir.
- Great.
We didn't have that 10 years ago.
What do you mean?
- Communications coordinator.
- Right.
Oh, lots has changed. Come meet the team.
Ssa david rossi, this
is ssa emily prentiss.
Sir.
Ssa derek morgan.
It's an honor, agent rossi.
Please, just dave.
And dr. Spencer reid.
Sir, if I could talk to you later about
your work with the scarsdale skinner.
Psycho-linguistics is an
incredibly dynamic field,
and the fact that your profile of his
reading habits ultimately led to his capture
- is something I find so incredibly
intrig-- - reid, slow down.
He'll be here for a while. You
can catch up with him later.
- Sorry.
- No problem, doctor.
Maybe you guys can talk on the jet.
- Oh, yeah, that'd be great.
- The jet?
We have a jet now.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah. It comes in pretty handy.
Come on. J.J.'S waiting.
Carrollton, texas, is a suburb
just outside of dallas.
4 days ago, michelle colucci found
this flier on her front door.
She found it?
Meaning she wasn't actually missing?
Yet. She took the flier
to a friend's husband,
detective yarbrough,at
the carrollton P.D.
Who told her it was probably just a
halloween prank, and he sent her home.
Well, I don't blame him.
Halloween brings out
the fool in everyone.
Still, he stopped by michelle's
house later to check on her.
The door was open, and when
he went inside, he found this.
He still thought maybe it could be
some kind of a prank, until yesterday.
Michelle was found floating in a
small creek just outside of carrollton.
She had been sexually assaulted...
and her face had been removed.
Removed? It wasn't animals or fish?
The dallas county M.E. Say that the
edges of the wounds were smooth,not torn.
A very sharp instrument had been used.
He also found water in her lungs.
Oh, my god!
What is that?
Technical analyst penelope
garcia, this is ssa david rossi.
Is it gone,J.J.?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You're safe.
OK. Just to, um...
carrollton,texas,has
nearly 117,000 residents,
a diverse population with
A... it's all in there.
I'm sorry.
Very happy to meet you, sir.
I'll be in my office.
Sorry.
She's different.
You have no idea.
Uh, so, the unsub tells her she's going to
go missing to psychologically torture her,
then tortures her physically.
Textbook sadist.
A sophisticated one.
That's elaborate.
Number one.
That particular mask is
known as a false face.
It's most commonly worn during
halloween and mardi gras.
Creepy. I rest my case.
False face.
Her face-- he mocks
it, then destroys it.
Oh, and, hotch-- local media
has the story. It broke big.
Tell carrollton we'll be there
first thing in the morning.
- Let's stop this one at one.
- Yes, sir.
If you want to take some time to get
situated, maybe start on the next case?
I'm not back to get
situated, hotch, I'm here to work.
Everybody get your things
together. We're going to texas.
Abbey, what's the latest?
Police sources tell me they
have no leads in the case
they are calling the
"have you seen me"Murders.
Where the hell do you get this stuff?
No, not you, agent jareau. The television.
The press is saying we gave
this thing a stupid name,
like it's some kind of
damn game or something.
Just...
call me when you all get in tomorrow.
I'll take you wherever you need to go.
All right. Good night.
Abbey, do we know when
this flyer first surfaced?
We have heard reports that ms. Colucci
received this flier late tuesday afternoon
when she returned home from work.
*****
Never saw the point at
throwing an egg at anything.
DALLAS, TEXAS
Or even the connection to
halloween, for that matter.
What the hell...
oh, my god. That's me.
Oh, my god!
Let's go over victimology.
Would you like to join us, dave?
Reid, what have you got?
Uh, michelle colucci was single,
lived alone, no boyfriend
and no ex-husband.
Dating?
There's nothing in the reports.
She was an architect.
Friends and co-workers say
she's a class workaholic.
Basically a loner who
rarely went out of the house.
So she's extremely low risk.
If it wasn't someone she knew personally,
it's possible she was being stalked.
- Interesting.
- What's that?
Oh, I'm just thinking out loud.
- Something to add?
- No.
Sorry to interrupt.
Well, she's pretty.
It could be that the unsub
met her casually and...
made her part of some kind of fantasy.
And he tries to act on
it and she rejects him?
So he tortures her, out of anger?
Masks often represent a state of mind.
This one's blank, expressionless.
Doesn't really coincide with anger.
Reid, it's hard to imagine he did
this out of anything less than rage.
Hey, guys.
What's up? You got something for us?
A list of michelle colucci's clients.
She designed office space. Mostly
big corporate remodeling plans.
No private
clients, one-on-one contact?
Doesn't look like it, no.
- Thanks, baby girl.
- Yeah.
It's right this way, ma'am.
Police Department CARROLLTON. TEXAS
- Detective yarbrough?
- Fbi?
We got another flier--
this time metro dallas.
Enid white.
Her roommate called
dallas P. D. This morning.
Enid never game home after
walking her dog last night.
So she is missing.
Well, he wallpapered the neighborhood with
fliers for 2 blocks around their apartment.
Outside. That's different.
No one saw him putting them up?
Dallas P. D. Is still
canvassing, but nothing so far.
They're waiting for
you on the new scene.
- Mind if I keep this?
- Not at all.
Morgan, you and prentiss go
to michelle colucci's house.
J. J. And I will talk to enid's roommate.
Dave, do you mind walking the disposal
site with the detective and reid?
Whatever you need.
We'll regroup in an hour.
These houses sure are close together.
Yeah.
So how do I get a woman out of
her house without anyone seeing me?
Well, he must have been watching her for
a long time and knew that it was safe.
There isn't a lot of
cover on this street.
I have a vehicle.
Big enough so I can
watch without being seen.
But not so big as to
draw attention to itself.
No.
Neighbors will notice a strange vehicle parked in
front of their house day after day, night after night.
It's human nature.
You would notice something out
of place in your own neighborhood.
And you would definitely notice a man
repeatedly standing on your street.
Yeah. It just doesn't make any sense.
He didn't watch from here.
As we reported earlier, enid white
is still considered missing...
big story.
Leeches.
Haven't had something this
big to play in a long time.
Did the press run with
the story about the mask?
Mask?
A mask was left at michelle
colucci's apartment.
First time I'm hearing about it.
Good.
- Let's make sure that stays ours.
- Yeah.
Miss white's roommate says that enid walks
her dog every night at the same time,
takes the same route, right
down this street.
Nothing a stalker likes
better than routine.
Well, she definitely would have seen this
if this was here
before she went missing.
A couple of neighbors say they may have
seen a guy putting up a flier during the day,
bueaey rt thlly couldn't
remember anything about him.
All right, well, we're gonna have to
know everything we can about the victim.
I know you sent some
stuff over to quantico,
but it would help us if we could
interview the roommate ourselves.
We have her downtown now.
- Where's her dog?
- Excuse me?
If she was abducted while she was
walking her dog. Where's her dog?
We went over this
area pretty thoroughly.
There's no evidence left.
I just want to stand where she was.
Dr. Reid, do we still keep all the old
files in the fourth floor storeroom?
I think some are up there. You know, most
of our information's on computer now.
Right.
Have you had a chance to go through
our data since you've been back?
Not yet.
You'll be amazed.
The original
team--
I mean, you interviewed something like,
- uh,45 serial killers, right?
- Something like.
Today we have interviews
with over 1,000 offenders.
Serial killers, child
abductors, sex offenders--
I'll go through it with you sometime
if you like, answer any questions--
sounds good.
Michelle's body was found right here.
I really thought it was a prank.
You can't really blame
yourself for that.
She made herself dinner.
Excuse me?
She had time to make herself dinner.
I mean she was home
for a while before he...
there was time to help her.
Water.
Obliterates a body...
destroys evidence.
But you weren't in the water
that long, were you, michelle?
She had rocks tied to
her to weigh her down.
She floated to the surface
before there was any other damage.
Just what was done to her already.
The salient point is that it was the
first thing the unsub wasn't good at.
Green river dumped most
of the bodies in the water.
- But they weren't weighed down.
- Yeah.
We know now it's'ause he
didn't care if they were found.
He had no connection to them.
This is where I'd wait.
Yeah.
I'd never be able to
see you from the house.
Prentiss.
He was here a lot.
Watching everything she did.
we got anything?
Agent rossi pointed out that since
the victims were weighted down,
it suggests the unsub
didn't want them found.
It suggests some sort of
connection between them.
Detective, how long was michelle missing?
She was found on the fourth day.
So if she wasn't in the water
long, then he held her for 3.
Garcia?
I've been running all of
enid white's credit cards.
And?
She made a purchase at 9 A. M. This morning
at a sporting goods store in dallas.
This morning?
What did she buy?
A shotgun.
Thanks.
The man was seen posting fliers around the
neighborhood where enid white was known to walk her dog.
The police are still unable to give
us any information at this time,
and they are saying they
still have no possible leads.
We will continue to keep you posted
as we receive more details
about the hunt for enid white...
she can buy a gun that easily?
This is texas.
There's no license or waiting
period for most rifles or shotguns.
Is there video surveillance of
guns sales in sporting goods stores?
There's supposed to be.
J.J.,Call the store.
Find out if it was enid or the
unsub using her credit card.
Right away.
Detective yarbrough.
There's an urgent call
from a woman on one.
Detective yarbrough.
My name is enid white.
Where are you, enid
The news reports said that the police didn't believe
that other woman when she saw the missing fliers.
That was a mistake, enid.
I have a gun.
I don't think I can stay
awake very much longer.
Enid, this is agent hotchner of the fbi.
We believe you, and we want to help you.
Can you tell us where you are?
El royale motel in dallas.
It's room 6.
I saw the fliers.
Hurry, please.
He's gonna kill me.
Don't move, enid. We're on our way.
Fbi!
Clear.
She's gone.
20 minutes.
We were here in 20 minutes.
I can't believe we lost her.
We may not have lost her.
He kept michelle for 4 days.
But we got nothing.
That's not true. Look at
the difference in the scenes.
What do you mean? There's
the masks, the fliers.
Yeah, but these fliers weren't tacked up,
they were just thrown around the room.
So?
He left in a hurry like
he knew we were coming.
OK, this was under the bed.
972 area code.
That's carrollton.
The hotline number.
She used a cell phone.
You can get a cell interceptor
at any electronics store.
You can?
Yeah. They don't cost that much.
He probably sat right out here
and heard everything she said.
But if he followed her here from dallas,
why wait till she
calls us to move on her?
To make sure it was the
police who found the mask.
We need to gather your
men and give a profile.
He's a white male.
His shoe prints have been examined
and put him at about 5'11,165.
So we've narrowed it down to
anyone of average weight and height.
Exactly.
Speak and be recognized
by your empress, mortal.
Is this the technical analyst girl?
Who's this?
Dr. Reid said this was your
direct line from the team.
It is.
This is agent dave
rossi. We met yesterday.
Of course, of course.
I'm sorry--sir.
Uh, yeah, I already started processing the
footprint information on michelle colucci--
no, no, no. This is about something else.
All the past open cases the
B. A. U. Worked on are on computer now?
Most of them.
There may be a few left to catalog.
If I give you a victim's
name, could you find the old records?
Oh, records are my specialty, sir.
The original case--
I'm going back 20 years.
Won't be a problem.
The name is galen.
Diana and richard galen.
They had 3 children.
OK. I will get back to you
super fast. Scout's honor.
No, no, um, just put a file together.
I'll get it when I get back.
It's really no problem, sir. I
could just send it--
not necessary. I'll look
at it when I get back.
And let's keep this between
us, if you don't mind. For now.
OK.
Thank you.
My pleasure entirely, sir.
There's a sophistication and patience in what
this unsub does that suggests a level of maturity.
We believe this puts his age
in the mid-30s to 40s range.
Michelle colucci was taken
from the primary crime scene
and disposed of at the tertiary
crime scene 4 days later.
That means she was held
somewhere for at least 3 days.
You can't really just hold a
victim anywhere for days on end,
so he most likely has access
to a house of some kind.
And he's also fairly tech savvy.
The fliers were made on a computer.
And it's probable that he used a device
to intercept enid white's phone call.
Witnesses in enid
white's neighborhood say
they may have seen a white
man putting up fliers,
but none of them could describe him, even with
all the media attention this case has received.
Great.
Actually, what that tells us is that there is
absolutely nothing remarkable about this man.
He is exceedingly average.
As you said, detective
yarbrough, average height, average build.
It extends to his
professional life as well.
He most likely works in a field where he
doesn't stand out, doesn't really make a mark.
His lack of distinction
is part of his psychopathy.
We have hundreds of interactions
with people every day.
Most of those involve someone
overlooking someone else.
Most of us don't pay any attention to
being ignored, but to this kind of unsub,
each oversight is intentional.
Especially when it comes from
his object of sexual desire.
He begins to obsess over her
until she's all he can think about.
And the rage builds until
he has to attack that person.
So he's pissed off
that nobody notices him?
Have you seen me?
Wait. That's not about the women.
No. The masks are
about the women--
number one, number 2.
The fliers probably refer to him.
Removing his victims'faces transfers his
feelings of being ignored into a mission
and it gives him a sense of power.
And the power can make him arrogant, but
it doesn't make him notable.
So how the hell do we
catch an invisible man?
I'm pretty sure we can
get him to contact you.
What?
Well, the crime scenes show he wants
to deliver his message to the police.
He isn't going public.
Hopefully, by playing on his anger...
J.J.,How'd they get that?
Not from
me. I--
hotch, I called all the local police
departments and I stressed withholding the mask.
I called them.
What?
I said the fbi thinks the
masks mean he's impotent.
Can I speak to you for a second?
Why would you do that?
It'll make him contact us.
He's screaming for it.
We aren't prepared.
Prepared?
We need to set up a trap and trace.
Trap and trace?
They never stay on the
phone long enough for that.
Dave, they're a lot faster
than they used to be.
We also need to prep the
detective on what to say to him.
He's not gonna want to
talk to the detective.
He's gonna want to talk to the fbi.
We don't step over the
local police like that.
They called us in.
Yes, but if the perception is that
we're to embarrass the locals by telling
the media that we're gonna fix things,
then they'll stop calling us.
Relax, hotch. I've got this.
You see, that's the problem, dave.
There is no I.
We function as a team.
I've been doing this before
you were out of high school,
probably before the rest of
your team was in school at all.
I know that.
Things have changed.
The bells and whistles changed.
An unsub is still an unsub, and
I know how to deal with an unsub.
- No, dave, it's not just that.
- Hotch.
What?
Garcia found something.
Garcia, talk to us.
So, michelle colucci
recently drew up the plans
for a remodel of 3 floors of a
company called techco communications.
It's a high-tech communications
company in downtown dallas.
And enid white?
Worked there until 2 months ago.
He's on 2.
The unsub?
Demanded to speak to the fbi.
This is fbi supervisory
special agent david rossi.
You called me impotent.
Did I?
I'm not impotent.
Why are you whispering?
You lied.
Is someone around you?
Are you at work?
You have to tell the news the truth.
I'll get you on the news, then
you can correct me yourself.
No, you, you, you correct it.
By the way, I was, um, looking
at the police security tapes
for the day michelle
colucci went missing.
What?
You watched her long enough to
know she didn't have visitors.
She was a loner.
Yet you knew that detective
yarbrough was coming over.
You must have been right here
in this station when he told her.
Now, your face is gonna be on one
of those tapes, and when I find it,
I'm gonna paper this city with
it, just like you did with those women.
Everyone will see it.
They won't be able to ignore you now.
But you won't inspire fear, you'll
inspire hatred and ridicule,
because the only power
someone like you has is a mask,
and once that mask is removed,
you'll be as insignificant
as you've always been--
a loser!
You just signed enid
white's death warrant.
Lieutenant, I need you to lock
the techco building down tight.
Nobody in, nobody out. It's vital.
Rossi, you really think the unsub's
still gonna be there after that call?
Of course. He thinks he has
all the time in the world.
You think they got an image off
the police security camera yet?
The security camera doesn't
work. I lied about that.
You lied about that?
He doesn't know.
Dave, that was incredibly reckless.
Hotch, he didn't weigh
the body down well.
What do you mean?
He didn't want michelle
found so quickly.
He screwed that up.
This kind of guy, when
he plans something,
if he has the time, if he's
in control, he's meticulous.
But being on the edge of the river, out
in the open, he was not in control.
He was in a hurry, and he made a mistake.
That's what you're hoping.
Trust me.
With an unsub like this, you
need to throw him off his game.
His hand needs to be forced.
I know that, dave, but the point
is, you did it by forcing ours.
- Is the building sealed?
- Top to bottom.
Yarbrough, make sure it stays that way.
Garcia, which floors did
michelle carlucci remodel?
Got
it--7,8,9.
Morgan, take 7.
We're looking for a
rank-and-file employee
who made a scene in the last
20 minutes or was here and gone.
Prentiss,8, reid,9.
Don't approach him. Just...
try to get a name, maybe a picture.
He's somewhere in this lobby.
Why?
Can't you feel it?
Display your credentials. Fbi.
He thinks we know what he looks like.
Yeah, reid?
Got him.
Sir?
Sir!
Max pool.
We have your address, max.
There's no place to go.
This is agent rossi, max.
If you do what you're thinking, you
won't get to tell them I lied.
Come on, max, slowly put your
hands on top of your head.
Listen to him, max.
I know what you're thinking
and you don't have to do it.
It doesn't have to end here, max.
Please.
Down!
- You OK?
- Yeah.
- He's gone.
- What about enid white?
We have his home address.
Is she there?
Let's hope so.
"Home" by Chris Daughtry
You said out there, the
team shares everything.
That's right.
There is no I?
It seems a big thing to withhold.
Separating from your wife, your child.
What are you talking about?
You used to call haley 10 times a day.
We've been together 48 hours, I
haven't seen you call her once.
Haven't mentioned her.
And you're not going home now.
What's your point?
I guess you're just not used to sharing.
My private life is
not the same as a case.
I'm just saying, sharing
is a learned skill.
You know...
when this all started...
there were only a few of us.
We'd go out on the road alone.
We didn't... groupthink.
We don't groupthink.
We think as individuals, and we share
the thoughts with the rest of the team.
We don't write them down in a little
notebook and keep them to ourselves.
Dave.
All this-- the people we've
helped, the ones we've put away, it'S...
because of you and the
guys who started this unit,
who believed when nobody else did that
there was a way of understanding
these crimes and getting ahead of them.
And?
I don't see that you
have anything to prove.
You don't have to come back.
I know that.
So why?
Maybe I have unfinished business.
=www.ydy.com/bbs=