Previously, on criminal minds...
- I met a guy.
- Where?
Coffee shop.
I fixed his computer.
Maybe i could
take you to lunch.
Can you believe that?
A complete stranger.
It happens.
Not to me.
Not like this.
I think you should
always trust your gut.
Maybe you should
walk the other way.
I was wondering
if you'd let me
Make that thank-You
lunch a dinner
I'm asking you out,
garcia.
Hey, garcia.
I've been thinking about
doing this all night.
I was inside.
I heard the shot, but i didn see anything.
Gsw, chest through abdomen.
???
Airways paten,
good breath sounds.
Get a backboard
and a c-Collar.
- Is she gonna make it?
- Ma'am.
Can you hear me?
Hi. Hello.
Can you tell me your name?
???
60 and dropping.
Her name is penelope.
Ma'am, please.
Thank you.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Ma'am, did you
hear anything?
It sounded like a--
A broom handle snapping in two.
I didn't even realize it was a gunshot
at first.
Stay with us.
Can you hear me?
Can you hear my voice?
On 3--1, 2, 3.
There we go.
There you are.
Everything's great.
Yeah.
Can you tell me your name?
Penelope garcia.
Let's get her in, guys.
Go, go, go.
I think she works
for the fbi.
Penelope, everything's
gonna be fine.
Great. You're doing so good.
Hang in there.
Step.
Stay with me.
- Stay with me, penelope.
- Curb.
That's it, penelope.
You're doing great.
Stay with us.
What, you trying to make me
look bad by staying here
later than me?
J.J.
Sats are dropping--82.
Come on,
wake up and breathe.
She's hypoventilating.
Hand me the bag.
Come on.
Come on, penelope, stay with us.
30-Year-Old, single gsw,
chest to abdomen.
Pulse?
Tachy in the 140s.
Dropped her systolic
to 78.
Intubate, and red-Line
to the o.R. Now.
Hang in there, penelope.
Hang in there.
Come on.
Go, go, go, go.
She's in surgery.
There's no word.
This is crazy.
- On the i-Pack.
- Yes, doctor.
- Clamp.
- Field's too bloody.
I need suction.
Can't find the source.
Turn up the suction.
Here we go.
What do we know?
Police think it was
a botched robbery.
Where's morgan?
He's not answering his cell.
I'll call him again.
What aren't you saying?
I spoke to one of
the paramedics who brought her in.
It doesn't look good.
She's in v-Tach.
Charge to 360 and clear.
Wait. We gotta find
the bleeder.
- She'll go into v-Fib.
- We have to find the bleeder.
They can't give me
an update.
Morgan's phone just keeps going
straight to voicemail.
Where the hell is he?
Another 750
out of the chest tube.
How's it getting up there
when she's bleeding down there?
Pressure's dropping.
67 over 42.
Bullet must have ripped
right through the diaphragm.
And bagged
the splenic artery.
Put direct pressure.
Right here.
- She's bleeding too quickly.
- More blood.
- We're way behind.
- More pressure.
All right, keep pressure on the artery
while i tie her off.
Ok. Hold on.
???
V-Fib.
Clear.
Lidocaine 100 on the bones.
No change.
Charge.
300.
Clear.
No change.
- Charge.
- 360.
This isn't working.
Charge.
Nothing still.
Clear.
±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
Criminal minds309
-=Ææàãğü×öä»×é=-
·­òë: ğ£¶ô:
ê±¼äöá:abbiemcgee
William shakespeare wrote:
"Love all.
"Trust a few.
Do wrong to none."
Clear!
Nothing still.
Clear.
She's back.
???
Good job, guys.
Whew. All right.
Suction.
???
And prolene.
She's been in surgery
a couple hours.
I was at church.
My phone was off.
There's nothing you could
have been doing here.
The police
got any leads?
I spoke to
the lead detective.
He doesn't think we'll get
anything from the scene.
Penelope garcia?
- Yes.
The bullet went in her chest
And ricocheted
into her abdomen.
She lost a lot of blood.
It was touch-And-Go
for a while,
But we were able
to repair the injuries.
So what are you
saying?
One centimeter over
And it would have torn
right through her heart.
Instead, she could actually walk out
of here in a couple of days.
And i'd say
that's a minor miracle.
She needs her rest.
You can see her
in the morning.
- Thank you.
David and i
will go to the scene.
I think the rest of you should be here
when she wakes up.
I don't care about protocol.
I don't care
Whether we're working
this officially or not.
We don't touch any new cases
until we find out who did this.
Hey, garcia.
Our guess is he saw her enter,
then kicked the door in after her.
He robs her, she tries
to chase him,
Then he turns and shoots her
as he's getting away.
You have an estimate
on how far away the gunshot was?
Approximately 15 feet.
Any reason besides the door
That you think
it was a robbery?
He took her purse, dumped half of it
before he took off.
Did you find
a shell casing?
So he hit her
square from here?
Hell of a shot
on the run.
Why does he risk coming in
to an enclosed courtyard
To steal a purse?
World's
boldest purse-Snatcher?
It doesn't make sense.
Yeah.
Good.
We'll be right there.
She's up.
Hi.
No tears.
I'm afraid
if i start crying
I'll come unstapled.
How are you feeling?
Oh...
Confused...
Stupid, and...
In pain.
Are you up for
some questions?
I never saw it coming.
He seemed...
Deliciously normal.
You know him?
You were right.
I should have
trusted it.
What are you talking about?
It's that guy
i told you about.
The one i met
at the coffee shop.
I wanted to believe
he was interested in me.
Forget that.
I let my guard down.
Do you have any idea
why he would have done this?
Did he threaten you?
Did he want something?
I just thought
he liked me.
Ok. Um...
we're gonna--
We're gonna come back
in a little while.
We need a name.
James colby baylor.
J.J.
Can you stay for a sec?
We need to stay calm.
Don't tell me what to be.
Do you remember anything
she said about him?
No.
I just talked to hotch.
They think he used
a revolver.
Who the hell
uses a revolver?
Somebody who doesn't
want to leave
Shell casings
behind as evidence.
What about witnesses?
None so far.
And he staged it
to look like a robbery.
Which means
if he's smart enough
To use forensic
countermeasures,
Odds are the name he gave garcia
is probably bogus.
What did she say?
She made me promise not to talk
about her like a victim.
So victimology--Why garcia?
Look at her.
What are you saying?
You don't look like that
by accident.
She wears her individuality
like a shield.
Leading someone
to be antagonistic?
She stands out. Single woman.
Could be someone was
watching her for a while.
The sadist who gets off
on gaining her trust
And then trying to kill her?
Pretty common.
Kemper, bundy, robert anderson--
They all had
an element of it.
What's bugging you?
A sadist who just happens to
choose an analyst for the fbi?
I asked her
to go out last night.
But she was pissed at me.
She blew me off.
So you ended up
in church?
Yeah.
What does it mean?
On one hand,
if she'd gone out with me,
She would have never got shot.
On the other hand...
What are the odds
that the first time i pray in 20 years,
She's on the table?
She's asking for you.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
Good news, bad news.
The morphine's wearing off.
When i was in the ambulance,
I could hear
the song heroes
Playing in my head.
I kept flashing in and out
of consciousness.
Everything
was really bright.
And i remember thinking,
Wait...
Is david bowie really god?
We have a, uh...
We have a sketch artist
coming in.
I'm still a little hazy.
It's ok.
Anything you tell us
will help.
Yeah.
This guy say what he did
for a living?
He said he was a lawyer.
Did...did people know him
where you went?
He said he wanted
to show me a place.
It was half an hour away.
You drove together?
What kind of car?
White.
4-Door sedan.
American.
It smelled new.
Rental car maybe?
Maybe.
I don't know.
I don't look at things
like you guys do.
I don't see danger--
Ok. Take it easy.
Take it easy.
What else can you remember?
He smelled good.
Good night.
He seem nervous?
I thought he was just afraid
to kiss me good night.
Hey.
You sure
you're up for this?
Hey, garcia.
Yeah.
I've been thinking
about doing this all night.
I could hear him walking.
He leaned over me
and i held my breath
So he'd think
i was dead.
What happened here?
A shooting.
It was horrible.
She's in intensive care.
She survived?
I have no idea how.
Miracles of science, right?
Yeah.
They get the guy?
No clue at all?
Probably some crackhead.
It's crazy.
Police around here
can't even keep you safe.
This whole city's going to hell.
You look like crap.
Well, 4 days, no leads,
i feel like crap.
Any word
from the hospital?
She's out of the icu.
Doctor said she could go home
in a couple of days.
Reid and morgan
are replaying it with her
And they'll
keep us posted.
We can always round up
the 3 million guys
The sketch looks like.
That was the police.
They took the sketch
back to the coffee shop,
Restaurant,
came up empty.
I even ran it
through vicap.
No hits.
No luck with
the rental car companies.
No prints at the scene.
No shell casings.
The cell phone the guy used
to call garcia at work
Was a disposable.
The guy's a cipher.
Hypervigilance, right?
Something like that.
You know, most people
these days are looking
- For a semi-Automatic.
- Yeah?
Yeah. Holds more rounds.
You don't need more rounds
if you don't miss.
Penelope, i know it's gotta be hard
to keep reliving this.
I just don't know what else
there is to remember.
Let's start
with the behavior.
That's all--That's all profiling really is,
just noticing behavior.
Sweetheart, any details you can remember
will tell us who he is.
- Ok?
- Mm-Hmm.
All right, so let's go back
to when you first arrived
at that restaurant.
Was he nervous?
No.
The opposite, actually.
Can i start you
with anything to drink?
We'll have a bottle
of sancerre.
Actually, i drink red.
Trust me,
You'll love it.
So he was trying
to impress you
By showing you how
he can take charge.
I guess so.
Tell me about his watch.
It's a fake rolex.
You sure about that?
I know my knockoffs.
Clearly he was playing
with it, though,
'Cause he wanted you
to notice. I mean,
He wanted you to think
that it was real.
Garcia, are you ok?
I'm feeling really exposed.
You're doing just fine.
Just fine.
So you work
for the fbi.
- That's glamorous.
- Mm-Hmm.
If you want to call
14-Hour days
Cloistered in a small, dark room,
surrounded by violent images,
Glamorous, then hells yeah.
Absolutely. It's paris
in the twenties.
You work murder cases?
Mm-Hmm. 24/7.
I see.
That's the big-Time
right there.
You're like a cop
and big brother
All rolled into one.
I like to think of myself
As a tireless crusader
for world karma.
Right.
What about you?
Ah, i don't know.
School in new haven,
Law school in boston--
Cambridge, i guess,
technically.
It's all
one college town.
What kind of law
do you practice?
I was a city attorney.
But once you've had
a murder case dismissed
For judicial ineptitude
or a random collateral
estoppel,
Let's just say private practice starts
making a lot of sense.
People can get away
with murder
For other people's
incompetence.
Well, why am i
telling you this?
I'm sure you see it
all the time.
To karma.
City attorneys
don't try murder cases.
What?
He knows enough
to use legal terminology,
But he's not actually
a working lawyer.
I think we're looking at someone
who failed out of law school
Or didn't pass the bar.
Did garcia say if he gave
any details about the cases
- He was supposedly working?
- No specifics.
If he failed out of the system,
it could explain
Why he's got a working vocabulary
and not much more.
It could also
explain his anger.
Even in his lie,
he rails against
Other people's incompetence.
Well, he's clearly a narcissist.
The clothes, the watch,
the subtle hints
At where he went to school.
He's faking humility
When he's saying new haven
and cambridge
Instead of yale and harvard.
J.J., we need an analyst
Who can, uh,
put our information
Through the legal databases.
I'm on it.
Now, you sure another tech
is ok with me in her system?
We're kind of weird
about that.
We just need you to run
some bar association records.
Why doesn't she do it?
She's in the hospital.
You're talking about
the analyst who was shot.
That's right.
You know who hit her?
That's what we're hoping
to find out.
What?
We're the gatekeepers to a whole
lot of information, man.
It's enough to make us all
a little paranoid.
You know, i could have
done this at my computer.
First we need you to look up the name
james colby baylor
And see if it shows up
anywhere in the system.
Whoa.
What is it?
This system is insane.
It's completely linux-Based.
Open-Sourced programming.
You don't see this
in government systems,
I mean outside of, like,
switzerland.
James colby baylor.
Right. I get it.
Chop-Chop. Jeez.
Uh-Uh. Nothing.
All right, let's start with a list
of everyone in the area
Who either failed
the bar exam
Or was fired
from a large law firm
In the last 5 years.
What, are you serious?
That's got to be, like,
thousands of names.
Try narrowing it down to
anyone with the initials j.C.B.
He had monogrammed shirts.
Trust me, they ain't cheap.
Is there a problem?
This might be the coolest
girl i've ever met.
You've never
laid eyes on her.
Well, her gooey
is mind-Blowing.
The list.
Oh, that's weird.
Well, this isn't good.
What's hotch doing?
Right now i'm guessing
he's wishing
Anybody else was the leader
of this team.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
You know, i've had
better dates.
What's going on?
We found an encrypted file
on your computer.
Are you involved in something
that i need to know about?
No.
Hotch, what's going on?
Could this be connected
in any way to whoever shot you?
I don't think so.
I need the password.
Is this
really necessary?
Yes.
The password.
Gilman street.
Thank you.
They don't honestly think
garcia's a security risk, do they?
I don't know.
We've been ordered by internal affairs
to stop working the case.
What?
And until this is cleared up...
You've been suspended.
I'm sorry.
Right.
- What are you doing?
- I need to get out of here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Please, baby,
Listen to me.
We're gonna get it
straightened out.
I'm gonna find out
who did this to you.
Okay? I don't give a damn
what i.A. Wants me to do
Or doesn't want me to do,
but right now you need to rest.
But...one of
the last things i said
Before he shot me was,
"everything happens for a reason."
Derek, if i lose faith in that,
then nothing in my life makes sense.
I get that.
No, you don't.
Is this really
necessary?
It's protocol.
Yes, it's necessary.
Mr. Lynch here will do
an audit of her computer.
I will oversee
the investigation.
A federal employee
was just gunned down
And you make it seem like
investigating her is more important
Than finding out
who shot her.
Well, that's not true.
The police have jurisdiction,
and trust me,
I will offer them
the full force of the fbi
To solve this case.
With all due respect,
sir, the b.A.U. Is part of that force.
Look, i'm sorry. I realize
how hard this must be.
But?
But the first thing
you look at is victimology.
Correct?
The bureau needs to know
what she's involved in
And whether it has to do
with why she was shot.
She's not involved
in anything.
And you're certain of that.
Absolutely.
What do you know about how
she was recruited to the fbi?
After my parents died, i...
Kind of went off the rails
for a while.
I dropped out of cal tech.
I lived underground,
Basically.
But i kept teaching
myself code.
It was like the one thing
that kept me together.
The bureau keeps track
of computer hackers--
Ones who have the skill to
be either extremely useful
Or a potential menace.
So garcia
was on a watch list?
No. Watch lists are long.
I'm talking about only a handful of people
on the planet.
What did she do
to get on that list?
I'm afraid i'm not
at liberty to answer that.
So they
offered you a job?
Mm-Hmm.
Like frank abagnale.
The bureau figured
if you can't beat 'em,
Hire 'em.
Yeah. Something like that.
Garcia, what's on
the encrypted file?
I'm required to keep a record
of everything the team does.
And after my system got hacked
and elle got shot,
I just didn't want anyone else
to be able to get at you.
We'll talk to the doctor,
see if he'll clear you to leave.
Hi. I'm mike fleming.
I'm on till midnight.
Officer cranbeck
will be here after that, ok?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Come on,
let's get you inside.
Come on.
It washes off.
I promise.
I, um...
I would expect
nothing less.
You should be
flattered.
Not many people
are invited in off the grid.
Super-8?
Yeah.
I always imagined myself
fighting crime.
My parents were hippies.
I think it horrified them.
How old were you
when you lost them?
18. Drunk driver.
I volunteer once a week
To counsel family members
of murder victims.
Baby, you don't get enough
of this stuff at work?
I look at those crime scene
photos all day long.
I can't know that
those families are out there
Trying to cope
and not do something to help.
You do know it was stupid
to encrypt that file?
Yes, i know.
Old habits, i guess.
You need some rest.
You're right.
Go.
Be free, my love.
Hey. I'm not
going anywhere.
I'm fine. I got my
goon squad parked out front.
Goon squad
or no goon squad,
That couch right there
is gonna be my best friend
Until we find this guy.
Now leave it alone.
Ok.
But if you're thinking
of trying to take advantage of me...
Let me call my doctor
so he can revive me afterward.
Hey, silly girl.
Hmm?
I love you.
You know that, right?
I love you, too.
Go to bed.
Can i help you
with something?
I need you to stop
right there.
Stop--
Garcia!
What's going on?!
Stay right there.
Stay there!
Come here.
Come here. Come with me.
Get in the corner.
Garcia, you listen to me.
Take this gun.
I don't believe in guns.
Ok, trust me, they are very real.
Take it.
All right, you keep your finger
off that trigger.
If somebody walks through
that door,
You grab ahold of it
and you squeeze.
Fire, you hear me?
- Morgan!
- Stay there!
107 leavenworth.
I got an officer down.
Repeat--Officer down.
Send me an ambulance.
All right,
this is dispatch.
We copy your request. Ambulance.
Aah! Aah!
Garcia! It's me.
Don't shoot. It's me.
It's morgan, baby.
Why is this
happening to me?
I don't know.
What's going on?
I don't know. This guy's
getting seriously bold,
And i can guarantee
it's not over.
You ok?
I don't know what
he wants from me.
Could you know something
about him?
I don't know.
Maybe you have
something he wants?
I don't know who he is.
I'm so scared.
I know.
Just so you know,
Your office called
cato tell me
We're supposed to
run point on this.
They don't want you
working the case.
We're just here
to comfort a friend.
I'm about to have to tell
a good friend's wife
Her husband got murdered.
I don't care
what your office says.
Any help you can give
is good in my book.
Thanks.
I'm sick of being
behind this guy.
We gotta end this.
Hey. Did you get
a look at him?
Nothing solid.
Garcia, we need to get you
back to the hospital.
- No.
- You know what?
You should still be there.
We need her someplace safe.
I feel safe
with all of you.
We can take you
to the b.A.U.
Garcia?
Ok?
Get in the corner.
When we were at dinner...
They wanted to seat us
by a window,
But he insisted on sitting
at the worst table in the place.
And he sat with his back
to the corner.
Detective.
Can you clear the room
for just a minute?
I got a dead cop
downstairs.
I consider this
part of the crime scene.
I know.
Just a couple of minutes.
Do what you gotta do.
Thank you.
Tell us about the car.
Why?
Just go with him.
You said it was white,
4-Door, american. What else?
That's it.
It was just a car.
No, come on, think.
Anything. Go back.
The seat belt was buckled
behind his back.
Why does that matter?
It wasn't a rental.
It was for surveillance.
Agents don't wear
seat belts.
They need to get out
in a hurry.
All right,
let's cut the crap.
You need to be straight with us.
Right now.
Look at me, not them.
I'm not hiding anything.
You got shot. Most people
get shot for a reason.
Eyes here!
Ease up, rossi.
You got a roomful
of people here
Willing to believe that an fbi agent
has tried to kill you.
We need to know everything
you do on company time
That we don't know about.
- What?
- Come on, man.
- It's nothing bad.
- Spit it out!
It's ju--
I counsel victims' families
And they know where i work,
so sometimes they ask me
To look into cases for them.
What does that mean?
It just means
that the cases,
The unsolved ones,
i tag them,
So whoever's
investigating them
Knows that the fbi considers them
a priority.
You're not authorized
to do that.
I know. I was just
trying to help.
But whoever's working those cases
thinks you're watching them.
I just wanted to put pressure on them
so that they don't slide.
How many cases
are we talking about?
I don't know. 7, 8 maybe.
I need to get into
my system.
You can't.
You're suspended.
Wait a minute, garcia.
On your date, you said
this guy was pressing you
To find out if you were
working murder cases.
Hotch, we gotta look
at those files.
I told you, i'm sick of this
jagoff being in front of us.
Dave's right.
We'll go back to the b.A.U.
Morgan, reid, prentiss,
you stay here and make sure
No one forgets
to log out of the system.
Garcia should
not have access.
Understood.
What the hell?
Oh, no, you don't.
I do not have time
for this.
All right, no chance.
Huh.
And yet...
Oh, you want to play?
What is she doing
in there?
Do you really want to know?
Oh, no.
You are not seriously
trying to backhack me?
Oh, nicely played.
Ok.
New plan.
Well, now, this is just
way too easy.
Yeah, that's right.
Chase me.
I thought you had skills.
Oh, boy.
Have fun getting out
of the wormhole.
Those are all the cases
i flagged.
Ok.
Everybody take a copy.
We need to see
if any of the agents overlap
In all of the cases.
Now...
What were you looking for?
There aren't any agents
working on these cases.
But the same deputy
was a first responder in 3.
What's the name?
Jason clark battle.
What are the cases?
Uh, all 3 were drive-Bys,
At close range,
Shot with a revolver.
- Is that him?
- Yeah.
He's been honored twice
as a hero.
So why is he
stuck at deputy?
Because even to his superiors,
Something was off about him.
Makes sense.
The showy clothes,
The subtle bragging.
He presents himself
As a prominent attorney
when he's actually
Just a deputy sheriff.
Underapprecied in the world
And overappreciated
in his own mind.
I don't understand.
I think you may have stumbled
upon an angel of death.
I thought those are nurses
who put people out of their misery.
Yeah, that's one model.
The other is someone
Who puts people at risk
in order to save them.
So he shot them
so that he could save them?
Yeah. And when he couldn't,
he made it look like a random murder.
It's how he was able
to be the first responder.
It's called
hero homicide complex.
It's most commonly found
in firemen who set fires
In order to save the day.
Garcia.
You flagged these cases.
He thought you were onto him.
I wasn't.
But you're the only person
in the world
Who was gonna make the connection.
In his mind,
He had to eliminate you.
Deputy battle, please.
Ok, what time
is his shift over?
No, no message. Thank you.
Ok, he didn't sign out
to a location.
His shift is over at midnight.
Until then, i do not want this guy
knowing that we are onto him.
- Why?
- What's the profile say?
He'll keep getting bolder
trying to cover his tracks.
And if that doesn't work,
he'll die shooting.
Great.
Thanks for having me in.
Oh, we want you to know
we take bureau interference
With local law enforcement
seriously.
I appreciate that.
It's good to know we're on the same team.
Mr. Lynch, i need you
to access some files.
Yeah, i'm kind of busy.
We'll step in here.
It'll just take a second.
Deputy.
Jason battle.
B-A-T-T-L-E.
I just don't understand
why one of your analysts
Would be looking into
my murder cases.
To be honest, the woman
we're talking about is currently
Under investigation.
You don't think
she could be involved
In a killing somehow,
do you?
We haven't made
any determinations.
Wouldn't it be easier
to just let me speak to her?
I'm afraid
she's in the hospital.
This the woman
who was shot?
Yeah.
Every cop in the city's
working overtime,
But they can't come up
with anything.
Think she might be
dirty?
Like i said, we haven't
made any determinations.
Well, until you do,
is it possible
To remove my files
from your system
For security's sake?
Yeah, we can do that.
Mr. Lynch?
Yes, sir.
Ok, that's funky.
What's going on?
He just logged in
to my system.
There's a link up on my screen.
Maybe it's a mistake.
No. He's good.
He's not careless.
Could he be trying
to show you something?
He could be baiting me.
What do you mean?
If he's with internal affairs,
And i follow his lead,
whosever login i use could lose their job.
What's your gut say?
He's a hacker.
We have a code.
You trust it?
I have to.
Do it.
Make contact.
It's the b.A.U.
God, that's him.
Hotch, it's morgan.
He's in the b.A.U.
Deputy sheriff, mid-Bullpen,
just past my desk.
Got him?
I got him.
Don't let him know
we're onto him.
He's a classic narcissist
With a hero homicide complex,
and he's spiraling.
If you let him know we're onto him,
he's gonna start shooting.
He's trying to prove to himself
He's smarter
than all of us.
It's too crowded in here.
We can't get an angle on him
Without putting people
in jeopardy.
We gotta slip somebody
in behind him.
Can you get us the cameras
outside the bullpen?
Is there a problem?
No, i'm sorry.
It's--It's not my system.
It's taking me longer.
Oh, my girl.
Come on, j.J.,
pick up the phone.
Pick it up.
J.J., it's morgan.
Listen to me.
Listen to me
very carefully.
Okey-Doke.
You're sure my files
are wiped off the system?
Yes, sir.
All right,
i'll keep you updated
On our investigation.
He knows they know.
This is crazy.
We gotta get over there.
- I'm going with you.
- No, you are not.
You do not have time
to argue.
You're a cop.
You know this isn't
gonna end well.
You're standing
in the middle of the fbi.
You think i'm afraid
of the fbi?
I know how this
is gonna end, and so do you.
I'm a decorated officer.
That's right.
And this is not how
you want to be remembered.
You're in control here.
You write the ending.
Your choice.
The best minds in the fbi.
You can't even stop me.
He's clear!
It's really over?
Yeah.
It's really over.
Now can we please
get you back to the hospital?
I...
Oh, don't worry about
your reinstatement papers.
He'll sign them as soon as
his hand stops shaking.
Hey.
I never wanted you to have
to do something like that.
I never even blinked.
You do whatever it takes
to, uh...
Protect your family.
How's garcia?
She'll make sense of it.
And you?
How's your faith?
Day to day.
I think someone's
watching you.
Do you believe everything
happens for a reason?
You.
You're good.
You're better.
Kevin lynch.
Penelope.
ææàãğü×öä»×é
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
»¶ó­¼óèë