prevIously On Criminal Minds...
I Met A Guy.
I'm Asking You Out,
Garcia.
Hey, Garcia.
I've Been Thinking About
Doing This All Night.
I Just Need You To Run
Some Bar Association Records.
Why Doesn't She Do It?
She's In The Hospital.
Whoa. This Might Be
The Coolest
Girl I've Ever Met.
Her Gooey Is Mind-blOwing.
I'm Not Going Anywhere.
This Couch Right Here Is
Gonna Be My Best Friend
Until We Find This Guy.
Now Leave It Alone.
Ok.
Kevin Lynch.
Penelope.
You're Good.
You're Better.
los angeles, california
No One Sees
True Night...
What's Really There
In The Dark
It's Not That
They Can't See,
They Simply Don't.
They Feel
An Elemental Force
That Scares Them Into The Deepest Reaches
Of Their Minds...
But They Refuse To See
The Actual Source...
Something Wane Them,
Just Out Of Their Reach.
Something Cold
And Frightening.
Something Inhuman.
These Are Victims 6 And 7
Within A 2-Week Span.
All Killed With
A Bladed Weapon?
Yeah.
The Attacks Are Getting
Progressively Worse.
The First 5
Were Lone Victims.
He's Getting Bolder.
And More Vicious.
Tell L.A.
We Can Be There By 9:30.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
CRIMINAL MINDS 310
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译: 校对:
时间轴:迫榨二人组
I Can Open My Own Door.
Not On My Watch.
Now, Will You Zip It?
What The Hell?
What?
What Happened In Here?
Oh, What, The Mess?
I Got That.
Partially.
I Guess The Guy Who Was
In Here Going Through Your System--
- Kevin Lynch.
- YEAH.
He Made A Little Bit Of A Mess.
Don't Worry About It.
He Changed Everything.
Changed Everything?
What Are You Talking About?
He Adjusted The--The...
Oh...Forget It.
It'll Be...
Go. You Need To Get
To L.A.
No, Listen, I'm Gonna
Stick Around For A While.
I Think You Might Need Me.
Stick Around?
Yeah.
The Team Can Handle
One Case Without Me.
They'll Be Fine.
Honey, I Know You Love Me,
But The Prospect Of You
Whirling Around Here
Trying To Fix This
Is Actually More Frightening
Than Getting Shot.
Garcia, Are You Sure?
I Am Completely Fine.
- Look. Full Range Of Motion.
- Stop, Stop, Stop.
- No Pain. Uhh! Uhh!
Will You Stop It
With The "Uhh." Stop.
Go.
You Know I'm Just
A Phone Call Away.
Thank You.
Go.
Oh!
Kevin Lynch,
You May Be Cute...
But If You Ever
Mess With My Stuff Again...
I...
"Superman Is, After All,
an alien Life Form.
"He Is Simply
The Acceptable Face
Of Invading Realities."
Author Clive Barker.
What Should I Say?
I Don't Know.
Just Say Something.
Ohh...
Why'd You Hang Up?
I Hate This.
It's Not That Big A Deal.
I Don't Want To Leave
A Lame Voicemail Message.
All You Have To Do
Is Say Your Name.
Like Yours?
What's Wrong With Mine?
Come On,
I Want Something Fun.
You're A Writer.
You Promised To Help.
All Right, All Right.
Why Don't You Say
You Can't Answer The Phone
Because You're Outu'
Living Your Life.
You Hate It.
I Love It.
Hey, This Is Vickie.
I Can't Come To The Phone Right Now
'Cause I'm Out Living My Life.
Leave It At The Beep.
My Hero.
Quid Pro Quo?
Oh, I Love It
When You Speak Latin.
Wait Till You Hear
My French.
Jonny!
I Know You're In There,
Jonny.
Come On, Jonny, Open Up!
What?
Oh. I Don't Check On You
For A Few Months
And You Fall Apart.
What Do You Want?
Are You Serious?
You Have A Book Signing
In An Hour.
I'm Not Going
To A Book Signing.
Uh-Uh.
No, No, No, No.
I'm Your Agent,
And We Got An Advance
From The Publisher, Baby,
And It's A Big One.
Give It Back.
Come On, Jonny.
These Are Your Fans.
They Schlepped To A Gallery
And Camped There.
All Night.
Now, I Don't Know
If You Noticed,
But It Rained On Them.
A Lot.
Ah Ha Ha. Check And Mate.
Get Dressed.
I Got A Coffee
Waiting For You
In The Car.
What's This?
It's Something
I'm Working On.
What Do You Mean?
That Sentence Needs
An Explanation?
What About Blue 6?
I'm Doing Something New.
Blue's Due In 2 Weeks.
Not Gonna Happen.
Not Gonna Happen?
I'm Not Feeling It Anymore.
Not Feeling It.
Stop Repeating
Everything I Say!
Jonny, Stop It.
You Have Commitments.
You're A Professional.
What The Hell Is This,
Anyway?
All This Blood
And Decapitations.
When Did Your Art
Get So Violent?
I'm Working On Something New.
I'll Call The Publisher.
Seriously, Not All Pedestrians
Have The Right Of Way, Ok?
We're Already Late!
My Headache Isn't Gonna Get Any Better
With You Screaming.
I Got To Admit, Jonny,
The Art Is Amazing.
Violent As Hell, But...
Amazing.
This Character--
What's His Name? Night?
That's The Whole Name,
Just Night?
Not Very Catchy.
What About, Uh,
Night Man Or i don't know...
True Knight.
With A "K."
No "K."
- I'm Just Saying--
- No "K"!
Message Received.
I'm Just Asking Questions
Here, Jon.
You Know How We Kind Of
Work These Things Out Together?
You Think
We Work Together?
I'm The Talent,
You're The Leech.
What Is Wrong
With You Today?
Ha Ha!
Are You Gonna Work All Night?
I Have A Deadline.
I'm Hungry.
How Does Someone
So Small Eat So Much?
Let's Go Get Some Jerky.
- It's Midnight.
- So?
You Really Want To Go Out
In The Middle Of The Night
For Jerky?
Teriyaki Jerky.
Hurry Up.
Will You Hurry Up?
Seriously, Would You Just
Hurry The Hell Up!
I Swear, If We're Not There
In 5 Minutes--
Whoa.
Something Big Happened.
Seriously, This Is Huge.
Should Have Listened To Me.
It Wouldn't Have Saved
That Much Time, Reid. Let It Go.
The Interchange Between
The 405 And The 101 Freeways
Is Consistently Rated
The Worst Interchange
In The Entire World.
Why Do You Know That?
It's A Government Report.
So What?
So You Work
For The Government.
What, You Don't Read
The Reports?
On Traffic Patterns
In A City
2,500 Miles
From Where I Live?
2,295 Miles.
Don't Make Me Smack You In Front Of
All These People.
I'm Grady, Lapd.
Derek Morgan.
Dr. Reid.
The Rest Of The Team's
In An Suv Behind Us.
Yeah, Stuck In Traffic.
Uh, So You Had
2 More Victims Last Night?
They Were Discovered A Little After 3:30
By A Cleaning Crew
Finishing Up
In The Building.
So That's 7 Victims
Over The Past 2 Weeks.
Bodies Are In The Alley.
What's Left Of Them.
Same Victimology?
We Don't Have Positive I.D.
On Either One Of Them Yet,
But The Clothing Fits.
You Really Think This
Is Only One Guy, Huh?
The Level Of Overkill
Suggests An Unsub
In A Psychotic Break.
Multiple Unsubs In Violent
Psychotic Breaks
Operating In The Exact Same
Location
Is Exceedingly Unlikely.
Yeah, It's Probably One Guy.
* Ooh, La  *
* She Was Such
A Good Girl To Me *
* Ooh, La... *
He Was Supposed
To Be Here At 1 P.M.
It's 1:11, Gus.
I Just Talked To His Agent.
They're In Traffic, Ok?
Maybe They Should Have
Left Earlier.
Look, You Want The Agent's
Number So You Can Call
And Tell 'Em Off?
I'm Just Saying.
A Schedule's A Schedule.
It's Probably
The Police Activity Holding Them Up.
It's All Over
The Scanner.
There Were Some Murders
Near Here Last Night.
Murders? Plural?
2 Bodies.
Robbery-Homicide's Been There All Night.
R-H Only Comes Out
For The Major Cases.
If Jonny Mchale
Doesn't Show, I Promise You,
I Will Take My Considerable
Business Elsewhere.
You Can Leave
Right Now, Milo.
Seriously, Where Would You Go,
Hero World?
They Never Get Anything
Day Of Release.
It's Always Over--
I Present To You...
The One And Only...
Jonny Mchale.
Jonny!
Jonny, I Love Blue!
Hey, This Way, Jonny!
- No.
- Jonny.
Jonny!
Bobby.
That Was The Personal
Appearance?
Milo, Seriously, Leave.
They Hate Me
At Hero World.
Seriously.
Jonny?
Jonny. Jonny?
Come On, Come On,
Come On, Come On.
Hey, This Is Vickie.
I Can't Come To The Phone
Right Now
'Cause I'm Out Living My Life.
Leave It At The Beep.
Vickie, Call Me, Please.
Just Call Me Back.
I'm Sorry.
- Uhh!
- Uh!
Oh, My God.
Oh, My God!
He Jumped Right Out
In Front Of Me.
There Was Nothing--
There Was Nothing I Could Do.
Oh, My God.
Can You Get Up?
You Ok? Let Me Help You.
- You Ok? Are You Ok?
- Can You Get Up?
Aah!
- Stop! Stop!
- what's wrong with you?
Let Go Of Him!
Aah! Jasper!
Jasper. Oh, My God.
Jasper!
You Son Of A Bitch!
It Was Your Fault!
You Ran Right Out
In Front Of Us!
It Was Your Fault!
Baby, Are You Ok?
Jasper.
I'd Say It's Definitely
Our Guy.
Same Victimology.
Hotch...
This Guy's Getting
Off-The-Charts Brutal.
Do You Know That
A Domestic Cat
Loose In A Normal
Neighborhood
Is The Equivalent
Of A Small-Scale
Ecological Disaster?
Excuse Me?
They'll Kill Anything
They Can--
Bugs, Rodents, Birds,
Other Cats,
Small Dogs If Possible.
Anything.
That Got Something
To Do With This?
An Unsub In A Violent
Psychotic Break Is Worse.
You Ran right Out
In Front Of Us!
Stop!
What?
you're blind or ???
This Is A Crime Scene,
Moron.
Go Around.
Oh, Careful There.
Hurt Yourself?
How'd That Happen?
I Think I Fell.
I Was Running.
Are They Dead?
Looks Like It.
Are You Sure?
My Name's David. Rossi.
What's Yours?
Jon Mchale.
Live Around Here?
Jonny!
Where'd You Go, Man?
What Happened To You?
I Need To Get Out Of Here.
Come On.
The Car's Right Here.
Seriously,
Are You All Right?
I Think She's Mad.
Who?
She Won't Call Back.
I Left Tons Of Messages
Every Day.
Who, Jonny?
Vickie!
Jonny--
I Have To Tell Her
I'm Sorry.
Just Rest, Jonny,
All Right?
It'll Be Ok.
Hey, This Is Vickie.
I Can't Come To
The Phone Right Now 'Cause--
Mmm. I Love Jerky.
More Than Anyone
I've Ever Known.
Do You Love It?
Love Isn't Really
The Word I Would Use.
My Mother Loves It, Too.
Think I Got It From Her?
I Highly Doubt
Something Like That's Genetic.
It's Probably More
Environmental.
I Wonder If The Baby
Will Love Jerky.
When Did You Find Out?
For Sure
This Afternoon,
But I Already
Kind Of Knew.
Oh, God.
If It's A Boy, I Want
To Name Him Jonny,
After His Daddy.
Oh, Vickie.
I Know A...Great Therapist.
She's Helped Me Through
A Lot Of Dark Times.
Go Away.
She's Really Good.
I Can Get You
An Appointment.
Leave.
Ok.
We Can...
Go To The Comic Shop
Some Other Day, All Right?
No.
Jonny, They're Your Fans.
Look, It's Not Your
Problem Anymore, okay?
You're Fired.
What?
Get The Hell Out.
But You're Gonna
Need Me To...
Help You To Get
This New Book On Its Feet.
Get Out Of My House!
Go!
Uhh!
Hey, This Is Vickie.
I Can't Come To The Phone
Right Now 'Cause I'm Out Living My Life.
Leave It At The Beep.
Uhh!
Just Take Me Home.
So, This Area
Is More Or Less
The Geographical Center
Of The Scenes.
Detective Brady's
Putting Together A Taskforce,
So We Can Canvass These 3 Blocks
In Both Directions.
Any Idea How Many
Residents That Covers?
Garcia Estimates
Close To 3,000.
A Lot Of These Buildings
Are Single Room Occupancy.
High Turnover Rate.
So It's Transient.
There Aren't A Lot Of Records.
- Press Conference Went Well.
- good.
I Think The Media
Understands
What We're Looking For.
Should Be On Local
Affiliates Now.
Hopefully We Can Thin Out
The Suspect List.
Ohh!
Oh, My God.
Aah! Aah!
I Wonder If The Baby
Will Love Jerky.
Baby?
When Did You Find Out?
For Sure This Afternoon.
But I Already
Kind Of Knew.
If It's A Boy, I Want
To Name Him Jonny,
After His Daddy.
Vickie...
I Love You So Much.
Wait. Wait, Wait, Wait.
Oh, My God.
I Promise First Thing
In The Morning
I Will Buy A Big, Big Ring.
Jonny,
You Don't Have To.
Vickie Wright,
Will You Marry Me?
Vickie?
Jonny.
Stop! Aah!
Aah!
Vickie?
Same Type Of Victims?
All Gang-Bangers.
Good Riddance,
You Ask Me.
Who's That?
It's Benson.
He's From
The Gang Taskforce.
If Anyone Had
A Violent End Coming...
What's The Scene Like?
It's Actually
The Gang Leader's
Personal House.
Guy Named Glen Hill.
Street Name Is Reaper.
Guess Why.
Only Benson And Me
Have Been Inside.
I Didn't Do Much.
I Kind Of Backed Out The Minute I Saw Him.
How Many?
6. 4 Inside, 2 Outside.
No Survivors At All?
Never Thought
I Could Feel Sorry
For These Gang-Banging
Sons Of Bitches.
We'll Be There
In A Few Minutes.
He Actually Went To
The Gang-Bangers' House.
The Other Victims Were In
Alleys And Dark Corners.
It Could Be The Unsub
Was Initially Just Defending Himself.
Like Bernie Goetz,
Riding The Subways With A Gun,
Waiting For Someone
To Confront Him.
Except He's Seeking
Them Out Now O
Because Psychotics
In A Break Always Devolve.
Only A Matter Of Time
Before He Becomes Dangerous
To Those Closer To Him.
No! No! Stop!
Vickie?
Ohh.
Oh!
Where's Vickie?
Jonny?
You Scared Me.
Do You Need Something,
Sweetheart?
Oh, You Hurt Yourself.
Where did Vickie Go?
I'm Sorry.
She Was On The Fire Escape.
- Who?
- Vickie, My Fiancee.
You Have A Fiancee?
She Was On
The Fire Escape.
When?
Just Before I Came In.
Oh, Caesar Was Out There.
I Saw Her Come In Here.
Jonny, Nobody
Came In Here.
- don't lie to me.
- I'm Not Lying To You.
Where Is She?
No!
T.S.K?
Twenty-Third Street Killers.
Looks Like They Tried
To Fight Back.
They Failed.
Are we Sure This Isn't
Some Kind Of Gang
Retaliation Kind Of Thing?
You're On The Taskforce.
Ever See A Street gang
Do Something Like This?
Yeah, But...
One Guy?
One Guy With A Weapon, Psychotic Rage,
Surprise On His Side.
Yeah, Just Look At Any School
Or Workplace Shooting.
So What Do We Do Now?
Ready Doing It.
An Unsub In A Psychotic Rage
Stands Out.
Agent Jareau's Got The Media
Playing The Press conference every hour
She's Putting The Profile
Out To The Public.
Someone In This Man's World
Knows He's In Crisis.
Hopefully They'll
Recognize The Description.
Hotch.
You Need To See This.
Bitch! I Know
She Was Down There.
I Saw Her!
Oh, God.
Jonny?
Suhh!
Uhh!
- No!
- Lapd Hotline.
Yes, Sir.
Right.
I Got One Says He Thinks
It's God's Mighty Vengeance.
Could Use
Some Help Down Here.
Lapd Tip Line.
Agent Jareau?
We Have Some People Out Front
You Need To Talk To.
Ma'am, Could You Hold,
Please?
They Saw
Your Press Conference.
Uh, Detective, Line 3.
Fbi!
What Did I Do?
What Did I Do?!
Uh! Ow! Wh'd I Do?
i haven't done anything.
There's Been
A Big Mistake Here.
Then It'll Work
Itself Out, Jonny.
I Just Dracomic Books.
I'm An Artist.
That Guy Out There, Bobby,
I Fired Him.
He's Probably Just Mad.
He's Not Mad At You
At All.
Then Why Would He Say
That I Did Something?
That's Why He's Here,
Right?
You Remember I Read
You Your Rights?
Jonny, Look At Me.
Tell Me That You Understand
That You Can Have A Lawyer Present
Before You Speak
To Anybody.
I Don't Want A Lawyer.
Tell Me
That You Understand.
I Understand.
Somebody's Gonna Be In
To Talk To You Real Soon.
There's Been
A Big Mistake Here.
I Haven't Done Anything!
That's A Lot.
There's More.
Did You Find
The Murder Weapon?
Didn't Need To.
Why Is That?
Mr. Mchale Is A Very Sick
Young Man.
This Is Exactly--
Yeah.
Can You Go Get The Mug Shot
Of Glen Hill?
Yeah. Give Me A Minute.
Is That All From
Jonny's Studio?
Yes, Sir.
He's Not A Killer.
He's Just Sick.
You Did The Right Thing
By Coming Here, Mr. Kim.
Now, You Said You Hadn't
Seen Him For A Couple Months
Before Today?
Yeah.
I, Uh...
You Get Busy, You Know?
There Was No Reason To...
You Know...Go There.
That's Glen Hill.
He's Missing.
You Think I Know
Where He Is?
6 Months Ago
He And His Gang
Victimized You
And Your Girlfriend, Right?
What?
They Attacked You
On The Street.
No.
And You Couldn't Identify
Any Of Them
After You Got Out
Of The Hospital.
This Is Crazy.
Hey, How You Feeling,
Baby Girl?
I--I Just Can't Seem
To Get My Chair Adjusted
Just Right Again,
But...
Other Than That,
I'm Mortified.
Mortified?
Please Tell Me The Unsub
Isn't Jonny Mchale, the graphic novelist.
don't Tell Me You're
The Grapa Fan Of This Guy.
Oh, My God, yes.
He's A Genius.
Well, Sweetheart, you should see what he thought
The Victims Looked Like
Before He Killed Them.
Sometimes For An Artist,
The Only Difference
Between Insanity And Genius
Is Success.
I Believe You're Suffering
A Post-Traumatic Form a Psychotic break.
Psychotic?
You Have Been
For Weeks.
Come On.
It's Possible
You Don't Even Know.
How Could I Not Know?
That's A Page From Something
I'm Working On.
We Know.
This Is A Murder Scene
From 2 Nights Ago.
You Were There.
Yesterday.
I Talked To You.
We Have Photos Of You.
Wait. This Is Real?
These Are Members Of
The Twenty-Third Street Killers.
Glen Hill's Gang.
And There Were
6 Gang Members Murdered In That House
Last Night.
This Was On Your Drawing Board
When We Arrested You.
No, No, This Can't Be.
It Doesn't Make Any Sense.
This House Belongs
To Glen Hill.
There Was A Trail Of Blood
Leading Out The Back Door.
We Believe That You Took
Mr. Hill With You When You Left.
Is This His Phone?
It On The Floor
When We Took Him Down.
Looks Like All The Calls He Makes
Are To The Same Number.
Dial It.
Maybe It's Somebody
Who Can Help Us.
Or At Least Help Him.
Hey, This Is Vickie.
I Can't Come To The Phone
Right Now 'Cause I'm Out
Living My Life.
Leave It At The Beep.
Vickie?
Vickie.
That Was His Girlfriend.
All These Calls Were Made
Within The Last 2 Days.
Sometimes What An Unsub Does
Actually Makes Sense.
These Are Just Drawings--
My Imagination.
Severe Ptsd Is Not Uncommon
For Victims Of Violent Crime.
Victims?
You're Bleeding.
It Looks Like
A Grazing Gunshot Wound.
did they Shoot You
Last Night?
Look, Stop It.
I Would Know If I'd Been--
--
A Victim.
yOu Remember
Being In The Hospital?
I Was Never--
That's Your Medical Report.
They Cut You Open,
Mr. Mchale.
Call Ahead.
We Got...
You Were Nearly
Evisceraevis
They Said It Was a Miracle You Lived.
Miracle?
You Think Living
Was A Miracle?
All Your Drawings Reflect
Actual Crime Scenes.
All Of Them But One.
Where Is This Crime Scene,
Jonny?
- Is This Glen Hill?
- Where Is He?
Where's Glen Hill?
Aah!
No! No!
You Don't Know
What's Out There!
No One Knows
About The Night!
We Don't Want
To Hurt You, Jonny.
It's Ok, Son.
It's Ok.
I Couldn't Help Her.
Jonny, You Don't
Have To...
Vickie Wright,
Will You Marry Me?
Vickie?
Jonny.
Answer Him, Baby.
The Man Ask you
A Question.
We Don't Want
Any Trouble, Guys.
Don't Much Matter
What You Want.
Look, I've Got A Little Bit Of Money.
It's Not A Lot--
Answer Him!
Yes, Yes,
I'll Marry You.
It's Ok, Vickie.
It's Ok.
See, Bro? You Got More
Than You Thought.
You Got A Fiancee.
- No! No, Jonny!
- - No!
Jonny! Aah!
- Get Off Me!
- Jonny!
Help! Stop!
Get Off Me!
You're Not Gonna
Want To Miss This.
They Made Me Watch.
It Can Help You
If We Can Tell The Court
That You Told Us
Where Glen Hill Is.
They Made Me Watch.
I Know. I Know.
They're Animals.
You Were Sick. You Didn't
Know What You Were Doing.
Where's Glen Hill,
Jonny?
You're Not Gonna
Want To Miss This.
Aah!
Just Leave It Alone
Until I Get There.
Hey. Hey. Hard-Head.
Don't Make Me Spank You
When I Get Back.
Don't Listen To Him, Garcia.
He's All Talk. Ow!
J.J., He Just Hit Me.
You Boys Behave
Or I Will Ground You Both.
Is That One
Of Jonny Mchale's Books?
Yeah, It's, Uh,
It's Called Blue.
It's About A Girl
Who Thinks She's A Real Human Being, Right?
But It Turns Out She's A Robot
That Was Built By Her Uncle.
So It's Pinocchio.
Yeah,
It Is Like Pinocchio,
Only, Uh, Set In A High School
In Outer Space.
Oh, By The Way, What
Happened To Vickie's Phone?
Phone?
The One That Jonny
Kept Calling, With Her Message On It?
Oh, We Gave Them Both
Back To Him.
You Know, I Couldn't Imagine
Having Nothing Left
Of Someone But A Voice Message.
I Think I'd Never Stop
Listening To It.
Yeah, It's Sad.
Hey, Did You Know
That Carlo Lorenzini,
The Guy That Wrote
Pinocchio,
Was Said To Be Obsessed
With The Human Nose?
- As A Matter Of Fact,
- Wow.
pinocchio Wasn't Even
The First Character--
Interesting. Coffee?
I'm All Right. Thank You,
Though, For Asking.
Something Wrong?
He's The First Unsub
I've Worked
Who Wasn't A Bad Guy.
You Know?
6 Months Ago,
Jonny Mchale Was Just
A Regular Person.
Every Unsub Is Ill
On some Level.
Most Can't Help
What They Do
Any More Than Jonny Could.
But He Went
From Successful Writer And Artist
To Brutal Killer
In 6 Months.
He Suffered
An Unbelievable Tragedy.
I Know.
I Get It.
So What's Bugging You?
It Just Makes Me Wonder...
Are We All Capable Of Becoming
Something Like That?
Life Is A Hell Of A Thing
To Happen To A Person.
You Really Don't
Have To Do This.
Woman, Will You Hush.
I Can Do It Myself.
I Just Can't Grip Anything Too Tight Yet,
And When I Tried To Do It,
It Kept Falling--
Will You Sit
Your Motormouth Down.
Oh...See, Now,
That's Perfect.
Yeah?
Totally.
Well, There You Go,
My Sweet Lady.
My Hero.
I'm Nobody's Hero.
Mmm!
Hey, Do You Know
Who Frank Miller Is?
Frank Miller. Um...
It Sounds Familiar.
Unsub?
No.
Graphic Novelist.
300? Sin City?
Oh. Right, Right, Right.
Cool Movies.
Anyway...
He Said Something Once
And It Makes Me Think Of You.
"The Noir Hero
Is A Knight
"In Blood-Caked Armor.
"He's Dirty,
"And He Does His Best
To Deny The Fact
That He's A Hero
The Whole Time."
Hey, This Is Vickie.
I Can't Come
To The Phone Right Now
'Cause I'm Out
Living My Life.
Leave It At The Beep.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入