Previously on "Ugly Betty"...
We're with immigration
and customs enforcement.
Mr. Suarez,
you're under arrest.
We're having a party up on 25 with
human resources if you're free.
Well, I--I'd love to go,
Henry, but--
- But you have a boyfriend.
- Yeah, I do.
Marc, can I have
some privacy please?
Come on, Willie.
We don't have any secrets,
not anymore.
Come work for my magazine.
You'll have your own
assistant within a year.
She told me about the job offer.
I would never stand in your way.
You didn't grow up wanting
to be my assistant.
# It's a marshmallow world #
# in the winter #
# When the snow comes... #
Making a list?
Checking it twice?
A list?
You know, naughty or nice.
Most people around here fit
into the first category,
but, you, Betty,
you're always nice.
No, it's just Daniel's expense report.
I'm done. Here.
# That's how it goes #
# whenever it snows #
# The world is
your snowball... #
No way. 8,479?
That's the exact number of
stars visible from earth...
on an ideal night.
- How do you--
- Just something I know.
Hey.
Is that mistletoe?
No, it's just holly.
# In winter, #
# it's a marshmallow world #
Wow.
You know what, Betty?
You're just the girl
I've been looking for.
What time is it?
Oh, my god.
I'm gonna miss my plane.
I'm gonna miss you.
It's been an
amazing three weeks.
I know.
It's all been sort of intense.
Actually, I've been meaning
to talk to you about that.
I think we should take a
breather while I'm gone.
A breather?
What are you talking about?
Well, time to cool off, apart--
just to make sure
all this is real.
Oh, I know it's real, Sofia.
I love you.
Oh, Daniel,
what do you know from love?
Your heart racing...
palms sweating...
can barely breathe
when you see me?
Actually, yeah.
All of that.
Well, that's not love.
That is hormones, infatuation,
good sex.
Look, this isn't just
about sex, Sofia.
Although, it has
been pretty good.
- Right?
- Daniel.
Come on,
I can see a life with you, Sofia.
Okay.
If this is all real, prove it.
Why don't you see other
women while I'm gone?
I'm giving you the green light.
I'm serious.
And if you don't get sweaty palms
and all that when you're with them,
then maybe this is real.
I'm not gonna cheat on you
just to prove I love you.
That's-- that's crazy.
Don't think about
it as cheating.
Think  about it as
proving your theory.
See, I need you to convince me
that there's only one woman
that you feel this way about--
me.
It was just a dream, girl.
Don't get too freaked out by it.
But I barely even know Henry.
I-I don't get it.
I have a boyfriend.
Did I ever tell you about
my Jose Mendoza dreams?
Ew. That pimply guy who
owns the bakery on 85th?
He was really into the Herbalux
digestive tonics. Don't judge.
Anyway, about a month ago,
I had this dream.
We were going at it in this
big bowl of cake batter.
Never mind.
That's not the point.
Anyway, the point is,
do you see us dating now?
No, of course not.
You know why?
Because it was just a dream,
and dreams don't mean anything.
Yeah, but Henry isn't Jose.
It--it's different,
and well, we did go on a date once.
Well, lunch.
Stop. You go to the Pro Buy party with
Walter tonight and just forget about it.
Hilda, I kissed Henry.
In your dream.
As long as you don't actually
do anything, it's harmless.
Betty, we're all tempted
sometimes, right?
Just avoid this Henry guy,
and everything will be fine.
Justin! Honey, let's go!
- Hi.
That girl has the vocal
cords of a large cat.
I heard that!
And the ears of whatever
animal hears best.
A dolphin.
It's just something I know.
Dad, did you check in with
the immigration people today?
Today, yesterday, tomorrow--
isn't it enough that they
dragged me away like a criminal?
Just calm down.
I'm just trying to help you.
They sent me to some program
called I.S.A.P.
They're sending over a
caseworker next month.
Do we have to talk
about this right now?
- Holidays should be about family.
- Hey, watch it!
What?
Accident-- mom,
Gina, Christmas tree.
Well, it's officially the
start of the holiday season.
You ran over my Christmas tree.
Well, I was aiming for you.
Besides, you left it in
the middle of the street.
I just took it off the tracker.
I had to put it somewhere
when I opened the front door.
The street is public property,
unlike this house which is not,
so get out!
You better watch out.
I know when you're sleeping,
and I know when you're awake.
Oops.
Ho, ho, ho!
You're late.
Love the crystal menorah next to
the sterling silver Santa. So taboo.
Don't you just
love the holidays?
They're fabulous.
So is Nico coming
home for Christmas?
She's spending the break
with her father in Dubai.
Besides, you know Christmas
mornings for me are all about
- martinis and valium.
- Yummy.
You did not just take
the whole wheat bagel.
You  know I always eat that one.
So sorry, Wil.
I thought we were sharing everything
now  that I know about
our mysterious friend.
Right?
Right.
That is so wrong.
I know, believe me. We've been
consistently over budget every issue.
We had to cut costs somewhere.
- Boo!
Come on. An office party at the office?
Thall be fun.
Yeah, like waxing is fun.
Thank you for your
enthusiasm, Betty.
Actually, Betty has something
to be excited about.
She's been offered an amazing
new position at "MYW,"
and I hope she'll
consider taking it.
We'll be looking
for her replacement.
Any of you interested,
leave your résumé with Betty.
And that's it. Thank you.
Daniel, what are you doing?
Something you're far
too loyal to ever do.
But if I leave,
who's gonna take care of you?
Well, I guess we'll just have
to find someone as good as you.
Better get started.
Well, I could try, but if I
don't find the perfect assistant,
I'm not going anywhere.
I mean, there's not enough time--
Betty, Betty, sometimes we all
have to take leaps of faith.
You know, you being with Sofia
is the best thing for you.
Speaking of Sofia,
I'd like to see you in my office.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Would it be inappropriate
to throw a good-bye party
and not invite her?
You know who would be
perfect for that job?
- Anne Hathaway.
- No. Me.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, love your confidence.
Wait a second. Sofia wants you
to go out with someone else?
- That doesn't make any sense.
- I know, it's crazy.
She seems to think some other
woman will make my palms sweat
and my heart race the
way they do for her.
Well, how do you
know they won't?
Look, I--I've never been
good at being faithful,
but no one has ever made me
feel the way Sofia does.
In fact, I stopped by to see Nigel
on the way to work this morning.
I'm through with
being a bachelor...
for good.
Oh, my god.
Are you serious?
I mean, congratulations.
That's great.
Look, I-I know what
you're thinking,
but I--it--it's like they say--
Well, what do they say?
When you know, you know,
and I do know.
Well, I'm so happy for you,
Daniel, and for Sofia.
Thanks.
You know, they are just on loan
until I figure out which one
is gonna be perfect for her.
Well, I'm very glad to hear that you have
no intention of testing out her theory
because I know how you get
around beautiful women,
and Belle Jolie is sending over
their lingerie line today...
on their models.
Hello?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Hey, Betty,
I love your sweater.
Did you make it yourself?
Amanda, look, I need to plan a
"Mode"-worthy party for $500,
get Daniel a new assistant
and get Justin a signed photo of Lindsay
Lohan in two days. I'm kinda busy.
Well, today is,
like, your lucky day.
Hire me. You know you wanna.
Are you serious? After what you
and Daniel have been through?
What is the very first
thing I ever said to you?
"Are you the before?"
Okay, the second thing.
"Are you delivering
something? "
Whatever. The point
is I wanted this job
way before you or Daniel
ever came to "Mode."
I have a brain to go with
this beautiful body, Betty.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Look, I can prove it to you.
Let me help you plan the party.
I've got tons of connections.
Plus, I can get
loads of free crap.
Well, I mean,
I could use the help.
Okay, you're on. Anything else?
Oh, yeah. Snow's here.
Oh, man. I'm sorry. I--
It's you.
Henry, hi.
You got a little,
um, right here.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
That--that was
very unprofessional.
Uh, let me help
you clean this up.
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't worry about it.
Actually, Betty, you're just
the girl I've been looking for.
Oh, no, um,
I'm sure that there are other girls.
Uh, it's about the party?
I'm supposed to oversee
the budget, so...
guess I'll be on top of you
for the next couple days.
Partywise.
Oh. Right.
All right.
Okay.
Oh, crap.
Transcript : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com
The models are here.
Show them in.
Oh, no.
That's my ex-girlfriend Aerin.
She broke my heart.
She was my first.
First supermodel.
God, that girl knew how to--
Hey.
Aerin, what are you doing here?
Taking my clothes off.
Uh, could you give us a second?
Sure.
Do you need me to stay?
No, I'll be fine.
Just bring the rest of the models in.
Oh, right. That's gonna help.
Amanda?  No.
No. No.
Amanda?
No.
Daniel, um,
I just wanted to let you know
that your girlfriend's plane,
uh, landed safely,
and that, um, the photo department
is ready for the models.
Okay, come on.
Okay. Bye. See you later.
# Now listen here, chipmunks #
# to this advice #
# You better be good #
# and you better be nice... #
Betty,  this is Ralph. Wa!
He's our store manager-- the man whose
job I one day aspire to hold. No.
Good to meet you, Betty.
Hi.
And if anyone can fill these size 13s,
it's Walter.
This is my wife Jackie.
- A pleasure.
- Nice to meet you.
Hey, Paulie, let's get one
of all of us together, yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Squeeze in.
There we go.
- Thanks.
- Got it.
Huh? Betty,
welcome to the Pro Buy family.
Thank you.
Walter, should we let
the lovely ladies chat?
Stewie made an ice luge.
Bring it!
Betty, honey,
we have so much in common.
I used to work in
Manhattan, too--advertising--
before I married
that adorable lug.
Oh, wow.
Do you still work in advertising?
Mm-hmm. Right here at Pro Buy.
The commute's a breeze.
I'm not one for lots of travel.
Never even been on a plane.
Do you miss it-- Manhattan?
Never. You'll get
tired of it, too.
We're Queens girls,
Betty, born and bred.
We belong here.
Thanks.
Marc?
Hello?
It's me.
Have you come up with a
solution to our little problem?
You mean Marc?
I'm working on it.
He won't be a problem much longer.
Do what you must
to shut him up.
Don't worry.
After I'm done, he will be silenced...
permanently.
Princess cut...
canary...
6 carats.
Oh, my god.
- Shot?
- Oh, thanks.
Jackie, can I ask you a
question that's kinda personal?
When did you know that
Ralph was the one?
From the first moment.
He took my breath away,
still does.
When did you know with Walter?
Well, you s-see,
I'm--I'm not sure that I do yet.
Oh, don't worry, honey.
There will come a time,
and you'll just know.
Yeah, I hope so.
For what it's worth,
I've heard Walter's sure
he's found the one.
Did you go to the funeral home?
They never delivered a
casket to the mausoleum.
A relative claimed Fey's
remains in the morgue.
A relative?
It's all I could dig up.
After all of this,
Fey Sommers is really dead.
Good morning, sunshine.
Brought you a little present.
Whole wheat.
Too late.
Yesterday was carb day.
Of course.
So are you sticking around for
the Christmas party later tonight?
Unfortunately.
You'd better show up, too.
You never know what
surprises might be in store.
By the way, Marc,
what is your home address?
W-why?
Just sending a special
delivery your way.
'Tis the season.
Seriously, I've read every
issue of "Mode" ever.
Did you know Danny
Meade dated Fergie
back when she was on
"Kids incorporated"?
- Oh, wow.
- See? I am perfect for this job.
Okay. We'll let you know.
- Not going so well?
- Nope.
I  don't even think the right
person for this job exists.
Well, you never know.
Party update-- I got us five
cases of champagne "donated"
by this bartender I
know at Double Seven's.
A friend of mine who used to
work at Lizzie Grubman's company
got us six white Christmas trees
left over from Diddy's party,
and I used to date
this sculptor guy--
would you prefer the ice
sculpture be the "Mode" logo
or a snowflake?
I would go snowflake.
Wow. Snowflake it is.
So I guess you can stop all that
boring interviewing then, huh?
Look, Amanda,
I really appreciate the help,
but that doesn't
erase you and Daniel.
You're just--you're not the right
person for this job. I'm sorry.
Hey, Betty?
Ornaments.
Thought it might save
you a couple dollars.
Thanks, but, uh, the budget's all set.
Amanda got us some amazing deals.
Seems like a lot of
people owe her favors.
So basically,
you don't even need me.
Nope.
Hey, did you know that
the snow inside these
was originally
particles of gold foil?
Sounds beautiful, right?
I had never even seen real snow until
I got off the plane in New York.
What? How?
Oh, uh,
I grew up in the desert. Tucson.
I used to think all snow looked
like gold foil till I got here.
Silly, huh?
No, not at all.
Okay, "soccer ball,
"renewed subscription to
'Martha Stewart living,'
"karaoke video game,
"for grandpa never to go away"?
Oh, Justin, don't worry.
He's gonna be...
Who moved all our decorations?
And what's Santa
doing to that elf?
This has the skank prints of
Gina Gambarro all over it.
Well, you did run over
her Christmas tree,
and Christmas is a time
of love and forgiveness.
Grow up, Tiny Tim.
This means war.
Well, I like the
claymation Rudolph best.
You know they did
that with puppets?
They called it animagic.
Just something you know?
Yeah, I have this weird talent
for remembering useless facts.
Oh, no, it's not useless.
It's... it's cute.
Thanks.
I've been meaning to ask,
is this--
No, uh, it's just holly. Holly.
You know what? I need to get back
to work so you should probably go.
- Uh, okay.
- All right.
Uh, I guess I'll see
you at the party?
Okay.
Here, take this.
What?
It's an ornament. Take it.
Hey, watch the hair.
I can explain.
Amanda, please just tell me that you
met some rich, gorgeous stockbroker,
you're engaged and you're
running off to Paris together.
- Ooh.
- Amanda!
What, like that's
so impossible?
That's one of Daniel's rings,
isn't it?
Take it off! We have to put
it back before he notices!
You know those things must be worth,
like, hundreds of dollars.
It's stuck!
Just help me get it off!
Look, I know what
you're thinking,
but I don't have "feelings"
for Daniel anymore.
Ew.
Anna Freud might
disagree with that.
What?
Amanda, you're in denial.
Okay, I used to be all
crushed out on Daniel.
I admit it.
But when I found these rings,
it was finally real.
He's ready to commit...
just not to me.
You can't deny your
feelings, Betty.
And I don't feel
anything for Daniel,
not anymore.
I am going to get this ring back to
where it belongs before he finds out.
I promise.
Thanks.
'Scusey.
28, huh?
Hey, you don't know a Marc St.
James, do you?
I hate that guy.
# They have Christmas #
# down in Mexico #
# A lot of places #
# that you wanted to go #
# They have something #
# that you don't know #
# Santa's gonna do the mambo, uh! #
# Santa's doing the mambo #
# this Christmas #
# Santa's doing the mambo-- #
Amanda! Thank god you're here.
Are you packing heat?
Always.
Amanda, I'm not
flirting with you.
Does anyone here have a gun?
Look around. We're a bunch of unstable,
hungry, back-stabbing bitches.
Do you really think anyone
would sell us guns?
Just relax. Have a drink.
That's easy for you to say.
Your boss doesn't want you dead.
# Mambo, Santa, mambo #
Oh, sorry.
Don't spill.
You might electrocute yourself.
I'm just joshing.
You look totally...
radiant.
Seriously.
Well, thank you. You, too.
Hey, people actually look like
they're having a good time
and the office
looks extraordinary.
Well, everything looks better
when you dim the lights
and drink a bottle of champagne,
trust me.
You really pulled it off.
Thanks.
So does that mean you
think I can do your job?
Well, you're obviously smart enough.
You've proven that.
But that's not the problem.
Daniel needs somebody who's
gonna be looking out for him,
and I don't know
if you've noticed,
but his personal life tends to get
in the way of his professional life.
What's Daniel doing with
McSlutty over there?
I thought things were
getting serious with Charo.
Exactly. I'll be right back.
Wait!
Let me run interference with
the trashionista tonight,
see if I can't fill
your shoes after all.
# Mambo, Santa, mambo #
# So you wanna mambo, Santa, mambo #
# Come and mambo if you can #
# Shoo-be-doo-be-doo #
# Mambo, Santa, mambo #
# Well, here comes Santa #
# with eight reindeers #
# He come every time about this year #
# here is something #
# that you don't know... #
...a heart for Wilhelmina,
courage for Marc and
a brain for Amanda.
Marc?
You never saw me.
Oh, crap.
Ow!
Betty? Are you okay?
Hi.
Oh, there it is! Just...
I was just making sure that
everybody was being safe.
You know,
office party hook ups and...
That's very responsible of you.
- You need some help?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Hey, you should come
back to the party.
Uh, beauty is
making snow angels.
Well, in the plastic snow.
I just came for this.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Have fun.
- You, too.
Santa, I've got a thing
for men with beards.
Christina, that's a fake beard.
This way.
Oh, god, I thought it was bad enough
watching Santa come down the chimney!
Marc.
Well, hello there.
We've been looking all over for you.
Please come with us.
Love to.
There you are.
Here I am.
Doing a little research?
Actually, I just, um,
read it for the articles.
That's really funny.
You know, um...
I'm actually wearing
those right now.
Daniel! Aah! Aah! I need you!
There's a fire in the--
Oh, screw it.
Just stop kissing that tramp!
You are practically engaged.
Look at that.
Dry as a bone.
I'm sorry, Aerin.
You're--you're beautiful.
I know.
But I'm in love
with someone else.
Her?
'Cause I'm sure the three of us could,
uh, work something out.
Uh, no! Not--not her.
Whatever.
There's other men at this party,
you know?
I am so good.
Are you girls still
playing that little game?
This is not a game, papi.
You know,
Gina's parents won a cruise to Alaska
in a supermarket sweepstakes.
They're gone for a week.
Maybe you should give her a break.
You know, forgive, forget.
- A little holiday spirit?
- Yeah, right.
Santa?
Well, if it isn't the
bitch who stole Christmas.
Ow! I think it's broken.
Well, I hope it was worth it.
Come on.
Why does it always have
to be such a comp--
competition with you, Gina?
Why? Are you serious?
Hilda, we have been competing
ever since you stole my
"electric youth" routine
and won miss junior
teen Queens.
I can never win with you.
I guess I should
just stop trying.
Well, yeah.
Why don't you come inside?
You need to get some ice on that.
Come on, we got eggnog...
and brandy.
It's a Christmas miracle!
Well, will you give
it to him already?
Willie, please. I didn't mean
anything that I said, ever.
In fact, I will never say anything
again, if that's what you want.
Merry Christmas, Marc.
Huh? What? This?
It's a 2007--fresh off the lot.
It's Jody Pennette,
Pennette auto mall.
This is...
bigger than my apartment.
Are you trying to, uh...
buy my silence?
'Cause that's a
definite possibility.
So I think I found you
your new assistant.
Really?
Who?
Well, this might come as
a surprise to you, but...
it's Amanda.
Amanda who?
Amanda--pretty blonde,
kind of a bitch,
sits at the big circular desk?
Mmm... nope.
Doesn't ring a bell.
I'm serious.
Look, Daniel, I wouldn't leave if I
didn't know there was someone here
to protect you.
And, tonight,
Amanda proved that she can.
You're right.
She did.
So... if you're serious
about this, then...
I guess this is good-bye.
You've earned it.
I don't know what to say.
But thank you...
for everything.
I'm very proud of you, Betty.
You know, you've...
you're destined for
bigger things than this.
Wait, so... the other gifts,
that wasn't you?
Uh, what other gifts?
Never mind.
Merry Christmas, Daniel.
Merry Christmas, Betty.
Sofia, hi.
Uh, I've got
something to tell you.
You do take my breath away.
You make my heart beat faster.
You make my palms sweat.
But that doesn't mean
I don't love you.
It means I do.
Sometimes your
heart knows things
your mind can't explain.
And my heart...
doesn't race for anyone else.
I love you, Sofia.
It's, um, Daniel, by the way.
Betty! Betty!
Where are you going?
Oh, I swear to god!
- That is impossible!
- No, it ain't.
Justin, does this
need more glitter?
Absolutely.
Oh, my god, okay, hold on...
show me.
Okay, you start over here.
Did hell freeze over?
- Anyway, I just don't understand.
- You start at the middle...
Is there an easier
way to do that?
Well, I was gonna wait for it to melt,
but, uh...
So...
Betty thinks you should
be my new assistant.
Really?
Yep.
I do, too.
Really?
You're more than just a pretty face,
Amanda, even I know that.
So what do you think,
can we do this,
work together?
Absolutely.
Professionals.
Looks like I missed some party.
Ted Lebeau...
Hey, juanita, move your feet.
So what's eating you?
Ha ha.
Hilda, what if I'm 45
and I've still never
been on a plane?
If you wanna fly on a plane,
you're gonna fly on a plane.
You're a dreamer, Betty.
And look at you-- you're 22 years old,
you already work at "Mode."
You can do anything.
Well, I sure hope
you're right...
about everything.
What is that? Let me see.
Walter loves you
so much, Betty.
I wish you could appreciate
that a little bit more.
I do.
I just wanna know for sure.
You know, like...
like when you heart races
and your palms sweat?
Have you been drinking the
Herbalux extreme energy tea?
That's probably Walter.
Ho, ho, ho.
Hey, Walter, merry Christmas!
Hey, uh... how come your Christmas
lights spell "Hilda sucks?"
Don't ask.
So you're ready for
your last present?
Ta da!
Walter! You?
You've been...
Yeah, well, Daniel helped me sneak
the other presents into the office.
I wanted it to be a surprise.
Hello.
Hi, is Betty there?
- Yeah, who's calling?
- It's Henry.
Her, uh... friend from work.
Hello? Are you still there?
Yeah, sorry, um...
Actually, you know, Betty's busy.
Can I take a message?
Yes, please.
Tell her, about the party, uh...
You know what?
I just wanted to let her know
that Rudolph's on tomorrow night.
She can call me if
she wants to watch it,
you know... together.
Uh, okay, I'll tell her.
Thanks, bye.
I know that you think I don't "get"
your new life in Manhattan, but...
I wanna try. I...
I wanna be a part of it.
Thank you.
Ooh, candy canes! Yummy.
Don't you just love Christmas?
Transcript : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com