Previously on Ugly Betty...
Oh, my god.
That nepotistic son of a
bitch gives my job to his...
His son.
Who do you work for?
I'm your new assistant.
He made Daniel hire you
'cause he didn't want his son
to be tempted to sleep with
his assistants anymore.
I'm in love with someone else.
Gina Gambarro?
You broke my plasma!
I'm very unhappy.
It's a setback.
But it's just a matter of time.
Once he's out of the picture,
the company will be
ours for the taking.
Great bunny.
Oh, thank you.
My sister gave that to me when
I graduated from Queens College.
One of america's
best value colleges.
Yep, yep, that's the one.
It's sort of a good-luck charm,
seeing as I am doing
what I've always wanted to--
magazine publishing.
Well, kudos,
and I certainly applaud your efforts
at personalizing your desk.
So... different.
So you.
Marc!
I have to go.
Oh, it was an amazing
night for me, too.
Listen, I gotta
get back to work.
I will call you very,
very soon, okay?
All right.
No idea who that was.
Good morning, Daniel.
Can I get you some coffee?
Actually, I was wondering
if you had a chance
to look at "page six" today.
No.
"Daniel Meade's assistant confirms
he was wearing a Dior suit,
Gucci tie and Maggini shoes."
Yeah, that's what you wore.
Isn't it?
The Magginis are a problem.
But you said that they're the
most comfortable shoes you own.
No, no, they are. Unfortunately there's
a whole sweatshop thing with them--
cambodian kids,
forced labor, I don't know.
Point is, it's best if people
don't know I wear their shoes.
Okay.
Listen, Betty.
The press, people in this business--
they have a way of taking the truth,
twisting it around.
We always got to
protect ourselves,
twist it around
ourselves if we need to.
I got it.
Oh, hey. I got that Natalie
Whitman meeting in a few minutes.
Wow, she's my favorite.
I love those Jenna Fletcher movies,
and her catchphrase,
"you do the math."
You know she gains 30 pounds every
single time she does that role?
Yeah, and apparently she
hasn't lost any of it.
Do you want in on that meeting?
Me? Um, wow!
Yes. Yeah, that's amazing.
Thank you, Daniel.
Remember, you and me,
we're a team.
And I will take that coffee now.
Black, extra sugar. Thanks.
Has Wilhelmina Slater,
"Mode" creative director,
got over her humiliation of being
passed over for the boss' son?
That's the question
on everyone's lips
after the recent regime
change when Daniel Meade,
slutty scion of parent company,
Meade Publications,
was named new editor in chief.
Daniel took over after the hot,
hot death
of former editor Fey Sommers
in a fiery car crash.
The world is still in mourning
after the fur-loving fashion
martyr lost control of her vehicle
after being chased by angry
animal rights activists.
You wanted to see me?
Just  checking in.
Yeah, no.
Everything's going terrific.
First issue goes
to press tomorrow.
Natalie Whitman,
the star of the Jenna Fletcher movies,
is our featured layout.
"You do the math."
Yeah, that's right.
Good.
Daniel, I don't
need to remind you
of the importance
of succeeding here.
"Mode" is a stepping stone for you,
but a significant one.
You do well, eventually you'll
end up sitting where I am,
running the company.
Have you been getting the book?
The book.
What book are you
referring to, exactly?
"Editor in chief for dummies."
The book, Daniel.
The book.
The mock-up of the
entire magazine.
Each department submits their
section throughout the day.
Photo, style, advertising--
all of "mode's" secrets.
The person in charge of the
magazine takes it home overnight
and gives their notes.
The person who controls the
book controls the magazine.
Thank you, Edgar.
You're very welcome,
miss Slater.
Which is why,
if you're ever going to succeed here,
and hopefully be sitting
where I am someday,
you have to control it.
The book is
your responsibility.
And right here we're going to
smooth out all of the chin fat.
Good, good. Tighten that punem.
Lean out the arm flab.
Downsize these hips about 15%.
At  least.
And this area right over here.
My breasts?
Lift them up a notch.
Sag begone.
It's gonna be great.
You are going to look amazing.
Okay, I didn't think the
pictures looked too bad.
I thought that I looked--
I don't know.
- Normal?
- Yes.
Natalie, you're absolutely right.
You look... normal--
wonderfully so.
And if this were any other magazine,
that would be fine.
But this is "Mode."
And we are not about normal.
We are about... aspirational.
So why not,
with the help of modern technology,
give yourself the opportunity to look
as stunning as you possibly could?
Hmm.
You.
- Me?
- Yeah. What do you think?
Oh, well, I think you look gr--
Natalie, as editor in chief,
I say,
why not take
something that's hot
and  make it super hot?
It's a tres good career move,
and remember, we're still trying to
land you "2 million dollar baby."
Okay. I guess you
guys are the experts.
I'll let you do your magic.
Okay, it's gonna be fabulous.
Listen, the features people want
to finish your interview...
Print out the finished version,
put it in the book.
And by the way, why have I
yet to see any sort of concept
on that Beyonce pyromia
spread we talked about?
Oh, I'll get right to it.
I'd love to see that as well.
Yeah, sure.
Wilhelmina, do
you have a minute?
For you, Daniel, I have two.
I'm editor in chief.
I should be receiving the
book at the end of each day.
Well, with all your responsibility,
do you really think you have the time?
Take my advice.
Focus on the big picture.
Don't be afraid to delegate.
That's what I'm here for.
Wilhelmina, certain things
fall under my purview.
The book is one of them.
So from now on,
I'm going to start reiving
the book every night.
As you wish.
That was strong in there.
Very editorial.
Well, the book is my responsibility.
It's way too important.
You know that scene in the movies
when the guy is on the plane,
and he's handcuffed
to the briefcase?
You want to handcuff
yourself to the book?
No, it's--it's a metaphor.
By the way, the next time
you find yourself on the spot
like you did in
there with Natalie,
you just gotta kinda go
with the vibe in the room.
Even if I don't agree?
If it's the best thing for
the magazine, definitely.
You know what? I left my P.D.A.
in the conference room.
Can you grab that for me?
Sure.
Has anyone seen my bunny?
It's, um, pink...
green tummy, graduation cap.
No?
How dare he embarrass me like
that in front of everyone?
The tall jar of mayonnaise is
clearly making a power play.
Well, if that's
what he wants...
What are you thinking?
We give him the book.
Leave the unretouched Natalie
Whitman photos in there,
he signs off, it goes to print,
enraged publicists,
celebrities canceling their layouts.
"Mode" in chaos,
and you'll be the only guiding
light left to lead the magazine out.
Uber clever.
Thank you.
Ooh, Marc, at that arch. Ah.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Oh, those look damn good.
Hook me up, girl.
- Ooh.
- I'm a vegan.
Carnivore here,
through and through.
So tell me, what exactly were they
retouching on Ms. "You do the math"?
Everything.
I never even realized how
much they do to these people.
The chin, the butt,
the hips, the teeth--
Oh, you don't even know.
They ever got their hands on me,
I'd look like a
pre-crack Whitney.
And I never even got to tell
her what I really thought,
which was that she looked
great the way she was.
That's the business we're working in.
Perfection sells fashion.
It's all fake and unattainable,
but nobody seems to get it.
I get it.
Really? Would you buy a
magazine if I was on the cover?
Yeah. "National Geographic."
I  would buy any magazine that you
were on the cover of, Christina.
Are you trying to suffocate
us with that putrid smell?
Oh, they're empanadas.
They're disgusting.
Oh, my god.
There is nothing here except
non-caloric space food.
And I am starving.
Can I have one of those, please?
Yeah. Of course, yeah.
Oh, wow. You know,
I might as well eat the whole thing,
because they're gonna make me
look like Nicole Richie anyway.
So what do you guys think of
the latest Jenna Fletcher movie?
And you can be honest,
'cause I'm not one of those actresses
with some huge ego.
Oh, it was really good.
I enjoyed it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
So how do you guys
put up with working here...
Funny thing,
being on the other side,
everyone believing
you've perished.
We have to assume Bradford was
behind this "fiery car crash,"
but where do we
get the evidence?
We have to find a way
to get it out of him.
Then he goes to jail and
we take over the company.
Simultaneously, we need to
get Daniel out of "Mode."
We can't have him waiting in
the wings to take over.
Hopefully I'm making
strides in that direction.
So the question is,
how do we get to Bradford?
Well, I can't confront him directly.
He'll just fire me.
Then we use Daniel.
I didn't know you spoke german.
I don't.
I just own the newspaper.
I found something you
should be aware of.
Estate sale for Fey Sommers.
I can never just be
rid of this woman.
Who knew you hated
Fey Sommers that much?
Who said I hated her?
Anyway, I was thinking I'd break
into the place today, go through,
see if there's
anything incriminating.
I'll do it.
I have a key.
Besides, you don't know
what's really incriminating.
What's wrong, pumpkin?
Nothing.
Oh, wow. The book.
I'll give it to him.
No, no.
This is too important.
I'll give it to him directly.
Here you go.
Wilhelmina's notes
are already inside.
She said pay close attention
to the Fanny Pack article.
She's not sure we're hitting
the emotional arc just yet.
- Thank you.
- Toodles.
So Wilhelmina's office gave me two
tickets to Pagliacci at the Met.
It's boring as all hell, but there is
a little alcove on the second floor
where we can do all
sorts of naughty things
and never get caught.
This can wait till the morning.
See you tomorrow, Betty.
Do you need me to
do anything else?
Oh, just keep working.
A little overtime,
and you can afford invisaligns.
Hi, this is Daniel.
Leave a message.
Hey, uh, Daniel, it's me.
I'm in your office,
and I saw that you left the book out.
Um, I don't know if I should
just leave it here...
um, or not.
Um...
I mean, I guess I'll just take
the book home for safekeeping,
and I'll bring it back
tomorrow morning.
Okay, um... bye.
I mean, she was so nice.
She sat there and talked to us,
like, forever.
What was her name again?
Natalie Whitman.
Never heard of her.
Hello! From the Jenna
Fletcher movies.
"You do the math."
Well, dad,
she did have some of your empanadas,
and she said they were great.
Really? Bueno,
the woman has good taste.
Here.
What's  that?
It's the mock-up for the
next issue of "Mode."
- Oh, my god.
- Hey, be careful!
You have the book?
Wait, Justin,
how do you even know what the book is?
I saw "Prada" like,
seven times.
So how did you get it?
Well, my boss was rushing out
of the office and he forgot it,
and I didn't want to just
leave it there, so...
Hey, look,
your name on the masthead.
Really?
Well, sort of.
They spelled it "Betsy" Suarez.
Oh.
Ay, what a day.
No matter how many
times I explain it,
no one has a freakin' clue
what an antioxidant is.
Look what I found at the door.
Wow, 9-volt batteries.
Prince charming's really
going the extra mile.
Ay, mama, you gotta be a little
bit more forgiving, okay?
Walter cares for you.
Well, he should've thought about that
before he left me for Gina Gambarro.
Listen to me. That poor thing--
he didn't stand a chance.
That girl is predatory.
Is that why they call
her "Gina Hyena"?
Exactly.
What's this?
It's a mock-up of the
magazine where Betty works.
It's all nice,
but what's the problem with having
some latinas somewhere
in here, huh?
You gotta give these things
a little flava, you know?
- I'll get some dulce de leche--
- Ew!
Natalie Whitman is still fat.
Oh, wow.
Daniel didn't swap out
the unretouched photos.
He's gonna put her
in as she really is.
That's awful.
Justin! That's great.
Oh, I bet you that's Walter.
Ay, Betty, be nice.
Where the hell's my $4,000?
What are you talking about?
Uh, you broke my flat screen.
Gina, I did not break your--
Listen, you barged
into my house
like a little mexican
banshee and slammed my door.
Thing smashed right on
the floor 'cause of you.
Well, maybe if you stayed away
from what wasn't yours...
Oh, are you still
hung up over that?
Look, I want my money or a comparably
priced 50-inch plasma installed.
Bitch, out my house.
- Oh, no, you did not just call me a...
- Oh, yes, I did!
Please be careful
with the book.
Gina, leave.
Fine.
Have it your way.
But remember, Betty,
I'm a bad seed.
I did a year in juvie.
Ooh, I'm gonna whup
that girl's ass.
Did I miss something
on the telenovela?
See? This is why I don't
want us to have a dog.
Have you guys seen the book?
- What book?
- The book, dad.
The "Mode" book.
I came downstairs and it was gone.
- You lost it?
- No, I didn't lose it!
It's just in a place
that I don't know about!
It's gotta be here somewhere.
If I show up at work
without that book,
the entire layout for the magazine--
Daniel's first issue-- is gone,
and it goes to print tonight.
Come on, people lose things.
Stuff is backed up by computers.
It can't be that big a deal.
- What is going on?
- She lost the book.
- I'll go check the living room.
- I'll make you some eggs.
Dad, what is food gonna
do for me right now?
It's a crisis. I cook.
Betty!
It was slid under the door.
"I have your precious book.
Maybe if I had a
new flat screen TV,
I'd have something better
to do with my nights
than break into
people's homes." Gina!
Justin, put your headphones on.
That bitch!
Oh, my god!
If that showerhead could pay my bills,
I would marry it.
- Hey, uh, Daniel, it's me...
- We're gonna be late.
Not that late.
Do you like it when
I bite your ear?
- Damn it.
- Oh, I guess not.
- I gotta call Betty.
- Okay, buzz kill.
She took the book home
to her house last night.
To Queens? Ew!
Hello?
Yeah, this is Daniel
Meade for Betty.
I have to tell
him what happened.
Justin, headphones.
You do not tell
this man the truth.
You lie.
We will get that book back.
I promise you.
Hi, Daniel.
I  just got your message.
You took the book home?
Yeah, um,
I didn't know where to leave it.
Betty, you're an assistant.
You never,
ever take that book out of the office.
What, did she need it to fix the
wobbly leg under her coffee table?
Listen, nothing spilled on it, right?
There's no--no rips, tears, anything?
No, no, no, unh-unh.
No, nothing like that.
Fire her. Fire her right now.
I would be such a
better assistant.
Why don't you go get dressed?
Okay, but I'm telling you,
you're gonna get it back,
and there's gonna be
chimichurr-o sauce all over it.
Listen, uh, Betty,
I know it was an honest mistake.
You have it. It's safe.
That-- so that's all
that's important.
Yeah, um... it's totally safe.
Um...
I'm looking at the layout of
Natalie Whitman right now.
Um, and by the way,
I think it's very brave and impressive
that you used the
original photos.
What original photos?
You know, the--the unretouched
pictures of Natalie.
I never approved that.
Wait, are there unretouched
photos in that book?
- Yeah, I thought you had approved them.
- This isn't happening.
Look, if those-- if those photos ever
got out, it would be disastrous, Betty.
Okay, Betty,
do not let that book out of your sight.
I'm sending a car over to
pick you up right now.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, I'm--I'm--I'm holding it.
Bye.
I am in big trouble.
What?!
Hilda just told me that Gina
Gambarro stole your book.
Give me the phone.
I'm calling her parents.
Dad, I'm not 6.
She's right. I'll handle this.
I'm gonna show that skank a whole
new use for her curling iron.
Hilda, don't.
I don't need you guys to fight my
battles. I... can handle this.
I'm an adult.
Please! Gina, please!
Look, I have
something you want,
and you have something I want.
Give me my 4 grand so
I can get a new TV,
and you get your book back.
I don't have $4,000.
Then I probably
won't take a check.
Gina, this is my job.
You cannot do this to me.
Oh, look at that.
I accidentally tore a page.
No, no, no, no, don't.
You don't do that. Don't do that, Gina.
Maybe you learned a
little lesson here.
No one screws with
Gina Gambarro.
Then maybe you've
learned a little lesson.
Gina Gambarro should always
latch her back door.
Get out of my house.
I will call the police so fast.
This is trespassing.
Oh, what do you call breaking
into our house last night?
Look, she replaces my TV,
and she gets her stupid book back.
Okay, I am only gonna
ask you one time.
Where is it?
I don't seem to remember.
Well, maybe pulling that weave out
of your head will jog your memory!
It's right here!
Hilda, just stop. Stop.
The car's here. It's no use.
Look, I just--I need to go to
the office and deal with this.
You are paying for this.
Well, I guess we
owe you $4,000...
and fifty cents.
Hold the elevator.
Hold it!
That was close.
You get a chance to
look over the book yet?
You know, we really can't
proceed until you sign off,
and we do go to press
by 6:00 tonight.
I was, uh,
just getting my notes together.
I'll be ready for
our meeting at 10:00.
What did you think overall?
Looks... pretty good...
except for the unretouched
photos of Natalie Whitman.
Unretouched photos?
Yes, somehow they made
it into the mock-up.
Lucky I caught that, huh?
Could have been a big one.
Actually surprised
you missed it.
- Well, I--
- Don't sweat it.
You're probably just reaching
that age where you have
to start worrying
about glasses.
Happens to everyone.
Love, you're gonna
have to slow down.
I can't understand
what you're saying.
Now what exactly is
a Gina Gambarro?
My neighbor.
She's the one who has the book,
and she's holding it ransom.
The book?
The book with the unretouched
photographs of Natalie?
- Oh, dear.
- This is bad, isn't it?
Uh, well, I wouldn't count
on "employee of the month."
Oh, my god!
What?
Christina, everything up until
this point has been a big lie.
I didn't get the job
because I was qualified.
I got the job because Bradford
Meade didn't want his son
to be tempted to sleep
with his assistant.
And you have more
than proven yourself.
It doesn't matter.
I keep getting told that I have
to twist the truth to fit in,
and maybe I just don't
belong at "Mode,"
and my bunny is paying
the price for it.
Your bunny?
Listen, sweetheart,
there's an awful lot of information
coming out of your mouth right now,
and to be honest,
I can't really make
any sense of it.
Look, I just need to
come clean to Daniel,
tell him the truth.
Well, the truth
might get you fired.
Well, I need to do it.
Bye, Christina.
There's hardly any traffic
on the bridge, miss.
We should be there in no time.
Great.
This must be my lucky day.
Vampira told me to let you
know they're still waiting
on your notes from the book.
Uh, uh, just tell them
I'm--I'm still going over it.
I, uh, I ran out of post-its,
okay? Yeah.
Oh, and, uh, call Betty again.
Find out where the hell she--
Okay! I'm no seeing
the book in your hands.
Why is that?
Because Gina Gambarro has it.
Gambarro? Gambarro.
Is that a-a new designer?
No, it's an old slut.
She broke into my house, and she took
it, and now she's holding it ransom--
What? W-w-wait.
You told me you had the book.
- You said you were looking at it.
- Yeah, I lied...
or I twisted the truth to try
to buy some time and fix it.
Betty, you don't lie to me, ever.
We're on the same team.
I mean, we cannot afford to have
those unretouched Natalie proofs
out there in any way,
shape or form,
and I-I cannot tell
you how royally screwed
she and this entire
magazine could be.
Because there's pictures of
what she actually looks like?
Exactly.
How much does this Gina want?
$4,000.
Daniel, I-I will pay
you back with interest,
or you can take it out of my
check for the next five years.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, stop, uh...
we're gonna deal with this later.
Get my checkbook out of my top
drawer and meet me downstairs.
We're going to Queens.
Daniel, they're all
waiting for you.
Oh, right.
Well, it looks like our 10:00
meeting is finally beginning.
We're all very excited to hear
your thoughts on the book, Daniel.
Where is the book, anyway?
Oh, uh,
it's back there in my office.
I see it.
Well, don't you need it to go
through your notes with us?
Uh, actually,
I just came in to tell you all
I-I think you did a
great job on this issue,
and I don't really
have any notes, so...
Well, I do. You mind if I get it
back so I can go through mine?
You want the book back.
If it's not a problem.
Actually, um, I might want
to take one more look at it,
just to make sure everything is perfect,
you know?
So why don't we meet back here,
in say, three hours?
It's great to see everyone.
Jeff, how's the wife?
We're separating.
Great to hear it.
Our fearless leader.
That's it.
Who put the bunny
in the toilet?
This is not funny!
Who thinks this is funny?
Oh, really?
Well, whoever's doing this,
if you think you can break me
that easily, you're wrong.
You can take my bunny...
but you can't take my spirit.
Hello there.
You have something
that belongs to me.
Oh, you.
I want that book.
I have your money.
Well...
What are you doing here?
I'm working.
Where did you get the TV?
You guys are a little late.
Someone else found
out about the book.
Who knew this thing was like
the freakin' dead sea scrolls?
Anyway, they came by earlier
and gave me enough money
for a new flat screen.
L.C.D.-- even
better than plasma.
Oh, my god.
Someone else has the book?!
Mets cap, big sunglasses,
knew all about the book...
Of course, if I had known it was you,
I would have held out.
I swear this is purely
a professional visit.
There's nothing between us anymore.
We're not even friends.
I don't even like her.
Walter, I don't care.
- You don't?
- No.
- Did you get my gift?
- The batteries? Yeah, thanks.
They'll really come in handy
during hurricane season.
No. Don't you remember when
we first started dating,
and you stopped by Pro Buy?
I was doing shipping
and receiving.
A box of 9-volts.
First time we kissed,
you said, "careful"--
"Careful, we're gonna
'cause a spark."
Yeah.
Hey there.
Whassup?
We need to talk.
We need to figure out who did this,
how they found out
and stop them before
it's too late.
I know... I'm so sorry...
Rumors are flying around
town that horrifying,
unretouched photographs
of Natalie Whitman--
still carrying her Jenna Fletcher
weight like an albatross--
have been lost by
"Mode" magazine.
Now if and when they turn up,
we will immediately broadcast
them right here on "Fashion TV."
Remember,
we only make others feel
bad to make you feel good.
I have no idea
how this happened.
The book was not in my
possession at the time.
Absolutely, I understand
the severity of this.
Though I think it'll just
be Daniel at the meeting.
He is, after all,
the editor in chief
and the man in charge.
Yes.
How was Queens?
Like the lost city
of hoochieville.
This Gina Gambarro
didn't miss a beat.
Jumped right for the money.
Poor unemployed thing
just couldn't bear
missing another
episode of Tyra.
Good work, darling.
So you're leaking the pictures?
Ah, of course not.
Just the rumor that
they're there.
There'll be a great deal of
sweating and hand-wringing.
Bradford will realize once and
for all what a dolt his son is.
And we swoop in with the missing
proofs and make ourselves...
I'm sorry...
make you the hero.
Where to, Mr. Meade?
Can you just drive
around for a little bit?
You know,
I could say I was mugged.
I could get my golf club.
You could hit me across the face.
Break my nose.
Daniel, there are a lot of things
I'm willing to do for this job.
That is not one of them.
Plus, how are you gonna explain
being in Queens, anyway?
Betty, my father could
fire me over this.
Maybe I should just have
them take me to J.F.K.,
get a one-way ticket to Paris.
No, Rio.
It's cheaper,
women are much hotter...
I could get a little
place in Ipanema.
And then what?
I don't know. Drink. Party?
As long as I escape the pressure of
ting to be something I am clearly not.
Daniel, if I can suggest...
instead of trying to
escape this or spin it,
why don't you just
tell the truth?
Or you can just blame me.
I don't mind being your
fall girl--guy--person.
Whatever.
If you could just twist
the truth one last time
and give me a good recommendation,
I'd really appreciate it.
Driver, take us back
to the Meade building.
This is an atrocity.
I don't--I don't even
know how to spin this.
This is bad.
This is Mel Gibson bad.
We are so incredibly sorry.
You know,
"sorry" is not gonna cut it.
If those pictures appear on
the internet, on television,
our P.R. firm will never allow any of
our clients anywhere near your magazine.
How did this happen?
Well, it's um...
it's complicated.
They were in my office's
possession at the time.
What do you intend
to do about it?
Well, we have people
out there searching.
We're making phone calls.
We're doing everything
we possibly can.
What does--what
does that mean?!
Will you put a sock
in it already?
What's he gonna do?
Dispatch a commando unit for pictures?
Just calm down.
Just trying to protect you.
Then come up with a solution.
I am trying to come
up with a solution.
Do you know how this could hurt your
career if these pictures got out there?
No one wants to hire a fatty.
What's this gonna publicize,
the fact that you can't lose any weight?
You know how in those samurai movies
they'd rather kill themselves
than be captured or defeated?
Ritual suicide.
It's called seppuku.
Like the beer?
Anyway, this whole situation
with you taking the book to
Queens reminded me of that.
And I figured, rather than live
with the shame of the screwup
and probably end up
getting fired anyway,
wouldn't you rather just quit?
Se-pu-ku, Betty.
- You know what?
- Hmm?
You really do belong
here more than I do.
And I truly hope that you
get everything you deserve.
Oh, thank you.
Bye.
Can you hold the
elevator, please?
Hey, empanada girl.
Betty, right?
Yeah.
God, what happened
to that bunny?
It looks like it was
stuck in a blender.
It probably was.
It's had a tough
couple of days.
So you moving offices?
Actually, um...
I'm quitting.
But I'm probably
fired anyway, so...
What? Why?
Look, the whole business with
the book and the photos...
it's my fault,
not Daniel's and not "mode's."
I was taking care of the
book when it was stolen.
It's just a lowly
assistant screwup,
and I don't want it to
reflect badly on anyone else,
and I'm really sorry for
any pain or embarrassment
or hurt that it
might cause you, but
for what it's worth,
I really did think that those
unretouched photos were beautiful.
And the truth is...
well, I'd kill to
look like you.
It was my fault. No one else's.
The book was my responsibility,
and I left it out of my possession.
I was careless...
stupid.
And I know what
you're thinking.
No.
No?
I'm thinking, for once my son is
actually being honest with me.
He's in a meeting!
I need to speak to
him right away.
I tried to stop her.
Look, I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I need to speak to you.
Okay.
First, you can't fire that
wonderful assistant of yours.
Oh, yes, he can.
She inspired me to come
up with a solution
to fix this whole problem.
Get me Bradford.
He's on line one.
Bradford, good news.
The book and the
proofs turned up.
Well, my people were on
a manhunt and, uh...
what do you mean
it doesn't matter?
On--on "Fashion TV"? Wha--
In a stunning new twist in
today's major fashionistic drama,
Natalie Whitman has decided
to preempt any embarrassment
her missing photographs
may have caused
by allowing "Mode" magazine
to reveal the real her
and publish the pictures
completely unretouched.
I just wanna put a spotlight on
the hypocrisy of this business
which seems intent on making
any normal human being
feel like an outcast.
Does this audacious move by recently
installed editor Daniel Meade
mark the beginning of a newer,
nicer "Mode"?
God help us all.
Great news, isn't it?
Wonderful.
So it turned up?
Anonymously dropped
off at the front desk.
Lucky thing.
Indeed.
I'll make sure it's never
out of my sight again.
Please do that.
Good night, Daniel.
Good night, Wilhelmina.
Night.
Bastard.
Well, I've done the
best I can with it,
but to be honest,
I think you're screwed.
Well, thank you, Christina.
- Do you have 'em?
- I do.
- Here they are.
- Thank you.
Bought myself another day so I
can honestly go through this.
You know, come here.
Take a look at this.
"Betty Suarez,
executive assistant."
You found the error?
That's my job.
Oh, um... so these are
american-made, non-sweatshop,
and I promise you they're as
comfortable as the Magginis.
Thank you, Betty, really.
You know I'm actually--
you can go home.
I'm gonna be here
for a little while.
Okay. Good night.
Bye, Amanda.
And though my bunny and I
are a little worse for wear,
we're here,
and we're staying,
and it's gonna take a hell of a lot
more to get rid of either one of us.
Good night!
Whatever!
I'm still prettier.
This is Daniel.
It's amazing how little we can
know about the people we love.
Your father, for instance.
What? Who is this?
He's a man of many,
many secrets, Daniel.
Dig a little deeper,
and you may find he's capable
of practically anything.
Transcript : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com