[Man Wheezing, Coughing]
[Man]
The Navy...
wantedtohearmystory.
Theysaidlowedit to the dead
to tell them the truth.
I told them
where tostick the truth.
[ Coughing ]
I'm the last one
who knows...
what killed the men
aboard that submarine,
who knows
it was a suicide mission.
But I'll burn in hell before I tell
the murderers who sent us there.
That's why we've comehere
all the way from Washington, sailor,
to hearyour story, to make sure
thatjustice is served.
You said that
afteryour outburst,
the X.O.,Johansen,
locked you up with your captain.
johansen did
what he had to.
That's war.
Some are sacrificed
so that others can live.
You've gotta get us
out ofhere !
[ Screaming ]
Let go !
[Man]
But when thatdoorshut,
Iknewmylife, allourlives,
hadjustbeensacrificed.
johansen !
Open this door !
- [Pounding]
- Open this door!Johansen!
[Man] Forthe fiirst time,
wesawthe enemy that waskilling us.
That thing...
was causing theslow,
painful deaths.
And I prayed one oftheJapanese
depth charges would finish thejob.
You called this thing
"the enemy."
You're saying
it was an entity ofsome sort ?
The Navysays we weresent
torecoveranA-bomb,
that's why wegot
all theseburns.
Give me a freakin' break.
Whatever it was,
we were sent to guard it.
This was what exposed
the crew to radiation ?
Before it slithered away,
back to where it came from,
back into the sea,
back into who knows what.
That thing...
is still down there !
The Navy'll denyit,
butyou've got to make sure
the truth gets out.
I can trustyou to do that,
can't l, Mr. Mulder ?
You can trust all ofus.
Excuse me. I'm looking
forWalter Skinner.
-He was brought in with a gunshot wound.
-[Man] AgentScully.
Agent Fuller.
This is Agent Caleca. We got
the call from the D.C. police.
- How bad is he ?
- We don't know. He's been in surgery.
- What happened ?
- Hothead drew a gun. Skinner
happened to be in the way.
- What doyou have on the shooter ?
- A description.
A handgun was recovered in the
parking lot, unregistered, no prints.
- Our guys got two partials
offthe cash register.
- Hair and fiber ?
- This happened a few hours ago.
- This is the assistant director
who's been shot.
We have to
make all resources available.
Excuse me.
- How is he ?
- He came out ofsurgery all right,
but he's in pain.
I've seen him before,
the man who shot me.
[Bell Dings]
Give me the key.
When we get there.
I want to make sure we get there
together. Give it to me.
What's "C.I." mean ?
When we get there.
[MonitorBeeping]
How's he doing ?
He's on steady Demerol.
He's in and out.
- I thought I asked for guards
to be posted outside.
- We put in a request.
This wasn't a random shooting.
I want guards posted here,
and I want them here now.
- It's a matter ofpulling men
offsomething else.
- I've heard the excuses.
I don't care ifyou and
Agent Caleca have to stand
out in the hallwayyourselves.
This man has to be
protected, okay ?
[EngineStarts]
I thinkwe're being followed.
A dark sedan with its lights off.
It wasparkedon theshoulder
abouthalfamileback. Speedup.
Speed up.
[ Engine Accelerates ]
[TiresSquealing,
Engine Revving]
Get out.
- Where's the digital tape ?
- I don't have it.
[ Groans ]
[ManScreaming]
[Man #2]
Hey, areyouallright ?
[Screaming Continues]
- I got a messageyou called.
- Goodmorning.
- We found something I knew
you'd want to see A.S.A.P.
- On the shooter ?
Yeah. The partial prints
we pulled from the cash register
didn't add up to anything,
but we found saliva
on Skinner's shirt that wasn't his.
This is an analysis ofthe secretors
and other hemofactors.
Which tells us we're looking
for a male, probably in his 40s
with blood type B-positive.
- We already know all that from
the waitress's description.
- There's more.
We were able to chromosome-stain
the hair fibers we picked up last night.
- We still gotta find the guy
before we can get a match.
- We canrunhis indicators...
againstallsuspectsarrestedin
the D. C. areain thelastcoupleyears.
That takes too much time.
You know what ? Run it anyway.
Can I borrow this for a little while ?
- Go ahead.
- Thanks.
Wepickedhim up lastnight.
Theburnsaresomatic,
caused by close proximity
radiation exposure.
Same as the French sailors
aboard that salvage ship. Identical.
- What's the prognosis ?
- It'sjust a matter oftime.
This kind ofabsorption will have
a rapid effect on cellular activity,
giving rise to the onset
ofmassive and malignant cancers.
Has anyone been in
to see these men ?
No. Yourorders
were toisolate them.
Butl think weshouldget
aspecialistinherebecause,
frankly, I'veneverseen
anything like thisbefore.
I have.
Doyou know what caused this ?
Have the bodies destroyed.
But-- But, sir,
these men aren't dead yet.
Isn't that the prognosis ?
Guess I'm not dead.
[ Chuckles ]
What happened ?
-Maybeyou could tell me.
-The state police found you unconscious.
You were strapped in
the passenger's seat ofa rental car...
that had been
driven into a ditch.
We were run offthe road
by two men.
- Who's "we" ?
- Krycek.
Krycek ?
He was in Hong Kong.
He's got the digital tape.
He's been selling information.
Is that what
the men wanted ?
They ordered him out ofthe car.
I thought theywere gonna kill him.
I thought theywere
gonna kill us both.
And then there was
this bright fash.
That's all I remember.
Well, it may not be the best time
to tell you, but...
you're not the only one
in the hospital.
- Skinner's been shot.
- What's his condition ?
A bullet perforated
his small intestine.
The doctor seems
to think he'll be fine.
- Who shot him ?
- I'm notsure.
But I have an idea.
What are those ?
P.C.R. results.
This one belongs to the man
who shot Skinner.
Yeah, and who does
this one belong to ?
The man who shot Melissa.
You may all be wondering why I've called
you here on such short notice.
We've received disturbing reports
from our intelligence sources.
A French salvage vessel
came into San Diego,
its crew all dying of
radiation exposure.
Its last given position was the site
where we recovered the U.F.O.
How could they have got information
about that location ?
We haven't been able
to determine that.
The Frenchgovernment
has deniedanyinvolvement.
Well, they got those
coordinates somehow.
It seems we have
an information leak, gentlemen.
Has our associate in Washington
looked into this ?
Apparently,
hehas respondedto thesituation...
in a way that I don't think
any ofus would have anticipated.
- How doyou mean ?
- I don't have all the details yet,
but I've asked him to come here
and explain it himself.
Hi.
How areyou feeling ?
Like someone's been
inside my stomach redecorating.
What haveyou turned up
on the shooter ?
We've determined that the man who shot
you is the same man who shot my sister.
I betyou had to work
to get that, huh ?
Yes, I did.
You don't seem surprised.
Three men came to see me
a few days ago.
They warnedmeaboutpursuing
yoursister'smurderinvestigation.
Doyou realize
whatyou're saying, sir ?
I'm not advancing any
conspiracy theory here, Scully.
You're saying they
closed down my sister's case...
not because oflack ofevidence,
but because they didn't
want us to catch the killer.
You should be very careful
about the accusations thatyou make.
The man who shotyou--
You said thatyou'd seen him before.
Several months ago,
he was one ofthe men who attacked me...
in the stairwell,
with Krycek.
He was working
with Krycek ?
- They're the ones who stole
the digital tape from me.
- Damnit!
- Krycek. Mulder had him.
- Listen tome.
Anger is a luxury thatyou
cannot afford right now.
Ifyou'reangry,
you'regonnamakeamistake,
andthesepeople
will takeadvantage ofthat.
You've seen how they operate.
- I'll be okay.
- Scully--
Ifyou can't keepyour head,
it's all right to step away.
That's exactly
what theywant.
[ScullyReading]
'Addendum to casenumber621517.
In theabsence
ofanyoffiicialresponse...
tomyrequest tohave
mysister's casereopened,
Iam nowpetitioning to
devote fulIBureauresources...
to thesearch forAlex Krycek.
SinceAgentMulder's release
from thehospital,
wehavehadnosuccess
locating Krycek...
orthe twomenhe described
ashisabductors.
Personally, lbelieve Krycek
is thekeytoidentifying...
thelargerforces
behindthe crime weare investigating.
Healone canname theman
whoshotmysister...
andexplain thestrangeradiation deaths
aboard the Frenchsalvage vessel. "
Itlookedgreatonme
in thestore.
- What's this doing here ?
- I had it fown in from
San Diego as evidence.
- Evidence ofwhat ?
- The suit was covered
in a thin film ofoil,
as was the French diverwhen I found him
lying delirious on his kitchen foor.
- What kind ofoil ?
- From the reports I'm getting,
it's the same substance...
that was found on the French diver's
wife when she was discovered...
on the foor ofa Hong Kong
airport bathroom a few days ago.
According to the analysis,
it's 50-weight diesel oil, Scully.
That's thesame oil usedon World Warll
submarinesandon P-51 Mustangs.
- I don't understand.
- This oil is not only
50 years old, Scully,
but its composition has been altered
by exposure to radiation.
I still don't understand.
How did this get onto the diver
and then onto the diver's wife ?
I don't think this isjust ordinary
diesel oil, Scully. I think it's, uh--
I think it's a medium.
A medium being used by some kind
ofalien creature that uses it to...
bodyjump.
Soyou're saying this stuff
has intelligence.
I think that it came offof
whatever they pulled from
the bottom ofthe Pacific Ocean.
It's been waiting down there
for 50 years for another host,
another body to bring it
up to the surface.
Waiting tojump into the diver
and then into the diver's wife.
- And then to Krycek.
- Krycek ?
I think that Mrs. Gauthierwent
to Hong Kong under the control
ofthis thing to find Krycek--
- I know-- I know how it sounds.
- Is anybody not looking for Krycek ?
No, but I think the $64,000 question is,
what is this thing looking for ?
And now that it's in Krycek,
what does it want ?
~~[P.A.: "Blue Danube"]
- Nothin' to it.
- You should call upon
our services more often.
We show a talent for
these G-man activities.
You mean ifl want somebody
whacked on the knee with a lead pipe ?
Only ifyou want
thejob done right.
It's gone.
- [ Shouting, lndistinct ]
- [ Gunfire ]
- Grenade !
Where is it ?
I've been expecting you.
- [ Gun Cocks ]
- Put that down !
I have whatyou want.
[DoorOpens]
You made us wait.
There was a weather delay
on the shuttle from Washington.
You had business there ?
Yes.
You, uh, may have
already heard.
We've heard
you acted on your own...
and moved the salvaged U.F.O.
to another location.
These new attempts to recover it
have increased our need for security.
Who else is looking for it ?
In the event,
I moved it as a safeguard.
Somebody better damn well
find out how the French
even knew where to look for it.
I can assureyou
it'll be absolutely inaccessible now.
Why not bring it to Nevada,
like the others ?
Leaks in security and
a heightened public interest
have made Nevada unviable.
- Is this why I was called here ?
- No.
We'd like an explanation
about this business...
with the assistant director
ofthe Bureau, Skinner.
Random shooting,
for all I know.
They have a waitress who's
given a description ofthe shooter.
Theyreleaseda composite
ofhis face to thepress.
One ofyours, isn'the ?
I don't know
what to tell you.
- Ifhe did, he acted on his own.
- Good Lord.
- This is a very serious
exposure for us.
- I'll take care ofit.
My advice toyou, sir,
is to understand the priorities here.
Get thisshooteroutofthe country
as quicklyaspossible.
Ifthe assistant director
l.D.'s him,
ourwell-placed operatives won't be
able to stand in the way ofan arrest,
compromisingbeyondrepair
thesecrecyofour work...
and the security, as you so arrogantly
assert, ofour project's future.
It'll be handled.
I've got something here:
writing.
Somebodywrote on top ofthe package
and left an impression.
- Let me see that.
- Your guys at the F.B.I....
turnedamajorserialmurderer
witha vestigialpenimpression.
- It does look like something.
- Your sci-crime guys at the
Bureau have a laser there...
that can measure any change
in a surface down to a few nanometers.
[Man] They canliftaperfect
impression usingmagnetic toner
andasheetofMylar.
An electrostatic device
is appliedto thespecimen
andrenders theinformation...
by drawing the toner from
the indentations to the Mylar surface.
- Actually--
- Actually, it's a phone number.
New York Cityarea code,
555-1012.
Now, don't drop that.
That's a finely calibrated piece
ofinvestigative equipment.
- I gotta make a phone call.
- I'll be damned.
[Phone Ringing]
[Ringing Continues]
Yes.
No. This is a private line.
You must have misdialed.
No. There'sno onehere
to takeyour call.
I'm sorry.
I can't helpyou.
Please hold on.
Who is this ?
Who gaveyou
this number ?
You probably know him.
A man named Krycek.
- Alex Krycek ?
- Yeah.
Nice guy. Killed my father.
You wouldn't happen to know
where he is, doyou ?
It's Mr. Mulder, isn't it ?
[ Chuckles ]
It's so nice ofyou to remember.
Mr. Mulder,
can we meet somewhere ?
Oh, I would love to.
Giveyour phone number to my assistant.
He'll call you back in five minutes.
Tell him I'll meet him
in three hours in Central Park,
near the lighted walkway
off79th, near the reservoir.
When you hang up,
have this number disconnected.
Well, we got a name
to go with the face.
- Beautiful.
- Hisnameis Luis Cardinal,
native of Nicaragua,
School ofthe Americas alumni,
career mercenary,
apparently impressed a lot ofpeople...
with his marksmanship
during the lran-Contra deal.
- I'll bet.
- That's actually the good news.
- Whatdoyoumean ?
- He entered the country
without a visa or papers.
We can't find anything on him: address,
phone number, financials, nothing.
- Does he have an alias ?
- Several. None checked out either.
InaIllikelihood,
thisguy'salreadyoutofthe country.
Damn it. They think they
canjust get awaywith it.
I wish
I could tell you otherwise.
Keep looking for him.
We've... pretty much
exhausted our avenues.
- What's it gonna take ?
- At this point ?
Other than a sign from God ?
I've seen stranger things,
believe me.
- [DoorOpens, Closes]
- I believe she has.
I trust we're alone.
We're all alone
in New York City, sir.
You're looking forAlex Krycek,
to kill him... in revenge.
- What makes you think
we haven't done that already ?
- What for ?
Tell me whatyou know,
and I'll consider giving you Krycek.
No. You answer
a few questions for me first,
Iike what was pulled offthe bottom
ofthe Pacific Ocean.
It was a U.F.O.,
a so-called Foo Fighter...
downed byAmerican fighter pilots
in the Second World War.
- Left there until now ?
- There were salvage attempts.
A U.S. sub was sent in 50 years ago,
but there were complications.
- Almost the entire crew died.
- Yes. It's still a mystery.
A mystery to whom ?
The cover story said
it was the third A-bomb bound forJapan.
But the truth is,
no one knows what killed that crew.
- I know.
- Doyou, now ?
- You give me Krycek, and I'll tell you.
- Mr. Mulder,
I've given you
so much this evening.
You've offered me
next to nothing in return.
You haven't told me
anything I didn't already know.
I'm curious.
Ifyou've encountered Krycek,
why didn'tyou kill him then ?
'Cause he has the tape.
Ah, yes, the tape.
The tape he's been
selling those secrets off.
You don't know
where he is either, doyou ?
You're
looking for him too.
Mr. Mulder,
anyone can be gotten to.
Certainly,
you've no doubt ofthat.
Mr. Mulder !
- [ Ringing ]
- Scully.
[ Mulder]
Scully, it's me.
Those two guards you had posted outside
Skinner's room. Are they still there ?
- They should be. Why ?
- I wantyou to get down there
and double-check for me, okay ?
- I got it covered, Mulder.
-Just get down there and check, okay ?
Nurse, what happened to the guards
who were outside this room ?
- They've left.
- Where ? And what happened
to the man in this room ?
-Mr. Skinner'snolongerapatienthere.
-Where is he ?
The orderlies wereherea few
moments ago, andtheytookhim away.
- Where did they take him ?
- To another hospital.
- The ambulance must havejust left.
- Thankyou.
I'm with the F.B.I. Areyou
transporting a Walter Skinner ?
Yeah.
Is there something wrong ?
No. Everything is fine.
I'm just gonna ride with you
the rest ofthe way, okay ?
Agent Scully,
what areyou doing here ?
I just wanted to make sure
you got whereyou were going safely.
[ Exhales ]
What is it, Scully ?
just lie still.
[ Horns Honking ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
Federal agent !
Stop right there !
- Areyou Luis Cardinal ?
Areyou Luis Cardinal ?
- Please.
- Areyou the man that shot my sister ?
- Please don't kill me.
- You shot my sister !
- Please. I can tell you.
- Tell me ! Tell me !
- Ican tellyou.
I can tell you whatyou want.
You want... Krycek.
Ican tellyou whereheis.
Please !
Please don't shoot me.
[Siren Wailing]
- [TiresScreeching]
- [Man] Drop thegun !
- [Police Radio Chatter]
- Put thegun down !
Putitdownnow!
F.B.I.
- Don't move ! Easy !
- Got him.
Standback, please.
- [Handcuffs Clicking]
- Get up !
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- Yeah. Mulder.
- Mulder, it's me. Where areyou ?
- I'm at the airport in New York.
- What areyou doing ?
I'm looking for
my rental car agreement.
- What areyou doing in New York ?
- I'll tell you when I seeyou.
Mulder, your instincts
were right about Skinner.
Wejust arrested a man
forwhat looks like attempted murder.
Who ?
- It's him, Mulder,
the man who shot my sister.
- Uh, Scully--
Mulder, listen to me.
He says he knows where Krycek is.
I don't know ifthis
makes any sense toyou,
but he says that he's headed
towards an abandoned missile
site somewhere in North Dakota.
I wantyou to meet me
at the D.C. airport in an hour.
I wantyou to get two tickets
on the first fight to North Dakota.
- What's in North Dakota ?
- The salvaged U.F.O.
There must be
200 silos out here.
Ifl'm correct, theywere
all filled with concrete...
in accord with the disarmament treaty
when the base was decommissioned.
I didn't sign
any disarmament treaty.
- My ears are still popping.
- We're eight stories down.
[ Squeaking, Clanking ]
Where's the concrete ?
Apparently, nobody else
signed that treaty either.
One down,
one hundred ninety-nine silos to go.
[Scully]
These tunnelsmustgo on formiles.
[DoorCloses]
He's here.
Hold it right there ! Halt !
Hands in the air !
Come on ! Come on !
He's here.
- You led him here, didn'tyou ?
- There's nothing here
but holes in the ground.
-Why areyou here ? Why all these men ?
-I don't oweyou any answers.
The U.F.O.'s here.
That's what Krycek's after, isn't it ?
Krycek ? Alex Krycek
disappeared five months ago.
- We saw bodies in there.
Men with radiation burns !
- You saw nothing !
You won't
get awaywith this !
You can't bury the truth !
[FootstepsApproaching]
Take these away.
[Grunting]
[Man Groaning]
[Painful Groaning]
[ Continues Groaning ]
- [Knocking]
- Yeah.
- Agent Mulder.
- Sir, I didn't expectyou
back to work for a few weeks.
I was looking forAgent Scully.
There was something I wanted
to talk to her about.
Actually,
I wanted to talk toyou.
I wanted to thankyou
for everything you did.
You mean getting
shot in the gut ?
You got shot becauseyou stood up
to these people.
I thinkyou're proceeding from
a mistaken impression. What
I did I did because it's myjob.
From what I understand,
you putyourjob and your life
on the line for Scully.
This isn't my crusade, Agent Mulder.
A woman was murdered.
I mistakenly thought
we could bring the man who
committed that crime tojustice.
- What doyou mean, "mistakenly" ?
- That's what I need
to talk to Scully about.
I wasjust thinking about something
that a man said to me.
That the--
That the dead speak to us
from beyond the grave.
That that's
what conscience is.
That's interesting.
I never thought ofit that way.
You know, I thought...
when we found him,
this man that
killed Melissa, that--
that when we brought him tojustice,
I would feel some kind ofclosure.
But the truth is,
no court...
no punishment,
is ever enough.
I came here to
tell you something, Scully.
There may be somejustice,
just not the kind you're looking for.
What areyou
talking about ?
They found this man, Luis Cardinal,
dead in his cell.
- How ?
- They made it look like a suicide.
The men he worked for
couldn't take the chance that
he'd point his finger at them.
And what about Krycek ?
Oh, he was there.
I know that.
You think
they got to him too ?
I don't know.
But ifthey haven't, theywill.
I doubt it'll weigh on
their consciences, though.
I think the dead are
speaking to us, Mulder,
demandingjustice.
Maybe that man
was right.
Maybe we
bury the dead alive.
[Pounding]
[Krycek]
Help! H-Help !
Uhh !
Help me !
[ Agonized Screaming ]
- [Pounding]
- Help me ! Help ! Help !
No ! Help me !
Help me !
Help me ! Help me !
[ Screaming Continues ]