[Man Chattering]
[Woman] That's a little
hard to believe.
[Man]Really?
No, I'm pretty much of a homebody.
But all that changed,
just from your words,
the way you saw things.
I knew
I wanted to meet you.
Well, I hope you’re not
too disappointed.
Lauren, we have a real connection,
which is rare.
Most men don't feel
that way.
Most men don't know
what they're missing.
- [ Nervous Giggle ]
- What?
I can't believe this.
I-l mean, I can't believe
that after three months,
we finally meet in person,
and you're--
I don't know. I'm just
really enjoying myself tonight.
Oh, no. Oh.
Here. Let me help you.
My sister gave it to me.
For good luck, I guess.
Kind of dopey, huh?
I mean, a cloverleaf.
How blatant can you get?
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
[ Muffed Screams ]
[Indistinct
Police Radio Chatter]
Cock-a-doodle-doo.
Rise and shine in there.
Mother of God.
[Policeman]Dispatcher,
this is car seven-three.
I got a D.P. out on the lakefront
at Erie and Capitol. Over.
[Chattering]
We're not 1 00% certain,
but from the driver's license,
we suspect that
it's Lauren Mackalvey.
I want you to get on it.
All right.
We'll check this out.
- Why don't we go and check around?
-Sounds good.
Agent Mulder?
Alan Cross, Cleveland P.D.
Thanks a lot for coming out
so quickly.
- This is my partner, Dana Scully.
- Hi.
We found the purse in the front seat
of that car over there.
According to the license,
her name is, uh, Lauren Mackalvey,
but, uh, we're not sure
yet that this is her body.
You're not sure?
We couldn't make a positive I.D.,
considering.
Wendy Sparks,
she's our bureau liaison.
She thought this would be, uh,
closer to your area of expertise.
Any indication what would have been
the cause of death?
We were lucky to get her into the bag
without her body falling apart.
This substance, did you find it
anywhere else in the car?
In the carpet
or the upholstery?
As a matter of fact, no.
So, it was only
on the victim's body.
That's what
it looks like.
Why?
Do you have an idea
what happened here?
No. Not yet.
We'll call you when we find
anything else concrete.
- Detective?
- Yeah, sure. Call me.
[ Chattering ]
Mulder, what do you think
it is?
A couple months ago, a case came across
my desk from the Mississippi office.
Four women from Aberdeen
had disappeared in less than a month.
- Disappeared?
- Only one of the victims was found,
but her body was too decomposed
to perform a viable autopsy.
- What we saw was not decomposition.
- I know.
I want you to find out what this
is while you’re at the coroner's.
What about you?
Where are you going?
I'm going to try to find out
if Lauren Mackalvey was a lonely heart.
Each of the Aberdeen victims answered
personal ads in the local papers.
If this is the same killer,
he’s just getting started.
[Computer Keys Clacking]
[ Chuckles ]
[Knock At Door]
Yes. What is it?
The handyman replaced the locks
on the storage closets,
and I wanted to bring by
your new key.
I know what you do,
Mr. Incanto.
What is it you think
that I do?
With all your typing and those packages
from publishers in New York?
You're a novelist, right?
Or an editor.
You see,
I'm a writer, too.
What a coincidence.
Shouldn’t you be off
writing or something?
I don't mean to impose, but would you
mind reading something of mine ?
It won't take much time.
They're poems.
Certainly.
Good-bye.
[ Door Lock Clicks ]
Oh, it's you.
That's not a problem,
is it?
No. Just that Dr. Kramer didn't tell me
that you were observing the autopsy.
I'm not observing.
I'm performing it myself.
You're a medical doctor?
You sound surprised.
I don't know.
I, uh, I guess maybe I am.
- Why?
- It's nothing personal, Agent Scully.
I'm just... old-fashioned
in certain regards.
"Old-fashioned"?
The truth is,
I question the wisdom...
of assigning female law enforcement
officers to certain types of cases.
Like this one?
Whoever killed Lauren Mackalvey has
a definite attitude toward women, right?
So this has to be affecting
your judgment.
I appreciate your concern, Detective,
but it's not necessary.
All I want to do is solve this case,
just like you.
Look. I'm not being sexist here.
I'm just being honest.
Where would you like
the autopsy report sent?
You can fax it
to my office.
The date is August 29.
The time is 4:1 5 p.m.
The subject's name is Lauren Mackalvey,
Caucasian, female.
Approximate time of death
uncertain.
Cause of death unknown.
[Woman]
It just doesn't make sense.
He seemed so nice.
I thought you said you never met
the man Lauren was with last night.
I never did. He just seemed nice
on the computer.
Oh, they met through
an on-line service?
In one of those
chat rooms.
You know, where people get together
to talk about whatever they're into.
Right. Do you remember what chat room
Lauren was in when she met him?
"Big and beautiful. "
She had kind of a weight problem.
But "2Shy"
didn’t seem to care.
It wasn't about sex
with him.
- "2Shy"?
- That was his on-line name.
Lauren used to...
read me his letters.
They were amazing.
He knew exactly
what to say.
Sure as hell fooled me.
She read you his letters. Do you think
that she kept any hard copies of them?
Actually...
I saved them myself.
If you want,
I could get them for you.
Yes.
Can I use your phone?
Yeah, it's right
over there.
[ Phone Ringing ]
- Scully.
- Listen, Scully.
Our killer may have moved out of the
personal columns and onto the internet.
I'm going to send out
a localized on-line warning.
How do you know
it's the same guy?
Because he opened the account with one
of the Aberdeen victim's credit cards.
I just called
the on-line service.
Mulder, meet me in the coroner's office
as soon as you can.
- Did you find anything?
- There's not going to be an autopsy.
[ Scully] It's a metacarpal
from Lauren Mackalvey's hand.
In life, bones have
the tensile strength of forged iron.
Even in death, they remain strong.
But look at this.
What did this
turn out to be?
It's organic,
mostly hydrochloric acid.
Similar to what is secreted
by the gastric mucosa.
It's similar
to stomach acid?
Almost identical,
only twice as acidic.
I also found trace amounts of pepsin,
which is a digestive enzyme.
So, you're saying
that this did that?
I don't know how else to explain
such accelerated autolysis.
Okay, what's in here,
Scully, theoretically should contain...
the same cellular components
as her various tissues, right?
Skin, muscle, blood.
In some broken-down form,
yes.
In the results of your chemical
analysis, did you find anything missing?
- Missing?
- Yeah.
I don't think so.
All of the body tissues
were accounted for.
Except there were extremely low,
almost trace amounts of adipose.
Fatty tissue.
That could explain
the weight discrepancy.
What weight discrepancy?
Well, the M.E. recorded
Lauren's weight at 1 22,
but her driver's license
had her at 1 65.
Well, she probably lost weight
since the license was issued.
Actually, Lauren's roommate said she was
quite nervous about meeting this guy,
because she'd put on
some weight recently.
[ Scoffs ]
What possible motivation
could the killer have...
for removing
his victim's fatty tissue?
I mean, who do you think
we're dealing with here?
I don't know.
God, I look awful.
Please tell me it's the mirror.
Ellen, this wasn't
some public-service announcement.
It was an on-line warning by the F.B.I.
aimed at women in Cleveland.
Give me some credit,
will you, Jo?
I happen to be
a pretty good judge of character.
Look. I'm not trying to
freak you out or anything.
No? Well, you're doing
a pretty good job of it.
I just think you should
be careful, that's all.
Do you think
this is easy for me?
I finally connect with someone
I like who seems to like me.
I'm scared enough to meet him
for the first time...
without you telling me
he's Charles Manson.
I didn't say that.
Besides, it's not like
he's some stranger.
I've been chatting with him
every day for over a month.
I know. And he's probably
as great as he sounds.
But what if he isn't?
[ Sighs ]
- Check it out.
- Want a little chocolate tonight ?
[ Chattering Continues ]
- Hey, baby. Right here.
- [ Horn Honks ]
[ Chattering Continues ]
[Woman]Right over here, baby.
I'm here.
Got what you need over here,
if you'd like some of this.
Ooh, yeah.
See something you like?
- You want some?
- He have the hots for you, baby.
I think so.
-[Laughs]
- Hey, hey!
What do you like, baby?
Uh-uh. No kissing.
Anything else you want
is fine, but no kissing.
[Belt Clinking]
What are you doing?
[ Screams ]
Aah! Oh!
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Screams ]
There's a place we can go near here.
Nice and cozy.
Okay.
[Woman Laughing]
[ Gasping ]
Uh-uh. Forget this.
Oh, my God.
[Man]Make sure you get statements
from all of them.
Her name was Holly McClaine.
She's worked this area
for a couple of years now,
but she wasn't most Johns' first pick,
if you know what I mean.
What happened?
Looks like our guy again.
One of the other girls found her.
All of the air passages are blocked
with what appears to be...
the same viscous hydrochloric acid
we found on Lauren Mackalvey.
You know what this stuff is?
Hey, this is still my case.
We're dealing with
a serial murderer...
who's using an on-line service
to attract his victims.
All single women
looking for Mr. Right.
That doesn’t jibe
with a $20 hooker.
No, it doesn't. Something must have
gone wrong last night.
He was forced
to improvise.
We're still talking about
a guy without a consistent M.O.
Not necessarily.
These are letters he E-mailed
to Lauren Mackalvey.
They contain lines from a handful of
1 6th-century Italian poems.
So he has a copy of
Bartlett's Quotations. So what?
You won't find any of these
in Bartlett's.
- I'm not sure I follow you.
- Look at this.
Ginaselli's La Vita Nuova,
Castionni's Il Cortigiano,
and a few others I won't
even try to pronounce.
These are from obscure text from
privately-owned libraries that only lend
to academic affiliates.
You're saying our-- our suspect's
a college professor?
Or a graduate student,
a visiting fellow, maybe a translator.
What we need to do is compile a list
of everybody in the Cleveland area...
who has these kind
of credentials.
- Can you do that?
- Yeah. I'll get right on it.
Here's something else
that might help.
The killer should have
an identifiable wound pattern from this.
Looks like she took
her pound of flesh, huh?
[Doorbell Buzzes]
Yes?
[ Man ] I got a package for Incanto
from Stratcher Publishing.
- Leave it.
- Sorry. I gotta get a signature.
[ Sighs ]
Hello, Mr. Incanto.
Good afternoon, Jesse.
[Woman]Jesse, did you find
those drop cloths yet?
Oh, Mr. Incanto. I didn't know
you were out here.
I'm just picking up a package.
Jesse, did you know
that Mr. Incanto's a writer?
I know, Mom.
You told me a thousand times.
[Embarrassed Chuckle]
I’m putting those poems together.
If you don't mind,
I’d like to drop them by sometime.
just slip it
under my door.
After you’ve read them,
can I take you to dinner somewhere?
- [Jesse ] Give me a break.
- I'm busy. I have a deadline.
I don't believe this.
-[Knocking At Door]
-[Man]Excuse me.
I wish you weren't
always so rude to him.
I don't care.
He creeps me out.
Plus he smells gross,
like he uses dish soap for after shave.
[ Scoffs ]
[ Computer Keys Clacking ]
[Cross]
Okay.
Blaine just gave me the list from the
university. How's it going over here?
[Scully]Good.
We're just expanding the search...
to include the faculty rosters
from the local community colleges.
We-- Oh, excuse me.
Sure. I'll let you know
what we turn up.
[ Mulder]
Did you find anything?
We're almost done
with the list.
That skin you found
under the prostitute's fingernails?
I had the lab check the DNA results
against the known offenders database.
And?
Well, it says here
they didn't find a match.
No, but they did
find something else.
Check the next page
where it's circled.
"The skin sample contains no oils
or essential fatty acid."
There are any number of factors
which could have caused that result.
Where are you going
with this?
Okay, it's not yet the finely-detailed
insanity you’ve come to expect from me.
It's just a theory,
but what if he's not doing this...
out of a psychotic impulse but rather
out of some physical hunger?
Maybe he needs to replenish
this chemical deficiency to survive.
From a dry-skin sample,
you're concluding what?
That he's some kind
of a fat-sucking vampire?
I don't know how else to explain
Lauren Mackalvey's missing adipose.
I bet if you check the Aberdeen victims,
you'd find exactly the same thing.
This killer secretes a digestive
substance which renders the fat--
Which he ingests before
the rest of the body dissolves entirely.
There are examples
of this in nature, aren't there?
Yeah, scorpions predigest
their food outside of their body...
by regurgitating onto their prey.
But I don't know too many scorpions
who surf the internet.
Okay, but if I'm right, then we're
not just looking for a serial murderer.
We're looking for some kind
of genetically-different human being,
a creature who may be responsible for
who knows how many missing persons...
throughout the United States.
We've combed every faculty list
and academic journal in Cleveland.
Came up with 38 names.
I figured we'd divvy up the list,
and I'd get the captain
to put more people on it.
I'd like to brief them,
if that’s okay with you.
Sure.
- [ Beeps ]
- [ Computer Voice ] You have mail.
[Knock At Door]
Mr. Brenman?
I'm Special Agent Scully from the F.B.I.
Would you mind if I ask you
some questions?
Thanks. I'm sorry
to bother you.
I'd like to ask you
a few questions.
Sure.
[Scully] These are all
university addresses.
Chances are he spent
most of the morning on campus.
Scully.
I wouldn't have made
a good Amway salesman.
- I knocked on more doors than--
- Cross hasn't checked in yet.
We've been trying his cell phone,
but there's no answer.
- I'm treating you.
- No, I insist.
After the way I stood you up,
I'm the one who should insist.
Please?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have--
It's a kind of eczema.
I've had it since I was a kid.
Oh.
You know, I still feel so stupid
about the other night.
Ellen, you don't have to
make any excuses.
Whatever reasons you had,
I'm sure they were good ones.
You were right, though,
about me being afraid.
It's a pretty hard habit
to break.
You're not still afraid,
are you?
- No, I'm not.
- Good.
Unfortunately,
I have to get going.
The last cross town bus
leaves in 1 5 minutes.
- You're taking the bus home?
- My car's in the shop. I'll call you.
- Don't be silly. I'll drive you.
- Ellen, you don't have to.
I'm driving you home.
Mr. Incanto?
So, how long
have you lived here?
Not very long.
You know, I only live
a few blocks away,
near St. Mark's, until some developer
decided to turn it into condos.
You can still see
the steeple.
Ellen, you don't
have to be nervous.
I'm not very good
at this.
It's been a long time since I've been
in this type of situation.
It's okay.
[ Fly Buzzes ]
- [ Flies Buzzing ]
- [ Sniffing ]
Why don’t you come up
with me?
I'll read you that poem
I told you about-- Il Cassone.
I don't know.
It's kind of late.
Well, I don't want to
say good night just yet, do you?
You know what?
You're absolutely right.
It's late.
I have a lot of work I have to do.
Excuse me.
[Flies Buzzing]
[ Sniffing ]
[ Door Creaks ]
Mr. Incanto?
What is it, Jesse?
Uh, do you know
where my mom is?
Your mother? No.
She takes a class down at
St. Frank's tonight, a poetry class,
and she was supposed to
be home over an hour ago.
I'm sure
she'll be home soon.
She didn't stop by
to say hi or anything?
No. Not tonight.
Okay. Thanks.
She'll probably
be home soon.
I'm going to New York
for a few days on business.
Don't worry
about your mother.
I'm sure she'll be fine.
[Chattering,
Phones Ringing]
-[Man]Cleveland P.D.
-[Mulder]His name’s Cross.
That's right. He would have been by
sometime this afternoon.
[Scully]
Maybe sometime this morning.
Do you remember
what time specifically?
Could you describe him
tome for verification?
Excuse me a minute.
Did you find him?
We just got a 91 1 reporting
a possible homicide...
from a young girl at one of
the addresses on Cross's list.
Police!
[ Chattering ]
[Woman]
Clear back here.
[Man]
We got two inhere.
Mulder.
The landlady's body.
We found her in the bathroom.
What about Cross?
[Scully]I know this is hard to
talk about right now,
but I need you to tell me
exactly what happened.
I smelled her perfume.
Your mother's perfume?
That's when I knew
he was lying.
She was wearing her perfume
when she left for class.
And you smelled it
in his apartment?
I was-- I was scared
that he'd hurt me.
I could tell he wanted to.
And then he grabbed me.
He grabbed you?
After I bumped
into the suitcase,
he grabbed me
pretty hard.
What suitcase?
It was next to the door.
He said he was going away
on business or something.
Did he say where?
Um, New York.
Okay, Jesse,
that helps us.
I'm gonna take a couple minutes
and go talk to Agent Mulder.
Mrs. Shepherd
is right here.
I'll be right back.
-Agent Scully?
- Yeah.
Why would someone
do this?
I don't know, Jesse.
The composite artist came up with this
sketch from a neighbor's description.
His name is Virgil Incanto. That's
what it says on his rental agreement.
But other than that,
there's no record the guy even exists.
There's no D.M.V.,
no birth certificate,
no Social Security,
not even a bank account.
- What about employment records?
- He's a translator of Italian
literature. Freelance.
His publisher pays him
in cashier's checks.
He told the girl he was
on his way to New York.
I'll check fight schedules
and have the airport issue an A.P.B.
What is it?
He's not going to New York,
Scully. Not now.
He's smarter than that.
He knows how to survive,
you know?
Well, how are we
going to track him?
Well, he made contact with each one
of his victims, right?
- Yeah.
- That means they're all here somewhere.
Each one of them--
past, present and future.
All the files
have been deleted.
- Any chance of resurrecting them?
- It's hard to say.
He deliberately reformatted
his hard drive.
This guy didn't want anyone
looking at his stuff.
[ Computer Beeps ]
Hmm.
The good news is...
I can restore
the erased files.
And the bad news?
These files are all
password-protected and encrypted.
It could take some time.
Well, we don't have
much time.
It'll take as long
as it takes.
[Doorbell Rings]
[Woman]
Joanne?
Is that you?
Who is it?
[Virgil]
Ellen, it’s me.
- It's late.
- I know.
And I'd like not
to wake your neighbors.
Can we talk about
what happened tonight?
There's nothing to talk about. You made
it pretty clear what you wanted.
- No, you don't understand.
- I think I do.
Look, Ellen.
I gave you a second chance...
after you kept me waiting
in that restaurant for two hours.
Give me the same courtesy,
please.
And then if you want me
to go, I'll go.
Only, let's not
do it out here.
Thank you.
You want some coffee?
I can make some.
Yeah. I'd like that.
[Door Lock Clicks]
You're right, Mulder.
They're coming up empty at the airport.
So I'm releasing the sketch
to the media.
We still have time to make
the morning papers.
That may not be necessary.
- "Friend"?
- That was Mackalvey's on-line name.
These are all his victims.
It's a regular grocery list.
We need this scanned
and sent to everyone on that list.
Done.
I'm gonna call the on-line service
and have them fax us...
the telephone numbers
of all those women.
[Phone Ringing]
The machine
will pick up.
Milk?
- I only have nonfat.
- No, no, no, this is fine.
-[Ring]
- Give me a minute, will you?
I'd like to put on
some clothes.
Ellen, you don't
have to do that.
I want to.
I'll be right back.
[Scully]Just lock your doors
until we contact you again.
You'll be fine, Ms. Innes.
He doesn't tend toward forcible entry.
Okay, thanks.
That was Cleveland P.D. They've reported
three women on the list as missing.
Well, we've already contacted everyone
on this list, except for these two.
- I left messages
on their answering machines.
- We'd better check on them.
-[Beeps]
- You have mail.
[Virgil]
Ellen?
I hope you're not on-line
with some other guy.
I was just E-mailing
my girlfriend.
- Your girlfriend?
- Yes.
What about?
Us.
What were you
telling her?
just how happy I am...
that you’re still
interested in me...
and that you hadn't rejected me
like I thought you had.
I'm glad you feel
that way, Ellen.
I know I do.
Look. I still haven't
changed my clothes.
Why don’t you go wait outside,
and I'll be right out?
You look beautiful, Ellen.
You don't need to change for me.
Please leave me alone.
Please.
What do you want?
No !
Could I help you?
We're with the F.B.I.
We're looking for Ellen Kaminsky.
She's in her condo.
She just E-mailed me a few minutes ago.
- Why? What's wrong?
Is something the matter?
- Get back in.
Ellen?
[ Sobbing ]
Mulder.
[Gasping]
You go ahead.
I'll stay here. Go.
[ Gasping ]
This is Federal Agent
Dana Scully.
I need an ambulance right away
to 658 South Hudson Avenue,
apartment number 23.
Request special chemical
burn unit.
[Cans Clanking]
Freeze! Federal Agent!
Now put your hands up
and step out where I can see you.
just--Just
don't shoot me, man.
[ Groans, Gasping ]
[ Grunts ]
[Gunshot]
[Mulder]Jennifer Flasket,
Kathy Miller, Hillary Turk.
Forty-seven women reported missing
in five states.
At least give their families
some peace of mind...
and tell us how many
are on that list because of you.
They're all mine.
Come on, Scully.
Open the door.
[Door Buzzes]
Why?
When you look at me,
you see a monster.
But I was just feeding
a hunger.
You're more than
a monster.
You didn’t just feed on their bodies,
you fed on their minds.
My weakness was no greater
than theirs.
I gave them
what they wanted.
They gave me
what I needed.
Not anymore.
[ Speaking Italian ]
The dead
are no longer lonely.
Let me out.
[ Door Buzzes ]