- Mr. Simon ? Are you ready ?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Excuse me, Warden.
It's 5:00, sir.
- How's Neech ?
- He's still in with his wife.
No, I mean how is he ?
How's he doing ?
Well, he won't eat his meal,
and he won't see the chaplain.
- Told him to get the hell out.
- What about the hired man ?
He's traveling.
All right.
Let's get Neech prepped.
Yes, sir.
If God can't save his sorry ass,
neither can l.
[Door Buzzes]
Time's up, Neech !
2,000 volts, man.
You ain't never
coming back, freak!
[Laughing]
[Woman] It's just like
I’ve always told you.
- I swear on my life, Neech.
- Time to go.
[Tapping Bars]
I ain't ever gonna love
another man.
You hear me ? I won't.
I won't betray our love.
Ever.
It's time, Neech.
Time to go.
That phone call's gonna come,
and the governor
is gonna come through.
Gotta go now.
[Door Buzzes]
We've got a hood
if you want it.
- It’s your option.
- No.
Is there anything
you want to say, Neech ?
Last words ?
Yeah.
I've been here 11 years, 56 days,
and now you’re gonna murder me.
The Lord says thou shall be
merciful and just.
I know no mercy.
Allah says the spirit
shall rise again...
and be reborn
into this life.
- The soul shall be recast,
- You should begin, Father.
-born unto new flesh.
- "The Lord is my shepherd--"
I will return to avenge
all the petty tyranny...
and the cruelty I have suffered.
I will be recast, reincarnated,
reunion of spirit and flesh.
Mark my words.
Five men will die.
- Save it.
- Five men will go down !
This will be my justice !
This will be my law !
This will be
my capital punishment,
and no stay of execution
will be granted,
for there is no prejudice,
no evidence to be admitted,
-no lawyer who did not
perform his job.
- Fry him.
These men will die
righteous deaths !
-[Electricity Humming]
- [ Straining ]
Napoleon "Neech" Manley.
He was convicted in 1 984
for double murder...
in the holdup
of a Florida liquor store.
The actual gunman
was killed in the pursuit.
Manley was driving
the getaway car and
got sentenced to death.
He was put to death in
the electric chair three days ago.
He'd been to the chair twice before,
but the governor granted him
last-minute stays.
Third time's a charm.
What's your interest in this ?
Manley was interesting.
He was well-read, charismatic.
He became a writer,
a kind of prison philosopher.
A week before his execution,
word went through the prison...
that Neech said he was
gonna be reincarnated.
He was gonna come back
from the dead.
Well, reincarnation has always
been popular on death row
for obvious reasons.
Apparently, this was more than just
a dying man's hope against hope.
- What do you mean ?
- Manley didn’t just claim
that he was gonna come back,
but that he was gonna take vengeance
on five men who had mistreated him.
Yesterday a death row guard was
found dead inside the cell...
that Manley had occupied
those 11 years.
His death cannot be explained.
[Scully]
Has a cause of death been determined?
Suffocation,
near as we can tell.
Somebody must have
snuffed him with a pillow.
[Mulder] Any idea how one of
your guards could get murdered...
in an empty cell like this ?
No. It's not supposed to happen,
not with all the precautions
we're taking.
I see the guards here
all wear panic devices.
Was the victim's activated ?
No. Apparently,
he never touched it.
[Mulder] According to our reports,
there were threats this might happen.
There's always
threats of violence in here.
Prison's nothing but
a police state, basically.
Do you give any credence
to Neech Manley's claims...
that he was gonna come back
and take revenge ?
Neech Manley. Hmm.
A smart man.
Very smart man.
In fact, if he’d stayed outside,
I would have figured him
for a Nobel Prize.
But he made a mistake.
Paid for it with his life.
A man of that intelligence,
you put him inside for 10 or 11 years,
you're gonna have
to pay for it.
- What do you mean ?
- There's nothing but bitterness
and resentment in here...
7 days a week, 24 hours a day,
365 days a year.
It gets honed
to a real fine point.
So you’re saying that
Manley planned this...
and is carrying it out
with the help of someone else.
Elaborate as Shakespeare.
Now, if you want to see
the victim's body--
[Guard]
Visitors coming through !
Woman on the block !
We're holding the corpse
until the state pathologist...
comes down this afternoon
and conducts the official autopsy.
That information should
help us solve the murder.
[Mulder] Did Manley have
many friends among the prisoners ?
A man has to have friends in prison
to keep an eye on his enemies.
- Mostly, people were
just afraid of him.
- Warden ?
- What is it ?
- The body.
I think you should
take a look.
I suggest you get it
into refrigeration,
or you're not gonna have
anything left to autopsy.
Oh, God.
[Mulder] I’ve been told
you believe Neech Manley's claims.
It's not a matter of how
or if he’s coming back.
The question is, when...
- is he coming back again ?
- What are you saying,
Speranza ?
You believe Manley
killed that guard ?
- How would you explain it ?
- A prisoner waits for
an opportunity--
Hey, look around.
We ain't got but an opportunity...
to itchy-scratchy
outside our cells.
Yeah, but you’ve got prisoners
on work detail. Trustees.
A man slips away.
This is "Q" block, death row.
Don't nobody come in and out of here...
without a guard watching,
and lately, you got double that.
Why ?
'Cause everybody's afraid
of what they say can't be true.
- Neech is back.
- Reincarnated.
Well, he would have called it
"transmigration of the soul."
- Into what form ?
- You, me, this mattress--
I don't know.
He didn't specify,
but he's back.
I can feel it.
The man was electric,
you know what I'm saying ?
Pure energy.
Would it be possible
to see the cell where
the guard was murdered ?
I'll open it up for you.
-Any idea how he did it ?
- Like I said, the man--
-[Wolf Whistle]
-[Man]
Yeah, sweet roja !
Nothing's been touched.
It's pretty much the way Neech left it.
[Flies Buzzing]
- Did you know Neech Manley ?
- Oh, yeah. I knew him.
- What was he like ?
- Neech ?
- Neech was so full of B.S.,
he couldn't stand it.
- How is that ?
He actually started to believe that crap
he'd been preaching all those years,
as if knowing all them religions
made him some kind of god.
- Who do you think
killed the guard ?
- I don't know who killed him,
but I damn well know
who didn't kill him.
Are you afraid at all ?
Me ? I just keep my ass covered
and my eyes peeled.
-Same as always.
-[Man]
Fornier!
Hey, down here !
I'm gonna check back
on your partner.
- Everything okay in there ?
-[Mulder]
Yeah, we're fine.
Shh !
[ Whispering ]
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I only want to talk to you,
okay ?
I know who he's going to kill.
There's a list.
One of the cons has it.
A man named Roque.
Who are you ?
My name's Parmelly.
I want to help you.
[Fornier]
Agent Scully ?
I was just looking around.
Not a place for a woman
to be doing that alone.
Mulder.
- I'm ready to go now.
- Okay. I'll be right there.
- Guard !
- What's wrong, Scully ?
I'm just ready
to get out of here.
[Door Buzzes]
[Man Laughing]
[Guard] I want every paintbrush
and putty knife...
to be accounted for,
understand?
Come on, gentlemen,
move it.
It's the guard.
It's Fornier.
Come on, you guys.
Break it up.
Get back.
I said get back.
I guess they haven't
recovered the body yet,
so it's going to be difficult
to establish an exact cause of death.
What did your
preliminary exam turn up ?
Well, it looks like the head
was severed just below the jaw line...
with repeated stabbing blows
from a putty knife.
There were no other indications
of trauma to the head.
From the eyewitness reports,
there were already fly larvae
infesting the flesh.
That seems unusual,
considering the short
time-of-death window.
Not altogether.
Here, let me show you this.
Lucilia Cuprina, better known as
the green bottle fly.
They can lay their eggs
within a minute after death occurs,
and they breed more rapidly
in a hot, humid environment.
In the anaerobic environment
inside the paint can ?
On my autopsy
on the first victim,
the lungs were absolutely
alive with infestation.
Hmm. What was determined to be
the cause of that death ?
Best I can figure,
given the lack of indicators,
he was suffocated to death.
Either that...
or he drowned.
[Jail Door Unlocks]
[Guard]
You've got a visitor, Roque.
- I hear you have a list.
- I prefer not to talk about it here.
Not on the block.
Guard ?
You's a dead man, Roque!
You hear me ?
I'm gonna peel that head
like an onion!
I'm gonna break you off
a big chunk! You hear me ?
He ain't gonna tell you
nothing but a bunch of lies !
You talk, punk,
I gonna make you my Maytag !
He's a liar !
How did you come by
this list you claim to have ?
I heard Neech on the bars one night
telling Speranza.
- How many names are on the list ?
- Five.
just like Neech said.
So you knew those two guards
were gonna be murdered.
I knew they were
on the list, yeah.
Who do you think killed them ?
I don't know.
I just know
who's on the list.
You want to make
some kind of deal, huh ?
That's right.
I want a transfer out of this hole.
Why ? Are you on the list ?
I ain't saying nothing.
Not until I get my deal.
Well, what if they don't
give you what you want ?
Then they're gonna see
the other three die.
- Can't do it.
I can't make that deal.
- You don't have the authority ?
No. If I make that deal,
I might as well go into
the deal-making business.
Every con with half a brain
would come up with a scheme like that.
What if it saves three lives ?
Isn't that a deal worth making ?
Look, my job is about
controlling anarchy.
I don't run this prison.
I just patrol it.
Basically,
it's war in here.
We have freedom.
They don't.
Anything these men want,
somehow it finds its way in here.
They want another prisoner dead,
somebody's gonna find a way
to put a shiv in.
These aren't prisoners.
These are guards
you've got being murdered.
Yes, and if I back down now,
all I'll be doing...
is sending a message about
the benefits of killing prison guards.
There’s a conspiracy
at work here.
I don't know
who's behind it.
But I am gonna crack it.
That's my job.
Ohh-- What the hell ?
Guard !
Guard ! Guard ! Get in here !
I guess he'll be able to finish up
that autopsy now, Scully.
[Scully]
He had quite a library.
[Mulder]
Yeah.
Looks like Neech Manley
knew his Bible.
Listen to this.
"I come in return
to the beginning of the end...
"to begin again
the journey of souls,
the godhead universal for whom
there is no death, only life eternal."
- What's that from ?
- Neech Manley, 1994.
This stuff goes on for pages.
There's references to the Hindu Atman,
Prarabdha, the Rosicrucians,
Zoroastrianism.
The man was obsessed
with reincarnation.
Being obsessed with it
doesn't mean you can do it.
Unless he knew
something we don't.
Like what ?
The secret password ?
Every major world religion encompasses
the idea of life after death.
That means millions of people believe
in some kind of transmigration...
or rebirth of the soul.
I'm sorry, Mulder.
That's not what I learned in catechism.
Well, even Christianity
teaches about the resurrection...
and ascendancy
of the heavenly body.
Do you honestly believe that
Neech Manley came back from
the dead to kill those two men ?
- Is there another theory ?
- A very good one,
and one much more believable.
That this is
a complex scheme,
that the headless man planted
behind the warden's desk...
is the work of
a conspiracy of inmates.
Or guards.
Okay, but imagine
if it were true, Scully.
Imagine if you could come back
and take out five people
who had caused you to suffer.
- Who would they be ?
- I only get five ?
I remembered your birthday
this year, didn't l, Scully ?
Well, here’s somebody
we haven’t talked to yet.
- She should know better
than anybody else.
-[Knocking On Door]
- Mrs. Manley ?
- Yes ?
We're from the F.B.I.
We’d like to ask you a few questions
about your husband.
I had this dream.
Had it many times.
They put Neech
in that chair,
then they
flipped the switch,
but that he wouldn't die.
They couldn't kill him.
He's a powerful man.
-A very powerful man.
- Did he share his thoughts
about dying with you ?
Neech wasn't afraid to die.
Because of his beliefs ?
Sometimes--
See, I only got to have
personal visiting days...
right before
the execution dates.
There was three
in the last 1 1years.
But sometimes...
I could feel
the power of his beliefs...
right through
that visiting glass.
You think he's come back,
don’t you ?
You know,
I think that
if anyone could,
it'd be Neech.
[Door Buzzes]
Getup, Roque.
Putting on the chains.
Hey, man, for what ?
The warden
wants to talk to you.
- Other way.
- Where we going ?
This way.
Let go of my arm !
I’m going !
What you want with me
anyway ?
Stop pushing !
Hey, Roque.
- I want to talk to you about this list.
- I ain't saying nothing.
Come on, Roque,
you got a big mouth.
What are you
shutting up now for, huh ?
Who's on the list ?
Am I on the list, Roque ?
Am I on that list ?
Is my name on that list ?
You're number five.
How's it feel to be
on death row, Warden ?
Did you catch
her body language ?
She was nervous...
or scared.
Of what ? That her husband's
gonna keep his word ?
A lot could have happened in her life
in those 11 years Neech was in prison.
- A lot probably did.
- You mean she thinks
she's on the list ?
I don't know, but I've been thinking
a lot about that list, Scully.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
Scully.
We're on our way.
That was the warden.
There's been another death.
- Who ?
- Roque.
They found him beaten to death
in the showers on death row.
[Man]
Gotta go now.
[ Gasps, Sighs ]
Oh, God.
You scare me
when you do that.
Why ?
You think it's him ?
- Wh-Where are you going ?
- I'm going to work.
Parm, I'm scared.
You feel me ?
I'm shaking like a little kitten.
Hey.
Now what are you
scared of?
What if somebody finds out ?
l-l mean, what if--
Will you stop
your worrying ?
Everything's gonna be
all right. Hmm ?
He ain't coming back,
Danielle.
He ain't.
Hey. Hey, you movin' in ?
Got room in my cell
for you, baby.
- Who found the body ?
- One of my guards.
- No one heard anything ?
- Nobody who should have.
I'm ordering a lockdown of this facility
until the situation is under control.
As far as I'm concerned, anyone
who had contact with Neech Manley...
is a suspect.
Warden ?
[Parmelly]
I warned you.
That's three.
Warden ?
Why Roque ?
Neech hated Roque.
They pretty near tried
to kill each other once.
- Then why the other victims ?
- Neech probably hated them too.
Did Neech have a history
with the guards who died ?
Neech had a small
behavioral problem...
about a year,
a year and a half ago.
Fornier and the other men
had to, uh, discipline him.
How badly was he beaten ?
- He took his licks.
- So there's a pattern here.
A logic. All these men had
a violent history with Neech.
They all caused him
to suffer physical pain.
- What are you getting at ?
- A lockdown may not
solve your problem, Warden.
- Sure as hell put a lid on it.
- If it’s a conspiracy
among the inmates.
But how many inmates could have
put that body in your office ?
How many
could have gotten access ?
You're saying
the guards are involved ?
I'm saying that Roque
may not be victim number three.
Now, I need a name from you.
I need the name
of Neech's executioner.
- It's confidential.
- How many men know it ?
Three men, including me.
We place an ad,
pay him in cash.
- There's no written record.
- His life may be in danger.
- There is no chance--
- Look at it this way, Warden.
If I'm right, it'll reduce
your list of suspects to four.
I said three men
knew that name.
I'm counting Neech Manley.
Mr. Simon ?
Perry Simon ?
Couple of days' worth
of mail.
Mulder.
What is it ?
Oh, God.
I told you, didn't I ?
You told me everything
but what I need to know.
Who else is
on that list, John ?
- I can't tell you that.
- How's he doing it, John ?
- I really can't tell you.
- And you’re just gonna
let those men die ?
- Ain't my call !
- They're gonna pin it on somebody !
- They're gonna pin it on you.
- They're gonna what ?
- What are they gonna do to me ?
- Put you in solitary.
One hour a week outside your cell,
no contact with anyone.
They say it can break a man.
I can't tell you, man.
You're afraid of Neech ?
- I saw him.
- You saw Neech.
Standing outside my cell,
big as life.
Tell me who else is on the list, John.
Who's next ?
I can't tell you
who's on the list.
But I can tell you Roque...
wasn't on it.
-[Door Opens]
- Roque's not on it ?
Mulder, can I have a minute ?
I’ve just been going over Neech's
phone calls over the last two months.
Over 30 of them were made
to a man named Danny Charez,
- twice as many as to his own wife.
- And ?
Charez has been here three times
to see Speranza since the first murder.
He could be working with him
on the outside.
Look, I've got nothing to hide.
Okay, then. What's your business
with John Speranza ?
I was trying
to get Speranza a deal.
- What kind of deal ?
- Retrial maybe.
Reopen the case.
I got some connections
with the government.
What kind of connections ?
I used to be an attorney.
Actually, I represented
Neech Manley.
You were Neech Manley's
defense lawyer?
I was 26.
I was court-appointed.
I had no business
on a death-penalty case.
Why help Speranza now ?
I heard about Neech's death list.
Word gets around.
And I know he blames me
for him getting fried,
so I figured
I got to try something.
You think Speranza's
got some sway with Neech ?
I'm just trying to save my ass.
I've been to the governor,
Speranza, Neech's wife--
Why Neech's wife ?
Maybe she's got some mojo with him too.
I don't know.
Anyway, I got run out of there
by her crazy boyfriend.
- She has a boyfriend ?
- Works at the prison.
Waving a freakin' gun
in my face.
- Hello, John.
- What do you want ?
Oh, no, sit down, sit.
I'm here to do you good.
- What you talking about ?
- I want to be your advocate.
I'm gonna get them
to look at your case again,
pull a few strings
up in Tallahassee.
- And what do you want from me ?
-Just call off the dogs.
That's all.
What do you say ?
Scratch my back, I'll scratch yours.
All right.
I'll have somebody
from the governor's office
down here to see you by this weekend.
[ Clanking ]
[ Gasps, Muffed Screaming ]
[Danielle]
Where have you been ?
- Out.
- Out. What do you mean, out ?
What's with you ?
You see who's sitting outside
watching this house ?
You see that car
out there ?
You know who that is ?
Huh ? It's the stupid F.B.I.
They came here tonight
asking about you.
- About me ?
- Said they saw you...
waving a gun in some lawyer's face
in my front yard.
- That's crazy !
- I thought you said nobody
knew about us. Now look it !
just look it.
A woman gets lonely.
Sometimes she can't wait around
for a man to be reincarnated.
I think we should
notify the warden.
[Engine Starts]
- Is that the man ?
- That's him.
Parmelly.
Yeah, give me Vincent Parmelly's
work sheet for the last week.
Thank you.
Now, you say you saw him
with Neech's wife ?
Yes. I hadn't reported it,
but that same guard also cornered me...
and made an overture
for prisoner Roque.
- He's tied in with Roque ?
- Well, does it make sense to you...
that Parmelly is
Neech's assassin ?
I don't know Parmelly that well.
He’s a transfer in from out of state.
He's only been here
six months.
According to an attorney,
he had brandished a gun
at the residence.
What attorney ?
A man named Charez.
- [ Scoffs ]
- You know him ?
Everybody knows Danny Charez.
- He was found dead earlier
this evening at his apartment.
- Murdered ?
Suffocated to death,
or so it seems.
Well, he could be
the fifth victim.
I think somebody ought to go out
and arrest Vincent Parmelly.
Oh, my God.
No.
Neech.
What the hell you doing ?
- He's here.
- What are you talking about ?
Neech. I saw him.
Somebody's here,
but it ain't Neech.
They're coming here.
- It's you, isn't it ?
- What ?
- You're him.
- You're crazy, baby.
[ Knocking ]
Put that gun away, Danielle.
That's the police out there.
- This is Agent Mulder.
Please open the door.
- I should've known.
I should've opened my eyes.
Mrs. Manley, we're federal agents.
Open the door.
- The way you touched me.
-[Mulder]
Danielle !
And the sound
of your voice.
Point that gun away, Danielle.
I'm telling you.
They're gonna put you away
just like your old man.
- Don’t you come near me.
- You're seeing ghosts.
Mrs. Manley, open the door.
[Knocking Continues]
She's got a gun
on Parmelly.
Center room, facing away.
- On a count.
-[Gunshot]
- Drop your weapon !
-[Scully]
Put it down !
- Put it down !
- Drop your weapon, Danielle.
Let's get a paramedic in here.
It was him.
He came back.
Forget it.
I swear it was him.
It was Neech.
- No, we're going this--
- What you talkin' about ?
- Somebody wants to talk to you.
- What kind of crap is this ?
Who wants to talk tome ?
Well, the warden's office
is that way.
- We’re going down here.
- Uh-uh. No.
Man, this is bull!
I ain't going for it!
What the hell is this, man ?
Why do you wanna talk tome
in the shower for anyway ?
What the--
john.
[ Laughing ] Hear about
your friend Parmelly tonight ?
- He's not my friend.
- Oh, he's not your friend ?
Well, it doesn't matter
anymore anyway, does it, huh ?
- You promised me a deal.
- Yeah, well, that was when
there was a deal to be made.
Who else was in on it, John ?