Name, please?
- Uh, Amy Jacobs.
- Okay, Amy. Fill out your address card.
And may I have
the next one in line?
Carl, I need a reload.
Hey, Carl. Hey!
I need more film.
I haven't loaded it yet.
Why do you even bother coming in
if you’re not gonna do your job?
Nobody's gonna spoil us.
Amy? Amy! Mom!
Hurry up with those drinks, Lucy.
We're backin' up!
What are you doing? These are regular.
They all ordered large.
What-- What happened?
Nobody's gonna-- gonna spoil us.
Nobody's gonna spoil us.
Nobody's gonna spoil... us.
Nobody's gonna--
Nobody's gonna spoil us.
Nobody's gonna spoil--
[Man]
Bushes, please. Flowers. Everything.
I'm looking for the agent in charge.
- And you are?
- Special Agent Mulder.
I'll let him know you’re here.
[Man]Can we get some shots
right here along these draperies?
Mrs. Jacobs?
I'm Fox Mulder.
I'm with the FBI.
I'm sorry about your daughter.
It's her birthday on Tuesday.
We're gonna do everything
we can to find her.
Who could do such a thing?
Who can take somebody
who wasn't theirs?
- I know you must be feeling--
- I'm sorry,
but how could you really
know how I feel?
It's blood.
Amy had a nosebleed.
Her little sister said
it happened when the kidnapper...
put his hand over her mouth.
We're running it anyway.
Walt Eubanks, special agent in charge.
Fox Mulder.
Any leads on a suspect?
A vague description
from the sister.
Hair and fiber pulled some promising
bits, but he didn't leave any prints.
Here or in the flower beds out front.
- What about the neighbors?
- Nobody saw anything.
Not a car. Nothing.
It was someone who knew her.
That much we can figure.
He knew right where he was going.
No, I'd bet that he didn't
know her so well, or else
he wouldn't have been so bold.
Either way, we're pretty much
chasing our tails...
until something or someone
turns on this.
What about this woman
at the fast-food restaurant?
- You heard about that?
- Yeah, that's why I came down here.
- Seems like a pretty thin lead.
- Mind if I talk to her?
[ Scoffs ]
Hey! Save me the time.
Great. Thanks.
Mulder.
Thought you missed your flight.
We were delayed in D.C.
I tried you on your cell phone--
Oh, I forgot it.
I left in kind of a hurry.
- Your message said something
about a kidnapping?
- Yeah. Fifteen-year-old girl...
named Amy Jacobs was taken
from her bedroom last night.
- 10:00.
- Is she here?
- No, they haven't found her.
- Well, what are we doing here?
A 30-year-old woman
named Lucy Householder...
was admitted here
shortly after 10:00.
She collapsed at work, suffering
from some kind of seizure...
and what her doctors
are calling "glossolalia."
- Incoherent speech.
- Technically, but whether
she knew it or not,
she was repeating the exact words
spoken by Amy’s abductor...
at the exact same time,
20 miles across town.
- That's spooky.
- That's my name, isn't it?
Turns out Lucy Householder
knows a little something
about kidnapping herself.
When she was eight years old,
she was taken from her bedroom
while her parents were asleep.
She was missing for five years
until she escaped and someone
found her by the side of a road.
Apparently, her abductor had
kept her locked in a basement
the entire time.
- They never caught him.
I'm Fox Mulder. This is Dana Scully.
We're with the FBI.
We'd like to ask you a few questions.
I'd like a cigarette.
They won’t let me smoke in here.
- Are you feeling any better?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I’d just like a cigarette.
A young girl was kidnapped last night.
Have you heard anything about that?
What are you asking me for?
Do you remember what
you were saying last night
when you collapsed at work?
- What?
- You were saying,
"Nobody’s going to spoil us. "
- Does that mean anything to you?
- No.
Can you think of any reason
why you might have said it?
- What'd I just say?
- Those were the exact words...
spoken by the kidnapper to
the little girl when he took her.
So you can see
that under the circumstances
it might seem strange--
So what's your point?
All of us kidnap victims
gotta stick together?
No. We just want to find
the little girl anyway we can,
and if you know anything--
Look, what I been through in my life
I wouldn't want to wish on anybody.
Doesn't mean I can make it
any better for me or anyone else.
All right. Well, thanks
for talking to us, Lucy.
Yeah.
Hey.
- When do I get out of here?
- As soon as your doctors feel
it's okay for you to go.
- No, they say it's up to you.
- No.
We can't hold you here.
You're free to go.
I guess she's not too big
on confined spaces.
Yeah.
- You're the one that called for a tow?
- No, not me.
- Gary Mosier?
- No, uh, wrong guy.
[ Sighs ] While I'm out here,
I might as well give you a hand.
It's okay.
We'll be fine.
Think it looks like
you're in a world of hurt.
Blown sidewall.
You're gonna need a new tire.
- Yeah, yeah. It looks that way.
- Got a spare in the trunk?
- Yeah.
- Twenty bucks cash.
My boss don't got to know about it.
- Have you on the road in five minutes.
- I can't pay you.
Make it ten. Pop your trunk.
Take me five minutes, max.
- Leave me alone!
- Hey, man.
What the hell's your problem?
Leave me alone!
Get out of here!
Lunatic!
Freak!
Agent Mulder.
Lucy Householder.
- You get anywhere on that?
- I'm workin' on it.
Got one of my guys on the line.
Says she's got a criminal record.
Prostitution, narcotics convictions--
- She's done some time.
- That doesn't surprise me,
given her history.
She's also got a boyfriend doing time
for assault and child endangerment.
Used to live with him up in the hills.
Pretty sketchy characters.
- I don't think she's involved.
- Closest thing I got to a lead.
I can tell him to shift some men--
No, let me follow up
on that, okay? Thanks.
- Mulder. Got something.
Something weird.
- What?
I was going over Lucy Householder's
medical workup, and something hit me.
- Her blood type is "O" positive.
- Yeah?
Forensics lifted two blood types
off of her work clothes:
"O" positive and "B" positive.
Two guesses as to what
Amy Jacobs' blood type is.
How could it be Amy Jacobs' blood?
Lucy was all the way across town.
I don't know, Mulder,
but it begs the question.
Because it matches the victim's
blood type? How many have
"B" positive blood, Scully?
One in five? That's hundreds
of thousands of people
in the local population alone.
We're not talking about
the local population.
We're talking about a woman
who's tied to this case, who had
somebody else's blood on her.
Lucy is a victim, Scully.
just like Amy Jacobs.
If she’s got any connection
to this case, that's the extent of it.
- Well, we'll know soon enough.
- What are you talking about?
I'm running a P.C.R. on her blood
to see if there’s a D.N.A. match.
- Will you keep that under your hat?
- Why?
Because I don't want Lucy Householder
treated like a suspect in this case...
until it's absolutely certain
that she is one, okay?
- Lucy?
- I'm cold.
- Brought you another blanket.
- We should call the doctor.
- No!
Let me see your face.
- What did you do to yourself?
- It's dark. Why is it dark?
- I can't see.
- You hold on now.
- I can't see!
Give your E.T.A., please.
Base, this is 17.
Our E. T.A. is five minutes.
- Over.
- How's she doin'?
- Fine. Blood pressure's back to normal.
- Temperature’s back up.
She must have gone down
the rabbit hole for a while.
You should get something to eat soon.
Get your blood sugar back up.
Well, what do you say, Lucy?
Can I take you to dinner?
- You feelin' better?
- Better than what?
Better than Amy Jacobs.
Wouldn't know.
If anybody knows, I say you do.
I got my own set
of problems now, thank you.
- How'd you scratch your face?
- Must have done it in my sleep.
- Are you using again, Lucy?
- I'm clean.
Passed my test last week.
Ask Henry.
With flying colors.
Have you ever experienced
temporary blindness before?
I've probably experienced just about
everything once or twice.
It's all been pretty temporary.
That girl's in trouble, Lucy.
And there's not a damn thing
I can do about it.
You understand?
I can't help you.
I think you can, Lucy.
- How?
- Well, that's something
you have to tell me.
- What can I possibly do?
- Lead us to her.
I don't know where she is.
I don't care.
I'm not interested.
That's too bad, Lucy, because right now
I think you’re her best hope.
If I'm her "best hope,"
then that little girl...
is in a hell of a lot more trouble
than you think.
What do you want?
Why are you doing this?
I want to go home!
- Mulder, I've got--
- Scully, take a look at this.
Is that Lucy?
Yeah. It was taken in 1 978,
the week she was found.
She'd been held in the dark
for so long, her eyes were
hypersensitive to the light.
Whoever held her captive
wasn't very big on conversation either.
She's 13 years old here and can
barely string two words together.
It's amazing she's gotten
anywhere in life.
Well, by most yardsticks,
she hasn't, Mulder.
I think we’ve got a break in the case.
- A big one.
- What is it?
School pictures were
mailed out this week to everyone
in Amy's class except Amy.
- One of Eubanks' men discovered it.
- Who's the photographer?
It's an outfit called
Larkin Scholastic.
The photographer checked out,
but his assistant was fired
the day after the shoot.
- A man named Carl Wade.
- Well, what have you got on him?
DMV's an old address, but he spent
a good part of the past 15 years...
institutionalized
for a bipolar condition.
The only thing current
we have on him is this photo.
It was taken by his employer
trying out a new camera.
- Have you shown this picture
to Amy's little sister?
- They're doing it right now.
I'm gonna take it
and show it to Lucy.
Lucy?
- Lucy, wait.
- No, I'm done with you.
I just want to ask you a question.
Lucy, wait a second.
Don't... touch me.
I don't like to be touched.
I'm sorry.
I was doin' okay until this, you know?
Figures.
I just want to show you
a photograph, okay?
You recognize him, don’t you?
Lucy!
Hey! Stop!
Lucy?
- Lucy?
What's happening to me?
He's probably changed a lot
over the last 17 years.
Did you even know his name?
Carl Wade.
He worked as a photographer's assistant.
School pictures, mostly.
That's where he saw Amy Jacobs.
So what do you want from me?
I want you to tell me
what you’re going through.
It might feel good to tell somebody.
I feel like it's happening
all over again.
You can actually feel what
she's going through, can’t you?
I don't want to go
through this again.
- Lucy, she needs your help.
- There's nothing I can do.
- Lucy--
Wait here a second, okay?
- What's goin' on?
- We're here to arrest Lucy Householder.
- Why?
- I think you know why, Agent Mulder.
What the hell is happening?
Mulder, the blood on Lucy's uniform
was an exact D.N.A. match.
- Lucy was covered in Amy Jacobs' blood.
- She didn't do it, Scully.
Mulder, it's incontrovertible evidence.
Agent Mulder!
- Where is she?
- She was just here.
Well, she's gone now.
Please!
I-I'm thirsty.
You shouldn't have run.
I was taking care of you.
I thought you understood that.
- Why did you run away?
- Please, mister.
I need some water!
You shouldn't have run!
Please.
I-I’m so thirsty.
I want my mom!
I don't want to die here.
Please? Please, mister.
- Don't let me die!
- You're gonna drive her away with this.
- She's been driven away, Mulder.
A half-dozen witnesses
placed her across town
at the time of the kidnapping.
- I'm well aware of the facts.
- Then trust me on this.
She's not working with Wade.
How'd she get the blood on her?
She may have bled it.
She bled Amy Jacobs' blood?
Yes, it may explain why
there was so little of it...
- on the carpet in Amy's bedroom.
- Agent Eubanks?
- Line three.
- I don't have time for
this nonsense, Agent Mulder.
We've got a young girl's life at stake.
I hate to say this, Mulder, but I think
you just ran out of credibility.
He's wrong, Scully.
You're protecting her
beyond the point of reason.
I'm protecting her because I think
she's connected to Amy Jacobs.
just not the way everybody else
thinks she is.
Did you consider for one minute
that the person she's connected to
is Carl Wade?
Carl Wade. Why would she be
connected with Carl Wade?
For the same twisted reason that abused
children crave their parents' love...
or hostages develop
sympathy for their captors.
I mean, maybe Lucy developed
some kind of emotional dependency.
After five years in a dark pit,
I'm sure she developed some kind
of connection with Wade.
just not the kind
that you’re suggesting.
It makes more sense than the notion
that she's bleeding Amy Jacobs' blood.
I don't how to explain it, but I think
that Wade's abduction of Amy...
triggered some kind of
physical response in Lucy.
- Some kind of empathic transference.
- Mulder, you can't--
That's how I account for
what Lucy's going through.
That's how I account for the identical
words that corresponded to Amy...
and the spontaneous wounds
and blood as well.
Then why did she run? If she's innocent,
what was she running from?
- Because she's afraid.
- You don't see what you’re doing,
do you, Mulder?
- You are so close to this
that you just don't see it.
- What don't I see?
The extreme rationalization.
Your personal identification
with the victim--
or, in this case, the suspect.
You're becoming some kind of
an empath yourself, Mulder.
You are so sympathetic to Lucy
as a victim--like your sister--
that you can't see her as a person
who's capable of committing this crime.
You don't think
I've thought of that? I have.
Not everything I do and say and think
or feel goes back to my sister.
You, of all people, should realize
that sometimes...
motivations for behavior can be
more complex and mysterious...
than tracing them back
to one single childhood experience.
Agent Mulder!
We've got a man on the way in
who spotted Wade.
Yeah, that's the guy.
I offered to fix his flat.
Tried to do the guy a favor.
He went wacko on me.
Started freakin' the minute
I got out of my truck.
What about the girl?
Was she with him?
I didn't see anyone else.
- She could have been in the trunk.
- Can you give us an exact spot?
Yeah.
Right in the middle of nowhere.
- Which way was the car headed?
- West.
Interstate 12, County 15, north.
903. Look at this. Right off the 903.
- Easton?
- That's where Lucy was found
17 years ago.
It's a small town, Scully.
Somebody's bound to know
Wade's face, where he lives.
But we already stick out
like a sore thumb, Mulder.
If we start canvassing Main Street,
somebody's gonna pick up the phone.
But he's a photographer, right?
- Yeah.
- He should have an account here.
Go.
Amy?
- Mulder?
- Yeah?
What's happening?
Did you find her?
Where are they, Lucy?
Tell us where Wade took Amy.
I don't know.
Anything happens to that girl, Lucy,
and you'll be tried as an accomplice.
- Were they here when you arrived?
- No.
- You haven't seen him?
Spoken with him?
- I said no!
- Then why are you here?
- I don't know.
just showed up for no reason
in particular? That's what
you ask us to believe?
I've been here before.
A long time ago.
It was where he kept me.
So, why are you here now?
Take her outside
and place her in custody.
No. I'll take her.
Come on, Lucy.
- Agent Mulder--
- It's all right.
He hasn't touched her. Not yet.
He wants to, but he can't.
That's why he takes the pictures.
What else, Lucy?
Tell me what else.
If he can't have her all to himself,
that's when he's dangerous.
That's when he'll start hurting her.
- Lucy, you came here to help her.
- No!
Why else would you come back here,
if not for Amy?
- You're sharing her pain.
- I can't.
You're the survivor.
You're the strong one.
Now Amy needs some of your strength.
- She's not gonna make it.
- She has to make it.
And you have to help her.
She's cold.
She's cold and wet.
Lucy, Lucy, sit down. Sit down.
Mulder, they found Wade's car
north of here.
- They're in the water.
- What?
There's a river near here.
I think that's where they are.
But the river's east, and they found
Wade's car a mile north.
Well, Wade lives here.
He knows these woods.
He could be doubling back.
Did she tell you that?
No, but I think that's what
she's trying to do.
Mulder, wait!
Stay with her, and get word
to Eubanks that Wade may be
heading towards the river.
Please. Stop.
I can't.
Come on! They're comin'!
- I can't! Please.
Nobody--
Nobody's gonna spoil us.
No! No, no!
Can you sit up? Can you breathe?
Are you able to breathe?
This is Agent Kreski.
I've got what looks like an
emergency medical situation.
Requesting E.M.S. Over.
Wade!
Federal officer!
Hold it right there!
She's not breathing.
No pulse either.
One, two, three, four--
- Come on, Amy, breathe!
...two, three, four, five--
There's nothing.
Mulder, it's no good.
- I'm sorry.
- Damn it, Amy! Come on!
Now stop. You can't help her.
Mulder, it's no use.
Mulder, stop it.
Stop it!
Mulder, stop!
Mulder!
She's breathing.
- Have you got her?
- Yeah, we've got her.
You have to get an E.M.S. unit here
right away with some heat and oxygen.
They're close. We've got them
up at Wade's place right now.
They're working on Lucy Householder.
I'm cold. I want to go home.
It's getting dark.
We have to get her off the river.
[Woman On Police Radio]
Rescue22, clear frequencies.
I don't know what happened.
She started coughing,
then she couldn't breathe.
By the time the E.M.S. guys
got here, she was already gone.
- How's Amy?
- She's exhausted,
but it looks like she's gonna be fine.
The doctors want to keep her
for a day or two, just to be sure.
How serious were her injuries?
Wade must have left her alone.
There were no injuries.
He must have dragged her
through the woods for at least a mile.
I know, Mulder.
I can't explain it.
She didn't have a cut on her.
And nobody wants to talk about that
right now. Everyone’s just relieved...
to have her back again,
to have her safe.
They finish up on Lucy?
Yes, they, uh-- They brought in
the state pathologist last night.
So I stopped by to get
the autopsy reports on my way.
She drowned, didn't she?
They found five liters
of water in her lungs.
She saved Amy's life.
Mulder,
whatever there was between them,
you were part of that connection--
did you think about that?
Lucy may have died for Amy,
but without you, they never
would have found her.
I think she died
for more than Amy.
What do you mean?
I think, finally, it was...
the only way she could escape.
The only way she could forget
what happened 17 years ago.
It was finally the only way
she could outrun Carl Wade.