Behold the mighty cockroach.
Believed to have originated
in the Silurian period...
over 350 million years ago.
They can be found in
every part of the world,
from the tropics
to the arctic.
There exists
4,000 known species,
and in a year,
a single female can produce
over half a million descendants.
Radiation doesn't kill them.
By evolutionary standards,
they are nearly
flawless creatures,
but creatures nevertheless.
Possessing only
a simple nervous system,
their behavior is dictated solely
by responses to environmental stimuli.
Unlike us, they are
incapable of thought,
of... self-illumination.
Compared to the roach,
we are gods...
and must therefore
act accordingly.
Is it true if you decapitate them,
they continue to live,
eventually dying
of starvation ?
Look, buddy,
I just kill 'em.
Well, that's why
I called you.
I thought that nowadays
you froze the insects to death.
Freeze them ?
Where's the fun in that ?
No, we got a new pesticide
that works like a fungus.
It not only kills
the infected roach,
but that roach then
spreads the disease...
to every other roach
it comes into contact with.
Well, just as long as you,
uh, get rid of them.
Bugs-- I don't know.
They drive me crazy.
[ Spritzing ]
Why, you arrogant little--
[ Chirps ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Panting ]
[ Screams ]
I forgot to tell you
I also found a roach on--
[ Groaning ]
[Cell Phone Ringing]
[Ringing Continues]
- Mulder.
- [ Scully] Where have you been ?
I've been trying to reach you.
My apartment complex was
being fumigated, so I thought
I'd get away for the weekend.
I came up to Massachusetts.
- Visiting your mother ?
- No, just, uh, sitting and thinking.
Widespread accounts of unidentified
colored lights hovering in the skies...
were reported
in this area last night.
Look, Scully, I know it's
not your inclination, but...
did you ever look up
into the night sky...
and feel certain that not only
was something up there, but...
it was looking down on you
at that exact same moment...
and was just as curious about you
as you are about it ?
Mulder, I think the only thing
more fortuitous...
than the emergence of life
on this planet is that,
through purely random laws
of biological evolution,
an intelligence as complex
as ours ever emanated from it.
The very idea of
intelligent alien life...
is not only
astronomically improbable,
but, at it's most basic level,
downright anti-Darwinian.
Scully,
what are you wearing ?
I understand what you’re saying,
but l, I just need to keep looking.
Yeah, well, don't look too hard.
You might not like what you find.
Isn't that what Dr. Zaius said
to Charlton Heston...
at the end of
Planet of the Apes ?
And look what happened.
- Scully, I got to go.
- What ? Mulder, what's going on ?
- [ Dial Tone ]
- Mulder.
How you doing ?
What are you doing ?
-Just sitting, thinking.
- Sitting and thinking ?
And talking on the phone ?
Who with, your drug dealer ?
Let me see some I.D.
The Bureau ?
You on a case ?
I heard reports of several
U.F.O. sightings in this area
last night. You see anything ?
No, sir, not personally.
But we did receive
a lot of telephone calls.
- Any more calls tonight ?
- No, sir.
The F.B.I. keeps tabs
on these things ?
No.
Excuse me, sir,
I don't like to pry,
but why are you sitting here
with your wiper blades on ?
Oh, I was just knocking off
some bugs that landed on my--
- Landed on my windshield.
- Cockroaches ?
Maybe. Maybe beetles.
I don't know.
I'm not really good with bugs.
[Woman On Radio]
This is dispatch. Come in. Over.
- Sorry to disturb you, sir.
- What's the matter ?
Another roach attack.
[ Ringing ]
- Hello ?
- I think you better get up here.
- What is it ?
- It appears that cockroaches
are mortally attacking people.
I'm not gonna ask you if you just said
what I think you just said...
because I know
it's what you just said.
I'm crouching over a bug exterminator
whose recently deceased body...
was discovered with cockroaches
crawling all over him.
The local sheriff says
that two other bodies were found...
in the same condition
this afternoon.
- Where are you again ?
- Miller's Grove.
It has a large
science constituency.
The other incidents involved
a molecular biologist
and an astrophysicist,
and the witness to this case
is an alternative fuel researcher.
These reports are not coming
from yahoos out in the boondocks.
The image
of those cockroaches...
has been permanently
imprinted onto my brain.
I see them every time
I close my eyes.
Try not to close your eyes.
How am I gonna sleep ?
And where ?
I'm certainly not
spending the night here.
Maybe you could get
a motel room or something.
- Were there insect bites on the body ?
- Insect bites ?
- No.
'Cause you know, millions of people
are actually allergic to cockroaches.
There have been reported cases
of fatal reactions.
It's called, uh,
anaphylactic shock.
- Anaphylactic shock ?
- Mm-hmm. Many such reactions...
have occurred to entomologists
or exterminators.
- Okay, we'll check that out.
- You still want me to come up ?
No, no, no. I'm sure you’re right.
Thanks, Scully.
- Who was that ?
- My drug dealer.
[Inhaling, Water Bubbling]
[ Exhales ]
- Dude, that's some good crap.
-[Man Chuckling]
Come on, it's your hoot.
Um, I don't know about this,
you guys.
You really ought to,
you know.
Try it.
This stuff takes your mind
and just sort of, you know,
expands it.
Well, something tells me it's
more than my mind you guys
are interested in expanding.
Well, how about
another beer then ?
- Okay.
- I don't know.
I think you’re
making a mistake here.
Beer is just, you know,
-beer.
- [ Beeps ]
But this stuff, it, like,
swings the doors
of perception so wide open,
you can see whole
'nother world out there.
But it's still like
this world, you know.
It tweaks your mind...
and does this whole
altered state thing to it.
And suddenly, you see
reality as it, you know,
really exists.
- Oh, God.
- Dude, what's wrong, man ?
Oh, God ! Roaches !
- Dude, you're freaking, man !
- Roaches ! Cockroaches !
- What's the matter, man ?
- What ?
[ Screaming ]
[Phone Ringing]
- Stay.
- [ Whines ]
-[Ringing Continues]
- Hello.
- I take it back, Scully.
I think you better get up here.
- Another roach attack ?
Yeah, and this was
no allergic reaction.
Two witnesses claim they saw
the victim screaming about
cockroaches burrowing into him.
Are there still insects
in the body ?
We haven't located any yet,
but there are wounds all over the body.
From the cockroaches ?
Well, the victim did attempt to extract
the insects using a razor blade,
but we're not sure all of
the incisions are self-inflicted,
except for the severed artery.
Was there any evidence
of drug use at the crime scene ?
Uh, well, he did have
a homemade lab set up,
but I'm not sure
what he was producing.
Aw, man !
Smells like a septic tank !
Would you make sure
this gets analyzed here ?
You know, Mulder, there's
a psychotic disorder...
associated with
some forms of drug abuse...
where the abuser suffers from
delusions that insects are
infesting their epidermis.
- It's called Ekbom's Syndrome.
- Ekbom's Syndrome ?
The victim cuts himself in an attempt
to extract the imaginary insect.
You still want me
to come up ?
No. You're probably right.
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's no bother. Bye.
-[Dog Barking]
- Hey !
Kids are brain-dead.
I couldn't get anything out of them.
What about some urine ?
For a drug test.
- Did you get it ?
- Get me a container.
Oh, I think I killed it.
[Sheriff] You killed it ?
You annihilated it.
It must have molted.
It’s just empty exoskeleton.
Well, at least we have evidence
that cockroaches were actually here.
We've got more
than that, Sheriff.
I think that bug's exoskeleton
was made of metal.
Nothing more than
a skin abrasion.
An abrasion caused by
a metallic substance ?
Why don't we wait until the analysis
of the compound is finished...
before jumping
to any conclusions ?
Uh, Agent Mulder, as a doctor,
I always find it best to be...
completely honest and
open with my patients,
no matter how unpleasant
the information.
What do you need
to tell me ?
No. I need you
to tell me something.
What the hell
is going on here ?
Wha--
- Are we in any danger ?
- I don't know.
- Well, should I evacuate my family ?
- I wouldn't know.
Doc, they're waiting for you
to examine the boy's body.
Yeah, uh, as soon I
take a little break.
After talking with Agent Mulder here,
I suddenly feel slightly constipated.
- What's his problem ?
- He's upset that I don't know
what's going on here.
So what the hell
is going on here ?
[ Beeps ]
I see the correlation, but just because
I work for the federal government...
doesn't mean I'm an expert
on cockroaches.
So you don't know anything about
the government's experiments...
- being conducted here ?
- Experiments ?
A couple of months ago,
an agent claiming to be from
the Department of Agriculture...
sets up base on
a couple of acres across town.
Nobody knows exactly
what's going on out there.
- It's top secret, very hush-hush.
- What are you suggesting ?
Killer bees were
a genetic experiment gone awry,
let loose on
an unsuspecting populace.
Who's to say the government
hasn't created a new breed
of killer cockroaches ?
You might want to keep that theory
to yourself, Sheriff.
No need to create a panic.
[Man] Oh!Oh, my God!
Help! Somebody help! Hey!
What the hell happened ?
Cockroaches.
He was covered in cockroaches.
- I don't see any roaches.
- When I went out to look
for help and I came back,
they disappeared.
Gently. Gently.
Hmm. Doesn't appear odd
in any-- Ooh !
[ Beeps ]
Next time,
let me handle the roaches.
[ Ringing ]
- Who died now ?
- The medical examiner.
His body was found next to a toilet,
covered with roaches.
- I really think you should come--
- A toilet ? Check his eyes.
Is one of them bloodshot
with a dilated pupil ?
- Yeah.
- Well, it's probably
a brain aneurysm.
- Brain aneurysm ?
- Straining too forcefully...
is very common causation
for bursting a brain aneurysm.
Well, how do you
explain the roaches though ?
- Did you catch any ?
- Almost.
I don't know
what to tell you, Mulder.
I just hope you’re not implying
you've come across an infestation...
of killer cockroaches.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- Mulder.
- [ Scully] Mulder ?
I've been doing some research.
Back in the mid-'80s,
there was a cockroach species
previously only found in Asia,
and since then, it's made
an appearance in Florida.
They've now completely established
themselves in this country.
- Do they attack people ?
- No, but they exhibit behavior
different than domestic breeds.
They fly for long distances,
and they're attracted to light.
- But do they attack people ?
- I'm suggesting that what's
happening out there...
might be the introduction
to this country of a new
species of cockroach,
- one that is attracted to people.
- That all makes perfect sense, Scully.
I don't like it at all.
Did you know that
the federal government,
under the guise of
the Department of Agriculture,
has been conducting
secret experiments up here ?
You're not thinking about
trespassing onto government
property again, are you ?
I know that you’ve done it
in the past, but I don't think
that this case warrants--
It's too late.
I'm already inside.
[ Sighs ]
Well, what's going on ?
What do you see ?
I'm in a house.
It's apparently empty.
- What does the place look like ?
- It's a, uh...
typical two-story suburban house.
Nice big living room,
sparsely furnished.
Nice carpets, fireplace.
Nice kitchen.
Modern appliances.
- Moving walls.
- Moving walls ?
Yeah. They're rippling.
Oh ! Cockroaches !
- What ?
- Cockroaches. They're everywhere.
Ah ! I'm surrounded !
Mulder, you've got to
get out of there right now.
- Nooo !
- Are you all right ? What happened ?
Flashlight went out.
Mulder, what's going on ?
Gotta go.
Mulder ! Mulder !
[ Dial Tone ]
May I ask why you're trespassing
on government property ?
- I'm a federal agent.
- So am l.
Agent Mulder, F.B.I.
Doctor Berenbaum, U.S.D.A.
Agricultural Research Service.
Doctor Berenbaum, I'm going to
have to ask you a few questions.
For instance ?
What's a woman like you
doing in a place like this ?
By studying how insects
respond to changes in light,
temperature, air currents,
food availability,
we can determine the best ways
to eradicate them.
Why all the secrecy
about your research ?
You've got some of
the good townspeople suspicious.
You expect us to advertise
that we've intentionally...
infested a house in their neighborhood
with thousands of cockroaches ?
But those, those cockroaches,
are they a normal species ?
They're a common one.
Have you ever come across a type of
cockroach that is attracted to people ?
Most cockroaches have been known
to actually wash themselves...
- after being touched by humans.
- Really.
So you’ve never seen
an instance where a cockroach
actually attacks a human being ?
There have been cases where a cockroach
has crawled into a person's ear or nose.
Nose ?
What is that there ?
Oh, it’s just
a pet project of mine.
Since an insect's exoskeleton
is a dielectric...
surrounding the conductive
medium of its body fluid,
when introduced into
an electrical field,
the brushed discharge will
result in a colored fare.
What is that
supposed to prove ?
Well, it's my theory that U.F.O.'s
are actually insect swarms.
I don't know if you know
anything about U.F.O.'s,
but all the characteristics
of a typical sighting...
are shared with
nocturnal insects...
swarming through
an electrical air field.
The sudden appearance
of a colored, glowing light
hovering in the night sky,
moving in a nonmechanical
matter, possibly humming,
creating interference with
radio and television signals,
then suddenly disappearing.
As, uh,
nocturnal insect swarms,
that's, uh, that's fascinating.
Everything about insects
is fascinating.
They are truly
remarkable creatures.
- So beautiful and so honest.
- Honest ?
Eat, sleep,
defecate, procreate.
That's all they do.
That's all we do,
but at least insects
don't kid themselves that
it's anything more than that.
Does my scientific
detachment disturb you ?
No. No, actually, l,
I find it quite refreshing.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
Not now. You know, um--
I have always found insects
to be very interesting.
Really ?
This is the fifth report
of a deceased body...
being found amongst
a horde of cockroaches,
but police are not confirming,
at least not yet,
that the insects have anything
to do with the fatalities.
Police have also disaffirmed the rumor
that these deaths were the result...
of an outbreak
of the Ebola virus...
somehow being spread
by infected cockroaches.
As for now, these incidents remain
under local jurisdiction,
but a nurse here did confirm
that an F.B.I. agent is on the case.
Police are asking that if you see
any cockroaches, don't panic.
Simply notify the local authorities
and evacuate the area immediately.
Reporting live, this is Skye Leikin
for Channel Three, Night watch News.
Then suddenly,
there was this terrible crash.
You know,
you could've been killed.
[ Blowing Nose ]
- [ Ringing ]
- Mulder, are you okay ?
- I can't sleep.
- What happened at the U.S.D.A. site ?
They're conducting
legitimate experiments.
I met an entomologist,
Dr. Berenbaum,
who agrees with your theory
of an accidental importation
of a new cockroach species.
Did he give you any idea
of how to catch them ?
No. But she did tell me
everything else there is
to know about insects.
- She ?
- Yeah. Did you know
that the ancient Egyptians...
worshipped the scarab beetle
and possibly erected the pyramids...
to honor them, which may just be
giant symbolic dung heaps ?
Did you know the inventor
of the flush toilet
was named Thomas Crapper ?
- Bambi also has this theory
I've never come acro--
- Who ?
- Dr. Berenbaum.
Anyway, her theory is--
- Her name is Bambi ?
Yeah. Both her parents
were naturalists.
Her theory is that U.F.O.'s are
actually nocturnal insect swarms...
passing through
electrical air fields.
- Her name is Bambi ?
- Scully, can I confess
something to you ?
Yeah, sure, okay.
I hate insects.
You know, lots of people
are afraid of insects, Mulder.
It’s just a--
It's a natural, instinctive--
No, no, I'm not afraid of them.
I hate them.
One day back when
I was a kid, I was, uh,
I was climbing this tree when I noticed
this leaf walking towards me.
It took forever to realize
that it was no leaf.
- A praying mantis ?
- Yeah, I had
a praying mantis epiphany.
And as a result, I screamed.
No, not a girlie scream,
but the scream of someone
being confronted by some
before unknown monster...
that had no right existing
on the same planet I inhabited.
Did you ever notice
how a praying mantis' head
resembles an alien's head ?
The mysteries of the natural world
were revealed to me that day,
but instead of
being astounded, I was...
- repulsed.
- Mulder,
are you sure
it wasn't a girlie scream ?
- [Man Screaming]
- What was that ?
- Oh, I got to go.
- Mul-- No-- Ohh !
- Did you hear that too ?
- Came from over there.
What the hell's going on ?
Hello ?
Is everything
all right in there ?
[Screaming]
Don't go in there, man !
[Phone Ringing]
What happened this time ?
One of the motel guests died.
Mulder, I'm coming up there
right now.
Scully, I think this man died simply
from a reaction to the cockroaches.
Two cases
of anaphylactic shock...
in the same day in the same town
is highly improbable.
No. I'm saying that I think
this man simply had a heart attack.
Word about
the cockroach infestation...
and the deaths related to it
has gotten out,
and I think this man simply saw some
cockroaches and scared himself to death.
- Regardless, Mulder, something
strange is going on out there.
- Maybe not.
All your conjectures
have proved correct.
The exterminator did die
from anaphylactic shock.
The teenage boy did die
from self-inflicted wounds...
and was getting high off methane fumes
derived from burning manure.
The medical examiner did die
from a brain aneurysm.
I still haven't been able to explain
the cockroaches at all these sites.
Or the fact that their exoskeletons
are made of metal.
Metal ? What are you
talking about ?
Mulder ? Mulder,
I'm coming up there.
Whatever.
- Can you tell
what kind of cockroach it is ?
- I should be able to.
The abdomen's still attached,
and we differentiate species
by their genitalia.
- Oh, my God.
- Is it abnormal ?
I'll say. He's hung like
a club-tailed dragonfly.
Excuse me.
Does it still look unusual ?
Well, yes,
for an insect genitalia,
but maybe not
for a microprocessor.
You're implying that
this insect is mechanical ?
What am I supposed
to be looking at here ?
Have you ever seen
anything like this before ?
Only in science journals.
I've read about
an artificial intelligence researcher...
who designs robots that resemble
and behave like insects.
I've never seen them myself, but I've
often thought of visiting his lab.
He works out of this town ?
[ Whirring ]
[Whirring]
- Doctor Ivanov ?
- Why are you scaring my robots ?
For decades, my colleagues
in artificial intelligence...
have attempted to create
an autonomous robot.
By struggling
to give their machines...
a human-like brain,
they have failed.
A human brain is too complex,
too computational.
It thinks too much.
But insects merely react.
I use insects as my model,
not just in design but by giving them
the simplest of computer programs.
"Go to the object.
Go away from moving object. "
Governed only by sensors
and reflex responses,
they take on the behavior
of intelligent living beings.
So this one is just programmed
to head towards any object...
moving within the field
of its sensors ?
No.
Then why is it
following me ?
It likes you.
Your contract is with NASA ?
The goal is to transport
a fleet of robots...
to another planet and allow them
to navigate the terrain...
with more intricacy than
any space probe has done before.
It sounds slightly fantastic,
but the only obstacle
I can foresee...
is devising a renewable
energy source.
In any case, this is the future
of space exploration.
It does not include
living entities.
I'm just speculating here, but if
extraterrestrial life-forms do exist--
Oh, there's no need for speculation.
I believe they do.
And assuming that they're more
technologically advanced than we are,
and if your own ideas about the future
of space exploration are correct, then--
Then the interplanetary
explorers of alien civilizations...
will likely be
mechanical in nature.
Yes. Anyone who thinks
alien visitation...
will come
not in the form of robots,
but of living beings
with big eyes and gray skin...
has been brainwashed by
too much science fiction.
- Can you identify this ?
- I'm not really good with bugs.
- A cricket's leg ?
- Try it under the microscope.
Are you all right,
Dr. Ivanov ?
Can you identify that ?
[ No Audio Dialogue ]
Sir ?
It's... beyond my comprehension.
Hey, kid, move it !
Gimme that !
[ Yelling ]
[Man]
Back off, buddy!
Get it ! Hurry up !
- Get your own !
- I saw it first !
[Yelling Continues]
[ Tires Screeching ]
[Man Shouting]
Hey, what are you, crazy ?
Why are you stopping ?
[Woman]
Hey, you idiot, you hit me!
[Man]
We gotta get outta here !
Excuse me,
do you sell road maps ?
- Could you tell me where they are ?
- Come on, hurry up !
- What's going on here ?
- Haven’t you heard about the roaches ?
They're devouring people whole.
Everybody's getting
the hell out of here.
Have you seen any
cockroaches yourself?
- No, but they're everywhere.
- Roaches aren't attacking people, lady.
They're spreading the Ebola virus.
Look, keep the change.
- We're all gonna be
bleeding from our nipples !
- All right.
All right, listen up !
I'm Agent Dana Scully...
from the Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
I am assuring you that
you are not in any danger.
Everything is gonna be okay if you just
calm down and start acting rationally.
Now, where the hell
are those road maps ?
Hey ! This last can is mine !
- Roaches !
- [ Screaming ]
[Engines Starting, Tires Screeching,
Horns Honking]
Well, Doctor, l, uh,
I appreciate you taking the time
to answer my questions.
Yeah.
Greetings from planet Earth.
Well, it's a cockroach,
all right.
It's not like the leg segment
you had me examine earlier.
- It’s just a typical cockroach.
- Even the...
Yes, even the genitalia
is normal.
Cockroaches are common in this area
at this time of year.
It's one of the reasons
I set up my study here.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- Mulder.
- Mulder, this town is insane.
- Where are you ?
- I'm in a convenience store
on the outskirts of, uh...
civilization.
Look, I think
I may have a lead.
Remember that Dr. Eckerle who was
the alternative fuel researcher...
that witnessed
the exterminator's death ?
Well, the fuel that he's researching
is methane gas.
Methane derived from manure.
- Manure ?
- He has an import license...
to bring in animal dung samples
from outside the country.
Now, maybe you can
confirm this with your Dr. Bambi,
but I think that cockroaches
are dung-eaters.
And if so, some of them may
have been shipped accidentally
in some of the samples.
This fuel research facility could be
ground zero for the infestation.
Scully, if an alien civilization
were technologically advanced enough...
to build and send
artificially intelligent
robotic probes...
to the farthest reaches
of space,
might they not have also been
able to perfect the extraction
of methane fuel from manure,
an abundant and replenishing
energy source on a planet...
filled with
dung-producing creatures ?
Mulder, I think you’ve been
in this town too long.
Where's the research facility
located ?
Wait, Bambi. You better wait here
until I make sure it's safe.
Be careful. We still don't know
what these cockroaches are capable of,
if they’re even cockroaches.
I'm not so much worried about
the cockroaches as I am
about the human element.
[Cockroaches Chirping,
Beeping]
[Cockroach Beeps]
[ Beeping ]
[Beeping Continues]
-[Gunshot]
- [ Gasps ]
Dr. Eckerle ?
They're after me.
First at my house,
then at the motel,
and then I came here
to get away,
but... they're following me.
You're not in any danger.
These insects won't harm you.
- I've seen them kill two men.
- They weren’t responsible
for those deaths,
but they might be responsible for ours
if you continue firing your gun...
in a plant full of methane gas.
Don’t you understand ?
The bugs.
They drive me crazy.
Let me guess. Bambi.
Fox told me to wait out here while
he checked inside first.
Should I come along
with you ?
No.
This is no place
for an entomologist.
- [ Beeping Continues ]
- Why are these roaches
making those weird noises ?
In Madagascar,
they have roaches that hiss...
by blowing air through the holes
in their upper thorax.
Really ?
How do you know
so much about them ?
I don't. That's why
we shouldn't kill these,
but capture them for further study.
Now, please.
Put the gun down.
- Have I lost my mind ?
- No.
You’ve just had
a very stressful day...
that's affected your ability
to think clearly.
Your judgment is
a little clouded right now.
It is ?
Then how do I know
that you're not a cockroach ?
Mulder !
[ Cell Phone Beeping ]
I assure you, Dr. Eckerle,
I'm just as human as you are,
if not more so.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
-[Ringing Continues]
- You are one of them !
[Gunshot]
- Mulder !
- Get out, Scully !
This whole place could blow !
Get down !
Crap.
It's like a crematorium
in there.
I don't think we’re gonna locate
the doctor's remains.
- Or anything else.
-Still, it's not as bad
as some of the other fires...
- we had last night.
- There were others ?
Four, to be exact,
plus 1 8 automobile accidents,
1 3 assault and batteries.
Two stores were looted.
Thirty-six injuries all total,
half of them from
insecticide poisoning.
But we didn't receive reports
on cockroaches or otherwise
for the last couple of hours.
Maybe this town's
finally come to its senses.
You two ought to go home
and get some rest.
You look pooped.
[Dr. Ivanov]
Agent Mulder!
They told me
I could locate you here.
Those segments
you showed me earlier,
may I examine them again ?
Well, they're
completely desiccated,
just like
the molted exoskeleton.
You know, many insects
don't develop wings...
until their last molting stage.
Perhaps whatever
these things were,
they had their final molt
and have flown off back
to wherever they originated.
Yeah, that would
explain everything.
May I borrow this, Agent Mulder,
for further study ?
I've already had
a similar sample analyzed.
It's nothing but
common metals.
What do you hope
to find from it ?
His destiny.
Isn't that what
Dr. Zaius said to Zira...
at the end of
The Planet of the Apes ?
It's one of my favorite movies.
Mine too.
I love science fiction.
I'm also fascinated
by your research.
Have you ever considered
programming the robots...
to mimic the behavior of social insects
like ants or bees ?
As a matter of fact, I have.
You know, I read in November of'94
in Entomology Extreme--
- Oh, I remember that.
- Your article about colonization--
Yes, I really enjoyed
writing that.
Smart is sexy.
Well, think of it this way,
Mulder.
By the time there's another invasion
of artificially intelligent...
dung-eating robotic probes
from outer space,
maybe their uber-children will have
devised a way to save our planet.
You know, I never thought
I'd say this to you, Scully,
but you smell bad.
[Mulder] "The development
of our cerebral cortex...
"has been the greatest achievement
of the evolutionary processes.
" Big deal. While allowing us
the thrills of intellect...
"and the pangs
of self-consciousness,
"it is all too often overruled
by our inner instinctive brain,
"the one that tells us
to react, not reflect,
"to run rather than ruminate.
" Maybe we have gone
as far as we can go,
"and the next advance,
whatever that may be,
"will be made by beings we create
ourselves, using our own tech--
[ Beeps ]
- "tech--
- [ Beeps ]
[ Beeps ]
"technology.
"Life-forms we can design
and program...
"not to be ultimately governed and
constricted by the rules of survival.
"Or perhaps that step forward
has already been achieved
on another planet...
"by organisms that had
a billion years head start on us.
"If these beings
ever visited us,
"would we recognize
what we were seeing ?
"And upon catching sight of us,
would they react
in anything but horror...
at seeing such mindless,
primitive, hideous creatures ?"