So I've got her spread-eagled
on top of a table in the law
school library after hours
and I am terrified
because,
Because you're afraid that...
I swear to god, I'm reciting tort
reform in my head so I won't come.
So finally I get her panties off
and she's sitting there buck naked
on top of all these back
issues of "the law review."
And suddenly I just know that
it isn't going to happen.
- You couldn't have...
- Right,
And she turns to me and she says,
"it's okay, Eli, you know.
It happens to everybody sometimes."
And she is so fucking understanding
that it really
fucking pisses me off.
And then she starts to say
all of these really shitty things.
Like what?
"Don't get so upset, Eli.
"It isn't manly."
I mean, what the fuck does
that even mean? What the fuck is manly?
Can you just give me a second,
please?
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
You're about an hour
and a half early.
I can wait.
Is everything okay?
Shouldn't you be in school?
We got out early.
You came here by yourself?
Where's your mom and dad?
I ran away from school.
I can't go back to school.
You know what?
You can stay here.
But I'm going to have
to call your dad.
- Are you mad at me?
- Not at all.
But I am concerned about you.
Do you want to tell me
why you ran away from school?
Bad day.
What happened?
- Can't I just sit here?
- I just thought...
you came here so early, you must have
something that you want to talk about.
I told you...
my mom's still away
and my dad's at work.
But you've got keys
to both their apartments,
and you came here.
Do you have any more ham?
You want me to make
you another sandwich?
Is that okay?
Sure.
I can do that.
But I hope by now you understand
that if there's something bothering you,
you can talk to me about it.
Somebody put dog shit in my locker.
That's terrible.
When was this?
I came down from the roof at recess
to get my gloves out of my locker.
When I opened it there was dog
dog shit everywhere,
all over my backpack and all my stuff.
And all my stuff. I went back
to the roof to tell my teacher.
- What did she say?
- She got a janitor to clean it up.
But recess was over,
so everybody knew what happened.
Do you have any idea
who was responsible?
But nobody saw him,
so nothing's gonna happen to him.
I remember what he did to your shoes,
so I guess this would be
his next logical step.
All through math
everybody laughed about it.
The teacher got upset 'cause no one
was paying attention.
That was my fault too.
Listen,
somebody did something awful to you.
That is not your fault, okay?
I asked my teacher
if I could go to the bathroom.
But I went to the lobby instead.
While the guard was talking
to someone else, I snuck out.
You weren't kidding.
You had a hell of a day.
But I'm glad you came here so
that we can talk about it.
My dad's gonna be so mad.
And he's already really mad.
- What's he mad about?
- Everything.
I've been staying with him
for two weeks since mom went away.
And he yells at me all the time,
no matter what I do.
- What do you do when he yells at you?
- Let him yell.
Do you ever
discuss the things you fight about?
He doesn't talk to me
unless he's yelling.
I think he broke up with Nina.
Did he tell you that?
No, but she doesn't
come over anymore.
That's my fault too.
That can't be your fault.
Nina told my dad
to make better rules for me.
And then they had this big fight.
Now she doesn't come over.
And when I see her at school
she doesn't smile at me.
- Do you miss her?
- Not really.
But I think my dad does.
He did a really bad thing
the day after the fight.
What did he do?
I shouldn't tell you.
It's up to you.
He bought a six-pack of beer
and drank all of it
and he fell asleep on the couch.
- And what happened?
- He didn't get up in time for work.
He yelled at me for that too.
"Why didn't you wake me up?"
But I didn't know
I was supposed to do that.
There was no way you could've known
what you were supposed to do.
My mom was supposed
to be back by now.
But she had to stay
on her vacation an extra week.
Have you told her about the fights
you've been having with your dad?
No, she'll just get sad.
If I were in your shoes,
I'd be really upset about all that.
I keep thinking you've sunk
as low as you can go,
but it turns out there's no bottom.
Why don't we just sit down?
We can talk about
- what happened to oliver today.
- I get out of my meeting...
I have seven messages from your school.
What the hell were you thinking
to just disappear like that?
Eric dumped dog shit all in my locker.
He did what?
Apparently during recess today
some kid vandalized oliver's locker.
Oliver's locker.
Nobody saw who did it. But all
the kids knew that it had happened.
I hate that fucking place
and I'm not going back.
Nobody told me that.
Why didn't you ask me
before you started yelling?
Because you still shouldn't
run off from school.
It's dangerous and you know better.
I think that what your dad
is trying to say is
that he understands
that you've had a bad day.
And he's just concerned
that you left school and you didn't
tell anybody where you were going.
I don't want to talk
about this anymore.
I understand.
Why don't you just go outside
and I'll talk to your dad, okay?
Where were you last week?
I'm sorry I couldn't be here.
First bess vanishes on this apparently
permanent vacation,
and then you go awol.
It's like rats deserting
a sinking ship.
It was an emergency, luke.
It's an emergency over here too.
Every day he comes up with a new way
to drive me up the fucking wall.
So you've had
a tough couple of weeks?
Bess calls every day. And we lie
and tell her everything's fine.
And she sa
she needs a little more time.
That must be pretty stressful
on you and oliver.
First he suddenly decides
he won't do his homework.
He says he's taking
a stand on principle...
the principle that school is stupid.
Have you talked to him about it
or were you hoping
I would say something?
I took away his tv privileges
and his computer privileges,
but he still won't do his homework.
He just sits there
and stares at the wall.
He certainly knows how to push
your buttons, doesn't he?
Next he decides to stop bathing.
What the hell am I supposed to do?
Climb into the shower with him
and soap him down?
I think Oliver feels powerless,
so he's refusing to follow the rules
because that's the only way that...
he can get some control.
Yesterday,
after he left for school,
I went into his room
and looked under his bed.
Past the mountain of dirty clothes,
there was all this food hidden in there.
I mean, half-empty packages of oreos
and doritos and cheetos.
I mean, there was...
Did you tell Oliver
what you'd found?
Yeah, and he got furious,
ran into his room
and slammed the door.
I should've gone in and talked to him,
but I was so exhausted.
I understand that
you'd be alarmed by all this.
But you know what?
I've worked with a lot of kids
in situations
similar to Oliver's and...
overeating is a pretty
common response.
You know, this...
This thing that happened
at school today,
it isn't the first time.
Oliver gets bullied a lot.
Have you done anything about it?
Now that the school knows
there's a problem,
they're obligated to help you
find a solution.
Well, now...
How are they gonna stop kids
from picking on Oliver?
I mean, you see why
it happens, right?
I mean, he's fat,
he's shy, he doesn't have
any friends and he smells bad.
If I were his age,
I'd probably bully him too.
Well, the way he's been...
behaving lately, I can see how
that would make you angry.
Sometimes I just wanna shake him,
and say, "if you keep acting like this,
no one's ever gonna be your friend".
"Is that what you want?"
That's unforgiveable, isn't it?
I think you wanna try
and spare Oliver
from the pain that
he's going through right now.
But you love him so much
and that makes you
frustrated and angry.
Yeah, but what good is loving him
if I can't help him?
But isn't loving him helping him?
I don't know anything
about anything this week.
So what else
has been going on, Luke?
Looks like I'm single again.
Nina and I had a huge fight
about Oliver.
And the reason I asked her out
in the first place
is because she liked him.
I thought she'd be good with him.
But it turned out
she just isn't on my side.
And whose side
do you think she's on?
Last week Oliver dropped a carton
of ice cream on the carpet.
Of course I got pissed off.
Then Nina came over and...
for some stupid reason,
I expected her to back me.
So you wanted her to help you
discipline Oliver.
But instead, she started
screaming at me.
She said I wasn't spending
enough time with him,
I wasn't setting
clear boundaries for him.
And how did you respond to that?
I told her if I wanted somebody
yelling at me all the time,
I would've stayed married to Bess.
That went over real well.
You know, at first,
Nina was a lot of fun.
I could come home at the end of the day
and just relax with her.
Then, all of a sudden, she started
scrutinizing my every move,
marshalling evidence against me.
I don't know, Paul.
Why do I keep choosing
these crazy women?
I'm not so sure, Luke,
that it's the women who are crazy.
I think it's the position
that you're putting them in.
So you're saying it's all my fault?
From what I've seen,
you enjoy having fun with Oliver.
But when it comes to making the rules,
creating a structure for him,
for a long time,
you let Bess do that job.
And then you hoped that
Nina would take her place.
So when he misbehaves,
you blame them.
You refuse to take responsibility
for Oliver yourself.
So can you see how that might...
how that might upset everybody?
Boy, now I could really use a drink.
Have you been drinking lately?
What did Oliver tell you?
Why would you ask me that?
Because the night I broke up with Nina,
I went out and got a six-pack,
drank the whole thing
right in front of the kid.
I thought, "let him tell Nina",
"or Bess, or you".
Why not?
So you wanted Oliver to tell us?
I don't care.
I never really had a drinking problem.
That was Bess being paranoid.
But the other night,
I'd just broken up with my girlfriend,
my kid was acting up,
my ex-wife skipped town,
you'd skipped town.
Shit, who wouldn't need a drink
after all that, right?
Are you saying you needed a drink?
You know, the week before
Bess went on vacation,
Oliver was on his best behavior.
But the second she left town,
he's turned into this monster.
Is he trying to get
some kind of reaction out of me?
I think that's part of it.
But I also think that
he was behaving so well
because he was trying to get
some kind of reaction from you.
That doesn't make any sense.
Well, look at it
from Oliver's point of view.
His family is breaking apart,
so he puts a lot of pressure
on himself,
trying to behave perfectly,
hoping that that
would solve the problem.
- So you're saying he was faking it.
- In a way, yeah.
He even tried to stop eating so that you
wouldn't be concerned about his weight.
He told you that?
But it didn't work.
He did everything right,
but it didn't solve any of the problems.
So now, maybe he's behaving badly
to try and make you feel
as badly as he feels.
I tell you, I liked him a lot better
when he was pretending to be happy.
Well, Oliver couldn't keep up
that behavior forever.
He had me fooled.
We talked to him about the adoption,
and that seemed to make him feel better.
I honestly believed
he was doing well.
Which is what I think
he wanted you to believe.
I've talked to him
about the adoption too, and...
The way he sees it,
Bess and you were fighting...
too much, and you gave
his brother away.
And things are so difficult
for him right now that...
I think that sometimes he wishes
you'd give him away too.
Does he even love me?
Why would you say that?
I didn't love my dad.
Not even when you were Oliver's age?
Sure.
I did love him back then,
but it was unrequited love.
You'll have to explain that
to me, Luke.
My father was the dean of students and
basketball coach at my middle school.
He was in charge of every breath
my brother and I took.
When we did well,
that's just what he expected of us.
And when we screwed up,
well, let's just say
he was a man of limited sympathy.
That's quite a lot to live up to.
You'd think that.
The year I was in the seventh grade,
he started taking long drives
on the weekends by himself.
My brother and I got on our bikes
and we rode around the neighborhood,
looking for his car.
And we found it in the driveway
of this little house.
My brother made me ring the buzzer.
The door opened,
and there was my father's secretary,
this nice lady who'd give us candy.
Then my dad came out of her bathroom
and started screaming at us.
What did you guys do?
What could we do?
We got on our bikes and we rode home.
And then I was lying awake
that night in the bed
and I realized my father's
secretary's living room
looked exactly like our living room.
Every piece of furniture
was exactly the same as ours.
He must've bought it all for her.
My brother told my mother
and shit hit the fan.
She packed us up and we left town.
We only ever heard from him
when he sent his check every month.
He was good about the money,
I'll give him that.
But we didn't wanna see him.
I mean, he sure didn't wanna see us.
He never met Bess or Oliver.
And when he died,
it was like a formality.
But lately...
It's like he's laughing at me.
I did everything right.
I proposed to Bess
when I got her pregnant.
I worked like a dog
to make a good home.
I never raised a hand to Oliver.
And now I feel like I'm standing
right where my father stood.
You know, just because you're getting
a divorce, that doesn't...
that doesn't mean
you're turning into your father.
And it doesn't mean that
you're gonna lose your son.
But that's exactly
what it feels like I'm doing.
It's inevitable that sometimes
you'll remind yourself of your father.
You see how you wound
your own children so...
so badly without even trying.
Suddenly, you almost
understand how he...
he could hurt you the way he did.
But you don't have
to become like him.
You're not doomed
to live your father's life.
You have a choice.
I think our session is almost over.
Would you like to say anything
to Oliver before you go?
Yeah, if we still have time.
Oliver, do you want
to come in for a minute?
I'm sorry you had
a bad day at school.
It's okay.
What do you say
we go get some pizza?
Maybe check out a movie
if there's something good playing?
On a school night?
You've been through enough today.
You deserve a break.
See you both next week.