- So was that so hard?
- I think we're okay.
VO: michvanilly, salomon.
208 - Week two
Oliver - Wednesday 4:00 pm
- Are we gonna play another game?
- Would you like to?
I don't know.
Since we met the last time I've been
reading up on the rules of blackjack.
I don't want to play right now.
Okay. That's fine.
Why'd you learn about blackjack?
Because I want to understand
more about the things you like to do.
Why?
Because... I think you're
a very interesting person.
- I'm not interesting.
- Well, I think you are.
You're really observant,
you're perceptive,
you've got a great sense of humor
and you're obviously extremely smart.
- My teachers don't think I'm smart.
- Really?
They say things like that?
I don't want to talk about school.
So what would you
like to talk about?
You don't have to talk
to me if you don't want to.
- I know that.
- I won't tell my parents.
You'll still get paid.
I'm not gonna force you
to talk to me,
but if you're having...
if there's anything you do
want to talk about,
this would be a good place to do it.
You know
why I don't want to talk about school?
- 'cause all my teachers hate me.
- They hate you? That's terrible.
I can't see any reason
why they would.
They're all mad
because I fall asleep in class.
Does that happen a lot?
- Pretty much every day.
- Well, then you must be...
you must be very tired.
No, school is just boring.
You don't like any of your classes?
Not really.
They're not about real things.
What do you mean by that?
Like, math is algebra...
it's not even numbers, it's letters.
- It's all fake.
- And what about all the other classes?
History, for example.
Doesn't that have to be real?
We don't have history...
it's called humanities,
and right now we're reading this
lame book called "Lord of The Flies."
Have you ever read it?
A long time ago.
In what way do you find it lame?
These kids crash on a deserted island
and start doing mean things.
And you don't find that realistic?
You don't need to crash
on an island for kids to be mean.
That's true.
Have you ever seen kids
be mean like that?
- You wanna see something?
- Sure.
They just gave
one of these to everybody at school.
- What is this?
- It's a turtle.
It's a turtle. Okay.
He's beautiful.
Do you think he's okay in there?
Do you want to let him out for a bit?
- Is that okay?
- Sure, go ahead.
- Okay.
- On the floor.
Do you have a name for him?
I have to take him home
and take care of him.
If he dies, I fail.
So why...
do you think that would happen?
I'm gonna forget to feed him
or leave him behind
and he's gonna die.
He looks really healthy to me.
It seems like
you're doing a great job.
I'm glad you took him
out of that backpack, though.
It looks like
it's a bit crowded in there.
Yeah,
I have to take all my books home.
Really?
You've got a lot of homework?
No, it's just sometimes
I'm at my dad's
and I forget a book
that I left at my mom's,
so my dad gets angry
because we have to go back to Brooklyn.
So it's best that I keep
all my books with me.
So since we last met, you've been
staying at your dad's apartment?
So you still feel
the same way as you felt before,
that you're just not ready
to stay with your dad... Just yet.
Well, I'm a little bit...
I'm a little bit confused.
Last week you said that the reason that
you couldn't stay over
at your dad's was because
you couldn't fall asleep
because of the noise.
Now you're with your mom and
you're still so tired you're falling
asleep in class. What's with that?
School's boring.
I just told you that.
So...
So do you have any trouble...
is he okay there?
I guess.
So...
you never have any trouble
falling asleep at your mom's house?
It's just hard to fall asleep.
Maybe the problem isn't just the noise
at your dad's apartment.
Maybe it's that you're having trouble
sleeping for other reasons.
Like what?
A lot of people
can't get to sleep because
they're really stressed
out at nighttime.
They can't empty their minds.
Do you think that's true about you?
Maybe.
I'm sure that there's a lot going on
in your life that must be stressful.
You think?
Is there anybody
you feel comfortable
talking with about how you feel?
Like who?
My parents?
That's one possibility, yeah.
Well, if I tell my mom,
she calls my dad
and then they argue.
And what kind of things
do they argue about?
Everything.
Today they had a fight because
my mom says I'm not getting enough
sleep and my dad says I'm not healthy.
And what does he mean
by that, "not healthy"?
Fat.
Has your dad ever told you
that he thinks you're fat?
I know he thinks I'm fat.
Everybody thinks I'm fat,
because I'm fat.
So,
being fat seems to be something
that really bothers you.
Do you think I'm fat?
What I'm concerned
about is what you think,
and I think it makes you upset just
from the way you talk about it.
I don't talk about it.
It's all the kids at school that do.
And what do they say to you?
We're reading "Lord Of The Flies"
and we have to write this essay on
the character
that we think we're the most like.
So everybody
in the class starts laughing,
because they say I should write
about the character named piggy,
which is the fat character
in the book.
So that's what they call me now...
piggy.
That's a pretty cruel thing to do.
Whatever. And last saturday,
this girl Maya had a Bat Mitzvah
and her dad got
all this chocolate for the party.
This kid Eric texts
everybody and says,
"if you want chocolate, then you'd
better get there before Oliver does."
Sounds like a real prize, this Eric.
He's an asshole. I didn't even want
to go to the stupid party anyway.
Did you tell your mom that?
Why not?
Because she would've called my dad
and then they would've had a fight.
So you went to the party
even though you didn't want to?
Kind of.
My mom dropped me off
and when I got there
I knew everybody
was upstairs in Maya's room,
so I snuck out the back door
and hid behind a bush.
You hid behind a bush
for the whole party?
It was fine till everybody
came outside to play in the snow.
Did anybody see you out there?
Eric came behind
the bush to take a leak.
And?
He pulled out his dick
and pissed all over my shoes.
What happened then?
And then
he went back to hang out with the other
kids and they went back inside.
Sounds pretty awful.
Did you tell anybody about this?
I know if it happened
to me I'd find it
pretty hard if I didn't have anybody
to talk to about it.
If I tell my mom,
then she calls my dad,
then they fight
and I don't want it to be my fault
What don't you want
to be your fault?
If they get a divorce.
Have your mom and dad talked
to you at all about
the divorce since last week?
There was this couple that came out
of your office earlier.
Were they married?
Did they look married to you?
Do I have to guess?
Why can't you tell me?
I don't tell my other patients
about you
and...
that means I can't tell you
about other patients.
Why would happy people come here?
Sometimes people come to therapy,
they talk about how they feel
and they leave just feeling better.
Can you make my mom and dad happy?
What I can do is I can
make communication between
your mom, your dad and you
a little better...
But I can't make them happy.
Would it be okay if I invited your mom
and dad into the room?
Sure.
Sweetie, come over here.
So you solve all the problems?
Are we good now?
Well...
One of the things
that we discussed was the...
was the importance of
both of you working together
to make sure that Oliver understands
what's going on here.
You got a pretty clear sense of how well
we all work together, didn't you?
Is there anything
the two of you would...
like to discuss with Oliver about
what's happening?
Well...
First of all, you probably
know this already but...
just in case it isn't clear,
your mom and I have decided
that it's best for all of us
if we don't live together anymore.
For good or for just now?
For good.
Is there anything you want to say?
Your dad's right.
For good.
Do you have any questions about
what your mom and dad have just said?
Why can't you guys
just live together?
There are a lot of reasons for that.
For one thing,
I'm sure you notice
how much we fight.
Because of me.
No, sweetie, you can't ever think
this is about you.
But you guys do fight about me,
all the time.
It's not your fault.
Look, the truth is,
your mom and me, we just...
can't get along anymore.
That's why we have to get a divorce.
And we love you very much.
We don't want to have you see us
go at it all the time.
So you are getting a divorce
because of me.
That's not the way to do it.
You're only confusing him more.
Well, at least I'm trying over here.
Do you understand what
your dad is saying?
They're getting a divorce because...
I get too upset when they fight.
No, sweetie,
what we're trying to say is that...
your dad and I,
we can't stay together.
Okay? But we love you.
We love you so much and we're always
gonna love you no matter what...
This is what always happens.
I don't wanna talk
about this anymore.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Why don't you wait
in the other room,
and maybe do some homework,
and we'll call you
in a few minutes, okay?
And you wonder why the kid
can't fall asleep at night.
Would you stop it?
At least I'm letting myself
feel sad about this.
- You don't think I'm sad?
- You seem to be priding yourself
on how quickly you can just move on.
Pride?
Look, I hate that
all this is happening,
but I don't think it's fair to our son
when you start crying in front of him.
Don't you think
I'm right about that, Paul?
Well, what I can tell you is that
I think that your son's sleeplessness
and his overeating
is probably caused by the pressure
that you're all under.
That's what I've been trying
to explain to her for months now.
You know he believes
the divorce is all his fault,
and that's entirely natural.
He also believes that
if he behaves in a...
particular way, it'll bring you two
back together again.
That's also a natural fantasy.
But because things
are so tense between you,
at the moment, he feels that...
he can't talk to you
about his problems.
For instance, there's a...
There's a boy at school
who's been picking on him.
And...
Oliver feels that he can't
speak to you about this
because he doesn't want
to upset you.
But I can tell you that he feels...
completely helpless.
You're saying that maybe
we shouldn't get divorced.
No, that's...
I don't think that's what I...
what I meant.
That's what you're thinking, isn't it?
How selfish and how cowardly it is
for us to just throw in the towel
and wreck our son's life over...
over small stuff?
- Small stuff?
- We're both stubborn, that's all.
We fight about stupid things,
like how late you could stay at work,
how my mother drives you crazy.
How my friends are a bad influence,
how I curse too much,
how everything I do
is a bad influence on our kid.
And so what?
I mean, really, so what?
We're supposed to be just perfectly
in love for the rest of our lives?
I can't believe
we're having this talk.
Maybe we're just going
through a rough patch here.
You know, what if
we just stay the course?
Maybe we'll come out
the other side of this.
Wouldn't that be better for Oliver?
Isn't there a whole book about
how parents should stay together
no matter how unhappy they are
and ultimately it's better
for the children?
That's a question that I think
a lot of couples struggle with.
What I care about
is what's best for...
for the three of you.
As bad as it's been between us,
it hasn't been any better now
that we're broken up,
not for me anyway...
And not for Oliver.
We owe it to him
to stop and think about
what we're doing before we just...
we move past the point
of no return here.
I'm already past that point.
You like to say things like that,
but is that really true?
I mean, come on,
are you really happy
living all alone so far away
from your family?
I'm seeing someone else.
- Why don't you come back and sit down?
- Pack up your stuff. We have to go now.
Bess, can you please...
- No, there's anything to talk about.
- I thought this was my night with him.
- He's not gonna go with you.
- So you get to make that decision?
Please, if you'll both sit down,
we can make the decision together.
He's not gonna go stay with him if
you're having women at your apartment.
Does Oliver know about
your new little girlfriend?
I guess he does now.
I thought you were the one who wanted
to break things to him gently.
Would you tell him that it's too soon
to start seeing women,
that it would be bad?
I don't think we're ever gonna
figure out what's good or bad for Oliver
if whenever either of you get upset,
you end the session.
- So you're gonna skip your class again?
- No, I dropped my class.
And it's a good thing, because one of us
needs to be responsible right now.
Now see? She's just using Oliver
as an excuse.
She's never gonna get her degree,
she's never gonna move on,
and she's gonna keep saying
it's all because he needs her,
and that's complete bullshit.
The kid needs to be allowed to grow up.
So, honey...
Oliver, this bag, it's a mess.
How is he ever gonna grow up
if you keep treating him like a baby?
Isn't it my night to go with dad?
Not if you're not ready.
It's fine.
It's my night with dad
and I want to stay with him.
- Do you think that's a good idea?
- Hey, it's our night.
He wants to be with me.
What's the problem?
No, it's no problem.
That's why we're here.
You have a good time
with your dad, okay?
I'll pick you up on thursday
after school.
See you next week, Paul.
Bye, mom.
Why don't you walk us to the train?
You're gonna get a bad back
carrying all this.
I can never figure out what I need.
So long.
Next time we'll stay
for the whole session.
That would be nice.
Take care, Oliver.
See you next week.
Can you give me a minute? Thank you.