- Put down your weapons!
- US Forces!
Just one more!
- Stay where you are!
- Don't shoot! I'm American!
- I'm on your side.
- American?
I know what you're looking for.
How much?
Relax, dad.
It's a write-off.
It's a rip-off, more likely.
- It's gorgeous, Emily.
- It's for the Christmas party.
You know, the one you're throwing
for your fantastic staff?
Who you've always said
are like family to you.
You're in this together, aren't you?
This is a conspiracy, right?
Dad, I'd like you to meet
Rick Massey.
Oh, yeah?
I'm Gillian.
Right. You're with me.
You, too.
Not too much on the lights
and that, right?
Dad.
I'm sure he likes you.
I wouldn't worry about it.
So, deputy assistant
to the President
for National Security Affairs?
- What's that mean? CIA?
- I work for the President.
I'm going with NSA.
I need you to boot up
your satellite link system.
What I'm about to tell you
is classified,
top secret.
Nearly ten hours ago in Afghanistan,
30 miles from the Pakistan border,
two recon marines were separated
from their platoon
during a skirmish with the Taliban.
They haven't been seen since.
Lieutenant Williams from Wisconsin,
Sergeant Hart from Arizona.
This is Hart's third tour of duty.
Williams' wife just gave birth
to a baby girl.
Key in the code JHK...
... 34ZY.
Within an hour of their disappearance,
predators, drones
and special missions units were deployed
in the search for them.
46 minutes ago,
one team found something.
Franko James Vincent from Baltimore,
so he claims.
- 34 years old.
- Oh, my God.
Or is this...
It's another John Walker Lindh?
An American who went over
to the Taliban?
Don't know yet.
All we know for sure is
he's given up a Taliban compound
in the Gremen Valley, where he swears
they're holding the two marines.
Well, I get what you want from me.
Transmit.
Ready.
You say you know where the Taliban
are holding two US Marines?
How do we know
you're telling the truth?
I don't want to die.
All right.
The part about not wanting to die,
that's true enough.
When did you join the Taliban?
I was an aid worker,
and...
teaching school
when the war broke out.
And I got very sick in a village
and they saved my life.
Just...
That's enough. That's enough.
Stop there.
No denial about being Taliban.
Well, the delay's not helping.
But, I wouldn't trust him
as far as I could throw him.
He's lying, then.
You'd need to bring him here for me
to get a proper read. Sorry.
While we mount a mission
to rescue those marines,
we'll have to treat him
as an operational asset in country.
No, if you think you're going
to send me to Afghanistan...
You do think you're going to send me
to Afghanistan, don't you?
And there was I,
dreaming of a white Christmas.
When could I be there?
Have a helicopter on the roof
that'll get you to Andrews in 20,
wheels up in 30.
And, Gill?
Not a word of this
to Emily, all right?
- What's that?
- It's secret Santa.
You pick a name and you get
that person a gift. There's a $20 limit.
- It's for the Christmas party.
- All right.
I've got to go away for a few days.
- Where?
- Just out of town. I won't be long.
The Christmas party's in 3 days.
You'll be back in time?
I wouldn't miss that for the world.
- Liar.
- No, it's...
fairy lights and...
really...
crappy music, and...
and goodwill to all men.
Right up my alley.
- Where's your boyfriend? Dick?
- Rick. Funny, dad.
Did I scare him away, did I?
For your information,
he went home to study.
Really?
All right.
In that case...
Here.
Get the best
Christmas lights for your tree
- that money can buy, all right?
- All right.
Dad, where are you going?
They need me in Florida.
- What happens if I pick myself?
- Then you put it back and pick again.
And besides,
somebody already has you.
- Who?
- It's a secret.
Why are you...
Well, dear...
- I love you.
- Love you, too.
This is going to be the best
Christmas party ever.
What?
You can't go to that place again.
I have never been to Afghanistan
in my life.
You know what I'm talking about.
Two missing marines, love.
Fear's healthy.
Don't forget it.
Right you are.
Bye, darling.
Foxtrot 31 delta.
Tango one romeo
headed for your 20, over.
Zero alpha, copy, bring it on.
This way, doc.
"Doc" I like that.
I do, you know? I do.
Right this way.
Watch your head here.
- Festive.
- The more I make, the better they get.
Welcome to the North Pole, Dr. Lightman.
John Parks, team commander.
How do you do?
Look, I see you're wondering
what idiot came up with the plan
to send me over here.
So, we have something in common.
Charlie team at altitude,
waiting for your go-order, boss.
Now, all you and I care about
are my 12 soldiers in the air,
ready to halo into the Taliban compound
our new friend here says
are holding those two marines.
Wait. You already
sent the mission over
before I even had a chance
to talk to you?
I moved my team
within striking distance.
I do my job, you do yours.
Final decision's mine, period.
No disrespect, but we don't have
a lot of time to screw around
before they start cutting heads off.
Okay, do me a favor, will you?
Just hold on the go-order
till I've had a chance to talk
to your new friend here.
I'll do my best not to screw around.
We gave him a shave, cleaned him up.
- Looks like one of us now.
- Sat-link eyes to your people.
Do you believe in Santa Claus?
Up.
Cheers.
Say hello to the folks back home.
I'm serious.
Hello.
He felt that.
Deep sadness at the mention of home.
What are those?
Paper snowflakes?
When Lightman asked him if he believed
in Santa Claus, I saw a flash of hope.
Where's home for you?
What?
Where's home for you, Franko?
1276 Bayview, Baltimore, Maryland.
Blurts out an address,
like he memorized it by heart.
I lived with my aunt.
Aunt Wendy.
- I'm sorry?
- Wendy Perriman.
My aunt.
Is that supposed
to mean something...
My Aunt.
Bayview what?
Bayview...
Avenue? Bayview...
Terrace? Boulevard?
- Street? What is it?
- Avenue.
'Cause you seemed pretty sure
about every other detail,
except for that
one small thing so...
Bayview Road, Baltimore.
And the natives
pronounce it "ballmer."
You know, I'm not buying much,
if any, of the whole aid worker,
Aunt Wendy story.
I mean, why lie about your Aunt Wendy
unless she's part of some
cover-up, some...
What is it?
CIA?
That struck a nerve.
All right.
Moving on.
How do you know where the Taliban
are holding these two marines?
Why give up that information?
Because I'm an American,
not like you.
Ex-CIA,
rogue lunatic... I mean, whatever it is,
any idiot can see that you've...
You've grown some deep...
hatred of all things Uncle Sam.
You know what I think?
I think you're just...
a traitor...
trying to save his own skin.
What's your Taliban name, Franko?
This close to the border
with Pakistan,
the Taliban never moves
more than ten miles
with prisoners
in the first 48 hours,
and only at night.
The place I told these soldiers about
is the safest place to hide that close
to where the marines were captured.
He said the first half of that
with extreme confidence
because it's probably true.
But he used the word "safest,"
inferring that the Taliban have more
than one place they hide out.
Where else might the Taliban
be hiding?
Nowhere.
Your shoulder begs to differ.
All call signs, stand by for go.
He's lying.
He's sending you
to the wrong location.
Charlie one, over target area now.
- You're sure he's lying?
- Yeah.
Well, 70%.
At best, he's sending you
to an empty compound,
at worst, it's an ambush, right?
Sit down.
70%?
It's not an exact science. If it was,
you'd have Bin Laden by now, right?
Here Charlie One, do you copy, over?
Abort.
Do it, Mo. Now.
Say again, abort the mission.
- You better be right, Dr. Lightman.
- Abort mission, copy.
Forget it.
No way in hell.
I get that you're a scientist,
but this is no place for experiments.
He's definitely hiding something.
Whatever it is, it's buried it deep.
And there's a connection
to your government somewhere.
I'm telling you,
you gotta let me dig it out of him.
You mean to tell me this
maggot's some sort of spy for us?
Yeah. CIA,
or related.
And either he's protecting
some long-term deep cover operation,
or he's just been out here too long
and he's flipped to the other side.
Those are just theories, doc.
Look, you already proved smarter
than that when you axed plan A.
Don't give up on me now or I'm on
the first donkey out of here, all right?
Whatever he is, whoever he is,
I don't care.
I need accurate intel from him,
and I need it yesterday.
No, you're right. Sod the science.
Give me a weapon.
At least I'll get home in time
for my daughter's party. I'm serious.
Weapon please.
Please. Ed.
State department? Pentagon?
Defense.
Special deputy operations and plans.
I'll be observing Dr. Lightman's
progress with the prisoner.
Top secret news sure does spread fast
in this town.
- Welcome.
- Cute.
This way.
He's ready for battle,
and he's smart enough
to know when to live
to fight another day so...
He's a warrior.
He's not a martyr.
These are 3 of the boys you tried
to lead to the wrong Taliban compound.
What was it?
Was it an ambush?
Was it an empty compound?
Empty compound.
That's something, I suppose.
Eh, lads?
We keep hearing this story
about you being a CIA agent
who got boned.
That you got sent out here
years ago,
left for dead.
- Is that right?
- If I don't get home to Texas, boy,
my wife is gonna take my daughter
and move back to Michigan.
Look, this is my last tour.
After this, I'm done.
Is it true you got boned by the CIA?
Still don't understand what you did.
- What'd I do?
- You went over to the enemy, you punk.
Attempt at anger.
No, wait.
Now, I get it.
I see your shame.
I see it.
It was either join them or die.
I mean, these 3, they might not
do what you did, but I might.
I'm a natural born coward, me. My blood
runs as yellow as the next man's.
Lightman just called him a coward.
How is this helping get
our marines back exactly?
Lightman just called him a coward
because he's about to present him
with an opportunity for redemption.
Watch.
But what you've got in
common with these guys
is that it's all about
living to fight tomorrow,
right, in the hope that someday soon
you get to go home.
If that's not on the cards,
then all that remains is
the last fight... you fight.
And then the question becomes...
which side of the fight are you on?
He's thinking about it.
Oh, God. I'm... crap. I'm so sorry.
Uh, here, let's...
quick, before it stains.
There is another
hideout in the area.
- But first, I have...
- First you have what ?
A condition.
It's a very common power play
for someone who feels
backed into a corner
with nothing to lose or gain.
You have a what ?
What do you got ?
Every time you ask me a question,
I get to ask you a question.
The truth buys you the truth.
You lie, I lie.
All right.
But first, you show me on the map
where the Taliban are
holding these two marines.
All right ?
OK, here.
There's two caves
with a tunnel that connects them.
It's been there for over 200 years.
Why didn't you tell us about
this place to start with ?
He's been with the Taliban too long.
You're still the bloody enemy.
Me, on the other hand...
I'm all that's between you two.
I'm really sorry about this. I needed an
excuse to talk to you away from Komisky.
We need to figure out some signals
or this is gonna get expensive.
Komisky's no stranger to Franko.
- You saw that, too ?
- Another thing I saw... he's careful
to keep himself off the sat-link cameras
hidden from Lightman and Franko.
Have you heard from
my dad in the last 24 hours ?
Yeah. Yeah. Why ?
He always calls to check in
when he's out of town,
and he hasn't this time.
His phone goes straight to voicemail.
Sweetheart,
he's really swamped right now,
and he'll call as soon as he can.
Guys, we're minutes away from...
Hi Em, how's the party coming ?
What are they minutes away from ?
Minutes away from what ?
He will be back before
you know it, ok ?
I gotta go, Em, all right ?
We'll talk later.
- Charlie 3
- That's it. That's the cave.
Bloody better be.
Tell me.
- Am I ever gonna get home?
- We don't have time for this game.
It's not a game.
It's a test of trust.
Right ?
Well, if you ever do get home,
you're pretty much screwed.
It's the right cave.
I'm 100% certain.
Charlie one, target confirmed.
Move, move.
Charlie 1, copy, out.
Stand by...
Contact !
Man down ! Man down !
Man down !
You and your science just let this
bastard lead us into an ambush.
Check for Charlie 3.
Charlie 3 is hit.
No! Back off !
What did he just say to you ?
He said, "kill me now,
it would be an honor."
You meant it, didn't you?
Who are you now ?
My Taliban name is Khaled.
My name is Mo... short for Mohammed.
Zero, Charlie one,
Charlie three's hit bad. Wait. Out.
Did you or did you not
send my men into an ambush?
I did not !
I told you it was a Taliban hideout.
Did you expect it to be guarded ?
Maybe you underestimate your enemy.
No, wait! No, wait!
He's telling the truth.
He was as shocked as you are
by what happened.
You're not going to kill
an unarmed man in cold blood
just out of sheer
frustration, so knock it off.
All right ?
You know that man ?
- You know that man ?
- I've never seen him before.
- Do you know that man ?
- Foster, who you got in there ?
- Ed Komisky, defense department.
Hi, Ed. I see you've met
my friend Franko,
a little bit ago.
There you go.
Amaising !
Is he one of the ones
who sent you here?
Is he the one that sent you here?
What did he tell you ?
Did he tell you, you gonna be a hero ?
Did he tell you, you gonna be patriot ?
Is that... what then?
Then what ?
That's between you and him ?
I'll be very happy to set up that face
to face meeting, but right now,
we've got some mess to clear up.
Move. Move.
Kill the feed.
Kill the feed !
What, he's shutting us out?
Get him on the sat-phone.
Order him to give us eyes back.
If you think Lightman is gonna jump
because you bark, you don't know him.
- Trust me.
- Call me if he comes back online.
You know Franko, don't you ?
The only reason I'm here is because
I want to see those two marines
- returned home alive.
- Us, too.
Look at you.
A minute ago, you said
you were willing to die
by this man's hand,
it would be an honor.
Now look at you.
You'd anything you can to get home
just because of what you saw
on that sat-Link.
Zero, Charlie 1, over.
Casualty, Charlie 3.
Chest wound.
If he calls in an air strike,
in a matter of minutes,
lot of people are gonna die.
Doesn't matter what side you're on.
When I got here,
you thought I was here
to help you, didn't you ? Didn't you?
There's another way in.
Where ?
When did you get hooked ?
Let's go !
Hurry the hell up.
What ? What ?
On war. On this.
You get high on being in the middle
of it all. Don't you ?
I can see it in your face.
Why are you doing this ?
Ok, you know what ?
There is no other way in. They're dead.
Look, I told you, you lie, I lie.
All right, Bosnia, 1994.
I didn't see direct action,
but I was
I was this close to it.
You get lucky just one time.
You survive, right ?
It's the rush. There's no...
There's nothing like it.
It's delusions of immortality.
Right ?
You're enjoying this.
Now it's your turn.
You owe me the other
tunnel to that cave.
- Tell them to go left.
- No. You tell them.
- You tell him !
- Tell them to go left about 100 yards.
There's a rock with an arch in it.
- This doesn't work, he's done.
- Yeah, so am I.
- Mo what's this ?
- Look at that.
This isn't just
a test of trust, is it ?
You're playing this game because
you think if this mission goes south,
then you're not
the only one to blame.
But ...
if it succeeds,
I'm gonna become
your brother in arms, right ?
I'm gonna be more likely to help you
somewhere down the road, right ?
Don't hold your breath.
Ms. Lenox,
What do you know about Ed Komisky ?
Mr. Komisky is a hangover
from previous administrations.
Man's more like a pentagon ghost.
We're beginning to think that he was
involved in some sort of operation
which abandoned this man
Franko in Afghanistan.
Are you aware
of any such operations ?
- You don't want to think about it ?
- I know no operations involving Franko.
No records exist of CIA
or any other agency's involvement.
But he could be an agency asset
that you have never heard about ?
I understand what you're asking.
But I'm not sure I can get
any answers quicker than you can.
Franko's Aunt.
I need her here as soon as possible.
- Can you do that ?
- Lightman's back on line.
- He needs our eyes and ears
for this next part. - We never...
Had this conversation. I got it.
If I help get these marines out,
I want my story told.
- That's above my pay grade. Dream on.
- It's right at my pay grade,
if your story's true.
That's the back entrance into the cave.
They're gonna hit a tunnel.
And they can go
one of two directions.
Left ?
Left is bad.
Charlie one, move right, over.
No, wait !
Wait a second !
If this is a back way into
it's also a back way out.
We mount a frontal assault. That way
they'll try and haul ass out back
with the prisoners.
That's what I'd do.
How about you ?
Hold, positions, Charlie 1,
hold positions. Set evac charges.
Stand by for enemy, over.
That's not Florida.
- How did you get in here ?
- You lied to me. He lied to me.
Charlie 1, hold positions.
Set evac charge.
Stand by for enemy. Over.
Dad ?
Emily.
Dad !
Did he just get...
No, he didn't.
Charlie 1, move to
alternate cave entrance now.
Charlie 3, Charlie 3,
Zero alpha, over !
How'd the Taliban find us?
They got his radio when he was hit,
used it for directions to find us here.
Fire support, confirm position. Over
Moving through tunnel now.
Going firm at tunnel intersection.
Contact ! Contact !
Marine prisoners and Taliban !
Taliban dead.
Evac complete. We have two marines
and rescue team complete.
- Setting evac charges now. Over.
- Copy that.
Alpha whiskey 1, standing by,
waiting for your signal. Over.
I confirm we need medic on board.
Over.
It's a direct hit.
The radios are dead for good.
They're out there on their own now.
Wait.
What about us ?
- You got any contingencies ?
- In case of loss ...
of comms during contact with the enemy,
we have 20 mins to haul ass out of here.
What happens in 20 mins ?
Smart bombs turn this place into
a parking lot, and everything in it.
So the only way that you can
get out of here is if you lure
the enemy into the kill zone,
which happens to be ?
- Copy that.
- Thank you very much.
All right, you wait here.
If I'm not back ....
in 18 minutes,
you leave by that door.
You know how to use that ?
- Not bad for a scientist.
- I've had my moments.
Torrific.
We've got 17 minutes.
You want to tell me
about your moments ?
That game's over now.
I mean...
besides, you're the one who
wants his story told, so...
How badly you want to hear it ?
All right,
answer's probably gonna stay
in this room anyway.
Ask your question.
What did you do in Bosnia?
Intelligence.
You seem like you don't wanna talk
about it, why is that?
- The past is the past, right?
- I can relate to that.
I know that you're trying to get
some common ground between us,
all right, Khaled but...
I didn't betray my country.
You betrayed something.
I betrayed myself, how about you?
Mr. Komisky, a moment of your time?
You too, Torres.
My real name is
Specialist Glen Welsh.
What branch of the military
were you in?
Back to Bosnia, your betrayal.
Sarajevo.
'94.
We were interrogating...
a Serb officer
about his sniper positions.
- We?
- MI6, British intelligence.
And I didn't believe him, so...
we changed his clothes
and chocked him out into sniper alley.
He lasted about 4 seconds,
got about 18 feet-ish.
His information was accurate.
But he's the enemy.
I'm a scientist.
I'm not an executioner.
War got the better of you, too.
Yeah, now your turn.
I was aiming for special ops.
Before I got there,
'99,
I got in a bar fight.
They threw me in the brig for 3 years.
Manslaughter.
I could tell you
my drinks were spiked, but...
- what would you care?
- Right.
Two years later,
and this is right after 9/11,
I got jumped in the brig
and was thrown in the hospital.
Somebody had knifed me in my back.
- That's when they offered me a way out.
- That man you saw on the SatLink.
Ms. Perriman.
Franko's Aunt Wendy?
Franko?
He's alive?
Where is he?
And they moved you
straight from the brig hospital
to a training facility, right?
Where?
Somewhere out west.
I don't know exactly.
They didn't tell me.
It looked a lot like this hell hole.
They trained you to do what?
They taught me Pashto.
They put me through their own brand
of special ops training, then they...
they dropped me
in the middle of Taliban territory,
posing as an aid worker
with Shia sympathies.
They said they're gonna be watching me,
that they'd have my back
and that they'd pull me out
when the time was right.
All right, but they didn't.
They never came back for you, right?
They betrayed you,
so you went over to the other side.
Is that it?
Did you ever kill
any American troops?
- That's a bloody lie.
- No!
Look,
you try...
to shoot over their heads,
but those bastards...
they just keep shooting back.
What?
What are you doing?
Hold still!
How did the people that put you here,
to know how to find you?
How were they tracking you?
I think I know.
Hold still!
If I'm right,
this is gonna prove your story's real.
What the hell are you doing,
Lightman?
All of you, help me hold him still!
Hold him still!
We gotta go.
Right now!
- Not until I've done this!
- You listen to orders!
I often have orders from the president.
Did I forget to mention that?
Now hold him still.
Give me the pliers.
My sister, Peg,
died giving birth to Franko.
I raised him
just like he was my own.
Have you two met before?
What elementary school
did Franko go to?
Who was his first girlfriend?
I believe you really did have a sister
who died in childbirth,
which is what makes your story
believable, to the Layman.
- It's not a story.
- Do you carry a picture of your nephew?
I imagine over the years
of not knowing
where he is or if he's even alive,
it might be a great comfort to you,
- a symbol of hope to have...
- That's enough.
You don't have to answer that.
They came to me after 9/11.
My sister's death didn't have to be
for nothing, they said.
She's definitely telling the truth.
I can tell you want to get this out,
so please keep going, Ms. Perriman.
Someone from the CIA did come to me.
I guess it was...
like an acting role, for my country.
You gotta understand,
I wanted to do something.
We all wanted to do something.
Including you, sir.
I believe that.
But you sent a man into Afghanistan
to infiltrate the Taliban.
Then what? You forget about him?
Or you just leave him there to rot?
- Or worse.
- We lost him.
The battery in his tracking device
died.
- The battery?
- It happens.
Know how hard it is
to find anyone out there?
I've heard.
We kept waiting for him to show up,
and when he didn't,
we assumed he was dead.
So...
please,
take your sanctimonious judgment
and park it somewhere else.
Snow.
If we don't get out of here, it'll be
the last white Christmas we ever see.
Not until I've done it, hold on.
Hold still!
There.
It's a tracking device.
- Two-year battery life.
- He is one of ours.
Why didn't you tell us
who you were in the beginning?
Orders.
I disobey, I'm dead.
The only person I reveal my identity to
is the man with the code. Nobody else!
The code was Aunt Wendy.
That's a reason.
But it's not a real reason, is it?
You can do better than that.
And these bastards caught me,
and they beat me.
Yeah. I was Taliban.
That's better.
Who are you now?
You're the expert.
You tell me.
You tell your mom?
Why not?
Same reason you didn't tell me.
Don't you think you should tell her?
He can tell her when he gets back.
Move out!
Let's go, go!
Let's go!
Move, move!
Move, go!
Lightman, you're out of here!
We saw it on your face earlier.
You've got orders never to let this man
leave this room alive, don't you?
Am I right?
These men remind you
of what you wanted to be,
So now it's about a last fight you fight
and which side of the fight you're on,
And if you finally get...
to do what you came here
in the first place to do.
I need 45 seconds of fight out of him
to clear the tunnel.
Here.
Where's home?
1245...
Glenview Park, Iowa City.
Say it again!
1245 Glenview Park,
Iowa City.
Nice job, doc!
Not really!
That's him.
Heard you helped get us out.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
Dr. Lightman.
The real Aunt Wendy.
Please,
don't do this.
This is a matter
of national security.
What story
did you people tell specialist Welsh,
Franko's, family?
Killed in action?
Died in the brig?
Died in the brig, nice one.
I was serving my country.
Our country,
you mean.
It's our country.
It's time you let that one go, mate.
You go public with this,
you'll be breaking the law.
I'm not going public.
I'm gonna tell a man's family
- the truth about their son.
- You know what I mean.
You know...
sooner or later you got to stand up
and be counted for our mistakes.
Your man, Franko, he went over...
to the Taliban.
That's a big mistake, but...
in the end...
you know what I mean...
Mr. Welsh?
What's going on out here?
Who are you?
Who is it, hon?
Do you mind if if come in
for a minute?
There're things I'd like to tell you
about your son, Glen.
Glen?
Do you mind?
Happy holidays.
Dr. Lightman...
Would you let me do the talking?
Just so long as it's the truth.
He's late.
Midwest is snowed under.
Delays everywhere.
My mom's stuck in St. Louis.
What are you gonna you do?
Hello, darling.
I know.
You shouldn't have had to see that.
I was scared, dad.
- I was really scared.
- I know.
Me, too. Me, too.
Is it...
naive to ask you,
beg you really,
never to do anything like that again?
Well, yeah.
It's a little bit.
- Let's share some of that.
- All right.
It's beautiful.
Darling...
Are you OK?
I'm not sure.
Good. You're not meant to be.
- You look nice...
- Thank you.
Ish.
I got you a secret Santa.
I'm watching you.
Oh, man.
Don't mention it.