Check this out.
You could get a lot of dough
for that thing.
Watch it.
What is that?
Someone's downstairs!
Call the police.
Where are you going?
No! Richard!
Group therapy folks,
report to the kitchen for KP duty.
Everybody else,
I'll see you in the common room.
Ava, come here.
Girl, you're gonna get me
in trouble.
OK, what's up?
Shut up two seconds
and I'll tell you.
Keep this for me, but you can't let
anyone see it or know you've got it.
- Where did you get that?
- Just promise.
You know I don't do promises.
Forget your stupid rules.
Just promise me.
- Or give it back.
- All right, I promise.
Ava, Marly, you got somewhere to be?
Yeah, I had an eyelash.
Yeah, it's still here.
- My wishes never come true.
- Let's go.
Calm down.
Slow down.
Are you actually praying?
Of course not.
That is so insulting.
You'll get your license
when you're good and ready.
- But I've been 16 for months.
- Which is my point exactly.
Parallel park just here.
- You get one shot.
- All right.
- All right, pull up.
- I am.
Pull up.
I am.
A little bit further,
All right, stop.
No cheating.
It's technology, dad.
The future is now.
- Puppy!
- Wait. What? Where?
Did I hit something?
I believe so.
It's not like I enjoyed it
or anything.
And I am paying for all the damage,
aren't I?
Don't hold a grudge.
Your face gets pinched.
Look at your mum.
I need you to listen to something.
And tell me what to do.
- All right, slow down.
- Just listen.
Ria, you have to come get me.
Something happened.
I'm not sure what,
but something bad.
I'm not even supposed to be
on the phone. Please, I need...
She sounds pretty desperate.
Yeah, well,
she's a liar and a delinquent,
which is she's been locked up
for 7 months.
You feel her message is a lie?
I don't know.
I never know with her.
Who is this girl to you?
She's my sister.
The Lie to team presents:
Épisode 216: Delinquent
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
www.u-sub.net
20 bucks says
those cops are here for Ava.
Sisterly love.
Half-sister.
The degenerate paternal half.
- I.D., please.
- Thanks.
Again, Ava is in solitary.
She's not allowed visitors.
No exceptions.
Can you just tell me if it had
anything to do with the cops we saw?
I can't discuss it.
- Grow a pair.
- Excuse me?
I was telling her to grow a pair
of testicles.
Metaphorically speaking,
'cause you're stonewalling.
Which is what people do when they have
something to hide. What are you hiding?
- Enough of this. Come here.
- What?
Ria, you have to come get me.
Something happened.
I'm not sure what,
but something bad.
I'm not even supposed to be
on the phone.
Please, I need...
All I can tell you
is that Ava's friend Marly
seems to have run away last night.
So you locked Ava up?
Why am I doing all the talking?
She's your sister.
Go on, say something. Go on.
All right.
So you locked up my sister?
That's brilliant, then.
Until she decides to share
what she knows
about how Marly evaded
our security system, yes.
You realize isolation
will reinforce her distrust
of authority and make her
even less likely to open up.
You must be a psychologist.
I must be.
There's really nothing I can do.
My sister,
my baby sister.
They won't let her eat.
They won't let her sleep.
The warden won't let me see her.
She's so scared and alone,
and now there's this girl
who's missing.
Now...
You take me to Ava
or I'll take that phone message
and these tears
to a friend of mine
at the local news.
Dax.
Tell Dr. Burns Ava has visitors.
I'd like him to observe.
What's with the old white guy?
I'm your sister's boss.
- The lie guy?
- Yep.
- You brought the lie guy.
- Ava, what happened last night?
- Like you care.
- I'm here.
I care.
You're super sexy.
You want to make out?
Absolutely.
Climb on board, darling.
- She's testing him.
- Ya think?
Sorry. I'll hold the condescension.
- You like making people uncomfortable.
- Yeah, I do.
How about you?
- Why so scared, then?
- I'm not scared.
The man is a deception expert.
Is it Marly?
I'll take that as a yes, actually.
You remind me of your sister
2 years ago.
A completely open book,
trying desperately to be inscrutable.
So why did you leave a message
on your sister's machine?
- I wanted to get out of here.
- Why?
Look around.
I get in one cop's face one time,
they toss me in juvie.
That's not all that happened.
They share a dad.
I gather he was pretty useless.
Stage four alcoholic.
Ava grew up being beaten
during his blackouts.
The mother ODed when she was 10.
Ava was in the next room.
And then she went into the system
when she needed intensive therapy.
The girl has been here for 6 months.
It's the first time family's shown up.
Dax should know.
He used to be a resident.
Now I'm a success story.
My social worker says
I have a recurrent shoplifting problem.
I say this ass deserves good denim.
It's a nice ass.
If I need something,
who's gonna get it for me but me?
If wanted out of here so bad,
why did you call me and hang up?
I heard somebody coming. I freaked.
Where's Marly?
I don't know.
- I don't believe her. Do you?
- Not for a second.
Fine.
I saw Marly last night.
She was sneaking out.
Crap.
- What's that?
- Lockdown.
Someone's hurt, right?
I'm a doctor.
Let me guess. It's Marly, right?
Marly's dead.
You can just say it.
Somebody hit her in the head
hard enough to kill her.
The police are investigating.
Whatever. You think they'll let me
go back to my room now?
You said that you followed Marly
last night when she snuck out.
- So?
- And your message said
that something bad happened.
- Ava, what did you see?
- Nothing.
You're lying.
She is lying, right?
All right, enough.
This is ridiculous.
- My turn.
- What are you doing?
You killed her, right?
- No, I didn't!
- Admit it.
- You bashed her head in.
- No, I didn't!
I think you're brilliant.
The way you manipulate your sister.
You play on all that guilt
she carries around for...
not being able to protect you
from your father.
But the funny thing is, right,
I don't have that problem.
Now, your friend is dead.
You can play tough all you like,
but you loved her.
You loved her like a sister.
That's why I'm gonna help you.
But first you gotta tell me
what you know.
You tell me or I'm gonna leave.
I'm gonna leave,
your sister's gonna leave
and you're gonna be stuck here
on you're own.
And we will not come back,
so tell me what you know.
She was pregnant.
Marly?
Who's the father?
- I don't know.
- Lie.
She was always crying
after she'd visit Dr. Burns. Ask him.
That's not good enough. I'm off.
- Nice knowing you.
- Wait!
Last night...
I heard her scream.
I didn't try to help her. I ran.
I was scared.
It's my fault she's dead.
The police want to talk to me,
you have no authority to be here.
Dr. Lightman is
under contract to the city of DC.
And I'll be liaising
with the metropolitan PD.
Enough
with the jurisdictional pissing contest.
You got a murderer in your facility.
Which means that your kids are in danger
and 1 of them is my associate's sister,
which makes you a very lucky person,
because you need me.
In that case, how can I help you?
I'd like to see the files of juveniles
who've been convicted of violent crimes.
- I'll need approval from the police.
- Consider it done.
In the meantime,
did you know that Marly was pregnant?
Ava did.
I bet she wasn't the only one.
- Were you aware of this?
- Yes.
I knew one of our girls was pregnant.
I decided I'll just keep that to myself.
Do you have any idea
who the father is?
Marly was disciplined for making out
with a kid named Tyrel Gardner
in the chapel a few months ago.
Tyrel. He might have been the father,
but he didn't kill Marly.
He was released last month. No way
he could have gotten in here last night.
Still, I'll pass on his information
to the police.
They can add him to
their interview list.
We all know these kids
aren't gonna talk to the cops.
We need to go to the source,
to go to Marly.
Group therapy is confidential.
Reynolds is back at the office.
I could call him.
You can call whoever you like.
It's still an invasion of privacy.
- A woman was murdered.
- I'm aware of that,
and I'm the only one here
who knew her.
- How about a little flexibility?
- I'll show you one session.
Marly's last.
Lightman means well,
but he's slightly insane.
Yeah, I noticed.
Look, Marly dying
wasn't your fault, Ava.
There's nothing you could have done.
What's wrong?
- Somebody went through my stuff.
- How can you tell?
The kids here steal.
I leave things a certain way.
Were they looking for something?
Come on.
- Someone think you know the killer?
- Where is it?
Ava, this is important.
Weird things happen in this place.
That's all I know.
Ava, why don't you start us all off
by telling us about a good memory.
Good memory?
Whenever my sister visited me,
she'd braid my hair.
After my dad had a bad night,
she'd do it for hours.
Why does Ava's memory
bother you, Marly?
The girl's ass being beaten.
Who cares about hair-braiding.
Marly really didn't like you,
did she?
I'm not here to be liked.
Whenever Ria stayed with us,
she got the worst of it.
I remember that.
She probably took it on purpose,
to protect you.
Will you pause it.
That's Maurice Jones, right?
I just flagged his file.
Dad's in jail.
Background of substance abuse.
Three arrests for assault.
You could have said the same thing
about me a while back.
Could we also say that you bludgeoned
your pregnant neighbor into a coma?
Man, you got no right
gettin' in my face!
You ain't gonna find nothing.
Get off me, man.
Hey, man, that ain't mine!
That's not mine.
You are under arrest
for the murder of Marly Lourdes.
- I didn't hurt that girl!
- You see that.
Yeah. Go on.
- Excuse me. He's telling the truth.
- Please step away.
We're deception experts.
You have the wrong person.
- That's what I'm saying.
- They always say they didn't do it.
I didn't kill nobody!
If he's innocent,
a murderer is running around this place,
and I'm not leaving Ava a sitting duck.
I'm calling Reynolds.
No, forget Reynolds.
Could you take Torres
back to the office?
- Why?
- Now.
Give me your keys.
That was touching.
How are you
at following instructions?
Stay close to the railing.
It's a dead zone for the cameras.
- Where's Ria?
- She's back at the office.
It's just me and you now.
I'm going to break you out of here.
And then what?
Then we catch a killer.
All day not one of you thought:
"Let's call Eli and tell him
why nobody's in the office."
Loker, a girl was murdered.
That's exactly my point...
It's a scary world.
Bad things happen.
I worry.
- And apparently you have a sister.
- Half-sister.
All right, so, if this Maurice kid
with the proclivity toward violence was
framed, who killed this pregnant girl?
The youth center psychologist
is a maybe.
There was definitely something
between him and Marly on those tapes.
I'll call the deputy Warden,
see if I can sweet-talk her
into giving you more access.
- Why don't you not.
- Look, is this little Torres?
I just remembered,
I got some work to do.
I'm gonna pretend like I never
saw her. You call me if you need me.
I've got some research to do.
You could be charged
with aiding and abetting.
- Or kidnapping!
- Yeah.
- I've been charged with worse.
- Sorry.
If I did get killed like Marly,
your life would get easier.
You're embarrassing me
in front of my boss.
I don't think she cares.
FYI, I'm not staying with you.
Tell me where you're gonna stay then,
some lowlife boyfriends?
I'm staying with Cal.
Now, don't go thinking that's a get out
of jail free pass, 'cause it's not.
As soon as this is solved,
you're back inside.
In the meantime,
you're staying with Foster.
- What?
- You heard me.
I suggest you leave.
OK. You must be hungry.
Foster, why don't you get
Dr. Burns on the phone
and have him come in here?
I believe you have his number.
- She should be with me.
- You're off the case.
- No, I'm not.
- You are. You blew your chance.
You're too close to see clearly.
Plus, she's gonna be fighting you
every step of the way. So...
Go home, Torres.
I mean that.
I told you I didn't know
Marly was pregnant.
Not only did you know she was pregnant,
I think you're the father.
I don't care what you think,
and I have to get back to work.
You don't have to go to work, and you do
care what I think. Why is that, exactly?
I don't even have to be here.
- Why are you, then?
- Foster said you wanted Maurice's file.
You got the hots for Foster.
I cared about Marly,
I wanted to help.
Now tell the truth, Burnsy.
I mean, assuming
that you're not the father, I can put
in a good word for you with Foster.
You're kind of a jerk.
I have been told that.
I get it, though.
I get it. You're embarrassed.
You're probably also embarrassed that
Marly made you all hot and bothered.
Marly was a kid. I never touched her
and I never wanted to.
That's actually true.
All right, then...
You're not the father.
What about this Tyrel kid?
You don't even know that, do you?
So what's all this guilt
that I'm seeing then?
I'm a psychologist.
My conversations with the kids
are confidential.
It's important that they trust me.
Ethics.
That's always so inconvenient.
How about this, then?
When...
did Marly tell you she was pregnant?
And she did tell you.
I know, because you got evasive
as all hell earlier.
3 weeks ago.
She begged me not to tell anyone.
I should have reported it
to the deputy Warden.
Marly would have been
transferred to another facility
and maybe she wouldn't be dead.
I didn't want to be one more person
who'd betrayed her. Can I go now?
No. Whatever it is, you're not leaving
till you say it. So...
The father of Marly's baby,
whoever it was,
one of her friends had a crush on him,
it seemed to cause a rift.
Friend?
Ava?
I don't know for sure.
I shouldn't be telling you this,
because you're just a child
and you need to be protected.
My dad's on his way.
I bet he is. I bet you just call
and he comes running in?
Because that's the
kind of dad he is,
a come-runninger.
Can I get you some coffee?
My dad is a run-the-other-wayer.
After he smacks you, of course.
Smack first, then run the other way.
Daddy's home.
Hi, Em. Good job. Go to your room.
If you drove here, you're fired.
I took a taxi.
I'm a responsible drunk.
Yeah, clearly.
Don't be mad at me.
I need to tell you something.
- Not bloody likely.
- Let me go. Get off of me.
What are you doing
drunk off your face
in my house with my daughter?
I had nowhere else to go.
- You're a good dad.
- That's not the point.
You're a good man.
You are. You try to hide it,
but you are.
Just tell me why you're here,
all right?
You don't have to be
so mean to me, you know.
I'm so cold.
Maybe you want to warm me up, Cal.
You stop that right now.
Tell me why you're here!
Oh, my god.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dr. Lightman.
The torres twins.
They throw themselves at me
from left and right.
How'd I get so lucky?
It's my sister.
She makes me crazy.
You're two sides
of the same coin, you know?
No, we're not.
Your dad taught you
to see the truth.
- He didn't teach me anything.
- And he taught Ava how to lie.
Look, I want to believe her.
I do, but that girl has lied to me
so many times.
You know, a couple of years ago,
she stayed with me.
She gave her boyfriend my key,
and he cleaned me out.
She says that he wanted to come over
and watch football
on the cable or whatever.
But I bet you she helped him carry
everything I own to the curb.
Well, did you ever consider
the vague possibility
that the bit about the game
might be true and that...
her boyfriend just
took advantage of her trust?
Here, drink that.
And frankly,
I'm more curious about
what you did to her.
Look, Ava's a liar
and a manipulator,
and she works every angle she can.
It doesn't matter who she hurts.
Actually, she's kind
of just like you.
You know, you might be right there.
But what if she's involved
in Marly's murder some way
and we helped her escape?
She could be halfway to New York
in Foster's car by now.
Ria always thinks
everything's my fault.
I'm sure that's not true.
We never lived together
'cause we didn't have the same mom,
but when I was little,
she would always come by,
help me with my homework.
She does love you, you know.
Yeah, I guess.
So what do you want for dessert?
What do you got?
I have got some ice cream,
of course, but I also have...
- Put her down!
- Let me go!
Get her!
The egg! Where is it?
Tie her up!
I'm trying! She's strong!
Shut up!
Don't put your hand on me,
you little bitch!
- I got it!
- No!
Let's go, I got it!
- I'm in here.
- Jeez.
What the bloody hell happened here?
- You all right, love?
- Yeah,
I'm fine.
I'm fine. Everything's...
Everything's fine.
You all right?
You should be proud.
She got me out of my ropes.
She untied me.
Good thing she was here.
I had nothing to do with this.
No? 'cause I find it very strange, the
night you come and you stay with Foster,
somebody broke into her house.
- It was Tyrel? You called him!
- I had nothing to do with this!
- You called him! He was here!
- Stop it!
- Don't defend her.
- You knock it off.
Ava was just as terrified as I was,
she had no idea this was gonna happen
or who they were.
Just no idea!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean...
You all right?
Take your time.
I had no idea
you were such a crybaby.
Cal, they were just kids.
They were kids.
I could tell by their voices.
There were-there were.
- There were 3 boys and a girl.
- From Covington, hey?
- Where are the cops?
- They're just gonna take
Ava back to juvie, and then they'll
arrest you for taking her from there.
We can take care of this on our own.
You're supposed to be
the sensible one.
Yeah, and you're supposed to take
unnecessary risks.
Not when it comes to you.
They were looking for this egg,
this little jeweled egg
that Ava had in her pocket,
I called Reynolds
and he's gonna put it into the system
- and see what he can find out.
- What's so important about an egg?
Ava won't talk about it.
She'll talk to me.
No, she won't.
Ava's gone.
Right, so now we think Ava's evil.
No, no, Loker.
She's just a confused
and scared girl
who got overwhelmed and...
I don't know what I think.
We got company.
He works for the Deputy Warden.
It's Dax, right?
Can I help you?
It's the group therapy sessions
you wanted.
You didn't get 'em from me.
Wait a minute.
Let's talk.
You sure you don't want sound?
Right now I'm only interested
in their physicality.
Dax took a big risk bringing these here.
Why would he do that?
You're the shrink.
Sometimes I wish
I were a fortune-teller.
Freeze it.
Her.
Will you bring her up?
You see how she shifts her shoulders
when she's confronted?
Will you bring up the sound?
You go into a store,
take, like, a lip gloss.
You got no idea
how much crap I take.
It ain't even hard.
Her voice was muffled
underneath the mask, but, yes.
Yeah, that's her.
She was at my house.
Look, she'll be here.
I told you, whenever Ava gets upset,
this is where she comes.
I've found her here
like a hundred times.
I'm sorry about what happened
to Foster.
I don't know, I should have known
better than to trust Ava.
All right, get out.
- Wait.
- Get out or grow up. It's your choice.
What? How am I not grown up?
I have a job, I have an apartment,
I pay my bills on time.
What more do you want from me?
All right, let me see.
Your sister's missing,
Foster's been attacked,
I've committed a felony,
you set a horrific example
for my daughter,
and you tried to stick
your tongue down my throat.
And not once in this entire adventure
have you been honest.
Now, see, that's what I'm talking about,
right there.
I mean, this isn't about your sister.
This all about you, isn't it?
Look, I just...
I can't be what she needs.
It strikes me all she needs
is for you to believe her for 2 seconds.
If you can't do that,
you might as well hand in your cards
and resign as big sister.
There she is.
Wait, no.
Let's see what she does first.
That's Tyrel.
Oh, my god.
That doesn't bode well.
If you were a guest in my home,
this is what I would do.
I'd offer you a drink.
Soda rots your teeth.
The point is to be welcoming,
you didn't give me that chance earlier.
I know you were in my house, Amber.
You and 3 boys
from Covington.
You don't know nothin'.
You know what I know?
I know that the turn of your arm
when you pull that chair,
it's pretty distinctive.
And I saw it just now.
And I saw it at my house.
- Dr. Foster's good.
- Yeah, she's the best.
Well, second-best.
Thanks for bringing Amber by.
These are my kids.
If Amber's in trouble, I want to know.
Tell me about that egg.
I don't know nothin' about that.
Just that we had to get it.
Yeah? Who's we?
Amber,
I can see you want to tell me.
Look at me.
I think you owe me.
The crew, OK?
One night...
every few weeks, we...
break into houses,
take stuff rich folks
spend millions on.
Who runs this crew?
Somebody's gotta get you out of there.
I ain't upper management.
What do you get
in return for your participation?
Early release.
You can get, like,
months off your time.
Who signs off on early release?
Deputy Warden, but she'd never be
involved in something like this.
I need to know who runs the crew.
I know you're scared,
but I can protect you.
Look at your face, bitch.
You can't even protect yourself.
You found her.
Yeah, safe and sound
and the custody of the FBI.
Me and Tyrel weren't doing
anything wrong.
Yeah, you weren't doing anything right,
either, were you?
Come on, this way.
Come on, Ava, I saw you.
I saw you put the mask on.
- Were you about to rob someone?
- No.
I didn't know anything about
what they were doing till tonight.
Tyrel told me.
Go on.
I just wanted to know
what it felt like.
They put on these masks
and they have the power.
I just wanted to feel that,
just for a minute.
But help me.
You are involved.
You had the egg.
I was just trying to help Marly.
I promised her I would keep it.
But I didn't do anything.
I believe you.
I'm on your side, OK?
And I'm sorry,
I know I don't deserve this,
but will you please trust me?
Please.
You a man, Tyrel?
Bet you think you're a real man.
I got news for you. You're not a man
at all. 'cause real men,
they don't let women
fight their battles for them.
- You're a little boy.
- Say that again and you're a dead man.
You're a little... boy.
And you're terrified to boot.
'Cause men, they admit it
when they're afraid.
So...
Be a man, Tyrel.
Tyrel, just tell them
what you told me.
I was recruited to the crew
when I first got to Covington.
A few months ago we did a job.
Some serious stuff went down.
- A guy died.
- The man's name was Richard Grange.
According to insurance reports, that
fancy egg was stolen from his house.
I kept it. Thought I might need it
for leverage one day.
So you gave Marly the egg
to protect her.
And you told her to blow the whistle
if she didn't get early release?
- I wanted her to get out.
- She was pregnant.
Why didn't you tell me?
The same reason I wouldn't tell you
who Marly's baby daddy was.
I promised her I wouldn't.
And I keep my promises.
You know, I think
it's time you told me
who you're afraid of.
He can't get you here.
You'll be safe.
Who? What is going on?
Dax killed Marly.
He wouldn't do that.
No, I know all about
the home invasion crew. I know that,
Dax was forcing you
to sign early release papers. So...
Please.
I'll lose my job.
I... I didn't have a choice.
Well, whatever he's got on you
must be good.
He threatened my family.
My parents are in assisted living,
and Dax said
all I had to do was sign the papers
and leave the service door unlocked.
All right.
Well, I don't want you to get bored,
So let's watch the telly.
You know,
people have killed
for this damn egg.
- You killed for it.
- No, man.
What happened at the house,
it was an accident.
All right, the man came at me.
I pushed back.
And he went over.
After that, I told
her I wanted to stop.
But she wouldn't let me.
What is going on?
Didn't I mention it?
Your assistant, Dax,
was arrested a couple of hours ago.
You said he was coming after me.
Oh, yeah, big time.
Yeah, he blames you for everything.
Even says you killed Marly.
Is that why you brought me here,
to accuse me of murder?
Let me out of here!
Keep watching,
this is a really good bit.
Dr. Foster says
you were the one that brought in
the group therapy tapes.
That was a big break in the case.
Why the sudden lack
of self-preservation?
I told you
that I wanted it to be over.
I wanted her to get
what she deserves.
You know, the funny thing is, right,
that every word
that comes out of that kid's mouth
is the truth,
and every word
that comes out of yours is a lie.
This is very embarrassing for you.
- Really?
- I've sacrificed everything for kids.
And that pisses you off.
You remember Ava's sister?
You know what pisses me off?
People who hurt the people I love.
I am the victim here.
You're the one with the massive bank
account. Of course, not in your name.
But the FBI have a hell of a knack
of tracking these things down.
I gave everything to my job, to kids.
I have given my whole life to them.
Well, don't stop now.
You're on a roll.
So, what, you spent your whole life
trying to drag these kids
up out of the mud, right?
And what do you get in return?
You get nothing.
I mean, that's how you
really feel, isn't it?
So now it's your turn.
Is that right?
How much money were you
gonna have to steal
before you could walk away
from these kids?
500 grand?
A million?
2 million?
Oh, 2.
Ambitious lady.
And once a man was killed
during a robbery, you had no choice.
Marly showed you the egg, threatened
to expose you. You had to kill her.
You can't prove any of this.
You admitted to know about
the robberies. You signed the releases.
And we have your bank records.
Dax made me do all of it.
Murderer!
- Shut up!
- Quiet!
It's my word against Dax's.
A juvenile delinquent,
a thief, a murderer.
- Who's a jury gonna believe?
- Tell her.
Every lie you told since you walked into
this room we have on tape.
We will walk a jury
through every microsecond
of every single one.
It is not your word
against Dax's anymore.
No, it's your word against mine.
You lose.
Put your hands behind your back.
You're under arrest.
The kids needed to see this.
It's therapy.
Unconventional therapy.
Absolutely.
Let's go.
Hey.
So Foster's got a friend who runs an
alternative boarding school in Richmond.
- And he said he'd take her.
- She's staying with me.
I'm petitioning for custody.
Once again you're fired.
You can't threaten
to fire people all the time.
Yeah, I can. Especially when they prove
to be complete idiots.
You don't get it. I promised her.
When I was in high school, I promised
that I would come back and get her
and we'd live together.
Our dad wouldn't be able to find us.
- We'd be free.
- Of what?
Everything.
- Our dad, mostly.
- Sounds peachy.
Yeah, but I didn't go back.
I just... I just left her there.
I broke my promise.
She needs help, love.
She needs to want help.
You got to let her find her own way.
Best part of being a parent.
Unfortunately.
- Tell Dr. Foster thanks.
- I will.
I should have been there more.
I didn't mean to leave you alone.
Stop. I can't cry my first day.
I'm really proud of you, you know?
I'm proud of you, too.
All right, go get smart.
I'm already smart, bitch.
- Hey. Watch your mouth.
- You're not my mom.
No, I'm not.
But I love you.
I love you.
- Well?
- You can't tell?
You failed.
I passed!
Well, done, girl. Well done.
So, can I drive home?
- No.
- What?
You're not driving again.
- No, come on.
- No, you crashed my car.