www.seriessub.com   www.sous-titres.eu
www.arcadya.net
Arcadya global team
Truthworteam
Well, he's lying.
The son of a bitch has been
playing us the whole time.
You really think we're that dumb?
No, I didn't say anything!
I didn't...
Expenses and overtime are two areas
we should really take a look at.
And, we should consider changing
our company investments portfolio.
- You started dating again, haven't you?
- Stop it, Cal, right now!
Stock broker?
Money manager?
Banker?
- I thought you wanted to have some fun.
- I'm having fun, don't you worry.
Really?
There's a visitor in your office,
Sally Robinson from London.
What?
Sally who?
Robinson.
High school sweetheart or something?
In my office?
Gotcha!
God almighty.
But my mates still call me Terry.
Come here.
Sally Robinson?
Hold on, is that a canoe
in your pocket, Cal?
Nicely played there, Mia.
Thank you anyway.
Excuse his manners.
- His ex-partner in crime.
- In a manner of speaking.
Gillian Foster. Current partner
in crime. Nice to meet you.
- You, too.
- All right, that's enough of that.
Good bye, Dr. Foster.
Cal, that is so charming.
It's been 22 years, isn't it?
- Jill, you fancy meeting us later?
- That's Gillian,
actually.
And she's busy.
- I'll take it.
- Call me if you need me.
So what are we drinking to?
How about Sally Robinson,
wherever she may be.
You wanker.
You all right there?
Don't start that bullocks
with me, Cal.
What?
With the eyes,
like you're reading my fortune.
No, I'm just pleased
to see you. Really.
Though a touch curious
as to why now.
Well, truth be told, I've thought twice
about looking you up
loads of times.
Terry marsh thinking twice.
Well, that's a first, isn't it?
Come on.
Where?
Listen, we'll do a deal.
What's past is past.
What's done is done.
It's just all water
under the bridge.
Fair?
Water under the bridge, then.
Hello, lovely lady.
I'm Terry.
- You should say hello to my dad.
- Hi, dad.
I'm Cara.
This is Alice.
- Stage names?
- Down, dad, down.
Forgive him.
Feast your eyes.
Not that way.
Over there, son.
I don't play cards anymore.
Look at me very carefully, Cal.
I did not get this jailbird
for nothing.
Don't make me say it.
I owe you my life.
There you go. I said it.
Do this for me tonight,
and then we're all square.
How much do you owe?
12 large.
- 12 grand?
- Like before.
I'll do all the talking and you...
Yeah, science.
It's texas hold'em,
no limit.
And this is my last 2 grand
in the world.
Cheers.
I've had a bit too much to drink
for this.
Yeah, well, that's rubbish.
But nice try.
- You're feeling luckier tonight?
- Hey, gents.
An old mate of mine,
Harry Sloane from N.Y.C.
How you doin'?
Hey, Foster.
Have you seen Lightman?
He's taking a personal day.
He's with a man who's
on the Scotland Yard watch list,
which means, when he's over here,
he's on the FBI watch list.
It's part of the
special relationship with the brits.
What's Terry done wrong?
Nothing recently. Watch lists are more
precautionary than anything else.
Yet, your tone is telling me
it's more than just a head's up.
It should also be telling you, I'm not
at liberty to discuss this any further.
G.B.H: Grievous Bodily Harm,
22 years ago?
They want you to dig into
Lightman's past with Terry?
Let's just say it's his immediate future
I'm more worried about.
Thousand.
I fold.
Call.
Down.
You OK, Terry?
I'm good for it, Lance.
- You know I am.
- I know you are.
We're all gentleman here,
someone get this man a drink.
Thanks.
Call.
All-in.
- I said...
- I heard you the first time.
Call.
Ten high.
You called me on a jack high.
- That's ridiculous.
- Apparently not.
Gentlemen,
it's been a pleasure.
Can we have a little break, please?
Just a minute.
Why not?
Order up eggs.
Cheers.
Do you mind?
Harry Sloane from New York City?
Are you out of your bloody mind?
I could hardly say
you're Dr. Lightman, the lie expert
and the reader of faces.
The 12 grand was just a teaser
to get me in the game, is that it?
How much do you owe this psychopath?
- How much?
- 95.
- 95 grand?
- Yeah.
You expect me to take
that money off these men
instead of just walking out of here
while I still can?
Excuse me.
You know what's going
to happen to me if you walk away.
So is this a prank
or a serious death threat?
Very soon now, you'll all be sorry.
It's all going to end this week.
The pain will stop.
Uniforms.
Private school?
College preparatory.
You're the only one this video
was sent to?
As far as I know.
It was...
left on my desk during the lunch hour
in an envelope marked
"Headmaster, urgent"
- Has anyone else seen the tape?
- Just the FBI,
- and now you.
- Have you closed the school?
School's out for today.
My first advice to you...
Close the school.
For how long?
Until we determine who made this.
So indefinitely.
Do you realize what that would do to us?
That would ruin our school.
So this is about money?
From handwriting analysis
on the envelopes,
student files, locker searches
and security camera tapes,
agents on site were able to make
a preliminary list of students
who might fit the profile.
25 names?
- Fit the profile for what?
- Homicidal intent.
Hands up,
who's heard of the Lightman group?
All right, well, we are scientists
who interpret human emotions.
This morning, with your help,
I'm going to run an experiment
which should be quite informative so...
Rather than listen to me drone on,
let's just get started, shall we?
Very soon now, you'll all be sorry.
It's all going to end this week.
The pain will stop.
No one's that good.
You two are working together.
Who is he, Terry?
You cheating me?
'cause I will put
a bullet in your head.
There's 105 grand there.
You and Terry are even now.
You keep the change.
We're all gentlemen here.
At least for now, with all those
witnesses in the next room.
I said he keeps the change.
Mate, say something.
You're welcome.
Don't mention it.
I love you, Cal.
Don't forget that.
Yeah, I'll see you
in another 22 years.
Rough night, huh?
No rest for the wicked.
Something tells me you know that.
You want to know what else I know?
You know your buddy, Terry Moss,
He spent 3 years in Bellmarsh prison
in England.
'87 to '90 for assault and battery.
Yeah, it was a long time ago.
And he's gone now,
and I'm tired,
and I'm hungover,
and it's none of your business.
It's my business if you spent the night
at the penthouse suite at the Park hotel
where there were prostitutes
and illegal gambling.
Those women were prostitutes?
How'd you know?
Did you follow us?
That's interesting.
There. Surprise and shame in less
than a second, and then nothing.
Pulling down the mask.
Put her on the list.
Go back a moment.
There you go.
See this girl?
Same girl, she glances at the teacher.
There you go, see?
And he catches her at it.
He's got his eye on her for some reason.
So does this girl here. Look.
Then she looks over at that guy.
Nice one, Loker.
Soon you'll be asking me
for a raise,
which I've been assured
that we can't afford so...
stand down.
Well, keep watching the tape, then.
- Be back in a minute.
- You look awful.
And yet, I feel so much worse.
I said 22 years,
not 22 minutes.
We're in trouble.
They know who you are
and what you do,
and they ain't happy.
- What do they want?
- You know,
they want to see you saw a girl in half.
What do you think they want?
They want you to be their magic man.
They're waiting around the corner.
And if you don't come now, then...
Then I'm done.
As in dead, done.
I'll see what
I can find out from him.
Your buddy's lost his FBI tail.
Do you have any clue
on where he could be right now?
Come with me, will you?
He's in my office.
He's in your office?
What is he doing in there?
I've got a major
bloody problem here.
You're damn right, you do.
You do understand that terry's involved
with an extremely dangerous criminal?
- Lance Mc Clellan.
- Lance Mc Clellan exactly.
He's a new-school crime boss,
educated, well-connected,
Hidden in plain sight.
This ends now.
Terry's family to me. There's no way
I'm going to let him hang himself.
I'm not going to let him
hang you either.
Wait, what's Mc Clellan's game?
It depends.
Which means you don't know?
That means that you're gonna help me
Help terry to help you.
If anyone's helping anyone here,
It's gonna be you
helping to bring down
Mc Clellan and Terry.
I know he's your friend,
but those guys are bad sons of bitches.
Mc Clellan sent Terry for me, which
means he needs something from me?
Whatever it is, he needs it quick.
If you're suggesting what I think
you're suggesting, you can forget it.
- You're not an undercover agent.
- Knock it off, I'm doing this.
- Not if I arrest you.
- You're going to arrest me?
I won a hundred grand
in cards last night.
I know a bluff when I see one.
You're not arresting me.
And you keep foster out of this.
Her focus needs to be 100%
on that school.
And I'm banking on you to have
my back for this.
Like a real FBI agent?
Something like that.
We're needed
in the conference room.
Torres is here with three kids
from the school.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Reynolds was just telling me
what a bad seed Terry was.
And it came as a bit of a shock
because there was I thinking
that he was a choir boy.
Stand up.
When did you make the video?
- What's your name?
- I didn't make it.
Exploding buildings,
that was news footage?
- Your name is?
- Stacey.
- I don't know.
Probably.
I couldn't...
I'm the one who made that video.
Jared rollins is my name.
I made the video.
Get your hands out of your pockets.
So what's the plan?
Is it a bombing
or a shooting or what?
Because you know,
there always is a plan.
You tell me.
So when did you make the video?
What does it matter?
I thought it would have
mattered a great deal to you.
I made it,
that's all you need to know.
Who did you send it to?
What?
It's all right there.
He's lying, he didn't make it.
Why would you lie
about making the video?
'Caus maybe
they all deserve to die,
Or at least worry about it.
Who?
They know who they are.
If he didn't make the video,
he sure wishes he had.
His face, body language.
It's homicidal intent.
- Your name is?
- Stacey.
That was news footage?
I don't know. Probably.
I'm the one who made it.
Jared Rollins is my name.
When he said he made the video,
He deliberately interrupted stacey.
And she's relieved.
He's covering for her,
he's protecting her.
Nice shirt. Help yourself.
I thought you'd fallen in.
That would be a quality
problem. How's your hand?
It's all right.
I don't know any approved torture,
But in your case, that is personal.
What's going on?
God!
You all right?
You remember those,
The property flips we used to do
back in London?
I only broke in and sold
the wrong man's miami mansion.
But it turns out,
he was connected.
Answer the question.
What are you dragging me into?
I don't know.
I swear to god, cal,
I do not know.
Well, come on, then.
Thank you.
Oh, shut up.
So the video
Even though you didn't make it,
does speak to your needs?
And which is partly why
you took false credit.
And you say they deserve to die,
but you're clearly scared to name them.
Take Jared back
to the conference room.
I need to talk to Stacey.
We're done.
- Where's Lightman?
- He's not in his office.
We're calling him, but it's going
straight to voicemail.
Where could he be?
That's not like him.
Could you keep trying?
Good of you to come.
I warn you, I'm not cheap.
Terry's life cover it?
Barely.
We have a deal, then.
I like to think of all of my people
as family,
but one of these three has been
informing on me to the government.
You're going
to tell me for certain
Which one is the rat.
So you can kill the man?
Three minutes.
Right, then.
All right, boys?
Well, you're right.
There is a liar in the room.
Liar's you.
What are you doing?
Now's not the time
to play the comedian.
Get up.
Give him one more chance.
He won't let you down.
None of these men is an informer.
But you already knew that.
Good.
Told you he was the best.
What I want to know is when
you told him that,
Was it last night?
- Last week, last month?
- Quiet, ladies.
Nice one.
Stacey, are you and Jasmine friends?
The exact same look
she showed for jasmine in class.
Contempt.
She's mean to me.
In P.E.,
In the locker room.
But she's not the only one.
I hate P.E.
Did you tell your teacher?
He knows.
I wish I didn't have
to ask you this,
but do you ever wish Jasmine
or any of the other kids
who are mean to you, harm?
Harm?
Like,
you think I made that video,
that it was,
I may have thought
about revenge but,
I don't want them to die.
She's telling the truth.
She doesn't want to harm anyone.
Please don't tell jasmine
I told on her.
Sweetie.
Maybe she is the one
who made the video.
All this is is her fantasy
of revenge.
Who's the P.E. Teacher?
- Why?
- It's not you, is it?
But I would never turn a blind eye
to bullying if I saw it.
Did you know that these kids
were picking on stacey?
I could see
she wasn't the most popular.
Is jasmine popular?
Yeah. I'd say so.
Very, actually.
It's the popular ones who think
they can get away with murder.
Spoken like a true scientist.
Trust me, I just know.
We should get jasmine in there now.
So you two go back a ways?
I'm sure Terry's
told you all about it.
Property scams.
You picked out the easy marks.
Terry took them for
everything they had.
If that's how Terry remembers it.
I remember you with the business
of picking out the right mark.
The absolute bloody
business, I swear.
Terry tells me
that you owe him your life.
Tell me about that.
I thought it was water
under the bridge.
Even so,
While we're waiting.
What's the faster say we were,
west ham supporters
at millwall game?
He saved you from soccer hooligans.
Manner of speaking.
Or were you two the hooligans?
Not guilty, your honor.
You see that look?
That look says that your time
on this planet is running out.
Put a cork in it, Cal.
That's enough.
See, it's always the same,
the criminal mind.
Never sees the end of the road.
Forever hoping,
often actually believing,
that there will be just
one more corner to turn.
Not his fault.
He's not the only one. I'm
basically wired the same way.
- They're on their way. 5 minutes out.
- Who?
The man that you're going to meet with.
See if he's on the level or not
Before I do business with him.
Call him back.
Cancel it.
- Excuse me?
- What?
Look out the window.
There's an FBI tail out there.
They've been on Terry like
a cheap suit since he landed.
- Don't play games, professor.
- You can thank me later.
Show me.
See it?
The blue one?
Not the blue one, the other one.
That one over from it, the red one.
The red station wagon.
Might as well have had
the blue light flashing on top.
Call him back. I'll meet
to the warehouse.
Get up.
A whole lot of people think that
it's just the victims of bullies
Who get hurt.
But the bullies
Pay a price, too.
- You know, maybe not physically but,
- We were just joking around at first.
About what?
Stacey's weight?
That, and...
I can't explain.
It got out of control.
I'm so sorry.
Are you, though?
It wasn't just me.
There are others.
If that video means what
I think it means,
That it's all coming to an end,
The pain, her pain, mine?
I wish it would.
I hate myself
for what I did to stacey.
But I couldn't stop. He didn't
want us to.
He meaning you.
And you still mean to tell me
you had no idea this was going on?
I can't be everywhere all the time.
Ducks the question
while grabbing for an excuse.
Classic deflection.
If Stacey made
that video, it's because of me.
- Where's Stacey?
- She went to the bathroom.
- How long ago?
- Few minutes.
More like 10, I think.
Come on.
Open up now, please.
- I can't find a pulse.
- Oh, my god.
I missed it. It wasn't
homicidal intent. I misread the sadness.
- It was suicidal intent.
- I need an ambulance.
Move it, move it.
Let's go, let's leave.
Three cars behind.
- The parents have been contacted.
- It's been taken care of.
Tell me she's going to be OK.
She's gonna be OK.
Stay here.
Talk amongst yourselves.
Was it really an FBI tail?
- And you just ditched them?
- Yes, to earn his trust.
That worked like a charm,
we got blindfolds and locked doors.
Are we even yet,
Terry?
Are we ever gonna be even
in your eyes?
You think that's what this is about?
It's about who's even with who.
That's a bit rich
coming from you, mate.
Mate,
I did 3 years in prison
saving your ass.
So what do I gotta do?
I gotta die to save yours, have I?
You should've come to me
in the 1st place
have been honest with me and said,
"Cal, I'm in a bit of bother,
could use some help
from a friend I can count on."
- You'd have done what?
- I'd have done something!
Anything's better than this!
I haven't heard from you
in over 20 years,
over twenty years.
What was that?
Let's just face it?
You wanted the past dead
and me along with it.
Apology accepted, by the way.
Where is Lightman?
My financial advisor, Harry Sloane.
How do you do?
I see you two
already know each other.
Any friend of Terry
is a friend of mine.
Pleasantries out of the way. Let's
get down to the heart of the matter.
The merchandise, Mr. Jones?
You say it is the best ever,
flawless, in fact.
I gave you my word,
man to man.
See, that's why I'm here.
Yes or no questions,
they only go so far.
So,
how flawless
is the merchandise?
The currency
is perfect.
There's a flicker of doubt there,
but might just be
about the deal in general.
Perfect counterfeit currency.
That's an oxymoron
if ever I heard one.
- What is this sideshow?
- He's telling the truth, though,
When he says that
the counterfeit's perfect.
He truly, he does believe that.
But then again, he's just...
What his name
down at the U.N.,
all over again, right?
Excuse me?
That guy,
he truly did believe
all that WMD nonsense.
Cleverly,
they sent him off down to the U.N.
To sell it.
- The rest is history.
- No one sent me here.
The currency...
is flawless.
I mean, I'm sorry.
- But... it's not good enough.
- Who is this ass?
Screw him, let's go.
We're not done yet.
No, you swore to me
that you would...
Is he telling the truth,
Dr. Lightman?
Yes or no?
Yes! He believes that he is, yes.
Good.
So do we have a deal or not?
Is this the best you've got,
Dr. Lightman?
Because so far, I'm under whelmed.
Or is there more?
Will you put me
in front of the actual counterfeit
with the bank notes in his hands,
and I'll know just how good
his product is.
Just you.
Terry can stay here.
Terry's with me.
It's not negotiable.
- No, I'll be all right.
- Don't be dumb.
You need to be thinking
about yourself.
Now you tell me.
It's not negotiable.
Come on!
Say nothing, Terry, not a word.
This is him?
- That's your counterfeiter?
- The best there is.
50,000 euros, right there.
Bloody hell!
- How many containers you got?
- That is not your concern.
Put it back.
- Name?
- He doesn't need to know that.
I gotta establish a baseline here.
Easy answers to easy questions.
Then I can get to bigger questions.
Otto.
Hammil.
Otto...
What's your real last name?
Frankel.
- How many kids you got?
- None.
- Have you been married?
- I'm not.
- Where are you from?
- Chicago.
Get on with it, please, will you?
These notes are counterfeit, right?
Yes.
How good are they?
We already tested a modest amount
without detection.
Well, Dr. Lightman.
What?
He hasn't answered my question yet.
Easy, fellas.
It's taken care of.
He was right.
FBI.
I don't think I can do this.
I'll be right here the whole time.
Don't worry.
Just take your time, Stacey.
You knew what they were doing to me,
Mr. Fitzgerald.
You didn't just ignore it.
You started it all.
- Stacey...
- You kept telling me
I was fat
and lazy in front of them.
- That's not true.
- Your hands and eyes say otherwise.
So do I.
I'm so sorry, Stacey.
You know,
I had a coach like you once
who had it in
for one of the kids on the team.
Constant verbal abuse
disguised as authority.
Eddie Johnston.
And nothing that Eddie ever did
was ever good enough.
- You're out of line.
- And the example
that that coach
set for the rest of us,
just like you did for Jasmine
and her buddies,
we thought it gave us the license
to make Eddie an outcast.
I never touched a hair on her head.
Right,
because we did it for you.
I wanted you
to have to live the rest of your life
knowing that what you did to me
made me...
You knew what this was really about
all the time.
I know,
because I sent you a video, too.
Which you neglected to mention,
Mr. Fitzgerald.
Making you guilty
of obstruction of justice.
And if this keeps you
away from kids forever,
I'll take it.
Right, Stacey?
Wait a minute.
One kid has a psychological breakdown,
an illness,
and I'm to blame?
- We need to talk...
- I don't...
Thank you.
There's a whitening of the skin
around the eyes,
which is a dead give away
for the kind of fear
that we try to hide when we lie.
And a slight rotation
of the right arm,
which is what we call in the trade
a shrug fragment,
which means he's got zero
confidence in what he just said.
The eyes...
of a cheat
who thinks he has all the cards,
but who knows
I'm telling the truth.
He's lying.
The son of a bitch has been playing us
the whole time.
Easy! I didn't say...
- You really think we're that dumb?
- Easy! I didn't say!
FBI! Nobody move!
Anybody else?
Down on your knees!
Now!
Move!
How do you do that?
Blanks.
Blanks?
No, I mean,
with your eyes.
How do you do that?
It's... just practice.
What's going on?
Put your hands behind your back.
I swear,
I'm getting too old for this,
Terry, I really am.
FBI have been onto you and McClellan
for a while now.
Special agent Hutton.
- Nice to meet you.
- You, too.
Superior work, Agt. Reynolds.
Likewise, my friend.
How's that for having your back?
That's just like a real FBI agent.
- Thanks a lot, Cal.
- What?
When'd you first realize
I was undercover?
Back at the poker table,
you were angry
and fearful,
but on my behalf.
Really?
Come on, let's go.
Hold on a second.
I'll tell you what.
Terry walks for his part in this.
- What?
- And then we're evens.
You know I couldn't have done this
without him.
He goes from here to the airport,
and he doesn't come back, ever.
You know,
you're one lucky son of a bitch.
Can I borrow him for a minute?
Just personal stuff.
Just make it...
quick.
I knew you were up to something
the moment you walked into my office.
Then I had to sit there
and watch you play me like...
one of those yuppies back in London.
McClellan had me
by the short and curlies!
Get out!
My best mate!
- What do you think I wanted to do it?
- You were in on this from the start!
They knew who I was before
I even sat down at that poker table.
What was that?
That was just some little test run.
What do you call this?
A couple of broken fingers
for a slice of that pie?
Do me a favor.
And you can stop treating me
like a bloody moron now!
Maybe I just came
to resent you, Cal.
Hate me, more like.
Years will do that, Terry.
You saw all the way through it.
You saw right through it
from the start.
Still helped me, though, didn't you?
You know why?
Because you always have been
and you always will be
my best mate.
Don't count on it.
I'll tell you what.
My debt is now paid,
in full!
No, wait a second, wait a second.
You owe me now.
I saved your bacon
and I covered your ass with the FBI!
I'm a very lucky man.
All luck is earned... in the end.
Go, then.
Off you go.
Don't you dare look back.
Have a seat.
- Why?
- This is an intervention.
What?
All right, so I had, you know,
a few drinks with a mate.
- More than a few, actually.
- This isn't about drinking.
Then if it's about poker,
I won a hundred grand.
Hundred grand?
105, actually.
It's not about gambling, either.
- What is it about, then?
- It's about you trusting us.
You were in trouble,
and you never came to us.
- Wait a minute...
- No, you wait!
We're a team.
And you risked your life
without letting us help you.
I wouldn't be here at all
if it wasn't for Terry Marsh.
Fine. So where does that leave us?
That leaves...
you all fired.
You gotta be kidding!
I didn't wanna do this intervention.
Just you, then.
Just you are fired,
for having no spine.
- I don't believe this.
- Good.
'cause I'm lying.
What, you didn't spot that?
Did your emotions get in the way?
You should really work on that.
This has been terrific.
Really fantastic.
Quite the intervention.
We should do this again
soon, very soon.
The intervention was my idea.
My mom died when I was young,
and my dad was long gone by then.
Terry and his family, they took me in
even though there was no room
and even less money. And one day, Terry
and I got into a little bit of trouble
with the police.
Not your concern, but...
they were on their way.
No way we could get out of it
without one of us
acting as decoy for the other.
- So Terry took the fall for you?
- Yeah, he did.
He said,
you're supposed to use
that brain of yours for something,
not be dragged down into the muck
by stupid bastards like me.
- He was right.
- Yeah, he was.
It cost him 3 years of his life.
So anyone who wants to compete
for my loyalty with Terry Marsh,
not really in a fair fight.
Good night, love.