Nana! Nana!
Someone, please!
My family is still inside!
Nana!
My daughter's still in there
with my mother-in-law! Please!
We'll find her.
You need to stay with your family.
Nana, please wake up!
Nana!
... OK. It's OK.
Are you all right?
It's okay, I got you.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
- Get my Nana!
- It's too dangerous. Come on.
I have to get my Nana!
- You can't help her now.
- Let go of me!
Dr. Lightman.
Hey.
Bernie Madoff.
That's anxiety and regret.
- Tell that to the Science Times, all right?
- Okay.
You've got messages from Wax
at the SEC, Kob at Treasury
and the FBI wants to schedule
another lecture. Also...
No downturn in the lie business.
Good morning.
You should put that down.
What, you don't like
women in masks anymore?
No, it's 'cause it's one of a kind.
Could you... yeah,
could you put that down?
Never mind.
I do so like it when
you get flustered.
It's rare, but highly enjoyable.
Why are you here?
You have such a
gift for small talk.
Really, you should've just gone
into the hospitality businesses.
Opened yourself up a little
bed and breakfast somewhere.
- Ria Torres.
- Zoe Landau.
- Hi.
- She's Assistant...
Assistant U.S. Attorney.
You always did like them so young.
Excuse me?
His proteges...
they're usually young.
It's easier for him to try to...
mold in his image.
Is there a reason you're here?
I have a case. I need your help.
You want to hire me?
Well, I don't want to remarry you.
What, do you have problem
working for your ex-wife?
My daughter is in a hospital
bed with second-degree burns.
My wife's mother is dead.
My house is gone.
This case is a top priority
for us, Mr. Ambrose.
So why hasn't anything been done?
Why isn't that son
of a bitch in jail?
You know that he did this.
Frank, she's asking for you.
I want Garcia behind bars.
He thinks you know
who started the fire?
Well, I have a witness
who saw Jack Garcia
running from the Ambrose house
right after the fire started.
That TV reporter?
Yeah.
He and Ambrose were
friends in high school,
but they had a falling out.
So you have a witness
that can put Jack Garcia
at the scene of the crime?
What's the problem?
The witness has a
slight credibility issue.
Who's the witness?
My mommy left me outside.
She went back in the house
to look for Maggie and Nana.
That's when I saw Mr. Garcia.
Hey, AJ, you ever tell a lie?
It's all right, honey.
That's all right,
we all tell stories.
But, today, I need you
to tell me the truth.
I am telling the truth.
I saw Mr. Garcia.
He ran out of the cellar.
You know the story of "The
Little Boy Who Cried Wolf"?
He said the wolf was
there when it wasn't.
So no one helped him
when the wolf really came.
That's right.
He told a lie.
And the wolf ate him.
If you don't tell the truth, the wolf's
going to come back and he's going to eat you.
What is this? What...
- Did you see Mr. Garcia?
- I saw him running away.
- I want you to tell me the truth now.
- I am telling you the truth.
The wolf's going to come back here
- and he's going to eat you up.
- You're scaring him.
- I saw him.
- I need you to tell me the truth.
He killed my Nana.
You leave my son alone.
Okay.
You used to be so
good with children.
We don't want an innocent man
going to prison for 20 years.
AJ was showing no
signs of deception,
so I raised the stakes a bit.
And he still wasn't anxious.
Now I think he tells
the truth, actually.
Good. Let's talk to Jack Garcia.
My place or yours?
Mine. I want Foster to evaluate AJ.
Ah, yes, Gillian.
What was that?
I didn't say anything.
What?
Let's talk to the accused,
and get you some medication.
Thanks to my college buddy,
Army Lieutenant David Kanuth,
I know how hard it is for our
wounded veterans to return home.
I'm Jack Garcia, and
this is what I know
"This is What I Know."
That really put you
on the map, right?
Selling the misery
of your old friends.
That's kind of what you do.
You're saying I burned
down a man's house,
so I could report on it?
Well, aren't you in the running
for some big new cable show?
I mean, the story of an
old friend losing everything
could help you along nicely.
You do not want to be interrogated
by this man, trust me.
It's kind of fun when you're
not on the other end, though.
I told you, we drifted apart.
I have no problem
with Frank Ambrose.
Never have.
All right, so, bad reporter,
good liar.
Not a great one.
When he talks about Ambrose,
this is what we get.
Contempt.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm familiar with that one.
I think we should probe
the relationship between Ambrose
and Garcia... see what
we can come up with.
Sounds like fun.
Cal?
What?
Zoe.
Gillian.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
She's calling.
Cal?
No.
What no?
You know what.
We... We... We have never
worked for her before.
We are not starting now.
It's an interesting case.
No... there are plenty
of interesting cases.
Do you not remember what
it was like after she left?
You wore the same shirt to the
office every day for a month.
I still do.
You saw the head tilt.
She's flirting with you.
No, that's ridiculous.
- She does this to you every time.
- No.
She is single again, Cal.
No, no, she's been
with Roger for what?
For the best part
of a year now, right?
Is she still? Did you ask her?
I don't know, look,
I'm taking the case.
I'll be fine.
- Cal...
- I'm in complete control of myself...
which is more than
I can say for you,
following me into the men's room.
The women's room, Cal.
The women's room.
Why don't you tell us
what really happened
between you and Frank Ambrose.
I told you nothing happened.
We haven't been friends in years.
Why not?
You grow older, things change.
Now, I, um...
Now we have nothing in common.
- Why do you feel contempt for him then?
- I never said that I don't.
You're going to have to
learn to lie better than that
if you want a real career
in front of the camera.
Uh, look...
Frank called me
about six months ago.
He'd just been laid off,
seemed desperate, so I asked him
if there's anything I could do.
That's one of my
favorites, that one.
I mean, it's amazing how
many times people say that
and they don't mean it, right?
Yeah, well, he asked me for money
and I gave it to him, okay?
You lent a guy money that
you hadn't talked to in years?
Yeah, we shared a past.
That meant something to me.
Apparently not to him.
I called Frank a month
ago... see how he was doing,
and that ungrateful son of a bitch
acted like I was squeezing
him for the money he owed me.
And now his boy is accusing
me of burning down his house.
You're damn right I feel contempt.
He sounded convincing.
Yeah, and he looked it.
You said that about
the Ambrose boy.
I mean, they both can't
be telling the truth.
What, are you losing your touch?
I'll evaluate the boy.
He may not be able to tell the
difference between fantasy and reality.
AJ may be imagining what he saw.
If he believes in his fantasy,
it could appear that
he's telling the truth.
I'm going to work on something
a little bit more tangible.
I'm going to get
the FBI to do checks
on Garcia and Ambrose.
But feel free to talk to the boy.
Take him to the zoo, if you like.
That's Roger. I should
probably take this.
How's it going between
you two... is it good?
Yeah, it's great.
Hey.
Oh, I love you, too.
I miss you.
- Well, that was a lie.
- What?
Oh, yeah. Well,
you know, she's been
with Roger for a long time,
and if there was something serious,
- she would have told me,
right?  - Uh-huh, uh-huh.
- Hey, I found out there are more printer...
- Yeah, could you call
the Ambrose family... see if they
can bring their kid by this afternoon?
Scheduling meetings... fantastic.
- Yeah.
- Hey, where you going?
I'm going to go help Torres
get started on the
Southeast drive-by shooting.
You know, who better than me to get
inside the world of gangsta rappers.
Sweet place.
For a guy who raps about
being true to the 'hood,
Caden doesn't exactly put
his money where his mouth is.
Detective Riley.
Dr. Foster, Ms. Torres,
thanks for coming.
Is that the, uh...
kid who was murdered?
Yeah. Dante Edwards.
Three nights ago,
he was leaving a club
when he took two bullets
to the chest in a drive-by.
You think Caden shot him?
Caden was seen arguing with Dante
at a party last week.
Dante is part of
Little Sid's entourage.
He's a rival rapper.
He and Caden have a big feud.
Caden's a bad man.
He raps about how he's
killed half a dozen men.
We nail him for this,
we can put him behind
bars where he belongs.
That's what I go for right now.
Now, that looks good.
On to the next.
You got a moment to
speak to Detective Riley?
I don't talk to cops, man.
My manager will
show you to the door.
Look, I'm sorry. My
cousin's not a snitch.
You know what would
happen to album sales
if people knew you all were here?
Listen, Davis, your cousin
doesn't want to cooperate,
we'll bring him in.
I can dig it.
Everybody, find another
room... the party's over.
Now.
What?
Did you know Dante Edwards?
Wow.
That's a lot of regret
- for a killer.
- Look, I didn't kill him.
You got a lot of loyal
folks in your entourage.
Maybe you got one of them to do it.
Let me tell you something.
Look, me and my cousin
grew up with Dante.
He lived three doors down from
us in the Carollsburg projects.
- And you're coming up in here...
- Cade, Cade, Cade...
No, no, no. Let me explain some
why I'm upset right now.
The world should know
this is unacceptable to me.
The world should know this,
B, and you're coming up in here
and accusing me
of killing somebody
that I grew up with?
Are we finished yet?
I haven't heard an alibi.
My cousin and I were here,
watching the Carver-Nova game.
Caden seemed to be
telling the truth.
Yeah... and his
sadness was for real.
You're saying you believe the guy?
The rivalry with Little
Sid's crew, the argument,
both point to Caden.
Okay, but why would a killer
show remorse for his victim?
Okay...
AJ, what about this one?
That's Santa Claus.
Yeah, it is.
Tell me about Santa.
He has a sleigh and reindeer.
He brings me presents.
Shh.
Quiet.
Have you ever seen Santa?
No.
I always fall asleep.
But I think I heard him
on the roof once.
Shh. I told you. Quiet, now.
Who are you talking to?
That's Penelope.
Quiet. I told you, be quiet.
You did that.
- Eh?
- You did that.
Penelope did that.
You're making that up.
Now, that's not fair.
She thinks you're cool.
There's no one there.
She told me that she thought
that you were super cool.
You're weird.
Your imaginary friend Penelope?
Yeah, it's the only girl
I know tells me the truth.
Hey.
What? Oh, sorry.
So...
it's clear AJ can
tell the difference
between reality and fantasy, right?
Yes, but that was your fantasy.
He's a little fuzzier
when it comes to his own,
I mean, he's still at the age
where he thinks Santa's real.
So you think he imagined Garcia
running away from the fire?
Yeah, I think so.
But I'll still get
him to draw some more.
It's a more direct
line to his unconscious.
I'm not sure we'll need it.
We still have a
receptionist here, don't we?
Jack Garcia wasn't the only person
that Frank Ambrose owed money to.
The guy's under a mountain
of debt... credit cards,
student loans, you name
it. Take a look at this.
Homeowner's insurance.
Housing prices have
dropped, but his home
was insured at the value it
had before the market collapsed.
His house was worth more to him
in ashes than it was standing.
You think I'd burn
down my own house?
I lost everything in that fire.
You made a lot of money
when the house went down.
That doesn't make me an arsonist.
Jack Garcia told us
how desperate you were.
Jack Garcia is the
one who did this.
He's a user.
He lives off the suffering
of everybody else.
Now, you believe that, don't you?
Come on! My son saw him.
What is the matter with you people?
So, how long are you stuck here?
My doctor said I could go
home at the end of the week.
It's not so bad.
It's been kind of cool here.
Really?
All my friends came by.
And it's nice having
my family around.
My dad hasn't left.
Oh, yeah? What about your mom?
Yeah, she's been here, too.
Do you believe Mr. Ambrose?
Yeah. Most of what he said.
But I'm interested in
what the daughter told you.
The family would've
been through a lot
and the kid would've
seen the worst of it.
What have you got?
A lot of anger from Maggie.
Towards mom.
Mom?
What are you doing?
Looking at Mum.
How did you know Mr. Garcia?
He's friends with my daddy.
She's holding her breath.
Anxiety.
I think I know why
Maggie's so angry.
That's great, AJ, okay.
Now, can you draw for me
what you saw the night of the fire?
I'm not done. That's all right.
I don't need to talk to AJ.
Uh, what was your relationship
with the man that
your son's accused?
Excuse me?
Were you having an
affair with Jack Garcia?
How dare you accuse me of having
an affair in front of my son!
Yeah. You're avoiding the question.
Are you having an
affair with Jack Garcia?
I'm getting my son and I'm going.
That's fine, but we'll
be back with a subpoena.
I suppose we could always
talk to your husband
and find out what
he knows about it.
Nine months ago, I was out shopping
and Jack walked up
to me in the store.
He had so much confidence.
Frank had lost his job.
We were really struggling.
We had stopped having
sex altogether by then.
So you had an affair?
Every minute with Jack was a chance
to be with somebody who
didn't know me or my problems.
I thought about leaving my husband,
but the children and I
are all that he has left,
and so I broke it off with Jack.
How did he take it?
He understood.
Look, this has nothing
to do with the fire.
It's easier to
believe that, isn't it?
I don't know what AJ saw,
but I know Jack Garcia
and he would never do
something like this to us.
Because of our daughter.
And sex was never the problem.
Well, you wanted to know
why I never cheated on you.
What about you?
You would've known.
Besides, I wanted to kill you.
I never wanted to hurt you.
I think that's what we
should focus on here.
Affairs make for
angry spouses, right?
What could possibly make me want
to burn down the Ambroses' house?
Your husband was having an
affair with Cheryl Ambrose.
Oh, she knew already.
He told me two weeks ago.
If you'd already told your wife,
then why didn't you tell us?
I wanted to, but she...
I told him not to.
It's not something I
wanted to see in the papers.
Look, the idea that my wife
would do this is absurd.
Is it?
She's still angry.
Not at Cheryl Ambrose.
I knew when Jack started
in front of the
camera, it would be...
different.
The Jack Garcia you see on
TV is not the man I married.
But marriage is about
figuring out how to make it
through when things change.
- She was lying to herself.
- So, that's it?
That's it, then? People just
change and then they move on?
Are you saying that I'm
the one that changed?
You left me.
You left.
Yeah, I left because of you.
Oh, it's my fault now?
No, I'm saying you
should take a hard look
at what happened before
you start blaming me.
Hey, I saw what happened!
I saw what was happening!
You know, I could see the doubt.
I could see the doubt
when you were standing
on the bloody altar!
Everyone has doubts, Cal! Everyone!
At the altar, with their
friends, in the maternity ward,
staring at the very best thing
that's ever happened to them,
but that doesn't mean it's
the only thing that they feel.
But you, you just...
you saw every doubt, every fear.
By the end, that was
all you could see.
You couldn't let go of anything.
I was trying to be honest.
Yes... I know. I know.
But I can tell you, sweetheart,
there really is such a thing
as too much honesty in a marriage.
So, what do you want?
You'd rather be with someone
- who doesn't really know you, then?
- How about someone
who doesn't need to
know everything about me?
Who I can surprise on his birthday.
Who doesn't need to point out
every time I'm even remotely
attracted to another man.
Someone with his head up his ass?
Someone who doesn't
study my eyebrows
when I'm standing in a thong.
Why are you here, then?
Why did you hire me, eh?
It's a tough case.
Doing my thing right now.
Living it up, baby,
that's how we do it,
you know?
That Caden?
Yeah. And Little Sid and his crew
at an album release
party last year.
The victim, Dante Edwards,
is behind him on the right.
They come up to me
like, "Little Sid,
please take me away
from this paper wrapper!"
I'm about to put a gun
in your face right now.
What's up, man?
Check out the fake anger.
If his anger were real, his
upper eyelids would be raised
and his lips would be narrower.
The rivalry's fake?
That feud is big business.
Sold a lot of albums last year.
So then why would Caden
or anyone else in his
crew want to kill Dante?
I'm thinking that the
murderer's not in Caden's crew.
Okay.
Let's take a look at our victim.
All right.
Which group does
Dante look like, the men on
the left or the men on the right?
Um...
The men on the left?
Oh, you have a sixth sense.
By that, I mean you see gay people.
You think Dante's gay?
Yeah, and so do you.
All the men on the left are gay.
A new study in
the Journal of
Experimental Psychology
showed that most people
can identify gay men
by face alone.
It has to do with the pattern
of muscle tension in the face.
And...
check out Little
Sid's newest album.
# It's my guitar on target #
# Like Dirty Harry, I'm
gonna make your day #
# I'm gonna take your ass out,
'cause your ass is gay... #
Oh.
Little Sid is one big homophobe.
If he found out one of
his entourage was gay,
no telling what he would've done.
We're looking at the wrong rapper.
All right, take a look at these.
More drawings?
Yeah.
So what do they mean?
Uh, well, here, the arsonist
has a tail,
and there, he's, uh,
he's breathing fire.
So they're becoming more....
More elaborate.
Exactly.
If it were a true memory,
he'd stick to what he remembers.
But AJ's embellishing his story.
Wait,
so he did see Jack
Garcia or he didn't?
Which one is it?
Well, AJ believes his story is true
the same way he
believes in Santa Claus.
Somebody he trusts
told him it was true.
It's an implanted memory.
Jack Garcia didn't start that fire.
We need to go talk
to AJ's parents again.
One of them may be using
their son to frame that man.
Maybe you didn't leave Jack Garcia.
Maybe he left you.
- What?
- You hated him
for taking away what
little joy you had,
didn't you? You hated him,
you hated your life, so
you set fire to your house,
and you told your son
to say it was Jack.
You think that I'd
burn down my own house?
That fire killed my mother.
People have done crazier
things at the end of an affair.
Cheryl was having
an affair with Jack?
You had two strong
motives, Mr. Ambrose.
Make a bundle of money on the house
and get back at the
man who stole your wife.
You knew she was
miserable in your marriage.
You had nothing to lose.
I had no idea that she
was having an affair.
I almost left my family for Jack.
Why would I want him in jail?
I had nothing
to do with this.
I would never put my
family at risk like that.
It wasn't Cheryl.
No.
Emotion she was
showing was genuine.
She's still fond of Garcia.
That's a shame.
But it'll help me make
the case against Frank.
What?
He had the motive,
the means and plenty of opportunity
to implant the memory in his son.
No, he was truly surprised.
He... well, hang on.
Cheryl was having
an affair with Jack?
See, he had no idea.
If he was surprised,
it was because we
knew about the affair.
Nah, you're wrong.
Oh, well, there's something
you're always certain about.
You don't see what I see.
You know, you... you really
used to be so charming
back before you became God.
You really don't care
what we think about
this case, do you?
- I didn't say that.
- Yeah, you did.
- No, I didn't. I didn't.
- Yeah. You did.
Something's off.
You split up with Roger?
Roger and I are fine.
I don't believe you, Zoe.
Fine.
You want to know the truth?
Yep.
Roger proposed to me.
He wants to marry me, all right?
You just got to telling
him about it now?
I'll got to get back to the office.
Have a wonderful
dinner, sweetheart.
Oh, yeah.
It's gonna be a blast.
What up?
Whoa! Speaking of fine ladies...
Damn!
What do we have here?
Easy, big guy. She's with me.
Such a shame.
'Cause I don't talk
to the po-po, baby.
Guess that means you
got nothing to say
about Dante Edwards' murder?
I guess not.
Ooh, now there's some real anger.
You must have been pretty angry
when you found out
Dante was gay, huh?
Dante was a smart dude, all right?
He got the business.
He knew to keep it on the DL.
Besides, I always knew which way
- he was swinging.
- Huh.
No disgust.
But your music's
full of hate for gays.
Look, I got records to sell.
So if I got to hate,
yeah, I'm gonna hate.
But I ain't have no problem
with Dante doing
his Broke back thing.
Oh, I see.
You're not homophobic,
you're just an ass.
Look, little po-po lady,
you don't know me, all right?
And you don't know
nothing about my business.
Maybe not, but I do
read people pretty well,
and you can't seem to say
Dante's name without showing anger.
Look, I found this
kid on the street.
I make him the hottest
mixer in the game,
and he go and run off with Caden?
So you had a grudge.
Hell, yeah, I had a grudge.
But that's no need
for gunplay, all right?
I'm a hustler, man, a entertainer.
I'm not no murderer.
Those guns are part of my "image".
Just for show.
Okay.
Any idea why Dante left?
I offered the boy a raise,
a new crib, but see, he
didn't want none of that.
So when you two
guys figure that out,
then we'll have
something to talk about.
Uh... uh.
Hey, Dad.
Hey. What?
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Yeah.
I hate this picture.
Let me see.
Oh, no, I like that one.
Why?
You and mom spent
the whole day arguing about
your research trip to New Guinea.
Yeah. We were happy then.
Well, look at the
smiles, they're real.
Well, guess it's good mom wasn't
the only one that was delusional.
Thank you.
She's not wearing
the ring, you know.
Eh?
She's not wearing the ring.
Why?
Come on, why do you think?
I mean, she's not sure about Roger.
She still thinks
she's in love with you.
What?
I mean, I see what's
going on with you two.
I always do.
I always have.
That's true enough.
Who are you calling?
Your mum.
Ugh! Get out of here!
We've got nothing else
to say to you people.
We're not here for you.
Hi, Maggie.
How are you feeling? You all right?
Not so good, eh?
How long have you known
about your mum and Mr. Garcia?
Oh, my God.
- She's a child.
- Oh, she already knows.
You've known for quite
some time, haven't you?
I'm tired, daddy.
Please, leave her alone.
Sorry, we can't do
that, Mrs. Ambrose.
Did you see them together, love?
Was that what happened?
It was, wasn't it?
Your dad didn't
know, but you did, eh?
Yeah?
Did you hear your parents fighting?
Must have been scary.
You afraid
Mr. Garcia was going
to break up your family.
I heard her.
I heard my mom.
She was on the phone.
She was talking to Mr. Garcia.
And...
she told him... she loved him.
And that she was thinking about
running away with him.
Oh, Maggie.
I thought if Mr. Garcia
got blamed for the fire,
they'd take him away...
... and we'd stay a family.
Baby, I wasn't.
I wasn't ever going to leave you.
I was just confused.
You weren't supposed to
know about any of this.
I was never going to leave you.
You burned down the
house to save your family,
didn't you?
You set the fire and...
and told you brother it
was Mr. Garcia, right?
I told
AJ to say it was Mr. Garcia.
I told him over and over
until he believed it.
But that fire,
it killed Nana.
I didn't start the fire.
It's okay. It's okay, sweetheart.
- I swear, I didn't.
- I know.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- Shh.
We love you so much.
It's okay.
Mommy...
We're all together now.
Nobody's going anywhere, okay?
We tell ourselves
we can protect them,
try to shield them.
But in the end,
they see everything.
- This is News 7 at 11:00.
- Oh, my God.
Well, the FBI's just
been called into this,
but from what we can tell,
the blaze started this morning.
And yes, we think it's
maybe the same person
who burned down the Ambrose
house earlier this week.
The FBI is currently
conducting our investigation.
FBI thinks we're looking
at a serial arsonist.
Are we sure the two
fires are connected?
Positive.
Same chemical accelerant,
same point of origin.
And serial arsonists don't
stop, they just get bolder.
Yeah, well, this one was
set in broad daylight.
That's bolder.
Yeah, we've got to find this guy.
Mr. and Mrs. Craig?
This is AUSA
Zoe Landau.
She's running the investigation.
Can you tell us what happened?
I was on my way to work
when I got the call. I...
I came home right away.
Aaron was already here.
I, uh, just gotten back from a jog.
The back of the house
was all up in flames.
I tried to save what I could.
- So, you lost everything?
- Yeah.
You can't imagine
how horrible we feel.
No, I can't imagine.
We need to talk to you.
Caden's not going to
talk to the cops again.
Well, that's why I
left them outside.
I just need five minutes.
Why didn't you tell us
Dante was coming to work for you?
How about, it's none
of your damn business?
Look, last time I was here,
when I was asking you about Dante,
I expected...
anger, hate.
But all I saw was sadness.
And then I found out Dante was gay.
Something you knew all along?
Yeah, I thought so.
I think I know why
he left Little Sid
to come work for you.
- Okay, lady, you're out of line.
- Am I?
Caden, what exactly was your
relationship with Dante Edwards?
That's enough, all right?
Why were you guys arguing at
the club the night he was killed?
You're not just gonna... like this.
Was it 'cause he was
threatening to come out?
'Cause he was threatening
to take you with him?
- Okay, you know what?
- Is that why you killed him?
You don't know what
you're talking about.
I had nothing to do
with Dante's death.
You didn't, did you?
You really did care for him, huh?
You loved him.
You know they buried him today?
And I couldn't even
go to the funeral.
Whoa...
...those are some
pretty strong feelings.
Contempt.
Disgust.
Is that true, B?
Is that how you felt about us?
Well...
I told you before.
I thought the
relationship was unwise.
Where you were the night
of Dante Edwards' murder?
I was here watching the
game, like I told you before.
That's a lie.
Cay, would you tell her?
Cay, would you tell this woman?
What you want me to tell her?
Cay...
That you were here with me?
'Cause you wasn't.
Where were you, B?
It was only a matter...
Where the hell were you, B?!
... before someone outed you two.
We built this together...
me and you.
I was protecting us.
Protecting us?
What? You forgot?
Cuz, come on, man.
What it was like
coming from nothing?
This house, the cars.
Caden...
You don't get any of this
if they know the truth about you.
I would've had Dante.
He would still be alive.
I have no idea who
Frank Ambrose is.
Why would I burn down his house?
I don't know. Maybe
you like starting fires.
Look, you have the wrong guy.
I didn't burn down anything.
What? You certainly
got a kick out of seeing
your house in ashes.
You can't imagine
how horrible we feel.
You could barely contain yourself.
Laurel and I... our
marriage is over.
We wanted to split up
for months, but we were
stuck in that house.
You couldn't sell it?
The value of the house had tanked.
We couldn't afford to sell it,
but now, with the insurance payout,
we can both go our separate ways.
Frankly, it's a relief.
Do you believe him?
Yeah, but I got a question for you.
Is your wife cheating on you?
Well, uh, we both had our
share of indiscretions.
That's a yes, then?
Cal?
Who's your favorite TV reporter?
Hmm?
Is this one?
Yes, Jim, they do think
that this fire was started
by the same serial
arsonist, and the FBI...
Mr. Garcia?
- ... to further investigate.
- Busy day?
As you can see behind me,
the fire's been brought
under control, and they want
everyone in the neighborhood
to know that you're safe, and
you can stay in your homes...
Just doing my job.
This is Jack Garcia reporting live.
You didn't stay around
to interview the victims.
I thought you were
Mr. Human Interest Guy.
Of course, interviewing
another lover
whose house is in ruins could
be a little awkward, right?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
That's a lie.
So, what is it?
You feed your ego by having
sex with married women,
and then, when they
grow tired of you,
you burn down their houses?
I had nothing to do with
either of those fires.
But you were having
sex with Laurel Craig.
Yeah, I thought so.
See, the thing is, I believe you.
I don't think you started
either one of those fires.
How long have you known
about Laurel Craig?
- Must have made you feel powerless.
- Excuse me?
Arson's about power.
And in female arsonists,
it's about revenge.
You're afraid that's
true, aren't you?
Right?
We have the FBI searching
your home right now.
Tell 'em, Sarah. Tell
'em it's not true.
I looked at all the
numbers in your phone.
I looked at your E-mail.
You planned a vacation with Laurel.
You took Cheryl to a benefit.
Honey, I...
Don't!
You humiliated me.
You and those women took
everything from me.
So you took everything from them.
# Four seasons in one day #
# Lying in the depths
of your imagination #
# Worlds above and worlds below #
# The sun shines on
the black clouds #
# Up the creek and
through the mill #
# Like all the things
you can't explain #
# Four seasons in one day #
# Blood dries up #
# Like rain, like rain #
# Fills my cup #
# Like four seasons in one day. #
Hey.
Heard you did all right.
Yeah.
Yeah, we did,
actually. It was okay.
Torres did, too, on the drive-by
with a little help from Loker.
How did it go with Zoe?
It's good, actually.
Yeah.
Roger's proposed to her.
You okay?
You know what I miss?
I miss the arguments.
You do?
What?
Probably not the best
time to tell her, though.
Absolutely not.
Thanks for your help on this.
My office is grateful.
Your office is welcome.
We're not a total
disaster together.
What?
I mean, working together.
Oh. And I know.
I should've told you about Roger.
It's just... I don't know.
I guess it just never
seemed like the right time...
No. Hey, so, if, um,
Roger makes you happy,
right, then we'll make it work.
For Emily, I mean.
Yeah. Thanks.
You should probably
wear the ring, though.
- Oh.
- It's a little confusing.
Okay.
All right, then.
Bye.
What was that?
Mom, I'm home.
Katie's mom is sick, so
we're staying here tonight.
That would be our daughter.
Oops.