Get up! Up! You got this!
Come on! Up, Orlando!
You got it. Move it around.
Go for the midsection!
All right.
Throw him!
Roll out of this.
Quit tippin' your punches out there.
He's leading with his egg, love.
Yeah, thanks. We got this.
Take a seat, Lightman.
Yeah, but,
trouble is his egg's empty.
He's dead from the neck up.
- No...
- He's going down.
Better help your friend, Simone.
Great win tonight,
but the celebration's over.
I put people to sleep,
and tomorrow fight,
they call me Sandman.
That's original.
You fightin' tomorrow?
You got your next date, then?
Si. I need the money.
Come on. I'll drive.
No. You my father now?
- Give me the keys.
- I'll do it.
- I'm gonna drive.
- You ain't drivin'.
- Why you gotta push me?
- Give me the keys.
- Gimme.
- I got it.
I got it.
Why do you fight...
You scratched me!
Crikey! That hurts.
You fight like a girl, you do.
Everything cool down there?
No, we're fine.
It's all fine.
God.
I'll give you a lift.
I'm taking the bus.
Suit yourself.
Papi!
Estupido!
Open the door.
I can do it.
Come on.
What do you...
La Lie to team présente:
Episode 218: Headlock
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
www.u-sub.net
You should just quit your job,
let me take care of you.
You wouldn't respect me.
Besides, what would your friends
and family think?
You haven't told anyone about us,
have you?
You comin'?
Dave, your phone.
Bernerd bloody Dillon.
I suppose he was always gonna crawl out
from under his rock, right?
Assistant special Agent
in charge Bernard Dillon.
He's Reynolds' new nanny then?
And all things Lightman group.
In this country, we say, "Bernard".
You might wanna get that right.
Bernerd!
- Dr. Lightman.
- We need your help with a murder case.
Who do you want me to kill?
Very funny.
The kid's name is Raul Campos.
He's 20, from Peru.
He was found last night,
three gunshot wounds to the chest.
We took the case over
when it was clear
that the victim was participating
in illegal underground fighting.
His fight last night
was caught on a camera phone.
A chip with the video footage
was dropped off
to one of our field offices
anonymously.
Torres is looking at it now.
We suspected
businessman Ron Marshall
to be bankrolling these fights.
These underground fights are savage,
illegal gambling orgies
populated by animals.
Marshall's already slipped
through our fingers once.
Your fingers?
No, I mean, makes it personal...
to you, bernerd.
What happened between us
is old business.
I'm a professional with a job to do.
I've moved on.
Peachy.
We're gonna bring suspects
from the fight last night here.
We don't have time
for by-the-book FBI interrogations.
If Marshall even gets wind
of what's going on, he's out of here.
A witness saw the...
the victim Campos in a heated exchange
outside a bar with an older male...
forties, caucasian, 160 pounds,
about 5'8".
You keep me in the loop, then.
I've moved on, too, Bernard.
Right.
Follow me.
- How'd you find me?
- Marshall got somebody in DMV.
He also got Orlando,
thinks he's the one that killed Raul
because he lost the fight.
Look, Orlando's not a killer.
I need you to prove that.
You're certain he's innocent,
are you?
We were shootin' pool
at Connor's when Raul was killed.
Look, Simone, I know
I'm only a scientist, right,
but don't insult
my intelligence, all right?
I'm sorry. I just...
Orlando's innocent.
I swear.
Please, man.
Marshall's gonna kill him.
He's like a brother to me.
You tell Marshall that the FBI
are all over him
on this one, all right?
The last thing he needs
is another corpse on his hands.
That's it?
Best I can do. Good luck.
See yourself out.
It's the morgue.
Skin cells were found
under Raul's fingernails.
They're running DNA now.
Excuse us?
One minute.
I'll be right back.
So what's up?
The DNA under the dead
man's fingernails.
Don't tell me that's from Campos.
I was with him
the night he was murdered.
White male,
forties, lean, devilish good looks.
Ring a bell?
So you were at the fight?
We need to lose
the DNA results, Ben.
Excuse me? We?
At the very least,
we need to mismanage 'em.
So you think that I'm gonna interfere
with a federal investigation?
Not gonna happen.
- If you're innocent, just come clean.
- Well, I would,
wouldn't I, but that tosser Dillon,
he's got it in for me.
If he finds out
that I'm prime suspect,
he's gonna push for an arrest,
and I'm gonna lose custody of Emily.
I need a bit more time.
Any progress on that footage?
The clarity's terrible, so I'm trying
to enhance it, see if I can...
if I can get a better read
on the crowd...
see if anybody's showing
any hostility towards Raul.
Mind if I sit in?
It usually takes a couple hours,
so...
I'm gonna stick around for it,
let me know when it's done.
Will do.
Want me to take over?
Really?
No argument or...
Come on, Lightman.
Pick up.
Did you see where Lightman went?
He went that way.
All you gotta do
is look after your fighter!
That's what I'm tryin' to do!
That's easy!
Look, I'm tryin' to look after him!
Just do your job!
Am I interrupting something?
What about "do not disturb"
don't you understand?
You tell him about me?
I thought you said
you weren't interested.
Simone tells me that you read faces,
some sort of scientist.
That's why you come
to all my fights?
All right, Raul the upstart,
he gives Orlando
a kicking in the ring,
and Orlando does him in.
Is that it?
You haven't read his face yet.
You'd never ask.
Where is he?
That's not a good sign, your eyes.
You're the only judge and jury
he's ever gonna see?
- Get him out of here.
- Keep your eyes stiff.
I might not be able to control myself.
He's in there?
Business is business.
Wouldn't it be better business
if you found out
if Orlando was the real killer
before you did him in?
Shall we?
Shut up.
So,
anything I say, you're gonna
get the truth out of him, is it?
I don't need you to tell me
how to do my business.
Got it?
Now look at me, all right?
Now, Simone says that you were shooting
pool there last night. Is that right?
I was at my girl's house, Lucia,
all night long.
She made anticuchos.
I'm sold.
Scientifically speaking, that is.
Explain the science to me.
What?
You don't think
I'd be able to follow?
Right. Look at him, all right?
He's not scared of you.
All right?
That's contempt, that is.
He thinks you're just another pansy.
You can't fight like a man.
There's nothing more that he'd like
to do than tell you that he killed Raul,
if only to look you in the eye
and show you what a real man is.
Do you follow?
Boss.
What?
Boss, we got a situation out here.
Boss, it's serious!
I didn't kill Raul.
Don't get up.
Found her wandering in here.
- Says she knows you.
- Who, me?
That true?
I never seen her before in my life.
My name's Sabrina.
I heard
you were looking for fighters.
Who told you that?
We might have met her.
At that karaoke place in that dump.
What was it called?
- Hyattsville.
- There it is.
Yeah. Yeah, right.
Damn girl, you clean up good.
I barely recognized you.
You gotta see
the hand speed on this one.
Ridiculous, for real.
I don't meet fighters here.
You never came here, and you never
come here again. You got me?
Go.
Now what about Orlando?
Orlando stays with me.
Are you out of your tiny mind?
Not that tiny.
I just cut you
out of an incriminating video.
Someone filmed you on their cell phone
at the fight last night,
so I thought I'd come over here
and give you a heads-up.
- You could have called me.
- I tried, like, about 10 times.
Now the FBI's saying they're gonna
post a reward for any more footage,
so I don't know what you're up to,
but you don't have much time
before they find you.
Just let them find me, then.
You don't really mean that.
Look, I go to those fights
just to look at the faces.
Right. And you read "playboy"
just for the articles.
Don't be daft.
Look at you.
You're all wired up
after your Sabrina act.
Takes one to know one.
You're off this, Torres.
I mean that, right?
Did they come out yet?
Two of Marshall's men just left,
but he's still in there with Orlando,
who's a dead man
for something he didn't do.
No, he's not innocent in this.
He's up to his ears.
I'll see you
back at the office, right?
Pleasure's all mine, by the way.
No need to thank me.
You're off this. I mean it.
I mean it, Torres.
Chesapeake boat charters.
Receptionist stepped away.
No one saw me come in, so...
your secret is safe.
- What's the occasion?
- I have to cancel tonight.
Some potential foster parents
are coming to the youth center,
and I have to interview 'em.
I brought this...
to buy your forgiveness.
I'm sorry.
I'll make it up to you.
I promise.
Forensics.
- This is Agent Carl Washington.
- How can I help you?
I need you to pull that rush order
off of DNA sample 2699b.
- Campos, right?
- That's right. The Raul Campos case.
You need this asap?
We're checking right now to see
if the sample was contaminated.
- I'm all over it.
- All right. Thank you.
What are you doing here?
Was just looking for Lightman.
Yeah, you and me both.
We found the next of kin.
Raul was wiring money
to an aunt in Peru.
She said his brother's here
looking for him.
- Foster's waiting for you.
- I'll be right there, sir.
My brother left a year ago
after a fight with my father.
Nobody knows where he went.
We all miss him.
So what did he
and your father fight about?
I can't really remember.
I think you do.
Why don't you tell us?
He wanted to be a rich man.
That's why he came here.
My father was angry about that.
He called it irresponsible.
It bothered you, too.
It was selfish.
He wanted to walk away
from his obligations,
from his family.
I should have never
have encouraged him.
How are you feeling?
Like my soul's been ripped away.
Just Marshall and the main guy.
You got a light?
- You clear the mess out of the office?
- We're good.
- You smell that?
- Yeah. Yeah, I do.
Fire!
Take that!
Put it out!
Come on!
You gotta be...
If that don't put it out, bring...
Right.
Get a move on.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
All right?
Get him out of here.
Can I get three club sodas,
please, darling.
All right, Orlando,
the reason I saved your ass...
All right, was so I could
ask you this question.
- Why'd you kill Raul?
- I didn't kill nobody.
Look at me when you say that.
Come on. I dare you. Look at me.
You see, save your breath.
'Cause your eyes just did
the talking for you.
I just accused you of murder...
You're worried
about what she's thinking.
Why is that? You think she killed Raul?
Is that it?
Yo, get real.
Why would I off another fighter?
You know, I think
she's got your nuggets...
in a vise, Orlando.
- You wanna talk to me about that?
- I just didn't...
Thank you, love.
I just didn't wanna let
her down, all right?
After all you done for me,
I just don't wanna disappoint you.
You know, I don't think
you're dead from the neck up.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Did you throw the fight?
Estas loco. Asabes?
Esta loco que estas hablando.
'Cause I don't think
that was your plan going in,
but something made you go down.
What was it?
- You're crazy.
- Maybe we should get out of here.
- That's a good idea.
- Wait. Look.
I'm the only thing
between you and the feds,
let alone immigration.
All right, hang on.
Scooch up, gorgeous.
All right, fine.
Me and Raul, we were close.
We're from the same part of Peru.
Asabes?
You always tell me
hate your fighters, right?
- I didn't hate Raul.
- And look where it got you.
You don't understand.
I needed to help him, all right?
Yeah, something was
making him run hot.
I'm not just talking
about when he was drunk
and he was bragging
about beating you.
What was it?
He said it was the shining path,
the senderistas de Peru, all right?
They knew he was here,
and they were coming for him.
He said it was gonna be his last fight
before he left town. That's all I know.
So you decided
you were gonna help him, right?
You take the count.
You gift him the cash. Is that it?
Good.
We're digging into Raul's whereabouts,
getting close to finding out
Just a second.
Asac Dillon.
What do you mean
our DNA request was pulled?
By who?
Put it back on.
Yeah.
For some reason, Agent Carl Washington
pulled our DNA sample off the rush list.
I had to put it back on the fast track,
but we may have a problem.
I'm gonna look into it.
You guys stay on your toes.
Yes, sir.
Come on! You got this!
Give it to him, baby!
Hey, there's something weird
with this FBI footage.
- What?
- It jumped like it was edited.
It should be...
21 minutes, 43 seconds.
But on screen, it's 21 minutes,
36 seconds. We lost 7 seconds.
It's probably on the hard drive.
I'll find it.
I forgot. Lightman called.
He said he wanted you...
to get ready to present
your research on lowland gorillas.
- When?
- This afternoon.
I have at least 2
days more work on that.
Well, better get on it.
- What about this case?
- I'll cover it.
Go do your thing.
You've seen Lightman? I've got a person
of interest I can't hold too long.
I think he's at lunch, but if you...
I can start the questioning,
- stall till he comes back.
- OK.
These were taken
from video footage of the illegal fight
you set up last night,
and it turns out it was at a warehouse
owned by a relative of yours.
I don't know nothing about a fight.
Your uncle sold copper out of
that warehouse for 26 years.
- What's that got to do with me?
- We know about everything.
We put a pin in every location
where you funded a fight.
I never funded anything.
You know...
You're a dead ringer
for this girl I know.
I guess we all have a twin.
Yeah.
Apparently mine is
a very dangerous man.
Can we have a word?
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
- Marshall's lying.
- No... no, he's not.
Are you afraid of him?
No.
Damn it.
Where's Lightman?
No offense, but with a chess player
like Marshall, I need a pro.
He's not gonna read
anything different.
If you want me to try again, I will.
Fine.
Let's go.
- Hi.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. I was checkin' in, you know.
Why don't you just
come right out with it?
I didn't wanna...
- Intrude.
- Yeah. That's it. No!
- Because that is not like you at all.
- Yes.
I'm seeing someone.
There. You happy now?
So you've got my back,
knowing my luck with men as you do.
Is that what you wanted
to check in about?
No.
- Mostly yes. All right.
- Great. Thank you.
No, really, thank you.
I mean that.
But now can you try
and do your best
not to stick your nose
into my business?
Yeah. I can do that.
Turns out our witness
who saw the prime suspect
has a history of drug abuse,
putting his credibility in question.
- I need you to talk to him.
- I'll be right there.
- I need you to take this one.
- OK.
- Thought I gave 'em my description.
- You did.
After taking a few hits of meth,
it seems.
Were you strung out last night
when you saw Raul?
No, I swear.
I didn't have any money.
You've had a couple of run-ins
with the law for drug possession.
Did you think giving an eyewitness
account would earn you some goodwill?
No.
Higher voice pitch.
That was a yes.
Did you really see a guy with Raul or,
was it made up to earn brownie points?
I'm tellin' you I saw him.
Kinda looked like that guy.
The suspect looked like this guy?
Yeah.
You heard of the shining path?
What, the senderistas?
They're a guerilla group out of Peru.
Yeah. They make the vikings
look like little boys
looking for a good wrestle.
Raul was scared of them.
He thought they were
after him for some reason.
What are you doing?
What does this kid mean to you?
He was a good boy. He was a little
misguided perhaps, but... Yeah.
Kind of like you at one point?
- What, you my shrink now?
- No, I'm just saying.
You put your nuts on the boot end
of a criminal enterprise,
and I'm trying to understand why.
I have my reasons.
Well, dollars to doughnuts, Raul was
killed by somebody in the fight world,
- maybe even Marshall.
- No.
Raul was the ATM! Why'd you pull
the trigger on a good payday?
Answer could be on the tape.
By the way, Dillon put your DNA test
back on rush status.
The results should be
here in a few hours.
- Do I look worried?
- That's him.
That's him. That's the guy.
That's who was fighting
with the kid.
I think you've made
a terrible mistake, mate.
- I saw you with him.
- You saw me?
- Yeah.
- You absolutely positive?
- Yeah?
You saw this face in the dark
with that astigmatism, did you?
- Who are you?
- This is Dr. Cal Lightman.
- He runs this place.
- Also live in this place.
So you're saying
you were here last night?
Oh, yeah.
I was with him.
Yeah.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Maybe it wasn't him.
Now, did you really
see an astigmatism?
No.
You're learning!
OK, so I saw something here.
Right there.
Raul flashed fear.
Yeah. He's...
Looking at something
to his left, right?
Yeah.
That would be you.
Park your mouth, Torres.
Put your brain in gear.
let's look at the other people there,
preferably behind me.
Freeze it there.
Push in. Push in.
Push, push, push!
Right about now, all right,
the fight is getting really,
really good, and the crowd
is going bonkers!
All except for this guy.
His body language
is completely relaxed.
He's not there for a fight.
So how did your girlfriend
track this down?
She called the charter
company, and... Thank you.
And pretended to be
her fiancé's assistant.
If I had to put money on it,
the guy charters a boat out
of Baltimore for 5 hours,
he's probably a drug smuggler.
So how long has your girlfriend
known her fiancé?
A few months.
She should be careful.
I don't know what I'm gonna tell her.
She's in love with him.
Look, you know,
if your girlfriend
can get that passport
and maybe his cell phone,
we can look into it.
- Sir, you wanted to see me?
- Yeah. Give us a minute.
- Have a seat.
- All right.
What's goin' on?
You impersonated Agent Washington
to delay the prime
suspect's DNA report.
Who are you covering for?
I've got something for you.
Right there. This...
is a picture, from the fight.
Well, I'm in it.
You were at an illegal fight
just to study faces? Correct.
For you, no extra charge.
Did you know Raul Campos?
Not personally.
No, but I seen him fight.
Your interest in which
was purely professional.
100%.
90 percent. OK...
80, actually, percent.
- Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
- Well, I... I misjudged you...
Bernard. I did.
I... because of the,
you know, history
between you and I, I...
you once wrote a report on me
based on a single interview session
which affected my
promotion schedule,
knocked me back easily 2 years.
No, I did do that. Yep. Which is why
I thought you were gonna come in here
and press charges and
strip me of my FBI contract.
And what about you?
He doesn't give a toss
about politics.
He's all about getting the job done.
"Big picture" Ben,
we call him around here.
Sir, Lightman just needed more time
to
canvass his fight contacts.
Right.
Now...
This...
Is the man you want.
All right?
Now, Reynolds here already has my people
working on getting,
better resolution
on the license plate, so...
He's all over it.
Ah, you're a sight for sore eyes.
I thought you were working late.
Yeah. The foster parents canceled.
What are you doin' here?
I was just... I was
looking for an earring... that I lost.
I thought maybe you
were looking for this.
It wasn't where I left it.
Who's Marco Gianelli?
This passport is for work.
That's all I can say.
It's for the youth center?
Yes and no.
Just tell me the truth.
I have to go.
I work for the DEA.
I'm an undercover agent. I've been
at Covington for the last 6 months
monitoring 2 ms-13 gangbangers
that we believe are part of a
new drug cartel in Mexico.
- Are you a real psychologist?
- Yes.
Look, I've withheld information,
but nothing that I've told you is false,
except meeting
of the foster parents.
Your real name, what is it?
Dave Atherton.
I'm just thinking...
About you and I, th-this...
- if this was part of your cover.
- No.
Absolutely not, Gillian.
The last thing that I expected
on this job was to fall in love.
And telling you everything
is incredibly stupid...
and dangerous.
But I don't wanna lose you.
You haven't.
When do I get to meet
my brother's killer?
Real soon.
I'll be right back.
You sure?
It was a rental car
and his name is on the contract, so...
- Incoming.
- Dr. Lightman.
We just got the prime
suspect's DNA back.
You've got some explaining to do.
You concealed a personal
relationship with the victim.
- Well, I was just trying to help.
- And you thought I was the dirty one.
No, I wasn't sure that you
were dirty, per se.
You know, I just...
I couldn't be 100% sure at the time.
How sure were you?
90%? 80%?
I didn't kill Raul,
you know, if that's where this is going.
- How can I be 100% sure?
- Find the real killer?
How do you explain the
fight outside the bar?
He was drunk.
- I was gettin' his keys.
- Don't take me for a fool.
Do you have any idea how overwhelming
the evidence is against you?
I'm not taking you for a tool.
- Fool!
- Whatever. Look, Bernard...
Just give me 10 minutes
in the cube with Juan.
So you came here to take
your brother back home.
Right? But you threatened him,
and then he ran away.
Why would I threaten my own brother?
I don't know.
You're a senderista, right?
You'd threaten your own grandmother.
I fight for the revolution.
So did my father, and so did Raul!
All right, calm down.
Calm down.
But Raul, he got away, didn't he?
He escaped.
Now, I don't know, but it seems to me
if you join the shining path,
that's a lifetime's membership.
You came here to remind him of that.
Or to, you know...
kill him if he didn't see sense.
I never found my brother.
You shot him... Didn't you?
You shot him in cold blood.
I was still looking
for him this morning.
That's enough, Lightman.
Mr. Campos, you're free to go.
Oh, what? Are you nuts?
I just hooked the bastard!
Juan.
Yes?
After the fight, right.
Raul was happy.
He was excited to go home.
Tell him that.
- He talked to Raul yesterday afternoon.
- All units, go.
Juan! Don't you move!
Don't move! Get on the ground.
Get on the ground.
Put your hands on the ground.
- Put your hands behind you.
- Juan!
Get up.
Let's go.
- Aye, aye.
- Hey.
Cal, you remember Dave, don't you?
Yeah. Uh, from juvie.
Right? Eh, Burns.
Dave Burns.
Right.
Did I get that right? Or did I make a
mistake, 'cause I'm terrible with names.
- You got it right.
- How are you?
I'm terrible with names.
I'm, you know...
Um, did I say something
there that surprised you?
Or is it... no, no.
I've got it right.
No, 'cause it's been donkey's years
since she's had a bit...
of anything special in her life.
I mean,
not that there's anything wrong
with her. Far from it. I mean,
she's just a little bit...
- Awkward.
- Awkward is good.
So you've had your fun, Cal.
All right. Just talk amongst
yourself for a minute.
Dave, do me a favor, all right?
She's my best friend, all right?
She's my best friend
and is probably the only reason
that this place hasn't gone under,
so you do me a favor,
you know. Just...
handle with care, you know?
Don't let him scare you off. Heh.
- I thought I told you to...
- talk amongst myself.
I got bored.
Really?
- Will you give us a second?
- Sure.
He seems nice.
- What?
- You OK?
What, me? Yeah. I'm fantastic.
How about you? You okay?
Illegal underground fights, Cal?
You could have told me.
You know, just because you share all
your dirty little secrets, all right,
doesn't mean I have to.
He's a good man, Cal.
That's all you need to know.
That's all I'm gonna share.
No, I got it.
No more questions, right?
I'm good.