Hello.
- Hi.
- My son.
Tim and I were just gonna
play a game.
I'm just not really
very good at games.
Well, my mom is. I guess
she's a lot smarter than you.
Kesheshian says goodbye.
- Peter... he's dead?
- Yes!
Agent Fundis, D.E.A.
I'm here to talk about
Peter Scottson.
- I'm his partner.
- The one who burps?
I get stares.
Children cry and run away.
Want you to give a friend
of mine a call.
We're shooting a movie
in one of our empty houses.
Needs a caterer.
I'd like to solve the mystery
of the school
that receives federal funding
yet permits a religious
curriculum in direct violation
of church/state separation
mandates.
Sit down, Shane Botwin.
I have cancer.
Puppies are coming off, Nance.
After reconstructive surgery,
you're gonna feel good as new.
I'm separated,
dancing my way to divorce.
You're gonna help me
celebrate.
My last two relationships...
both guys ended up dead.
Weeds - Season 3 Episode 8
The Two Mrs. Scottsons
Transcript by testexam
Synch : Macanto / [dx]
Michvanilly / San-A
Captain.
All right, Fundis,
tell me a story.
A man flying a kite
found Scottson.
We think he was stuffed
in a drainpipe
until a grate busted
in the rain and...
Up came Pete.
Can't you take something for that?
I've tried everything,
Captain.
Well,
pop a fuckin'breath mint.
- What did you eat, pastrami?
- On rye, Sir.
What else, Fundis?
Well, a close-range shot
to the head.
It's ugly.
Who, why, when?
I've been trying to figure
that out since he went missing.
You know, retracing his steps,
asking...
What's that?
Summer reading
from internal affairs.
Quite the ripping yarn.
Retracing his steps?
How about covering your ass?
You got another story
you want to tell me, Fundis?
My career just took a swan dive
into a shitcan.
I want to thank you for that.
I'd like to thank Pete, too,
since it appears
he was the brains
behind the skimming,
extortion, wiretapping,
evidence-planting operation
you two had going.
But good thing for us
he turned up the way he did
and we don't have to
get honest.
So here's the new story,
agent asshole motherfucker
choke-on-my-dick.
You got three days to find
whatever money is left over
from your little side business,
and before you clean out your
locker for early retirement,
take your uniform
to the dry cleaner's
'cause we have a fucking hero
to stick in the ground.
Peter Scottson served
with dignity and honor
in one of
our most difficult jobs.
And for those of us here today,
there will be no rest
until those who put him here
are brought to justice.
Dear Lord...
We sadly send you
another son in blue.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Ghost.
Amen.
Hello?
What are you wearing?
You gave me the day off, boss.
Oh, come on.
Indulge a pervert.
Black dress, black shoes,
black everything.
Bet you look better in red.
Not appropriate
for faking grief.
Don't know what that means.
Don't care.
- I bought you a gift.
- You should take it back.
Don't you want to know
what it is?
It's my day off.
When are we gonna have sex again?
When I'm feeling desperate again.
And when do you think
that might be?
You get lost on your way
to forest lawn?
Never knew the man.
Is Conrad around?
Do you see Conrad?
How about one time...
just for laughs...
I'll ask you a question,
and you maybe answer me,
you know, like a human?
What can I say?
You bring out the "fuck you"
in me.
Fine. Moving on.
Bringing good news.
You're free.
Abe Lincoln beat you to it.
What else you got?
I took care of your debt.
You don't owe Marvin anything.
I mean, you're gonna
have trouble
moving your shit on the streets,
but you still have me.
I have a new territory
opening up,
three times the size
of Agrestic, so...
You're welcome.
No thanks necessary,
since I assume...
None are coming.
- What's that?
- I'm making a buy.
Little miss Nancy do-good
burying her boyfriend
and back to dealing dime bags.
All things
in their proper place.
Praise Jesus,
blah, blah, blah...
Oh, am I boring you?
Well, I will stop
wasting your precious time.
We're a bulk business now,
so you can take your little
milk money down to the corner.
- Can I talk to Conrad?
- He's over with the pot clubs.
Large customers
with large money.
Now, you come back
with five figures,
and we'll do business.
Hell...
I'll even throw in a fountain.
Hey, Nance.
Doug.
Cooking in my kitchen.
There's a reason for that.
Andy's on set.
I'm helping him out.
Oh, that's nice.
Oh, that's from the tall one.
Leif garrett-y,
"blue lagoon-ish."
Said you were out of weed,
then took off with a blonde,
- tiny tits, big cross.
- Tara.
And your other one, big
vocab, creepy eyes.
He's outside
with what's-her-name.
- Celia's dyke.
- Isabelle.
Hey, Mrs. Botwin.
Hello, Isabelle, Shane.
An unlikely duo.
We've bonded through sin.
And school suspension.
- Suspension as in...
- Don't come back until you love Jesus.
- They call it reflection.
- And we got three days of it.
And how are we
going to reflect?
Wii tournament.
My first paycheck!
My son's bringing in
more money than I am.
Any chance I could borrow
$10,000?
How fast can you turn it around?
Seriously? I'll turn
it around in a month.
You got 10 grand?
If you could form a dummy corp
and I form a dummy corp
and you can find a supplier to accept
the check, I know an
accountant/councilman
with access to a certain
civic investment
- portfolio
- can you do it?
- have before.
- Do it.
Make it $50,000.
Aguatecture.
What is that, a colonic spa?
Shane, where's your
karate contact sheet?
Drawer by the coffee maker.
All right, Lex, come on, baby.
Big finish.
Show them how they do it
in jersey, baby.
Oh, yes! Lovely, people!
Cut! Cut!
Let's take a break.
Everybody, rinse out.
- We'll be back in 10.
- Wow Paul, great scene.
You're really an artist.
Well, thanks. We don't hear
that enough in this business.
And that's a tragedy. I mean, the
genre's been hijacked by amateurs, sure,
but when I see
your attention to detail...
the framing, the risks you take...
it makes this viewer...
I guess you should know.
- I've always wanted to...
- Be in porn?
Every caterer does.
Well, I think I could be great.
Look, I respect your ambition,
and I'd love to make it happen
for you, but I work with gods.
Jessica, she comes like a fountain.
Lex is packing a fucking Buick.
It's all about that something
special in this business.
What makes you special, Andy?
"Footfuckers," scene 1,
"A" camera, mark.
And action.
Coming!
Hello.
I have a package for Mrs. Dowling.
Are you authorized to sign for it?
Your feet must be aching
from all the walking around that you do.
Well, there's a lot of walking.
Well, why don't you come inside
and, uh... Take your shoes off?
Oh, that's right.
Use your something special, kid.
show me what you got.
Use that big toe!
That's fucking great!
"Foot Fuckers 2: Viva Las Vegas"
Scene 1, "a" camera, mark.
And action.
Coming!
Room service.
I ordered that about two hours ago.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
the elevator got stuck.
I had to climb all 43 floors
to get here.
Well, your feet must be killing you.
Listen, there's a huge market for these
fetish videos, mostly eastern Europe.
You're gonna be a huge star in Belarus.
I mean, huge!
Good! Good!
Get dirty, Andy! Get dirty!
I finish with
the backyard, Mrs. Dowling.
Okay, okay, thrust.
- Thrust!
- Oh, cramping, cramping, cramping!
Well, if it isn't the music man
of Majestic.
My partner in altruistic bullshit.
How are you this afternoon,
councilwoman?
Smiling.
You got my gift?
Not why I'm smiling.
But, yes, I did.
Piece of advice...
never send a woman a dress
she might not fit into.
- Did you try it on?
- It's a size 2.
Flattering and annoying
at the same time.
I thought your breasts
would look good in red.
Well, it's a nice thought.
Listen... I want to see you.
Wear whatever dress you want
or no dress at all.
I'm almost divorced.
Mazel tov.
Would you...
Like to help me celebrate?
You know where I live.
I do. I do, indeed.
See you, councilwoman.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Yeah.
All right, hold it up to your
mouth and I'll light it.
- How is it?
- It's...
kind of gross.
You feel anything different?
I feel like I want to brush my teeth.
Maybe it's bad shit.
But my dad gets it from your mom.
You know... My mom's... A drug dealer?
I saw her come over once.
I didn't tell anyone.
I won't tell anyone.
Thanks.
You gonna try it?
Yeah.
This is that moment where
I finally become cool, right?
No.
Just stoned.
Stop it.
That's very funny, Tim. Open the door.
Open the fucking door!
You don't talk to me.
- You can talk to me about anything.
- No, I don't want to talk to you!
Thanks.
that was my first boob.
How was it?
Good.
Do you want to touch my...
you know?
Not really into penises.
Why haven't we ever
hung out before?
I don't know.
My mom hates your mom?
I think my mom's secretly
in love with your mom.
I think my dad loved me
more than my mom does.
My mom's a bitch.
But I miss her.
I don't know why.
Do you feel stoned?
I guess.
I don't see
what the big deal is.
Yeah.
I prefer beer.
I prefer touching your boob.
You want to make a buy?
I said,
would you like to make a buy?
All right, let's just cut.
Cut.
You did great, kid,
you really did. Come on up.
You got
your foot in the door --
or in this case,
your foot in Jessica.
- Hey, go get Lex.
- Wait, wait ! That's it?
"Thanks for the foot.
go warm up the hot dogs"?
- I've been working all day here.
- What do you want, a medal? It's a job.
And, yeah...
go warm up the hot dogs.
Well, that's bullshit.
Hey, I'm talking to you,
Paul St. Moritz!
You know, I always stood up
for pornography.
I believed in it. I thought
it provided an essential service,
light up a young person's
imagination,
help a sexless marriage,
keep a predator off the street!
I thought porn was magical.
Now I see it
for what it really is.
It's a flesh factory,
and we are all slabs of meat.
Lex here is not an unbelievably
enormous dick.
And I'm not a foot.
- You're not a foot, Andy.
- Thanks, Lex.
We're human beings.
I gave you my something special,
and you ate it.
You took something beautiful,
like Jessica's vagina,
and you made it
just a place to put a foot.
You need to do some
soul-searching, my friend.
This whole industry does.
It exploits, it dehumanizes,
it degrades men.
Everybody back to one.
Back to one!
This is from Nancy.
First time I ever took a check.
She says
she wants her fountain.
Conrad!
- And what's your name?
- Judah.
- And this is...
- Sunshine.
Is that right?
Well, Mr. Judah, Ms. Sunshine,
you tell the city of Agrestic
we're impressed.
And you tell Nancy
if this check bounces...
- She better start running.
- I'll do that.
Stop.
- I want to, but I can't.
- Stop.
I have cancer.
I had cancer.
They cut them off.
These are, uh...
Spare parts.
I don't care.
- No, I need to leave my top on.
- Celia Hodes,
you're a smart,
ambitious, sexy woman.
I'm embarrassed.
I haven't gotten hard
on my own for two years.
I've been popping
magical boner pills.
- Magical boner pills?
- Yeah.
I took one in your driveway
half an hour ago.
Do you like my penis any less?
Hmm?
No. No, I don't.
We're used.
It doesn't mean
we can't be sexy.
Doesn't mean we can't
-- pardon my language,
fuck like bunnies.
Cool.
If I still had feeling in my nipple,
I bet that would be amazing.
All right, enough.
Listen to me.
I barely know you.
But the first time I saw you,
there was something about you
that was so familiar,
familiar in the best way.
Like we shared something, like...
we had a secret.
I just want to know you.
I don't know why.
I just do.
Okay. Stop talking.
- Hello.
- Hi
Mrs., uh, botwin.
- That's me.
- I'm Valerie.
You want to take a step up
to the X-ray machine?
Okay.
- You're the doctor?
- Oh, no, doctor's at lunch.
I just take the X-rays.
You can take out your breast.
What?
Oh, right. Right.
Mammogram's nothing
to be nervous about.
- It'll be over in a minute.
- Right. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You've got great breasts.
These?
You should see some of the jugs
we get in here.
Gravity's cruel.
All right, lift up your breast
and get as much of it
onto the plate as you can.
Just get it all on there. Just
spread it out from the bottom.
Just right on there.
Yeah, no, that's great.
That's great.
Okay, now you're gonna feel
a little bit of pressure
when I lower the top.
- Uh, uh...
- And smush.
Okay, I know it's probably
uncomfortable, but I'm fast.
Do you like this job?
Are you locked in?
Oh, yeah. Ready to go.
I know who you are.
Excuse me?
I...
know...
who...
you...
are.
So, Nancy Botwin,
why are you here?
And what do you want?
And why the fuck
are you stalking me ?