Previously on Grey's Anatomy...
Can I have the key back? I heard
we broke up. Can I have it, please?
Did you find an apartment yet?
'Cause I was thinking about getting one.
Can you make sure
I stay on Hahn's cardio service?
Where you going? You going to Joe's?
I'll meet you.
I can't sleep.
What's wrong with me?
Severe abandonment issues.
Psych is crap.
Derek kissed Rose?
- We were dating other people.
- That's not the point.
- You weren't ready.
- And Rose is?
You want to go to dinner
with me tonight?
We like to think
that we are rational beings...
Humane...
Conscientious...
Civilized...
Thoughtful.
This is your third session,
and you still haven't said anything yet.
Now while I love the quiet time, I'm...
I read a study that says
that just the act of going
to therapy is beneficial,
even if you don't say anything,
even if you just sit.
So you thought
you'd come here and just sit?
- That's how you'll solve your problems?
- I don't have problems.
What brings you here?
But when things fall apart,
even just a little,
it becomes clear...
We're no better than animals.
it's not that bad.
Once we get rid of the roaches,
the apartment...
The crapartment.
George, this is our home.
- We'll fix it up.
- With what money?
We'll figure it out.
I like it here, and i'd like it here
so much more if you'd like it here too.
We have opposable thumbs...
Look, I'm fine.
It's just...
I just haven't been sleeping.
You know, it's a...
Just been five weeks, and I can't sleep.
Five weeks since what?
Look... I work in this hospital.
I try not to listen to gossip,
but this is a very gossipy place.
- There are some things that I've heard.
- Derek's not the reason I'm... here.
- He's not the reason.
- Then what brings you here?
I gotta go.
I'm in this contest.
Dr. Grey, if you j...
We think...
We walk erect...
I'm up!
We speak...
We dream...
But deep down,
we're all still rooting around
in the primordial ooze,
biting, clawing,
scratching out an existence
in the cold, dark world
like the rest
of the tree toads and sloths.
- There's a contest going on.
- Sir?
Your residents...
They've been living in the hospital
around-the-clock
for the last 14 days,
engaged in a surgical contest
with a point system.
I don't know what you're talking about.
- They're committed. It's commitment.
- It's a lion fight.
I have one baby to get to day care.
I have 50 residents on my watch,
four surgeries on my schedule.
The lions can fight all they want.
I'm not zookeeper.
Keep your animals under control.
Yes, sir.
Move it!
- She's wretched... and mean.
- She's not.
I heard one of the nurses saying
that they've only been on five dates.
Yeah, 'cause Derek
knows she's wretched and mean.
What did you do to your hair?
You guys,
I know you're trying to make me
feel better, but I have to tell you,
this pausing to talk about
Rose and Derek, it just means...
Yeah?
- I'm gonna win.
- you bitch!
What? Keeping it clean was getting
in the way of the contest,
so I chopped it off last night. It makes
me faster and sleeker, like a cheetah.
You chopped off all your hot hair
for a stupid contest?
Not stupid.
Rock star contest.
Best contest ever.
You should try living in the hospital
for 2 straight weeks. It's amazing.
- This contest is for residents only.
- Yes!I know that.
Doesn't mean he can't still live here.
I feel juiced and alive,
my brain is clicking and running.
I have never been more on my game.
I'm kinda sad the contest ends tonight.
- I'm not. I want at prize.
- What prize?
Bailey won't tell us.
But I want it bad.
- Too bad you're never gonna get it.
- So on my game!
Good morning.
Thank you.
What do you see in her?
Is it the hot sex?
Is she an animal?
Is she a bobcat?
- Mark.
- Come on.
Lady on the streets,
tramp in the sheets, am I right?
Oh, yeah. She's amazing.
Hot, sweaty.
Very dirty, hot, sweaty sex.
You haven't slept with her yet?
She's waiting until we're serious.
She has morals. She's a lady.
Besides you know what's better than sex?
- What?
- Anticipation.
Anticipation, my friend.
Why didn't anybody wake me?
Why would we help you?
- There's such a thing as honor.
- Yeah, it's dog-eat-dog, karev.
Suck it up.
- You so are gonna do it.
- I'm so not.
You came in with Dr. Hahn?
Erica? Yeah.
We went out last night, and then it got
kinda late with the dancing and the...
Anyway... we never made it home,
so I hitched a ride here.
- You're hanging out with Hahn?
- Erica. Yes.
So you and Hahn are friends?
Erica.
See, this is the downside
of the contest.
I'm stuck here all the time,
Callie's living in my apartment
- and hanging out with hahn.
- They're trying to pick up guys.
I'm so glad I'm past that.
I don't need guys.
I don't need sex 'cause
this competition is my orgasm.
I should be hanging out with Hahn.
Cristina, would you focus?
It is so much more fun kicking
your ass when you focus.
- Who's winning?
- Yang.
- Surprised?
- What?
Let me see.
I'm 26 points behind?
That's not possible.
Count again.
- What about all the surgeries?
- Only 3 points for watching.
- You gotta do.
- I do do.
I can't make them let me do procedures.
- You gotta ask.
- You gotta take charge
of your own destiny,
make it happen, like this.
- What do you got?
- Otis sharon, 61-year-old male,
found unconscious on the street
corner with a swollen ankle.
Not it.
- I don't even know what happened.
- Initial B.P. was 90 over palp.
- Vitals stable after a bolus of NS.
- Okay, he's mine.
All of you back off.
- It's a swollen ankle.
- He passed out, he's pale,
altered, hypotensive and he has a rash.
You see a sprained ankle.
I see a medical mystery.
80 points.
- Stevens is the only one working today?
- No. We're all working. We got paged.
For the ankle. It's gone.
Now you're trolling for traumas?
Somebody could come any minute
with a critical injury.
- We're being proactive.
- Helping people.
You're trolling. And I've got
no one on post-op and pre-op.
Now move.
Help us!
Please help!
Help my brother!
- I'm gonna get a gurney.
- Help my brother.
- What happened to your hand?
- A bear.
- A what?
- He's really hurt.
- We tried to stop the bleeding.
- We were camping in the mountain.
- You drove all the way here?
- We couldn't wait for an ambulance.
- I'm fine.
- No, you're not. Let me see your hand.
Sir, let's try and get you
on this gurney.
- Careful.
- Step down right here.
I... intestines in the hands.
Intestines in the hands.
- Did you just say...
- Intestine in the hands!
Transcript: www.ydy.com
Sync: ¤AkaZab¤, Benj!
He just touched it.
He just... just put his hand out.
- He touched a bear?
- A cub, and then the mother came.
I bet she did.
Why would he do that?
We go camping all the time.
- I don't why...
- Okay, try to relax, Mr. Robinson.
All right, get me
a chest tube tray, please.
- Did I hear bear attack?
- Complete evisceration, chief.
Give me 100 of sux,
20 of etomidate.
Get me an intubation tray
and an OR room ready now.
Are you gonna put me under?
Sir, it'll be the best thing
that's happened to you all day.
Is my brother gonna be okay?
Please.
This whole thing's my fault.
I gotta know if he's okay.
They're taking him to surgery.
They don't know much yet.
We'll keep you informed.
Impressive hand, Phillip.
I can see right through it.
The bear cub, she just latched on
and wouldn't let go.
And then when Scott came over
to try to help,
the mother, she... Oh, god.
I can't believe
we got out of there alive.
He has to be all right.
He's gonna be all right.
He has to be, right?
Right?
He has to be all right.
You really don't remember how you fell?
One minute
I was walking down the street,
the next minute,
there was paramedics standing over me.
Have you been feeling dizzy lately,
like the room is spinning?
Maybe a little.
Any muscle aches?
Fatigue? Fever? Headaches?
Well, now that you mention it, yes.
Any recent travels?
I go back and forth to the east coast
for my job. Does that count?
- Notice any tick or mosquito bites?
- I live near a lake.
I get mosquito bites all the time.
Oh, god. Do I have something bad,
like malaria
- or west nile virus or something?
- Oh, no.
There's no need to panic. We're
gonna take this one step at a time.
Mama bear wasn't messing around.
Mama bears never mess around.
I have a ross procedure,
but I want to keep a close eye on his
chest tube outputs and blood pressure.
- What's the game plan?
- He's a setup for overwhelming sepsis,
so we're gonna deal
with the life threatening blood loss
and get out of there.
You can't touch him until he's stable.
I'm in OR 4. Can you make sure
I'm getting hourly updates?
I'd be more than happy
to apprise you of his condition.
Fine.
You don't get points for
sucking up to an attending.
Oh, shut up.
I hate this contest.
There's a lot of stuff in here.
A lot of stuff.
Stupid, stupid contest...
stupid, and irresponsible.
I want to play.
There's good stuff, free stuff.
I need a butterfly needle, a vacutainer,
and maybe an LP kit.
- I'm 26 points behind, I need it fast.
- What do you got? Something good?
Uh, sprained ankle.
You get 26 points for a sprained ankle?
Last time Callie treated
what we thought was a sprained ankle,
turned out the patient was malnourished,
perforated ulcer and died on the table.
That's the best case scenario.
Well, not the death part, george.
The medical mystery part. It's 80 points
for solving a medical mystery.
It's the holy grail of the competition.
Oh, yeah. Sometimes
an ankle's just an ankle, though.
Syncope, a very strange rash,
pale, insidious onset
in a guy who travels a lot.
This is not just an ankle.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, I could do a lot with these.
That's an underpad.
Underpads soak up urine.
Or... it could be a place mat.
Fruit bowl.
There. Done.
Beat you, busted hand and all.
- It's completely illegible.
- He's a slob.
Still beat her.
Okay, mr. Robinson, Dr. O'malley
is going to come and take you to x-ray,
and I am gonna take your wife
to the waiting room
until you get back.
She said wife.
I'm still not used to that.
- We're newlyweds.
- Congratulations.
She's my rebound girl.
He's a little hopped up
on painkillers right now.
- You're oversharing, honey.
- She thought she was my rebound girl,
but I rebounded her,
all the way to the church.
Only knew her ten days,
but when you know,
you know. You know?
I'm leaving you.
I'll miss you while you're gone.
Are you okay?
It's just, you know,
you marry a man like that...
Or a man like that marries you,
and he's cute and he's rich...
He's a catch by anyone's standard.
So you sort of sit around waiting
for the other shoe to drop,
because there's no way a man
like that marries you.
Or me.
I mean, he married me.
I'm sorry.
I must look like a crazy woman.
It's OK, but looks like you're bleeding
a little. Do you mind if I take look?
No, no. I'm... I'm fine.
I just scratched myself
on a branch when we were running.
Why are you looking at me like that?
CT is clear.
But it's deep.
That bear clawed you good.
God I didn't even feel it.
Adrenaline's a pretty powerful drug.
You're gonna have to repair the galea,
but it should reatach without a problem.
Squeeze my fingers
as hard as you can, please.
I just got happy.
I just got married,
and I'm really, really happy.
I don't have permanent
brain damage, do I?
It appears that you do not.
Okay, good.
Page me if any neuro deficits appear.
You got lucky.
Your scalp wasn't completely taken off,
so we can just sew it back on.
Your hair should cover the scar.
You won't even need surgery.
That's great.
Thank you.
Dr. Grey here will take care of you.
You go back to being a happy newlywed.
Don't worry.
He and Rose won't last.
He's hypothermic,
and his bowels are swollen.
We need to stabilize him in the ICU.
And try and get him back to the OR.
When he's less acidotic.
That'll give us time to deal with the
puncture wounds and the lacerations.
Sorry to say that one of you has
several hundred sutures ahead of you.
I'll do it.
I need the practice.
Her stitches are flawless.
I need the work.
They're flawless
because I practice.
- Karev, it's yours.
- Yes.
You need to update Hahn
on the condition of the patient hourly.
- That ought to keep you busy.
- That is a minute an hour.
I can suture for the other 59.
- Fine, you both do it.
- That's not fair.
This man was a chew toy for a grizzly
bear. There'll be enough to go around.
A lot of enthusiasm
for an afternoon of stitching.
Some people find it boring.
I value the fundamentals.
It's a point a suture.
Kiss ass.
It is a hairline fracture.
His ESR and CRP's were elevated.
I also appreciated
some swelling in the knee.
What does that mean?
There could be some sort
of inflammatory process going on.
- Inflammatory? That sounds bad.
- I don't want you to worry yet.
- Yet?
- Is there someone I can call for you?
Maybe you shouldn't be alone here today.
- How were his labs?
- WBC's normal, slightly anemic,
- potassium's mildly decreased.
- Okay, give him, a k-rider,
See if you can tap the fluid in his knee
to check for white cells or crystals.
Let me know if the tap's positive.
Good luck, mr. Sharon.
You think I need luck?
Oh, god.
I want to go home.
I want... Look, I want to go back.
I want to go back to when I was 30,
I want to stop smoking
when I was 30.
Or back to when I was 20 and
not start smoking in the first place.
I want to give up coffee
and junk food and beer,
and I want to be healthy
like my ex-wife always nagged me to be.
She was a saint.
she was a saint,
and I drove her away.
I want to go back
and not drive her away
so I don't end up at 60 sick and fat
and alone and scared in some hospital
with some beautiful young doctor
holding my hand.
She wouldn't be holding my hand
except she's trying to figure out
what horrible disease I'm gonna die of.
I... I want to go home.
- Where's the fire?
- Can't talk now.
Gotta kick Karev's ass suturing.
Since when are you friends
with my mentor?
A, she's not your mentor
because she treats you like crap,
and b, if you weren't living
in the hospital like a mangy dog,
you would've noticed
we've been friends for a while.
- You put in a good word for me?
- We don't talk about you.
- I let you live with me.
- He's getting on the elevator.
- Who?
- Alex.
Hold it! Hold it!
It needs surgery, but callie wants
to do 24 hours of antibiotic coverage.
I think we should just
irrigate and splint.
Okay. I'll take care of it.
Or I could take care of it, and you
could take care of the wife's scalp.
She needs lots of complex sutures.
You could get lots of complex practice.
Isn't that like a point a suture?
You don't want that?
I think this is bigger
than a broken hand.
He provoked a bear
and then drove himself to the hospital.
- Well, he was in shock.
- And he married his rebound girl.
- What?
- He married his rebound girl,
after knowing her for only ten days.
Nobody does that.
Who does that?
I'm thinking brain tumor.
I got married on the spur of the moment,
and I don't have a brain tumor.
That you know of.
I'll do the scalp.
- You will?
- I'm gonna watch you try to turn
a broken hand into a neuro problem
just to get some extra points? Nope.
It's not about the points.
I'm gonna watch you try to turn a broken
hand into a neuro problem just so you
have a reason to talk to Shepherd?
Nope.
I do not need a reason
to talk to Shepherd.
If I want to talk to Shepherd,
I'll talk...
What is this? Is this a hint?
I should be getting you more gifts?
A grateful patient gave them to me, but
since you're asking,
I do like a nice box of chocolates.
You're gonna die of a diabetic coma,
and I don't want any part of it.
- Cheapskate.
- Crackhead.
- Have you seen him?
- I have.
- Have you seen his eyes?
- I... Yeah.
- I'm trying to play it cool.
- I am playing it so, so cool.
I love him.
Oh, my god.
I... don't know you. I...
didn't say that.
What's with the flowers?
Are you asking as a resident
or a sister?
- Sister.
- I'm stealing stuff.
Are you okay?
Resident again now.
Stop stealing crap from the hospital.
22.
- Keep a lid on it.
- I like to know where I am.
PH is up to 7.28.
Yeah, not great, but it's improving.
Push another amp of bicarb for a boost.
- Karev's only at 17.
- You're not helping!
Did you just yell at the chief?
- Sorry, sir.
- I should end this competition now.
I mean, it's fine. Actually,
they're doing some nice work.
23. She's beating
the pants off of you, Karev.
Don't you have an update to deliver?
I think Hahn can wait
a couple of minutes.
Crap.
I thought you told me
to keep the animals under control.
From time to time,
I like to go to the zoo.
Dr. Hahn,
mr. Robinson is critical but stable.
We had to put him
on low dose levofed for his BP,
and he's put out 350 cc's
from his chest tube.
All right. I'll look forward to another
scintillating report in an hour.
Of course.
I'm thinking we ought to have
a little contest of our own.
You want to live in the hospital
like rodents?
Different kind of contest.
You and Rose,
you're not exclusive, right?
- So I'm thinking.
- You not serious.
One woman, 10 points.
2 women, same time, 20 points.
You get out in the morning
before anybody wakes up, 5 point.
- You are serious.
- You need a little spice in your life.
I'm just trying to help.
I am truly a worse human being
for knowing you.
- It's okay, mr. Sharon.
- It's not okay. It hurts.
I'm alone.
I'm all alone, and it hurts,
and I'm not okay. I'm dying.
By some lucky stroke of fate,
you fractured your ankle and ended up
at Seattle Grey hospital
with me as a doctor.
And I am gonna find
out what's wrong with you,
then I'm gonna do my damnedest
to fix it, and if I can't fix it,
I'm gonna assemble a team
of doctors better than me,
they're gonna do their damnedest, too.
Then you know what's gonna happen?
- What?
- You're gonna live a healthier life,
and maybe even call your ex-wife
because you're being given
a second chance at life and this time...
This time you can do it right.
You're gonna feel a little pressure.
Chief, Mr. Robinson's brother.
- Can I talk to him?
- Just for a minute.
Hey, man.
Hey, that you, Phil?
How you feeling?
I feel like a...
Like a bear ate my guts
out or something.
You touched a cub, man.
- What the hell?
- I wasn't thinking.
I... I'm so sorry.
So touching the cub, you knew better?
Of course he knew better.
He's having an early midlife crisis.
He's gonna kill us all.
I'm not having a midlife crisis.
Dude, dude,
you married your midlife crisis.
Just 'cause you got eaten by a bear, you
don't get to talk smack about my wife.
So was this spontaneous
wedding out of character for you?
You know what? He needs a little rest,
so let's have some quiet.
- Where was I?
- 59.
You are toast.
Tick tock.
Yang, no running in the hospital.
Why did we do a spinal tap
on an ankle fracture?
- He's getting a full workup.
- How many points?
What?
Look me in the eyes and tell me you are
not putting this man through painful
and unnecessary procedures
because you're trying to win a contest.
I'm doing this because my patient
had dyspnea on exertion,
headaches, fever, myalgia,
a confluent rash intermittently
over his entire body.
I'm working him up for
RMSF and doing lyme titers,
but I'm also worried
about a rare autoimmune
or rheumatoid disease because of his
high CRP and sed rates, or maybe lupus.
I'm doing a spinal tap too,
because he was altered
and is amnestic about his fall earlier.
I do want to win this contest,
but I also want to make sure
that a man does not leave this hospital
with meningitis or encephalitis
and discover when it's too late
that all we did was treat his ankle.
All right, then. Carry on.
When you hear hoofbeats, think
horses not zebras, right, Dr. Bailey?
Exactly, O'Malley.
Exactly.
Something tells me you're not just
worried about the damage to my hand.
Phillip, earlier today,
you were squinting at your paperwork.
I keep telling him he needs glasses.
And your handwriting was very
tiny and wasn't all that legible.
Is that normal for you?
Well, never been a straight-a student,
if that's what you mean.
Is he done, or are we done here?
- We could both use some rest.
- Humor me for one more second.
Okay, look straight ahead.
Tell me when you see my fingers.
- I see them.
- Tumor!
Sorry.
This is nice of you, really.
Dreaming up some brain tumor to make me
better about me making a bear mad.
Ever cross your mind I may be the type
of guy who's enough to pet a bear?
Jennifer, is he that type of guy?
Well, don't ask me.
I've only known him a few months.
Phillip, you knew better.
You touched the cub anyway.
- That, along with your other symptoms.
- What symptoms?
My vision's going bad.
So I get glasses, right?
But it's not just your vision.
Brain tumors have been known
to impede judgment,
prompt spontaneity, impulsivity.
He married a trashy waitress, right?
I mean, that's what you mean,
that he married a girl like me,
the rebound girl.
I'm just saying, I would like
him to have an MRI.
Just to be sure.
Well, the answer's no.
- Do the MRI.
- Honey, I don't need....
Do the damn MRI,
because you're wrong.
He loves me.
Mr. Robinson is doing better.
We were able to DC the levofed,
and he's intermittently awake and lucid.
His chest tube has put out
100 cc's since I last saw you,
and I'll be back in an hour
with another update.
Is somebody chasing you Dr. Yang?
- Excuse me?
- What are you racing around for?
- No reason.
- No reason?
Not because you're running towards the
finish line of this surgical contest?
That.
- Yes.
- Are you winning?
Yes. Once I finish my sutures
on Mr. Robinson.
That's too bad.
I was gonna let you watch me
put mrs. Witkowsky's new valve in,
but if a contest is more important
than a cardiac surgery, so be it.
I'd be happy to watch, Dr. Hahn.
Crap. Crap. Crap!
- Ankle guy?
- His CSF is spotless,
ABG's normal, the ultrasound is clear...
What am I missing? What am I missing?
- What?
- Right there.
- Where.
- See?
The fact that you're doing unnecessary
medical procedures to win a contest.
No! My god.
The fact that
you and Meredith are both doing
unnecessary medical procedures
to win a contest.
- Meredith has a medical mystery?
- No, she doesn'T.
Something is wrong.
You wanna know how I know that?
Great doctors have that extra instinct,
George. They just know.
Great doctors,
- they know when to stop.
- I have to have that instinct.
'Cause my instincts lately?
Very bad.
Really bad.
They told me to go for cardio. They
told me to have sex with a married man.
They are not serving me well.
I am in danger of going extinct
here if this keeps up,
and I am gonna win this contest if for
no other reason than I have to win it.
You paged me?
I thought you might like to see this.
Is that bear attack guy?
That's bear attack guy,
and that's his big old Brain tumor.
And I'm not requiring
an apology, George.
I'm not requiring an apology
because the fact that I may
have potentially saved a life today
is reward enough for me.
- You're calling me in to gloat.
- No.
I need a favor.
- What am I at?
- 87.
You're an underdog, aren't you, Karev?
Sir?
It's not that yodon't have the skills.
You have the skills.
But you're scrappy.
You're a fighter.
I like that.
I always root for the underdog.
I'm a fighter, but,
I'm no underdog.
Like this guy here.
He didn't...
He didn't provoke that bear.
His brother did it.
Now he's here, fighting for his life,
paying for someone else's mistakes.
It doesn't make him an underdog.
It just...
Well, makes him have to work harder
to overcome the cards he got dealt.
He's crashing. Hit that code button.
We got a code blue!
Code blue!
- This is Meredith's patient?
- Yes.
She didn't want to come to me herself?
Hey, I'm just... her intern.
Oh, my god.
Honey, I'm so sorry.
We did absolutely everything we could.
The stress was just too much
for his body.
There's more.
The neurosurgeon is going
to come in and talk to you.
No, I need to know.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I was right about the tumor.
You have something called
a malignant glioma.
This kind of tumor
causes behavioral...
It can cause inappropriate affect.
- Can you operate?
- No.
It's too invasive.
It's been growing a long time.
I'm so sorry.
Good.
Good, I deserve that.
I killed my brother, so
I don't deserve to survive.
Doctor?
I'm a symptom, right?
I mean, I'm...
I'm like the bear cub.
I'm just a symptom of this tumor.
That's what we're saying here, right?
Just so I'm clear.
I don't know.
I don't know that.
You're the only one who
could know that for sure.
When you say "negative,"
do you mean as
in bad or as in nonexistent?
Nothing bad came up.
What about all those alphabet tests
you were railing off?
I mean, they were elevated or something.
Yeah...
They were nonspecific.
They likely indicated that you
basically have a relatively minor flu.
I have the flu?
This whole day...
Everything you put me through...
You put me through all this for the flu?
I'm sorry. I am.
It just it seemed like
there was something more.
It really seemed...
I know it's hard to see
the silver lining here,
but think of the discoveries
you made today
about yourself and your life and...
and your ex-wife.
My ex-wife was a castrating bitch!
She was a castrating bitch, and I never
missed her for one day since she left!
Not until today!
And I missed her today because
if we were still together,
she would've shot
me dead a long time ago,
and I wouldn't have had to gone
through the hell you put me through!
I'm sorry.
- I didn't mean to. I really...
- You treated me like a rat!
Like a rat in some perverted lab!
Just give my prescription.
I want to get outta here.
The flu is a virus. It...
doesn't respond to antibiotics.
I suggest plenty of fluids and rest.
Fluids and rest?
Fluid and rest?
- I'm sorry.
- Fluids and freakin' rest!
I'm sorry!
I'm really, really sorry.
What you doing here? You spent the last
3 hrs watching a surgery. It's 3 points.
I'm trusting you screwed up enough
that it won't matter.
I could still win. I could.
I did get a lot of points today.
What's the matter with you?
Where's the trash talk, Charles Barkley?
She knows I'm the best.
- Who won?
- Congratulations...
- Dr. Grey.
The guy from the bear attack had
a brain tumor, and Grey caught it.
80 points for solving a medical mystery.
That's what put her over the top.
- I could've found a tumor.
- You didn't.
You chose to scrub in with Hahn
and watch for 3 little points.
Now congratulate Grey.
Congratulations.
Hey, don't you want your prize?
- A shiny pager.
- A sparkle pager.
- What's so great about a glitter pager?
It is special.
It is surgery's holy grail.
It's been passed down from resident
to resident, and now it belongs to Grey.
For the next three months,
whenever you all get a surgery,
you have to page this pager, and if...
Grey wants your surgery,
she has the right to take it from you.
Come on. Crap.
Enjoy the power, Grey.
Now may I recommend you all go home?
You smell, you greasy,
you need to bathe,
and I'm sick of looking at you.
Even my 1 year old here is sick of
looking at you. Isn't that right, bug?
Sick of looking at your little,
ugly faces.
Somehow I thought
I would enjoy this more.
- Well, give it to me. I'll enjoy it.
- Don't give it to her.
- Give it to me.
- Shut up. It's hers. She's the winner.
She's not gonna give it to you.
Give it to me.
Are you kidding me?
I don't like her.
I'm sorry, but as your friend, It's
my job to say it. I don't like Rose.
Why?
- You're not even sleeping with her.
- You don't like her 'cause
she's not sleeping with me?
That's a little weird.
- It's not weird.
- It's a little weird.
If you were sleeping with Rose,
I could understand
why you've been spending time with her,
but you're not. And it's just...
I thought that,
you know...
I thought it was just gonna be
you and me.
- Having sex?
- After. After Addison, after Meredith.
I have been patient.
I have waited while you partnered up
with these chicks, but now they're over,
and it's supposed to be just us,
you and me, two guys on the prowl,
on the hunt.
You're having trouble getting laid,
and you need my help.
I can get laid.
I can get laid whenever I want.
I do get laid whenever I want.
That's the point.
Women are everywhere.
I only have one person I can talk to.
- That's sweet.
- Shut up.
- It's really warm and fuzzy very sweet.
Are you serious about this woman?
I don't know.
Could be.
All right.
I'll give her a chance.
Good boy.
You're pathetic, and I'm a lesser man
for knowing you.
That's my line.
You can't use my line.
Thought you were off duty an hour ago.
I'm just catching up on some paperwork.
Piled up on you
during the contest, I guess.
- You know about that?
- I know about Otis Sharon
and the $120,000
worth of unnecessary tests you ordered.
Yeah.
Well...
I lost.
And I put a man through
hell for no reason at all.
I was a bad doctor today with
bad instincts, and I deserved to lose.
I don't know why I even bothered
competing in the stupid contest.
- So I don't need to yell?
- You should.
You can.
But you don't need to.
Good.
- Stevens.
- Yes, sir?
My year...
I lost by 2 points.
- You...
- You didn't invent the contest.
The contest is a lion fight.
So chin up,
put your shoulders back,
walk proud, strut a little.
Don't lick your wounds.
Celebrate them.
The scars you bear
are the sign of a competitor.
You were in a lion fight.
Just because you didn't win
doesn't mean you don't know how to roar.
Good night.
Good night, sir.
There's a little animal in all of us,
and maybe that's something to celebrate.
Our animal instinct is what
makes us seek comfort,
warmth, a pack to run with.
Hi...
Hello, Dr. Hahn.
I hope it's okay
I invited somebody over.
No, it's fine.
It's an honor to have you here,
Dr. Hahn.
I have to tell you...
- You won't believe it.
- Yes.
I was just going in there.
We may feel caged...
Are you kidding me?
We may feel trapped...
but still, as humans,
we can find ways to feel free.
Before you say anything,
before you say a word, just...
just hear me out.
I know it's not much,
and I... I know it's all stolen.
It's all stolen and...
and hospitaly and stolen.
You can turn me in if you want to.
You can report me for stealing,
cause obviously, now I'm a thief.
I've never even shoplifted a piece
of gum before, and now I'm a thief,
except I'm not.
I'm a nester. I'm...
I'm nesting. This is me nesting...
For you.
Because you hate it here.
You want to be at that big house
with Meredith and Izzie
where things are warm and you have your
friends and there aren't any roaches.
But this can be warm,
and I put out traps for the roaches.
And I...
I can be your friend.
No, I can be your friend.
I don't...
I don't have any friends here,
not... not really, except you.
And... and I don't have a home
to go to anymore, except here.
I just... I...
I can be your friend.
I complain a lot, don't I?
It's... okay.
No.
No. You know what?
I'm gonna stop. I'm just...
just gonna stop right now.
I'm gonna focus on what's good,
you know, like, like this crapartment,
like this apartment.
We are...
each other's keepers.
- Wish you'd have stolen a TV.
- I tried. They're bolted to the walls.
Still.
We are the guardians
of our own humanity.
And even though there's
a beast inside all of us...
I think I found a way to save lives.
I don't know for sure,
but I think we can save people
who have the kind of tumors
that Mr. Robinson has.
Mr. Robinson, the man
who was mauled by the bear.
I did all this research,
and I found this.
It's rare, and it's still untested
in humans, but...
I could find patients
for a clinical trial,
and I could do the lab work,
and I could track the results.
But I do need a neurosurgeon,
and you're one of the best.
It's not about us.
I would go somewhere else if I could.
But...
I don't know.
I think I found a way to save lives.
What sets us apart from the animals
is that we can think,
feel, dream and love.
And against all odds...
Against all instinct...
I think I better start talking now.
We evolve.