Come on.Come on.Come on.
Damn it.
Any first-year    med student knows that an
increased heart raten is a sign of trouble.
- All day of this.
- All day stuck with stevens.
Why are we in the clinic?
I thought we were
supposed to be surgeons.
Oh,not today we're not.Today is
gonna be about flu shots and enemas.
What a colossal waste of time.
Morning.
A racing heart    could
indicate anything...
From a panic disorder...  Oh!
- Oh,god.Oh,i'm sorry.
- No,i'm sorry.
I,uh,no,i,uh,didn't even look.
- I'm sorry.
- No,no.
What--what are
you-- no,no,no.
I-i'll leave.I'll leave.
No.
Sleep.You've been here all night.
Uh... How do you know that
i've been here all night?
- Wh--  to
something much...
Uh... I just knew it.
Much more serious.
You should wear your hair up more.
It shows off the back of your neck.
I like the back of your neck.
A heart that flutters...
Or one that skips a beat...
Hey,i thought you were,uh,sleeping.
No.Hunt was in the on-call room.
You had dirty sex with owen hunt?
No.It's-- it's not
dirty and it's not sex.
It's... Xe i don't know what it is.
Could be a sign    of
a secret affliction...
Hey,how's it going?
Oh,my god.Thank you
for asking.It's great.
I mean,he's fun and he's funny.
Even with no sex allowed,i mean,
we--we just laugh
and we--we talk and--
yeah.I don't want to hear this.
Come on.But you have to.It's just,
you're the only one who knows about
us,and--and i'm terrible at keeping secrets.
Keeping secrets makes me sick.
Look,alone people don't like to
hear about the together people,okay?
Even if the alone people are alone
by choice,it's--it's sort of mean.
It's sort of like bringing
a six-pack to an a.A.Meeting.
- But-- keep
it to yourself.
I am.
Uh,i need a favor.
My mother's journal--her ninth journal--
i need you to pre-read it for me.
- Why?
- My mother had an affair with the chief.
Your mother had an affair
with her chief resident?
- Rock on,ellis.
- No,no,no,no,no.
Not her chief.
Our chief.
Oh,yeah.You'll go blind reading that.
Or it could indicate romance...
Which is the biggest trouble of all.
What is that?
What you think it is.
That's dangerous.People who carry
guns are more likely to fire 'em.
Oh,i'm ready to fire it.
That's not the
problem.She's the problem.
She spooks easy.
I have to fire at the right time,in the
right way,otherwise she'll panic and bolt.
- She's not ready.Do you think she's ready?
- I don't know.
More importantly,if you don't know,you
shouldn't do anything until you do know.
- Dr. Sloan.
- Dr. Hunt.
Oh,let's make this quick.
- So we good to go?
- Yep.
Use it wisely.
I'm with you today.
So,uh,what's going on
with you and mark sloan?
What?Nothing.Why?No,why,why?
What did you
think is--was?
Well,because you've been on
his service for over a week.
Yeah,you know,i'm--i'm
really interested in plastics
a-as a--as a specialty.I'm
fascinated.I-i like f-faces.
vehicular blunt trauma,right
shoulder,stabilized in the field.
Somebody help us,please!
Jen,honey,slow down,will you?
Please,please,can you help my husband?
I ran him over with the car.
Sweetie,sweetie...
You have to calm down.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna be fine. I'm gonna be fine.
Okay,i'm calm.I'm ca.
- Okay. All right.
- I'm calm.I'm calm.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí ÏûÉùÄä¼£
GREY ANATOMU
hill Season 5Episode 14
Oh,my god,it's my brain.It's
my stupid,pregnant brain.
I left the car in drive.
Oh,god,baby.I'm so sorry.
It's a normal neuro exam.
Okay,well,he's got an inferior shoulder
dislocation and some associated fractures.
He'll definitely need surgery.
Sloan will debride the
burns when he's in surgery.
Surgery?Oh,baby.
Her b.P. Is 170 over 100.
give her 5 of hydralazine.
- Oh,my god.
- Sweetie,just calm down.How's the baby?
Kicking like crazy and
pressing right on my bladder.
Well,look on the bright side.At least,uh,she's
not running you over with a truck.
Thank you.
Hey,you wanted the s.U.V. Right?
Pregnancy-induced hypertension?
Yeah,i have to get her b.P.Down
before it starts affecting the baby.
Oh,nice couple.They'll have cute kids.
Yeah,not as cute as ours...  But cute.
What?
Nothing.
It's been three days--
three days of vacation--
the only three days i've ever
taken other than my maternity leave.
- Now i know i'm
behind,but-- bailey,i get it.
Jackson prescott was not an easy
case.I don't begrudge you that.
Okay,frankly,sir,i would rather
not work on another dying kid again.
But no need to worry,okay?
- I-i will catch up and
i'll-- i'm not worrying.
I'm promoting you.
I need another attending
in general surgery.
I'm submitting to the board that it
be you and that it starts this july,
the minute you've
completed your residency.
Now i know there was some talk a while back about
you getting tired of appys and gall bladders...
No,a f-full roster of appys and gall
bladders... Sounds just perfect,sir.
All right,all right.
But not today,though.Dixon's
requested you on her service.
This is subject to board
approval,bailey,though i'm not worried.
You have less to say now,huh?
Get outta here.
Dr. Dixon is not big on eye contact,so don't
be surprised if she doesn't look at you.
Also try to avoid physical
contact,uh,loud or disruptive noises--
she's okay,right?She's a good doctor?
Oh,no,she's amazing.
You couldn't ask for a better surgeon.
I'm only telling you so
you'll be better prepared.
Dr. Dixon,dr. Bailey,this
is,uh,dan and lisa pollock.
I need to see the
patient.Where's the patient?
Uh,right this way.
Uh,this is stacy pollock,age 9.
she's suffering from secondary
pulmonary hypertension due to a v.S.D.
Her e.K.G. Also shows,um,a left ventricular
hypertrophy,also evidence of right... Hi.
- Can i help you folks?
- Not him.
What's the trouble?
- Not him,either.
- Oh,uh,thank you.
We'll wait.
What about him?H-hello.
Yes,i'm sorry.Could you help us,please?I
would just-- we need to talk to a grown-up.
This is the chief of surgery.
No,just hold on,dr. Karev.
That doesn't mean i'm not a doctor.
How can we help?
- Uh,my husband and i,we-- our
children went off to college.
- One's at stanford.The
other's at,uh,u-dub.- Yeah?
- We tried something,a new thing and...
Something slipped,and we lost this-- rachel.
We were reading this
thing in a magazine.
Oh,here.
"20 techniques to reignite your nights"?
We did number nine.
- Um... Let's get you
in a gown so-- no,him.
- He did number nine.
- We  did number nine.
Yeah,i'm not the one
with it stuck inside my--
it's him.He's the patient.
Have a seat,and we'll take care of you.
Um... I'll... I'll stand.
you're taking him now, for surgery?
Yeah,it's a good thing.
We can get his dislocation fixed so we
can prevent problems with his circulation.
Her last b.P. Was
still up-- 162 over 102.
okay,well the o.B. Was worried
about placental blood flow.
Stay with her and just
try to keep her calm,okay?
- Okay.
- Cheeseburgers.
Painkillers are working.
Is there anything else
that i can get you?
Um,i'm okay.
Just--are you really
taking him now?
Yeah.
Cheeseburgers.Cheeseburgers.
She's,um,more relaxed when she eats.
Cheeseburgers calm her down.
Thanks for the tip.
Stacy has a v.S.D.,which has gotten worse over
time and has created pulmonary hypertension.
Does that mean she needs surgery?
- Yes.Unfortunately .....
- You okay?
If that child so much as looks like she's
going to die,i'm walking out of here.
I'll be performing a transcatheter
closure to repair the defect in the septum.
- That sounds dangerous.
- Is that dangerous?
That baby doesn't understand
a word she's saying.
All open-heart procedures have certain
risks,but this one looks fairly routine.
She was just saying that we're gonna fix the part
of your heart that pumps the blood to your lungs.
It should be a simple patch repair.
Uh,probably something easy to fix.
But a full midline sternotomy
incision may be required.
Okay,now she's just making stuff up.
The nurses have some
forms for you to sign.
okay.Oh,i like your socks.
thanks.They're for soccer.
I'm the best on my team.
Mom says it's bragging.
Dad says it's not.
- It's just the truth.
- You can't fight who you are.
If you're the best,you're the best.
When you fix my heart,how soon
will i be able to play soccer again?
I missed half the season already.
Well... Um,we'll... Have to... See.
Ah,cristina.
Did you tell her about the ring?
Oh,i don't want to talk
about your stupid ring.
Good.Don't.
Oh,you're not gonna do
a big thing,a||re you?
Like some big,romantic mcdreamy
thing?'Cause she'd hate that.
Well,she built a house of candles.
Yeah,for  you.She builtyou  a house of
candles...'Cause you like that sort of thing.
- She doesn't.
- Okay,thanks.
How is it?The journal.Is
it gross?Were they naked?
No,not yet.
It's kind of,um...
Hot,actually,but,like,uh,chastely hot.
It's all stolen glances
and loaded exchanges.
The thing reads like a
victorian romance novel.
Oh,that's good.Chaste is good.
I'll let you know when they do it.
Dr. Gary ballard,please report
to the information desk.
She said a thing about babies-- you
know,like babies were a totally ordinary idea.
She's not afraid.She's ready.
When are you gonna do it?
- Do what?
- Shepherd's proposing.
No kidding?
- Outstanding.
- yeah,thank you.
Uh,h-how are you gonna do it?
I don't know.I just decided.
Morning.Sir.
Shepherd's proposing.
Congratulations.That's a big step.
Thank you very much.You just
gonna tell everybody now?
You need advice.Hunt,you
ever propose before?
Uh,sorry.I'm not the guy to ask.
When are you gonna do it?
Well,more importantly,how
am i gonna do it?
So what do you use,like
a twist drill for that?
Uh,no,not if you don't want
a partial parietal hematoma.
Good luck.
Ahh... Just don't
tell anybody else,okay?
I thought i could trust you.
Of course you can trust me.
We got the short end of
the stick with this case.
Quit laughing.We're gonna get reamed.
Dudes,the patient can see you
giggling over here like schoolgirls.
- Enough wisecracks.
- Cracks.
- What's so funny?
- Sorry,sir.
These idiots were screwing around,and
i kinda got,uh... Sucked into it.
Enough.
Now if you children need a lesson in
professionalism,then come and see how it's done.
Mr. Kramer.
Your biplane abdominal
radiographs show a foreign body.
We will perform a sigmoidoscopy and
then proceed with manual extraction.
You'll get it out?
Oh,we'll get it out.
- Just hold it.
- That is the third time.
What's the problem?
- I-- she can't find a vein,and she's
poking me like i'm her needlepoint.
Look,what is wrong with you people?Didn't
you practice this on each other?
Look... All right,when you have a good
vein,it should feel bouncy,like this one.
Okay,now go in at an
angle,not at 90 degrees.Yeah.
Yeah,like that.Good.
Next time,she'll do it on you.
You know what,why
don't you run them both?
Listen up,you guys.
Before you run any more
procedures today,come see me first.
So... Clean bill of health from hunt.
You gonna get back on the horse,then?
Well,i wouldn't use the word "horse,"
but no.That's not gonna work out.
Things have changed.
I think i'm going to
have to break up with her.
You're what?What is
wrong with you?Why...
Sorry.I had to make sure
the patient's wife is stable.
She's hypertensive,and i think this surgery's
more stressful on her than it is on him.
Damn it.
There's a huge tear.
His clavicle fracture is
jutting into the artery.
Grey,hold this clamp.
I got this.I'll hold pressure.Page
hunt.Get him in here now.
No,they can't.
The patient's unstable.His subclavian's
bleeding out.They're paging dr. Hunt.
It doesn't look good.
Okay,thanks.
Oh,what'd they say?
Did they say it's going well or-- it's--it's
taking a little longer than-- than expected.
Okay.
But d-don't--don't worry,because
it--it's going great.
It is.Are you sure?
Yes,it--you know...  It's
good when they take their time.
You know,right now there is no reason to
believe that--that he's not gonna be just fine.
Okay.
Oh,thank you.
Hey,your pressure is way down.
Jen?Jen?
What's happening?
She's tamponading,her b.P.'S
crashed,and she has muffled heart sounds.
Oh,damn it.Okay,gloves.
Yang,betadine and get a local.
Stacy,sweetie,you're
gonna be all right,okay?
Don't worry.18-guage.
What are you doing?
Okay,lisa,you're gonna want
to,uh,turn around or leave.
You're not gonna want to watch this.
- Yang,keep the ultrasound over the effusion.
- Yeah,i got it.
Stacy,honey,you're gonna feel a little
pinch,and then a lot of pressure...
And then you're gonna
be all better,okay?
Here we go.
Good.Oh,good job,stacy.
Yeah,see?
It's all better.
Good job.
Good job,honey.
All better.
Her pulmonary pressures are high.
You're right.She's got cor pulmonale.
I'm moving up her surgery.Yang's
getting an o.R. Now.
I'll see you in there,dr. Bailey.
Let me know how it goes.
Great save,dr. Bailey.
I think you better stay.
I'm not scrubbing in on this one.
Bailey... You can handle this surgery.
Yeah,i can handle the surgery.
What i can't handle is feeling another
child slipping away right in front of me.
Mostly they don't slip
away,even the really sick ones.
Jackson was a special
case,and--and even he survived.
By the skin of his teeth.
But he survived.
Children are resilient,and
in all likelihood,
you're gonna open up this girl's
chest and fix something simple,
and then you're gonna hand
her back the rest of her life.
I'm telling you,bailey,you
want to be there for that.
Come on,come on,come on.Stabilize.
B.P.'S going up.
Going up.
Thank you.
Yep.Should be good to go.
Dr. Grey,jen harmon--
tell jen he's stable.
She's not.She had a seizure.
- A seizure?
- We got him,grey.
Go help her.
You're an idiot.
Excuse me?
You're an idiot.What is your problem?
He is proposing to her.
That makes little her his little sister,and
i can't sleep with any more of his sisters.
And she's young,and i'm her boss.
And i'm celibate.
What does that have to do with anything?
Celibacy is lonely.
Don't spend all your time
wondering what you are or--or--or
who you like or whether it's
right for you or wrong for you.
Just let yourself be happy,okay?
Before you find yourself
alone and celibate.
Does she really need a chest x-ray?
She's got the flu.
Say that after you've
ruled out pneumonia.
And be quick and efficient.
Keep a smile on your face,and make stupid,happy
small talk to keep them distracted and... Not panicky.
Okay.Should i do small talk now?
No.
Just tell me to lie still
and take a deep breath.
Okay,big breath in...
And then don't move.
So,uh,uh,how-- how
are you gonna do it?
Are you gonna,uh,go big,a
grand,romantic gesture?
Um... I-- i don't
know yet,chief.
I'm not sure that meredith's
a grand gesture kinda girl.
Oh,you want to do the grand gesture.
It's the opening pitch of your marriage.
It can determine the entire game.
You gotta go all out.
Now your plan should include flowers,candles,exotic
foods,live musicians and rowboat.
Skywriting is not out of the question.
- Now you gotta
go-- dr. Shepherd.
Yes.
Uh,uh,you got him.You
got him.Okay. Okay.
Um... What's up?
I need a neuro consult.
Okay.
Yeah,that's bet-- you
know,you better go.
Thanks,chief.
Okay.
Okay,okay.
How are we doing,mr. Kramer?
Oh,fantastic.
Good.
They didn't cover this in
the "what to expect" books.
They didn't say "expect seizures.
" i know.That's why we're
going to do an exam,okay?
Now i need you to look down for me.
Okay.
Ooh,what is that?
What?Um,dr. Grey.
Could you,uh,set up an m.R.I.
For mrs. Harmon,please,right now?
- But did you
see-- now,dr. Grey.
Okay.
Oh,you--you
saw something?
No,no,no.
No,i'm sorry.All right,can
you keep a secret?
You bet i can.
This is intended for dr. Grey.
It's supposed to be a surprise.
Oh,my god.And i almost blew it.
- Yeah.
- When are you gonna do it,today?
Oh,please do it today.
- Do it here so i can see.
No.I-i don't know.
No.I was told it's supposed
to be,like,a grand gesture.
Oh,well,rob proposed to
me in a supermarket aisle.
He said that was the place
he saw me for the first time.
So i said yes between the
cat food and the tampons.
That's romantic.
It was,actually.
We still have to do the m.R.I.,okay?
- Just to be safe.
- Okay.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Yes.
- Should i be scared?
- No.
Should i? No.
Eisenmenger's complex.
- Can it be repaired?
- Is it-- is it too far gone?
Children are resilient,yang.
- Nine times out of ten,you find something simple to
- fix...
What is it?
I can repair the v.S.D.,but this heart is finished.
This is one of the most diseased hearts i've ever seen.
Ecmo might hold her over,but without a heart-lung transplant,
she's going to die.
Dr. Bailey?Um,dr. Bailey?
dr. Bailey?It's okay,dr. Dixon.
I can take care of these sutures.
Her heart is too far gone.
There's far too much scar tissue to repair.
We have started her on i.V.Medications,
which she will need on a continuous basis.
For how long?How long does she--
until she can receive a transplant.
But... Months?
- Years,possibly.
- Years?
- S'll lay in a bed for years?
- I'm afraid so,yes.
Where's dr. Bailey gone?
You want to take narrow slices with the scan so you get a more comprehensive look.
What do you see?
Uh,i see... A crazy person taking expensive tests for no reason and,
oh,i see the chief finding out and expelling the crazy person,
and then,uh,i see,uh,joblessness,homelessness and depression.
Yeah,it does not look good,izzie.
It doesn't look good.
Somebody kick dr. O'malley out of the booth.
Hey,have you seen bailey?
No,but i have to talk to you.Derek is going crazy.
This morning i said something about having cute babies,and now ever since,
he's been acting weird and avoiding me and dropping conversations when i walk up.
I mean,he wants babies.He's always wanted babies.
Oh,he wants babies.
Maybe he just doesn't want my babies.
No,that--that's not it.
Yeah,because my babies will have alzheimer's and suicidal tendencies
and split ends.
Yeah,you might have something there.
No,i really don't think you do,though.
Who are you?
I'm jen.
How we doing?
We all set?
If--if you're gonna do it,do it soon.She's really freaking out.
Thank you.
They tried number nine?
Who does nine?
Personally,i'm a fan of five...
Seven,eight...
Well,pretty much 12 through 20.
i would try 15.
don't try 15.don't try 15.
i would try 16.
I've never done that before.
You'd try 16?
I would.
I totally would.
Um,don't do 16 too fast.
It can--you get hurt... Badly...
I've heard.
Do you know who likes a good 12?
Hey,you on call tonight?
Looks like it.You?
And you're saying if she misses even one dose of her medicine,that would be bad?
It would be fatal.
The drug needs to be administered at 3-minute intervals.
So she'll live in a hospital bed for years,you said.
No,no,there's another way.
There's a way she won't have to stay in the bed.
- With a diagnosis of pulmonary hypertension--
- ane girl needs a backpack.
- No,no--
- a backpack-- it has a portable pump
that will deliver her meds and allow her to play and go to school.
She can have a childhood until she gets her new heart.
This is something that we should have discussed privately earlier--
and she could leave the hospital?
Yes,she can.See,she has to wear the backpack at all times.
We will put you in a program,teach you how to administer the medications--
do you have a prettier one?
Oh,my god,dr. Bailey,thank you.
Dr. Dixon,thank you so much.Thank you so much.
Dr. Dixon... Oh-- thank you.
No! No! No! No! No.
Dr. Dixon. What--what can i do?How can i help?
You can observe protocol,and i was getting to that option,but it was too much.
It was just too--  too much yelling,too much touching,too much...
Okay,um...
- Then i'll leave you alone to,uh--
- no,no.
I don't need alone.I need pressure.
- I...
- I need my nervous system suppressed.
I need constant,deep...
Tight pressure across large areas of my body.
I need you to hold me.I need you ...
Um-- tight.Tight.Tight.Tightly.
Tighter.
You're a very tiny person.
I need a bigger per-- person than you.
Should i...
Oh,what--what can i do?
Uh,get over here and hug on dr. Dixon.
I was thinking more like a shot of thorazine.
Get over here.
Come.H--just... Yeah.
Good.
An aneurysm?A brain aneurysm?
All of your symptoms-- forgetfulness,dizziness,chronic headaches--
can all be associated with pregnancy.
The only reason we discovered yours is because of the seizure.
So what,you said you can-- you can fix it?
You can take it out?
We'll do it first thing in the morning,after rob's recovered from the complications with his surgery.
Complications?Wait,what?
You said--you said it was fine.
You said he was okay.You lied to me?
I'm--i'm sorry.I just-- i didn't want to worry you until i knew,and he's fine.
And you'll be fine,too.
But it could burst,right?
Jen,you  have  to stay calm.
You just told me there's a time bomb in my head.
I  promise  you that i'm not gonna stay calm.
Cows are squeezed tightly in a chute before they're slaughtered.
The chute applies intense pressure,resulting in decreased pulse rate,metabolic rate and muscle tone.
It calms them down.
The same principles apply to people like me.
A hugging machine is used to relax the sympathetic nervous system.
It slows the heart.
This is good.Th--
it's working.
- Oh,so we can stop now?
- No.
Almost there,mr. Kramer.Hold on.There.Got it.
Oh,my god.
Oh,thank you.
Never again will i try to spice things up.I'm not spicing anything up.
Well,you tried to step it up.
Anything above number five deserves props.
Sounds to me like you're doing pretty good.
You're together,you're both bending over backwards to find new ways to...
Make each other happy.
You take a step back,you'll realize that you're doing just fine.
"bending over backwards.
" you can let me go now.
You can let me go now.
Oh,sorry.
Dr. Stevens,i have the blood test results.
What is it?
Well,you're anemic.Um--
anemic?
Oh,my god.
Do you realize what you just did?
Your face said i was going to die not "go get a hamburger.
- " well,see,i-i--
- that's part of patient care,controlling your face.
I-i just w-- anemic.
This is fine.
This is no big deal.It's,like,nothing.
How's mrs.What's-her-name?
That's not good,is it?
Yeah.No.
Um... Her l.D.H. Is off the charts.
Oh,what is it?Is it--is it cancer?
Consult oncology.Start a workup.
It's okay.We'll tell her together.
Thank you.
- I don't want to keep secrets.
- Sorry?
I've been keeping secrets all day a-about surgeries and rings and--and you.
And--and that secret,the--the--the you secret,it's giving me high blood pressure.
And i-i don't want that secret.
We're having... A relationship.
And if we are,if we're in a relationship,then i need to be in it in front of my sister
and derek shepherd.
If we can't do that,then i can't do this.
- what's going on?
- Sorry.
- What happened?
- I'm sorry,i can't.
- Just leave--leave me alone.
- You're shaking.
I... Saw someone-- someone i knew.
I can't do this.I can't.Just...
Please go away.
Okay,it's--it's all right.
- It's okay.
- No,no.I don't want this.
I don't want this.I don't want this.
- I can't do this now.
- To relax--to relax your sympathetic nervous system.
It'll decrease your metabolic rate.
You will feel more panicked at first.
You'll try to resist it.You'll try to resist it.
- I don't want this.
- But eventually you will feel your pulse rate slow.
- You'll feel your pulse rate slow.
Your breath will come easier.
I'm sorry for my outburst.
I should've spoken to you first.
It was inappropriate,but i've come to expect it from pediatric surgeons,
always breaking protocol.
But i'm not a pediatric surgeon.
I've landed a few peds surg cases recently,
but i'm getting back to general surgery the first chance i get.
You touch the child whenever you speak with her,
you explain conditions to the child,
not just the parents,and you react to the patient as if it was your own child,
and you break protocol which is inappropriate,except in the case of pediatric surgery,
where protocols are constantly evolving.
You are not a general surgeon.
You're a pediatric surgeon
Um,did you eat?
- Let me change.I'll come with you.
- No,no,no.I can't.
I've--i have to,um... Work.
Okay,listen,you have been acting like a basket case
ever since i dropped that stupid little comment about babies.
And i'm glad i dropped it,because if you don't babies or you don't want babies with me and my crappy d.N.A.
,just say so.
You don't have to avoid me,and you don't have to make up lame excuses about work.
Meredith,i want your crappy babies.
you do?
- All of 'em.
- Okay.
- Do you want to eat?
- No.
I-i have--i gotta-- i have to work.
Oh,my god.
Did you use a bedazzler?
Circa 1986.
as seen on tv.
Dixon's right,you know?
You do belong in peds surgery.
My own baby almost died last year.
The doctors in this hospital-- my friends-- they all worked to save his life.
And i stood outside the room,feeling so...
Useless,so pointless and helpless,
like... I was losing everything in the world.
And when he didn't die,see,i knew i didn't want to be anywhere near that feeling again.
So i think that makes me pretty unsuitable for pediatric surgery.
I'd say...
That makes you uniquely qualified.
- You mind if i sit here?
- No,no.I'm just...
Overthinking.
You think he'll tell him?
If he's not an idiot.
Are you okay?
I don't... I'm fine.
Derek is a--
what are you doing?
I don't know.I just...
- staying here.
- Okay.
- Good night.
- Uh,he's planning to propose.
Wh-what?
The chief.
Your mother writes he,uh,told her he would leave adele and
come backand get on one knee and propose,but...
I don't think he ever did.
That's sad.
Is it?
Or romantic.
It seems we have    no control whatsoever...
Over our own hearts.
- hey
- Ortho,right?
- Yeah,right.
Hi.I'm arizona robbins.
Peds surgery.
I've seen you at the hospital.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah,no.
- I'm... Fine.
- People talk.
Where we work,they talk... A lot.
So for the sake of being honest,i-i think i should tell you that
i know things about you,because people talk.
You mean...
Terrific.
It is,actually... The talk.
People really like you over there.
They--they respect you and they're concerned and interested.
They really like you.
Some of them...  Really  like you.
You just--you look upset.
And i--and i thought that you should know that the talk is good.
And when you're not upset,when you're over...
Being upset...
There will be people lining up for you.
You want to give me some names?
Conditions can change    without warning.
I think you'll know.
Romance can make    the heart pound...
Just like panic can...
This is stupid.
- She's gonna hate this.
- What,the flowers?Girls love this crap.
It's a clich?
I'm a clich?
Clich?Became clich?
For a reason.
Because they worked.
It's great,isn't it,when you feel so strongly for someone,
and it's... It's not just about the sex?
It is...
It's true.
You should not talk like that.
Yeah,you're right.
Well,you're all set here.I'm gonna leave you to it.
Thanks.
Congratulations.
And panic...
Addison?
Can make it stop cold    in your chest.
What happened?
It's no wonder    doctors spend so much time   trying to keep the heart stable...
To keep it slow...
Steady...
Regular...
To stop the heart from pounding out of your chest...
From the dread    of something terrible...
Or the anticipation...
Of something else entirely.
=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: YTET- °îµÂÖí ÏûÉùÄä¼£
Greys Anatomy
Season 5 Episode 14
www.tvsubtitles.net