It's impossible to describe the panic
that comes over you when you're a surgeon
and your pager goes off
in the middle of the night.
Your heart starts to race.
Please don't be mine. Don't be mine.
Your mind freezes.
Your fingers go numb.
Not mine.
Wake up.
- I'm up.
- They're paging you.
You're invested.
I'm sleeping!
They're someone's mom, someone's dad,
someone's kid, and now it's on you,
because that someone's
life now in your hands.
Robbins, Karev's with
your patient in trauma two.
Torres, come with me. We
have a 15-year-old female.
She fell off the roof of her
house. Now I think that we should...
She's gonna be okay right?
Please, I just need to
know. Is she gonna be okay?
And this is her mother.
Mrs. Boyd, I need to bring Dr.
Torres up to speed right now, okay?
She's never been in any accident before.
She's never even broken any bones.
Oh, you paged me here at 4:00
a.m. for a couple of broken bones?
More like 50.
As surgeons, we're always
invested in our patients.
Laura Young, 30 weeks
pregnant. Car accident.
Head CT showed a subdural.
Shepherd's coming in.
Baby's in distress. O.B'S on its way.
Oh, it hurts. It really hurts.
Okay, wait. Hold on. Stop.
- Move the wand up.
- What?
Okay, baby's brain is hemorrhaging.
She needs a crash "c" while
shepherd handles the bleed.
Get ready to grab a
railand start running.
But when your patient's a child...
- Get another unit of packed cells, meet me in the O.R.
- Right away.
You're not just invested...
We need the O.R.
You're responsible...
Well, we need it, too.
We're already our way.
There's only one O.R
prepped this time of night.
Which is why we need it.
Mine's got a subduraro.
50 broken bones.
Stroke in the womb!
All right, uh, get
another O.R. ready now.
Responsible for whether or not
that child survives, has a future.
And that's enough to terrify anyone.
-=bbs. sfileydy.
com/bbs=-Proudly Presents
com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-Ring °îµÂÖí
corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com
What's her status?
Mom's heart rate and, uh,
BP has been fluctuating,
but she's ready for you.
All right, let's prep
her for a craniotomy.
Apgar's only 4. We need
to get to the nicu now.
All right, drain's in a good position.
Yeah, she's breathing over the vent.
Maybe we should consider extubating her?
Yeah, but watch for apneic episodes,
and keep an eye out for her CBC.
There's still too much
blood draining from her head.
What time is it, Karev?
Uh, half past 8:00.
Half past 8:00.
I've already beenwake for 5 hours,
and my day hasn't even started.
Rough way to start your morning.
A stroke before you're even
born... rough way to start a life.
Hey, I brought you some coffee.
Oh, you already have one.
Oh, no. I want your
coffee. I need your coffee.
Okay, when you see Cristina,
she is gonna be mad.
She's gonna be mad at me for not
paging her in here last night,
possibly mad at you for
not waking her up either.
Now I am handling
this. Do not engage her.
Do not provoke her. Simply
ignore her, all right?
Oh, that's your plan... ignore
the scalpel-hungry animal?
Yep, until I come up
with something better.
Okay, I know this is the first time on
a Peds rotation with me for some of you.
Not for others.
But I wanted you to understand that
I run my Peds unit a little
differently than you may be used to.
This is not general
surgery in miniature.
These are the tiny
humans. These are children.
They believe in magic.
They play pretend. There is
fairy dust in their I.V. bags.
They hope and they cross their
fingers and they make wishes.
And that makes them more
resilient than adults.
They recover faster,
survive worse. They believe.
In Peds, we have... miracles and magic.
In Peds, anything is possible.
Morning, Dr. Robbins.
Good morning, Dr. Wallace.
I see that you've already introduced
yourself to Mr. And Mrs. Boydyes.
Yes, reminds me of Hillary at that age.
Such an overachier.
Dr. Yang, why don't you present?
Excuse me, little... doctor boy.
Uh, Hillary boyd, 15 years old,
fell off the roof of her house.
52 acute fractures were diagnosed
when she was admitted last night.
An intricate and extremely challenging
OIF surgery was performed by Dr. Torres
and Dr. Hunt this morning before rounds.
Thank you, Dr. Yang.
If she fares well enough today,
I'd like to go in tomorrow to repair
her subtrochanteric fracture next.
Can anyone tell me the proper dosage
of ceftriaxone for a pediatric patient?
50 milligrams per kilogram per day.
And, Dr. Wallace, can you tell me the proper
dose for this patient if she were 42 kilograms?
2.1 grams per day... if
you carry the decimal.
Okay, who's presenting?
I am, Dr. Robbins.
Proceed.
Wallace Anderson...
10 years old... almost 11...
Been here for 7 months. In and
out over the past two years.
Suffers from short gut syndrome, which
means he can't properly absorb nutrition.
Exactly. Dr. Percy?
Uh, 15 intestinal surgeries to date,
plus a bowel lengthening
procedure, which helped for a while,
but recently, he's had to go
back to being fed through TPN.
How'd he do this morning?
We covered some pretty
advanced algebraic conversions.
Dr. Robbins helps me with my math and
science homework by letting me go on rounds.
- Fascinating.
- We try to keep his life as normal we can,
even living in a hospital.
But I can skip my homework on
Friday, right, since it's my birthday?
Since it's your birthday.
What about Dr. Robbins?
It is her birthday, too.
I'm afraid I can't skip
my homework, Wallace,
but I can come celebrate
with you like I promised.
Dr. Robbins.
We've requested a meeting later with Chief Wwebber
and a representative from the hospital board.
And we'd like you there, too.
Alright.
So they didn't give you any indication
as to what this meeting was about?
You know as much as I do.
You treated their son, right?
Well, you better pray that you
didn't do something to piss them off.
God knows that this hospital can't
afford another misstep right now.
It's a pleasure to see you again, paul.
Bethany, you look lovely.
We didn't think Wallace
would see his 9th birthday,
let alone his 10th.
And now this week, his 11th.
Which is why we'd like to offer Seattle
Grace Mercy West's Peds program a gift
of $25 million.
$25 million?
Half to go to research to continue
searching for a cure for Wallace's condition,
and half to the hospital itself.
I... um... I mean...
$25 million?
Happy birthday, Arizona.
I always knew that Wallace's
parents were wealthy,
but not $25-million wealthy.
I mean, that's "libraries
named after you" kind of money,
"saved babies in Africa and has dinner
at the White House regularly" type money.
People don't give me that kind of money.
You have an unfair advantage.
You work with children.
Oatmeal, side of fruit,
wheat toast, hold the butter.
Thank you.
You know what? That money is gonna make
such a difference for so many patients.
It's... it's really amazing.
Maybe I should start doing
more cleft-palate kids.
Everyone's a sucker for those.
Cheese omelet, extra butter,
cinnamon toast, crispy bacon.
Mine!
$25 million is pretty cool, right?
Best birthday gift ever.
Birthday gift?
Well, 'c... cause the money's a gift.
I mean, technically it's for
the hospital, not Arizona,
but since your birthday's on Friday...
How does Little Grey know
about your birthday and I don't?
Birthdays are just days
like any other days.
I don't like them. Don't
celebrate them. No big deal.
$25 million? That's a big deal.
Crap. I'm gonna be late.
I will see you there.
Okay, she's downplaying it, right?
I'm her girlfriend. I have to do
something for her birthday, right?
- Yes.
- No.
Of course you do.
A... a surprise party.
Bad idea.
Surprise parties are
hostile. They're dark.
People jump out and scream at you.
They never come to any good.
Karev.
Good morning, chief.
Uh, when you're free, come find me.
What's that all about?
He fired me.
And I refused to be fired.
So I say hello to him every
morning, and he says not a word.
Sounds familiar.
You haven't heard from stevens?
Not a word.
They'll come around
when they come around.
Chief, you need me?
Uh, I wish I didn't have to
saddle you with this, Karev, but...
What is all this?
As Stevens left no forwarding address,
and as you are officially
her next of kin,
this is her unpaid balance
of her medical bills.
Unpaid balance? I... I don't get it.
We work here at the hospital.
Ah, and insurance doesn't
take care of everything.
I'm sorry, but accounting's been
pressuring me since the merger,
and I can't ignore it any longer.
What's yours in for?
Mm, delivered her yesterday.
Stroked out at 10 weeks premature.
Yours?
Born with its insides on the outside.
Two days post-op. Resilient little guy.
More bleeding overnight.
Should we try FFP?
At this point, we should try anything.
Get me a repeat MRI.
And page me if she becomes bradycardic
or starts having apnea spells.
I'll be on rounds.
Um, I was picking up some labs from Dr.
Bailey, and I saw that you had these waiting.
Thought I'd bring 'em
by, save you the trip.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
I overheard a little bit of
your conversation with the chief.
I'm trying to save a baby
here. Get outta my face.
Got it.
Is he still sleeping?
No.
He had a bad night.
I can still go on rounds. I feel better.
Just give me a second.
You know what? How about if
you just take a rest for now.
And then you can join me
for evening rounds instead?
He listens o youmore than he does to me.
Well, yeah. She's a doctor, mom.
And you're just... well, a mom.
Well, how about you close your eyes
and you let me do what moms do, okay?
Bad dreams, bad dreams, go away.
Good dreams, good dreams, here to stay.
You have to do it three
times for it to work.
One more.
I want you to repeat his chemistries
and get an abdominal series.
He's had bad nights before, but I want to
make sure that we're not missing anything.
How's she doing?
Touch and go.
- How's the baby?
- Same.
Any news from the family?
No, I left a message.
Haven't heard back yet.
ICP is elevated.
BP won't stabilize.
Uh, 100 mics of fentanyl, please.
Laura?
Laura, can you hear me?
My baby. Where's my baby?
She's struggling, but she's hanging on.
Can I see her?
I'm sorry. No. You're
too unstable to move.
So is the baby.
I just want to hold her.
Please. I want to hold my baby.
Laura, I need you to stay
calm, okay? Laura, just...
What if she dies before
I get to hold her?
She can't. She can't go before
she's ever even been held.
It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
Push 10 of diazepam and give me
some supplemental 0-2, please.
Crap. 911. It's her baby.
She's bradying downd she lost access.
I'll start C-pap.
Dr. Robbins.
Not right now.
I think you're gonna want to see this.
It's the x-rays on Wallace Anderson.
All right, show me.
See? He has dilated loops of bowel.
All right, flip.
Flip.
Damn it. Damn it.
He has another bowel obstruction,
and he's not compensating. Okay...
I've got this. Go.
A nurse just checked that.
Yeah, a nurse checked
it, I'm gonna check it,
and three other people in the O.R.
are gonna check it. We're thorough.
Honey, please let them do their jobs.
Uh, Mr. and Mrs. Boyd.
We thought that you should know that
Hillary's tox screens from yesterday
show signs psilocybin
in her bloodstream.
What does that mean?
Well, it means that when she
fell from the roof, she was, uh...
Shrooming.
Magic mushrooms.
What?
Hillary?
Mushrooms?
Oh, come on. Can
everybody please chill out?
What in God' names were you thinking?
You know, I can't believe...
You're a disappointment, young
lady, a big, big, disappointment.
Dad, please. Okay, the last
thing I am is a disappointment.
I get straight A's. I'm on honor roll.
I run the student council.
I basically am the school paper, and
I tutor kids with reading problems.
I'm every parent's dream
come true, including yours.
I was exploring the bounds of my
consciousness with the help of a mushroom.
I made a calculated risk going
on that roof. Falling off?
Well, that was a low-probability event,
and even low-probability
events occasionally occur,
and this one did.
So, yeah, you're bummed I miscalculated
'cause it reminds you of your own fallibility.
I'm bummed, too.
Let's just leave it at that.
Cap refill is five
seconds. Push one of epi.
It's not working. Heart
rate's down to the 60s.
Starting compressions.
Could I help?
Doubt it.
At this rate, this kid's not
gonna last more than an hour.
She's only 30 weeks.
Pretty young to survive.
So what, you're just gonna
stand there and watch her die?
Mm, pretty much.
That sucks.
It is what it is. It's protocol.
Eping drives me nuts.
- Look, I mean...
- The kid's gonna die.
Deal with it or get out.
Hey there, girl.
I got you.
It's okay.
You're not alone. No,
you're not. You're not alone.
Wait. Hold on.
Are you saying you can't do more
surgery on him, or you won't?
It's not a question of if I can.
It's whether or not I should.
In my opinion, Wallace isn't strong
enough to handle another operation.
But with surgery, how
long would he have then?
I... I'm not confident that
he'll even make it ofthe table.
But if he did, how long?
I strongly advise against...
How long?
Maybe two months. I...
I'm s... I'm sorry.
But the moment that we've
been fighting for two years...
It's here.
So you need to prepare yourselves
and you need to prepare Wallace.
You think I've been pouring all
this money into research so that
you could find a cure
for some other kid?
- Mr. Anderson...
- No. You have to do this surgery.
Mr. Anderson, I'm...
You buy our son two more months.
You buy him more time so
that we can buy him a cure.
I'm sorry.
Robbins.
These aren't people who hear the word no
if they want surgery for their son,
they'll get surgery for their son,
whether or not you're the one to do it.
You've been with this boy since day one.
I believe you can do this successfully.
Don't walk away now unless you know
beyond a shadow of a doubt that you can't.
The surgery is a bad idea, chief.
But is it impossible? In your hands...
Is it impossible?
Okay, I'll do it.
I'll try.
Is that the preemie?
Oh, yeah. I was just, uh...
Well, I tried everything.
I just thought maybe somebody should
hold her before, you know, she...
Kangaroo.
What?
The way you're holding the baby,
it's called a kangaroo hold.
Uh, there's been cases where the
kangaroo has helped babies thrive.
But look, Karev, look at
the numbers. Look at this.
Heart rate's going up.
Yeah, it is, and her
temperature is normal.
Karev, you may have just kick-started
this baby's entire system.
Just by holding her?
Take off your shirt.
What? No. Take off your shirt.
No, no. Just...
The kangaroo hold, it's most effective
when there's skin-on-skin contact.
It's usually the mom, but, you
know, you're gonna have to do.
I'm not kidding. Take off your shirt.
Well, it looks like you used pretty much
every piece of hardware in the hospital.
Yeah, it makes you think twice
about shrooming on a roof.
And the mouth on this one? If I
talked to my parents like that...
Oh, my father would've...
Oh, you don't even want tknow.
I had perfect grades, perfect record,
and I said whatever I
wanted, did whatever I wanted.
My parents couldn't do a thing about it.
Want to hear about my childhood?
No? Okay. I'll just, uh, think
about it quietly in my own head.
All right, nailst in, everything's
tight. Let's take a look.
Fantastic.
End-tidal Co2 just
dropped from 34 to 22.
Oh, come on. Give me
a break here, Hillary.
She has a new murmur.
There's an air embolus in her heart.
All right, flood the field with saline.
Give me the bone wax. Page
cardio and set up a chest tray.
And put her in trendelenburg.
I can... I can aspirate it.
No, no, we wait for cardio
and we try to find the source.
No, it'll take me 30 seconds.
It might take cardio
half an hour to get here.
- Dr. Yang...
- I've done this before.
I know what I'm doing. She
could arrest at any moment.
Dr. Yang, no. End of discussion.
See?I t's the
skin-to-skin contact.
The baby can feel your warmth better,
sense your heartbeat better. See that?
The baby's own heart is
picking up in response.
Karev, what are you doing?
He's saving a baby's life, that's what.
Dr. Bailey, I...
Oh, no shirt. He's wearing no shirt.
Have you started to lactate yet?
Bailey made me.
Is this the room for the calendar
shoot? I was told it was downstairs.
Yeah, all right. That's enough.
Everybody out. Let Karev do
what he's doing in private.
What is he doing exactly?
Out. Out.
This is ridiculous. You're
wasting all this time down here,
when we should be dealing with
the heart problem directly.
We are following protocol.
Cardio is on its way, and we can find
the source of the embolus this way.
Screw it.
Dr. Yang, the patient is not coding,
and you are not qualified to do this.
Opening the left chest.
Oh, Yang, really?
- Turn on e fluoro.
- Dr. Yang.
Will someone please step on the fluoro?
Or do you want me to go in blind?
Dr. Yang, put down that scalpel!
Thank you.
Cristina!
Scissors.
Cristina
Cristina! Cardio's here, Yang.
It's done. I'm done.
Air embolus out.
The patient was crashing.
She was not crashing.
It was a procedure I've done before.
- I handled it, and she's fine
- Yeah, but what if she wasn't?
You could've lacerateder heart or cut the
phrenic nerve. She could've died on that table.
What then? It would've
been your license.
All so you could prove what exactly?
Well, I did it to stabilize the patient.
You were just watchingher vitals drop.
Waiting for a C.T. surgeon who would've been
able to take a more minimally invasive approach.
I could've done a thoracotomy myself
if I had thought it was indicated.
I've been around the
block once or twice.
You know, I kinda...
I kinda know what i'ing.
I'm aware of that. I was just...
You just thought ever...
You just thought... you just thought
everything would be better if you took charge.
And you know I have to report
this to the chief, right?
At a time when he is scouring
this place for people to fire.
Well, he's not gonna fire me.
Oh, r... of course not, 'cause
you're... you're invincible.
No, he's not gonna fire me because the last time that I did
an open thoracotomy for an embolus was with him in his O.R.
Only he was giving me words of
encouragement, not screaming in my ear.
For the record? You
rocked that in there.
Hunt's just jealous he
didn't do it himself.
Shut up.
Okay, you won't believe what
just happened in surgery with...
You okay?
Tell me I'm great.
- What?
- I need for you to tell me that I'm great.
You're great.
I mean really tell me, because I'm
about to go in on a surgery right now
that I'm not sure I should be going in
on, and I can't think like that, right?
I can't go into the O.R.
feeling like this. So...
I need you to tell me I'm great,
and make me... make me hear it.
You are great.
You... are... great.
Thank you.
Hey there. You ready to go?
I was gonna take you to the O.R. myself.
I've been here a while now, Dr. Robbins.
And... I've seen kids
go home and go away.
Like Evan... the kid from down
the hall with asthma last month.
He died the day before he
was supposed to be discharged.
- You're not Evan.
- And Chloe... the heart girl?
She was here for three
weeks before she died.
No one says you're gonna die.
I've been here for seven months.
I've been here the longest of
anyone on the floor, by double.
- Wallace...
- They say it's like going to sleep.
And maybe it is.
But what if I go to sleep,
and I have nightmares?
More traction, please. Damn it.
The mesentery's really friable.
Percy, a little help on the suction.
This is not a good idea.
This surgery... not a good idea.
Could we get a washcloth
for Dr. Robbins, please?
- No, it's fine.
- Just take a moment.
Thank you.
Pick ups, please.
I left you messages.
I'm sorry. I was in surgery.
There were complications.
I don't care, okay ?I operated on
Wallace tonight even when I knew better.
And I keep retracing every step, every
suture, and I keep going over it and over it...
- He didn't make it?
- He did.
He's in recovery. That's not the point.
What I needed from you tonight
was a little support for once.
- And you weren't here.
- Okay, you're scared, and so you're picking a fight.
- You get that, yeah?
- Yeah. Yeah. Fine. Whatever.
But I have helped you
through crisis after crisis.
And once I thought that I could come
here tonight, and I could get something...
- Let it go already. It's done.
- I have every right to be mad, Cristina.
You would've never pulled a stunt
like that with another attending.
I seem to recall Callie was there.
- Still didt stop me.
- Okay, guys, not now.
You took advantage of me and you
took advantage of our relationship.
Oh, please. The kid was dying.
Wait. What kid? What happened?
- Oh, so you didn't hear?
- No. , I didn't.
Cristina... she performed an unauthorized
and unnecessary thoracotomy against my orders.
She what?
I saved the patient's life.
Wait. Okay, so you were
there, and you didn't tell me?
I was going to, but you were
all, "tell me I'm great."
So... Oh, so it's my fault
that Yang went rogue on a child?
No... no, you know what? It
wasn't rogue. It was brilliant.
No, it wasn't.
You know, I... I'm done.
You got lucky today, Cristina.
And you may think that you can
get away with whatever you want,
but I am telling you, one of these
days, that luck's gonna run out.
Look... Wh... oh, okay.
So you're leaving, too?
Yes, because I have a patient.
Bitches.
All right, start an epI drip now.
More irrigation.
Just keep it coming.
Give me a babcock clamp.
Clamp.
Damn it.
Can somebody get me more light?
Pressure's dropping to 68 over 40.
Pulse is racing.
Come on, Wallace.
What the hell happened
to the Anderson boy?
He's in septic shock.
His body was too unstable to handle the
surgery, which is what I said in the first place.
- Well, maybe I can help.
- No!No, you can't.
Because as long as you're standing
there breathing over my shoulder,
I feel like I'm operating on a stack of
dollar bills... $25-million-dollar bills...
and what I need to be invested
in right now is this kid.
So please get the hell out of my O.R.!
More suction now.
How'd it go?
Damn it.
I'll let them know you
did everything you could.
Wait, Dr. Robbins, w... don't we have to tell
the parents, let them know that he didn't make it?
- No.
- What do you mean, no?
I mean no.
I will not be speaking
to Wallace's parents.
Mr. Jennings and the chief will
take care of that formality,
because as far as they're concerned and as far as the
Andersons will be concerned, I just killed their son.
I'm a liability, because if they
were to ask me, the truth is,
I would tell them that I did just kill their
son, and they should sue, and I am responsible.
But that's not in the best
interests of the hospital.
Am I close?
Yeah, I think we're on the same page.
My luck will run out.
It has nothing to do with luck.
He's being an ass.
You know what? I rocked that embolus.
- What?
- He cares about you.
- So?
So maybe he's a little bit right.
I get it.
I mean, I'm dying to get out of this bed and cut,
but you did an unauthorized procedure in an O.R.
I mean, you're an amazing surgeon, but if anything
had gone wrong, that would've been your career.
I mean, he cares about your career.
He's in love with you.
I hate...
married, happy you.
Go to work, and don't cut
anybody open without permission.
You shoulda seen Yang in that surgery.
I mean, she was fearless.
And you are hopeless. She's
completely out of your league.
Oh, I'm hopeless, huh?
I'm just... stupid.
He's married, and have I mentioned, a total
ass to pretty much everyone at all times?
Karev?
Did you stay here all night?
Uh, yeah. I... I guess I did.
Go home, get some rest. The
nurse will take over for you.
No. Uh, I... I'm okay.
I'm... I'm good here.
Well, you'd be good
in Peds, you know that?
You get invested. You
have good instincts.
You stick to your instincts.
You'd be good in Peds, Karev.
Yeah, I know. They, uh, say
I can have visitors tomorrow.
Cool. And, um, do you have anloopies?
Or whatever you have.
They only have me on 2
milligrams of morphine at a time.
I know. How lame is that? It's just...
Hey, little pusher girl.
I'm Hillary's doctor. And
now I have Hillary's phone.
So I'm gonna give this
number to the police.
- How lame is that?
- What the hell?
Okay. Uh, I know you think you can do
anything and say anything and handle anything.
And that's, you know, almost
true, except for the fact
that you fell off a roof 'cause you were so
high that you, what, you thought you could fly?
In surgery, you almost
died of a heart complication
because your body is so strung out from all the crap you've
been putting in it that it almost shut down completely.
Okay, that doesn't make you
smarter than everyone else.
It makes you an idiot.
The only reason why you're alive is...
you know, is 'cause you're lucky.
So just, you know, grow up.
Surprise! Happy...
I... I... um... I... I...
Told ya.
Hey, in retrospect, I realize now, that surprises
parties are hostile and this was a bad idea.
Please stop crying. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about the party.
Wallace died.
And he's supposed to be turning 11 today,
and instead, he's lying in a morgue.
Oh... God.
No, um... I'm... I'm sorry. I'm
sorry I... I can't... I can't stay.
No, it's okay. It's okay. I'll take
care of it. You don't have tstay.
Just... I understand. We're all
surgeons. Everyone will understand. I...
- Okay.
- Just go.
Might as well take advantage, huh?
What?
The party's a dud, but at
least there's free booze, right?
Right.
Go ahead and gloat.
Surprise parties never come to any good.
I think this party speaks for itself.
I don't get it.
You know, the best birthday of my life was
the surprise party that my parents threw.
I... I... I loved it so much.
How old were you at this party?
7.
Like I said, it speaks for itself.
If there's... if there's anything that
we can get for you, uh, help you with,
please just... just, uh, let us know.
I... I'd be more than happy to oversee any
packing that you need done from his room.
I've already arranged for a car if...
it's ready to take you home anytime.
Arizona.
Dr. Robbins, this is
a very sensitive time.
Let her be.
- Excuse me?
- I said...
Let her be.
It just doesn't feel real...
any of it. It just... it
just doesn't feel real.
Bethany, would you like to see him?
I have to admit, I'm impressed.
I never would've pegged you
for the babysitting type.
Are you heading home?
No, I got the baby.
Well, I'm sure somebody
else could take a shift.
- Do you want me to...
- I can't leave, okay?
Are you really so messed up that you
can't let one person be nice to you, ever?
I can't go. I can't go home. I
can't get Izzie to call me back.
She's... gone, could
be dead for all I know.
She left me with a $200, 000
medical bill, and I... I...
I can't do anything about it...
about any of it.
BuI can sit here and
I can hold this baby.
That I can do.
Then I'll sit here with
you for a little while.
Yang.
Doctor... can I Cristina
you or are we not there yet?
That's a no. Okay.
Dr. Yang, let me just tell you that
that was incredibly hot in the O.R.
Yesterday. Very deeply hot.
It was hot. You were hot.
Uh, you're drunk and you're in my room.
I... am, in fact, inebriated.
But that's legal, you know?
And even if I wasn't, you're the rule breaker,
which I think we established in surgery.
Really, you think that was hot?
Would it be really, really
bad if I just... you know,
'cause of the whole embolus
thing and you in general...
could I just...
Uh, no. I'm involved.
I'm involved.
Time to meet your mommy.
She's so beautiful.
They say, the bigger your
investment the bigger your return.
Surgery yesterday?
It wasn't just...
it was me.
- Can't you see that?
- See what?
See what? I... I can't just
ignore what happened, Cristina.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Look, I know, um... I
know I overstepped, so...
come home with me.
Please.
But you have to be
willing to take a chance.
Okay.
Bad dreams, bad dreams, go away.
Good dreams, good dreams, here to stay.
Good dreams, good dreams,
here to stay... stay.
You have to do it three times
for it... for it to work.
I know. She is the reason...
We will stil be giving Seattle
Grace Mercy West $25 million,
not because of you or your ass kissing.
It's because of her... her.
You have to understand...
You might lose it all.
The chief still won't talk to me.
Oh, he will.
When did you become such an optimist?
This is married, happy me.
Can we, uh...
Are you okay to...
Yes, we can. But if
you take that chance...
- Are you healed?
- I'm healed.
If you invest wisely...
the payoff might just surprise you.
I'm awake. I'm aw... um, see?
I'm... I'm totally awake.
I'm... there's hats and gifts and...
and... and doughnuts and lingerie.
Really?
I love you.
You do?
I do.
I love you, too.
-=bbs. sfileydy.
com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-ring °îµÂÖí
corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com