Previously on Grey's Anatomy...
Alex, please tell me that you
don't live with Meredith Grey.
The more available he gets,
the more I pull away.
I'm used to being number one.
I will help you.
We'll be like a team.
Dr. Hahn has agreed to become
our new head of cardiothoracic surgery.
Lookin'forward to it, Dr. Yang.
Ah, good morning.
Trout for breakfast...
Again.
Tonight we will have hot,
perfect sex.
I'm exhausted.
Maybe tonight's not the perfect night.
Before we were doctors,
we were med students.
Which meant we spent a lot
of time studying chemistry.
- That was...
- Aerobic.
- Aerobic bad?
- No.
Why, do you think it was bad?
- Okay.
No, I mean, obviously
we both were nervous.
Well, yeah, we've been,
you know, waiting for so long.
It was like...
- It better be good.
- No, better be worth it.
That's a lot of pressure.
Yeah.
- Let's just do it again.
- Let's get right back on that horse.
Organic chemistry, biochemistry...
We learned it all.
What's new with you?
I saw my half sister half naked.
- What's new with you?
- I had dinner and a movie...
With the chief.
You could stay.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna go.
Leave you wanting more and all of that.
But when you're talking
about human chemistry,
only one thing matters...
Either you've got it...
or you don't.
Dry cleaning.
Yeah. You want some coffee?
And tell them
that there is a stain
on the left sleeve
of the blue one.
I'm thinking Godfather tonight.
Sounds good.
"I'm gonna make 'em
an offer they can't refuse."
- That's Brando.
- Yeah. Got that.
XXX.
Hey, I'm taking Meredith Grey
from you this week.
Her mother was a good surgeon,
and I want to see what she's like.
That's not how it works here.
You get assigned a resident.
There's a schedule.
Well, the schedule doesn't take
into account certain things.
- Like what?
- Like the fact that I don't want Yang.
You can have stevens.
She's good,
and I'm sure Shepherd won't mind.
Won't mind what?
She's sassy.
She's a woman of substance.
You two have nothing in common.
Oh, I'm late. I had to drop
off the chief's dry cleaning.
You're doing his laundry?
- We're helping each other out.
- Yeah? What's he doing?
He has an extensive dvd collection.
You're dating the chief.
I don't care if you sleep with Lexie.
- I just can't do it at my house.
- It's my house.
Oh, get over it.
- It was a onetime thing anyway.
- Alex.
What? Seriously, one time.
What's the problem with you
and your sister anyway?
She's not my sister.
You look weird.
- I don't look weird.
- What's wrong?
- I look fine.
- I know you.
It's horrible...
The sex... with Izzie...
Horrible.
It's like she's trying too hard.
It's... You ever see a porno?
Not that Izzie's a porno.
She's an angel.
But it's like she's trying
to channel a porn star.
And she's trying to act
all dirty and sexy,
which sounds great, right?
But in reality,
I just want to say,
"Izzie,
"just 'cause you can do that with
your legs doesn't mean you should."
- I want to run.
- Run. Run. Run now.
- I love George.
- Oh, god.
I do. I love him.
And I'm so happy
because he's kind and smart
and, um, sweet
and sexy.
He's perfect. Perfect.
Except for the fact that
he kisses like a chicken.
You know, a chicken pecking
the ground for food,
just pecking
and pecking and pecking?
When he's pecking at me like that,
I forget that I love him.
I forget that he's kind
and sweet and sexy,
and I just want to scream,
"Stop pecking me!"
Did he peck you ke a chicken, Mer?
- Morning.
- Cristina needs me.
I'm painting Burke's apartment so I can
stop calling it "Burke's apartment".
A happy color... Red, like blood.
Plus, I am on cardio this whole week...
One of the benefits of living with
the person who makes the schedule.
I'm on post-op.
Again.
Second week in a row.
Trade with me.
Oh, yeah. No way.
- I was talking to Meredith.
- Why? I'm with Hahn.
Dude, wake up
and smell the surgical board.
3 days ago, there was
a code in room 2037
and no resident to cover it.
The schedule is a mess,
your mess.
Clean it up.
Chief had on his stern face.
Yeah, you know, I was...
I was happy this morning.
You know why?
Because I have back-to-back
surgeries today.
You have on
your I-want-something face.
Will you cover for me,
just do the chief resident thing
so I can stay happy?
Just today. Please, please.
- So you want me to...
- Be me.
But, you know, better.
Be you.
How's it going, Jerry?
If by "how's it going,"
you're asking me
if I've had the pleasure
of taking a crap yet, Dr. Karev,
The answer is it's not going.
Nothing's going. Nothing's moving.
It's been five days since
your bowel resection.
- You should be...
- Crapping by now?
What's the problem?
Did you people botch the surgery?
Is there crap leaking out into my body?
- The surgery was a success...
- Listen, Dr. Karev...
Oh, Mama!
I've been divorced twice.
My children won't talk to me.
I've battled addictions,
filed for bankruptcy.
My life has basically sucked.
But through it all,
the one thing I had going for me was
I crap like clockwork.
It's a simple pleasure.
I want it back.
So get your little prescription pad
and write me a prescription
to make me crap.
Grey and Hahn?
Hey, she can't do this.
She can't just not teach me.
It's her job.
- Torres has to make her teach me.
- If the chemistry isn't there...
It's not chemistry.
She doesn't like me.
She says it's chemistry.
No, I'm going to Torres.
Uh, Dr. Torres...
wanted me to tell you...
to find another specialty.
- Why?
- It's not gonna work with Hahn.
So you need to fin a way to make
it work with another specialty.
I suggest you try the ER.
- What?
- This isn't a request.
This is an order from
your chief resident.
The ER can be a candy store.
You've got car crashes, impalements.
What do you got?
Sprained ankle and an infected bunion.
It can also strip you
of your will to live.
Okay, go, troll, find me something good.
Meredith said anything to you about me?
'Cause she's been avoiding me for days.
What did I say to you about talking
to me about your personal life?
Help! My baby.
I was carrying her down the stairs
and I fell, and she hit her head.
She was crying in the car,
now she's not crying anymore.
I'm too scared to look.
Someone please tell me my baby's alive.
- Let me...
- She can't be dead, right?
You don't die from falling
down the stairs. She's...
Let me help. Let me help.
I'll take the baby. That's fine.
Oh, my god.
She's breathing.
Her fontanelle feels tense.
She's lethargic.
Take her to trauma
two and page shepherd.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- You're welcome. OK.
Okay, ma'am, you can,
uh, stop hugging me
so I can take care of your baby.
Ma'am.
Ma'am? Ma'am?
I'm not getting a hetbeat.
No pulse.
Get me a crash cart.
She's not breathing.
- Dr. Yang?
- Teresa Brotherton, lost vitals
and coded. I needled a tension pneumo
on the right side. She regained vitals.
Got so much air in the soft tissues,
it's obscuring the ultrasound.
Probably punctured an airway
as well as her lung. Feel that?
Uh, I was talking to Grey.
We've got it from here, Dr. Yang.
Call CT.
Tell them we're on our way.
And you didn't see him swallow it?
You were making your collages
while our son quietly choked to death?
It was one marble.
Brian, tell your dad
you're not dead.
And ask your mom
what the hell collage art is.
If you came to my studio sometime,
you could see for yourself.
Look, I'm too busy working
to pay for that studio...
Okay, mom, dad, just shut up, okay?
Sorry. They're annoying.
- Brian, that's rude.
- I wonder where he gets that from.
Well, there's not much we can
do except wait for it to pass.
- So he's fine?
- It was one marble.
He's not choking or drooling.
He'll be fine.
But I still get something?
You said after we went to the hospital,
- I'd get whatever I wanted.
- Absolutely, sweetie.
- You were really brave.
- Yeah, buddy, anything you want.
I want you guys to get a divorce.
- How about a puppy?
- No, don.
What? A boy should have a puppy.
I know we talked about it, but look...
We'll infiltrate
with a mixture of bupivacaine
then lido with epi
along these areas here.
Is there a surgery that
can make me look like her?
You're much prettier than Dr. Stevens.
Then how come I can't even remember
the last time I had sex?
I'll bet Dr. Stevens can remember
the last time she had sex.
- Harriet, don't harass the residents.
- She's young. She still has her looks.
Although, sweetie,
you're already getting worry lines.
What do you possibly
have to be worried about?
Nothing. I don't have worry lines.
Your frown line
is already prominent.
Whatever is wrong in your life,
you need to fix it quick.
Because once this stuff
starts to turn south,
honey, it is a long way back.
Trust me.
Know what this is?
Looks like multiple rib fractures
and a massive hemothorax.
Actually, it's you giving up OR two.
My patient is emergent.
What do I tell my patient?
If it were me,
I'd tell her to age gracefully.
Your baby has a slight
brain contusion.
Her brain's bruised.
It's minor. But I'd like
to keep her here for observation.
I gotta tell you, Dr. Shepherd,
I'm listening to you, but I'm not
hearing anything you're saying.
Dr. Hahn is taking my wife
into surgery right now,
and I need to go be with her.
You know what you're doing.
Go ahead and do it.
I need to go be with my wife.
Wait.
Um, what's your daughter's name?
She doesn't have one yet.
We just adopted her a week ago,
Just been trying to get to know her.
Clear. Charge.
clear.
Push the intracardc epi.
Get ready to cross-clamp the aorta.
The heart's responding.
Sinus rhythm.
All right, that's twice
in two hours
this woman has died.
Let's pick up the pace, everyone.
The less time
she's on the table, the better.
Quite a rush, huh?
Hahn took my OR.
She's pushy.
Pushy and rude.
- Is she doing a stapled tractotomy?
- Yeah.
She's trying to save
as much lung tissue as possible.
Doesn't make up for pushy and rude.
No, it doesn't.
You paged me?
Yeah, um, I was wondering,
do you think I could pick her up?
The baby?
I mean, the father
hasn't really been down here,
and she's been through
so much already.
That's not why you paged me.
- It's not?
- No.
You paged me because your legs
are still shaking from the other night
you're trying to work up
the nerve to invite me
to a friendly,
neighborhood on call room.
Actually,
I paged you because I wanted
to know if you could please
tell Meredith that I had no idea
that her house was your house.
I mean, she and I w...
We were making progress...
And now she must think
that I'm a stalker.
Sorry.
Uh, your issues can't be my issues.
But I am here for the
sex if you need it.
If I need it?
You know you need it.
Have you seen Dr. Torres?
She promised me a breakdown
for next week's E.N.T. conference
by the end of the day.
She asked me to pass it along.
Must have slipped my mind.
My apologies.
Oh, good. I mean...
This is good. This is...
- Nice work.
- Thank you. I mean, yeah.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, no, it's fine.
- Sorry.
- You go that way. I go...
You know, we...
we should...
We... Stop for a sec.
We should just...
We're a little nervous and...
awkward. We just have to admit that
we're nervous and we're awkward.
Yeah, it's a little awkward.
Because why?
Because we're nervous.
So we just need to, you know,
get over ourselves.
How?
We could pick a fantasy.
- What?
- You know, a fantasy.
We could pick a fantasy, any...
fantasy. Any...
I will do anything
that you want me to.
Anything?
- That's what you wanted?
- No.
I mean...
Yes, but...
That's not what I meant.
What did you mean then?
Okay, let's just not
ever talk about this again.
Please?
We have chemistry, George.
I know we have it because we had
the best sex I have ever had in my life.
- Do you remember that sex?
- I do.
It's vague and it's in flashes,
but I do.
I want that sex back.
- We can do this.
- Well, I want that sex back.
I think I chipped my tooth.
Well, I've been trying to do
what you said, but it's not working.
Uh, what... What did I say?
To try another specialty.
Yeah, Cristina,
I have back-to-back surgeries,
and I don't know
what you're talking about, so...
Dr. Bailey said it was your idea,
but I thought maybe
I could have some input...
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that.
The... Yeah, my idea to...
For you to...
try other specialties.
So can I...
Can I scrub in with you?
You hate ortho.
No, I love ortho.
But I can't observe anymore.
I need to scrub in,
even if it's on ortho,
Which I love.
Okay.
- Morning.
I'm a person of substance.
Plastics isn't all face-lifts.
I do many...
substantial, life-changing surgeries.
Um, the stain's still there.
So next time,
stand there, make sure
you watch 'em mark it
with the tape.
And everyone thinks
it's so easy being chief's girlfriend.
If you need to talk, I'm here.
Oh, hi.
I just came by
to update him on the baby.
But I can, uh, come back.
Listen, I had, uh...
I had no idea it was your house.
And, you know...
I'm not the girl who sleeps around.
I'm not. It's just, you know...
There's so much going on at home...
How is she doing?
She made it through the night.
That's a very good sign.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, well, she's strong.
She'll make it.
She's not gonna let that baby
grow up without a mother. Huh?
You're okay.
No, don't...
Don't try to talk, okay?
Your baby's fine.
She's feeding well.
She's doing great.
I can get her if you'd like.
Dr. Grey, why don't you go get the baby?
You're Dr. Grey, too.
Are you two sisters?
Uh, just same last name.
I was just thinking about
this crap I took in the army.
Still nothing?
I gave you a pretty good laxative.
Not strong enough apparently.
Have a seat, Dr. Karev.
If I can't crap,
you're going to sit here
while I reminisce.
Morning, Harriet.
Let's get you out of bed,
get you mobile.
I'm in too much pain.
Leave me alone.
The best thing for pain is to get you
out of bed, get you movin'.
- You'll feel much better.
- I will feel better if you leave.
- Harriet...
- Stop scowling.
You can scowl later when you actually
have something to scowl about...
When your ass expands
and you get a double chin.
But right now, you are young.
You should be having fun.
Go, start enjoying your life.
You're getting uglier by the minute.
Her heart stopped again.
They got it started, but...
I can't deal with her right now.
Could you just take her back?
Now!
Could you take her away now?
Dr. Torres,
could I talk to you a minute?
Uh, I'm in the middle
of a shattered femur.
Thank god for men
who ride motorcycles, right, Yang?
Right.
There are some scheduling
issues you have to deal with.
Yeah, can you handle it again?
Thanks.
I need to talk to Dr. Torres.
My patient won't crap and won't
stop talking about it. I'm done.
Is Dr. Torres in there?
My face-lift won't walk,
and she is abusive.
I can't work with her.
Dr. Shepherd's ready to discharge
teresa brotherton's baby,
but the father's in no
condition take care of her.
Okay, is there a problem?
Uh, just a little administrative
traffic jam.
Dr. Torres has it under control.
Okay, here's what's gonna happen...
Take crap man and put him in the
same room with lazy face-lift.
They can abuse each other.
The baby can stay another night.
Now get out of here.
And if anyone asks,
none of this was my idea.
Excuse us.
Where does it hurt?
- Everywhere.
- Didn't the marble come out?
Yeah, last night.
Oh, it really hurts.
I ate some more.
You what? You said you took
the rest from his room.
- I did.
- Well, obviously you didn't.
- Brian, how many did you eat?
- Eight.
Is this what you ate?
Brian, this isn't a marble.
This is a magnet.
Page Dr. Bailey.
Tell her it's an emergency.
The magnets take the path of least
ristance to get to each other.
If that means going through
the wall of the intestine,
then that's what they're gonna do.
Yeah. I'm looking
at perfed bowel here.
He's gonna need surgery.
Dr. Bailey...
There's another one, and it's moving.
Like a slow-motion gunshot.
All right, we gotta stop it
before it rips
through his stomach and kills him.
- Here we go, Jerry.
- What the hell is this?
Room shortage.
You're gonna have to double up.
- What?
- Yeah. Harriet, meet Jerry.
- This is absurd.
- Not so angry, Jerry.
It's not good for the complexion.
Right, Harriet?
Harriet, jerry may be monopolizing
the bathroom for a few hours,
so if you need to go, I'd go now.
- This is unacceptable.
- I n't even think it's legal.
My advice would be to get yourselves
discharged as quickly as possible.
See ya.
I have seven magnets in my tray.
He said he swallowed eight.
He has a hole in his diaphragm.
One could have wandered up to his chest.
- Forceps.
- Aren't you gonna repair the diaphragm?
First I want to see
if the magnet will find me.
You know he did this so his
parents would get a divorce?
They fight all the time, so...
He made himself sick so they
would take him seriously.
I bet they take him seriously now.
They said they'd try
not to fight so much.
I am elbow deep
in their 8 year old...
Sounds like something
a little extra effort can't fix.
You're probably right.
I am so right about so many things,
it'll make your head spin.
Her hands are beautiful.
I mean, surgically,
- The finesse.
- I was in ortho all day.
There is no finesse to breaking bones.
- Yeah, it's carpentry.
- Carpentry.
You want finesse, you should
try plastics. It's all finesse.
No room for error when you're dealing
with someone's face.
It's more than just face-lifts.
I'm a board certified E.N.T.
I take out tumors.
It's also a lot of face-lifts.
But even aace-lift...
I'm changing a life.
I'm holding someone's future
in my hands.
Holding a heart is way better.
She's good.
She's sleeping,
but we can go in if you want to...
Dr. Hahn said that Teresa's...
She's not in good shape.
Her other lung is leaking now.
And they can't operate
because her heart is too weak
from all the strain.
So they're gonna see if she's
gonna make it through the night
and reassess in the morning.
I am so sorry.
I need tknow who to call
just in case my wife doesn't make it.
I can't do this on my own.
I know what I'm capable of,
and I can't raise a kid
without my wife...
A kid that's not even my own blood.
The kid deserves a family.
And hey, I'm not a bad guy,
and I see her,
and she's...
She's good, you know?
She's...
She's a good baby, but I'm not...
You're her father.
She needs you.
She needs you now more...
- You're her father.
- I don't feel like her father.
I look at her,
and I'd... I just...
I see that she's not mine.
She's just a baby.
What did you do tonight?
I stayed late at work
because my house is a brothel.
What did you do?
Oh, no.
- What?
- Oh, dinner and a movie.
Dinner and a movie?
All right, dinner...
Uh, I'm sorry.
I'll just...
Okay, I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay?
It's a box of fun. You know?
It's just been...
Too much. Too much pressure.
Too much trying.
We just gotta get back to having fun.
- So it's a box of props?
- It's a box of fun.
Okay.
Can I...
A box of fun and booze,
'cause I figure it can't hurt.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, that...
- That's a...
- You know what? Don't say it.
This will work.
We will work. We just need
to take the pressure off.
We have the house
to ourselves tonight.
We're gonna have a drink
and we're gonna play.
- We'll play.
- Play...
with our box of fun.
You definitely
don't want to go in there.
- George and Izzie?
- Yeah.
The chief just saw me naked.
Nice.
I thought I said no having
sex with her at this house?
I didn't invite her over.
Um, Alex, do you want
to get a drink at Joe's?
Yeah, sure.
There's no rule that says
he can't have a drink with me.
Actually, there is. I'm making one.
No drinking with Alex,
no sleeping with Alex.
- What exactly did I ever do to you?
- Get your own friends.
Get your own life.
Stop living in mine.
Screw you.
I'll wait at the car.
I know that was mean,
but she's everywhere.
You say she's not your sister.
You say you don't want to know her.
So why the hell do you care so much?
I don't. I don't.
I don't care.
- Morning.
- Hey.
- Gotta get to work.
- Yeah, me too. Gotta go.
All I'm saying is, the next time
you have company, lock the door.
All I'm saying is, next time
you come over, you should knock.
Where is she?
It looks like
she finally got out of bed.
Oh, my God!
We're adults.
Don't look so shocked.
She always looks like that.
Well, I guess he finally crapped.
What?
Even they have chemistry.
Dr. O'Malley, he's...
Brian...
He's really gonna be okay, right?
Kids bounce back more
quickly than adults, so...
We used to be really happy.
I'm sorry?
My husband and I, we really were...
Before.
Brian was a colicky baby,
and Don lost his job,
and my mother died,
and all this baggage piled up.
I just keep thinking that
we have to get back there.
Maybe Brian's right. Maybe Don and I
do need a break from each other.
We haven't been happy in a long time.
She put her on a heart
and lung machine in her room?
Yeah. She wasn't gonna survive
another day without the surgery,
and she was too unstable
to transport to the OR.
So Hahn had to bring the OR to her.
- It's pretty genius, right?
- It's genius.
Make sure her lines are clear.
The last thing we need is a kink
to send her into arrest.
Anybody gets so much as a bad feeling,
we stop and we reassess.
She's gonna make it, right?
He said he's gonna give her baby up
if she doesn't make it.
She has to make it.
- Kinda busy right now, Lex.
- Road trip.
Mr. Brotherton, we need to go now.
I will send Dr. Grey out to you
with periodic updates.
I promise I'm gonna do everything
in my power to fix your wife.
- Got a thing for her.
- You don't have a thing for her.
I do. I do. I have a thing for her.
- Gonna end badly.
- You don't know.
- Yes, I do.
- What do you know?
- You're dating the Chief.
- It's not funny anymore.
It's overused.
- Lover's quarrel?
- Oh, Jeez.
We're not quarreling.
It's not a quarrel.
More importantly, we're not...
If I... go through
the trouble to choose a movie,
he should have enough
common courtesy to mention it
if he makes other plans...
A phone call, a note, something.
And if he'not gonna pick up my shirts,
just tell me.
I'll pick them up.
I'm perfectly capable of
picking up my own shirts.
No, you're not.
You're not capable of
picking up your shirts.
You're not capable of doing
anything on your own.
If I wasn't around, you'd starve
in a dirty shirt and die a lonely death.
Oh, for God sakes.
I offered you
a place to put your trailer,
and you've been taking
advantage ever since.
You can't pick up the dry cleaning
or do the cooking,
so I have to pick up all the slack.
Hold that thought.
You see? He can't handle the truth.
I definitely have a thing for her.
Do you have any idea
why the Brothertons' baby's still here?
I believe Dr. Torres decided
to keep the baby here for another day.
Why would she do that if Dr. Shepherd
was ready to discharge her?
I don't know.
You'd have to ask Dr. Torres.
I mean, if it was me
and the mother kept coding,
I might keep the baby around
so they could get
a little more time together.
And why did Torres
have Stevens and Karev
put their patients in the same room?
That's a clear violation of protocol.
You'd have to ask her.
But those two patients were impossible,
and neither one was willing
to follow post-op instruction, so...
I mean, if it was me, I would
put them both in the same room
so they could encourage each other
to get out of here.
And she told Dr. Yang
to find a new specialty?
That's a pretty odd thing
to say to someone
who has such an affinity for cardio.
Again, you'll have to ask Torres.
But maybe it has to do with the fact
that Erica Hahn's putting her
through her paces,
so Yang needs to see
what else is out there,
otherwise she won't fight hard
enough to stay with cardio.
I'm just guessing.
You need to ask Torres.
That's just what I'm gonna do.
It's been an hour.
We should've heard something.
Well, the fact that we haven't
heard anything is good.
That means that
they've got her in the O.R.
And they've opened her up.
You know, every step of this
that she survives is good.
Oh, God.
So we were able to find one puncture
in her remaining lung.
We're preparing
to place a patch over it.
And hopefully at's the only leak,
and hopefully the patch will hold.
I should be getting back.
You know, you said your wife bonded
instantly with the baby.
For some people, it's like that.
For other people,
they need a little more time
with a baby
before they can feel like a family.
I bet you know her better
than you think you do.
All I know is that she cries.
Okay? And she eats a lot.
We were going
through formula like crazy.
And she sleeps with her hand
up under her chin.
And she likes my wife.
Teresa soothes her, you know?
She puts her hand on her back...
She let's her suck on her finger.
But that's all I know.
That's five things no one else knows.
That's five things.
The patch is secure.
Water, please.
All right. Let's see
if I earned my paycheck today.
Go to manual. Give me a breath.
- No bubbles.
- So far, so good.
Another breath.
I see bubbles.
Patch is secure. Clamp.
We got another leak.
Grey, hold on to this clamp.
Dr. Torres, you got a moment?
I don't, I have two more surgeries.
The schedule's a little crazy.
- I'll get on it tonight.
- You're not, actually.
Okay, you're right.
- It may not happen till tomorrow...
- You're not gonna get on it at all.
Mr. Brotherton, we did
everything we could...
Cool lounge.
Yeah, no interns allowed.
I know that.
I was looking for you
because I was wondering if...
if you would meet me later...
in the on call room.
I can't.
- I thought you said that...
- I know what I said, but I can't.
Because of Meredith.
Look...
I'm not getting involved in
whatever you two got going on.
I'm not choosing sides.
Except... clearly you are.
You've been covering for Dr. Torres.
I've just been shuffling
a little paperwork for her.
You've been doing the lion's share
of the Chief resident's work...
All the responsibility
and none of the credit.
You deserve the credit.
You deserve the job.
I should've given it to you
in the first place.
I hope you'll take it now.
Because...
what you do and how you do it...
makes this hospital work.
Well, it's about time you noticed.
Can I pick her up?
Yeah, of course.
Nurse.
It's okay.
I remembered a sixth thing.
She hates the car seat...
Unless you put this
little duck up under her head.
You know?
I'm gonna name you Keisha, okay?
'Cause that's what your mommy
wanted to name you.
I am not stalking. I just...
I hate apples.
Hate them.
Think they shouldn't be allowed
to be a fruit.
That's one.
And...
Two,
I can draw really,
really well on an etch a sketch.
Like, really well,
I could be a professional if...
you know, that profession existed.
I play the trombone... badly.
I like math.
And I notice that you do this thing
with your hands when you're trying
to make a point, like this,
with your hands.
And I know that that's about you, but...
I do it, too,
so it's also about me.
And so that's five...
five things that I'm hoping
will make it
a little bit harder for you to hate me.
I told her I could draw
with an etch a sketch.
Of all the things I could've chosen,
I...
No wonder she thinks I'm pathetic.
I saw your transplant today.
I know.
- You have extraordinary technique.
- I know.
Can I buy you a drink?
I have... rather extraordinary
techniques myself.
You're not attracted to me.
You think you are, but you're not.
You're attracted to my skill
and my confidence and maybe how
hot I look with my hands on a heart.
But mostly, you're attracted to me
because I'm not attracted to you.
I told her I couldn't see her anymore.
You did?
Whatever. I don't need
another chick with issues.
Thank you.
Will you take my sister home?
Come on, she plays the trombone
and whatever.
Just take her home, please.
I finished painting.
I got fired.
I married Adele two years
out of college.
There's a lot I need to learn
to do for myself.
Just pick up your own shirts
from now on.
Taxi Driver?
Meredith is coming over.
Better get back to my trailer.
"You talkin' to me"?
De Niro?
Alex, I'm fine. Thank you.
Really, you can go.
What a pleasant surprise.
- It's Dr. Karev, isn't it?
- Yes, sir.
All right,
don't want to interrupt you two.
Wait, dad!
- You're going out?
- Just down to the store.
- Dad.
- It's just down to the store.
- Why don't I go?
- My car, it's right here.
I'm fine.
What do you need?
Scotch?
Vodka?
Gin?
Scotch.
Just...
Don't tell Meredith.
What did you do tonight?
Nothing.
You?
It's late.
Shouldn't you be going soon?
I just want to lie here
for a few more minutes.
That... was amazing.
- Finally.
- See?
I knew we had it in us.
That was as good as the first time.
It was better.
- Way better.
- Way, right.
Because, we weren't drunk, and well,
I'm not married. And...
That was just...
Incredible.
You're lying.
Well, so are you.
Chemistry...
either you've got it...
or you don't.
Transcript: www.ydy.com
Subtitles: Benj! & Kasius
www.seriessub.com