Previously on
"Pushing daisies"...
Charlotte was a nice girl.
What if you didn't
have to be dead?
Nobody can know.
You touch murder victims,
you ask who killed them.
You touch them again,they
go back to being dead,
- and you collect the reward?
- That's it in a nutshell.
- Who's the funny girl stuck to Ned?
- Childhood Sweetheart.
- Do they touch much?
- Wish they would.
What's she doing here?
That girl's got to go.
That girl's not going anywhere.
We haven't seen each
other in like 20 years.
Don't you want to
know about me?
- I want to know everything about you.
- We all have secrets.
Season 1 Episode 3 - The Fun in Funeral
For www.forom.com
At this very moment,
young Ned was 9 years, 34 weeks,
12 hours,
and 54 minutes old.
He was a gifted boy.
Not academically,
nor athletically.
He was gifted in a way no
other boy was gifted.
Young Ned could
touch dead things
and bring them
back to life.
But if he touched the
dead thing twice,
it died
again... forever.
The consequence of not
touching a dead thing twice
was as cruel as any consequence,
and that was
something else
had to die.
Young Ned rationalized
this consequence
was beyond his control.
He was not to blame.
But to remain blameless,
he had to understand.
He realized to give life,
he had to take it.
Death, however,
had a grace period.
What young Ned did not know was
how long that grace period was.
One minute.
Fearing the consequences
of his actions,
Ned vowed to never,
ever again bring the dead
back to life for more
than a minute...
Until he did it again.
The expression
"pie in the sky"
entered popular
culture in 1911.
It refers to a
dessert so sweet,
it can only be
found in heaven.
If you're craving
something before you die,
I recommend where the pie
maker makes his pies.
But if you're
like Chuck,
you may enjoy the pie
even after you die.
Her 60 seconds
came and went.
She stayed alive,
and instead,
someone else had to die.
He kept Chuck blissfully
unaware of this fact.
She was alive again.
That was that.
Which birthday do I celebrate?
I've got two of them now--
The first day I was alive,
the first day I was alive again.
The one that requires
less explanation.
You remember my 8th birthday,
right before my dad died?
You remember what you got me?
- A t-shirt.
- With a beaver on it.
He had little lipstick
kisses on his cheek,
and he was holding
a sign saying,
"Be kind to animals.
Kiss a beaver."
I suppose I should be celebrating
every minute now, shouldn't I?
I could be anybody now,
anybody I want.
I like that idea.
I'm gonna give that some thought.
The pie maker
liked that idea,
as well,
as long as her thoughts
didn't fall on...
Why is it only a minute?
A minute seems
awfully arbitrary.
Oh, a minute's a long time.
A lot can happen in a minute.
Besides, t-the longer
someone's around
that's not supposed
to be around,
the more likely it is that
something will happen--
not necessarily directly
or by any fault of theirs,
but, you know,
butterfly wings and such.
- What about 'em?
- They cause hurricanes.
Oh, right. Am I a hurricane?
A little bit, but I, uh--
I like the weather.
You really shouldn't do that.
Chuck wasn't the only storm brewing
in the pie hole that evening.
An innocuous low-pressure
system was forming
that would soon become
hurricane Olive.
Watching the pie maker kiss
the woman that wasn't her,
Olive stopped breathing.
It was as if all the
oxygen had left the room.
Espresso, please.
We have coffee.
- You have an espresso machine.
- It's broken--
Sits there being pretty,
but nobody touches it.
- Decaf or regular?
- No flavors--
- Hazelnut, french vanilla?
- Why can't sugar be enough?
Here's your sugar.
Oh, I forgot to breathe.
Ever feel like all the
oxygen left the room?
Oh, my, yes.
In that moment,
Alfredo Aldarisio recognized a
kindred spirit in Olive snook.
He also lived in constant fear
of the oxygen leaving the room,
but his pathology ran much,
much deeper.
He was haunted by the notion that,
at any moment,
the earth could lose
its atmosphere,
and he would be sucked
into the vacuum of space.
Excuse me.
A traveling
salesman by trade,
Mr. Aldarisio sells
pharmaceutical alternatives,
which he also uses to
manage his condition.
Medicinal.
You're not wrong about the
oxygen leaving the room.
The planet is losing atmosphere.
It's affecting gravity.
Volumes aren't what
they used to be.
They had to adjust
the kilogram.
Well, if you ask me,
the kilogram needs to
be taken down a peg.
- Decaf or regular?
- Regular,
lots of sugar,
more than enough.
Emerson Cod, private investigator,
made a business of murder,
but before he could get
down to business...
I feel like ice cream.
Musing on the idea of
setting someone on fire
doesn't mean you really
want to set them on fire.
It's just the thought of
it that makes you happy,
but only for a second.
Then you feel bad,
but that second can
be a lot of fun.
You thinking of setting
someone on fire?
No, I was just speaking
in the figurative.
But figuratively speaking,
someone should set you on fire for
throwing my heart under the bus
when you told me
he didn't want me.
- That was the truth bus.
- That wasn't the truth bus.
That was the bitchy
crosstown express.
By "bitchy," you mean
"frank and honest"?
If I want frank and honest--
Well, I don't want
frank and honest.
I never want frank and honest,
so let's just take it off the docket.
While we're on the subject
of frank and honest,
I don't like that girl,
not one bit.
Emerson Cod liked
her even less,
so much so,
it warranted a private
conversation with the pie maker,
but not private enough.
So, somebody died?
How did they die?
They died mysteriously.
He somebody or she somebody?
He. I told you I wanted to
discuss this in private.
Chuck is private--
- Part of my private.
- She ain't part of mine.
I don't know her.
So, what's the mysterious part,
the way they died or the circumstances?
I mean, did you find him
with a noose around his neck
and you didn't quite
know how it got there,
or did he drown in his bed,
but the sheets were all dry?
- You're obsessed.
- Am I?
Do you think dying
has made me morbid?
Come on.
- How did the somebody die?
- Said it felt like life
just got up and left him,
like I'm gonna get up and leave you.
Do you know what it could be?
It could be one of those
untraceable poisons,
or a four-stage poison,
when you have to,
like, touch four things
before it actually kills the person.
It could be that.
What did you say it
was besides mysterious?
I have not yet
expressed my opinion.
Would you care to
express it now?
My opinion is,
you need to take a coupon
for this conversation and
redeem it at another date.
- I want to use my coupon now.
- Redeem it tomorrow.
There's somebody in the county
fridge I need you to talk to...
In private-- My private--
which doesn't include her,
so she better not come.
I can write a book
on hand moisturizer.
Nobody wants the last thing
they've been touched with
to be ashy and dry.
Take a gander.
Smooth.
You got some serious
cracks going on there.
Put those up here.
Hi.
Thought you just came
by to say "hello."
You won't even know I'm here.
'Cause you leaving?
- No.
- Come on.
It makes her happy.
You remember what that
happiness looks like.
Redeem your coupon.
Oh, now you're
gonna listen to me.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I ain't gonna say another word.
"Future me," though,
is going, "I told you so,"
up one side of you and
down the other one,
but "now me" is just
gonna sit back and watch.
Oh, no.
"Oh, no," what?
The facts were these--
cunning and corrupt
Lawrence Schatz was
a funeral director
who made a living
off the dead
above and beyond his
job description.
2 days, 8 hours,
and 43 minutes before his death,
he was exposed as
a grave robber.
Oh. I-I was just prepping
the body for burial.
Your wife's gorgeous.
How did you guys meet?
But before any legal
action could be taken
and before the spoils of his
grave-robbing could be found,
Lawrence Schatz found himself in
the wrong place at the wrong time.
He was 44 years, 17 months, 10 days,
6 hours, and 9 minutes old
when he was in approximate
proximity of the pie maker.
But keep his sleeping
beauty alive
meant that someone
else had to die.
What if you didn't
have to be dead?
And one minute later,
the pie maker
took a life...
...And gave it to
someone else.
- Why are you running away?
- Vertigo-- dizzy.
The room started spinning,
and I, uh--
I think it's my shoes.
They're, uh, stiff,
and they pinch, and I, uh--
I think they're cutting
off my circulation.
That was mean.
That was a very mean thing you did.
Really? 'Cause "future
me" is here now,
- and he's got something to say.
- But you didn't touch him.
How are we supposed to
find out who killed him
- if you didn't touch him?
- Already know who killed him.
So the mysterious part
is how he was killed.
Already know that, too.
Okay, how was he killed,
and who was the killer?
Yeah? Who was the killer?
The pie maker's
eye twitched
in anticipation of the
lie he was about to tell,
but, instead,
what he told
was the truth.
- Me.
- What?
You killed someone?
Who did you kill?
- I didn't.
- You didn't-- that's why somebody died.
Please stop talking.
- You didn't what?
- Looky here,
you need a ticket
to ride this ride.
If your ticket gets punched,
then you got to take
somebody else's ticket.
- Why are you still talking?
- I'm ripping off the band-aid.
I'm not a ripper--
I pull up a corner a little at a time,
then I run it under warm water,
and I pull it up a little more.
- It's a process.
- Let it rip.
I didn't actively kill.
I'm not an active killer.
I'm not a killer.
- You killed someone for me?
- It wasn't my fault.
It's a random proximity thing.
There was no choice or
decision-making whatsoever.
- It just happened.
- But you knew it would happen.
I was incapacitated with
not being able to think.
I had one thought in my head,
and it was of you,
and it clogged me up so no other
thoughts could get through,
including the one telling
me to touch you again.
So every minute I've
been celebrating
wasn't really mine
to celebrate.
As Chuck considered the
life she was living
that was not her own...
...Olive considered the
life she was not living.
Might I make an observation?
- Compliment or criticism?
- A neutral thought, I would say.
It's neither complimentary
nor critical.
Neutral thought gives me pause.
Neutral for only this
portion of the conversation,
but I do have
complimentary observations
as part of a follow-up discussion,
which I intend
to headline with an offer to
repair your espresso machine.
- What's your neutral thought?
- You deem decidedly unhappy.
- I haven't decided that.
- No anxieties, neuroses,
- pathologies?
- Garden variety.
- What are you beating at?
- I'm beating at happiness.
I've beaten it into submission
and bottled it for convenience.
It's homeopathic.
Meaning it deeply
relates to gay people.
"Gay" only in that they
are bright and happy.
You never have to worry about the
oxygen leaving the room again.
Don't go bothering the
customers with this.
This is a pie house,
not some herbal crack den.
Chuck, say something.
I can't, for the life of me,
think of anything to say.
Oh, I forgot--
it's not even my life, is it?
Not now.
I feel violated.
That was my information.
There's your information,
and then there's my information.
That was our information.
You let a man die on our time,
a man who could have been me.
- It wasn't.
- But it could have been.
That was a business
associate of mine.
Who do you think hooked
us up with corpse bride?
But he stole stuff
off dead people.
Regardless of how he
ran his own business,
he never interfered
with how I ran mine.
You, on the other hand,
made me an accomplice to a murder.
Stop saying that.
I didn't murder anyone.
There was no malice
or forethought.
Okay, maybe
accidental,
involuntary manslaughter.
Oh, you accidentally,
involuntarily let dead girl live?
That's what I thought
you was gonna say.
Lawrence Schatz was murdered
enough for his brother
to hire me to find
out who killed him.
- Why did you take this case?
- You want me to take this case.
I'm making sure nobody
else solves it.
Look, I didn't want to go
down this road with you.
I'm sensitive to
your experience.
I understand that
it's traumatic.
But now I need to chat
with Lawrence Schatz
before he goes into
the ground tomorrow.
I'm not going back to
that funeral home.
It's returning to the scene of a crime--
that's just sloppy.
And by the way,
to ask him what?
I want to ask
Lawrence what he did
with all those precious
family heirlooms.
So you can...
return it to the families
and help heal the grieving?
Yeah, 'cause after the grieving stops,
you have Joy,
and with Joy comes money,
and Louis Schatz will stop asking
questions about how his brother died.
I'm not touching Lawrence Schatz.
It's too traumatic.
I am fragile on this issue.
- That how it is?
- Yeah.
That's how it is.
Whatever you say... killer.
The pie maker
rationalized circumstances
beyond his control were responsible
for Lawrence Schatz's death.
He was not to blame.
Rationalizing those
rationalizations
to the man he
inadvertently killed
was something he'd
rather not do.
I want to talk to Louis Schatz.
I want you to talk to him, too.
Why would I do that?
So you can apologize,
and I can say "thank you."
As the pie maker found himself
back at the scene of his crime,
Chuck found herself back
where her second life began,
now with the understanding
of how it began.
Have you already been here?
- Lawrence Schatz?
- Louis.
Lawrence is dead.
- Hey, Emerson.
- Hey, Louie.
"Darling Mermaid Darlings."
Yeah, we just
buried their niece,
lonely tourist
Charlotte Charles.
- You see they're on tour.
- I do. It's so exciting.
Tour was canceled.
They're in a dark place,
some kind of an emotional relapse.
Have we met before?
- No.
The cause of the Darling
Mermaid Darlings'
emotional relapse
was this...
After losing Chuck,
aunts Lily and Vivian had
a better appreciation
of the preciousness
of life.
With luggage packed,
bonnets cinched,
and sunscreen
vigorously applied,
they were ready
at last to start
their long-awaited
comeback tour,
but not today.
To their surprise,
there was something waiting
in the morning mail,
alongside the thrifty
nickel and the pennysaver.
It's from Charlotte.
In that moment,
only for a moment,
aunt Lily forgot
Chuck was dead...
or, at least,
dead to her.
Then she remembered.
Poor, poor Charlotte.
And with that,
the Darling
Mermaid Darlings
cancelled their
comeback tour.
I'm having a martini
and going to bed.
You know, uh, Larry died
on the same day we buried lonely
tourist Charlotte Charles.
- We don't often bury a celebrity.
- Celebrity.
Burying a celebrity,
even a pseudo-celebrity,
who's only famous
for how she died,
must be a coup for any funeral home,
I'd imagine.
It would be,
if it wasn't for Larry's
grave-robbing scandal
or his murder.
He's in here.
I got it locked,
so no one can defile his dead body.
Are you sure he was murdered?
I've been putting
it all together.
And, boy,
do I have a tale to tell.
And this is the tale
Louis Schatz told.
He detailed a series
of events that began
when he caught
his brother ***
I was just prepping
the body for burial.
Your wife's gorgeous.
How'd you meet?
Aw, Larry. How could you?
When word of Lawrence's
grave-robbing ways
spread through the sleepy
hollow of Coeur d'Coeurs,
there was
public outrage.
Bulk hate mail and death
threats by the hundreds
frightened the truth
out of Lawrence.
According to Louis,
he only confessed
his sins
to the one person he
knew would forgive him.
I buried it all where
no one could find it.
You have to give
everything back.
But I buried it really deep.
Louis insisted what his brother
Lawrence did not confess
was where he had hidden the
spoils of his grave-robbery.
That secret he took
to his own grave
when he presumably died
of heart failure.
But as Louis was besieged
by angry families
seeking the return of
stolen heirlooms,
he began to wonder--
What if it wasn't
heart failure?
What if his brother
was murdered?
What if, in the hundreds of letters
addressed to Lawrence Schatz,
threatening his life,
one of them was a promise?
What if his brother
was murdered,
and what if his
murder was next?
I told Larry it was bad karma.
The whole thing makes me sick--
just sick.
Do you know what it's like
to live in daily fear
that one minute
you could drop dead
right where you're standing because
of something somebody else did?
I feel like I could
smoke a cigar with you.
I don't smoke. That was Larry.
Here. Take it. He would.
It's true what they
say about twins--
His life was my life.
It's strange to share someone's life.
I feel like mine's tainted now.
I would love to give
back what he took.
Can we have a moment
to pay our respects,
while you go rustle up
that hate mail to go?
Yeah.
As they stood over the man
who died for one of them
and was killed
by the other,
Chuck and the pie maker
carefully planned
their words.
- Yes?
- I'm sorry for what I did.
It was mostly an accident,
but partially on purpose.
However inadvertent,
I am sorry I did it.
That's all.
Hello.
Lonely tourist
Charlotte Charles,
are you part of my
welcoming committee?
More like a beneficiary,
in that I'm still alive,
- which is why you're not.
- Am I a human sacrifice?
- Hey, Emerson.
- Oh, hey, Larry.
What'd you do with all that stuff
you stole off them dead people?
Why don't you ask Louis
what he did with it?
- Louis said you buried it.
- And you believed him.
You met Louis?
Hey, how did I die?
Did somebody kill me?
Hey, did Louis kill me?
- Nobody killed you, per se.
- Y-yes, they did.
It was so that I could live.
It wasn't personal.
I didn't pick you.
The selection is purely random,
but it didn't help that
you were in the next room.
Louis has all that
stuff you stole?
We stole--
it was a family business.
Louis has everything
but this watch.
My dad gave me a
watch just like that.
You were buried with it.
Well, you were supposed to be.
Caught me in the cookie jar.
You stole that
off my dead body?
Your dead body wasn't
doing anything with it.
Hey, what are you doing?
It's stuck.
- You better be playing.
- 29 seconds.
Oh, hell, no!
One minute's time
was nearing its end.
Random selection
was about to begin.
5 seconds!
Maybe I should let him
have his life back.
Not how it works.
No regifting!
That wasn't cool, you guys.
Look.
Aw, that was so sweet of my
aunts to bury it with me.
My dad had it,
and then I had it.
Then I suppose he had it,
which really steams me.
- You got it back?
- Yeah, I did.
It's nice to get things back.
My aunts cancelled their tour.
I was really looking forward
to hiding out in the crowd
with a big pair of
sunglasses and a parasol,
watching them perform
in their mermaid suits.
He said they were
in a dark place.
He said they had some kind
of emotional relapse.
- Couldn't we just...
- You can't see your aunts.
I'm sorry.
If Chuck could not regift
the life she'd been given,
she at least wanted to
find a way to share it
with her aunts
Lily and Vivian.
Anybody dead back there
that shouldn't be?
No.
Sweet.
After Lawrence Schatz was
exposed as a grave robber,
the mailbox at the Schatz
brothers funeral home
received 1,867
hate letters,
each one a catalog of heirlooms
feared stolen or lost.
Louis Schatz is a big,
fat liar.
And I say "fat" in reference
to his size as a liar,
not as a judgment of
his physical appearance.
I'm not mad at him for lying.
If I could pin my crimes
on some dead relative,
especially some guilty dead relative,
I'd certainly consider it.
That sucker played me
like boo-boo the fool--
Hiring me to make
him look innocent.
He knew all along where that
dead-people treasure was buried.
It's all right, though.
I'm gonna follow his lying fat
ass until he lead me right to it.
Then I'm gonna take it.
- You can't steal dead people's stuff.
- I'm not the one who stole it.
I don't condone what they did,
but it's once removed now.
I'm not the pirate--
I'm just looking for treasure.
- The pirate metaphore is weak.
- It's apt.
I find a dead pirate treasure
at the bottom of the sea,
I take it--
doesn't matter whose it was,
if whose it was is dead,
'cause it's mine now.
This-- this isn't a doubloon.
This is somebody's something.
Stealing from a pirate who
already stole is still stealing.
It's not once removed.
Somebody didn't
want that something
if they buried it with
somebody who can't use it.
What if Lawrence Schatz was
murdered for this buried treasure?
Well, was gonna be
before you got to him.
Why'd you have to
say it like that?
There's a lot of hostility
in these letters.
Do you realize how angry someone
has to be to put pen to paper?
I mean,
these people are furious.
Any one of them
could be the killer.
Lawrence Schatz
wasn't murdered.
He was accidentally,
involuntarily manslaughtered.
- I appreciate that.
- There ain't no killer.
***
murder was on
someone's mind.
As Chuck catalogued
another missing heirloom,
she considered what
her aunts had lost
and how it could
never be returned.
This is depressing.
Did you say "depressing"?
FDA-approved
pharmaceutical-grade herbology.
Like a bully for your emotions.
Emotions need to be bullied,
or at least groomed.
Indulging depression is like
indulging a horrible, willful child.
If you allow it
to run roughshod,
you'll find yourself
catering to its every whim.
So, bully it,
and bully it good.
Everyone needs to be
bullied sometimes.
Do you have any literature?
I have a pamphlet,
if you'd like to read that.
Our herbs for depression
contain proven ingredients
in the proper doses,
manufactured with the strictest
- of quality control.
- "Herbs for depression" sounds
- so much more civil than "antidepressants."
- And with fewer side effects.
- Can I have these?
- I can't just give it to you.
It's a controlled substance.
But I have a sample pack.
Chuck wasn't thinking
of herself.
She was thinking
of her aunts.
Though her life she was
living was not her own
Chuck found a way
for her living gift
to be the gift
that kept giving.
She took responsibility for
Lily and Vivian's happiness.
And took action.
Even after she was
dead and gone,
Chuck found a way to do what
she had done all her life--
Care for her aunts.
- Oh, you forgot one.
- Outside my zone.
Oh, it's not so far.
Do you want to be a delivery
boy or a delivery man?
Boy. You be a man.
But it's my day off.
And I'm a girl!
In her own way,
Olive identified with the
plight of the abandoned pie.
It was meant for someone,
and without a little effort,
it would never be with the
one it was meant to be with.
And tragically
for Louis Schatz,
he was meant to be
with his brother.
Hey, I didn't hear you
leave this morning.
I didn't hear you
come in last night.
I was having
conversations with myself.
What did you guys talk about?
I asked myself,
"if I were storming a castle
to save a Sleeping Beauty
from the jaws of death,
and in the melee,
my sword of truth flew swift and sure
and killed an unfortunate
outlaw huddled nearby,
how would I feel?"
Did you successfully
rescue Sleeping Beauty?
In this scenario, yeah.
And how would you
feel, hypothetically?
I'd feel happy and then bad,
and primarily happy,
and then I'd think
about it too much,
and then I'd feel bad again.
That's kind of how I
feel/exactly how I feel.
Well, I don't want you
to think I'm a killer.
I don't want to think
you're a killer, either.
I want to think of you
as Prince Charming.
I'm not setting a standard
for you to live up to.
- It's just--
- That's not good.
- Did you-- did you--
- No. No!
As Chuck and the pie
maker considered
the dead Schatz brother
in the freezer,
Olive snook considered
the consequences
of driving several
towns away
to make a delivery
to an address
that was not part of the
regular delivery route.
As she drew closer
to the front door,
Olive considered the
sheer number of crimes
against delivery people and
how they were on the rise.
S.O.S.! O.S.! O.S.! S.O.S.!
This pie smells delicious.
Pies for breakfast always
remind me of mother.
Vermouth always
reminds me of mother.
Why are we having pie,
- and who the hell are you?
- Forgive Lily.
The last time we had visitors,
there was a home invasion.
That was all over
the evening news.
You're Darling Mermaid Darlings
Vivian and Lily Charles.
I saw you perform at the
Callum County Country Fair
when I was a little girl.
Olive is in the pie industry.
Really?
Someone has made you
the happy recipients
of a pie from the Pie Hole,
as in "shut your."
Or, in this case,
"open your," 'cause it's real good.
The Pie Hole-- I like it.
It's provocative.
Well, you must love pie to
make it your life's work.
Lots to love at the Pie Hole.
There's gruyère
baked into the crust.
- Oh, I didn't even know we did that.
- Charlotte loved gruyère.
We recently lost our niece,
- lonely tourist Charlotte Charles.
- It's all over the news.
I am so sorry for your loss.
I'm sure you're
sick of hearing it.
I don't want to beat
a sentiment to d--
I'm so sorry for your loss.
This has to be from
that young man
who lived next door when
Charlotte was a girl.
Oh, he had a filthy
mind as a child.
He gave Charlotte a beaver
t-shirt for her 8th birthday.
- What did we call him?
- "Beaver boy."
Beaver boy.
Seems like he grew up
to be a nice young man.
Beaver boy did say
he was a pie maker.
I imagine he gives
lots of people pie.
Beaver boy's a pie maker?
Who was childhood
sweethearts with your niece,
lonely tourist Charlotte Charles,
who is dead?
Presently?
The truth about the dead
girl who wasn't dead
vibrated on
Olive's tongue.
She dare not let it out,
so she took another bite.
Not realizing Louis Schatz
was dead and wedged
between chilling dough
and yesterday's eggs,
Emerson Cod prepared to
monitor every move he made,
in hopes of finding
buried treasure.
- Hi, um, one of the Schatz brothers--
- It's Louis.
Louis Schatz is in my freezer,
and I'm not sure how he got there,
because it doesn't look
like it was his own doing,
on account of he's
dead and all.
- You being set up.
- He said we're being set up.
Why would anyone
want to set us up?
No, you being set up.
- Why would anyone want to set me up?
- Hell if I know.
Maybe they figure,
since you killed the other one...
- Have I been exposed?
- Does somebody know?
Somebody knows something,
and that somebody probably
already called the police.
Hey, the police are here.
Hi.
You need to follow us.
- Where are we going?
- You're going to heaven.
- I got in?
- Yeah, and heaven's closing
- in like five minutes.
- Or one, actually.
Heaven's closing in
like one minute.
Hey, Emerson,
you going to heaven, too?
- Yeah, we all going to heaven.
- That's so weird.
- We died at the same time.
- Mm-hmm. The rapture.
- No way.
- Yes way.
- Is Larry here?
- Yeah,
he told us to ask you what
you did with all that stuff
you stole off those dead folks.
Yeah, but first,
you got to tell us who killed you.
- Heaven would want to know.
- I choked on a piece of tongue.
Yours or somebody else's?
In this instance,
the tongue belonged to a cow.
Although Louis Schatz had
been limiting his portions,
they weren't so small they
couldn't block his windpipe
when he was confronted
by an angry customer.
He said something about
a civil war heirloom.
Then I lost consciousness.
I usually cough it up
before I pass out.
- 5 seconds.
- There's no seat belts in this car.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
What did you do
with all that stuff
you stole off
those dead... folk?
Sorry.
What are we gonna
do with the body?
We're gonna put Schatz
back exactly where he died
and show whoever this sucker
was who tried to frame you
how a sucker gets framed.
- We don't know who this sucker is.
- Yes, we do--
Wilfred Woodruff.
In Chuck's cataloging
of heirlooms feared
stolen by
trusted professionals,
she came across a particularly
angry death threat
written by one
Wilfred Woodruff.
Mr. Woodruff claimed
a civil war heirloom,
supposedly buried with
his grandfather,
was offered in an
online auction,
which was traced back to
the brothers Schatz.
Mr. Woodruff clearly stated
in writing that punishment
for insulting the
Woodruff family honor
in such a way was death.
- It's all locked up.
- What?
- I ain't gonna fit.
- You'll fit.
There's plenty of room.
Oh, the window looked
bigger from up there.
Are you stuck?
- No.
- Yes, you are.
You're like winnie-the-pooh.
Give me your paws, pooh.
You people stop pulling me!
Oh, this isn't good at all.
What part of "do not resuscitate"
don't you people understand?
Honey, did you
turn off the gas?
Wilfred Woodruff?
The pie maker considered
the choices he had made
that brought him to
this very moment,
a moment that
may be his last.
The irony of
being struck down
by the man who
murdered the twin
of the man he killed
was not lost on
the pie maker.
Also not lost--
his agility.
- Oh, my god!
- What's going on in there?!
- Wilfred Woodruff found his sword!
I propose to fight
it out on this line
- if it takes all summer.
- What line? It's ***.
You ***sses S.
Grant said that--
Not all of it,
just the last part.
Bad-luck missionary ridge--
My great-great-great-great-grand
pappy fought proudly against him
- ith this sword.
- Are you adopted?
Wilfred Woodruff
was not adopted.
On a hot day in the
summer of 1863,
Wilfred Woodruff's
great-great-great-great-grandfather,
Phan Bing Wu, was laying track
for the Central Pacific Railroad.
The decision was made
to find a better life.
As the civil war
was still raging,
the other men chose
to go northwest.
Why Phan Bing Wu chose to
run southeast is not known.
Some said it was the
hand of destiny.
Others felt it
was heatstroke.
Eventually, Phan Bing
was forced to steal
the clothes off a
former soldier.
Returning to
his journey,
he soon realized
he was not alone.
Phan Bing
immediately realized
he did not belong in this
place at this time.
But this time and place seemed
more than happy to have him.
Decorated for his bravery in
the Battle of Missionary Ridge
and the second Battle
of Murfreesboro,
Phan Bing went on to
found his own branch of
the Woodruff
family tree.
This sword was supposed to
be buried with my grandpa.
Instead, it shows up in
some online auction,
at which I take umbrage!
Remember, mind over matter
makes pooh unfatter.
I might be stuck,
but I can still reach my gun.
Now, you should know
that I was thrice named
alternate swordmaster
at the southern area
regional volunteer infantry
re-enactment regiment.
I wanted to be a Jedi.
You killed Louis Schatz and
stuffed him in my freezer.
- I put food in there!
- It wasn't my fault,
it just happened.
- Not like you killed Lawrence Schatz.
- Did not!
I saw you.
You didn't see squat.
Wilfred Woodruff
saw more than squat
when he approached
Lawrence Schatz about
his great-great-great-great-
grandfather's sword.
He saw the pie maker
fleeing the scene
of Lawrence
Schatz's murder.
I didn't touch Lawrence Schatz,
not till after he died,
and in his coffin.
I didn't touch Louis Schatz,
not until after he died
and I rolled him
onto a dolly truck.
- All because you wrote a nasty letter?
- I wrote a death threat.
Then someone died.
That has a way of coming
back to haunt you.
Unless you frame someone for murder,
you ass!
I had no choice.
Of course you did.
Everything we do is a choice.
Oatmeal or cereal,
highway or side streets,
kiss her or keep her?
We make choices,
and we live with the consequences.
If someone gets
hurt along the way,
we ask for forgiveness.
- It's the best anyone can do.
- I can do better!
Ned?
Help! Kick, pooh, kick!
At that very moment,
Chuck saw the pie maker
perhaps not as
he really was,
but as he would always
appear to her--
her Prince Charming.
Olive Snook's blood stirred with
revelation and opportunity.
She could see Chuck
had faked her death
for some
nefarious purpose.
I can smell trouble on her,
like she stepped in it
and it's stuck to her heel.
What she couldn't see
was the distant glimmer of
her own Prince Charming.
The broken
espresso machine,
sitting there,
being pretty,
with no one to touch it,
had been touched,
filled with water,
and packed with coffee grounds.
For the time being, the romantic
gesture was lost on Olive.
Her espresso was
much too bitter,
but this would not
be her last cup.
Not bitter at all
was Emerson Cod.
He learned a lesson from
the brothers Schatz.
It wasn't what
he had gained.
It was what he
wanted to lose.
He didn't want to lead
the life they led--
Not to say he no longer wanted
to make a living off the dead.
He made a decision while
wedged in the window that day
never to be
wedged again.
At that same moment,
Lily and Vivian Charles were
enjoying a wedge of happiness
with gruyère baked
into the crust.
Woodruff was charged today for
his involvement in the death
of Louis Schatz-- a key player
in the grave-robbing scandal.
The gift of life Chuck had
been given was, indeed,
the gift that
kept giving.
She went about matching
hate mail with heirlooms
and regifting them to
their rightful heirs,
like she had been regifted
to the pie maker.
I would do it again.
Oh, I think it's
nice the way it is.
No.
I made a choice,
and I would do it again.
I let Lawrence Schatz die,
and if I was faced with
that choice right now,
I would make the same choice.
You could put me in a loop,
and I would make the
same choice every time.
That's how confident I am
that it was the right
choice for me to make.
I'm sorry if that makes
me a bad person, but...
I'm not sorry that
you're alive.
I like that you
made that choice,
and the fact that you
did it on purpose--
Well, it makes it far more fun
than if you did it by accident.
I'm gonna see if I've
got some plastic wrap.
Thanks to Raceman
for the transcript
Subtitles made by the Bloc Team
For www.forom.com