Previously on "In Treatment"...
I'll put yours in the dryer
And they'll be ready by
the end of the session.
Well, you'll have to help me.
I haven't got dressed on
my own since my accident.
How on earth do you manage
with two broken arms?
I don't.
She's cool. You could
learn a lot from your wife
About how to talk to people.
Are there people who say
things about you, Sophie?
Some of the girls at the gym
might be jealous of you, and,
how close
your relationship is with Cy?
Don't talk to me like i'm a child.
How do you get along with Cy's wife?
I don't wanna talk about them.
"During first session
appears to be very impressive,
Sensite,
mature for her age,
Very intelligent
And a highly-independent personality."
Do you really think
those things you wrote?
Absolutely.
It isn't serious. It
comes off in a week.
My cousin stayed over last night.
She's here visiting colleges, so,
she got to sleep in my room,
And I had to sleep on the couch.
When I woke  this morning
i couldn't move my neck.
I had to go to the doctor's today anyway
To get my casts off,
but he took one look
at me And he was like,
"i don't think so."
He put this thing on me.
He left my casts on too because--
I don't know why, actually.
I guess taking them off might
cause too much rain on my neck.
I found something for you.
I thought you should have it.
- In here?
- Yeah, in the front pocket.
It's for your collection.
It's a catboat.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
It's a going-away present.
This is our last session,
right? You said three.
No, I said
at least three.
If you're totally sick of listening
to other people's insipid lives,
Then maybe you can look at it
And it will make you feel
like you're somewhere else.
"Insipid"--
That's a good word.
I read thesauruses for fun.
I'm not a freak, okay?
I just like words.
I thought you could use it.
It must really suck having to listen
To other people's problems all day.
So does that chair, like,
enhance your brain function?
i don't think so.
Can you read minds?
Unfortunately, no.
Yeah, it would be a
lot easier if you could.
It would.
Can I try the chair?
Sure.
Please.
Thank you.
How are you? You look tired.
I'm okay.
Maybe you should take a nap.
Maybe.
I've noticed that,
uh, Cy's drawing is--
Is gone.
- Did you erase it?
- Yes.
How do you feel about that?
How do you think I feel?
Maybe a little scared
Because this could be our
final session?
Why would I be scared?
Is the evaluation going to be bad?
I don't think it's the evaluation
that scares you.
I think it's the possibility that um,
you won't be coming back.
Sorry, but no.
I bought you a goodbye present.
See ya.
I know it's a goodbye present,
But there's another way to look at it.
Maybe
you want to leave something behind
So that I won't forget you.
- You said you liked the boat.
- I do.
If you don't want it, i'll take it back.
Do you want to take it back?
So...
if someone my age
wants to start therapy,
How would it work?
Well, we'd take it at
that person's own pace,
Not like these
last few sessions--
The evaluation, the
three-Session deadline--
Nothing like that.
See, the person who's in therapy
controls the gas,
So to speak,
And the wheel for that matter.
So it's like driving a car?
Yeah,
it's a bit like driving a car.
So...
pretend i'm in therapy now.
All right.
I said pretend.
So,
what do I do?
Why don't you tell me a
little bit more about the boat?
I got it years ago
from a homeless woman in New York
when I was just a kid.
What were you doing in New York?
We were on a "family" vacation.
Why do you say that, "family" vacation?
Because it wasn't a real vacation
and we weren't a real family.
No sand, no ocean--
That's not a vacation, you know.
That's bullshit.
My dad took me to central park.
There was this old woman
right at the park's entrance
Selling these little wooden toys.
She looked so miserable.
And I remember thinking,
"it's worse for her."
|| I had just enough money
left from my allowance
To buy the boat.
By the time we came home, it was over.
What was over?
- Their marriage.
Actually, I think it was over
during the vacation but they were, like,
pretending or something.
I went to school,
i went to practice
And I came home
and they were waiting
for me in the kitchen,
Smiling like those movie stars.
Like
movie stars?
You know, those smiles
that movie stars do?
Those big smiles
but their eyes are all glazed over.
Like--
And then my mother starts to cry.
Then my father says
to her in this voice...
"Olivia, leave it to me."
And then he starts to cry.
And i'm just standing there
stuck in the kitchen
Hungry as fuck with these two babies.
I don't remember the
day he actually left.
I just remember that day in the kitchen.
- Where did he go?
- Back to New York
With his new wife.
And I stayed here with my mother
Who's totally depressed.
Cy and Darlene--
They lived close by,
So,
they helped me get to practice and back.
They didn't want me to give it up.
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's just the way you talk about it,
Like you're not so
upset about the breakup
As
the way they did it.
Maybe that's what's making you sad.
I'm not sad.
Is that what people are
supposed to do in therapy?
Sit around and whine
over all their problems?
It's never going to happen.
That's what she would do.
I am nothing like her--
Your mom?
Where was your dad while
all this was going on?
I told you, in New York
with Natasha.
Did you ever consider living with them?
No.
We once thought maybe, but...
- It didn't work out.
- Why not?
They needed their space.
They didn't last anyway.
He wanted me to live with them.
He was really pissed
that she said no, so,
it really soured their relationship.
So you blame yourself?
Whatever way the cookie crumbles,
you're still to blame?
How old are you?
What do you mean, how old am i?
People really don't
talk like that anymore.
Really?
Your logic has
has some flaws, Sophie.
You aren't responsible
for what your parents did.
You couldn't be.
Were you a gymnast before--
Before you met Cy?
I don't remember a time before I met Cy.
I've known him since I was so little.
Besides my father,
They're the only people
who ever believed in me.
Cy discovered me gymnastically.
I was dancing around
on a log in the backyard
To entertain Dana.
You know, doing spins and things.
He put me on a beam the next day.
Their house was like my house.
I had a key.
Before my father left,
When he and my mom were
fighting all the time,
I slept over.
I had these really
bad attacks back then.
My stomach would start to shake
And then my whole body
would start to shake.
Sometimes i'd start throwing up
And I couldn't make it stop.
They took me to the
emergency room one night.
We never told my parents.
Why not?
I ruined their family.
I did, I really did.
Darlene was so good to me.
I was--
She really was good to me.
She told me
before she left for Wisconsin
That she was only going
because she knew I would be there
To take care of Dana.
She said she didn't trust Cy,
but she trusted me.
She trusted me and I ruined it.
You're thinking he used me.
You're wrong.
He kept trying to stop me.
He kept saying,
"Sophie, you don't
know what you're doing.
We'll get to a place and
there'll be no turning back."
He's a really good person, Cy is.
He's a gentleman.
He kept saying,
"you don't know what you're doing."
But the thing is, I did.
And what were you doing, Sophie?
At first, I thought
it was my imagination.
And then he stopped talking to me
while Darlene was home.
You know, like he was embarrassed,
Like he was hiding something.
And sometimes i'd catch
him holding his breath
While he was looking at me.
He loves me, I know he does.
So I knew
even before Darlene went away,
I knew that he loved me.
And then she left for six months
But Cy wouldn't have sex with me
Even though everyone
assumed we were doing it,
That we'd been doing it for months.
Cy said it was a line that we absolutely
Positively would not cross.
We'd been sleeping
in the same bed--
Just sleeping.
And then one night,
The night before Darlene came home,
I woke up in the middle of the night
And he was awake.
Then he--
I--
It happened.
It felt like nothing at all.
Like nothing?
Not good?
Not bad?
Kind of like--
Kind of like I was watching it happen...
on a really small black
and white television.
Like
i was checking my e-mail
At the same time.
Like I wasn't really there.
I don't know.
The next day we pretended
like it hadn't happened.
Then at practice that afternoon
We had this big fight
in front of everyone.
Because of what happened?
Because I fell off the beam.
I'd been going for this back bend
And for some reason I thought the beam
Was longer than it really was
So,
i bent right off of it.
I fell flat on my back.
I just stayed there
Trying to breathe,
Afraid to move,
Afraid that i'd broken something.
Then Cy came over and
started screaming at me.
"We've got two days
until this tournament
And you've lost your focus.
Now get back up there and do it right."
That night I slept on the couch.
Then in the middle of
the night Cy came in
And i thought that--
But he wanted me to
put Dana back to bed.
She'd had a bad dream
and come into his room looking for me.
So,
I put her back to bed
and then we talked.
He kept talking about my potential.
He said it would ruin
both of our careers if this got out.
He said we had to stop.
That's it.
We almost had sex again that night,
but he didn't want to.
That's it.
A few weeks later
Darlene said she wanted to talk to me.
She said that Dana had
become too attached to me
While she was in Wisconsin
And I probably shouldn't
come over for awhile.
But it was pathetic
Because I know her, you know?
She was lying to me.
I couldn't look at her.
I just said i'm sorry.
She said,
"don't be silly.
Kids forget quickly.
Grownups don't but kids do.
Dana will forget you."
Dana will never forget you, Sophie.
You don't think so? No.
I'm sure of it.
Darlene
is terribly wrong.
Grownups
can forget.
Children can't.
When I left, darlene gave me a present
That she got for me in Wisconsin.
What was it?
An apron...
with cows on it.
She knows I like to cook and
I collect things with cows on them, so,
it was sort of...
Perfect.
The accident...
it happened that night?
I woke up in the ambulance.
Do you remember how you got there?
I don't even remember
walking away from the house.
I remember her giving me the apron.
I didn't want it. I
tried to give it back...
but she said,
"Take it so you don't get dirty."
And then I think she kissed me.
It must've been at their door because,
now I remember stepping back
and seeing the whole house.
- What did you see?
- Nothing.
I saw thhouse from the outside,
That's all.
"I'll huff and i'll puff
And i'll blow your house down."
So what the fuck are
you gonna write now?
Are you asking me if I think
the accident was your fault?
Yes.
When you came here this morning Sophie
You to me that they would
going to take the casts--
- You're stalling, Paul.
- I'm trying to explain to you--
You know, but you're afraid to tell me.
Sophie, what I need
you to understand--
I understand!
I understand everything.
I understand why Darlene
kicked me out of the house.
I understand why you're
lying to me right now.
Okay, I get it!
- I fuing get it!
- Sophie...
let's finish the session.
- I have to use the bathroom.
- Okay.
Sophie?
- Are you all right?
I'm gonna open the door now.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
I'm so sorry. I don't
know how that happened.
It's no problem. Don't worry about it.
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
It's just a picture frame.
I can clean it up later
on. It doesn't matter.
I don't wanna fuck
everything up here too.
No, don't worry about it.
If you had to write
the evaluation now--
But I don't have to write
the evaluation now, Sophie.
If someone held a
gun to your head--
No one's holding a gun to my head.
Are you holding the gun?
I wanna know waht you
think ! What do you think ?
Do you think that you
did this to yourself ?
I don't remember!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
- What does your instinct tell you?
- I don't have any instinct.
- What does your heart tell you?
- I don't have a heart.
You know from what you've told me already,
I think that you're having
quite a difficult time
- Taking care of  yourself recently.
- So?
So it doesn't mean that you
deliberately ran into that car.
So what would you write?
i don't know, something
along the lines of...
"as a result of the anxiety
She felt preceding the incident,
The subject may have been distracted,
Acted irresponsibly but
we cannot conclude
That the accident was a
premeditated, willful act--"
- That sounds really vague.
- I can't be any more
specific than that.
I'm not a magician.
I don't know anything more
than what you've told me.
I fucking hate you!
You never say what you really mean.
You know, you're just like
all the rest of them.
Why can't anyone ever tell
anyone else the truth?
I can't listen to any more
of your stupid bullshit words.
"A willful and irresponsible act"?
Just say it--
She tried to kill herself or not.
If you think I did, then say so!
What's the problem?
There's a difference
Between not being careful
Because you feel vulnerable
And wanting to commit suicide. No!
You don't see the difference? No !
It's just like the picture frame.
I didn't mean to break it.
I didn't even see it,
But it's broken. I broke it.
In terms of the evaluation,
There's a really big difference.
That's what i'm trying
to get you to understand.
- What?
- Sophie, the problems that you had
Before the accident--
They're still there.
Even when they take off
the neckbrace and take off the casts,
Those problems are
still going to be there
When you go back to your
normal everyday routine.
You're gonna have to face them again.
'Cause if we're not careful,
something like this could happen again.
That's what you're really
asking me, isn't it?
If you go back to your life,
Will you find yourself in front of a car
Again someday soon?
You make me sound like a time bomb.
It's true, I ruin everything.
- No, you don't.
- Yes, I do.
You said I wanted to go home
because there's nothing
more For me to ruin there.
It's obvious.
Well, let's look at it another way.
You could really build
something at home.
With my mother? Are you on crack?
I have to go soon.
Can I ask you something before you go?
Where do you feel...
safe?
- What?
- Where are you happy?
Where do you feel--
Where do you feel safe?
I was happy with Cy and Dana.
I ruined it.
You erased the drawing from your cast.
'Cause I was angry.
Is there anywhere
else that you're happy?
On the beam.
I can spend hours
walking back and forth--
Dive, dive and swish.
"Dive, dive and swish"?
What does that mean?
It's a song I sing to
myself when i'm up there.
It reminds me of a pelican
diving down to catch a fish in its beak.
Could I hear the song?
I have a wish, to sing and fish,
Down by the sea, just you and me,
???
Dive, dive and swish.
And on the dive i've
drop my foot off the beam and,
And on the swish I swing it back up.
- You feel safe up there?
- Yes.
You know you can't
live up there forever.
You have to come down,
eventually.
Goodbye, Sophie.
Hello, this is Paul Weston. I'am,
your daughter's therapist
And I was wondering
if I could talk to you.
I understand they're about to remove
Sophie's neckbrace and her casts
And I think that we should discuss
Her return to the gym and to training.
So would you mind calling me, please,
At my office? Thank you.