Previously on In Treatment...
I left home.
You really helped me with that
in our last session.
You showed me that leaving home
was my own personal decision.
Could you be mad at me
for something else?
- Like what?
- Because I met a patient of yours.
I got the dates wrong
and I accidentally met laura.
- Should I go for her?
- I can't give you dating tips, Alex.
She's the kind of woman that can...
Could drive a man insane.
Am I right?
- Bye, Melissa.
- Bye. thank you.
I'm early, huh?
Yeah, but it's okay.
It's not a problem.
I was in the area,
I didn't want to go home
and have to come all the way back.
- It's okay.
- Are you sure?
- You don't have things to do?
- I'm sure.
This is from Laura.
I think it's a check.
Who knows?
Synch: Benj!
I'll pay you for the extra time.
- No need, it's okay.
- No, no.
I insist. It's another 20%?
$30, hold on.
Do you feel better now?
- What do you mean?
- After paying me, do you feel better?
What are you trying to say?
I guess that I'm...
I'm surprised by
how much effort you put into
showing your contempt
for this process and for me.
Relax, okay?
It's just the way my mother raised me.
I don't know what it's like
with you people.
I don't like charity,
so I like to pay for what I get.
Well, I'm glad you're getting
something here, Alex.
Listen, let's not make
a big deal out of this, okay?
You want me to admit
that this therapy is worthwhile?
Okay, I'll admit it:
this therapy is changing my life.
Happy?
Can we drop it now?
How many patients do you have?
- Why is that relevant?
- I'm just curious.
- Like today, how many patients already?
- Why are you asking me this?
'Cause I wanna know
what kind of money you make.
Let's say you have 8 patients a day,
times 5 days a week,
$150 a pop.
It's pretty good living there, doc.
$24 grand a month.
- Do you wanna buy me out, alex?
- What?
Well, $24,000 a month
and I'm all yours.
And you'll be my only patient.
It must be hard for you
to be in this position,
to be perceived as weak.
And you have this need
to regain your strength.
You bring me a check from laura.
You've asked me about
my patients and my income.
And you've done everything
you can to put me in my little place.
Did I offend you?
No, I'm kind of used to it.
But then all our sessions start
out like that, don't they, Alex?
Maybe I was expecting
something a little different today,
maybe because you were early,
or because...
you've been asking around about me.
Do you want me to tell you
why I was early,
or do you wanna just go on and on
with your theories?
I'd love to hear.
I went to the base today.
I thought I'd pop over before my session
here and say hello to my boys.
When I got to the gate,
I realized I forgot my id.
Now usually that's not a big deal.
But there's a new grunt at the gate...
Some real...
okie from Muskogee.
I told him,
"look, call the base commander
"and tell him
that lieutenant Prince is here."
So he goes in the booth, calls,
comes back a minute later,
and he says
I'm not on the approved list.
Now of course this is a real sensitive
issue these days, as you can imagine.
Still I said, "To hell with the list.
This is what you do: you call Dana
"the secretary,
tell her to talk to the commander,
"and you tell him
that lieutenant Alex Prince Jr.
"is waiting at the gate."
So he goes in,
he calls, he comes back, and he says...
He says, "I'm sorry,
but the commander is in a meeting."
Now maybe he was in a meeting
and he couldn't be disturbed.
Or maybe they were stuffing
their faces with doughnuts.
Or maybe he just didn't give a fuck.
I don't know.
I told that guard, I said,
"Look, you tell Dana
"if she took the commander's cock out
of her fucking mouth once in a while,
"then maybe she could hear better."
Man, I was this close
to knocking that motherfucker out.
Anyway, I didn't get in so I left.
And that is why I got here early.
Not...
Not an easy experience.
No, it's bullshit.
Now I gotta come and deal with this?
I got you coming at me like this?
That was the tip of the iceberg.
My shitty week started on saturday.
Why? What happened on saturday?
Okay, we're gonna pretend here.
All right.
We can pretend.
You know what happened.
Do I?
I wish you would've warned me
about Laura last week.
It would have saved us both
a lot of heartache.
I slept with her, okay?
With Laura.
That's what happened on saturday.
But I'm sure you got a full
play-by-play from her already.
Did she or did she not
talk to you about it?
I'm not at liberty to discuss
my patients or their sessions.
Now what is that?
Code language for she did discuss it,
but you won't tell me?
It was pretty weird.
She called to ask me
if I wanted to come over for dinner.
No problem, right?
So when I got to her place,
I looked at her.
I looked at how she was dressed.
I looked at the table.
I looked at the wine. And...
I realized that dinner
was obviously just a code name for sex.
This whole thing was like a ritual.
A ritual?
Yeah, and all the rules.
First, of course, there's the meal.
She doesn't look like a cook, right?
But she made a big effort.
For starters,
she prepared her own sushi...
California rolls.
- They weren't that great actually.
- It didn't taste good?
It was just for show.
Don't you get it?
That's the problem nowadays,
everything's for show.
If you wanna make sushi,
take a fucking course.
Go to a real japanese grocery.
Don't make it with uncle Ben's rice
and imitation crabmeat.
- Come on.
- Did you say anything to her?
Of course not, no.
The dinner was just a lead up
to us getting in bed.
I told you that.
It didn't really matter.
So did you want to sleep with her?
Yeah, but...
it has nothing to do
with wanting anything.
It was all premeditated.
It was like a mating ritual,
like the masai tribe
in Tanzania, but for yuppies.
Anyway, so we got up from the table,
we went to her bedroom and had sex.
And that's what happened on saturday.
It's interesting that you tell me
so much about this
ritual of you going
to bed together, but...
nothing about
what happened between you.
I'm sure that you've had lousy sushi
before, but...
I don't think you've been
with another woman for a long time.
- Isn't that correct?
- But you know what happened.
So why do you have to hear it from me?
You're very preoccupied with
who knows what and who said what.
What's important
is how you felt about it,
how the experience was for you.
The sex?
The sex is all that anyone
wants to talk about.
But is it really as important
as you people make it out to be?
Well, you tell me.
I know that's what it says in all
your textbooks. I know that.
But I ask myself,
"Is it really the key to everything?
"Or is it just the simplest answer?"
but you're the one who started the story
by saying that the sex was the issue,
that all the rest was just... foreplay.
Okay, I'll tell you what happened.
Otherwise you won't feel
like you're doing your job, right?
But before I start,
there's something I've gotta know.
Did you ever jerk off
to anything a patient told you?
What?
Come on.
Come on, you must hear
some crazy stories from women...
Explicit shit, fantasies.
Did you ever jerk off afterwards?
Are you concerned that I'll masturbate
to something that you tell me?
Me? No.
I'm talking about you've got women
they sit here on your couch.
They tell you all about fucking.
It must get to you sometimes.
I know it would get to me.
Do you masturbate?
There you go again, you're answering
a question with a question.
All right, i'll answer with an answer.
I'm a human being.
I masturbate sometimes.
My fantasies are
about many many things,
all sorts of women.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
That in that regard i'm not that
substantially different from you?
That's the first time you've ever
answered one of my questions.
In any case, you won't masturbate
to me and Laura's story.
I guarantee you that.
You may think of it the next time
you're having sex with your wife
and you're trying not to come.
It must have been a very...
complex experience for you,
being with...
Being with another woman
after all this time.
Complex, right.
I gave a shitty performance.
I made every possible mistake.
I was a mess,
to tell you the truth.
During dinner, before we had sex,
I started thinking about my first date
with my wife Michaela
about 15 years ago.
Jesus.
We had gone out to this bar together,
at the time she was the liberal type.
She'd talk openly about everything...
Foreplay, favorite positions,
cuddling afterwards...
"cosmo" type bullshit.
And among other things, she told me
that researchers found that wine
arouses women sexually
and represses men's sexual desires.
Have you ever heard that?
I don't know what made me do it,
but at one point
during my conversation with laura,
we hit one of those deadly silences.
I suddenly told her that
alcohol sexually represses men,
while women, it...
And she... of course,
she didn't respond.
She just gave me one of those looks
saying, "Why are you telling me this?"
- Why did you tell her?
- I don't know.
Maybe it was a way to...
move the conversation in a sexual
direction, make things go forward.
A kind of signal that
she had been cleared to attack.
Is that what you wanted?
For her to... attack?
Do you think that she
understood the signal?
Yeah.
- Is there another way of getting it?
- It might have sounded like
an apology in advance
that you didn't have any...
real sexual...
desire for her.
I don't think so.
She wasn't even too fazed by it.
She just changed the subject right away,
like I had said something nasty,
something inappropriate
at the table with all that sushi.
And that's what pissed me off.
Like all her faggy doctor friends
she hangs out with always say
exactly the right thing.
So listen, the first chance I got,
I looked her right in the eye and I said
"Baby, I have to go to the bathroom.
"I'm a bit nervous.
It's my first time
"since I left my wife."
This time she could barely
squeeze out a smile,
even a phony one. And from then on,
every few minutes, i'd mention my wife
and the separation...
Even in bed.
I did it every chance
I got just to see her squirm.
I think I got her
completely out of the mood.
She was totally turned off.
We had sex.
It was more like two animals mating.
I wasn't that hard
and I came pretty fast.
Even on the way to the shower
I threw in another
"I'm sorry, it was my first time
in so many years," just for dessert.
I don't know why I kept saying it.
Were you thinking about your wife?
No.
Or feeling guilty maybe?
No, why would i?
Well, because any of those reactions
would have been natural, Alex.
We haven't talked about your...
Your separation,
how you feel about it.
No, that's not what this is about.
The separation
was the right thing to do.
I haven't even looked back on that.
Don't you get off topic.
What is the topic?
Do our stories match, me and laura's?
That's what I want to know.
Look, on the one hand,
you describe this feeling of...
helplessness, weakness,
as if you were dragged
into sex against your will.
You feel that you didn't
perform too well,
so you felt...
Somewhat humiliated.
Then to gain back
some strength and control,
you make these references
to your wife...
in order to belittle Laura.
Belittle her?
You really make some
pretty far-out connections.
She belittled me.
Her whole attitude is...
- It's patronizing.
- You're sure?
You're the one who suddenly felt weak,
so you attacked.
You wanted to regain control.
It reminds me of the beginning
of our session when you came in here.
You were vulnerable from
what happened at the base.
You give me the envelope from Laura
and then you throw your money
on the table,
as if you wanted to humiliate me,
to make me feel small.
How's your machine?
It's good.
Thank you.
Are the clients happy?
I'm gonna make me some coffee,
by the way, if you want some.
If you've decided
to stop being a tea man.
Alex, can we get back to this, please?
We're onto something here
and I don't want to lose track.
Just give me a second here, okay?
I realize we're onto something.
I just need a break.
Respect that.
I want you to tell me something...
Honestly.
Do you really think you can help me?
If we sit here and
we talk about fucking a few times...
You'll be able to solve all my problems?
I don't have the
answer to that question.
Yeah, I knew you'd say that.
You know, that's what
kills me about you people.
'Cause any other professional...
I go to a doctor, he takes a look
and he says, "This is what you got.
"This is how long you have to live."
If I went to a mechanic, he'd say,
"$2,000, it'll be good as new."
But you people,
you don't guarantee shit.
Can I tell you a story?
What kind of story?
It's a jewish parable
that a friend of mine told me.
These two friends are condemned
to death, but the king...
He liked them
and he didn't want to kill them.
So instead, he tied...
a thin rope across this abyss,
and he told them both
to walk over the rope.
Whoever made it to the other side
would be allowed to live.
So the first one walked over the rope,
and he makes it safely
to the other side.
And after he made it,
his friend yells out to him,
"How did you do it?"
And the other guy answered,
"I have no idea.
"All I know is that...
"whenever my weight pulled me
to one side...
"I leaned to the other."
It ain't exactly Lord of the Rings.
True.
So what does it mean?
That you have to maintain balance
in your life?
I think what it means is
that there are no simple ways
of jumping over an abyss,
or ways that work for everyone.
I think what you're looking for, alex,
is a million-dollar magic trick,
and I don't have that.
I truly believe there is no simple way
to jump across an abyss.
Instead, we have to work in
small internal steps.
The question is whether you want us,
you and i, to engage in that process.
Eyes on your instruments.
What do you mean?
It's one of the basic
principles in aviation.
You ever heard of vertigo?
Sure.
When you go into vertigo
your directional perception changes.
You're spatially disoriented.
You'd be flying at mach 2 nose
down and think you're taking off.
So that's the first thing
they teach you at pilot school.
You go into vertigo, you look
only at your aircraft's instruments.
Ignore your feelings completely.
Rely on your instruments.
That's what the air controller tells you
if he thinks you're freaking out,
and that's what you're telling me now.
Eyes on your instruments.
So you want me to...
put myself into your hands.
You wanna navigate me.
Rely on you.
And on one hand, you're right.
That's why I came in the first place.
But keeping my eyes on the instruments
is what got me here.
What do you mean?
'Cause I kept my eyes on the instrument,
I dropped that bomb
so accurately into that window.
I relied only on my commanders.
And I killed innocent people.
And now I'm supposed to rely on you.
Alex, I don't want you to rely on me.
I want you to rely on yourself,
on your own feelings.
The most I can ever be to you is...
an air traffic controller
who tells you to try to ignore
the expectations of everybody else.
It's the expectations that give you...
That give you vertigo.
What's the first step,
- on the way to my new life?
- Well, what...
What would you like to do?
I think I'll go fuck her again.
Yeah, I'll fuck her,
well and proper this time.
I'll fuck her slow and good.
I'll take my time up into that...
sweet, hot little pussy.
I mean, what's the big deal?
She thinks she's the belle of the ball.
Fuck that.
She must be pretty miserable
if she's coming to see you, right?
Don't assume that everybody
who comes to see me is miserable, alex.
Look, doc, when I came to pick her up
from here yesterday
she was like a complete psychopath.
One minute she's hugging me,
completely over the top
like we're in some kind of movie.
The next minute, I close the car door,
and she's like, "Take me home.
"I'm too tired to do anything today."
I mean, what the fuck?
She turned as cold as ice.
She was two totally different people.
- Go figure what goes through her head.
- Listen to what you're saying.
You're belittling her again.
Hey, you don't think she belittles me?
You don't think I know she's completely
and totally hung up on someone else?
Check this out.
Saturday, after we had sex,
she straddles my leg.
She starts rubbing up against me
as if i'm not even there.
It so obvious she's fantasizing
about somebody else.
And then she starts crying.
Tears and everything.
She's just crying, and I ask her,
"Laura, what's up?
"Everything okay?"
She doesn't even look at me.
She doesn't even answer me,
like I'm just her dildo. So...
Don't tell me I belittle her, okay?
I know this is going to sound crazy
after everything I just said...
But do you think we have
a chance together, me and laura?
- If we really work at it?
- I don't know, Alex.
I couldn't even...
I don't know that.
I think it could happen.
I mean, like you said, doc,
it's a long series of...
small steps, right?
Yes it is.
Well, our time is up for today.
Already?
Why don't we continue next week
where we left off today, okay?
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.