Stay away from this.
- Got nothing to say to you.
- Man, what the hell you...?
Excuse me, everyone...
if I could have
your attention please.
It doesn't matter
if we ever meet again.
You may be immortal, Lorena,
but you are dead to me.
I wish you hadn't said that.
And I have a message for you
from Reverend Steve Newlin.
I've covered her,
she's only stunned.
Get the humans.
Get in, get in. Come on.
Let's go.
Go! Go. Come on.
Get in. Go.
Go. Go.
- We didn't think he'd really do it.
- Too late.
Sync: mpm & Arrow
I can't breathe, you weigh a ton.
Had to shield you.
Heal yourself,
what are you waiting for.
Can't.
- Silver.
- I'll go get Godric.
No time.
Suck it out.
Yuck, I can't,
it's too gross and...
it's... you.
I...
dying....
Son of a mother.
Got it.
The other one.
You're kidding me.
Oh, God, oh, God.
You tell the cowards who lead you,
the cowards who send children
to do their killing,
that a vampire showed mercy
where they had none.
Who's dead?
Stan, Paolo, Catherine,
two human companions.
What are you doing?
I sucked silver out of Eric's chest
and saved his life,
even though I really didn't want to.
She was superb.
Eric was in no danger.
He... What?
A tiny falsehood.
He was already healing.
The bullets would
have pushed themselves out.
This way,
he's forced you to drink his blood.
You're connected.
He'll to sense your emotions.
You big lying A-hole.
You're right,
I can sense her emotions.
- Sweet.
- I'll never do anything for you again.
Monster.
- It's not your fault.
- I think I'm gonna cry.
Everyone, please.
Y'all listen up.
They may come back.
Go to the Hotel Carmilla,
they've been alerted,
security is in place.
Help me.
Almost there...
I could kick myself.
I'm so stupid, I wasn't thinking.
He did take bullets for you.
- At least we both came out alive.
- I know better than to believe one word
out of that man's mouth.
I sucked his chest.
What is wrong with me?
Eric has had a thousand years
practicing deceit.
He lied to prove his power to me.
He counted on your goodness,
- there's no shame in that.
- But his blood, Bill.
I tried to spit it all out, really,
- but some of it must have gone down.
- It only takes a drop or two.
He'll always know where I am
and how I feel...
always.
That's the worst of all.
Not the worst.
What do you mean?
Don't be surprised if...
you feel some...
attraction to him.
Sexual.
To Eric?
That's impossible,
I can't stand him.
It is possible.
It's another consequence
of the blood.
It would have happened
sooner or later.
He was determined
to form this bond with you.
I could kill him.
I concur.
Maybe I'll get used to it.
Or maybe there's an operation.
I can't be the only vampire virgin.
You know...
intercourse
isn't the only way to have sex.
But I want to have intercourse.
Well, sure.
We could do everything,
when we figure out how.
You should break up with me.
Hell, no.
That thing that grows back,
it's just a thing.
I ain't perfect either.
I'm a guy that people laugh at.
Even my friends, but you never have.
I don't ever wanna hear you
talk about breaking up.
I won't,
I promise.
In fact, you mean so much to me,
I want you to meet my mama.
You mean it?
Nobody ever wants
me to meet anybody.
No, don't get too excited.
Look, she hates vampires
and she's gonna ask you
all kind of questions
or she may not talk to you at all,
which then you'd be lucky.
Well, I don't care what she does.
You're introducing
me to your family,
I never even hoped for that.
I'm proud that you're my girl.
The sun's coming up.
I guess it's time
for that damn cubby hole.
I'll go in with you.
Please, it's...
It's not very comfortable.
I'll have to build us
a tricked-out doublewide.
That is so romantic.
But, for now,
I'll sit right here
till you fall asleep.
You are the sweetest boy
in the world.
And you're too good to me.
There ain't no such thing.
- Good night.
I'll sing to you so you know I'm...
Know I'm right here.
My sweet vampire...
Oh, my goodness,
how much did you drink this time?
Nothing, as far as I recall.
Same for me.
You must've dropped a little acid,
it was floating around.
- Hippies.
- That's not funny.
It's embarrassing, is what it is.
I will never understand that.
Why be embarrassed
about pleasure and laughter?
Why be ashamed of letting go?
Because I've never been
this out of control.
Control. It's a cage this stupid culture
uses to lock up who we really are.
We need to be out of control.
We crave it.
But there's gotta be some kind
of control or things would be chaos.
Sounds good.
I do like a little chaos.
Of course you do.
Everybody does.
They just can't admit it.
I don't wanna be blacking out.
Is that what you think it is?
Because I have a little theory
about blacking out.
Maybe you rose
to a higher state of consciousness.
We're all bashed up.
There's nothing higher about that
except for we must of been high.
My mama blacked out for months
at a time, I'm a blackout expert.
- Are you?
- Certified.
What about the saints of India?
What about the mystics
of every religion?
What about them?
They would black out.
Run and dance through the streets,
levitate, act like monkeys,
run around naked.
- Everybody thought they were crazy.
- They were crazy.
They were ecstatic.
All that fake civilization
bullshit just fell away
so they could dissolve
into the infinite,
so they could lose themselves
and unite with their god.
Look at you.
A few bumps and bruises.
That's a small price
to pay for bliss.
Bloody Mary, anyone?
Come on now, Bud. Cut us loose.
All I did was lose my pants,
there's no law against that.
I only got your word for it
I was mating with a tree.
None of us did anything.
Let us out of here.
You got no evidence, Bud.
You got no right
to keep me locked up.
I can't sleep.
Join the club.
They made me think
I was worth something.
You were a star in Bon Temps.
I was the throwaway.
Everybody always
thought you hung the moon.
No, that ain't true.
Well, they like my athletics
and my good looks,
my sex abilities,
but they don't like me for me.
And Steve and Sarah, well,
they acted like they did,
before they tried to kill me.
They stopped my mind
from going around and around
thinking about...
Other stuff.
What other stuff?
But Soldiers of the Sun?
My Lord.
Didn't you for one second think
what Gran would say?
Guns and suicide bombers...
Don't... Don't talk about Gran.
I won't talk about her.
I can't.
Why?
Because I don't...
Because I don't wanna feel anything.
But we have to talk about her.
We can't stop remembing her
or loving her because
it hurts too much.
She'd never stop loving us,
would she?
We'll keep her alive in our hearts
and our prayers
and that's the way it's gotta be.
And Mama and Daddy.
That's right.
Mama and Daddy...
and Gran.
Our whole family's gone, Sook.
Everybody who counts.
We're all alone.
We're all that's left.
So you know what we gotta do?
We gotta grow up,
we gotta stick together
and we gotta be good to each other
or we're letting them down.
I'm sorry about...
everything I ever done to you.
I'm a dumbass fuck-up.
Yeah, but you wouldn't be
if you used your brain instead of...
just letting it take
up space in your skull.
That's not dumb,
that's lazy.
You think so?
Well, I could try,
I guess.
I'm sorry too.
I always love you, Jason,
even when I wanna
stick your head in a bucket
and kick it around the yard.
And I love you,
even though
I wish you'd cook for me more
and you were normal
with a normal boyfriend.
I didn't have any say
about being normal.
We were born the way we are.
- I'm all wore out now.
- Me too.
May His holy light shine upon you...
Can you believe, they're on TV.
You kidnapped a prominent
member of our community.
- He volunteered.
- Did he?
I didn't even know he was there.
- ... that's no crime.
- He came to us.
Because everybody
wants to be burned.
You use your tax-exempt
religious institution
as an anti-vampire
terrorist enclave.
The Constitution gives us
the right to defend ourselves.
You attacked us.
You murdered my father.
That's an allegation.
This is a fact:
you and your church armed
a suicide bomber
that killed vampires and humans.
We are fighting for God's green
earth and daytime
and Christmas and Easter eggs
and all that's sacred and good.
We are fighting for...
Human rights. Human rights.
- May I finish my thought?
- What, you were done.
If he's not the center of attention,
he flips out.
They are cuckoo.
How can you have a dialogue
with these people?
You need to read you
some Saint Paul, missy.
I hate your hair.
There's a witch
and a son of a bitch.
Fuck you, Newlins.
- Now can we see the freezer?
- Why?
Where they found that woman
with her heart cut out.
It was the walk-in refrigerator
and you are
one sick buzzard.
Go find some roadkill,
because you ain't eating here.
What do you want?
A knife, a fork and a spoon,
if that's not too much trouble.
They're in the back,
go get them yourself.
I could use some help out here.
Merlotte's, hurry up.
Lisa, lunch is your job,
you got a microwave,
that's all you need.
Come on, Coby'll eat cat food
if you put mayo on it.
Mama's gotta work.
I'll tell you what,
I am shit scared.
Oh, my God.
She was clumsy, stupid and mean, but I
wouldn't wish that death on a possum.
Plus that poor soul
out in the parking lot?
What if there's a curse
flying around out there?
I'll look out for you
if you look out for me.
When's it gonna stop?
Order up,
I think.
Please quit being so much more peculiar
than you usually are.
Please talk to me.
If what we did was so terrible...
Don't cry.
I didn't mean to be peculiar at you.
I just don't know what we did.
Well, we had sex.
Didn't we?
- Did we?
- You can't remember?
Don't take this the wrong way but...
nope.
Baby, me, neither.
I mean, not for sure.
- Is that good?
- I don't know and I don't care
as long as you're not mad at me.
Well, to tell you the truth,
I can't remember the last time
I had sex with anybody.
Gimme some sugar?
Where's my corn?
Come on now, the wait's forever.
- I want my damn corn.
- See you later.
I got it.
I know, I'm late.
Go ahead, order lunch on me.
- Stop.
- What the fuck is this?
He didn't do it.
I don't know what happened.
What you mean you don't know?
Don't gimme that bullshit.
What'd you do to her?
- I don't hurt women.
- It was an accident.
You put your hands on my cousin
bitch ass motherfucker?
I'm gonna show you how it feels.
- You might take those eyelashes out.
- Stop.
You been kicked and punched you all life
then you  get with this motherfucker.
He's poison.
He ain't never gonna change.
- And he may wind up killing you.
- Fuck that, you motherfucker...
Enough.
Stop.
- I ought to beat your...
- Please, do so.
- Do it!
- Eggs, enough!
Way to go, son.
What the fuck you all looking at,
you ugly-ass necks.
My Hoyt would never have run off
to Dallas without a word
with murders all over the place.
My Hoyt would never have
left me worried sick
thinking he was dead.
Or worse.
With a vampire.
- Go ahead, speak your mind.
- See what I mean?
All of a sudden,
you're a different person.
I sure do wanna be.
What do you think
your daddy would say?
I have no idea, because the only time
you ever mention him
is when you're trying to make me
do something I don't wanna do.
So while we're at it,
let's talk about that.
I want my sweet child back.
I haven't done anything
to deserve this.
What are you doing
with vampires anyway?
They are wrong, wrong, wrong.
They are devils.
Why do you have so much hate in you?
- I don't.
- That's a flat lie.
Who do you think you're talking to?
My mama.
- Who hates Methodists.
- I got my reasons.
And Catholics.
Just priests and nuns.
- African-Americans.
- Hush, that's a secret.
People who don't
take care of their gardens,
who parkup on their lawn.
- Ladies who wear red shoes.
- It looks cheap.
Families with lots of kids.
And checkered curtains and cats
and dogs, and bait,
every girl that I ever liked.
And the more that I like them,
the more that you hate them.
I simply object to a girlfriend
who will kill you and eat you.
- I think that's reasonable.
- You don't even know her.
Full of hate.
I see you now.
Well, it's not my fault,
it's the way I was raised up.
Jessica may be a vampire,
but she's the one for me.
- You don't have any say over it.
- You are breaking my heart.
You know,
I've let you run me around
because I didn't wanna hurt you,
but those days are over.
Now, I want you to meet her,
but if you can't be nice,
then I will leave this house
and never come back,
And don't think I won't.
Please,
you're my one son.
I'm not yours, Mama, I'm mine.
You're my baby boy.
I'm not a baby,
I'm a grown-ass man.
Finish your sentence.
What was I saying?
You were telling me
why you'd be a terrible vampire
and I was disagreeing.
Well,
I don't feel right without a tan.
It's true.
And I'd rather be alive than undead
and then y'all are always killing.
You've killed a man.
But that was for self-defense,
not for lunch.
You'd adapt, like we all do.
Trade the sun for moon and stars.
Not me. I want them all.
Greedy.
Yeah, I am.
I love it.
You have the right temperament
for a vampire.
What,
I'm high-maintenance,
bloodthirsty and old as dirt?
Bloodthirsty, yes.
I am not.
Everybody thinks you're a darling,
don't they.
I am a darling.
Yeah, but you're ruthless
when it comes to people you love.
You'll do anything for them.
Your brother...
your friends.
Me.
Where's Bill?
What do you care?
You've already abandoned him.
I have not.
I love Bill.
I used to think you had
no sense of humor.
I used to think
you were made of cold hard stone,
and empty inside.
And now?
You're a big faker.
You're deep.
You feel.
There's love in you.
Only for Sookie.
You don't want Bill.
He means nothing to you.
This is the beginning.
Hey, there she is.
She's come to get us out.
That she is.
- We had a good time, didn't we?
- Oh, yeah, we did.
Sheriff Dearborne?
None of y'all is going anywhere
till you simmer down.
Don't make me tell you again.
Sheriff Bud Dearborne?
Is that Maryann?
Hey, the party's back here.
Sure is.
Sit down and shut up.
Come on, Bud.
It stinks in here.
Now, Bud, come on.
There's coffee if you want.
Sheriff, you look exhausted.
What's going on around here?
Hell if I know.
Seems every person in Bon Temps
is getting arrested, but they
don't know what they done.
Kenya's out in the wagon
collecting some more.
We been up all night.
A major crime wave.
Misdemeanors, crazy things
I never saw in over 40 years.
Misdemeanors, that's not so bad.
Maybe you could let a few of them go,
save yourself the work.
I'm about ready to,
but they're all riled up,
might still do some damage.
Let me help, I'll talk them down.
It's my best thing.
I'd be grateful, can't hardly
keep my eyes open.
Now, what can I do for you?
I heard Sam Merlotte is here,
I couldn't believe it.
A fine upstanding businessman.
I have a lot of respect for him
and I'd like to help him out.
I'm not prepared
to let him go, he's a suspect
in a homicide.
- That can't be.
- But I'll show you where he's at.
I know the way. Sit.
Have a little rest.
There.
You went fast.
Stay.
Can we come over
to your house and play?
I want Sam Merlotte.
He's right there.
Now I am really irritated.
Free.
I never thought
you'd be so pretty, Ms. Fortenberry.
And I can't tell you how
grateful I am that you came.
Even if you were 20 minutes late.
I couldn't decide what to wear.
Hon, I know what that's like.
Sure. You try this on,
or try that on,
is it the black shoes
or the red shoes
or the...
Then there were people in the road.
They wouldn't budge till
I practically ran over them.
I could have been killed.
Well, them, too.
Let's get you some dinner, Mama.
I'm not hungry.
You want some more sweet tea?
I'm not thirsty.
Hoyt is a very, very, very good boy.
Mostly.
You don't need to tell me that.
You're as good as I am.
Better.
No, you are.
You are.
I surely wish
I could meet your people,
- see what your family's like.
- Mama.
Somebody made me a vampire
against my will, Ms. Fortenberry.
I don't have a family any more,
except your wonderful son.
I'm sorry for you.
That wasn't fair.
But Hoyt has a bright
future ahead of him.
And by bright, I mean in the sun.
If you think I'm gonna
let him wander around
all hours of the night
for the rest of his life
with an orphan vampire,
you got another think coming.
I believe that's up to Hoyt.
Y'all don't.
- I'll fight for what's best for my boy.
- So will I.
And I can give him
everything a human could.
- Not hardly.
- Like what?
Babies.
Well, now you did it.
- You happy?
- You'll thank me one day.
Not today.
- When are you coming home?
- Never.
I gonna need another one of these.
All right, let's do this motherfuck.
- You can't do that.
- That's against the rules. Come on.
We play by my rules,
that means no rules.
Okay, then.
Come in, it's open.
Deal. Deal.
- Deal what?
- Whatever.
Well, look is here. Aliens.
Oh, who's that?
Ms. Thornton, welcome, join us.
- No, we good.
- We're taking Tara away from you.
- Is that right?
- That's right.
Listen to me this one time
for your own good.
Don't be ridiculous,
take a load off,
- we're in the middle of a game.
- Strip poker.
Ms. Thornton, what's your drink?
Vodka. Whiskey.
- Hairspray. Antifreeze.
- Damn.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Are you even in there?
All yours.
The bottle's sweating.
Icy cold, thick,
pours like oil.
I don't know what you is,
but I feeling you
and you're a soulless bitch.
That almost hurt.
I am clean and sober,
as you well know.
I'll never take nothing
from you except my girl.
- Let's go.
- Fuck off.
She's my girlfriend, talk to me.
You ain't a boyfriend,
you're a domestically
violentsick motherfucker.
- Get up, I ain't playing. Let's go.
- She's not going anywhere.
I'm begging you,
don't let them do you like this.
We'll keep you safe.
It would be the first fucking time.
Your eyes. What'd you do to her?
Throw a bible at me now.
Pull my hair,
scratch my face,
break my head with a bottle.
Hit me back.
I won't hit you back.
Go ahead and kill me,
I'll never strike you again.
Leave him alone.
Move.
Hurry up.
Don't bother.
Go on, run, you fools.
Go. Go. Go.
She'll come back
and she'll bring them with her.
Come on.
Do you have any fucking idea
of the PR mess you've made?
And who fucking has
to clean that shit up?
Me. Not you, me.
I should drain every one
of you bastards.
Stan went after the church on his own.
None of us knew anything about it.
Really. Because everyone
who met Stan in the last 300 years
knew he had a kink about
slaughtering humans.
But you, his nest mates,
his Sheriff, had no clue.
And how were we supposed to know
that this time he meant it?
Not my problem.
Yours.
- Don't talk to him that way.
- Don't talk to me that way.
Let's get to the point.
How did they manage to abduct you?
They would have taken
one of us sooner or later.
I offered myself.
- Why?
- Why not?
They wanted you to meet the sun.
And you were willing.
What do you think?
I think you're out of your mind.
- And then I hear about a traitor.
- Irrelevant.
Only a rumor,
I'll take full responsibility.
- You bet you will.
- You cold bitch.
Listen,
this is a national vampire disaster
and nobody at the top has
any sympathy for any of you.
Sheriff, you fucked up.
You're fired.
I agree, of course.
Isabel should take over.
She had no part in my disgrace.
Godric, fight back.
What are you saying? She's a bureaucrat,
you don't have to take shit from her.
- You wanna lose your area, viking?
- You don't have that kind of power.
I'm on TV.
- Try me.
- I'm to blame.
I should have contained Stan
the second Godric went missing.
I remove myself
from all positions of authority.
Works for me.
I owe him.
Ms. Flanagan,
Godric rescued me
from a really large rapist
who probably would've killed me too.
- That's nice. Moving on.
- Listen,
And he rescued humans in that church
plus a whole lot of vampires.
You think it's a PR mess now,
it could have been a hundred,
a million times worse.
You should thank him.
For getting kidnapped?
For attracting a suicide bomber?
For piss-poor judgment?
I think not.
Don't.
It doesn't matter.
Tell me about the bombing, please.
Every single detail.
A boy walked in the lair.
I thought he was
someone's human companion.
I sacrificed everything
for that child
without a thought for myself.
He doesn't notice.
He doesn't care.
He isn't grateful.
He's running wild now,
he's headed straight for hell.
The God Who Comes
demands his sacrifice.
Where is Sam Merlotte?.
He ain't been here all day.
Well, find him and bring him to me.
A while back
he was planning to leave.
Bring him to me.
... watch him, grab him,
he almost got you, Mike.
- He almost got you.
- Come on. It's the 21st century.
There's gotta be a way... Crap.
That is one nutty ostrich.
Come on, Mike, come on,
now, grab his hand...
I heard you were here.
What a fucking fiasco.
You're lucky I don't send
you all to the Magister.
Godric, come to my suite
to fill out the forms.
Soon.
First I have something to say.
I'm sorry.
I apologize for all
the harm I've caused,
for all our lost ones,
human and vampire.
I will make amends,
I swear it.
Take it easy, it's just
a few signatures.
- Look in my heart.
- Listen to me.
- There's nothing to say.
- There is.
On the roof.
We have a score to settle.
- Not now.
- Yes, now.
Have I made my point?
It's done.
I'm part of her now.
Get out of the way.
I'm going to find Godric.
None of this has anything
to do with us.
Godric is not your concern.
If it weren't for him,
I wouldn't be standing here.
He's in pain,
he's suffering.
I gotta do something.
Don't you think
we've done enough for Dallas.
You of all people should
understand how he feels.
What if it were you, Bill?
What if in 1800 years,
you were Godric?
All right, but I'm coming with you.
I wish you could,
but it'll be dawn in a little while.
If we don't stay long, I'll heal.
I will not let you take the chance.
With Godric there,
you don't have to worry about me.
You are so tender-hearted,
you feel obligated, I can see that.
But, Sookie, in all honesty,
what can you do for him?
I don't know.
I just gotta be there.
It doesn't make sense,
but you understand?
I do.
Two thousand years is enough.
I can't accept this,
it's insanity.
Our existence is insanity.
- We don't belong here.
- But we are here.
It's not right.
- We're not right.
- There is no right and wrong.
Only survival
or death.
I told a lie,
as it turns out.
I will keep you alive by force.
Even if you could,
why would you be so cruel?
Let me go.
I won't let you die alone.
Yes, you will.
As your Maker
I command you.
I'll stay with him.
As long as it takes.
It won't take long.
Not at my age.
You know, it wasn't very smart.
The Fellowship of the Sun part.
I know.
I thought it might fix
everything somehow.
But I don't think
like a vampire any more.
- Do you believe in God?
- Yes.
If you're right,
how will he punish me?
God doesn't punish,
God forgives.
I don't deserve it.
But I hope for it.
We all do.
You'll care for him?
I'm not sure, you know how he is.
I can take the blame for that too.
Maybe not.
Eric's pretty much himself.
Are you very afraid?
I'm full of joy.
But the pain...
I want to burn.
I'm afraid for you.
A human with me at the end,
and human tears.
Two thousand years,
and I can still be surprised.
In this, I see God.
Goodbye, Godric.