We need sanctuary.
Oh, my God.
What have you done?
I staked a vampire,
the lover of Russell Edgington.
- Are you insane?
- Where can we go?
A human home would be safest.
We've both been invited into Sookie's.
That's out of the question.
You never panic.
Should I be panicking?
Ginger, dear, where do you live?
Across the river in Bossier. Why?
We need your house. Now-ish.
Because of the V-Feds?
I'm sorry, Miss Flanagan.
The bar is closed.
Thank you. I already ate.
Tru Blood only, of course.
Can't stay out of trouble, can you?
The VRA is two states away
from ratification.
I should be kissing asses in Oregon,
not cleaning up after you
in fucking Louisiana.
I promise
- there is nothing amiss in my area.
- Shut up.
You're making my head hurt.
Officers...
silver him.
Where is he?
- Where is he?
- In the study, sire.
Talbot.
My Love me.
Nice, is it?
I suppose
I should have mentioned that.
There's an old tarp out back.
Normal couples do not do this.
Thought you'd given up
on being like normal couples.
What would you rather be doing?
Sitting on the sofa,
watching television?
Used to be my idea
of excitement, you know.
You've spoiled me.
Just once,
I'd like to...
not find a dead body in my house.
Is that asking too much?
He was sent to kill you.
If I didn't kill him,
he would have come back for you.
You have to trust me.
Don't you?
I do.
I try to,
but then there's things like...
Like?
Like that secret file you got on me.
The one Russell Edgington showed me.
Birth records, family trees,
newspaper clippings
about me.
He said it's yours.
It's true.
I collected information to find out
why Eric Northman
has interest in you.
I assume it has to do
with what you are.
- Do you know what I am?
- Truly, I do not.
I'm doing my best to find out.
I don't know
how you did things in the 1800s,
but keeping a file
on the woman you love
is creepy.
I have to know what you are,
or else I can't protect you.
But you have to trust me
and stop thinking of me
as a thing to be protected.
I took care of Debbie by myself.
I'm not afraid
to spill a little blood anymore.
Much as you want to be human,
I'm meeting you halfway to vampire.
What?
This is where I come up with an excuse
to get you the fuck up out of here.
Like, "I gotta get to work early".
Or, "I think I got food poisoning".
Or, "Would you help me
clean the lice out of my bed?"
- I go with ticks.
- And which is it this time?
I guess you can stay.
Good answer.
Really.
Very good answer.
I like your ink.
They say the Olmecs and the Mayans
used to worship the jaguar.
He's strong and elusive.
He holds power
over the universe.
Yeah?
Is that what you think of yourself?
Okay, my high school
was the Jaguars.
That's more like it.
But it's pretty anyhow.
I told you, he's not here!
Where the fuck is he?
- Why ain't he got you chained up?
- I don't know!
Stop it! I can't think!
Just freeze!
Hands on your head.
- You a cop? Is he?
- Don't answer.
- Not really.
- What are you asking?
Ransom? We ain't got much.
- Ransom?
- He wants money!
No!
What are you talking about?
I won't leave you.
You're mine
since you was 4.
{\She's her own woman,
she can do what she wants.}
She's not an object.
You're the one who kidnapped her.
What?
She came to me.
Is that true?
I'll kick your ass
if you ran out on me.
- Don't talk to her like that!
- Don't make me hit you.
- I hate it when you make me hit you.
- Dude! I got the gun! Shut the fuck up!
Why does he think I kidnapped you?
- He raped me too.
- What?
- Cocksucker, that's my girl!
- I didn't rape no one!
Give me the gun, baby!
You bitch!
Why the fuck did you hit me?
Give me that.
- Could you not make me a rapist?
- I'm sorry.
It was the best I could think of.
We better tie him up
before he comes to.
- He's a lot stronger than he looks.
- All right. I'll get my handcuffs.
No. He can escape handcuffs.
What?
What is he, a magician?
Rope. Trust me.
Bring me rope.
The downstairs is clean.
I told you there was nothing.
It's been wiped.
I'm a Virgo.
I like to be neat.
Your screeching fang-cushion
of a barmaid,
who's been glamoured so much
she can't remember her own last name,
does know that no one goes down there
with so much as a mop and a promise.
Suddenly it's as sterile
as an operating room.
It doesn't prove anything.
If only we had a Magister
to decide that.
Relax.
It's not like you killed someone.
Just need your official statement.
That's all.
Webcams.
For the Authority.
Members of the Authority,
it's Nan. Can you hear me?
Good.
As regards to the matter
of the disappearance of our Magister,
last known whereabouts,
this dump in Shreveport, Louisiana.
You have before you Eric Northman,
Sheriff of Area Five.
Smile for the cameras.
I spiked it a little.
Looks like you could use it.
Listen.
What you went through sounds like
more than one person can handle.
You're here.
But I don't think
I'm doing too much good.
- Have you ever thought about?
- I'm not going to a shrink.
Pour my guts out to a stranger
is the last thing I need.
Tell me you'll think about it.
I got it.
You're lucky it's just me.
Arlene's fixing to throw a Molotov
through your brother's window
if you don't get here.
Why? What's going on?
There's all kinds of noises, Sam.
Girl noises.
Ordinarily, I wouldn't keep anybody
from enjoying themselves.
Enjoying?
She sounds like she's being murdered.
I got me two kids with school
in the morning
and a pregnant woman
who says she needs nine hours sleep.
It's for the baby!
I tried knocking on the door,
but they ain't answering.
It's late for you too, but...
No, it's all right.
I'll be right over.
Five minutes.
Bend over! God, make me.
Come on! Hold on!
I gotta run over to the apartments.
You wanna...?
All right.
There's a pattern.
The Turks told folk tales
of shape shifting jackals
at the fall of Constantinople.
The Aztecs were decimated by disease
from the Conquistadors' war dogs.
Each time, there's been wolves
fueled by vampire blood.
I nearly found him
in Augsburg in 1945.
His wolves were in the service
of the Wehrmacht.
He disappeared after the war,
and I...
I thought
he finally met the true death.
Now he's returned.
Do you know why?
In times of conflict,
Russell Edgington
inserts himself
into the affairs of men.
To what end?
He claims it's to prevent humans
from destroying the planet
and themselves
and thus our food source.
But Tru Blood changed all that.
Humans are no longer food for us.
- The Great Revelation.
- Russell opposes the Great Revelation.
And he doesn't want
to coexist with humans.
He wants to subjugate them.
- The Authority will not...
- Fuck the Authority!
Russell's words.
Verbatim.
This is why he killed the Magister?
No, he killed the Magister
because the Magister defied him.
He kidnapped the Queen
because she refused him.
Now, if the Authority
or the AVL stand in his way,
well...
These are treasonous allegations.
- Why didn't you report this?
- I should have.
But the Authority has existed
for only a few hundred years.
My history with Russell Edgington
goes back nearly a thousand.
My family was massacred.
All of them...
by wolves.
I managed to kill one
and I watched him change into a man
at the end of my sword.
And these wolves,
they're the same.
Sweden,
Germany, here.
With all respect,
I did not report
Russell Edgington to you,
because I want him to die
at my own hands.
I have waited a thousand years
for this.
Yes, I understand.
I'm flying immediately to Portland.
Thank you.
What?
Is that it?
The Authority
will review your statement
against the frankly,
strong possibility
that I've lost an entire night's worth
of air time
promoting the VRA in order
to listen to a load of bullshit.
But some do believe
in a fair hearing.
Americans.
Miss Flanagan.
Russell Edgington is a threat
to our very existence.
But he is a king.
One who donated a half a million dollars
to the American Vampire League
you say he's trying to bring down.
Weird?
Bring in a couple of spare coffins
for Sheriff Northman and his...
Whatever you are.
You're on lockdown
till the Authority makes its ruling.
Jump up and down.
Let's see them titties shake.
Jesus, put on some clothes.
Sorry, can't hear you.
Let me put on some clothes.
From the bar.
Yeah.
This here's Nicole.
Natalie.
It's okay.
We ain't done much talking.
Are you high?
I am. You want some?
Do you want me to go?
I don't wanna get you in trouble.
He's gonna do nothing.
He's stuck in the mud and drag me in.
Seriously, dude.
Look at yourself.
I'm naked, she's naked.
We're partying.
And you're standing there.
How you have a good time's
your own business.
Believe me,
I've done it all and more.
Yeah, he says that.
Where'd that guy go?
You can't be bothering the neighbors
while they're sleeping.
You telling me that
as my landlord or my dad?
Fine. Whatever.
Yes, sir.
We'll keep it down.
That all?
I'll see you in the morning.
That's your dad?
Where'd you learn that?
- I used to be a rodeo champ.
- Really?
Okay, call.
Renard Parish Sheriff's Department.
There's a guy tied
to a tree by Jefferson Road.
It's about three miles
north of I-20.
He's got a bag full
of vampire blood in his pocket.
I think he's some kind
of drug dealer.
Is he in need of medical assistance?
- Does he need medical assistance?
- That's good enough. Come on.
Shit.
You should have let me sleep
last night.
Got a 12-hour shift.
Hey, Ruby, you almost done in there?
It's time for us to go home.
You have got a excellent
selection of cosmetics.
I'll give you that.
I'm ready for you now.
Can't nothing hurt me
when I got on my war paint.
Something different about you.
I don't think so.
You ain't got your mask on.
'Cause you been in there
hogging all my stuff.
I see you.
My son is shining through.
Did he do this to you?
I guess you can say that.
I'll be damned.
Maybe God loves fags.
That sounds like a compliment.
Ruby, we gotta go. Come on.
You need to bless the Jell-O
so everyone can eat. Come on.
All right, now.
You go ahead.
Without my ring.
Come see me, La La.
All right, Miss Lady.
Eat your vegetables.
- So I'll see you?
- When I see you.
- What happened?
- Who's she?
This is Crystal.
She's with me for the day.
It's like a ride-along.
You okay?
We had a man down last night.
- Which man?
- Kevin!
He's alive, barely.
His mama's at the hospital with him.
What happened?
He went to answer
a distress call around 2 a.m.
I thought it was a crank.
Some moron called
disguising his voice,
said that there was a guy tied to a tree
holding a bag full of vamp blood.
I didn't know.
We sent our man into an ambush.
They smashed him up like a piñata.
Crushed his windpipe.
Boy's impossible
to understand as it is.
- Shit.
- That's awful.
Goddamn it.
Can't be losing deputies
my first week.
He's the only man I ever loved.
I gotta go type up a statement.
Just give me one second.
Taking our boy to his arraignment.
I'm real tore up about this thing
with Kev.
What you want, a hug?
I got ulcers so big,
coffee's coming out of my bellybutton.
Is that even possible?
You got three seconds.
I got an idea
about who might have done it.
Did we find a bag of V at the scene?
Kenya put it in evidence,
along with some guy's clothes.
Word on the street
is that the meth lab
we busted in Hotshot,
they're dealing V now.
Where'd you hear that?
You want your cops
to protect their sources, don't you?
You ain't a...
Just go on.
I was thinking,
if we can connect the V
from the fuck-knuckle who jumped
Kevin back to Hotshot,
then that would give us probable cause
to raid 'em again, right?
But you probably
thought of that already.
It's one of several theories I got.
Got a call into the lab.
I tell you what.
If it turns out our V addict
is from Hotshot,
I'm calling in the FBI, the DEA,
the ATF, the DOJ and Blackwater,
and we're gonna send that shit hole
back into the slime
it climbed up out of!
I'm behind you, boss.
All the way to the end zone.
And if you need any muscle
with Kev gone.
Go make sure Rosie hasn't
drowned at her own desk.
- That was my cousin.
- Really?
Right? From Merlotte's?
Everybody, this is my friend
from my new job.
We ain't hardly had a chance
to know each other,
but guess we're in the boat
together now, huh?
I don't know.
I'm not even sure why I...
Don't worry.
We ain't as scary as we look.
I promise.
How about I start.
Hey, y'all.
I'm Holly.
It's been a while since I spoke,
but there's enough new faces here,
I figure I ought to take a turn.
I'm a rape survivor.
Easy for me to say now,
but took me ages to be able
to put those words together.
And it's women like y'all
who helped me the whole way.
Fifteen years ago
I was locked in a room
and raped by my coworker
for five and a half hours.
And every day
I face not only my memory of that,
but that part of me who...
Who wants to feel sorry for herself,
and expects the worst out of people.
But that's not
who I was raised to be.
And I still believe
that people are worth trusting,
and every day, that piece of me
gets a tiny bit stronger
and wins out just a tiny bit more.
It's Hadley.
What are you doing in your house?
I told you to leave Bon Temps.
They're coming for you.
They came,
they gave it their best shot
and I'm still here.
Come on, I'm begging you.
You and Jason are
the only family I got left.
Where are you?
Sook, do you think you could come
to the aquarium in Monroe?
I got someone I need you to meet.
Stay right here. I'll be right back.
Oh, my God. Is that...?
I took him out of day care.
His daddy doesn't know.
I haven't seen my son
in over a year.
Sweetie, you're gonna lose him for good
if you don't bring him back.
- Did anybody follow you?
- What?
Whatever it is you're
not telling me, now is the time.
Shit. I screwed up.
I got involved with a vampire.
Her name's Sophie-Anne.
She's the Vampire Queen
of Louisiana.
Are you kidding me?
I told her things.
I told her about you
and the powers you got.
- Why would you do that?
- I didn't think anything of it,
but then suddenly
she got interested,
and now I think Russell
Edgington is interested.
Shit. It's my stupid fault
all these vampires are after you.
- What do they want with me?
- They don't think like regular people.
I don't know why they do
half the things they do.
But you just... You gotta get out
of Bon Temps. Please.
I'll find someplace to lay low.
Why haven't you left?
Hunter, sweetie, come say hi
to your Aunt Sookie.
I need to know if he's like you.
Please. If he is,
I have to protect him.
Hunter, come on, sweetie.
Come on, baby.
Who is this lady?
Where's Daddy?
Why isn't he here?
It's okay.
We don't have to talk.
Come on.
Which is your favorite fish
in the aquarium?
It's all right. No one knows.
Just us.
The blue one.
The blue one's nice.
I like the orange one too.
You don't have to be scared.
Your mama loves you very much.
Mama's real scared too.
Mama's more scared than me.
Sweet Lord, no.
We have to go.
- Where are you taking him?
- I got some friends.
The less you know, the better.
Come on, baby.
- She knows! She knows!
- Come on!
That's great. Thank you.
- Where's the rest?
- It's all on the table.
My white ass, it is.
This here's $2.
Sounds good to me.
Four Daughters of the Confederacy
with French manicures just told me
I was the best server they ever had.
- Don't tell me they left me $2!
- It ain't my fault they're cheap.
- We can hear you in the dining room.
- In all the years that you've known me,
since when has a four-top
left me a $2 tip?
I don't have your money.
Turn that fucker upside down
and shake it out of him.
- I'd like to see him try.
- Settle down.
Sam, if that little runt
keeps stealing my tips,
I'm gonna need a raise.
That's a good one. A raise?
For what?
Service that fucking sucks?
I'm taking
that money out of your salary.
Nice. So you're gonna
take her word over mine?
Shit. Is there anyone
you don't let walk all over you?
Un-fucking-believable.
I've had two boys just like him.
You ain't ever gonna get
him to admit he took it,
but dollars to doughnuts, he ain't ever
gonna try to pull that on you again.
God, time was this was
a nice place to come to work.
I've seen worse.
A lot worse.
I mean, the kids, God love 'em,
but coming here was
the best part of my day.
You still get to eye your man
through the kitchen window.
That's worth something, ain't it?
I don't know for how much longer.
The baby coming...
it ain't his.
I never said that till now.
The daddy, he's gone.
He's dead.
But that man
was pure evil.
I'm bringing an evil child
into this world.
I know I am.
And sooner or later,
Terry's gonna find out.
I got a time bomb in me.
Six and a half months left
of fooling myself and everybody else
before the best man
that ever walked through my door
gets blown to smithereens.
How am I supposed to live with that?
You want this baby?
I don't.
I can't believe I just said that.
You need someone
to go with you to the clinic?
I can't do that.
No, that is wrong.
It's plain wrong.
That's your business.
But you ain't no time bomb.
There's other ways to resolve it.
Come on, now.
No, it's impossible.
This is daylight.
How did you...?
You killed her.
Come back!
- You killed Sookie.
- I haven't.
You've taken her blood.
I can see it in you.
- I love her.
- You think you do.
You only want her light.
She's safe.
She's alive. I swear to you,
I would never harm her.
Leave her alone, vampire.
We will protect her.
How have you ever protected her?
We have. Believe me.
- Who is we?
- Now, why would I tell you that?
Sookie needs to know what she is,
so that she can protect herself.
Please.
What in God's name are you?
Did you sleep at all?
I'm fine.
Are the guards still outside?
Whatever the Authority decides,
I will not allow you
to take any responsibility.
You didn't kill the Magister.
But politically,
I'm a much cleaner scapegoat.
Who's easier to pin it on?
The Sheriff in your custody
or a king who might be anywhere?
And if they search Russell's palace,
they'll find the remains of his lover.
- What did he do to you?
- Nothing.
But he was the nearest thing
to Russell Edgington's heart.
He had to die.
A hundred years I've been with you.
Why did you never say anything
about Russell or your family?
You didn't need to know.
What good would it do
to share my pain with you?
You didn't need to carry
it all by yourself.
I am not weak.
I was the sole survivor.
The burden is mine alone.
We've lived through
so much for so long.
It can't end this quickly.
Everything ends.
Even the immortals.
If I can't go on
you must make a new vampire.
It is your time to be a maker.
I am so hungry, I could eat a horse.
Two?
- This here's...
- Follow me.
You ain't even gonna say hi?
You could always come during the day
or on nights when I'm not working.
There's even other places
you can go eat.
This is my place.
I've been coming here for years.
Besides, you called it off,
so, what do you care?
I don't.
It's fine.
Well, then in that case,
I'd like for you to meet Summer.
Jessica, I have heard so much.
Shit.
She didn't mean it.
I am so proud of you.
Why?
Because you chose life.
I love vampires
as much as anyone else,
but they have no life in them.
Look how sad she is without you.
She pulled you into the night.
I'm just so thankful
you chose to come back with me.
Can't do much antiquing after dark,
can we?
I saw the look in T-Dub's eye.
He thinks I'm the snitch.
Why else would I be
at the Police station?
You gotta quit worrying about them.
Tea-Bag,
he's in your rear-view, darling.
Because I got
the sheriff's ear today,
and we...
are gonna bust Hotshot.
What?
Round 'em all up
and take 'em all down.
So you just lay low for a day,
maybe two.
What's gonna happen to 'em all?
They'll go to jail.
They're my kin.
We gotta get up there and warn 'em.
You'll go running back to the people
you've been trying to get away from?
Back to Felton, who hit you
and almost killed Kev?
How'd he get away anyway?
We strung him up like Christmas ham.
There are folks up there
that don't touch the drugs.
And the kids,
they don't know nothing else.
You can't send them into the system.
You can't.
A visit from the chef.
It's my lucky day.
I wanted to meet the sick fuck
who ordered the veggie burger
with bacon.
I was just curious to see
if you'd actually do it.
For you,
I'd do all kinds of things
against my better judgment.
That's why I come back.
For the personal service.
You don't finish that,
then you ain't getting no dessert.
The nurse from Meadow Glade?
Is this a thing?
If you call
two days in a row a thing.
For me, it's a record.
Still plenty of time for it
to blow up in your face.
Well, fuck you too.
I didn't mean...
Never mind.
That's just...
Forget I said it.
Ain't no reason
why you shouldn't trust him.
I told him all the shit about me,
and he keeps coming back.
I don't know if he a fool
or a fucking...
miracle.
If he can handle your mama,
I'd go with miracle.
Hallelujahs.
Bless Jehovah,
it's about fucking time.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
No, I'm happy for you, baby.
I'll be right back.
Guard my dolls.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to scare your girlfriend.
It's all right.
Couldn't help yourself.
She seems...
short.
We can't all...
So she know you hate dolls?
We don't really talk much about me.
Does she at least make you happy?
I hate her.
God help me, but I fucking hate her.
Everything is dolls and show tunes
and cleaning stuff
and she will not stop talking.
And I feel
like it's making me crazy.
Then what are you doing with her?
Guess it beats sitting around
thinking about you.
You okay?
Come on.
What the fuck is your problem?
Is he inside?
Look.
The American Vampire League
protects your murderer.
Perhaps they even sent him.
They will suffer for their sins,
my beloved.
I swear...
to you...
they...
will...
suffer.
You look like shit.
Well, I feel fantastic.
The ruling is as follows:
The Authority disavows
any knowledge of our interview,
your statement or, indeed,
this ruling itself.
None of this ever happened.
What?
Missing royals, dead Magisters.
It's a political tar, baby,
no one wants to touch
not with the VRA
this close to ratification.
Russell will not stop killing.
What if the human public
learns of it?
That's why
you're going to take care of it.
Quietly, discreetly,
and most important of all,
completely off the books.
You wanted revenge,
it's yours.
What resources
are you gonna give me?
- We're not getting near it.
- How do you expect me to kill him?
He's three times my age.
Listen, you whiny little bitch.
The only link between Sophie-Anne,
Russell and the Magister is you.
You brought us
this steaming pile of shit
and you're going to make it go away.
Bring me his fangs,
or I will have yours.
He did it once, he'll do it...
Stay there, baby.
You little two-faced whore.
Watch your mouth, old man.
Oh, yeah? Fuck you.
That's my daughter.
You think you can turn on your people?
Who do you think you are?
I didn't raise no snitch!
You are not welcome here.
You got a problem, take it outside.
Let's go, daddy-O.
And you?
- You said you hadn't seen her.
- That's true. I hadn't seen the kid.
You can't man up to your own lies,
you fucking pussy.
Come on,
let's get the hell out of here.
Who's a pussy?
Who's a fucking pussy?
That's my daddy!
You fucker!
You gotta stop him!
Get his arm, Hoyt.
Easy.
He's still breathing,
but he's in bad shape.
All right, hold on one second.
You got him?
Grab his legs.
Listen, bro.
You gotta meet me
at the ER door in 20.
Thanks, bro. I owe you.
He said come on down.
Come on, man, let's go!
Wait!
Wait! Stop!
You can't fucking go with him.
That son of a bitch used you.
You hate him.
My daddy is the only one I got.
If you can't understand that,
you don't know a thing about me at all.
Crystal, I know
when you're being an idiot.
You're running right back to the people
who've been controlling your life.
You're right.
I don't need no one
controlling my life.
Especially not fucking you!
Fuck!
Don't.
It's an ugly, ugly sound.
I killed you.
That's what everyone said,
that you did it.
I thought, why would anyone
spread such vicious lies?
Why would you kill
someone that you loved?
I do not love you.
They said that too.
That, I refused to believe.
I had to see for myself.
You wanna know what hurts the most?
You didn't mourn.
If you had a shred of love
in your heart for me,
you would have mourned me.
I love you so much.
You don't love anything.
You can't.
Because you are a psychopath.
You violated me
and terrorized me,
because that's what vampires do.
And you are calling that love.
I'll mourn you, Tara.
I'll mourn you to my very marrow.
The only pity
is you will never know how much...
I will grieve.
Come on! If you're gonna
fucking kill me, kill me!
What's taking you so long?
You want to hear me beg for my life?
Is that it?
It's the only thing y'all can feel.
The destruction of life,
because you ain't got none in you.
You sick motherfucker,
I won't give you the satisfaction!
Why do you want to die so much?
Why do you want to make me kill you?
Because the second I'm gone,
I'll be rid of you forever.
I'll be free
and you'll have nothing!
Shut up!
Your heart is beating so fast.
I want to feel it stop.
Take your hands off her.
This is a private conversation.
It's none of your concern.
Run along.
Move the fuck away.
What, you gonna shoot me now?
You do realize I'm a vampire.
You could empty every round in me,
and I'll heal.
Not if I got wooden bullets.
Please, come on in.
Where have you been?
I've been calling you for hours.
I dunno how to explain it.
Like I was only away for a few minutes,
and then suddenly it was past 11.
You mean you overslept?
Listen.
Where did you go?
- Did you visit the Queen?
- The Queen? Why would I?
Do you know the Queen of Louisiana?
Well, yes.
I was her subject.
I saw my cousin today,
she said she used to be with the Queen.
And now the Queen is working
with Russell to come after me
and anyone else like me.
Do you know anything about that?
I think I know why they want you.
Why didn't you say anything?
I only learned it today.
I'm not sure
what it was or...
how I even got there.
Perhaps it's because
I had drunk so much of your blood.
I know what you are.
We're heading to the airport now.
I've got the speech here.
I'll have it all memorized
by the time we land in Oregon.
No, go ahead. I'll hold.
Miss Flanagan.
Recapping the top stories this evening,
in Salem, Oregon,
both pro and anti-vampire advocates,
rallied in anticipation of the state's
upcoming ratification vote
on the Vampire Rights Amendment.
Polls show the measure gaining support
in recent months,
although nearly 20 percent
of the country remains undecided.
Does that help you decide, America?
Do not turn off the camera!
You've seen how quickly I can kill.
Ladies and gentlemen...
my name...
is Russell Edgington,
and I have been a vampire
for nearly 3000 years.
Now,
the American Vampire League
wishes to perpetrate the notion
that we are just like you,
and I suppose
in a few small ways we are.
We're narcissists.
We care only about
getting what we want,
no matter what the cost,
just like you.
Global warming,
perpetual war, toxic waste,
child labor, torture, genocide.
That's a small price to pay
for your SUVs
and your flat-screen TVs,
your blood diamonds,
your designer jeans,
your absurd, garish McMansions!
Futile symbols of permanence
to quell your...
quivering,
spineless souls.
But no.
In the end,
we are...
nothing like you.
We are...
immortal.
Because we drink the true blood,
blood that is living,
organic and human.
And that is the truth
the AVL wishes to conceal from you.
Because let's face it, eating people
is a tough sell these days.
So they put on their friendly faces
to pass their beloved VRA,
but make no mistake,
mine is the true face of vampires!
Why...
would we seek...
equal rights?
You...
are not our equals.
We will eat you...
after we eat your children.
Now time for the weather.
Tiffany?