What did you say?
You heard me.
Come on.
Keep up, slowpoke.
Well, hey,
I don't know what you're saying.
You're so lonesome, Sam.
I saw it in your eyes
last night at the lake.
What?
- It was dark, you did not.
- Did too.
You're carrying that secret
like a 2-ton sack of feed on your back.
It doesn't have to be that way.
Secret. What secret?
Fibber.
I ain't in the mood tonight,
little girl.
Hey, your own self.
Sync: mpm, Arrow
for the sub factory
Jesus Christ!
Jesus Christ, you...
You... You're...
Shapeshifter, and proud of it.
How'd you...?
How did you find out about me?
Last night in the woods?
I watched a dog jump in the water
and it came up you.
Isn't this great?
Yeah, it's... It's pretty great.
You're not alone anymore.
Crap. Hand me my drawers.
Good party.
Later, darling.
Wait... Wait.
It's in the air, I guess.
Looks like it.
See you at work.
Right.
Come on, special lady.
Wait!
Shit, she's following me.
Oh, shit, oh, shit.
What the fuck are you?
Go away, don't hurt me.
I am the last person
you should be afraid of.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
Sookie Stackhouse.
- Gotta go.
- We have to talk about this.
We don't.
Have a good evening, sir.
Well, excuse you.
- Don't.
- He didn't hear.
He's glamoured, can't you tell?
Listen.
His mind's full of fog
and disco music.
By the way, they can't glamour me.
Can they glamour you?
No, but I fake it.
You ever hear any vampire thoughts?
God, no.
Don't even say that out loud.
I didn't.
Listen, I don't know what little fried
corn-on-the-cob town you're from,
or what candy-ass vampires you're with,
but this is Dallas, baby.
You watch your tone of voice.
And don't you call me "baby."
Dallas vamps are serious
and scary as shit.
Mine are too, thank you very much.
I had to learn quick
how to handle myself.
If they knew what we could do,
they'd suck us dry.
They'd do worse than that.
You think I don't know?
That's why we need to swap
stories. We can help each other.
I don't want any help.
Just forget about it.
You can't tell anybody about me,
please.
Jessica, we discussed this.
All I did was order him
off the menu.
You didn't say
not to order off the menu.
I would no more allow you
to feed on that young man
than to watch the pornography
on television.
Porno?
Hey, Sookie, there's dirty
movies on TV.
I know. Yuck.
To your room, please.
Tru Blood.
You are going to be so sorry
when I get an eating disorder.
Private!
Keep out!
- Where have you been?
- I was asking the bellboy,
if there's a candy machine,
what's a continental breakfast...?
You cannot wander off on your own.
The situation here
is more complicated than we thought.
We don't know nearly enough
about the Dallas vampires.
They can't touch me.
I'm yours.
Every...
single...
part of me.
Completely and totally...
yours.
I'm don't think it matters to them,
sweetheart.
As long as it matters to you.
Tell me you understand.
Promise me you'll do as I say,
not because I say it,
but for your own sake.
Bill, I've known since the airport
that we're up to our necks
in a big old vampire mess again.
I don't want to get beat up or dead,
I'm not gonna do anything stupid.
Is this room secure, do you think?
- Yeah, I believe so. But...
- Then, honey...
for a little while,
let's not worry.
We have something to be happy about.
I don't think so.
Yes, we do.
We're in a vampire hotel.
It's light-tight.
For the very first time,
you don't have to leave me alone
in bed at dawn.
I forgot about that.
I didn't.
My only desire is to keep you safe.
Your...
only desire?
Well...
You're talking to the man.
Hoyt Fortenberry?
Who's this?
Jessica Hamby.
Maybe you don't remember me.
Oh, my Lord.
I remember you, all right.
I can't stop thinking about you.
Really?
I mean, really-really?
Really-really, and some more.
- Hoyt!
- Can you hang on?
Who the heck is calling you
at this time of night?
It's a girl, isn't it?
I know it's a girl.
You tell her it's not decent
or ladylike to... How dare
you lock the door on me
in my own house?
So where were we?
Well,
you were telling me
how you couldn't stop thinking about me,
and,
I can't stop thinking about you.
And I'm all bored here in Dallas.
You want to watch TV together
long-distance?
Or I could tell you
about my comic book.
We could do both.
I mean, I would just love that.
So it's called Space Tomb.
And this time
they're on the planet Historion
Sea Leopard's just pitching a fit.
Get up! Get up!
- I said get up. Put on your sweats.
- What's happening?
Come on, let's haul
your butt outside,
you pansy fangbanger.
- Let's go!
- God!
My God, that's right.
Rise and shine for God!
Come on, let's go.
Move, move, move!
Stand up straight.
Make a line you can be proud of.
Let's go. You're supposed
to be leadership material.
Mrs. Newlin?
I know you're wondering
what this is all about.
Well, God needs your obedience,
God needs your will
and your faith.
And in due time,
all will be revealed to you.
Could somebody reveal a bathroom?
Because I really need one.
Sorry,
not till you've earned it.
Jumping jacks, everyone.
Let's go.
Maximum effort.
You too good for this?
I'm telling you right now,
I want to see a change in your attitude.
I want to see command presence.
You don't want to do the Lord's work?
You feel like walking away? Go ahead.
You stay, you drop and give me 30.
I said give me 30!
I'll tell you when you can laugh,
you pissant little sinner.
Give me 50.
Start pushing.
Anyone else?
That the best you ladies can do?
You disgust me, all of you! Pitiful!
I pray Jesus isn't
watching this crap today.
Come back.
I'm here.
I'm right here with you.
I was just thinking
about Sookie's gran.
She was like my real mom.
Such a good person.
Truly good, through and through.
- What would she think of me?
- She'd like you.
She did appreciate a handsome man.
Well, I wish I could've met her.
Me too.
She made this house the one
place in the world I felt safe.
And now I'm gonna live here.
Happy day after your birthday.
It was the only good one
I ever had, because of you.
The first of many, Tara Mae.
This is a continental breakfast?
What's wrong with it?
I just thought it would be more...
continental.
Well, the danishes are Danish.
- And they're free.
- Free?
I didn't know.
Would it be all right if...?
- Yeah, whatever.
- Now, Barry, let's get to it.
Why won't you just leave me alone?
Because I've never met
another telepath,
- have you?
- No.
- And don't say that word.
- It's what you are.
Nobody knows
what it's like to be us.
We need to stick together.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Yes, it is.
My life is shit.
I can't do anything
normal people do.
If I'm not around vampires,
I can't hardly think.
I used to feel exactly the same.
- Like I had a disability.
- More like a curse.
But lately,
since I met my boyfriend,
it seems like telepathy
can come in handy sometimes.
You can even make a little money.
I'm starting to see it
in a whole new way.
Then you're even crazier than I am.
Brazilian wax.
Feels like that bitch ripped
out my female organs.
Get a vamp to pay for laser.
Somebody bite me.
Concentrate. Shut her out.
Concentrate so hard your hair hurts,
till everything goes quiet.
- Concentrate...
- Quit!
Do you know if Hotel
Carmillais is hiring?
- There wasn't anybody at the desk.
- No, ma'am, we're fully staffed,
but you can fill out an application.
We'll keep it on file.
Come with me.
You can control it.
I wish it was true.
Barry, it is.
I can teach you how.
There's enough people
in my brain already.
You're on your own.
Right this way.
I dreamed you were gone.
You did?
That's funny, because...
I was.
It was only for a few minutes.
I had to.
Bill, it's the most amazing thing.
I met another telepath.
He's not very nice
and he's not very good at it.
But... it's wonderful knowing
there's somebody besides me.
You made him aware of your gift
after everything I've said?
Not on purpose.
We were in each other's heads
before we knew it.
I thought you'd be happy for me.
The more people know what you do,
the harder it is for me
to protect you.
He can't even admit
what he is to himself.
He's not gonna do
any talking about me.
- You can't be sure.
- Yes, I can.
I'm good at this.
If all I'm supposed to do in Dallas
is shut up and take orders,
I might as well be slinging
beers at Merlotte's.
You're the one who told me
I was more than a waitress.
You are.
- But...
- What?
Never mind.
Talk to me.
Lean on me.
I've leaned on you plenty.
Well, here I am,
responsible for you and Jessica,
and yet no decisions are mine
and it makes me feel...
Like a human?
Like a waitress.
You're walking in my shoes
and it's giving you blisters.
Eric is strangely intense
about all this.
It's not like him.
I don't trust it.
Don't you worry about Eric.
We'll do the job and go home.
A deal's a deal.
Sookie, you know what he's like.
What's it to him
to break a contract with a girl?
A woman.
He needs me.
He won't want to make me mad.
I can't lose you.
You never will.
Hope you're enjoying
that Co-Cola, Arlene.
Well, thank you, Daphne, I am.
Because unlike you, I actually
did my closing prep last night.
I'd appreciate it if you gave me a hand,
just for today.
Then you'll never learn.
Now, some people around here
might let you slide on by,
but I'm thinking
about your future as a server.
- That's real generous.
- Don't forget to make the iced tea.
Hey, good-looking.
Hey... you.
Could you make
the iced tea for me, please?
- Don't you do it.
- Please?
You better not.
- The hell with you all...
- See what you did?
Mean old freckle-face
redheaded witch.
Good morning, Daphne.
Back at you, boss.
Hey, why'd you take off last night?
I looked everywhere for you.
I just went for a little run.
You know, I always seem
to need one after a shift.
Hey, me too.
I reckon you had all you could
handle for one night
- anyway.
- I reckon you underestimate me.
- Guess we'll find out.
- When?
Soon.
Better be.
Terry, Lafayette's back!
Thank God, brother.
Thank God.
Can we talk?
Where the fuck have you been?
Couldn't pick up a damn phone?
Sorry.
Sorry's not good enough.
Not only did you leave us high and dry,
but there are people here
who give a shit about you.
We didn't know
if you were alive or dead.
Ordinarily, right about now,
you'd be telling me to fuck off
in some colorful and creative way.
Well, you want to talk,
do some talking.
All I want to know is,
can I have my job back?
I ought to tell you to fuck off.
All that pressure in the kitchen
just about put Terry back
in the VA hospital.
Of course you can have your job back.
The place ain't the same without you.
Thank you, Sam.
What happened to you?
It's midnight.
You're out of ammo.
You got five hungry vampires
snapping at your ass.
What are you gonna do?
- What are you gonna do?
- Run.
Run fast.
Get up.
You gotta keep going.
You have five hungry, snapping vampires.
Fuck it, I hate this, I just
want to be a bank teller again.
That's fine, dude.
Let the vampires chew you up.
You're not good enough
to lead for the Lord.
That's how you do it, Stackhouse.
- You better pace yourself.
- This is my pace.
Asshole.
Are you still here?
Or did you come back?
Karl and I slept over.
Don't you remember?
Maybe not.
You were having a very nice time.
What's all this?
Looks like we need a place to stay.
Stay today?
Stay tonight?
Little while.
But you have your own home.
That's not mine.
- What?
- It belongs to one of my clients.
He was out of the country,
but he's back this morning.
I'm sure I told you, no?
No. You... You didn't.
Look, I... I hate to tell you this,
but this isn't gonna work.
But I assumed...
And we've all been so happy
living together,
that you'd want to have us close.
Maryann, I'm a guest here myself.
I can't be having a houseful of people
Sookie doesn't even know.
She wouldn't mind.
You explain how much we mean to you.
Don't get me wrong,
I couldn't be more grateful
for everything you've done.
But I don't feel right about this.
You can't move in.
I'm sorry.
I see. Okay.
Did you know Maryann wants us
all to be roommates here?
No, cool. I guess that other guy
came back from Peru.
No, not cool.
Not gonna happen.
I just moved in.
Okay, fine, we can go
somewhere else, if that's how you feel.
That's all you got to say?
- Relax. It's no big deal.
- Are you, nomads? Fucking Bedouins?
We move around a little bit.
Nothing wrong.
Nothing except I didn't know.
You could've told me.
Who cares? What matters
is being with the people you love.
Other things matter too.
Like knowing the truth
about people you love.
So while we're on the subject,
what exactly is your thing
with Maryann?
When I was ready to lay down and die,
she lifted me up, same as she did you.
Now you follow her?
I'm not her dog, if that's
what you're trying to say.
And why all of a sudden are you
so paranoid about Maryann?
Because I'm trying not to be a fool.
You know what this is really about?
Your history's so fucked up,
you have no clue what family is.
That's not fair.
I do have a clue.
Sort of.
Kind of.
Who gives a damn about a house?
Maryann, Karl and me,
we take care of each other.
Of you.
That's family, Tara.
How are we gonna work on
our defensive tactics
if we can't even climb a fence?
Let's go.
Next, come on.
Come on.
Get up there.
Let's go, come on.
Come on.
- You should have paced yourself.
- If you're lying down,
you better be dead.
Stand up.
Come on.
Why do you embarrass me?
Why do you straight-out
embarrass me?
What's your name, failure?
Luke.
It's Luke.
Luke, your entire family
has been ambushed by vampires,
and they're bleeding to death
on the other side of this fence.
Yeah, they are.
Your mama and daddy
are drowning in buckets
of their own blood
calling your name.
It's gonna be over in 30 seconds.
Let's go.
Nice work, Luke.
They're gone. Massacred.
You'll never see them again
and it's your own damn fault.
- Stay right there.
- I tried.
Now what are you gonna you do?
He's a big fat loser.
He's brought shame on himself,
shame on you
and shame on his religion.
What's a real leader gonna do?
Just get rid of me.
Just leave me.
Up to you.
Luke, look at me.
It's only a damn fence.
Come on.
I got you, brother.
It's not too late.
You're gonna save your family.
Now that's a freaking soldier
of God.
Good job.
- Good job, Jason.
- Praise His light.
Good work!
- Next! Let's go, let's go.
- Come on, guys.
You should have told me Eric
hired a fucking human, Isabel.
Now, wait just a minute.
- Respect her.
- Thank you.
I couldn't tell you, Stan.
You've been off on your own for days.
Are you certain Godric was abducted
by the Fellowship of the Sun?
They're the only ones
with the organization and manpower.
But they're amateurs.
It doesn't make any sense.
This is Godric we're talking about,
2000 years old.
Old don't make you smart.
Besides, there's no proof.
If they've got him,
I'll hear it. That's my job.
There's no reason to wait.
We need to take these fanatics down.
Full-out attack.
Exterminate them
like the vermin they are,
leave no trace.
Vampire-hating church annihilated.
Wonder who did it?
Fucking brilliant.
I doubt the King of Texas
would approve the destruction
of our international
political agenda.
Fuck that.
The great revelation
is the biggest mistake
- we ever made.
- Don't use Godric
to make your own little power play.
You're completely incompetent!
What's happened to Godric
that he surrounds himself with clowns?
We invited you as a courtesy.
This is not your territory.
You have no voice here.
Yeah, sheriff.
Why don't you run on back down
to Louisiana?
We don't need you or your puppets.
I'm not going anywhere.
- And I'm nobody's puppet.
- What we need is a plan.
- I have a plan.
- It's not a plan, it's a movie.
It's not a movie,
it's a war.
Idiots.
- I'm in the middle of something...
- I know.
... you can't come in here
in front of my people.
- I want to talk to you about it.
- I've got to get them to respect me...
- We are supposed to be partners.
- We are partners.
Then why does Gabe
always know more than I do?
- I don't have time for this.
- You mean you don't have time for me.
This is very valuable information,
Gabe.
It's excellent work.
I told both of you,
I don't care for this.
You're going too darn far.
Thank you, Reverend Newlin.
I'll put things in motion.
Thanks.
You don't listen to me at all
anymore.
What?
- You wanted me?
- Yes! You were fantastic today.
- He was such a warrior.
- So you said. I'm impressed.
You're rising
to the next level recruit.
I am? What's that?
Come take a little walk with me.
- I'll go too.
- We got it, honey.
I'm going to show you something
that very few people have seen.
Man to man?
Sometimes I almost understand
why some people believe in divorce.
But you got Sarah.
I got her
even when I don't want her.
You know I'm just kidding.
- All right, you ready?
- Yes, sir.
Light of Day Institute
Research and Development.
Holy sh...
Holiness!
We're not exactly sure yet
of all the ways to take them out.
At first, we just focused
on the guns,
but then we thought,
"Hey, what's a wooden arrow?"
It's an itty-bitty stake.
That's right, Jason.
An itty-bitty stake
to drive through a vampire's dead,
rotten heart at 324 feet per second.
And that's all she wrote.
I got silver bullets,
silver bullets with holy water,
wooden bullets.
- We talked about those.
- Yes, sir.
A flamethrower.
Man!
Silver throwing stars.
Now, that I wouldn't
have thought of.
Decapitation might work,
so we got a guillotine on order,
just in case.
- What...?
- That's...
Machine like a giant razor.
Cuts the heads right off.
I bet that'd do it, all right.
There's one good thing about having
these hellbeasts among us:
we'll find better ways to kill them.
Keep it running.
We're not going in.
You wanna give me your order,
please?
We already gave our orders
to that other girl, twice.
Sorry, she sucks.
What's wrong with that fool bartender?
Where's our beers?
You don't need any beers.
Your butt's as big as a barn.
You look like you're pregnant.
Nice of you to show up
for work tonight.
I said I was sorry.
I would have got fired.
Lucky you slept with the boss.
Step up your game.
We're way behind.
Arlene, don't make me fire you
for talking trash.
You be nice to her, Sam.
It's Tara's fault, anyway.
- What's my fault?
- Sleeping where you eat.
Jesus Christ, Terry,
what'd I ever do to you?
You leave him alone
and give me my beers!
You know what?
Here they are.
- Fuck you very much.
- Fuck you too.
I'm gonna go just get my...
- Son of a...
- Go, Daphne.
Bitch!
Congratulations, Arlene.
You're Merlotte's Best Waitress
for Life.
Quite frankly, I aim higher.
Aim the plates for the tables,
that's all I ask.
I hope I'm nicer to the people
when I'm your age.
How freaking long
do I have to wait for my 7 and 7,
diet and rum,
two Scotches and a screwdriver?
- You never gave me that order.
- You just weren't paying attention.
- No, you weren't and yes, I was.
- Cos, what's the holdup on my tequila?
- You never asked me for a tequila.
- You know what? Tara's on drugs.
Tara, you high?
I wish I was,
the way everybody's dogging me.
Fuck all y'all!
Daphne, get up on my way.
We're done.
Get on outta here.
Bathtub's occupied.
I know.
Did I stay too long?
Do you want me to leave?
Please don't.
I'll help you.
Mary Magdalene washed
the feet of Jesus...
and dried them with her hair.
Isn't that lovely?
But wasn't she, like...
a hooker?
She was not.
Everybody thinks so,
but that's not in the Bible.
She admired Jesus,
she loved him,
and she wanted to show him.
You don't mean it.
No, I don't,
but I ought to.
Do you know what I think?
I think that after all your trials,
heartache and pain,
God wants you to have a reward.
Are you sure?
Let me reward you.
Let me help you find
your way back to joy.
We take them all out at once.
Pre-emptive strike.
Of course, so the federal government
can bombs us back to the Middle Ages.
Things were better then.
Then go to Romania and live in a cave,
you ranchero poser.
Godric has protected you,
made you rich,
and you stand here spitting
and scratching like infants.
Don't any of you care
that there's a traitor in your midst?
- No.
- Impossible.
Somebody tried to kidnap me
from the airport.
You were the only ones
that knew she was coming.
Explain.
- Unless it was you...
- Or you.
If y'all argue any more,
I'll either fall asleep
or start screaming,
so this is what we're gonna do:
I will infiltrate
the Fellowship of the Sun.
- Absolutely not.
- Let her speak.
Since Bill glamoured the kidnapper,
no one knows who I am.
I'll pretend to join the church,
and check out all their thoughts.
No. During the day,
none of us can help you.
It'll only take a little while.
Really, Bill. It's simple.
Waste of time,
when we could drink them all.
I want no part of this.
There's no easier way to find out
if they're involved.
If it leads us to Godric,
we'll do it.
The decision is made.
A few words.
So tell me,
how goes
your human-vampire relationship?
You knew it would come to this.
She was just clawed and poisoned
by a creature we don't know
and we can't find,
and now, in Dallas,
you're playing with her life.
It's no game to me.
All this for a colleague?
For the sheriff of Area Nine?
Why?
Godric is my maker.
Thanks for helping me close.
I broke a lotta things today,
it's the least I can do.
I'm sure you'll make it up to me.
I'm sure I will.
Nice,
you run a little hot.
Everybody else is...
98.6 but I'm always around 100, 101.
Me too.
It's a shifter thing.
I never knew.
I can't believe I'm the first one
you've ever met.
I mean, we're not common,
but we are out there.
Ran into a few werewolves,
but nobody like us.
What's it feel like when you change?
Like sparks
running all over my skin.
Used to scare the shit out of me.
Me too.
But now it just feels awesome.
There's...
There's sort of a build.
Like, a pressure.
Where does it start?
Here?
Maybe...?
Maybe here?
Probably here, because that...
That's where it hits me.
That's it.
Right about there.
And sparks start flying inside too.
And you feel all lit up
like a broke power cable.
Or a Christmas tree.
And you just...
explode.
Are you gonna say or should I?
Say what?
Nice rack.
Nice balls.
I have to ask a question.
Human stuff.
I'll wait for you at the elevator.
Excuse me, is Barry the bellboy
working tonight?
No, I'm sorry, Barry quit today.
What?
Shoot.
Are you waiting up for me?
I guess I am.
Rough night?
Really rough.
We looked at houses today.
We didn't find anything,
but don't worry,
we'll be out by morning.
I filled the fridge with your favorite
things and I made you dinner.
Don't go.
I'll call Sookie.
I want you to stay.
You're so good to me.
You know why I'm good to you?
Because you need it so much.
And because it makes you
bloom like a flower.
Look at you.
The King of Sheba.
Hey, baby.
You saw them in the lair tonight.
Despicable.
Vicious, petty, vile creatures.
You're different.
You're not like them.
Bill, you're not.
You have a heart,
whether it beats or not.
You can love.
There wasn't one other vampire there
that could say the same.
Let's slip away back
to Bon Temps right now.
Let them devour each other
and leave us alone.
You know we can't do that.
Stan's as nutty as a fruitcake
and I gave my word to Eric.
If anything happens to you
in that church...
Don't say it.
Don't even think it.
I'll be in and out,
easy-peasy.
It's been a long night.
Don't feel like you have to...
Quit talking crazy.
I just meant
I would be satisfied
to simply hold you.
I would not be satisfied.
Not one bit.
Then what do you want, Sookie?
Say it.
I want you.
Every which way.
I just...
want you.