Spicy.
Who's a pretty girl? Huh?
You're a pretty girl.
You're pretty.
Yes, you are.
Piss off.
I know it's not too good
to be all matchy-matchy,
but you and your...
dusky little bloodbeast
are totally at odds with my decor.
Nobody cares what you think
about anything. Shut up.
- I'm awful sorry.
- No, you're not.
- Good girl.
- Ignore him. He's the cleaning lady.
Psycho fugly thug.
You know him?
I thought I did.
Why is she here?
- She wants to be with me.
- Hence the restraints.
She's mine.
Relax. Nobody wants her.
Certainly not I.
Why is he here?
Because I have a present
for you, sir.
Please.
You're not supposed
to bring work home.
Darling, king.
You never disappoint.
Shall we retire to the study?
What is going on here?
What's wrong with you?
Your behavior is somewhat erratic.
Help me.
As always, the deposit
will go to your trust account.
But I want cash.
Last time you had any real money
you ended up at the slots in Biloxi,
slaughtering a group of elderly women.
They wouldn't let me have a turn.
Why are you dragging
another girl around?
So sloppy.
I'm tired of cleaning up after you.
This is one
is spectacularly different.
She's such a fucking disaster.
We could be twins.
The attraction is electric.
You're a huge freak.
But I like your work.
Bill Compton
is lying to me.
Yes, sir.
Who keeps a dossier on his human?
Why would he care about
her family tree?
Sophie Anne's overstated
perfume is all over this.
That's what I thought.
She's already escaped us once,
this barmaid.
Send a wolf, what'd you expect?
Maybe I should send you back
to Bon Temps
to acquire Sookie Stackhouse.
I don't have to go anywhere.
She's in Jackson.
I'll let you play
your little game of hard to get.
You're gonna be that much sweeter
when you're mine again.
You know, Russell was right.
You're not very smart.
You played yourself into a corner,
you tiresome cow.
What happened back there?
Why were they shifting?
- You almost shifted.
- Couldn't help it.
When that energy starts rolling,
it takes you over.
We're lucky we got out
of there alive. Fuck!
I know it was terrible-
You don't know anything.
If you don't slow down,
you're gonna kill us.
And I am not gonna die
because of your shitty girlfriend
and a Mississippi pothole!
I had to be mean to make you listen.
I'm sorry.
She wasn't always shitty.
We were great together.
When she wasn't drinking
or cheating.
She used to play horseshoes
with my dad,
help my mom plant tomatoes.
But tonight she was half-naked
in a wolf skin, getting branded.
Tell me more
about Russell Edgington.
He's just some rich vampire.
That's all I knew till tonight.
- I gotta talk to him.
- Are you out of your fucking mind?
The brand, the blood, the vampire.
He knows where Bill is,
or he knows who knows.
I promised Eric
I'd keep you out of trouble.
You ain't going near him, Sookie.
This is completely unnecessary.
I told you I come in peace.
Hello. Have we met?
Eric Northman, sheriff,
Louisiana Area 5.
I've come to see the king.
Talbot, royal consort.
Permit me to facilitate.
Let him go, you idiots.
I humbly request permission
to hunt your territory
for the vampire missing
from my area.
I appreciate your courtesy, Eric.
It's very old-world.
Nobody has manners anymore.
It was all so beautiful once.
Your fugitive,
what's his name again?
I'm responsible for him,
and I'm ashamed to admit it,
but he's wanted
for selling vampire blood.
That's heinous.
Are you sure?
Let's ask him.
Voilà.
He's not missing,
and he's way too square to deal V.
You tried to pin that on me?
We all know it's your queen
behind this, Northman.
And that you did
the selling for her.
You see, Mr. Compton has
accepted a position in my court
and therefore keeps nothing from me.
You're here of your own accord.
Which means...
Sookie is no longer mine.
A king in front of them,
a queen behind them,
and they're talking
about a human girl.
Men.
Your Majesty...
I confess.
I sold the blood at my queen's command
and accused Bill to protect her.
So, what do I do now?
Unless I give the Magister Compton,
he'll murder my progeny.
Darling, so sad.
The Magister
is a nasty little...
anachronistic toad,
a ridiculous remnant
of the Middle Ages.
The only power he has over us
is the power we give him.
There may be a way
to solve all our problems.
Sleep here.
You're more than welcome.
How can I refuse?
You can't just walk back in here.
Give me my key.
Shut up!
Don't tell me what to do!
It's my key,
and I'll use it whenever I want!
You walked out on me.
You got no right.
We'd still be together
if you weren't so weak!
- Keep it down.
- Don't tell me to keep it down!
Because I don't give a shit
about the neighbors!
I'm here to save your fucking life.
Liar. You drug addict.
You sold your soul to a vamp.
I saw you.
He's more than a vamp.
You ignorant redneck.
- If he knew what you saw...
- Fuck him.
I'm warning you...
if anybody
finds out
what went on at Lou Pine's...
That's your neighbor?
- Hell, no.
- She got nothing to do with this.
You're fucking my wolf, bitch.
In my house.
Like I did with Coot and Roy
and Bobby and Travis.
Like you did with Coot and Roy
What'd you say to me, whore?
I can throw you out,
blood or no blood.
No, I'm not sleeping with him.
But you traded this good person
who loves you
for a shot of V,
that burn on your back,
and a dumb biker who's half the man
and half the wolf that Alcide is.
I will fuck you up!
I will cut you!
Back off.
Where is Bill Compton?
Who the hell is Bill Compton?
Do you like your new gown?
I picked it out especially
for my lover.
Thank you so much.
Even when I'm away from you,
I can feel your flesh molded to me.
That's how close we are now.
That's really sweet.
I know.
Almost forgot.
You have a text message.
"Bitch, where are you?"
You said no boyfriends. Who is he?
Who's Lafayette?
I'll rip your throat out.
He's my cousin.
And he's gay.
Well, how do I get rid of him?
How about...
"I'm busy, bitch"?
No, "bitch." He wrote "bitch."
Too many "bitches. " "Hooker"?
In his other messages,
he calls you "hooker. "
"Hooker." No, "hookah".
That's a water pipe.
Tell him I'm okay.
Say, "Trust me, motherfucker."
"Trust me, motherfucker. "
Brilliant.
Watch how fast
I type "motherfucker".
It's cool, right?
Amazing.
I'll delete it
so you can watch again.
Look. Look at me.
Love you.
I'm a fan of the regular mulch,
myself.
That's good for everyday,
but I love that red mulch.
I use it in all my flowerbeds.
It would look so good
by your wishing well.
I don't know.
That seems kind of wild.
Morning, Kenya.
Morning, Kevin.
Morning.
- What you doing here?
- What am I doing? I'm here to work.
Really?
Chomping at the bit.
Point me at the crime scene
and let's go get her.
Acting Sheriff Andy Bellefleur,
would you come out here, please?
Can it wait? I was just going
to the restroom.
Morning, boss.
I'm ready for my first day.
I guess this means you find
my performance inadequate.
I'll if you don't get out to the corner
and cross them little kids to school.
What's going on, Andy?
Why does Jason Stackhouse
need a desk in the Sheriff's Department?
Nobody else is using it.
What do you care?
Run those folders in the conference room
over to the courthouse?
Please, Deputy Jones.
I don't want a desk.
I wanna be out in the field,
where it's real.
That's where I shine.
This ain't magic, Jason.
You gotta learn the ropes.
Trust me, I'm pushing you
through fast as I can.
Now, Rosie's home with female pains,
so for now,
you're in charge of the phones.
Can I at least have a uniform?
Let me get right on that.
Easy.
He's just showing me
how strong he is.
Makes me proud.
Watch it.
- That's your damn father.
- I know exactly who he is.
It's nothing.
It's a little game
they ought to play in private.
He'll make it up to me.
Won't you, boy?
Maybe you need to talk
amongst yourselves, all right?
Y'all listen to Sam.
He's always got the good ideas.
It's all been said.
Look at you.
You doing what I think you're doing?
Me, Terry Bellefleur...
I'm moving in with Arlene Fowler.
Congratulations.
You're cracking my ribs, buddy.
Now, it's gonna be okay.
Sure, it's scary.
She's a little crazy, but so are...
Is everybody, you know?
Don't worry.
I ain't worried.
I've never been so not worried.
This is what normal people do, Sam.
They fall in love.
They make each other laugh.
And they move in together.
They raise kids.
They fight over money.
They get old and fat together,
and it's normal.
And it's happening to me.
- I can't believe it.
- Well, I can.
Nobody deserves it more.
Baby?
I don't feel too good today.
I ain't cleaned nothing,
I ain't cleared nothing out.
I'm the luckiest man in the world.
Coming, honey.
We can't be kissing right now.
Just put that in the living room.
Happy for you, Arlene.
I never thought
it would happen again.
And again.
And that other time too.
But especially now.
Sweet Jesus, I am a hurting gator.
You know...
Hey, Joe Lee.
I got these tenants here.
You could be my on-site handyman.
Handyman?
I got a list as long as my leg.
- Well, if it don't hurt my back.
- He'd love to.
Time for work, bro.
Have a great day, Sam.
It's gone too far
and it's picking up speed.
I gotta tell the packmaster
everything.
Gonna run errands.
Won't take long.
- What's a packmaster?
- Goddamn it.
I gotta do what I gotta do.
This is were business.
We mustn't tell you anything.
I've been listening to private thoughts
since I was a little girl.
Keeping secrets is how I survive.
Then I'll have to dig it out of you,
and I really don't like to do that.
Pack isn't a democracy.
Most weres don't have much sense.
You saw.
They're all teeth and fight and sex.
Packmaster's our alpha.
He makes the big decisions,
keeps the rest of us in line.
How much does your packmaster
know about last night?
That's what I have to find out.
Then he'll tell us what to do.
- I'm coming along.
- I'm not breaking another rule for you.
Then you might as well
invite Debbie over to tear me up,
'cause that's what she'll try to do.
Work with me, Alcide.
It gets easier.
I'll take the car accident
on Euclid.
I'll take the vandalism over
at the high school.
What do I do?
File that for me.
You're driving me nuts.
I can't work a desk no more, Andy.
It's sucking the life out of me.
I need a cold case.
I need a special assignment.
I need some fucking thing
to do right fucking now
or I'll blow up like a M80
and take this whole place with me.
Don't worry.
I'll give you just what you need.
Suck on that thing.
Don't play with it.
There you go.
Now, this here cigarillo
is called a Macanudo Ascot.
But my personal favorite, boyfriend,
is the Schimmelpenninck panatella.
I don't care what they call it.
It tastes like shit.
Pussy.
Tommy, can you go inside for me,
please?
I got five more minutes.
Get, please.
How you doing?
What happened to her?
Excuse me?
You ain't got to be gentle.
She hated me and I hated her.
Just tell me how she died.
What, your mom?
Of course you'd think that.
I'm such a... idiot.
I should have told you from the start.
She's good.
She...
She threw her breakfast
in my face yesterday.
Well, that's good, I guess.
It's her style, for sure.
So, what are you doing here?
I came by to see you.
Somebody been talking to you?
You heard a conversation
with my name in it?
Because whatever was said,
it ain't fucking true.
And you best not tell nobody
for your own fucking sake,
you feel me?
Look, man, it's my day off.
I thought that maybe
you'd like to go watch a movie.
Me?
You don't want to. Forget about it.
I don't even know why...
It's a bad idea anyway.
It's just that I'm working.
- Till when?
- Eleven.
Eleven.
I would go with you, but...
No, I get it.
I'm going inside now.
What are you doing?
I'll hang.
It's only nine hours.
Nothing else to do.
After you.
Oh, Lordy.
If these were ordinary were junkies
scoring on the street,
I wouldn't be here,
but they're organized
and drinking from the source.
Sookie was there.
She can back me up.
You'll be disciplined
for exposing us to a human, Alcide.
Yes, sir.
It's not his fault. We only wanted
to tell you what we saw.
I already know all about it.
Then you have a plan?
Whatever it is, I support you, sir,
a hundred percent.
Do nothing, tell no one.
- How's that help the pack?
- Russell Edgington...
There's nothing I can do about him.
He's the goddamn vampire king
of Mississippi.
Colonel Flood,
That gang is recruiting.
We can't sit back and let some fanger
- pick us off one by one.
- Edgington is ancient.
He's had a pack of weres serving him
for centuries all over the world.
Now he's on our doorstep.
We gonna be smart.
Let him do what he wants to do
until he goes away.
If he's part of our history,
you should have told us about him.
I am saving us from extinction.
I'd rather be extinct
than slave to a dead man.
Don't know what else to do.
There's no one to help me.
He'll kill us all.
Maybe I'll just leave town.
I'm scared shitless.
Show no fear.
Don't question your packmaster, boy.
We gotta do something.
Let him go.
He can't help. He's afraid.
Bullshit.
Obey.
It wasn't bullshit.
I know.
I trust you.
"I'll give you what you need."
Goddamn piece of shit.
Son of a bitch.
Now what?
License and registration.
What for?
What'd I do?
We can discuss that further at a point
in time according to regulations.
License, registration
and your insurance card.
I don't think so.
You'd better.
- I'm a cop.
- I don't think you are a cop.
Are you resisting me?
Because if you are,
observe the official police vehicle
where I came out of.
Where's your badge?
Where's your gun?
Where's your shirt?
All right, all right.
It's no secret.
I'm a Deputy Sheriff liaison,
which means I'm in training.
But I'll be a cop real soon.
Real soon.
So give me your ID.
Please?
You don't give up, do you?
No, ma'am, I don't.
Why were you crying
the first time I saw you?
I wasn't crying.
I never cry.
I'm Jason Stackhouse,
and I wanna know you.
But since you're not gonna
write me a ticket,
because you're a fake policeman,
and I got milk and mayonnaise
in the back, well...
Well, at least tell me your name.
Crystal.
And your phone number.
No phone.
- Everybody has a phone.
- I don't.
- Meet me tonight at Merlotte's.
- Can't do it.
I'll be there, Crystal.
Excuse me,
can you hand me them peanuts?
How's your first night going?
I'd rather carry crap
than change tires.
Well, that's great.
It'll be a busy night.
Well, it's always a busy night
when you're the only waitress.
How come you never
look me in the eye?
Because I do not care
to be hypnotized,
which is apparently
what you walking dead people like to do.
Hi there.
Welcome to Merlotte's.
I have a very romantic
red vinyl booth for the two of you
right over there, and...
And whatever happens...
do not tip your waitress.
Do not.
Alrighty, then, let's go.
So you been here before?
Not since my daddy joined AA.
But it sure does feel good
to be back, especially with you.
You feel free to order
anything that you want.
- Doesn't matter how much it costs.
- Thank you.
I don't eat much.
I don't wanna get fat like my mama.
At least not
until I had a baby or two.
I can't wait to have babies.
I'm real excited about it.
Probably in like another two years
or so, but...
What's the matter?
My ex.
What, him?
For real?
He look like he got bombed by radiation
on his way to middle school.
That's a giant sixth-grade boy
right there.
You don't know him.
He's really very sweet.
Come on.
He's Little League.
You're a smoking-hot vampire.
You're the majors.
And a "hell, yeah" too.
What?
Get your ass home now.
No, I'm not gonna.
I got a job now.
I don't give a shit about no job.
Do what I say when I say it.
You hear me, you little shit?
Why?
Tara, why?
I was afraid.
Of me?
You were afraid of me?
That's insane.
But you tied me up.
To keep you safe.
What other reason could there be?
You have no idea
how much you've hurt me.
I feel like I've been staked.
I'm sorry, Franklin.
It's my fault.
My head is all confused.
Can you forgive me?
It's not you I'm afraid of,
it's this place.
All the other vampires...
they're the ones who scare me.
I'll never let them touch you.
There's only you.
They don't exist.
You've circled certain names here.
I wonder why.
You're joking.
Am I?
I never saw this
before you showed it to me.
I don't even know what it is.
Where did it come from?
Franklin Mott found that,
in your house.
With all due respect,
why would you believe him?
It's my word against his.
Well, exactly.
He's an old friend.
- I'd trust him with...
- Your genealogy?
My genealogy.
Earl Stackhouse, Sookie Stackhouse.
Those are the circled ones.
I have a theory, Bill.
Do you know what I think?
No, but I'm fascinated.
I think telepathy runs
in this family.
I think you've been playing
Track the Telepath.
You are trying to discover
the origins and the meaning
of your human's curious
mental condition,
because somehow,
somewhere,
there is a payoff.
It's a theory beautifully built,
of air and imagination.
But it has nothing to do
with me, sir.
Excuse me, sir, can I talk to you?
In private?
Guard!
Buddy.
I deserve more of a welcome than that,
the news I got for you.
Sorry, I'm just kind
of waiting on somebody.
I pulled every string in my collection
on your behalf today.
I'm a deputy?
Pretty damn close.
They'll wave everything
but the physical.
- Boy, I'm in.
- And the written exam.
Wait, we talked about this.
I can't take no test.
You gotta. Come on, it's easy.
You just shove all that stuff
in your head, write your answers,
and forget it all the next day,
learn on the job, like everybody else.
Come on, get your head up off the floor.
You'll do great.
Who's the girl?
Got a new one?
Don't matter.
She ain't coming.
You gonna break?
You break.
Or I will.
Whatever you want.
You drove all this way
and waited all day
and most of the night so...?
It was fun.
You know?
Drinking beers,
talking to people.
Watching you do your thing.
My thing? That?
No, no, that is not my thing.
Still got to look at you.
Did you look at me?
I can't be looking with all that grease
flying around the kitchen.
Right.
But I saw you.
Every now and again.
So we gonna play?
I'll play.
And I'll break.
I don't want you coming
in here running the table,
making me look bad.
I don't think that's possible.
Listen at you talking
all that bullshit to me.
Can I stay with you tonight?
How come?
You know... brother time.
- You tell your folks, though.
- Yeah, I will.
I mean it.
I said I would, and I will.
You're lying, and that puts me right
in the middle of the Mickens,
which is exactly
where I don't wanna be.
Something's going on with you all.
I feel it.
I know it.
What does Joe Lee want from you?
Nothing.
He's just a prick.
You can talk to me, Tom.
Sure.
You're a little edgy, bat boy.
- Get out.
- What are you gonna do?
Tell the king?
He's off you, bro.
You're on his shit list.
Everybody knows it.
Even his dirty little lapdog.
You know what else I hear?
And this is sexy good news.
You're gonna love this.
I know I loved it.
Your Bon Temps piece of country ass,
your little blond ho
is fucking a werewolf
right here in Jackson.
- Suck that dick.
- Where?
Where is Sookie?
Thought you stood me up.
I didn't.
I tried to go in there
a couple times.
It was too...
This ain't right.
I shouldn't be here.
I shouldn't be anywhere near you.
Why?
It's the way it is.
You don't understand,
and I can't explain.
Listen, don't go.
I gotta.
Take a walk with me.
Just a little walk.
You're an outdoor girl.
I'll tell you that for nothing.
You're happy here in the woods.
Maybe so.
I'm that way too.
We got that in common.
Something's happening to us.
I don't wanna jinx it.
Those things you can't explain.
I don't care about 'em.
That's what you say now.
I'm pretty sure I mean it.
And I just might mean it forever.
There is no forever for us.
It's only now.
- That ain't true. It couldn't be.
- It is true.
Now is everything.
Now is perfect.
I've never been happier
in my whole life
than I am right now with you.
If you don't want me
to touch you more,
if you want me to stop here...
I'm gonna have to step away,
because I'm...
I'm all upset.
We got that in common too.
Please accept my apologies.
- A matter to which I must attend.
- Trouble?
Not really.
More of an experiment.
Perhaps I can be of service.
Indulge my boy Talbot, will you?
Let him give you the full tour.
Makes him positively blithe.
I have a child of my own
in the Magister's bony hands.
- If you could help as soon as poss...
- All in good time, Eric.
You.
Boys only.
Show me everything.
Man.
That's a call, right there.
Don't open it.
What do you mean, don't open it?
Fuck.
You sneaky shifter piece of shit.
Give me back my boy.
Tommy, get over here.
I'll beat you blind.
Breaking down my door?
Who the hell do you think you are?
- Go home.
- I ain't leaving without my son.
- He ain't going anywhere with you.
- You don't get it,
you dumb motherfucker.
I own him,
head to tail.
Fuck you, you broke-down bastard.
You don't own shit.
You live in a house I own.
You wanna keep it, get out,
before I throw your ass
in the parking lot!
You don't think I'll do it?
I'll do it.
I'd love to do it.
Sorry.
I'm liquored up.
I can't even think straight.
He's gotta...
to learn responsibility.
It'll all be better in the morning.
What the fuck was that?
What's the matter?
Who made you cry?
I'll kill him.
Nobody.
It's only I'm hungry,
and they brought me this.
And I can't eat day lilies.
Tell Talbot we don't want
his fucking flowers!
And don't come back!
She wants to be with me!
God, you are sexy.
We need to talk.
Don't say that.
Women say that, everything goes black,
and I wake up surrounded
by body parts.
Baby, no, no, it's okay.
That's not where I'm going at all.
I'm into you.
I mean, really into you.
But if we're gonna be together,
you have to remember
that I'm alive.
I have needs,
like food.
- You're right. I'm ashamed.
- No, baby, it's just a thing.
- I'll remind you.
- I can do better.
- Let me take you somewhere for dinner.
- I would love that.
There's Shoney's in Vicksburg.
Great.
We'll celebrate
your last night as a human.
What?
I'm proposing.
I'm gonna turn you.
Will you be my vampire bride?
And what is this?
Japanese vampire erotica
from the 16th century.
Exquisite detail.
You learn any tricks?
You know as well as I
there's nothing new except someone new.
It's an eclectic collection.
You should see
what we have in storage.
Russell's a greedy little boy.
He wants what he wants
and he takes it.
He's the same way about people.
Watch out.
And this?
Some random tribal crown.
He must have a hundred of them.
This one's Scythian, I think.
Viking.
It's beautiful.
Quite.
You have to go now.
Is that all you have to say to me?
There's no time.
You must take her away.
Wherever I'm going,
you're coming too.
It's too late.
There's no hope for me.
You've gotta get her out of Jackson
as fast as you can.
- I believe him.
- What do you mean, there's no hope?
You have to leave now.
I will, but tell me
what I'm running from.
Come on in.
That's for Debbie, fucker.
Grab the girl, you imbecile.
Uncle Coot is gonna get you.
Maybe not!
Fantastic!