Guess who turned out to be
completely unworthy of our trust.
Why? What's happened?
He's been hiding something very...
interesting from us all.
Are you serious?
I am almost 3000 years old.
Eric, get her out of here, please.
Eric, what are you doing?
I wouldn't let go of this
if I were you.
I don't know what it is,
but I do know it's quite valuable.
Eric, what the fuck?
I've not had the pleasure
of tasting it,
but all my instincts say
it would be quite extraordinary.
I will never,
ever forgive you for this.
It thinks we're equals.
But it's wrong.
- Isn't it?
- Indeed.
Do you care nothing about our home?
- Talbot, not now.
- When?
What are you going to do
with our Mr. Compton,
if I may ask?
Marco, Klaus, take Mr. Compton
to the slave quarters.
There, my dear, you will kill him.
- But what's...?
- Do not defy me!
I am your king!
Your Majesty.
Take Miss Stackhouse
into the library, Eric.
I wanna ask her a few questions
after I repair the state
of affairs of my marriage.
Bill, I will get you out of here.
You save her, I beg you.
If you do kill him...
I will kill you.
Please.
Please try.
Without that sanctimonious
little prick, Godric,
to save you,
I would just love to rip you open
and wear your rib cage
as a hat.
Please tell me you were just doing that
for the king's benefit.
I don't think anyone plays the king
of Mississippi and gets away with it.
I certainly have no intentions
of trying.
Why are you even here?
You had other things to deal with.
I do, and I need to think.
So please don't take this
the wrong way, but shut up.
Eric, please, I'm begging you...
What is your...
vegetable of the day?
That would be the peas.
How are those prepared?
Those are dumped out of a can
into a big pot and heated up.
Where do you think you are, lady,
Red Lobster?
I am paying good money to eat here.
You wanna keep
any of that cheap dyed hair
you better stop mouthing off to me.
Tap the titty.
That sucked.
And not in a good way.
- Lafayette, I got an order.
- What?
Sam and Tommy already done gone.
Ain't we closed yet?
Curlers over there
wants the chicken fried steak,
extra gravy on the side, extra mash,
no veggies.
- Hell, no.
- You want me to help?
Can you cook?
I can do a lot of things.
Oh, Lordy.
"And I want a freshly cut
lemon in my iced tea,
" not some dried-out thing
that's been sitting around all day."
Dagnabbit.
Look what I just did.
I got lemon juice on it too.
Sorry. Arlene,
sometimes it just happens.
Please don't kill me.
I'm pregnant.
That probably just makes
you wanna eat me even more.
This is why people hate y'all.
I just haven't eaten in days.
I love how warm you are.
I feel like I'm on fire.
Me too.
That's because we are...
on fire.
I ain't no virgin.
Me neither.
But you make me feel like one.
Not me.
You make me feel
like 110 percent woman.
Don't hurt me.
Or do.
I don't care.
What the hell's
that supposed to mean?
I ain't into any pervert stuff.
What?
I didn't mean it like that.
Then what in blazes
was it you did mean?
I meant...
Don't break my heart.
What did I say?
This ain't right.
It ain't
I wanted to just get a taste
of something
I could remember forever, but...
Goddamn it, I ain't gonna
let you see me cry.
There's no reason for you to cry.
Not when you're with me.
I'll take care of you.
I gotta go.
Keep it down.
- I ain't letting you go.
- Ain't nobody owns me.
When am I gonna see you again?
Never. This can't happen.
It's too dangerous.
Dangerous? Why?
Just forget me, for both our sakes.
So all that stuff about caring
about me, that was just crap?
I never said I cared about you.
Maybe you dreamt it.
You big phony.
Big hat, no cattle.
Do you mind?
I'm trying to think here.
I thought you said my life was
too valuable to throw away.
You are valuable, that's very clear.
I'm just not sure why.
"I'm risking everything,
because you mean so much to me.
"You make me feel almost human."
You mean nothing to me,
understand? Nothing.
I'm close to getting something
I've wanted since I was still human.
Do not get in my way.
I hate your fucking guts,
Eric Northman.
I promise I will
pay you back for this.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
A husband's work is never done.
- Leave us.
- As you wish.
Now, tell me what you are.
I'm a waitress.
Yes, and I am Marie of Romania.
I'm a very patient man,
Miss Stackhouse.
One can afford to be
when one is immortal.
But my patience
is not without limits.
God, I hate leaving the kids
with Terry this long.
He's always so frazzled
when I get home.
Where's Lafayette?
He and that Jesus guy left.
Said to tell you to lock up
before you leave.
But just so you know,
this necklace is pure silver,
and I take garlic supplements too.
Just because my fangs popped out,
doesn't mean I'm gonna use 'em on you.
I just wish this awful night
was over.
You know every single one
of my customers stiffed me?
Let me take care of her for you.
Don't kill her or anything.
Excuse me, ma'am?
You're not hungry anymore.
I want you take all the money you have
and leave it on the table
then head to the ladies', alrighty?
She'll be gone soon.
You okay in there?
Ma'am?
Thank you so much.
You are the best waitress
I've ever had.
Not such a bad night after all, huh?
You got a nice tip
and nobody got killed.
See you tomorrow.
No fucking way.
So what?
I was born here.
You never wanted to leave?
Ever since the day I was born.
I've been places,
I just never stayed.
I've always come back here.
You're not done with this place.
Feels like it's not done with me.
So where you from?
- I was born in Catemaco.
- Catemaco.
But mi mami dragged me
all over the fucking globe.
Texas, Uruguay...
Portugal, you name it.
Montreal.
No papi?
No, I've got one.
It's just nobody knows who he is.
Mami was raped.
Get the fuck out.
Makes all those jokes your mom
cracks about me raping her
that much funnier.
Maybe I was wrong about you.
Maybe I actually can relate
to you.
Why would you think
that you couldn't?
Does term "Satan in a Sunday hat"
mean anything to you?
Bitch, my name is Jesus, bro.
I am the polar opposite of Satan.
You'd better be.
Can I kiss you?
Fuck me.
I shouldn't have asked.
I should have done it.
I have a rule, though.
No sex on the first date.
Sometimes I have a hard time
keeping that rule.
I think we should follow that rule.
- Give us somewhere to go.
- Yeah, right.
Unless...
Because I'm feeling something
all kind of intense with you.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
I'm not sure I should trust it.
I'm getting kind of hard
just looking at you.
Damn.
Isn't it warm out for a fire?
I suppose it is.
I love a good fire.
There's something
primal about it.
Always makes things more dramatic.
Now...
it's time for you
to answer my questions.
Fine. I have some questions
for you too.
Honey.
There's a fine line
between feisty and delusional.
You're not really
in any position to bargain.
- You don't know that.
- Now it's getting interesting.
So I'll answer one of your questions
and you'll answer one of mine?
Who goes first?
Are you the king of all vampires?
Heavens no, my dear girl.
I am merely the king of Mississippi.
- Do you have a crown?
- I have several.
That's two questions.
My turn.
What are you?
You're definitely not human.
- My parents were human.
- How do you know?
And how do you know they were
your parents, for that matter?
My grandfather was like me.
Which is?
I can hear people's thoughts.
And shifters', werewolves'.
Not vampires'.
How dreadful that must be.
Oh, you have no idea.
Who cares
what anyone else is thinking?
My turn.
Is Lorena gonna kill Bill?
If she knows what's good for her.
But she'll take her time.
He's been her drug of choice
for centuries now.
She's gonna have a hard time
letting go.
Please.
You can stop her.
Why would you want me to?
Are you aware
that your noble Mr. Compton...
has been keeping
a secret file on you?
On your family?
- What the...?
- My turn.
What are you besides a telepath?
And what on Earth makes that light
come out of your hands?
Don't make me force it out of you.
I don't know.
I never even knew I could do it
until recently,
and I don't know what I am.
Maybe I'm an alien.
All I know is it's something big,
so if I were you I wouldn't hurt me
or anyone I care about.
- Are there other powers?
- It's my turn.
Are there other powers?
Once I threw a chain at somebody
and it wrapped around his neck
by itself,
like that face-crab thing
from Alien.
That's all.
No wonder the queen is so...
fascinated by you.
There's a queen?
Sweetheart.
You really don't know
anything at all, do you?
I do miss the 1930s.
Such style,
elegance.
People knew how to behave,
and what was expected of them.
They knew how to avoid
creating tragedies,
for the people they loved.
I may not be able
to make you feel...
anything for me,
but...
I will make you feel.
You have always so enjoyed
making others suffer.
And there's nothing wrong with that.
Especially having been made
to suffer...
as I have been.
You haven't suffered
at the hands of others
for a very long time.
I am suffering now.
Please,
do it quickly.
Even as you face the true death...
I will be inside you.
Not Sookie,
me.
I wish I had known you
before you were made,
before you turned hard.
I would've liked
to have seen you smile,
with light in your eyes...
instead of darkness.
That...
would have been something.
I have no choice.
Where you been?
Tara, I will not be policed.
Of course not. I'm not pol...
I just really missed you, Franklin.
Couldn't wait for you to get back.
Really?
It's hard to believe.
You haven't even noticed
that I've shaved.
I wanted to...
I wanted to look nice for you.
It's our wedding night tomorrow.
By the way, your friend Sookie,
she's been brought here.
What is Russell gonna do to her?
So that means
my work for Russell
is officially over,
which means you've got me...
all to yourself.
Don't promise me something
you can't deliver, now.
Untie me.
Two hands are better than none.
Why,
you wicked little strumpet.
I'm gonna drink your blood
tomorrow night.
- Oh, yes, you are.
- I want it now.
I wanna experience
being high on you,
while making love to you.
Knowing it's my last act as human,
I wanna have the most amazing sex
any human can have,
before I give myself to you...
Kinky.
Fucked up.
Crazy.
- I'll go there.
- I bet you will.
- Will you?
- Bring it.
Bite me.
Bite into my flesh, taste my blood,
my sinew, my bones.
Open me up.
Taste me, drink me,
feed on me.
You don't have to ask me twice.
Fuck, yeah!
Kill me.
Kill me hard.
Wait a minute.
That's not how you play Kaiserspiel.
Kaiserspiel?
We're playing Karnoffel.
I'm sorry.
I haven't played this game
in centuries.
Russell taught me this game
when I was still human.
How long have you been together?
Just shy of 700 years.
Although sometimes
it feels like 7 million.
Well, I hope he knows
just how lucky he is.
Believe me...
- he knows.
- Get your hands off me!
- Carlo! Take this.
- Let go of me.
- And have Timothy bring the car around.
- Let me go!
- Where are you going?
- I have business.
- Again?
- Yes.
Save Bill!
Would you accompany me this evening?
- It would be an honor.
- You never take me anywhere.
Because you prefer
to be in the company of sycophants.
Deep down, my darling,
you're a very weak character.
He's in one of his moods.
Never mind.
We have much more pressing
matters at hand.
We're gonna see
an old friend of yours.
Get your creepy hands off me!
I have powers!
I'll use them, I will!
Don't worry, Sookie,
I'm gonna get you out.
Wait until the sun comes up.
I'll find you. Be ready.
Because we're gonna need
all the luck in the world,
but I'm gonna get us out of here.
I'm not giving up without a fight.
You have no idea
what awaits you on the other side,
my beautiful bride.
No more pain.
No more fear.
No more rules.
Tell me, Eric...
- May I call you Eric?
- Certainly.
What exactly is your relationship
with Miss Stackhouse?
Well, her lover, Bill Compton, is...
Was a constituent of mine.
I'd keep an eye on that
because she was of interest
to my queen.
So, no personal attachments?
I do not get attached to humans.
Still, you have to admit,
she is quite delectable.
My tastes lie elsewhere.
Lorena thinks
you killed one of my werewolves.
I killed a werewolf.
I was not aware it belonged to you.
To save Sookie?
To save myself.
I wanted to question her
regarding Bill's disappearance,
and it attacked me.
Only a very young
and very foolish vampire
could be killed by a werewolf.
You are neither.
Only a vampire with no self-respect
would save this werewolf.
They are primitive creatures,
and I will freely admit
that I despise them.
You're the first vampire I met
who didn't feel the same way.
Of course I do.
They're more dog than man.
Stupider than dogs, actually.
But it seems beneficial to me...
to use them,
rather than destroy them.
How exactly do you use them?
I give them the blood.
Come, now. I know that you yourself
have been dealing,
so don't pretend
to be a vampire fundamentalist.
If all the supernaturals would stop
squabbling among themselves
and unite,
we could conquer humans
in a matter of days.
- This is your plan?
- I prefer to call it my dream.
Well, I like this dream.
Throughout history,
I have aligned myself with
or destroyed those humans in power,
hoping to make a dent
in mankind's race to oblivion.
What other creature
actively destroys its own habitat?
You're preaching to the choir.
I mean, do you remember
how the air used to smell?
How humans used to smell?
How they used to taste?
I remember everything.
Preening little fool that he was,
Adolf was right about one thing.
There is a master race.
It's just not the human race.
Should we have taken the I-12 exit?
We're not going to Shreveport.
Don't worry.
We'll deal
with your Magister problem in time.
Well, this is my...
humble abode.
It's amazing.
You think so?
And that...
That is beautiful.
That's my girl.
Tonantzin.
No, that's the Virgin Mary.
But it's also...
Eleggua and Chango.
These guys
are pretty fucking hard-core.
What do you offer them?
Lafayette, man, these guys,
they have to be appeased, bro,
or else they will fuck you up.
Seriously,
I sing for Eleggua.
I put out shots of tequila for Chango.
He drink 'em?
Smart-ass.
He blesses 'em,
and then I drink them.
Well, maybe I should put out
a couple of shots for him right now.
Or...
we could offer him something else.
Evening, faggot.
Bitch.
First your fucking non-American car,
faggot.
We gonna fuck you up, cocksucker.
Yeah, fucker.
- Shit.
- Last time you fuck with me.
- Dumb-ass hillbilly.
- Shit.
Make no mistake, cracker.
You're gonna get
my fucking ride fixed.
How am I supposed...
Ain't my fucking problem.
Why don't you just sell all that shit
I dropped by your house last night?
I ain't selling no vampire blood.
It's evil.
And crystal meth ain't?
Calm down, man. You got him.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go tell your mama
two faggots whupped your ass, bitch!
Come on.
Are you a drug dealer?
And V?
Man, that shit's so intense,
it ruins most people's lives.
You know what, man?
Just take me back to my car.
Whatever you want, bitch.
Ludis! Another hundred dollars.
Hadley, Ludis,
go down to the Circle K.
Get me a couple hundred more
Deuces Wild tickets.
Mama's feeling lucky tonight.
Mama couldn't be more wrong.
- You killed my guards.
- Only a handful.
The rest were surprisingly
unwilling to die for you
and have defected.
Hadley?
Your human is safe.
I'm not here to needlessly slaughter.
- What do you want?
- You,
my darling Sophie Anne.
I want you...
to accept my proposal of marriage.
I've turned you down
countless times.
Why would I accept now?
Because in addition
to never touching you,
I will settle all your debts.
Come on.
The Magister
will eventually determine
it was you
who was selling our blood.
I've already pinned it
on Eric Northman.
Is that really all you've got?
There's the IRS.
The American Vampire League
will let them put you in prison,
make an example of you,
assuage the right wing's fears
about vampires running Wall Street.
They have no dominion over me.
I'm a queen.
I have known some of the finest queens
who've ever lived.
You,
my dear girl,
are no queen.
Go fuck yourself.
Sweetheart, you go fuck yourself.
I am older and stronger than you.
I only submitted to you in the past
because of respect.
But you framed me.
So I renounce any
and all allegiance to you.
I am his now.
I refuse to grant you...
I will rip your head off
and throw it in the pool.
And I will have fun doing it.
Your call.
Very well, then.
So, yes or no?
Goddamn it.
Splendid.
Sun will be up soon.
We'll spend the day here.
We'll stop by Fangtasia
- on our way back to Jackson.
- As you wish.
I hope I didn't overstep any boundaries
just now.
I quite enjoyed that.
It is my honor,
and my duty,
my king.
I'll make sure your betrothed
is properly restrained.
I want my Hadley!
You should go to ground.
And not be with you
when the life flows out of you?
I cannot.
And what will you do then?
Find another man
that you deem honorable?
So that you can turn him into a...
violent, hateful thing
like yourself,
destroying whatever it was
you loved about him to begin with?
It's all my fault, isn't it?
You never enjoyed
killing those humans,
writhing naked in their blood,
making love to me
as the light died in their eyes.
I forced you to do all that.
You did not.
Be a man...
... and admit you liked it.
Just as you liked,
enticing all those starving men
with your flesh,
luring them
into your maker's clutches
so that he could murder them,
and defile their bodies
in unspeakable ways as you watched.
I am not István.
Really?
He made you his mirror,
just as you tried to make me yours.
He is the reason that a girl,
who once marveled
in the beauty of all life,
now delights in...
bringing pain and horror
to every moment.
You never embraced our nature.
Your nature...
was never mine.
I welcome death.
Because only then...
will I be truly free
of the disease...
that is you.
Come on, Peaches.
We gotta get us some.
Sorry, ma'am.
We kind of thought you
would've retired for the day.
Aren't you supposed
to be patrolling the grounds?
We was just gonna keep an eye
on your prisoner for you,
make sure he didn't get away.
Really?
And I suppose feasting on his blood
never crossed your minds.
It's my fault, ma'am.
I begged Coot to let me get some.
And I got a bone to pick
with this asshole.
He jumped me last night,
killed three of my wolves last week.
Come on.
Let us just have a little taste.
It's just going to waste
all over the floor like that.
Of course.
Suck whatever's left
right out of him.
Fuck, yeah!
Drink directly from the source, right?
This is for Louie, fanger.
And Darryl.
And Jimmy.
This is just 'cause I fucking
feel like it.
You mind?
I'm trying to eat here.
Come on, baby.
Let's turn this here dead man
into a fucking raisin.
That is simply not true.
You can't hypnotize away
the facts, Miss Flanagan.
Ratification would send
a bad message to our nation's children.
It would be tantamount to
full-on government endorsement
of deviant vampiric behavior.
The American people
are too smart for this fear-mongering.
- It's not fear-mongering.
- Please.
We have all seen
that leaked fundraising presentation
which outlines
an aggressive strategy
that's designed to capitalize
on fear and misinformation.
It's all a vast
right-wing conspiracy.
It's no accident at claims of how we
intend to prey on America's children...
Thanks for letting me crash here
last night.
You gonna tell me what's going on
between you and Joe Lee?
Why he came after you last night?
- You scared of him?
- I ain't scared of him.
I just hate him.
He's a drunk.
Gambles away any money we ever get.
Fuck him.
He's the one scarred you up?
- He wishes.
- Don't lie to me.
I ain't lying.
He ain't never laid a hand on me.
He knows better.
Well, there's something messed
up between you and him.
Now, you may not wanna talk about it,
but we're gonna talk about it.
But I'll talk about it
when I'm ready.
Fair enough, long as it's today.
Good morning.
I brought y'all a mess
of my secret-recipe corn fritters
fried in bacon grease.
You ain't had good
till you've had these, Sam.
Thank you, Melinda.
When you gonna start
calling me Mama?
Soon as it starts
to feel comfortable.
Well, you take your time, darling.
We got a lot of road to cover,
you and me.
Can I have a little
heart-to-heart with my youngest?
It's okay.
I'll just take these fritters
with me.
Put 'em on the lunch menu.
You wait and see.
Folks will be lining up for them.
"It's okay"? It's okay
for your own mama to talk to you?
He's looking out for me.
Wellho the hell's looking out
for me and for Joe Lee?
I don't give a shit of him.
Listen to me, little boy.
You wouldn't be here
if it weren't for him.
I was ready to end my pregnancy
'cause it would take me off the circuit.
It was Joe Lee who said I ought
to go ahead and have you,
case you turned out to be
a shifter like me.
What a saint.
He wanted to use me
just like he'd been using you.
That man ain't never left me
no matter what, and he could've.
You're the one that never left.
He ain't leaving
because we're his goddamn meal ticket.
And what would we do without him?
You ever think about that?
My back's done shot from all
the years I spent in the ring.
I ain't able to work now.
You wanna just leave me to rot
in an alley somewhere?
Course no, Mama.
I did it till I couldn't do it anymore,
and now it's your turn.
It ain't right.
The world ain't right,
you selfish little shit.
Without you, we ain't gonna survive.
We can't do it.
- Yeah, but maybe with Sam's help...
- You can't trust Sam.
He may be blood,
but he ain't family.
And he ain't never gonna be.
He looks down on us.
Thinks he's better than us.
- Yeah, maybe he is.
- Yeah, maybe the fuck he is.
But you think he's willing
to take care of us over the long haul
once he knows the truth?
Me and Joe Lee's all you got, son,
all you ever will have.
And in your bones,
you know that to be true.
Fuck.
Who the hell are you?
I'm here to see Crystal.
What for?
That's between me and Crystal.
Is that so?
All right.
Babe.
Somebody here to see you.
Who the hell are you?
What? Crystal, it's me, Jason.
It's a joke?
I ain't never laid eyes on you.
I don't know
who put you up to this or why,
but it's not funny.
And I'd appreciate it
if you'd leave and my fiancé alone.
- Fiancé?
- You heard the lady, asshole.
Why don't you get off our land
before we kick you off?
Yeah, dumb-ass.
What's taking so long?
Bitch already said
she ain't know you.
Sorry, ma'am.
Must have confused you
with somebody else.
You showed him.
Whoever the hell he was.
- That little blond girl isin there?
- What's it to you?
Talbot's serving her blood
for dinner,
and she's only supposed
to be eating almonds.
- That's what it is to me.
- Nobody told me about almonds.
If she ain't eating that,
Talbot ain't gonna be happy.
If he ain't happy,
Russell ain't happy.
If Russell ain't happy, you dogs
ain't getting any vampire blood.
Now open up the goddamn door.
Great. You fell asleep
and let her escape?
- Come on.
- What the hell are you doing?
Killing vampires
and saving your ass.
I'll fill you in later. Now
let's get the hell out of here.
Eggs over easy, sausage,
white toast.
And he wants them eggs runny...
I know what over easy mean,
goddamn it.
Well, you're in a sorry mood today.
That's right, I am in a fucking
sorry-ass mood.
You got a fucking problem with that?
Have you seen Tommy?
No, and I got two tables
need busing.
Oh, and, Sam?
I thought you had a no-pet policy
on those apartments.
I do.
I see.
Unless it's your kinfolk?
I don't appreciate you
letting them have that dog
when Coby and Lisa
can't have a hamster.
What dog?
That mean-ass looking pit bull
that your mama and daddy brought out
and piled into their van this morning.
Like you don't know.
I got kids, Sam.
I can't be having some killer dog...
Damn, everybody's ignoring me today.
Goddamn it.
He's got werewolves
patrolling the grounds by day.
But if we can get to
one of his cars, hotwire...
I've gotta find Bill.
What? He was covered in blood.
He was gonna let them kill me.
I ain't risking my life to save
his dead ass, and neither should you.
He may not be dead,
and they forced him to do that.
That's not who he is.
I am not leaving without him.
Then you're a fucking idiot.
Just find us a way out of here.
- Thanks for getting here so fast.
- What the hell's the goddamn emergency?
Well, listen.
I need to know
if there is any dogfighting
in Renard Parish.
Hell, no. We don't allow that.
What about nearby?
I can't share official intra-parish
intelligence with civilians.
Lives are at stake.
And speaking of, I already saved
your sorry ass once, so you owe me.
I heard about some raids
over in Union Parish recently,
down towards the north end of Bernice.
Thanks, buddy.
Get the sheriff
anything he wants for breakfast,
on the house.
Where the hell'd you learn
to drive, Sam Merlotte?
- Get out of the vehicle, please.
- What?
Get out of the fucking vehicle, boy.
Don't make me say it again.
- You can't...
- Ma'am, nobody's talking to you.
I'm gonna give you one last chance
to get out of the vehicle
before I start to get mad.
What the fuck, dude?
I'll tell you what the fuck!
My God.
Ma'am, you wanna keep it quiet?
Careful, that's my throwing arm.
You should have thought about that
before you decided to engage
in lewd behavior in public,
which, in case you didn't know,
is against the law.
- You ain't no fucking cop, man.
- Not yet.
But I'm gonna be one real soon.
And I got my eye on you.
I ain't doing nothing
you never did yourself.
But here's the difference
between you and me.
Something about you is wrong.
And when I find out what that is,
I'm gonna fuck you up good, boy.
- You got it?
- I got it. Fuck.
Good.
Now get the fuck out of here.
Fucking freak.
You got that right.
- This is fucking intense.
- This is how it's always gonna be.
Oh, God.
You taste like fucking life itself.
I would do anything for you.
Will you take me to 4-Ever Young
and buy me anything I want?
Better.
I'll steal it for you.
I love you, you fucking lunatic.
Not more than I love you,
you hot bitch.
Hotter than hell. Hottest bitch in town,
and I fucking own you.
Trash.
Fuck.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not one of them, I swear.
I'm a good guy.
- What do you want?
- I'm looking for Sookie Stackhouse.
You got a car?
Please.
Say something.
Please, don't be dead.
Not after everything
we've been through.
I won't let you go, I won't.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
I'm gonna make you well
if it's the last thing I ever do.
Because I love you,
and I am not about to let you go.
Isn't that heartwarming?
This is all your fault.