Honestly, have you ever
seen anything lovelier?
So graceful. So full of life.
And those eyes....
Make you feel like
the only man in the room.
Plus, six breasts.
Any man's gotta love that.
Fred doesn't have six breasts. Right?
Sorialus the Ravager. And, yeah,
she's the one from my vision.
Coming to destroy the humans
that killed her mate.
But not for another month or so.
I'll file her under "pending."
- You gonna ask her out?
- The Ravager?
Fred.
Yes. But, you know, timing.
I'll make my move when the iron's hot.
Get it done, Johnny Reb, so I can hear
about something besides your hot iron.
Am I very boring on the subject?
There was a time when you thought
I was the loveliest thing in the world.
Well, I....
You're an extraordinary woman.
- I....
- At ease, soldier.
Just like to hear it every
now and then.
I was the ditsiest bitch in Sunnydale.
Could've had any man I wanted.
Now I'm all superhero-y,
and the best action I can get...
...is an invisible ghost
who's good with a loofa.
I'm sorry, I missed that last part.
- You are a gentleman.
- Who's doing what with a loofa?
Not loofa. Loo-fah-nooc....
- It's a demon.
- So you went with dark colors today.
- Ask me why I'm smiling.
- I will, because it's scaring me.
We are stepping out.
You are a remarkable woman.
The way you shovel food into your
mouth.... That is some Olympian feat.
Was I a pig? It's just that breakfast
goes so quick and I'm always so--
I just wonder where it goes
in that stick-figure body you got.
- Stick? You're a beast.
- Come on. You know you're gorgeous.
Morning, friends and neighbors.
Are those the tickets?
- See, I got to the ticket place--
- Morning, Fred.
I'm paying you back. This is on me.
Mahta Hari is the tightest band in L.A.
You guys'll be tripping out.
- The thing is--
- I'm good for it.
Don't worry about
Connor's college fund.
The time I saw Mahta Hari, they were--
The Blinnikov World Ballet Corps.
I got to the ticket place, and boom!
Tonight only.
You got ballet on my
Mahta Hari tickets?
- The Blinnikov World Ballet Corps.
- He says that like it has meaning.
This is a premier company.
And they're doing Giselle.
This is all like some horrible dream.
I've heard of them.
Very ahead of their time.
I saw their production of Giselle in 189O.
I cried like a baby. And I was evil.
- I think it sounds exciting.
- Yes.
No! This is not Mahta Hari.
This is tutus and guys with their
big-ass packages jumping up and down.
- I will never trust you again.
- Get over it. Do we get dressed up?
- Of course.
- I'm in.
Guys, seeing real ballet live,
it's like another world.
These guys are tight.
You'll be tripping out.
Don't be using my own phrases
when we've lost the trust.
Come on. Working day, cases to solve.
I'm not still paying, right?
'Cause this is like a nightmare.
It's such an honor
to have the company here.
All of L.A. is buzzing. To have
the Blinnikov performing Giselle....
I can't imagine
what tonight's going to be like.
It will be the performance
of a lifetime.
I guarantee it.
Are you certain
this is the place for us?
We could go to Cavegirl's House
of Burlap, but that's so last season.
The guys are renting tuxes.
We've gotta step up.
But aren't we, you know, poor?
There's a custom amongst my people:
Buy a dress, wear it once
and return it the next day.
It's all about hiding
the tags while it's on.
Oh. Okay.
I'm very excited. I love the ballet.
I haven't seen much, but my family
used to go to The Nutcracker...
...and I had my first sexual dream
about the Mouse King.
Face me.
Hm.... Uh-uh.
- Can I ask you something?
- You guys are perfect for each other.
- I have magic powers, remember?
- It's not like we've said anything.
But he's so sweet and commanding.
I feel so comfortable around him.
- I don't even know if he feels--
- He feels.
- Feelings?
- There's definite feelings.
We find the right outfit for tonight,
there may be actual feeling.
And we have to find a dress for you,
something that will make Angel crazy.
Fred, sweetie, Angel is crazy.
I know he's gonna want
to look his best for you.
That's right. The world's champion is
gonna worry about his outfit.
Is it gonna be all right?
Is there a stain?
Relax, crumb cake.
I got this soda water working overtime.
- Connor burps like a champ.
- At least he's sleeping.
Who wouldn't, with that sweet
Irish lullaby you crooned?
Just a hair flat on the bridge,
but, more to the point, Cordelia?
What about her?
I read you while you
were singing, you big corn-muffin.
And can't say as I blame.
I mean, what a woman she's become.
You're not supposed to be reading me.
Anyway, you read me wrong.
Sorry, strudel.
It's not just when you're singing.
We got a term in Pylea: "Kyrumption."
- I know it.
- When two heroes come together--
There'll be no coming together.
All anybody wants to talk about is--
Can't fight kyrumption, cinnamon buns.
It's fate, the stars. Kyrumption is--
Stop saying that.
And stop calling me pastries.
You're a man of many limitations,
Angel, but you're a man.
You got a heart.
And Cordelia's a hell of a lady.
If I thought she liked to wear green,
I'd be elbowing you out of the way.
But she's out of my league.
She's a champion, Angel.
Old school. And besides...
...we all know you got a thing
for ex-cheerleaders.
- What have I got to offer her?
- Do I even have to answer that?
You just have to act.
Let her know what's brewing inside...
...because it's real.
You don't want to miss that shot.
- Lorne, Cordelia, she's--
- She's what?
I was just saying that
you're not much of a ballet fan.
Disregard everything I said.
I forgot how homely she was.
- You look like....
- Like a ballet fan?
An aficionado? A devotee, in fact?
Tonight I've decided that we don't have
to be our incredibly dreary selves.
Tonight we're a couple
of young sophisticates...
...enjoying an evening
of classical dance.
- How's that sound?
- Sounds just right.
- You gotta promise not to laugh.
- I promise.
It's gotta come from the heart.
Will you stop being such a little girl?
I said, I promise.
This is what your promises are worth?
I'm having trust issues.
I'm sorry, it's just....
My God, you're so pretty.
There's not a lot of people
could say that to me and live...
...but the way you look...
...there's no way I can fight you.
Tonight feels, I don't know,
kind of magical.
- Is that stupid?
- Not at all.
- Finally came out of hiding.
- And look at my reward.
- Yes. Isn't she a vision?
- There's a lot of that around.
No, thank you.
There will be no visions tonight.
- How can you be sure?
- I had a vision.
Thank you.
The iron is hot.
Sorry they're not closer.
Getting five seats together--
Don't be silly. Best place.
Got the whole panorama from here.
Back here we stand less chance
of setting off the under-70 alarm.
Back in the day I'd always get box seats.
Or just eat the people who had them.
Don't let's reminisce.
We're here. Enjoy.
- Bravo!
- I loved it.
- It's just intermission.
- That isn't drool, is it?
- It's okay. It matches the back.
Gloat all you want. These guys
are tight and I am tripping out.
They certainly
live up to their reputation.
- Has the choreography changed since--?
- No. Nothing's changed.
- It's wonderful they're able--
- I mean, nothing's changed.
These are the same dancers
I saw before.
Impossible. We're watching the
exact same troupe you saw in 1990?
I think he said 1890.
That's much more impossible.
Somebody want to tell me how we're
watching a show starring people...
...who should have died
60 years ago?
Well, it's a puzzler.
Are there snacks?
- So, what are we thinking? Vampires?
- They're not a tanned bunch.
That would explain
the precision and athleticism.
Some of those jumps were....
You know,
I was cool before I met y'all.
- Dancing vampires. Who's not scared?
- Not it. I'd know. I'd sense it.
Even all the way back there?
With the panoramic view.
- We should check it out.
- After the show we should go backstage.
I was thinking now.
You guys go back. I'll snoop.
I'm with Snoopy. Magic of the ballet,
not really getting to me.
How will the dancers keep time
without your rhythmic snoring?
- That's gonna come back to haunt you.
- Go.
Hurry.
- Check out the zeppelin.
- Lot of muscle for a ballet company.
Should I distract him
while you slip by?
Don't be stupid. I'm him and the most
beautiful woman is making eyes at me?
It's either a bachelor party
or a scam.
What did you just call me?
- Sorry. You're not stupid.
- No, after that.
I think I'll go with my patented
sudden burst of violence.
Hey, hold on. I have an approach
that's a little more subtle.
- Say, do you like bribes?
- Do I ever.
We really want to go backstage.
Okay. But this isn't so much
a bribe as it is a tip.
And since I'm not parking your car,
there's really no way--
Okay. That's how we do it.
Okay, you saw the building
when we drove by...
...do you remember it going on forever?
It's clearly a spell
or a time flux or something.
I don't think we want
to be rushing in here.
Let's get the others
and talk options.
Works in theory.
This is her dressing room.
Prima ballerina.
It's unchanged.
She would wait for him here.
It's warm. It's very warm.
I feel it.
Something happened here.
- Angel?
- Yeah?
I want you to undress me.
You what?
It's just another costume.
I want you to see who I really am.
You're the only one who can.
I....
This isn't us.
We're acting this out.
Someone is....
Whoa.
- Did I just ask you to undress me?
- Is that what you want?
Please, I....
- You want me to make love to you?
- You know I do.
- But you're afraid.
- What if he finds us?
I'm not afraid.
I'm not afraid of anything.
I'm only alive when you're inside me.
- Cordelia.
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
- No. We so need to be out of here.
- Yes.
- This isn't out of here.
- I know. All right.
- Open the damn door.
- It's kind of hard.
I kind of noticed.
Whoa.
- That's a fair assessment.
- What the hell is that place?
Spirits in there. Energy trapped
in time. It took us over.
Scary. Well, it's a good thing
it wears off right away.
Yeah. It's a good thing.
Go to sleep lullaby
You've been fed and you're sleepy
You'll be with Uncle Lorne
Who in no way resents
Not being asked to go to the ballet
And is certainly not thinking
Of selling you to the first
Vampire cult with a decent offer
You just sleep on, little nipper.
Uncle Lorne's gonna
make sure we're alone.
Won't be gone a moment.
Oh, my God.
- You sure this is the way?
- I'm sure it's a way.
Place is a maze. I'm hoping
there's another room we can--
- Damn it.
- What?
I said something back in that room.
Something important. Do you remember?
- You're only alive when I'm--?
- Not that.
No, of course. I was just--
Oh, hey. I said you were afraid.
- And I said, "What if he finds us?"
- She had a secret lover.
They were afraid of someone.
I'll bet that someone is the reason
why we're stuck here. We left too soon.
We? Who? The room?
It's a clue. Those spirits or energy
or whatever are still in there.
We can figure out what happened.
We have to go back in.
- I'm marveling at the wrongness of that.
- You want to wander around forever?
There are other rooms that....
All we have to do is play the scene.
Get in, get out. No one gets happy.
What if there is no more talking
in that scene?
I've been possessed by the spirits of
old lovers before. It never goes well.
I've got my little cross
if things get out of hand.
It's awkward, but it's not us.
So long as nothing is removed
or inserted, it's all forgotten.
It is us, Cordelia.
It's you and me.
Kissing you, it's....
- It's not something I can just--
- Come on. It's not that horrible.
Up to his ass in demon gore, fine.
But ask him to mack on a hottie
and he wigs.
My champion, ladies and gentlemen.
- Angel!
- Huh?
- What?
- And Cordy.
They've been gone way too long.
You're right. Come on.
- We're gonna miss the end.
- Sorry.
Anything coming?
Okay, let's take it from the middle.
I want you to undress me.
- You want to have sex.
- Yes, but I'm scared.
- But you're afraid.
- And afraid. What if he finds us?
- But I'm not afraid of anything.
- Only good inside. Blah-blah-blah.
Maybe it only works the one time,
when the energy--
At least Angel left us a trail.
Deal with them.
I can't be bothered right now.
- This is wrong.
- Hush.
You don't know him. He has power.
The power to do this?
Stefan, his power is unnatural.
He could....
What? Kill us?
Worse.
Kurskov owns the company.
He doesn't own you.
He doesn't know that.
He thinks I'm his.
That I dance for him.
He's nothing but a deluded fan.
He thinks I love him.
Come away with me tonight.
We'll disappear. Even he won't find us.
Stefan, everything
I've worked for is here.
- You can still dance.
- Can I? I don't....
- Not yet. Maybe when we're--
- Don't. Don't make promises.
Help me.
Help me be not afraid.
This is very not right.
- Do you hear--?
- There's something.
Someone's in pain.
Either that, or someone's in fun.
Oh, no. Oh, no!
Oh, thank God.
Good. They were probably interrupted
by Kurskov or his lackeys, right?
We're done with--
We're done!
Now that sounds less like fun.
Charles!
Fred, stay between us.
Wesley!
Can you handle the other?
Well, then, just us.
A little help!
Thank you.
- You all right?
- Yeah. We gotta move.
- You think they're not dead?
- You just looked really hot doing that.
Yeah.
Run.
Who's laughing now?
Well, you. But I still win.
That's good. Should hold.
You okay? You hurt?
I'm fine. I just thought--
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't fall apart like this.
- Scared I'm gonna die on you?
- Don't even--
And all I ask is one last kiss...
...as the light is dimming.
- You think that's funny?
- It's just a scratch.
But I thought it was....
Hey. Hey.
You really that worried about me?
Probably think I'm an idiot.
I think if you care that much...
...the wound is definitely deep.
The light is dimming.
And all I ask...
...is one last....
- You guys all right?
- Charles got stabbed.
- Couple of stitches' worth.
- Same guys that attacked us.
- Cordy, your tag's showing.
- Any idea where we are?
Cordy and I hit a mystical hot spot
back in one of the dressing rooms.
The prima ballerina had a lover
back in the day...
...and there was this Count Kurskov
who owned the company.
He had a thing for the girl
and they were mightily afraid of him.
- He had powers of some kind.
- He was a wizard.
He was obsessed with the girl.
When he found her with the other man,
he went insane with jealous rage.
Pulled her out of time...
...out of any reality
beyond his theater, his company.
He swore she would dance
for him forever.
- How did you--?
- I hit a hot spot too.
And now we're stuck here?
This kind of temporal shift can't
just exist. It has to be maintained.
That requires power and concentration.
If we overload him somehow, we might
be able to slip back to the real world.
- Man with a plan.
- Great. So how do we overload him?
I imagine that requires some energy.
- The more we kill, the more he makes.
- Look.
And that's draining his energy.
Angel, go to the stage.
- The Count will be watching.
- I bet he has a box.
Find his power source
and destroy it. We'll loosen his hold.
By making more monsters?
Man with a frightening plan.
Back here. They can't surround us.
You two.
Stay close together.
I'll take point.
- I hope you're in the killing mood.
- I should do all right.
Hello?
Who are you?
There's no one. You're new.
I'm pretty old, actually.
I've seen you dance.
Everyone sees me.
It was Giselle then as well.
Always.
I know what's happening.
Count Kurskov...
...he's punishing you.
He made me. He owns me.
When I dance, it's only for him.
Do you believe that?
It really doesn't matter.
I'll dance, I'll wait here
and then I'll dance again.
That's all.
A hundred years,
doing the same piece every night.
Is that enough? What about Stefan?
I waited too long.
I should have gone when he asked me.
I should have disappeared, but...
...I wanted this.
This dance, this....
I hesitated...
...and I lost everything
that mattered.
Now all I do is wait.
But you dance.
There's a section in the first act...
...during the courtship dance,
where my foot slips.
My ankle is turned
and I don't quite hold...
...every time.
He doesn't notice.
He doesn't even know ballet that well.
But always, at that same moment...
...I slip.
It isn't just the same ballet.
It's the same performance.
I don't dance.
I echo.
Please...
...can you make it stop?
- It's working!
- There are dozens of them.
- Yay, us!
- It has to be weakening his hold.
I can help you,
but you have to do something.
- What?
- Dance something new.
- I can't.
- He's losing control of all of this.
But you have to take the stage.
It's not too late.
You can change things.
Where's your power center?
- How dare you?!
- I'll guess.
- You have no right.
- Save it.
She was my love.
She danced only for me.
Yeah. You love her that much?
Start a website.
You'll have to clean the wound.
Do you want something for the pain?
What pain?
Do you think I can still return it?
Because otherwise we'll have
to take on a lot more cases.
Cordy?
You know, we should probably not talk
about our little adventure.
Anything that might have been seen.
Anything that might have been perky.
- I want to pretend it never happened.
- Exactly.
Wipe it from my memory.
What? Was it, like, disgusting?
No! I....
I would just want....
If we were to....
I would just want it to be...
...new.
Start at the beginning.
Lost me in the middle.
Cordy, you and I, we've been
working together for a long time.
What I mean is, you've become...
...a truly extraordinary woman.
I know we haven't
always gotten along...
...but I think that, you know, we....
- Groo?
- Yes!
We grew closer together, and I think--
- Groo!
- Princess!
Oh, my God, I can't believe it!
- I feared you'd forget who I was.
- Remind me.
He just showed up.
Once everyone in Pylea
got their freedom...
...the political situation
got sketchy.
The Groosalugg here got deposed
and they set up a people's republic.
So he came looking for his true love.
- That's good for her.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna check on Connor.
- Well, he's sleeping.
That's a surprise.
I thought for sure she was
meant to be with Angel.
I guess you never
can predict those things.
You know?
No, I guess you never can.