Previously on Angel:
I've fought vamps and demons,
but never had a Fred before.
He's not taking the baby
overnight. He's taking it for good.
- Justine?
- I just need to do this.
- Wes thought Angel--
- Was going to kill Connor.
He had a reason for taking Connor.
We have to tell Angel.
- He'll forgive Wesley?
- Maybe begin to forgive.
You son of a bitch!
You think I forgive you?! Never!
You're a dead man! You're dead!
It's hopeless.
Half these files, I can't read
the clients' names.
Friz, Frizzana, Frizzlecar?
What does this say?
I think it's Frzylcka.
They were that couple that called
with the squatter in their lair.
Wesley was supposed to--
He was supposed to
see to that.
- He was too busy stealing the baby.
- Don't.
Okay?
How's it coming?
Any headway on those files?
- Some, sort of.
- There's so much to keep track of.
Still, times like these,
it's good to keep busy.
Throw yourself into work.
Stay active.
He lost the only
child he'll ever have.
Oh, sugar, I know. I know.
- I wish he'd talk to us.
- Leave him alone.
The rage has passed,
but you really want to know?
I'm sure he's not planning to...
...finish what he started.
Wesley's too smart
to show his face.
We're back!
And we're bearing gifts.
What happened?
I'm so sorry.
No more bets.
The wheel's in motion.
Place a bet, place a bet.
Table six. The one in blue.
Palmed a king in his left hand.
And, Benny...
...just take the left hand. We can
make money off the right.
You.
Good.
Bring him in.
His marker's up.
Time to collect his soul.
I'm just here, okay?
- This house is thick with sadness.
- Tell me about it.
Home is where the heart is,
but these hearts are broken.
I wish to aid my princess
in her time of need.
I brought clothing and food
for her shiv-roth.
The vigil of the bereaved.
I almost forgot that word.
We can't help their pain.
Is that why you're leaving?
Me? No, no, these are....
- They're not mine.
- They are Wesley's, then?
You might want to avoid
saying the name.
- Wesley. That was it.
- Don't be ridiculous, Monica.
- It was Sherman.
- You don't know any Shermans.
- It was Wesley. Irish fellow?
- English, you old bat.
That's who we were talking to.
Is he here?
- He's on sabbatical.
- Sorry for the mix-up.
It says you have a squatter
in your lair?
- Damn Skench demons. They're all alike.
- Here we go.
- Person spends his half-life--
- Building a lair.
And what happens?
A Skench demon squats.
On your coffee table. Ask me how
often I've listened to this.
- Like you ever listen.
- You have so much to say.
Skenches. I've heard about them.
Impish kind of demon?
- Like a leprechaun?
- Leprechauns don't exist.
- Now, Syd, don't embarrass the lad.
- Oh, sorry, kid.
Skenches take over a house,
drive out the people?
You can't stay.
The shrieking all night
and the projectile phlegm.
The only thing worse is putting up
with her for 300 years.
- You've been married three centuries?
- Ever since the mitosis.
Not that I'd mind being
a single-celled organism.
Oh, shut up, Syd.
I thought getting rid of them was
easy. Don't you lop off its head?
- If you can avoid the phlegm.
- Syd has a phlegm phobia.
I do not.
I have a phobia about sputum.
I think we got everything.
I'll clean out your
Skench problem.
We'll call you
as soon as it's done.
- Call me anytime.
- For crying out loud.
She's a 16th of your age.
Put your eyes back in your head.
An amoeba can dream, can't he?
Man, you hear those two?
It's beautiful.
All that time,
and they're still in love.
The way they finish each
other's insults, it's....
Beautiful.
- Is there evil to vanquish?
- Thanks, bro. I got it.
Just a demon under
Alvarado and Clark.
- Bye.
- Don't forget your machete.
Yes, dear.
He's fortunate to have such
a woman looking after his weapon.
I'm not touching that one.
Probably best to keep
this stuff out of sight...
...just in case....
I gotta run. I have a reading
in Topanga Canyon.
It's a good time for house calls...
...considering the vibe here.
- Hey, if he needs anything, just....
- I'll call.
Hi, Wesley.
How are you feeling?
It's not permanent, though.
I brought you some stuff
from the office.
Things there are....
Well, things.
Gunn and I found your notes
about the baby.
The prophecy.
You thought Angel was gonna kill him.
You were trying to protect him.
Both of them.
I wanted you to know
I understand that.
And I also wanted to say...
... what Angel tried to do to you
was wrong...
...and I'm sorry.
But he was right to blame you.
You should have come to us.
You should've trusted us
instead of Holtz.
You were our friend,
and you didn't even--
If Angel sees you again,
he'll kill you.
This time for real.
Don't come back to the hotel.
Ever.
The prophecy was false.
Angel was never going to hurt Connor.
It was all for nothing.
Hail to you, potential client.
How may I be of service?
- This Angel Investigations?
- It is. You in need of some help?
So...
...you must be Angel.
Gotta be it.
Smells like old people in...
...here! Gross!
Okay, definitely not a leprechaun.
Must be my lucky day.
Wanna bet?
- What do you want?
- I wanna talk to him.
- You got an appointment?
- No, I got business.
Over here, slick.
A little touch-and-go.
- You packing?
- No.
He could kill you 10 ways
from Sunday.
- But then he'd cook me too. Clean.
- Told you.
- Not everyone's as honest as you, bro.
- I ain't your bro.
You got a name or just a 'tude?
Name's Gunn.
Charles Gunn, if I'm not mistaken.
Man of the streets...
...protector of the young.
What can I do for you?
I want something.
I don't traffic in wants.
I supply needs.
Things you gotta have now,
or you'll die.
- They tend to be more valuable.
- I need it.
Then maybe I can assist.
What is it?
Money? Power?
Love?
Very nice.
She's a real beauty.
I can make it happen...
...but there's a cost.
I guess you know that.
Nothing to pay now,
but one day you will. The cost...
...is your future.
What future?
Well...
...there's that.
I need you to state for the record
of your own freewill.
You're sure you wish
to mortgage your future...
...for your present happiness?
I'm sure.
Shake on that?
Good.
You made a deal. Signed a blood oath
trading your soul.
- You think you can get out of it?
- Who said I'm trying to?
- You're giving away your soul.
- What are you saying?
Some broad.
You're falling for her hard.
- Fred.
- We don't get a name, just an image.
We watch the Akashic records.
Wouldn't we know...
...when one of our souls
was transferred?
Isn't Fred a guy's name?
None of mine. I'm here to say
you broke the contract.
Your soul ain't yours to give.
It's Mr. Jenoff's to take.
- I gotta see him.
- What you gotta do is pay up.
- I'm not the same person I was then.
- We get older...
...and we pay our debts to him.
There must be something
else he can take.
I have never heard that before.
Now, listen good.
You have got 24 hours
to get your house in order...
...and get down to that casino.
If you're thinking about...
...running or cheating, don't.
Because we'll take your soul
and the girl's.
- She's got nothing to do with this.
- Keep it that way...
...or you can get her killed.
It's up to you now, slick.
See you tomorrow.
You okay?
- What?
- I said, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Seemed rude to chow down
in front of Angel...
...so I took a little break.
- You are not okay, pal.
- I'm just tired, but--
Cordelia here. I can see the misery
on your face.
- I know what's going on.
- You do?
It's pretty obvious.
Angel's lost his son,
Wesley's gone, and you are...
...happy as a kid in a candy store.
Um, happy?
And racked with guilt because
of it. Well, don't be.
You and Fred are meant to be.
I get that now.
She's a doll.
I was a little slow on the uptake.
I thought she and Wes, but....
The way you look at each other.
This place could use...
...a little happiness right now.
You and Fred have your...
...big, bright futures ahead of you.
I'm here to tell you it's all
right to enjoy it. Life goes on.
I should enjoy my future.
I'm just saying. One thing
I learned on Hell Mouth:
Every day is precious. You never
know when it may be your last.
I never figured I'd be around
this long...
...or have this much.
Some people never know
one day of joy. You're lucky.
Maybe I am.
So live a little.
We don't have any pressing cases,
and I haven't had a vision in, like--
Oh, wait.
I'm having one right now.
It's of you and Fred.
Taking tomorrow off.
And see, my visions.
Never wrong.
Have some fun.
All right, ready?
Red T-shirt...
...your dark-blue blue jeans,
gray boots.
Oh. Was I right about any of it?
Okay, that was just a warm-up.
Yellow long-sleeve tee...
...gray cords, tan boots.
See?
Record secure. Never takes me
more than twice.
Me?
Maybe you should come
over here and find out.
Of course, if it takes you
too long....
- It won't.
- Hey!
Sorry, I have to cancel.
Somebody just walked in.
- He better looking than me?
- Way.
And he brought me
breakfast in bed.
- Voila, madame. Room service.
- Cool.
- You didn't cook, did you?
- Nope.
Food from your favorite diner.
Pancakes and waffles?
I'm in starch heaven. Yum.
- Is today special or something?
- Yep, very special.
- How come?
- Because we have the day off.
- We do?
- We'll spend every minute...
...having the best day of our lives.
- Well, now it's official.
- What?
You are the best boyfriend ever.
Pancake kiss!
How we feeling today?
It's been rough,
but I have good news.
There's no sign of infection
or rebleeding...
...and the swelling's down.
We can stop worrying...
...about your airway
becoming compromised.
I'm gonna release you today.
Is there someone that can pick you up?
Friend or a family member
we can call?
I think he was gonna be left-handed.
The way he'd hold on to your fingers...
...his left hand always squeezed...
...just a little bit tighter.
Kid had a grip.
He was gonna be a southpaw for sure.
When you live as long as I do...
...you eventually lose everyone.
You don't get used to it,
but you expect it. You deal.
But he was just....
He was just a little....
You think you know about living
because you have this long life.
That's really all you have.
I mean, in my case, anyway.
Then one day you wake up...
...and you have something else.
The future.
I had a son.
And now for our next item
of pleasure, we got movies galore.
You pick. You wanna hit the 12-plex?
See every preview?
Like seeing a year's
worth of movies at once.
Your shake okay?
It's your favorite. Double mocha.
- I'm kind of full.
- Oh, my God. This is serious.
It's Sixth Street tacos,
fish sticks at the pier....
Don't fold on me.
We got more fun to go today.
I'm all for fun.
It's just, I might explode.
Right. Sorry.
No more food. But movie, club,
shopping, fun still to be had.
- You wanna go to the roller rink?
- I'm kind of wiped.
We've been having so much fun today.
Don't you think
we should save some...
...before all the other people get
sad because we took all the happy?
I blew it. I tried too hard.
No, it's been like the most wonderful,
beautiful day ever.
Aside from the knot in my tummy.
Being with you is always special.
We don't have to cram the rest of
our lives into one single day, right?
Oh, my God.
You did try too hard.
You haven't been yourself.
You did this because
something's wrong.
- No.
- Something is terribly wrong.
Charles, do you have leukemia?
I see it on the news.
They're young, in love...
...their whole lives ahead
when tragedy strikes.
- I'm not sick.
- You're not?
- You promise?
- I'm not sick.
Thank God.
I feel much better.
Except for the terrible knot inside.
Which isn't the food at all.
It's us.
What's wrong with us?
- It's nothing.
- Oh, that helps.
- Maybe we should go.
- We should stay here...
...and you should stop lying to me.
I know something's wrong.
Just be honest and tell me.
Charles.
Whatever it is,
we'll get through it.
No, we won't.
What?
This isn't something
we're gonna talk through.
We share our feelings, then hug.
- I don't like how you're speaking.
- Too bad.
- Why are you being mean?
- I'm being honest. You want that?
Yeah.
Be honest.
Is it me?
Wow, you finally figured
that one out.
- What's wrong with me?
- Now I gotta make a list?
- I don't think I have enough time.
- Are you joking?
- What's happening?
- You and me are over. Done.
- No.
- Am I asking? I'm telling. Enough.
- I don't believe it.
- Better start.
But wait. Wait.
Is there someone else?
What's her name?
Her name is "I'm a real woman, not a
stick figure." Get the picture?
- Yeah.
- Good.
I won't sit here and pretend I know
what you're going through...
...or that I could begin
to understand your feelings.
The last thing you need right now
is someone saying...
...that given time, things will
get better, or the hurt will go away.
Because it won't get better.
The hurt's never going to go away.
If you lived another 200 years,
you'd never forget...
...how Connor was taken from you,
and you shouldn't.
You loved your son, Angel...
...and you'll go on loving him...
...and missing him.
You'll go on living too.
You'll do that.
I don't know how.
You don't need to.
The how works itself out.
Life will just keep happening.
There'll be people who need us, and...
...we'll help them.
Because that's what we do.
- Fred.
- I'm sorry.
I was gonna knock, but it wasn't
a good time, so I didn't.
- I don't know what else to do.
- What is it? What's wrong?
It's Charles. I think
he's in terrible danger.
I'm here to pay my bill.
- Wow.
- I know, huh?
- I am sorry this has come to pass.
- I'm confused.
- What was unclear?
- Well, upstairs...
- ...you said Gunn was in danger.
- He is.
- And you think that because...?
- He broke up with me.
But not really.
- No?
- No!
- That is good. I'm relieved.
- This is worse, much worse.
- I wish he had broken up.
- Are you sure he didn't?
- Those things he said to you--
- I know he said those things...
- ...but he would never say them.
- Those things he said?
Exactly! That's why I know
he's in trouble.
Let me get this straight.
You and Gunn are dating?
Not anymore, I guess!
- Fred, honey.
- Don't you see? He hurt me.
And the only reason he'd do that
is to protect me.
Whatever it is, it's gotta be bad
because this hurts like hell.
I guess we better help him.
We are not losing another
member of this family.
This is Gunn,
leave a message,
Still no answer at his place
or on his cell phone.
Oh, no.
- This does not bode well.
- We'll split up.
To cover more ground.
It is a good plan.
Fred and I will check out
his old gang haunts.
- Or if they know any of his enemies.
- Exactly.
- You two go by his place.
- Report his truck stolen.
Not a bad idea.
Get the police involved.
We should leave Lorne a note.
If we come up with nothing,
we'll regroup.
We could leave these small
rectangles behind...
...like that creature who
inquired about Gunn.
Right. Good.
What? Let me see that.
Rectangles with telephonic digits
so people can get in touch with us.
- Somebody came by looking for Charles?
- Yesterday.
Remind me to give that rectangle
to Gunn once we find him.
I'm confident we shall.
- Works for Jenoff.
- Jenoff?
The Soul Sucker.
Charles Gunn.
I'm impressed.
Not a lot of guys walk through
that door willingly.
Not the second time, anyway.
She must be special,
to give her my merchandise.
I'm making good on my debt.
Don't talk about her.
- Don't think about her.
- She's not part of the deal.
- Hold him.
- I'm not gonna run.
But touch me, and you better.
Let's get this over with.
Gunn!
- Charles!
- Fred!
Hey.
- Angel.
- I know.
- We are surrounded.
- We have to save Charles.
- I know.
Who's a guy gotta kill
to talk to the boss?
I'm the boss.
- Why are you disrupting my business?
- You're disrupting mine.
You're about to deprive me
of a valuable employee.
Charles Gunn works for me.
A good businessman looks into
the background of employees.
Had you done that, you might've
learned he's short-term material.
I'll make a deal with you.
You release him, forget what
he owes you, I'll let you live.
Thank you.
Kill them.
Double or nothing.
You offering me your soul?
- Chance to win it, anyway.
- How stupid do I look?
You're a vampire.
I can smell it.
Take a bigger whiff.
I'm a vampire with a soul.
You're that vampire.
I choose the game.
I win, we walk out of here.
Gunn's debt disappears.
You win...
...you get us both.
Brilliant stall tactic.
Now, what's the plan?
- This is the plan.
- Really?
Really. We're gonna win
Gunn's soul back.
This is so wrong in so many ways.
It's not money or a bunny Angel's
playing for. It's my boyfriend.
Don't be nervous.
Been around a long time,
won a lot of bets.
We're different.
I get lost and lose things.
- And I can't lose Charles.
- I'm not gonna lose.
You worried about this?
Like taking candy from a baby.
If we must rely on luck,
I prefer the odds of my sword.
- We should fight our way out.
- Fighting puts us at risk.
- My way is safer.
- If you win.
If you lose, won't you go evil
and kill everybody, including us?
- Am I wrong?
- Not wrong in theory.
- But I've gotta go with ace.
- I'm gonna win.
If I lose, you know what to do.
- Make it quick.
- You know I will.
Jenoff lets me have the bodies
when he's done.
One hand of cards. You win...
...this man walks free.
I win, I keep his soul,
and I get yours.
Name your game.
Omaha, Texas Hold 'Em...
- ...Seven Card Stud.
- How about a cut of the deck?
High card wins.
Vampire's not only got soul,
he's got guts.
- Feeling lucky?
- After you.
- A three?
A three. You lose.
- That quick enough?
- Works for me.
Charles!
- Angel?
- No need to say thanks.
Right. If killing him was that easy,
I would've done it.
Now we fight.
Anybody else in here owe this guy?
Let's go.
Say it again,
a little slower this time.
I was terribly, terribly
wrong to break up with you.
- And say those mean and untrue things.
- Good.
Now say it into the tape recorder.
I'm really sorry,
and I'll never do it again.
- I'm just glad you're all right.
- I'm all right if you and me are good.
We are, aren't we?
- Just one last thing.
- Name it.
Who'd you trade your soul for?
That....
- That was a long time ago.
- I know. Tell me...
...and we'll never talk about it again.
Who was she?
Charles....
- That was before I met you.
- You must've wanted her pretty bad.
Guess I did.
Just tell me.
It....
It was a truck.
I was 17 years old, and I sold
my soul for a truck.
- Not this truck.
- Don't go dissing my girl.
Your soul wasn't
worth air conditioning?
This truck kept me alive. Helped me
save a lot of other lives too.
I know it sounds dumb...
...but I didn't think a soul
was that big a deal.
Didn't think I had a future then.
Now I do.
What is it about you
that makes me melt?
Maybe it's that I love you.
That's gotta be it.