www.Team-NCIS.com
Post up here
while I take care of business.
Is that for me?
Teek?
Is that you?
You got a decision to make, Tara.
Do we walk out of here,
or do I have to carry you?
NCIS Season 6 Episode 18
Knockout V1.0 FQM
Synchro: Gaillots.
Rereading: Bruno & Magic Turtle.
www.Team-NCIS.com
African-American male
in his late 40s.
Despite his distended features
from time under the water,
Chicago PD managed to identify
him as one
Tyler Keith Owens.
They fished him out of Lake Michigan...
two days ago.
That is just hours before Director
Vance's departure with McGee and...
Preliminary cause of death believed
to be multiple gunshot
wounds to the chest and abdomen.
He was shipped here
by the Chicago M.E.
I've been asked to perform
the autopsy,
by Leon Vance.
His effects are up with Abby.
Also at the request of Leon Vance.
Leon Vance is working a case.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, this is ridiculous.
Ziva, have you seen my...
Probie, have you...
You are with each other...
in Chicago with Vance.
I'm not in Chicago.
Because I got to go to Arizona.
It has nothing to do with my...
lack of prowess
on protective detail.
Excuse me!
Okay, listen up, everybody!
I need your full attention here!
Lenny, Squiggy, Q-tip,
Q-Bert, Bungo Straits, Vertical Bill.
Can you hear me back there?
Natalie, hi.
You look very nice today.
I have lost my wallet.
So, if you've seen it,
please return it to me.
There will be no judgment.
Maybe even a small reward.
Hi, boss.
I lost my...
You're gonna say "mind"
or "marbles",
- but, I lost my...
- Job?
Have you heard from Ziva or McGee?
Hold on.
It's the prince of darkness himself.
I'll be right up there, but Boss wants
to talk to you for a second.
He hung up.
He's setting up a videoconference
up in MTAC with... with Vance.
Good. Let's go.
Well, he just said me,
but I think we can... we all go.
Where'd you hide my wallet?
What?
Hold on for the Director.
DiNozzo,
I got an assignment for you.
We're transporting
a key witness to DC.
I want you to sit on her
till we get back.
Witness to what, Director?
We believe she's got information
relating to the murder of a Marine.
Word gets out that we have her,
she could be in danger.
Witness' name is Tara Kole.
Her flight lands
at National in 40 minutes.
Is that you I see lurking
in the background?
You're conducting an investigation.
I understand you might feel your toes
being stepped on, Agent Gibbs.
Me handing out
assignments to your team.
Not taking it personally.
Are you suggesting I am?
Are you?
May I have the room, please.
Both rooms.
Tyler Owens disappeared
more than a week ago.
And, yes, he was a friend.
Local authorities haven't been able
to generate a single lead.
Proximity to Great Lakes Reserve Center
help convince 'em to cede jurisdiction?
Death of a Marine is
our jurisdiction.
Yeah, well, he looks to be about 50.
What is he, a general?
Former Marine.
Is it going to be a problem
for you to sit this out, Agent Gibbs?
It's your case...
Director.
There was no sign
of foul play at his residence.
Tyler Owens was last seen
ten days ago at his place of business,
the South Side Gym.
That was Tony.
Again.
Is he looking for his wallet?
He keeps asking what we're doing
in the "Wine-dy" City.
- It's "windy".
- It's not so bad.
- What'd you tell him?
- I told him we were doing our job,
Director,
and that he should do the same.
Good.
Car?
Out front.
Destination?
Thinking I'll go for a workout.
Abs, what do you got?
I am not at liberty to discuss
the details
of Director Vance's case with you.
And I would certainly hope
that you wouldn't try to bribe me.
I wouldn't do that.
Because I can't say a word
about the five slugs
that Ducky pulled out of Owens' body.
Not that there's a word to say,
'cause I don't even know
if these 40-cal S & W's
are a match to the weapon
that was found in deceased's pocket.
Not that I would tell you
if they are.
I'm assuming that your curiosity
is purely for educational purposes.
After Ducky does the autopsy,
we should be able to calculate
how long
the accumulated postmortem gases
took to counteract the weight
that kept Owens submerged.
He was weighed down, huh?
With what?
Weights.
Mismatched set.
15 pounder, 20 pounder.
They were threaded
through the deceased's belt.
Well, it wasn't a mugging.
I need you to keep your...
educational inquiries
more abstract, Gibbs.
I said that I wouldn't say
anything to you...
and I'm not going
to lie to the Director.
Owens carry a weapon?
These are amazing, Gibbs.
I can't hear anything.
But, you know, feel free to...
muse out loud to yourself.
If this was my case,
I'd see if Owens was registered.
I'd run a search.
Gibbs, you really need
to find something to do.
"Idle hands are
the Devil's plaything."
Just picture Mephistopheles
sitting on his...
throne of fire,
playing with his collection of...
idle...
hands.
Sorry I couldn't help you, Gibbs.
Get your left up, Campbell!
You're dropping your left!
Your other left, son!
Man, it's a damn shame.
Damn shame.
Coach Owens was never really
a contender,
but he was a great teacher.
Tough as nails, drove you hard.
Man worked your last nerve.
But there was a method
to his madness.
Brother pulled me off the wrong path,
set me right.
So, Owens was revered by everyone?
Within these walls,
he was the black Miyagi.
Not a full set.
- You were counting?
- The dumbbells.
- You're missing a few.
- We're lucky to have what we got.
Keep movin' them feet, Campbell!
Spit!
Lubricate the man.
Yo, Spit, hold the bucket up.
So you can actually hit
something you're aiming at?
Thanks.
Let me see the towel.
I used to carry the bucket myself.
- For real?
- Yeah.
Gotta start somewhere.
Climb the ladder.
You done pounding on my boys, Leon?
I don't know, Ike,
you got anybody left?
What do you say, David?
Want to go a few rounds?
I think that would violate
my primary assignment.
Only if you manage
to lay a glove on me.
Excuse me, darlin',
but this gym ain't coed.
Another time.
Just say when.
Yeah?
Run, get us a sandwich.
You know what I like.
Okay.
Leon, let's talk.
Don't forget your jacket.
I lost it.
Go borrow mine,
it's the one on the end.
Okay, thanks.
His probably got stolen.
Trying to teach the boy
to stand up for himself.
Things that bad here, Ike?
Same old same old.
Nice flight from Chicago, Ms. Kole?
Uneventful.
Had enough excitement, though.
Being abducted by Leon.
Yeah.
Well, plane travel's not
what it used to be, is it?
Bet there wasn't even a movie.
I'm a big fan of movies.
You don't have to make small talk
with me if you're uncomfortable.
I'm not uncomfortable. It just
seemed like, the way you said it,
that you had a relationship
with our new Director,
and I said "new Director",
by the way, not "nude erector".
That's a homophone.
Unintentional, of course, but...
The Director...
he was just a ball of fire
when I knew him.
No direction at all.
Well, I guess we were all
someone else then.
We?
Tyler. He was my brother.
I didn't know that.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Anthony.
You're very sweet.
My...
patron saint.
Actually,
St. Nicholas
is the patron saint of...
St. Anthony's who you turn to
when you've lost something.
So, who does Anthony turn to
when he's...
lost something?
How do you know I've lost something?
I may not know my saints,
but I definitely know my sinners.
I miss Tyler.
Seems like just the other day
you two coming through that door.
Couple of string beans
fresh off the bus from Ohio.
That was his idea, you know.
Oh, don't I know it.
Made sense he'd be the one to stick
in this business while you went off.
That was his idea, too.
Always pushing me.
'Cause when you're young,
it's all gas pedal and no brakes.
Took a few false starts, but...
you both learned patience.
Throw a quick left-hand jab,
not meant to do any damages.
Messing with the other guy's vision.
Right cross, brings the hands up.
Work the body combinations
till that chin sticks out.
Bang! Sets up the uppercut.
But you can't rush that haymaker.
Action...
reaction, action.
Tyler knew the art of the knockout.
That's how I know he didn't just jump
into something out there.
Yeah.
I'm thinking the same thing.
I figured you'd be back one day.
You ready for this title fight?
Talking about Joe Banks?
Is he still top dog?
Hadn't seen his face in a long while
before he showed up a couple weeks ago.
He got a lot more cautious lately.
Yeah, Banks doesn't use
a cell phone.
He avoids electronic communication.
- Leaves no trail behind.
- Except slime.
He bought out a lot
of fighters over the years.
I think Banks got sick of Tyler,
poaching the local talent.
That's what I think!
Well, you got to have muscle
to stay on top.
That would make Tyler an obstacle.
You got the muscle
to chase down his ghost?
I'd rather lure him in.
Make him come to me.
Rope-a-dope.
What do you got that he wants?
You just spread the word.
Banks can find me in DC.
Our bloater became a floater.
Yes. Whoever intended our fellow here
to rest in his watery
grave forever didn't count
on the effects of putrefaction.
You know what they say about
the best intentions, Doctor.
Road to hell was paved with 'em.
Time of death?
Between four and ten days ago.
A gas chromatography of the fatty acids
should provide a more exact time-frame.
Mr. Palmer,
why don't you enlist Abby's help
to finish those?
Yes, Doctor.
- Well, what do you have there?
- Background...
Tyler Keith Owens.
You're gonna get
that girl in trouble, Jethro.
Born Cincinnati, '63,
juvenile record in Ohio.
Illinois driver's license, '81,
boxing license, '83.
Professional record of 19 wins,
14 losses.
It's not too impressive.
Bit of a journeyman career.
Tax returns show he stayed
in Chicago since it ended.
Very thorough.
No.
Something's missing.
No military record.
Ducky,
if this guy ever was a Marine,
Leon Vance is the only one
who thinks so.
If he's not...
then our Director has overstepped
the bounds of his authority.
The last time you saw Tyler Owens
was at an exhibition bout
at the South Side Gym?
We were checking out the fighters.
The "we"...
you are referring to would be...?
I was escorted by Joe Banks.
Joe Banks.
That name sounds so familiar.
Well, your Director seems to think
he's a notorious crime boss.
Must be from a movie, maybe.
Well.
What service do you perform
in the employ of Joe Banks?
I think you know.
I need you to be explicit.
The same as you do for your boss.
Anything he asks.
Yeah.
Well, my boss doesn't really ask
for things.
We're supposed to figure it out
on our own before
he gets really angry.
He gets very... angry.
What happens
if you don't figure it out?
We get a smack
to the back of the head.
That hasn't happened for a while,
actually.
Maybe we're getting better
at our jobs.
I know I am.
You know, Anthony,
I could help you
with your problem...
if you'd like.
My problem?
My job is to read men.
To know what they want,
and what they need.
And I...
see a man in need.
Hi, Ziva.
Hey, look, it's Ziva.
Ziva, Tara. Tara, Ziva.
We have met.
I am here to relieve you.
Well, then,
I'm relieved.
You look it.
What's the word, Doctor?
Owens went down fighting.
I would hope so.
Powder burns on his left palm
indicates that he was...
probably grabbing the barrel of the gun
when the first shot was fired.
That's the one that grazed
his right shoulder there.
The next two rounds went
into his abdomen,
perforated his stomach
and lower intestine.
Probably put him on the ground.
But he was still alive.
The kill shots entered his chest.
Damage to the heart
was catastrophic.
Death from that point would be...
rapid.
This pattern of attack
suggests an untrained killer.
Yeah, it was sloppy.
My condolences, Director.
I understand this man was
an acquaintance of yours.
I hadn't seen him in some time.
But once, you were quite close?
Gibbs was here.
What's his issue?
There is a lack of recorded evidence
that Owens was ever a Marine.
You can't believe everything
you read on a piece of paper.
I don't know,
the levels in the fatty acid...
Miss Sciuto.
Director Vance.
Welcome back.
- Has Gibbs been here?
- Now that you mention it,
I do detect
the lingering aroma of "Old Spice"
and sawdust.
But that could just be from...
We used...
ethanol and benzophenone
in our analysis.
That would explain the "Old Spice".
And the sawdust?
I...
- am taking up woodworking.
- Really?
I'm gonna build a coffin.
She is.
Did you get any actual work done,
or just woodwork?
Tyler Owens was killed 11 days ago.
That's fight night
at the South Side Gym.
It's the last time
Joe Banks was seen.
Well, the striations on the slugs
match the gun disposed
of along with Owens.
It was reported stolen
in a burglary in Chicago last year.
Street piece.
I wasn't able to get prints off
the dumbbell or the gun.
Water covers up a lot of mistakes.
This guy might have gotten really lucky.
Well, not too lucky.
He pulled us into it.
Did you get any organic material
from his hands?
I did, but it's not human.
It's a...
It's a bird feather.
There was some stuck
in his belt buckle, as well.
Maybe it got lodged
when he was in the water?
It's not likely
he was shot by a bird.
Is there anything else
you need to tell me?
No, sir.
That's everything, and I've been
completely candid with you, sir.
Great.
Now I have to build
a freakin' coffin.
He's a good-looking guy.
You two serious?
He does not live here.
He travels a lot.
Long-distance relationships
are impossible.
Relationship?
I do not know.
Maybe you should be looking
for something
a little closer to home.
Director.
I trust my people are treating you
all right?
You don't have to go through
all this trouble to protect me.
It's a long drive from Chicago,
but he will come for you.
You're counting on it, aren't you?
I'm not here for protection at all.
I'm the bait.
I'm sorry about Tyler.
- I'm sorry I wasn't there.
- Only half of that is true.
You cut both of us out of your life.
- I miss him...
- Not like I do.
But he's gone.
You can't undo that.
Would I have even seen you again
if your hand wasn't forced?
This is your worst fears
come to light.
You think I'm scared of Banks?
That is not what I'm talking about,
and you know it.
You're scared of yourself,
and pinning a body on Joe
is not going to make it go away.
He had nothing to do
with Tyler's death. I know him.
If that were true,
you would have quit him years ago.
Take Ms. Kole
to the southeast safe house.
Set up a rotation
with McGee and DiNozzo.
I'm going to want somebody
with her at all times.
Yes, sir.
Where will you be?
My wife will kill me
if I'm late for dinner.
Hey!
Daddy's home!
Is this the Vance residence?
It must be.
I missed you, Dad.
Hey, Jared.
- What did you bring us?
- That's it, Kayla...
you just get right to it.
Why don't you give me a hug first?
- I missed you.
- Me, too.
Your father wouldn't have gone
to Chicago without bringing back some...
Frango mints.
- What about me?
- What about you?
You didn't think I'd forget about you,
did you?
These...
are very old...
and they're very special to me.
Cool.
- They smell.
- That's from hard work.
Hard work stinks.
Yes, it does.
- Mine smell good.
- No, no, not till after we eat.
Now, you two go wash up.
Give me the mints.
- Thanks, Daddy.
- Come on.
So, I did good?
You did.
What, not great?
Why didn't you tell me
you had a friend coming by?
I have a policy
against bringing work home with me.
Well, that's your policy, Leon.
You disobeyed me.
You've been hijacking my case.
Aggressive choice of words.
Aggressive actions.
Demand an explanation.
Your predecessor
used that seat
for a personal agenda.
Dangerous.
You're not about
to let that happen again.
No.
Anything in my history
to suggest I would?
I don't know enough
about your history.
- Where did that come from?
- The CIA.
You got that big
and axe to grind with me?
Assume the dead man was a Marine.
He was.
And your friend.
Was that, too.
Still doesn't explain
why you wouldn't want me on the case.
You think you can do
a better job than me?
I think it's my job and not yours.
You're right...
seems neither of us are doing
what we're supposed to.
Who is he to you?
You haven't opened it.
Situation was reversed.
You did me the courtesy of asking.
So you're asking my permission?
Are you prepared for me to say no?
It's your call.
Leon?
You know I don't like it
when you chew on those things.
Gibbs, you're staying for dinner.
I was a freshman at the University
of Maryland, and Leon...
was at the Navy War College in Newport,
Rhode Island. You never told him?
Never had the occasion to.
You know he graduated
Annapolis, right?
But he had to resign
his commission in the Marine Corps?
That's funny,
I used to think I could spot a Marine.
I didn't get to serve.
Second lieutenant,
but he took a medical
discharge 'cause he detached
the retina in his right eye from boxing,
so he's going to teach Jared
to be careful with those things, right?
Oh, yeah...
yeah, I'll teach him.
He studied all the time,
except for this one night
he just had to see a Terrapins game
because he couldn't miss...
Len Bias.
The best basketball player
ever to come out of Maryland.
Until Carmelo Anthony.
Carmelo was the number 3
pick in the draft.
Lenny Bias was the number 2,
and he would have even been better if
he hadn't died two days after the draft.
- From...?
- Drugs.
And how many times did he do drugs?
Once.
Bias put up 36 points that night.
Okay, now, everybody in the student
section was just going crazy,
right, just jumping up and down.
There's finally a time-out,
and we all... you know,
just kind of start taking our seats.
Right?
Except for this one guy
who's kind of just standing there
staring at me.
OK?
With that baby face.
- Gross.
- That's how we met.
Wash, dry... come on.
- In the kitchen.
- All right, guys.
- But I washed last.
- No, I washed last time.
- It's my turn to dry.
- Let's go.
How is that for a history lesson?
Okay, Tony, clear to approach.
I'm on the street.
Door-to-door service.
Check and make sure
you didn't leave anything back there.
- What's this?
- Tony, I think she found...
My wallet.
Can you prove that it's yours?
Yeah. If you open it up, you're going
to see my big
fat smiling head
on the driver's license.
There seems to be
something else here.
You're making a circular crease
in the leather.
- That would probably be a...
- I think she knows what that is.
Now, why don't you want me
to see it?
Could it be that it's nearing
its expiration date?
She doesn't know anything.
Get out of the car.
- Get behind me.
- Why, what is it?
Town car.
Inside.
Let's go.
Ziva's radar is acutely tuned.
Yeah, she doesn't miss a thing.
Nice family, Leon.
Kids want to rescue
a pit bull from a shelter.
Can you imagine?
Come home to your new house
and find this wild dog has...
ripped up your stuff and dumped all over
your place while your back was turned?
I think pit bulls get a bad rap.
Is that right?
Yeah.
They're affectionate.
They're smart, loyal.
Keep you safe.
Treat 'em right.
Don't lie to 'em.
Who would lie to a dog?
Owens was a Marine.
I'm sure there's a reason
why there's no record of it.
I don't need to know it.
You hold on to it.
You keep me honest.
Don't know if it's necessary.
I ever need to know anything...
Yeah, I know, you'll ask my wife.
That Ms. Kole sure
has a one-track mind.
Sure wish her boss
would come get her.
The elusive Joe Banks.
You think that's Vance's plan?
I don't know...
what do you think?
"They pull a knife, you pull a gun."
"They send one of yours to the hospital,
you send one of theirs to the morgue."
"That's the Chicago way."
It's Connery.
- Untouchables.
- Excuse me.
I was told I could find
Tara Kole here.
Are you Joe Banks?
Wait.
Say that again,
but more like Abe Vigoda.
Joe Banks, Tom Hanks.
Joe Versus the Volcano.
Which is the story of a guy
who is hired to go and jump
into a volcano because
- he's got a brain cloud.
- Is that what you got?
Maybe from repeated head trauma.
Get Mr. Banks settled.
John Patrick Shanley, who wrote
and directed Joe Versus the Volcano,
won an Academy Award for Moonstruck.
He also wrote and directed
the movie Doubt,
which came out recently...
it was pretty good...
but in the middle there,
clearly, there was a goofy phase.
I forgot what that feels like.
- It's been a while since...
- I know.
- Physical contact.
- I... know.
You know?
You know.
Any advice?
Snap out of it.
I have no response to that.
I wasn't invited here, as it were.
This is an interrogation room.
You've seen your share.
And not the worst.
Not the best.
Well, you know who I am.
Am I supposed to know who you are?
Name's Leon Vance.
Fancy footwork.
Wicked right cross.
I never forget a fighter.
You could have been big-time.
I am.
A lot bigger than you have tried
to take me down.
Sit down.
Tried to retire,
but they don't let you out the game
so easy when you still hold the belt.
Don't I know it.
Tyler Owens.
Was sorry to hear about that.
How did it happen?
Bodies don't drop
without your say-so.
He's not who we think he is.
What do you mean?
His worst days are behind him.
1994.
Second-degree murder, not guilty.
Aiding and abetting, 1996.
Not guilty.
RICO,
2000, mistrial.
You are everything Tyler hated.
Pusher.
Fight fixer.
Murderer.
Man, you're talking about sounds
like somebody to be feared.
That's how you keep
your people quiet.
I'm gonna let 'em know
they can talk now.
People?
You mean Tara?
She'll never say a word against me.
She will, once she knows
she doesn't have to be afraid of you.
She's never had a reason
to be afraid of me.
Why wouldn't she incriminate you
then?
Let me tell you something, partner.
First of all, you're way off base.
Second of all, there are laws
protecting her
against saying things like that.
Protecting both of us.
He's your husband?!
That's what I wanted to see.
What?
That's what it looks like
when you know you're wrong.
- I wanted to see if you even knew.
- How do you marry a man like that?
- Joe's changed.
- You expect me to buy that?
He hasn't been hiding
from prosecution. He's out of the game.
He's a good man who doesn't want
to become a target for some...
- punk to make a name off of.
- You calling me a punk?
I'm trying to get justice.
You're lost, I can see it.
- What happened to Tyler?
- I don't know.
What do you think?
Tyler was family.
It's a shot at Joe
as much as anything else.
Joe and I...
fell in love.
It happens.
He lost his hunger.
He found something else.
When a man
that powerful loses a step,
there's always somebody
right behind him, waiting to take over.
That's right.
When you're in charge,
you always got to watch your back.
Sad truth.
Sometimes,
you just can't protect
the people you love.
Blood on concrete?
Chicago PD thinks
this might be the crime scene.
It's a couple blocks
from the South Side Gym, en route
- to Tyler Owens' residence.
- He never made it home.
What about Joe Banks?
Tara says they spoke that night,
but that was all.
Director Vance let him go.
Still holding her.
- Big boss was wrong.
- So far. But...
you can't make an omelet
without breaking some legs.
- You're never making me breakfast.
- That's the truth.
- It's supposed to be "eggs".
- Cook them yourself.
Did you resolve things
with Director Vance?
- Well, we made a breakthrough.
- He let you in?
We had dinner.
That does tend
to alter a relationship.
It's been far too long
since you and I had dinner.
I'll tell you what, Duck.
You do me a favor, I'll buy.
Name it.
I need you to reexamine this body.
Something specific
you want me to look for?
Evidence of surgery.
I checked in with a friend on Vice.
Banks has divested himself
from his entire enterprise.
You got a lot of friends in Chicago.
Tyler was more than a friend.
That's the man that taught me
the difference between
surviving and really living.
He was my hero.
You're not giving up.
In 30 years, the national rate
for solving murders dropped from...
80 to 60%.
You know why that is?
Murder got less personal.
Drive-bys, drug crimes, turf wars.
I owe Tyler my life,
there's no way I'm giving up.
He might've been a hero to you.
Owens was still just a man.
Motive could be simple.
So what did he have
that was worth getting killed over?
Just a name.
Wasn't involved in drugs.
Killer didn't take his money...
or his shoes or his...
His coat.
Nice heavy leather coat.
Duck down.
Don't throw anything. I didn't mean to
say anything to Gibbs, I'm really sorry.
Ms. Sciuto,
I don't care what you told him,
as long as you tell me
that those feathers were duck down...
the ones that were discovered
on Owens' body.
Hungarian goose,
to be specific, probably used
as some sort of filler in...
An inexpensive winter coat.
Wasn't stolen.
Kid got rid of it
because it was covered in blood.
Good work, Abs.
Too much work. Don't ever put me
in that position again.
Okay, I won't.
But I will help you
with your project here, if you want.
It's a coffin, not a boat.
All right, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Damn it, Spit.
-Hey Ike, It's Leon.
- Hold on a minute.
Ike, it's Leon.
Can you hear me?
You figured it out?
Too late.
This kid Spit started bragging
about it.
How he took down the champ.
A couple of fighters took justice
into their own hands.
- He'll live?
- It's too soon to tell.
Tyler had a philosophy...
you had to earn
your way into the ring.
He didn't want this next generation
to make the same mistakes he did.
This kid didn't see it that way.
Get tired of working
for his respect.
Thought he could take it with a gun.
Kid thought nobody noticed him.
Tyler was just standing
between him being
invisible and everybody
knowing who he is.
I'm headed back to Chicago.
I'm gonna take Tyler home
for a memorial service.
Is there anything
you need before I go?
Nothing that can't wait.
You're driving
all the way back to Chicago?
Oh, it's not so bad.
Joe's good company.
I'll escort Ms. Kole out.
Okay.
I need to speak to you.
For some reason,
you can see right through my disguise.
How bad's the dry spell?
Saharan.
- Never been a problem before?
- You kidding me?
Not since Lisa Mullen taught me
to play doctor in the second grade.
What's changed?
Real doctor,
real love, real bad breakup.
Messed you up pretty bad, huh?
Kicked off a slump with women
that's unprecedented in my adult life.
I've tried everything.
I mean, I'm dating constantly,
but I can't seem to get it right.
I'm not closing the deal, you know?
Like there's a saboteur in my head.
I'm making every rookie mistake. I'm
talking about myself too much at dinner.
I mean, I'm talking about my ex,
I'm talking about my feelings, I...
I scare 'em off.
Crying?
DiNozzo men don't cry.
You'd be surprised...
how many of my clients just want
a shoulder to cry on.
Opening up...
is the first step.
Let's skip to the last step.
That's easy.
Pick the right woman.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's fine.
It's a struggle...
to become the man
that you want to be.
It's harder than you want,
it's longer than you want,
and it takes more out of you than...
than you expect that it should.
Silicon band around
his right eyeball.
Ocular surgery.
No doubt to repair
a detached retina.
What has this to do with his death?
Nothing.
I don't know if Tyler became
the man that he wanted to be,
but I do know he wanted to be
the man that he ultimately became.
He was a leader, he was a teacher,
and he taught those hard lessons
to so many of us here.
He helped us to see
that it might be possible.
To be someone else.
To be better
than you might have dreamed.
Our dreams got bigger
because he told us
that it was possible.
I hope his legacy
lives on in each of us.
For every life that was touched
by his generosity.
I know that Tyler Owens
will live on in me.
Thank you.
www.Team-NCIS.com