www.Team-NCIS.com
I can't. I'm still working.
Hey, this is my big week, man.
I made more tips today than
all last month.
Yeah, I got four more deliveries.
Yeah, I'll hook up with you
around 7:00.
Yeah, whatever.
NCIS Season 6 Episode 11
Silent Night LOL V1.0
Synchro: ¤AkaZab¤ & Gaillots.
Rereading: Bruno & Magic Turtle.
www.Team-NCIS.com
I used to love this game as a kid.
Oh, me too.
My mother preferred
I played with dolls.
My favorite was G.I. Joe.
David, thank you.
My pleasure.
I enjoy shopping...
especially when it's not my money.
Good.
That was security.
A Detective Kemp is on his way up.
- Anyone know where Gibbs is?
- Detective Justin Kemp?
That's the one. Metro Homicide.
Why, do you know him?
Sort of... you know...
What does that mean?
We have a mutual friend.
I used to date Kemp's wife.
How...
many dates we talking about here?
Guys, what's it matter?
I don't know.
Like two, or three?
Four.
- Not a big deal.
- Oh, it's...
Four months.
At least four months.
- That is...
- That is a big deal.
So what's Kemp doing here?
Investigating a home invasion robbery.
Double homicide, it's an older couple.
And how does that involve us?
They don't want to discuss it
on the phone.
Close your mouth, Ziva.
He's married.
- Kemp.
- DiNozzo.
- Special Agent Gibbs.
- Sorry to ruin your Christmas.
It's December 23rd.
We're not going anywhere.
Found fingerprints at the crime scene.
Ran them through AFIS...
I got a hit, a Ned Quinn.
A former petty officer.
Vietnam vet.
We had a witness,
a delivery boy.
Worked with our sketch artist.
Looks like an older version of...
- him.
- Can't be.
Quinn died in a fire in 1991.
That's why I'm here.
According to V.A. records,
Quinn's buried at Arlington.
McGee, pull a copy
of the death certificate.
Boss, this is not good.
It's a sixpence.
What does it have to do
with Christmas?
Everything, Abby.
It's a tradition.
That coin has been baked, well,
steamed actually,
into every Mallard Christmas pudding
since the 1850s.
It brings good fortune and luck
in the coming year
to whoever finds it on their plate.
Assuming
they don't choke to death on it.
Sadly,
with no extended family here,
I've let the tradition lapse.
Next year, Ducky,
you and me, we're going
to make Christmas pudding.
I'd like that.
I like everything about Christmas.
Except for...
that Chipmunk song. And shopping,
I hate shopping. I never know
what do get anyone, specially Gibbs.
What do you get for the guy that has
nothing and wants nothing?
Some squeaky shoes.
Hi, Gibbs!
Bye, Gibbs.
Something wrong, Jethro?
Fingerprints found
at a double homicide yesterday.
Belong to a petty officer who's supposed
to have been dead 17 years.
- His death certificate.
- Oh, dear.
Someone's in trouble.
I signed it?
Graduated with honors
from the University of Virginia.
He was accepted
to its medical school,
but didn't go.
Enlisted in the Navy.
Became a corpsman instead.
Attached to the First Battalion,
Ninth Marines.
The walking dead.
Came home from Vietnam in 1972.
Was treated at V.A.
for post traumatic stress disorder.
Quinn became addicted to methamphetamine
and was in and out of rehab.
His wife divorced him in 1980,
and got full custody of
their three-year-old daughter Melissa.
He started living on the streets and
supposedly died
with seven others in a fire
at a halfway house on Canal Street.
There was nothing to hint that Quinn
was alive until yesterday's murders.
A lot of years in between.
Where's the ex-wife and
the daughter now?
Wife lives in Alexandria and
the daughter lives in Clearfield.
McGee, go with her.
... massive charring.
Pugilistic contractions
of the extremities.
Heat fractions.
Evulsion of the brain...
large and small intestines.
My voice had
a deeper timbre in those days.
You make a mistake, Duck?
The city M.E.
was unable to make a positive
identification from the charred remains.
So I was called in in the hope
that Quinn's military medical and dental
records could confirm his identity.
Unfortunately, due to the victim's
heavy drug use,
he suffered from meth mouth.
Which deteriorated his teeth
and made a dental match impossible.
DNA?
That was not an option back then.
All I had to go by was an examination of
the skull and measurement of the bones.
From which I determined only that
it was a male,
Caucasian,
about 40 years old and six foot two.
- Well, fit Quinn's description then.
- And since
the remains were found in Quinn's room
with all of Quinn's personal effects,
we both naturally
reached a circumstantial
and logical conclusion.
What's more,
nobody turned up
claiming to be Quinn.
Well, if it wasn't him,
then maybe...
he killed someone and
covered it up with the fire.
In Quinn's file,
it says that he was treated
for his PTSD at Bethesda.
By a psychiatrist,
one Dr...
Dr. Pryor.
Yes. As I recall, he's still there.
I need to talk to him.
Thanks for coming over, Mom. I just
have to get a few stocking stuffers.
Go, go. As long as I'm home by 6:30
to help your father brine the turkey.
You know how he gets.
Have you seen my car keys?
Jordie, did you take my keys?
I'll get it.
Hang on, hang on.
You stay here, my sweet boy.
Afternoon. NCIS.
I'm Special Agent Timothy McGee,
looking for Melissa Fox.
Who is it, Mom?
- Are you Connie Wheeler?
- Yes.
We need to ask you some questions
about your former husband, Ned Quinn.
Fingerprints found
at a crime scene match his.
Look...
that can't be.
He's been dead for 20 years.
If he were alive,
do you have
any idea where he might be?
I couldn't even offer a clue.
He's been out of our lives
since the divorce.
Melissa, have you had any contact
with your father?
Her father...
is my husband Ed.
He raised Melissa since
she was four years old.
Ned Quinn has never been
a part of her life.
I only have vague memories of him.
If he is still alive,
I don't want him to know where we are.
He's already destroyed
our lives once.
- Mommy, Mommy, I'm done.
- I'm sorry, excuse me.
When he came back from Vietnam...
he was a drug addict.
I tried, but he didn't want my help.
I moved on.
We both moved on.
I don't remember Quinn.
Apparently
we treated him over a three year period,
1979 to '82.
What were you treating him for?
He suffered from survivor guilt.
Blamed himself for a buddy's death.
Oh, my God.
I heard there was a Santa
in the building.
Abby...
He's great. Rosy cheeks,
wire-rim glasses.
Your beard looks so real...
That's because it is.
Abigail,
Dr. Pryor is a psychiatrist.
He's here to help me find...
To find out who's naughty and
who's nice. Hello?
You think I could get a picture?
Why did Quinn blame himself
for his friend's death?
Well, he and another corpsman
switched patrols a week
before their tour was to end.
The other guy
got killed in an ambush.
You last saw him in '82.
The fire was in '91.
Have you any idea of anything that
happened in the intervening years?
No. Like a lot of those guys,
he stopped coming.
They give up.
Did he have any violent tendencies?
I don't remember.
I have to be at the Children's Hospital
party in 30 minutes.
Anything that I once knew about the man
is in here.
Thank you, Dr. Pryor.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you, Santa.
I just suffered
for hours through the...
good doctor's rambling notes.
There is nothing to suggest
aggressive or impulsive behavior.
Per his service record,
Quinn left Vietnam on
December 30, 1972.
The Vietnam Veterans Memorial Wall
listed 58,000
plus names of the dead and
missing in chronological order.
According to its Web site,
17 military personnel died that week.
Of that number, two were in Long Khanh
Province where Quinn was stationed.
Only one was a Navy corpsman.
Roger Laurence Grant.
Yeah.
After the Vietnam Memorial
was dedicated,
Quinn went regularly to the wall
to pay tribute to his fallen friend.
If Quinn is still alive,
there's a chance
he might honor Roger Grant's memory
by visiting the Memorial
on the anniversary of his death.
December 24th.
Tomorrow.
- He does not dress like a cop.
- Who?
Your Detective Kemp.
You are a little fascinated by him.
- He come from money?
- Married it.
We're missing
the office Christmas party.
That could have been you.
- What is her name?
- Guy in the blue hoodie.
Could be Quinn.
Go check him out.
Too young, too fat, too female.
Answer my question.
She pretty?
Gorgeous.
She was perfect, okay?
Witty, smart.
That was 12 years ago. She's had kids.
God knows what she looks like now.
So...
what happened?
You ever...
regret...
not having a wife
and kids?
Especially during this time of year.
Hanukkah is all about family.
Is it not the same with Christmas?
I'm gonna check out
the guy in the blue hoodie.
It is a woman!
Hey, Gibbs.
The party's starting
to wind down up there.
Hollander had to be sent home
in a cab, fourth year in a row.
I brought you and McGee some eggnog.
Right.
Two for McGee.
Speaking of McGee...
and Ziva...
and Tony...
It's Christmas Eve.
- Go home.
- I can't.
- I have to go shopping.
- Then do it.
I don't know what to get anybody.
What do you think Tony needs?
- An attitude adjustment.
- Gibbs, you're not helping.
Right this way, please.
- Hi.
- Abs.
Merry Christmas.
Boss, this is Melissa Fox,
Ned Quinn's daughter.
Melissa, this is Special Agent Gibbs.
He's in charge of the case.
- Hi.
Thank you for seeing me,
Agent Gibbs.
I just wanted to make it clear
that...
my mother doesn't speak for me.
She wants no part of my father.
I do.
I have all
these childhood memories of him.
Maybe they're just fantasies, but...
don't get me wrong.
My stepfather is...
wonderful.
But I hoped...
one day to connect
with my biological father.
Did you try?
My mother protected me from him.
She didn't even tell me when
he died.
How'd you find out?
I did a search when I was 21.
Excuse me.
He's here.
Should we take him down?
No.
I'm on my way.
Thanks.
Sorry about that.
I'm still reeling from the possibility
that he might be alive.
Unlike my mother,
I'd very much like to see him.
It's like a piece of me is missing.
No matter how many times
I come here,
it still gets to me.
You look at a name,
you have to look at
a reflection of yourself.
You are among the fallen.
Yeah.
Difference is you can leave...
the names don't.
No.
Death is permanent.
Except in your case, Ned Quinn.
It's been a long time since
anybody's called me that.
He hasn't said a word since
we brought him in here.
Not surprising for a man
who spent 17 years hiding.
Skin and eyes clear,
good hygiene, no tremors.
Clean and sober.
All he had on him was eight dollars
and a key to a long-term downtown
hotel room. No ID.
Metro P.D. is on the way
to pick you up.
You'll be their problem.
That's your buddy.
Petty Officer Grant.
Corpsman.
Just like you.
Corpsman saved my life once.
So you're a former Marine, huh?
So what happened
at the Taylor house then?
Your fingerprints
were all over the place.
I didn't kill them.
You were there.
Why?
I was out on the street
with my sign,
looking for work, and the Taylors
picked me up. They needed help...
decorating their house
for the holidays.
You never met them before?
No, they said it was
their traditional way of extending
a helping hand to
those less fortunate.
Well, if you didn't kill them,
who did?
I don't know.
I was in the garage.
I was digging...
decorations out of boxes.
When I got back, I found them.
There was blood everywhere.
The husband was already dead.
The wife was on the couch.
I put her on the floor,
I tried to administer CPR.
But it was too late.
- I'll be back.
- Where are you going?
I want to catch the city M.E.
before he leaves his office.
Wish me luck.
Why'd you run?
I'd been dead for 17 years.
Who's gonna believe me?
How long has Quinn lived here?
Who?
The guy in this room.
Rembrandt?
I've been here 12 years.
He's been here longer than that.
Rembrandt ever give you any trouble?
Never. Pays his rent every Saturday,
in cash. Keeps to himself.
All right.
We'll say good-bye to you
downstairs.
Bye.
Downstairs. Thanks.
Guy's got some personality.
Check this out.
That's pretty good.
Not what I expected to find.
Not what I expected to be doing
on Christmas Eve.
- What did you expect to be doing?
- Not this.
You had no plans.
I had plans.
I had big plans.
Big, big plans.
I was ten blocks away
when the fire broke out.
So who died in your room?
Another tweaker.
I didn't know him.
He told me where I could cop. I told him
he could crash there till I got back.
When I did, there were...
fire engines and cop cars
all over the place.
Why didn't you just identify
yourself?
I realized they thought
I was in the room.
And in a rare, lucid moment,
it occurred to me
that my ex-wife and my daughter...
might be better off...
if I was dead and...
they could receive
my military benefits.
That was the only decent thing
I ever did for them.
So you disappeared.
You hid.
It's not hard
if no one's looking for you.
You work for cash,
you pay cash for what you buy,
you don't need a name.
- Did you leave D.C.?
- Thought about it, but never did.
Abby, I thought you went home.
Did Gibbs tell him that his daughter
was here and she wants to meet him?
No.
He has to.
It means everything to her.
Abby, this is not
a lost puppy for you to rescue.
You cannot make this better.
This is a murder investigation.
I think Gibbs should tell him.
And I think...
you should stay out of this.
Missed the party,
don't have to miss the food.
Hey, Ducky,
I found these in the conference room.
They're pretty delish.
You might want to try some of this,
Ducky. It's pretty good stuff.
No, thank you.
- What'd you find out at his place?
- Nothing to tie him to the murders.
Appears to have led
a non-criminal and invisible life.
Actually, he's an artist,
sketches.
Pretty good stuff.
- You catch the M.E.?
- Yes.
Mr. Taylor died of blunt force trauma
to the head
from what appears
to be several strikes of a hammer.
Mrs. Taylor, heart attack.
Ligature marks on her wrists suggest
that she was restrained by handcuffs.
But what is much more interesting:
our suspect...
is telling the truth.
He was trying to save Mrs. Taylor.
- How do you know that?
- Quinn's bloody fingerprints
knew what they were doing.
And compression bruises
on her chest suggest
he was trying to perform CPR,
Jethro.
And he knew to put her
on a hard surface, the floor.
Kill the husband, try and save the wife?
Doesn't make sense.
- Kemp's here to pick up Quinn.
- I will go get him.
Keep him here till I get back.
How can he eat those things?
Yeah?
Nice work finding Quinn so fast.
I got a lot of help from Ducky.
Same guy that declared him dead
17 years ago.
Well...
Jackie is furious.
I was supposed to be home hours ago.
All right,
time to start the Christmas holiday.
You're not here to wish me
a merry Christmas, are you?
I can't get a handle on Quinn.
He faked his own death and
we can place him at the crime scene.
But you don't think he did it?
I think we may be handing over
an innocent man to Metro.
And you're concerned
they think they've got a slam-dunk case.
They're not gonna look any further.
This was taken last Christmas.
Is that your wife?
Nobody looks that good
in a bikini after two kids.
That hotel is awesome.
Is that a Ritz-Carlton?
No, no, that's...
that's my father-in-law's villa.
So, where's Gibbs?
I need to get Quinn downtown.
We're gonna hold him here,
Detective Kemp.
- Leon Vance.
- Director.
The Navy's got unfinished business
with former Petty Officer Quinn.
What exactly?
Faked his death.
His family collected death benefits.
With all due respect, Director,
I've got him for a double homicide.
Not even close.
You know you won't be able to get
Quinn in front of a judge for days.
Relax. Enjoy a little family time.
What am I missing?
Why is NCIS interfering
with a Metro case?
Fine. Tomorrow's Christmas.
I've got two bikes and
a dollhouse to put together.
We'll be back with a court order
the day after tomorrow.
Let's go.
You asked for it.
You better work fast.
You only have a day.
- Merry Christmas.
- Hey, guys. What's up?
I hope no one has plans.
Keep Quinn in interrogation.
- We'll watch him in shifts.
- What do I do?
You and Duck go home.
It's late.
Get some sleep.
Oh, I haven't slept on Christmas Eve
since I was, like, four.
Since I started camping out in front of
the fireplace trying to catch Santa.
I should have pulled
a fingerprint off his milk glass.
I may need you both tomorrow.
Yes, I have to go visit Mother
in her new home.
May I walk you to your car?
How is she?
Driving the nurses crazy.
Kemp is focused on Quinn's fingerprints.
He's not looking at anything else.
- Do our own investigation.
- Visit the crime scene?
- Kemp will go ballistic.
- Boss,
I googled the dead couple
for background information.
Found something interesting here.
Six months ago,
the husband, Avery Taylor,
filed a multi-million-dollar
patent-infringement lawsuit
against Paradigm Industries.
Get out of town.
What?
Paradigm Industries
is owned by Gary Vanderlicht.
Metro Detective Justin Kemp's
filthy-rich father-in-law?
All right, that's it.
I know when I'm beaten.
How are we going to get
the game back in the box
and make it look like
it was never opened?
I am an expert at repacking and
re-wrapping.
Christmas mornings, I knew what was
in each present under the tree.
You peeked?
Is anybody in there?
Agent Gibbs?
When are the police
coming to pick me up?
Not for a while.
Because of the holiday,
shifts are not fully staffed.
I think you know more
than you're telling me.
Are you hungry?
Do you need anything?
A pencil and paper.
I can't sleep.
Sketching relaxes me.
Oh, yeah, I know,
sharp object.
I promise I won't stab myself.
Not a happy Christmas morning
for the Taylors.
Hey, wanna make this interesting?
I bet you five bucks I can crack the
alarm code before you can pick the lock.
I will take that bet.
Okay.
How did you do that?
The one, the four,
the seven and the nine are worn.
The code had to be a combination
of those four numbers.
People like to choose numbers
that are easy to remember:
address, anniversary,
birthday, birth year.
Being a good Boy Scout,
I came prepared.
The Taylors were born in 1947.
Five bucks.
Sorry, loser.
- What do we think the police missed?
- If we believe Quinn,
he found the wife's body
on the couch and moved it on the floor.
- They wouldn't have known that.
- Got it.
Kemp's investigation focused
on the fingerprint evidence
and the couple's bodies,
which were found here...
and here.
Let's check out
the rest of the house.
That's good.
So were the sketches in your room.
Did you take art classes in college?
No.
Rehab.
I guess being pre-med,
you don't really have a lot of time
to take electives.
You wanted to be a doctor.
'Nam changed things.
Looks like a chair was moved.
Found fibers, hair and...
- Watch!
- A button.
Found the chair.
Looks like somebody wanted
to get something on the upper shelf.
It's a safe.
It's empty.
I'm guessing Metro police got it wrong.
The robbery netted more
than just the jewelry the wife
was wearing and the husband's cash.
Dust it.
Security patrol.
Who are you guys?
NCIS.
We received an alarm.
I thought you turned it off?
It's
our top-of-the-line HS 3000 system.
It's a double-redundant.
If you don't punch in the code twice,
it sends a silent alarm.
Double redundancy,
how could I know that?
Thought the police had a suspect.
- What are you guys doing here?
- They asked for our help.
They didn't tell us.
We got work to do.
NCIS...
heard about you guys.
I've been in the private
security business for three years.
Doesn't pay very well.
Does NCIS take applications?
Merry Christmas, Tiny Tim!
- What are you doing here?
- Well, today's Christmas.
I just came from church.
I didn't have anything planned and
I wanted to be with my team.
Where is everybody?
In the field.
- How's he doin'?
- You know.
Does he...
mention his daughter?
No.
- You think he'd like to see her?
- I don't know. Why are you asking?
Because Melissa's in the lobby and
she wants to see him.
How did she know that we found him?
Well, she might have figured it out
when I called her and told her.
Abby, what, what are you doing?
You called her? Gibbs,
- Gibbs is gonna kill you!
- No, he won't.
Think about it, Tim.
This is
the greatest fairy tale ever.
There's a little girl and
her dad leaves.
And then he lives on the streets.
And then he dies.
And she's never gonna see him again.
She's never gonna get to say...
all the things that a daughter
wants to say to her father.
And then she grows up and
she has a child of her own,
and then...
wonder of all wonders,
he comes back from the dead
and they get reunited...
on Christmas!
- Abby, are you finished?
- Please, please, please, pretty please?
Do it for me, okay?
Just, just tell him Melissa's here.
You'll understand when you see
the sparkle in his eye.
All right.
You have a visitor.
- Who?
- Melissa, your daughter.
- She's here?
- Yep. Wants to talk to you.
I don't want to see her.
And you tell her that
she was better off when I was dead.
Okay.
Here, let me,
let me help you with that.
Got it. Thanks.
So how'd you hook up with NCIS?
See if DiNozzo is finished
in the garage.
She's cute.
So, maybe I could, you know... well,
good luck with the case.
Think we just got
a Christmas present.
What the hell is going on?!
Metro Police Chief
just gave me an earful.
Claims you broke into their crime scene
and corrupted the chain of evidence.
- Tell me you didn't do that.
- How'd he find out?
Metro got a call
from the home-security firm.
Come on, Daddy!
This how you spend your Christmas?
Most people are home opening presents.
Yeah, most people.
Cops are on their way
to pick up Quinn.
- Leon, we're late.
- Get him ready.
- Hey, Gibbs.
- Looks like we got the murder weapon.
Blood on the hammer
matches the victim's type.
You're not gonna like this, Gibbs.
The prints on the handle
belong to the victim...
and to Ned Quinn.
It looks like mine.
Your prints are on it.
Look, the Taylors hired me to help them
decorate their house.
I brought my toolbox.
When I left,
I was in a hurry.
I didn't stop to see
if I brought my hammer.
You said you were in their garage.
- That's where the hammer was found.
- I don't know how it got.
What do you want me to tell you?
You know, you're getting harder and
harder to believe.
Right, Sherlock.
Vietnam Vet, stoner,
a man with no name.
It's got to be me.
Metro police are here.
I will have McGee bring you down.
You make it a habit,
keeping people waiting?
- What's the rush, Kemp?
- It's Christmas.
Maybe if you had a family,
DiNozzo, you'd understand.
How did your daughter
like the dollhouse?
She loved it.
Yeah, she took it with her
when she left this morning.
- Where did she go?
- A family tradition.
Yeah, we spend the week between
Christmas and New Year's at the villa.
Yeah, right now they're
on my father-in-law's G5.
Thanks to you guys, the Chief's
on my ass, wouldn't let me leave.
And if I'm luck
I'm getting out of here late tonight.
Well, I really feel for you, Kemp.
Life's tough.
- Where's Quinn?
- On the way.
You gonna explain to me
why you broke into the crime scene?
Are you gonna explain to me why you
didn't remove yourself from this case?
Why would I do that?
Avery Taylor was suing
your father-in-law.
You have no business
investigating Taylor's murder.
- What are you talking about?
- Paradigm Industries?
A little case of
patent-infringement?
All right, let me tell you
a couple things. Okay, one:
my father-in-law
is the CEO of a holding company
that owns over a dozen
multi-million-dollar companies,
and two: he never
discusses business with me.
I don't like
what you're insinuating.
Are you going to tell him
we found the murder weapon?
He never asked.
Thanks, I was running on empty.
God!
They put nutmeg in it
for the holidays.
What do you got, Abs?
The hair on the couch
belonged to Mrs. Taylor.
I'm still working on the fibers.
As for the button Ziva found,
it was made exclusively
for a clothing manufacturer
in Scranton, Pennsylvania,
who specializes exclusively
in military and police uniforms.
Dusting the safe
produced an unknown print.
Mistletoe.
You run the print through AFIS, Abs?
No.
- I didn't say it was a fingerprint.
- Well, what was it, Abby?
It was a fabric print.
Most likely made from a glove.
Should've worn latex.
Leather and fabric gloves
have a distinct weave, grain,
wear and stitching pattern.
In this case, an old leather one
with U-shaped scuff and a frayed seam.
You bring me a glove, and I'll tell you
if it left a print on the safe.
You might've redeemed yourself, Abs.
What'd I do?
Called Quinn's daughter. McGee!
Got it, Boss.
Taylors' home-security
system interfaces
with the company's central
dispatch via the Internet.
Your hunch was right.
The alarm was deactivated
at 2:17 AM this morning.
Between the time Kemp
sealed the house and you...
Broke in.
Well, I was gonna say
gained unauthorized access.
Alarm was reactivated
four and a half minutes later.
DiNozzo, call
your ex-girlfriend's husband.
Have him meet us at the Taylors'.
Ziva, get the car.
How about Ziva makes the call and
I get the car?
Or not.
I'll do it.
You guys really don't have lives,
do you?
What are we doing here?
Arresting the murderer.
He's in a holding cell,
downtown, Gibbs.
What is it with you people?
First you declare him dead
now you're trying to help him
beat a double-homicide rap?
This was a home invasion.
But not for the wife's jewelry
or pocket change.
It was all about the safe.
DiNozzo, break in.
With great pleasure, sir.
What safe?
I guess you missed this.
Okay.
So, what?
It was Quinn.
His bloody prints
were all over the place.
Yeah, because he was trying
to save the couple's lives.
He was in the garage
at the time of the murders.
Last night,
while Quinn was in our custody,
somebody deactivated the alarm and
planted the murder weapon.
- A hammer.
- In the garage.
Trying to seal the case
against Quinn.
Wait, you had a murder weapon and
didn't tell me?
Who knew about the alarm code
other than the Taylors?
We have company.
Hi, Harvey.
Hey, what's going on?
Lose a button?
Looks just like
the ones on your shirt.
Found it on the couch.
Where you handcuffed Mrs. Taylor.
Other thing you left behind
was a print...
on the safe.
You didn't know that gloves
could leave prints, did you, Harvey?
Are those yours right there?
Look at that.
Frayed seams.
That's a TASER, Harvey.
You only have one shot.
Non-fatal.
There's five of us.
Don't move!
- Just breathe through it.
- God!
He confessed?
He knew they kept cash and
jewelry in their safe.
Didn't know that Quinn
was in the garage.
When the wife panicked,
She went into cardiac arrest.
The husband freaked,
attacked the security
guard with the only weapon
he could find. Quinn's hammer.
- The guard overpowered and killed him.
- Abby, it's beautiful.
A cotton-ball bouquet.
See what I got.
- Cufflinks, made out of...
- Spent nine-millimeter slugs.
Friction makes us static.
Would you stop that?!
I'm still humming from the TASER.
Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight you're all going to share in
a DiNozzo family tradition.
Caramel popcorn, hot mulled cider
and the greatest, greatest
Christmas movie of all time,
It's a Wonderful Life!
Wonderful.
- We can't start until Gibbs gets here.
- He said not to wait for him.
Where is he?
Where are we?
- Melissa's house.
- No, Gibbs.
You don't know me.
- I ruin lives, I am poison.
- Give yourself some credit.
You're not the same person
that dropped out of her life
when she was three years old.
You've changed.
- I don't need this. I don't.
- She does.
There's too much time that's passed.
If I had one wish for Christmas,
it would be to hug my daughter.
That can never be.
You have that chance.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas, Dad.
Merry Christmas, Son.
Merry Christmas !
www.Team-NCIS.com