www.Team-NCIS.com
Code Red in secure inpatient
wing, second level. Code Red.
Floor supervisor report
to station immediately.
This is a Code Red.
Team-NCIS.com presents:
NCIS Season 5 Episode 10
Corporal Punishment (Version LOL V1.0)
Synchro: Akazab, Kasius.
Capture: Swsub.com
www.Team-NCIS.com
Come on, Iron Fist,
hit me with your best shot.
Could you be careful, please?
This is number 14.
It's the first appearance of Sabertooth.
Does that make you want to hit me?
It's really tempting.
But I think I'm gonna pass.
Maybe Ziva'll do it.
Maybe Ziva will do what?
Been working on my six-pack.
You know... Abs.
You and Abby have been drinking?
No, abdominals.
No more beer gut for me.
I've been training hard-core,
getting the core hard-carved.
- Hard as wood.
- To match your head.
You know, I think you're afraid
that if you hit me as hard as you could,
I'd think I was being tickled
with a feather.
I will take a swing at your six-pack.
Well...
It's more like a four-pack
and then there's this one sort of long,
stubborn one, never mind.
Do it.
As hard as she can?
As hard as you can.
- You know that's how Houdini died.
- Ziva, did you kill Houdini?
It is possible.
I do not remember all their names.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, do it.
Escaped mental patient.
Exactly what I'm thinking, boss.
Bethesda Naval Hospital.
Attacked an orderly busted up the place.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, come on, I don't need the rescue.
Seriously, give me your best shot.
Right now.
Oh, yeah!
Not bad.
Not as good as Gibbs, though.
Cramped quarters.
In-patient wing.
It's a secure unit.
Least it's meant to be.
How long's he been here?
Got shipped home from Iraq
about two weeks ago.
He's been receiving treatment
for post-traumatic stress.
What happened to him?
Beats the hell out of me.
Guy didn't talk much.
That's typical of PTSD.
The shrink's been trying to get him
to open up as part of his treatment.
What's the other part?
Meds.
Combination of antidepressant
paroxetine and
mild sedatives that help him sleep.
Might want to consider something
a little stronger.
He did this with his bare hands?
Yeah.
Impressive.
Outside.
You already done in here?
Yeah. Don't need to look the one place
we know he's not.
Corporal Damon Werth, Force Recon,
part of the Second Marines
stationed in Ramadi.
Transferred out 15 days ago,
ahead of his unit.
Brief stops at Ramstein Air Base
in Germany, then here.
What happened
after he went out the window?
He jacked a ride
pulling out of the driveway.
Where's the driver?
There was a lot going on, I...
Where's the driver?!
I don't know.
Boss, I could pull up the exterior
cameras, might be able to see something.
In fact, I could probably
be doing that right now,
instead of talking about it.
All right, listen up, people.
Our fugitive has been on the run
for 90 minutes.
It has been three hours, Tony.
Average foot speed over uneven ground,
barring injuries,
is four miles per hour.
He's not on foot. He's in a car.
What I need
from each and every one of you
is a hard-target search
of every gas station,
residence, warehouse,
farmhouse, henhouse,
outhouse and doghouse in the area.
Our fugitive has a name and it is...
Corporal Damon Werth.
Hey.
The Tommy Lee Jones speech,
every time we have a fugitive, really?
He's not just a fugitive.
Werth took a hostage.
Who?
Dr. Adrian De La Casa.
BOLO out on his car.
De La Casa's
one of the attending psychiatrists
on the ward, had the graveyard shift.
Involved in Werth's treatment?
Might help his chances.
He knows who he's dealing with.
At least someone does.
What does De La Casa think of Werth?
Well...
Patient exhibits paranoia,
delusional fantasies,
hyperactivity,
tendency towards violent outbursts.
What does Werth think of De La Casa?
Doesn't say.
I think I'm staring at the man
in charge right now.
You are?
I'm gonna find out what Corporal
Werth's status is.
So are we.
Yes, sir.
Apologies.
Senator Hawkins. Ray Vincent.
Senator's Public Affairs.
You're Gibbs?
You need to work fast.
This could be a potential PR disaster.
It's always my primary concern.
See,
the thing is,
in three days,
the senator is scheduled to give
Corporal Werth the Silver Star.
Your missing Marine's a hero.
When you're dealing with a guy
on the run, you gotta
climb inside his head
think his thoughts.
What would he do?
Where would he go?
Did a one-armed man murder his wife?
Would he dress up like a clown
and join a traveling circus?
Like Jimmy Stewart
in The Greatest Show on Earth.
Do any of your ideas come from reality?
Sure.
Just not your reality.
Could you try to zero in
on Werth's reality?
Considering that the dude skipped
the loony bin,
maybe a little bit of non-linear
fuzzy logic is the key to tracking him.
Maybe he was accused of a crime
he didn't commit
and is trying to promptly escape
to the Los Angeles underground.
He's not the A-Team, McGee.
He might be,
aside from a single medical incident
that delayed his career
Corporal Werth is your poster boy
for the Marine Corps.
Performance evals?
Rapid improvement in every facet since
he enlisted four years ago.
Strength, speed, stamina,
mental acuity, everything.
Steady promotion up the ranks,
due to make Sergeant.
The only time Werth has been
away from the Marines
was to go to England
for a joint training exercise
with British SAS.
That was his vacation?
How did he do?
He aced it.
I have to brief the senator
and then try to run interference
with the media.
You'll update me every half hour, yes?
The clock is ticking on this, people.
Sophie, yeah.
Let the senator know that I just
met with NCIS and it's under control.
The suit fill you in
on what happened in Iraq?
Werth's unit was ambushed and captured.
He was being tortured
when he broke loose.
He killed his interrogators
and carried all three
of his men to safety.
Leathernecks nicknamed him
"Corporal Punishment."
What else you got?
Werth's life.
Locations of interest.
Boot camp at Parris Island,
stationed at Quantico then LeJeune
before shipping out overseas.
Family?
Unmarried. No siblings.
His father is retired SAS,
mother is a behavioral therapist.
They live in Michigan.
Senator Hawkins' home state.
Friends in the area?
Yeah, I don't think he had any friends
outside of the Corps, boss.
Dr. De La Casa?
Navy Captain.
Resides in Reston, Virginia.
He works at Bethesda.
So he'd have to take
the Dulles Toll Road every day.
So he would have a SmartTag, McGoo.
Scanned on 267 yesterday.
Again this morning,
entering Virginia.
Tried to triangulate De La Casa's cell,
but it's either switched off
or Werth's laying low
in the countryside, out of range.
Wait,
SmartTag, just entered the District.
Try his cell again.
- Hello?
- Who is this?
Gibbs. NCIS.
I'm looking for
a Dr. Adrian De La Casa.
Well, look harder.
Northwest DC. If he leaves his cell on,
I can get an exact location.
Do it on the way.
Just lights.
For what?
Dr. De La Casa?
Yes.
I thought you were him coming back.
Where'd he go?
I don't know.
He did something with my laptop
and disappeared.
What's with the lights?
Boss?
Now he knows what we look like.
I kept trying to get through to him,
but he didn't seem to recognize me.
Well, it's not unusual for PTSD victims
to exhibit
dissociative behavior.
You're the medical examiner?
I am. But I have also done an extensive
study of the science
of psychological profiling.
Well, the patient.
Corporal Werth.
Werth...
He didn't speak for some time
after he took the wheel.
He seemed confused by his surroundings.
Well, what gave you that impression?
He kept mumbling something about sand
or the lack thereof.
Expected to find himself in the desert.
I believe so.
I tried to talk to him,
he stopped the car, and accused me
of manipulating the environment.
Of making him see things
that weren't there.
Why you?
He may have thought
I was a voice in his head.
Obviously,
I tried to convince him otherwise.
He subdued me,
bound me.
You didn't resist.
I was afraid for my life.
He picked up on that fear.
Made him feel in control.
He could've been riding an adrenaline
high following his escape.
Then he asked about PFCs
Whitney, Stone and Heatherton.
The other men in his unit.
He wanted to know where they were,
where we were keeping them.
Where are you keeping them?
We're not keeping them.
McGee managed to
blah, blah, blah
computer-geek stuff and he
figured out that the
video feed was being accessed from
a public site a few blocks
from the garage.
While he watched us.
Yep, that is exactly true.
Last files accessed
on De La Casa's laptop...
were Patient logs.
Yeah.
- Three names in particular...
- Whitney, Stone, and Heatherton.
Well, that's kind of creepy,
that you can...
Whitney and Heatherton
were treated and released
for wounds sustained in combat.
Transferred to LeJeune
for redeployment.
Stone?
His injuries were the most severe.
He's undergoing rehabilitative
physical therapy at Walter Reed.
Werth is on his way there.
Is he going to break out
of one hospital
just to break into another one?
I'm going to go warm up the car.
Jethro,
Werth's behavior is consistent
with post-traumatic stress.
But he didn't harm De La Casa
unnecessarily.
He still had the mental capacity
to booby trap the car.
It shows that somewhere in his mind,
he's operating clearly.
It's his training, Ducky.
As a syndrome,
PTSD is in its infancy,
even though the symptoms
had long been recognized
by returning soldiers.
Shell shock.
Yeah. Well,
there was a landmark legal case
The Buffalo Creek Disaster.
A West Virginia coal
mining community was
utterly destroyed when a dam gave way
during a heavy rainstorm.
Psychologists descended
upon the ruined valley
to identify the common malady
that afflicted the survivors.
Nightmares, insomnia, paranoia,
depression, memory loss.
You know the symptoms well.
Now, I'm of the opinion that Werth
is replaying a scenario
that he's already completed.
He thinks he's still at war?
Well, it's not uncommon
for PTSD victims
to respond to a trigger of some sort.
I've read accounts
of Buffalo Creek survivors
where they became hysterical
at the mere sound of raindrops
on a tin roof.
You think Werth has a trigger, Ducky?
I think you should be careful.
McGee, David...
Perimeter.
- It's Stone right there.
- That's it, Nate.
Don't be afraid
to put all your weight on it.
It feels weird.
It'll feel less weird
once you get used to it.
- PFC Stone?
- Yes, sir.
- Call me when you're done.
- Thanks, Karen.
You heard from Corporal Werth?
Got him in a brig at Bethesda.
They won't even let me in to see him.
He broke out this morning.
Good.
He's not a prisoner.
Shouldn't be treated
that way in the first place.
He may try to find you.
Hope he does.
He saved my life.
I'd give it right back
to him if he need it.
'Cause of him,
I might even be able
to return to combat.
You do that, Devil Dog.
Corporal Werth doesn't realize
that he ever left.
He thinks you're in trouble.
Corporal wouldn't hurt me.
Yeah, but would he hurt
someone else if they got in his way?
What do you want from me?
Well, let's see what we've got here.
Cameras on the north and south gates.
Possible point of entry
from the fire escape.
That's odd.
Dr. De La Casa.
I thought he was headed home.
Why would he come here?
He didn't.
Werth has his badge.
Gibbs,
Werth is here.
I know.
Drop your weapons!
Kick 'em away.
You don't want to do this, Corporal.
Nate, come on,
we're getting out of here.
I'm okay, Corporal.
I'm safe.
Stop moving.
We're not.
The other two!
PFC Stone, get up now! That's an order!
Your leg.
Left it in the desert.
Remember?
You carried me out on your back.
Corporal, you're safe now.
You and your men, you rescued them.
We're here to help you.
Trust him, Damon.
He's a grunt.
He's one of us?
We have to take you into custody.
You understand that?
Put it down.
McGee, back off!
Boss...
Damon, don't do it!
Damon!
- No, don't shoot him! Don't shoot him!
- Sit down!
Damon!
Stay down!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Calm down!
Tony has a broken nose.
McGee has a dislocated shoulder.
But we caught the guy.
What is he even doing here?
He should be locked up.
- He's an animal.
- He's not an animal.
He's a man.
Are you defending him?
He attacked for no reason.
- The guy's a killing machine.
- He's a Marine.
Who was willing to give up everything
for his country.
We have a responsibility to him.
Oh, spare me the samurai code of honor.
Noble respect for your combatant,
it's admirable but he tried to kill Tony
and he tried to kill McGee.
And me, too.
Believe me, we are fine.
Calm down.
Ziva, can't you just let me get it out
for a second?
I mean, I'm not like you. I'm not some
totally emotionless perfect warrior.
God...
Agent Gibbs,
you've met Karen Sutherland.
Briefly.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
How are your people?
They're busted up a little,
they'll be all right.
Ms. Sutherland
is a research and development
engineer at Biotech.
Defense contract.
I specialize
in next-generation prosthesis
designing, fitting,
modifications.
Lot of business lately.
Too much, unfortunately.
But we're trying to create something
positive out of all the loss.
Have you seen your share
of traumatized warriors?
I'm sure, 30 years ago,
most of the returning
vets you work with would have died
in the field.
Well, broken bodies are easier to heal
than broken minds.
My company also develops
alternative therapies
to treat the psychological conditions.
Competition for DARPA funding
must be intense.
If I may,
what's going to happen to Corporal Werth
now that he's in your custody?
Why exactly do you want to know?
Personal curiosity.
It seems a great many people
are interested in Werth's well-being.
I've had several calls
from Senator Hawkins' office,
about a Silver Star presentation.
Werth abducted a Navy medical officer,
assaulted Federal agents.
But you don't intend to charge him.
He was not in his right mind.
Then he should probably
go back to the shrinks.
For all the good it did
the first time around.
What would you have us do with him,
Ms. Sutherland?
Well, that's not my place.
I just witnessed his incident.
It was frightening.
I'm concerned.
We all are.
What do you intend to do
with Corporal Werth, Agent Gibbs?
Talk to him...
Marine to Marine.
Why didn't you have
that looked at in the ER?
I am fine.
You shouldn't be embarrassed.
Invincibility is not
a human characteristic.
Gibbs is going to interrogate him?
Yes. I'm sure
that Gunnery Sergeant Gibbs
has a notion of how to get through to
Corporal Werth's troubled mind.
You got yourself in a mess, Corporal.
Gonna have to get yourself out.
What seems to be the problem?
What seems to be the problem, Marine?!
I want to kill someone, sir!
Anyone in particular?
Anyone will do, sir.
Does that feel right to you, son?
No, sir.
It does not.
I'm not right, sir.
But it's not my fault.
Tell me what it feels like.
Needles and pills.
Needles and pins?
No, sir. Needles and pills.
They put a cloud in my head.
It's dark behind my eyes.
I can't see in there.
Who drugged you?
I don't know.
I can't find it. I can't...
remember.
You got to help me.
At ease, son.
I will.
His symptoms are in no way exclusive
to post-traumatic stress.
You believe him?
Irritability, delusion, hostility...
All of these could be an adverse
reaction to any number of medications.
And in his field evaluation,
I find references to anxiety,
paranoia,
and they all predate his capture.
Too long in Iraq?
I do not get the impression
he suffered in the field.
Yes. That does seem
to be his natural habitat.
Look, you have established a rapport.
Perhaps you could convince him
to part with urine and blood samples.
I made a promise to this Marine.
Plan to keep it.
So, I guess he's a liar, too.
Other than low concentrations
of sedatives and anti-depressants,
his blood was clean of drugs.
Well, the results of Werth's urinalysis
should confirm that then.
I can't just turn off
one part of my head right now
and turn on the other part.
You know what?
I don't even care.
I need you to draw
upon that considerable capacity
that you have for
empathy, for a moment.
I don't want to help him.
This young man you deem
to be a villain may,
in fact, be a victim.
What are we looking for?
Probenecid, spironolactone, furosemide
and any other uricosurics
and diuretics.
Masking agents.
Look at me.
Like Jack Nicholson
in Chinatown.
Stupid can!
You know what happened to the kitty cat
who got too curious?
Don't make me break out my Jack,
'cause I will.
Straw?
No, I'm good.
I got the one arm.
- Thank you.
- Maybe it was you, McGee.
The one-armed man?
Thought it was
one of those vets we met
at the Walter Reed Hospital.
Wrong case, Tony.
We even have a case?
We already got the guy.
What are we doing?
What did we miss?
What's happening?
They gave him painkillers.
My fingers are finging.
You hear that?
Excellent work, Agent Gibbs.
- You'll be receiving a commendation...
- Where is he?
Orders from SecNav.
Werth is being transferred
back to Bethesda.
The doctor will see to him.
Make sure he's presentable
for your photo-op?
The man is entitled to his medal.
All you care about is selling the war.
You don't support the war?
I support the men fighting it.
A complex series of masking agents
hampered detection,
but we've managed to find
Oxymetholone stacked with Nandrolone.
In addition, countless other compounds
that we have yet to identify.
Anabolic steroids.
Steroids?
Well, testosterone levels far beyond
even the most reckless of bodybuilders.
The science at work here
is very advanced,
with every indication
that it's been going on for years.
Werth's behavior is likely the result
of steroid-induced psychosis.
Someone is using that Marine
as a lab rat.
Abby's mapping Werth's blood work.
Already found a bunch of steroids,
well covered.
Would have been masked
from standard drug testing.
Drug testing's big bucks, McGiggle.
NFL, NBA, Major League Baseball...
They all face the same problem.
Don't forget the Tour de France.
How could I?
Those short little shorts.
He could have been injected
his entire career. Werth is not
just a Marine
with post-traumatic stress.
Someone has tried to create
a super-soldier.
He's in a hospital bed.
Weak.
19 years old.
He's just been rejected by the Corps.
His dream of becoming a Marine
over before it starts.
Because he's Four F,
has an anemic blood disorder.
Three years later, he's ripping through
boot camp. Attending physician
calls the improvement
in his blood-cell count miraculous.
It's not a miracle, it's an experiment.
Someone turned Damon Werth
into Captain America.
Werth's Swiss cheese brain
means he can't name the mad scientist.
Any chance the attending
was Dr. De la Casa?
No such luck.
As far as I can tell, they didn't
cross paths till a couple weeks ago.
Then who?
Who would benefit
from an experiment like this?
Well, there's big money
in pharmaceuticals.
What?
Find out what kind of research
the Biotech corporation does,
and everything on Karen Sutherland.
- DiNozzo.
- Yeah, boss.
You're with me.
The pursuit of juicy
government contracts spurs a lot of R&D.
Yeah, it runs the gamut from pills
that will keep a person
awake for days at a time to
biomechanical exoskeletons to...
nanoparticle technology.
A hell of a company.
I feel like James Bond
walking into Q's laboratory.
Well, DARPA's money did pay
for night vision, lasers and stealth.
And the Internet.
That's a light-emitting diode.
It speeds the healing process.
Might help the damaged cartilage
in your nose, Agent DiNozzo.
Your company builds super-soldiers.
Not a term we use in-house, Agent Gibbs.
Connotes killing power.
Our mission is to increase human
effectiveness,
durability and longevity.
What point in the development process
do you begin field testing
on human subjects?
We're subject to government oversight.
That's too bad.
All these cool toys,
and someone else tells you
how to play with 'em.
Can I ask you a question?
You ever jump the gun a bit with the...
magic pills?
Cut through the red tape?
Work out the kinks?
In-house?
Corporal Werth.
His condition is pharmaceutically-based.
Steroids.
I appreciate you've taken
a special interest in his case.
And you, too.
He's highly decorated.
You're highly decorated.
Silver Star?
That's a lot in common.
You've done your research.
That's the word on my door.
Well, he is a Marine, and you're an...
- ex-Marine.
- No such thing as ex-Marines.
Put our lives in each other's hands.
Accept that you're part
of something greater.
That sounds like a religion.
More a faith.
Well, steroids are extremely hazardous.
Carry many health risks.
I wish I could help you,
Agent Gibbs, but...
our company does not conduct
dangerous experiments
on human test subjects.
In case you were wondering,
he doesn't care about the medals.
I keep his in a drawer.
She's lying.
Of course she is.
They do human testing on power drinks.
Why not Biotech?
Abby, I really...
I need my arm to access
these financial records.
You have nothing to do?
I created a blueprint
of all the compounds
that Werth was given.
If you can find me
an existing experiment, I can match it
and prove that he was their guinea pig.
I need to get Biotech to open
their ultra-secret books.
If there's anything you can do
that could get you off of me...
I'm so glad you...
- smell like garbage.
- Yeah.
I know. I was going
through Karen Sutherland's trash.
- Find anything?
- She recycles
and composts.
Who composts?
Those a pretty extreme lengths
to go to for this guy.
But...
I understand now.
No true warrior should be felled
by invisible forces.
It's dishonorable.
And that other thing I said...
I know that's not really true.
What does that mean?
What she just said.
What other thing?
That I do not have feelings.
I do have feelings,
though I do not express myself
the way Abby does.
No one expresses themself
Themself?
Themselves?
Themself.
What were you having feelings about?
You said you were having feelings?
I said I have feelings.
Not that I am having feelings.
That is a pretty sophisticated
grammatical differentiation.
Don't change the subject
with your big words, McNerd.
Ziva said she had a feeling.
Tell us about this feeling.
What was this feeling?
I felt...
overwhelmed...
temporarily.
Which does not often happen to me,
when we were wrestling with Werth.
What?
What is this look?
Nothing.
You like him.
I thought he was powerful.
You really like him.
No, I am saying he is stronger
than any man I have encountered, but
strength should not decide a battle.
There is a weapon for every fight.
- You itching for a rematch?
- Want to roll around on the ground
- with him some more?
- I am trying to describe something
- complicated.
- It's not complicated, Ziva.
- It's Conan.
- To her Red Sonja?
Nice.
It only lasted a moment.
You had a moment.
A moment and a feeling.
And a smack to the head.
Broken nose, dislocated shoulder.
It's been a banner day.
Easy on the painkillers, DiNozzo.
Director have any luck, boss?
Public affairs guy is stonewalling.
His main concern is keeping
Werth docile for the ceremony.
They don't wanna know
how he got that way.
Or they know already.
What do we know?
Looks like Karen Sutherland is
the bleeding heart she appears to be.
Volunteer consultant
with Doctors Without Borders.
Donates to several charities
for the mentally disabled.
If she's got a fault,
it's that she cares too much.
Which is something
we might be able to exploit, boss.
I told you that information
is proprietary.
- I can't discuss it with you.
- Cutting-edge research.
Financial temptation
must be hard to resist.
You're wasting your time
if you think I'm selling secrets.
McGee.
You spent your summer traveling
through Africa with a team of doctors.
You've been poking around my life?
Only fair.
This report from the World Health
Organization features several children
who received treatment
for land mine injuries.
Called their rapid healing "miraculous."
I hear "miracle,"
I look for answers.
Can't just take it on faith, huh?
You didn't sell any secrets.
You gave them away for free.
Your heart's in the right place.
Your LED device is low-cost,
highly effective,
but it is corporate property.
The super-soldier program.
If anything on this comes back to me,
my career is over.
Hope it answers all your questions.
You could've just asked nicely.
This is nicely.
Platelet acceleration,
human growth hormone
and cybernetic implants.
These people have read
way too many sci-fi comics.
Some of these experiments
are more "fi" than "sci."
One of 'em makes people
glow in the dark.
What do we got?
- A couple of surprises.
- Good or bad?
Would it surprise you to learn
that Karen Sutherland has reviewed
every single human research project
at her company since you met with her?
Time stamps on the files
she downloaded.
Worried her company
might be responsible.
- Are they?
- For a lot of questionable experiments,
definitely.
But as far as our guy...
This is the map I compiled
of all the chemical compounds
that are running through Werth's blood.
This is a blueprint
of the chemical compounds
the Biotech Corporation
is experimenting with.
None of them match.
Werth's not their test subject.
Sutherland'll be relieved.
She's not responsible.
Someone else is.
The Director managed to get a list
of every super-soldier proposal
- competing for funding from DARPA.
- None involved steroids.
Whatever's been done to Werth was...
somebody's pet project,
but they didn't leave a trail.
He's the only evidence the experiment
ever took place.
The only one who knows who did it.
If he could remember.
So if the experiment went wrong,
and Werth's behavior over the past
several days would suggest it has,
then if he does remember...
He's in danger.
We need to protect him.
All that's standing
in our way is a senator
and the entire military medical complex.
I'm sure they'll be happy to see us.
Nothing, sir.
I'm losing you...
Sunspots, X-rays, tunnel.
Agent Gibbs, you and your team
are not welcome here.
You are not to interfere
with Corporal Werth's treatment.
I'll have you forcibly removed!
Sorry about that.
Clumsy.
- Not supposed to use in a hospital.
- Especially my hospital.
Corporal Werth is safe here.
Except perhaps from himself.
You'll excuse us if we don't take you
at your word.
Look, I'm taking every measure
to rectify past mistakes.
I'm ashamed to admit
I missed a diagnosis.
You verified Dr. Mallard's findings.
Werth is on a rapid detox program
which should flush his system
of the steroids in three to five days.
There a reason we had to do
all your work for you?
We try our best, but we can't keep up
with the numbers.
We don't have the time or the facilities
to extend that type of attention
to every patient who presents with PTSD.
I want to see him.
He's under heavy sedation.
He's fine.
No, she asked to see the patient.
Probably not a good idea
to stand in her way.
Geez.
What, no funny movie reference?
It's not funny.
The IV contains clonazepam
- while his system clears itself.
- Can he speak?
He's somewhat clear when he's awake.
Is his mind returning?
I hope so.
Corporal Werth?
Damon?
- Where am I?
- Hospital.
What's all this?
- We're getting the steroids out of you.
- Steroids?
You remember?
Who did this to you?
Who did this to me?
Damon?
- Hey, Damon?
- Like I said, he's very weak.
Damon!
Wait... this isn't right.
- What's happening?
- The system's crashing.
It's set too high.
- What is that?
- Adrenaline.
Hold him down!
Hold him! Hold him!
Give it to him.
You're gonna be all right, Marine.
- She's pulling a Pulp Fiction.
- On an Hulk.
- What just happened?
- I don't understand this.
His machine was cranked up
to the wrong level.
The sedative was poisoning him.
So you tried to kill him?
Bury the evidence
of your little science experiment?
I don't understand this...
I set the rate,
wrote the orders clear as day.
Who carries out your orders?
Jenkins!
Going down?
I said going down.
You should probably stay down.
That's a nice watch.
A little ostentatious for my tastes.
Must've been hell to pay for.
Especially on an orderly's salary.
Found a loophole in the system.
Doctors fill out orders.
You take the drugs from the pharmacy.
But occasionally, they don't make it
to their intended destination.
Yeah, you made quite a little business
out of that, haven't you?
What is the street value of...
Nandrolone,
and Oxymetholone and Winstrol?
You even know what these things do?
Liver, kidney disease,
sterility,
roid rage.
This guy here...
beat his wife half to death.
At least three others are dead.
They're all patients of yours.
They did that to themselves.
Werth goes off the reservation,
the cops are circling the hospital.
And then someone
amps his machine up to 11.
I don't know what happened, all right?
These things can be unreliable
sometimes.
Didn't want Werth to start talking about
who was sticking the needle in him?
Listen, I didn't stick the needle
in any of those guys.
Who did?
I'm embarrassed by my behavior.
It doesn't even feel
like me in my memory.
We have determined the source
of the steroids,
but not who did this to you.
You remember?
- It hasn't come back yet.
- Disappointing.
Would have to be someone close to you,
someone who has been with you
wherever you go.
- Perhaps someone in your unit.
- We have to investigate them.
Unless...
you remember who it is.
Courage doesn't have anything
to do with medals.
It's simple.
You run to the gunfire,
not away from it.
I don't know what I'd do, Gunny,
if I couldn't be a Marine.
It's in my blood.
I can't imagine how it felt.
When your own blood was keeping you out.
The orderly was just
your most recent supplier.
You gave yourself the steroids.
And the masking agents,
so no one would ever find out.
All so you could become some...
super-Marine.
Just a Marine.
That's it.
Ceremony's off.
- You're canceling it?
- Have to.
The senator can't step on stage
with that guy.
- He won't get the medal?
- That's up to the Marine Corps,
but I sincerely doubt it.
He'll be lucky to be just discharged.
This is a nightmare.
Ray Vincent.
When?
Great!
I'm on my way.
www.Team-NCIS.com