To everything, there is a season,
and a time to every purpose.
The world needs to know
about my findings,
that's all that's important!
It is one thing to publish a book
in the comfort of the university,
it is another to leave
everything behind,
chasing a theory that is pure fantasy!
The earth spins at 1,000 miles an hour
as we desperately try to keep
from being thrown off.
Like the first blush of winter
that signals a great migration.
Was there any warning of their arrival?
She has a name: Jessica.
A sign, a single event
that set this chain into motion?
This is what you've been waiting for.
Was it a whisper in God's ear?
Be the one we need.
Survive. Adapt.
Escape.
And if we could mark
that single moment in time,
that first hint of the prophecy
of approaching danger...
I found a tape of a conversation
my father had with a man named Sylar.
Hello, Chandra, you made me this way.
... would we have done anything
differently?
Could it have been stopped?
You helped me to discover
my potential.
Or was the die long ago cast?
And if we could go back,
alter its course,
stop it from happening... would we?
My name is Hiro Nakamura!
I'm here to save your life!
Hey, Charlie!
Charlie, come on over here,
and blow out the candles!
Hold that thought, okay?
I just gotta make a wish.
Come on.
Come on, honey!
Please, listen.
Very important.
Say: "cheese!"
Can I help you?
I hope so, Mr. Gray.
I can fix it.
My watch isn't broken.
Actually, it is.
Yeah, the self-winding coil is loose.
Your watch is running two seconds slow.
How did you know?
Just a talent I have for...
the way things work...
how the parts should go.
That looks rather complicated.
That... The body's standard,
but the parts, the insides, are German.
1917.
I've been working on it for seven years.
How much do I owe you?
Please.
Don't worry about it.
You didn't come here for the watch.
I came to find you, Gabriel.
My name is Chandra Suresh.
I'm a geneticist.
I have a theory about human evolution.
And I believe you...
are a part of it.
Read it.
If you'd like to talk more, I've written
my phone number and address inside.
License and registration.
Oh, this isn't my car, I kinda stole it.
Can you take off the glasses for me,
please?
I'm gonna have to ask you
to step out of the car.
No, I don't feel like it.
That wasn't a suggestion.
Well, here's a suggestion.
Why don't you go get back in your car,
and eat a dozen donuts.
That is what you cops like to do, right?
I said step out of the car. Now.
I think you really want to eat
some donuts.
Major developments!
Lori Trammel skanked
her way through the entire
football team!
Who told you that?
The entire football team.
Anyway, somehow she found shame
and resigned.
Turned in her pom-poms...
I'm in? Are you kidding?
Claire, destiny is calling you.
Come on, try it on.
You can model, I'll take pictures.
We'll totally commiserate the event.
I think you mean "commemorate."
And...I'll try it on later.
'Kay, most girls can't wait to get
their uniforms on. I mean,
except Lori Trammel.
She couldn't wait to take it off.
Why do you have to be like that?
Okay, first of all, I've earned that.
And if you don't want it or this,
Kristy Chan is salivating
for your position.
I want it, I do.
Then show it!
Show me some S.P.I.R.I.T!
I'm not gonna drool!
Then prove it, Claire!
Prove it!
Oh, my God.
What were you girls doing?
This is gonna need stitches.
I'm gonna take her
to the emergency room.
Jackie, honey, grab my purse. Let's go.
Come on, come on.
- Mr. Bennett?
- Yes.
My name is Chandra Suresh.
I need to speak to you
about your daughter Claire.
No, no.
I teleport from future.
Do not go to work tomorrow.
Very, very...
it wasn't raining yesterday.
April showers.
It's been storming all week.
April? No, no, October.
No, april 24th. It's my birthday.
Birthday cake?
Happy birthday.
Transcript: www.sadgeezer.com
Subtitles: www.sub-way.fr
Hi, my name is Niki.
And I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Niki.
I'm one year sober today.
Happy anniversary!
I work 60 hours a week.
I stink of cigarettes.
I got a kid so smart
that he is flunking out of school.
My husband can't find a job because
no one wants to hire an ex-con.
There's a leak in the roof.
And I'm feelin' thirsty.
Feels like too much for one person.
So why are you here?
I don't want another year to go by
without you in my life, Nicole.
Not being in your life
was never my choice.
You kinda made that happen.
Look, I know how you feel about me.
And Lord knows I deserve it.
I was awful to you,
and everyone I ever met.
You weren't awful,
you just weren't there.
You can't be awful
if you're not present.
You know, I'm married now.
I heard. Look, Nicole...
I would love to meet him some time.
I really want to get to know
my grandson and my son-in-law.
And you.
Yeah, well, I don't know
if I'm ready to get to know you.
Hey. What's going...?
Ladies, ten and a half.
You know, the reason I became a nurse
was to wear shoes like this,
- thank you very much.
- Of course.
- Get a drink?
- Yeah, it's right inside.
- I told him it wasn't funny.
- I know.
- Hey, mom.
- Hello, sweetheart.
- How are you? Come on in.
- I'm good.
Your father is very proud of you.
- And still couldn't make it.
- Well, he had a meeting.
Mr. Linderman's in Atlantic City...
Listen, I did this without his blessing,
and without his money.
Okay? So I think it's only right
that we celebrate without him.
I have always wanted a nurse
in the family.
- We have enough lawyers.
- Thanks, mom.
So, Peter, have you chosen a specialty?
I'm thinking of hospice care.
Taking care of dead people?
They're not dead.
They're dying.
And I think it's noble.
Thank you.
What's the pay?
Honey.
You know, I'm gonna go call the sitter,
and when I come back...
you are gonna dance with me.
What's going on?
The DA wants me to prosecute Linderman.
Dad's biggest client.
The DA thinks Linderman's
mob ties run so deep,
if I can take him down,
the empire crumbles.
You do that, though,
dad'll go down too.
You used to tell him
he was a criminal
for protecting criminals.
Here's a chance to set things straight.
Take the stink off the family na...
He's still our father.
No matter what he's done.
You go after him,
you're never going to forgive yourself.
Ever.
Come on, handsome.
- Hold this for me, will you?
- Yep.
May I?
So... what? You're gonna cut me open?
I'd like to run some tests.
EEG, EKG, nothing invasive.
A friend at Columbia
has access to an MRI.
Mapping the brain ?
Measuring alpha waves,
resting rates, neuron clusters.
The brain controls
every human action,
voluntary or involuntary.
Every breath, every heartbeat,
every emotion.
If the...
soul exists,
scientifically speaking,
it exists in the brain.
When I was a kid...
I used to wish some stranger
would come and tell me my family
wasn't really my family.
They weren't bad people,
they were just...
insignificant.
And I wanted to be different.
Special. I wanted to change.
A new name, a new life.
The watchmaker's son...
became a watchmaker.
It is so futile.
And I wanted to be...
important.
You are important, Gabriel.
What do you think my abilities might be?
Grand theft auto, larceny,
robbery, arson,
and suspected of murder in Oklahoma.
That's no way for a young lady
to behave, now is it?
You need a goal, Eden purpose.
Let me go.
Now!
You know, with your ability,
you can get anything you want.
Created your own morality.
There's no person in the world
that could say no to you.
Now there is.
Matt.
What are you doing?
What?
What are you doing sitting here?
Detective test is in an hour.
- Right.
- You're not chickening out, are you?
No, man, of course not.
All right, good, 'cause second time's
the charm for you, I can feel it.
Just don't go being a nervous wreck
this time, okay?
What's up with the donut?
You're like a walking cliche.
Yeah, well, you know what?
After today, I am gonna be
a different man.
Confidence! I like that.
Right? Let's go crush it.
Hello, what's up?
I don't know what we'd do
without you, Hiro.
Because, you have such
an amazing attitude.
I have gift for you.
Happy birthday.
A Japanese phrasebook.
I love it.
Oh, now we can understand
each other better.
Maybe you visit Japan.
Very soon.
Get out of Midland, far away.
You speak Japanese very quickly.
Lately, I've just been able
to remember everything.
You have power,
big memory.
It will only get stronger in the future.
The future. Right.
I keep forgetting
that's where you come from.
You don't believe me?
I bend time and space.
Yeah, of course you do.
Charlie, honey. Your order's up.
- Where'd these come from?
- Flower store,
two blocks from here.
Funny.
Hang on, I have an order up.
Already finished.
Lynette!
You have got to see this!
Hiro's a magician!
Oh, no,
it's not a trick.
A very, very bad man
is going to come here and...
tomorrow, the Swallow
will slay the Dragon.
Having a drink with your sister?
Thinking about it.
Used to be,
couldn't go an hour
without missing Jessica.
It's important not to forget.
Hal is back.
He came to one of my meetings.
He wants to meet you and Micah.
He won't meet anybody
unless you want him to.
He's got money.
He could...  he could help with tuition.
We can get Micah
into that private school.
Now, you wanna have Hal over,
let's have him over for dinner.
We can all say a prayer for Jessica.
My brother Peter, the hospice nurse.
Can you believe it?
It's a perfect fit.
He's selfless and empathic...
he's self-centered and righteous.
Self-righteous.
He's a hell of a lot nicer than you.
He can afford to be.
He hasn't been under as much scrutiny.
My dad did what he had to do
to take care of his family.
And that's something that Peter
is never gonna understand.
And you do.
It's my responsibility.
It's my inherited... birthright.
I didn't ask to be dad's favorite.
I never asked to be loved more
than Peter, but that's just...
the reality.
What does this guy want?
How is she?
She's been in surgery for ten hours.
It's something with her back, her spine.
I should probably call mom.
She's got the kids.
It's what Heidi would do.
You have your phone?
You're not hurt?
Landed 300 feet away from the wreck.
Couldn't tell you how I got there.
Couldn't tell you much of anything.
Let me see that, let me see.
Yeah, that's a bad cut.
You need to lie down.
No, not until Heidi's all right.
Won't get a signal.
Do you remember the other car?
- What?
- In the accident.
Who told you that?
I had a dream right before you called.
My wife's in surgery,
and you're dreaming.
That's great.
There was another car, wasn't there?
Wasn't there?
It was Linderman's guys.
Must've found out about the DA's plans.
It's my fault for even considering it.
Taking them on.
This is... this is not your fault.
This is dad's fault, okay?
And you know, you know
that this is not gonna end.
If...
if I agree to take the DA's case,
will you give a deposition?
Against your father?
- Mr. Petrelli?
- Yes?
Please.
They did it!
See, the Swallows slay the Dragons!
"The Tokyo Swallows defeated
the Chunichi Dragons yesterday
"with a surprising rally
with two out in the ninth."
What, what is this? Baseball?
You read Japanese flawless.
In one day.
You have power.
I have power too.
So because you knew
this baseball team was gonna win,
I'm supposed to believe
you're from the future.
There is an ancient Japanese tradition,
origami.
- Folding paper.
- I read about that.
Yeah, it says if a person can fold
1,000 cranes,
you'll be granted one wish.
Yes.
How did you...
A trip to Japan?
I don't care if you don't believe me.
Just...
please tell me you'll go.
Only one ticket?
Just in case you said yes.
Why do you repair watches, Gabriel?
My father didn't really gave me
a choice.
Yes, but why not do what you want
to do? Why not change?
You use a phrase in your book...
evolutionary had imperative.
That which we are destined to do.
Sea turtles die on the same exact beach
where they were born,
lions slaughter gazelles,
spiders eat their young.
They don't want to.
They have to.
Well...
the good news is you're healthy.
You mean normal?
What, there's still no signs?
Well, maybe tomorrow.
We're still going to the CT scan, right?
I think we should prepare
for the possibility
that I may have been wrong.
You may not have a special ability.
I am so close.
I can feel it.
You came to me!
I am on your list!
These tests aren't 100%.
Don't give up on me.
There are other opportunities
I need to focus on.
What... what, these people,
they're important? This guy?
Brian Davis,
you think he's... telekinetic?
Moves things with his mind,
or are you just gonna
toss him aside too?
You better leave now, Mr. Gray.
That's a very generous gift, Hal.
Oh, it's amortized over 10 birthdays.
Hell, then, you skimped.
Thanks, grandpa.
It's my pleasure, young man.
Now, go break the Internet
in half, or something.
If I could buy stock
in that kid right now...
I wish his teachers saw it that way.
We want to move him
into a private school,
it's just, you know, we're trying
to figure out the details.
Details?
If you're trying to ask me
for something,
it's already yours.
It's a man's god-give right
to dote on his grandson.
Thank you.
It'd make a really big difference
for us.
You know, I feel lucky
that you even let me through the door,
after all the things I've done.
Stop saying that.
You didn't do anything.
Why do you keep doing that?
Doing what?
You... you're only
as sick as your secrets, Nicole.
I know the mantras, Hal.
I've been reciting them for over a year.
Well, I guess I'll go see
what the boy's up to now.
You are doing great.
What the hell is this?
You've torn the whole damned
computer apart!
That computer cost $2,000!
What the hell you think you're doing?
You okay?
I have no business being here.
Then why did you bother?
I owe you more
than an apology could ever do.
- What am I supposed to do with this?
- I don't know.
Make your life easier,
I don't care how, okay?
What did you do that was so bad
I can't have my father back?
You really don't remember, do you?
So what's going to happen to my Claire?
How is this...
this genetic abnormality
going to effect her?
I don't know.
It's possible nothing might ever happen.
It's possible
I might be wrong.
Where did you find this picture?
Union Wells high school website.
She's growing up so quickly now.
I couldn't do anything to stop it.
You cannot,
try as you might.
You have a daughter?
How old is she?
She...was five.
I'm so sorry.
Mutations are
much like cancers or diseases,
meant to eliminate a species.
Shanti had a genetic anomaly,
and that was the portal
into my research.
My hope is that...
no one will suffer as she did.
If you do figure this out,
what happens then?
We can change the world.
Give people hope for the future.
That is your daughter's destiny.
I'd... very much like to meet her.
You can see how that might be a problem,
for my family?
Yes, of course.
Let me think on this
and the best way to proceed.
Well, I appreciate your coming,
Mr. Bennett.
It was educational.
You do remember.
How could I forget?
Nicole!
Not Niki.
It's me, daddy, Jessica.
The daughter
that you threw beer bottles at.
The daughter that you choked.
The daughter that you killed.
I didn't kill anyone!
No... it was an accident.
And they left Niki
with you to be your punching bag.
I came to apologize, Nicole.
Apologize?
You don't apologize to Nicole.
You apologize to me.
Niki doesn't remember.
But I do.
Someone had to be there to protect her.
I remember
the stink of alcohol on your breath.
I took every punch,
so that she wouldn't have to.
You are not Jessica.
You have no idea who I am.
You need help.
You're right, she does.
I thought she had learned
to protect herself,
but no such luck.
You're going to go away,
and never come back.
Cheerleading, huh?
- What do you think?
- I think I can't wait
to go to my first game.
Well,
you might be getting a little bit old
for the bears
from around the world, but...
- No, I'm not.
- No?
I love my bears.
Am I a terrible person?
What are you talking about?
I wanna be a cheerleader.
I mean, I've worked hard
to be a cheerleader, but...
sometimes, Jackie can just be a...
A bitch?
Yeah, a bitch.
No, it's your actions
that make you good or bad,
cheerleader or not.
Let's take a look at that hand.
The pain went away,
but I think it's still kinda...
That's healed really nicely.
Hey, baby.
You hungry?
Thought I'd make some eggs...
carbonara style.
Does that sound good?
I didn't pass again.
You studied so hard.
It's not about the answers, Jan.
I know all the answers.
I don't know
why you don't just tell them the truth.
Yeah, I'll just waltz in
and tell them I can barely read,
half the words I see backwards.
There's a good career move.
My baby.
Don't.
Come on.
A little morning sex,
some eggs...
everything's gonna seem so much better.
How can you wanna kiss me?
You're my hero.
You are everything that I want.
Hero.
I'm a hero.
Look at me.
11 years,
and I am still directing traffic.
I'm ready to give the deposition.
There isn't going to be one.
What are you talking about?
Can't back out now,
we gotta tell the DA everything.
About Linderman, about dad, all of it.
Dad's dead.
He had a heart attack this morning.
Take comfort
in the fact that he didn't know
his sons were about
to stab him in the back.
24-hour samurai film festival
at the drafthouse in Austin!
Austin?
That's over 300 miles away.
We can make it in time
to see Yujimbo,
Seven Samurai,
and The Hidden Fortress.
It'd be perfect for our trip to Japan!
You still do want to go?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
No, it's not that.
It's just... ever since I met you...
I don't know, you just,
you've made me so happy.
You make me happy too.
Well, it's more than that.
I don't let people get very close.
There's a blood clot in my brain...
inches away from an aneurysm.
I'm dying.
But...
I'm supposed to save you.
You did.
Before you got here,
I'd decided to give up.
But you have made me feel more alive,
and more full of joy
than I could have ever imagined.
Charlie?
Can I help you?
Yeah, somebody called me?
My name is Brian Davis.
Yes, I called you.
My name is...
My name is Sylar.
Gabriel Sylar.
It's incredible.
Can you make it go away?
Why would you wanna do that?
I don't know what this is.
Or who I might hurt.
I don't want it.
You're broken.
What?
Suresh was right. It's so clear now.
How it all works,
pieces fitting together.
It is in the brain.
So you can help.
Don't worry, Brian,
I can fix it.
It's an evolutionary imperative.
Whatever bad you've done in the past,
it's over.
You have a rare opportunity
to start again, to rewrite the past,
to do better.
But if you're not interested,
we could just...
put you back in your old life.
Odds are you'd be dead in a week.
What do you want me to do?
There's a professor.
Dr. Suresh.
He has a list of names.
You're going to get Claire Bennet's name
off that list.
I'm sorry about the glass.
It's just glass.
About the other day...
I should've behaved myself.
I was uncalled for,
- I'm sorry.
- You were angry.
A man can say and do
the most awful things when he's angry.
Well, I'm different now.
I feel I've been given a chance
to start over.
A new life, new identity.
New purpose.
I came halfway around the world
looking for proof,
I threw him out the door.
No one returns my phone calls anymore.
They all think I'm insane.
I don't.
These people
are all out there waiting to be told
that they are important.
Waiting to unlock their true potential.
I know it.
I can feel them.
We'll find them together.
We are the future.
This list...
You found them.
these people...
their future is written on their DNA.
Just as the past, it seems,
is written in stone.
I have something I have to tell you.
Was the die cast
from the very beginning?
Or is it in our own hands
to alter the course of destiny?
Of all our abilities,
it is free will
that truly makes us unique.
With it, we have a tiny,
but potent, chance to deny fate.
And only with it
can we find our way back
to being human.
I loved her.
www.sub-way.fr