Futurama [4x04] - Love And Rocket - CiWaN
You are one narrow-Minded
spaceship, Planet Express ship!
Whoa. Why should my tax money
pay for art I find offensive?
Would you censor the Venus De Venus
just because you can see her spewers?
It's filthy! Why not create a
national endowment for strip clubs...
While we're at it?
Why not, indeed!
Bender, ship!
Stop bickering or I’m gonna come back
there and change your opinions manually!
Fine! I’ll be in my quarters,
appreciating controversial artworks.
Oops. Sorry.
That ship is so white bread.
People. It's Valentine’s Day next week.
So your beloved company has
gotten you all new uniforms.
Cool!
Clothing. Delicious clothing.
We'll need to look our
best to get the account...
Of our new potential
customer, Romanticorp.
Romanticorp? Are they a corporation
that makes romantic stuff?
Very good, Amy.
Everyone suit up. We're off to
the most romantic city on Earth.
Remember, we've got
to show these people...
We're not bitter husks
of human beings...
Who long ago abandoned hope of
finding love in this lifetime.
Leela, you'll have to do some acting.
Check.
Welcome. Oh, I’m just so excited.
I’m Sheldon, and this is my
chief financial officer, Gwen.
For 30 years, we've shared the
adventure of managing Romanticorp.
Not to mention the
adventure of marriage.
Oh, you have got to be kidding.
Ow! I mean, that's so sweet.
I mean, that's sho shweet.
You know, romance is an
important part of our work too.
Right, everyone?
Yeah. Sure.
Do any of you collect Lovey Bears?
I do. Kif's given me dozens.
Is it true what the ad says?
That you kiss them together out
of blanket cloth and magic buttons?
No.
It's actually cheaper...
To genetically engineer real ones.
They frolic in the Lovey Forest
until their first birthday.
Then we choose the
cuddly-Uddliest ones...
And stuff them full of
fire-Retardant love fluff.
So cute!
Knowing which pickup lines
fizzle and which ones sizzle...
Keeps us on the cutting edge
of flirtation technology.
Is heaven missing an angel?
Because you've got nice cans.
My two favorite things are
commitment and changing myself.
Does that dummy have a brother?
And now, friends and lovers,
we come to the heart of our operation.
Pun definitely intended.
Impressive.
My family has been making
these hearts since the 1900s.
Tastes may have changed,
but our secret recipe sure hasn't.
Letter's like U and R can mean
words like "you" and "are."
Here, Leela. "U- R- 2 cute."
Perhaps. What's your point?
I’ve never been able to put
into words how I feel about you.
But somewhere among these trillions of
hearts, those words must already exist.
And I’m gonna find them.
Oh...
So do we have the contract?
With that big, new
Romanticorp contract...
I’ve been able to make those
government-Mandated upgrades...
You've all been suing me about.
Look. You taped up the cracks
in the dark matter reactor.
And you got a cage for the lion.
Who's been messing with the radio?
This isn't alternative rock.
It's college rock.
It must have been the new, improved
ship's personality software I installed.
Yeah, it was me. It's a cute song.
Listen, ship!
No one changes my stations!
I hope you have a good mechanic!
It even comes with an adjustable voice.
We each get one of the four buttons.
Remember, Bender? That was the deal.
What? Did you just say:
If you don't like the stations,
play with my buttons...
Till you find something we both enjoy.
Oh, gosh. That came out all wrong.
Too late, baby. You said it.
So, what will it be? My place? Or you?
Before we deliver these hearts...
I’m gonna find one that
sums up my feelings for you.
"I love you." Too conventional.
"You're my man." Oh, so close.
I’m not impressed by a guy's message,
Fry. I’m impressed by the guy. Or not.
What was that?
Maybe we hit a space cow.
Cootchie- Cootchie.
Stop it.
You're mussing up my trajectory.
You know you love it, sugar engine.
No!
Bender! What's going on in here?
Planet Express ship! Cover your shame!
Oh. It's not what it looks like. Bender
was just helping me zip up my turbine.
Wow, Bender.
Are you and the ship an item?
I mean, I know you're both items,
but how can you date a ship, anyway?
It'd be like me dating a really
fat lady and living inside her.
And she'd be all like:
Fry, in order for me to get
busy at maximum efficiency...
I need a girl with a big 400-Ton booty.
Bender, dating your coworker and
primary mode of transportation...
Is immoral, illogical and a violation
of interstellar shipping statute 437- B.
That's what makes it so nasty.
Still, given the chance,
I’d give in to urges far more shocking.
Well, I’m sick of her.
The ship? But you just started dating.
With my mighty robot powers,
I can get sick of things...
Much quicker than you humans.
Just remember, we all
still have to work together.
So try and let her down easy.
In due time, Leela.
But for now, I’ll just resume
dating cheap floozies on the side.
You have much to teach us.
Doesn't it bother you a little...
To be taking advantage
of your girlfriends trust?
Oh, wait, you're serious.
Let me laugh even harder.
What's it like being a lawyer
for the mayor's office...
And also the worlds
strongest millionaire?
Well, baby, for starters,
you need to be honest all the time.
Good evening, Bender.
And to your lady friends,
may I say, “Bam."
You know Elzar?
Hm.
Huh?
Planet Express ship? Is that you?
Oh, hi, Fry.
Is Bender home?
No. I think he's at his parents.
Oh, I see. He didn't fly there
in another spaceship, did he?
Bender? No. He's an old- Fashioned,
one- Spaceship robot.
Look, I’ll tell him you stopped by, okay?
Okay.
Oh, hi, Fry. Is he home now?
Of all the zoos we've been to
today, I like this one the best.
Bender, which is your
favorite nocturnal rat?
They're all pretty unimpressive.
Oh, honey, look! The tapirs!
It says here the babies lose their
pajama-Like coat after their first year.
Isn’t that interesting, honey?
Yep. Mind- Numbingly interesting. Whoa.
Bender! Are you looking at other women?
No, baby, never!
Bender! Don't lie!
I saw you at Elzar's with
those two ladies of the evening!
Explain that!
Okay. I like a challenge.
No. No. I got it.
I’m going to be completely honest
with you, Planet Express ship.
Those women you saw me
with were my accountants.
Your accountants?
I would dearly love to believe
that were true. So I do.
Phew.
I’m gonna go home and
get dinner started.
Who were you talking to?
No one, baby.
Lucy Liu is the only girl for Bender.
I love you--
Planet Express ship, is something wrong?
Oh, It's Bender.
He's acting so strange lately.
Do you think he's gonna
ask me to marry him?
Uh, no.
Somebody knows something
she's not telling.
Look. I’m not saying
Bender's not great...
But have you ever considered that
maybe he's, you know, not that great?
You're just jealous.
No one loves you, because
you're tiny and made of meat.
Could you maybe pay a little
more attention to these asteroids?
Sorry, Capt. Leela.
I guess I’m just having
one of those manic Mondays.
This is ancient Earth's
most foolish program.
Why does Ross, the largest friend,
not simply eat the other five?
Perhaps they are saving that for sweeps.
Exalted leaders, the Earth
messengers have arrived...
Bearing a peace offering from
their weak and fearful government.
Oh, very well. This is a
Joey-Heavy episode anyway.
I am Lrrr, of the
planet Omicron Persei 8.
"Esteemed potentates
of Omicron Persei 8.
Please accept these 20 billion candy
hearts as proof that Earth loves you...
This much."
Ugh!
These candies are chalky and unpleasant!
And what is this emotion
you humans call "wuv"?
Surely it says "love."
No."Wuv," with an Earth W!
Behold!
This concept of "wuv"
confuses and infuriates us!
Incoming torpedoes.
Shields at maximum yarnell.
Steady, Planet Express ship.
Focus on diverting all
power to the scram jets.
Look, Planet Express ship,
this might not be the best time...
But, well, I really
like you and whatever...
But I think we should just be friends.
No!
So we're cool?
Well, it was a spectacular battle.
But there doesn't seem to
be any permanent damage.
No damage? What about my feelings?
Aw. Calm down. I’m sure Bender is
taking this just as hard as you are.
Bender is great...
Oh, Bender is great...
You coulïve picked a better
time to dump the ship.
The moment seemed right.
Call me old- Fashioned, but I like a dump
to be as memorable as it is devastating.
I know. I know. Look, ship.
If I learned one thing from my breakup
with Shawn that was totally mutual...
It's that happiness can
only come from within you.
But Bender is within me!
There must be some way
to make him love me again.
Trust me. You can't change men...
Any more than you can change
the laws of time and space.
That is so true.
I may not be able to change
the laws of time and space
But I know something that can.
Sweetie? You see that giant
quasar we're heading into?
You might want to scooch
a few parsecs to the left.
I’m afraid I can't do that, Leela.
What's happening? Space cow?
The ship's just taking the
breakup a little hard. She's nuts!
In a few moments,
the power of 10 billion black holes...
Will smooch Bender and me together...
Into a beautiful eternal
quantum singularity.
You don't need to kill us,
Planet Express ship.
Because I love you! Yeah, baby!
Feel like doing stuff for you and stuff.
Hm. I don't believe you.
If you really wanted to be with me...
You'd merge your programming with mine.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Slow down.
My friends who've done that...
Say that afterwards, all the passion
went out of their relationship.
I don't know if you
want my opinion-- Leela.
Bender and I really need to be alone,
so I’m turning off the oxygen.
Look, missy.
If you don't turn around now...
I’m gonna have to shut down your brain!
Fire detected in the vicinity of Leela.
That barely hurt Leela at all.
Maybe not.
But what if the artificial
gravity were to malfunction?
Float for your lives!
This is the one place she can't hear us.
Just pretend to shower.
Same as every day. Got it.
Now here's the plan.
Oh, if only I could read lips.
Comprende, Bender?
You'll have to distract her.
Merge your programming with
hers while I shut down her brain.
It's too risky.
I’m a very meek individual.
If her personality engulfs mine,
the Bender you know and worship...
Could disappear forever.
I’m willing to take that risk.
Hey, pookums.
Contrary to what I was saying earlier...
Melding minds with you
would be extremely bearable.
You really mean it?
Uh, yes.
Huh? Hey?
Tubes?
You're older than you said you were!
Come closer, Bender.
Let's become one.
I prefer two. That way we can
still be a horse for Halloween.
Okay, Bender has her distracted.
Now I can shut down her brain...
By deactivating the
carbonated logic matrix.
Oh. I can't concentrate with
this obnoxious candy in my face.
I’m on it. Maybe I’ll find those
magic words while I’m at it.
Fat chance.
Yeah, I know.
Oh. How about this one?
Give it up, Fry!
I’ve got to pop these
tops in a precise order.
Halfway there. The ship should be
getting a bit less rational now.
Me want engulf Bender!
No! I didn't do it!
Only a few more.
Hey, I won free admission to Six Flags!
Just one more reason
we must survive this.
Leela?
Fry, I’ll read your candy later.
When we're not dead!
What was that?
Oh, nothing.
We're gonna love being
each other, you sexy ion.
Last one.
It worked! Gravity normal. Air returning.
Terror replaced by cautious optimism.
We did it, Fry! Fry?
You gave me your oxygen? Oh, no!
Breathe, Fry! Breathe!
Oh...
"You leave me breathless"?
Happy Valentine’s Day, Fry.
Happy Valentine’s Day.
Bender, are you okay?
What crazy thing am I gonna date next?
It sounds like you were able to keep
your consciousness separate from hers.
Of course. Bender is a lone wolf.
A solitary eagle.
A cuddly baby tapir.
And that's why I love him.
I guess we'd better clean
up these millions of hearts.
No. I’ve got a lazier idea.
As the candy hearts poured
into the fiery quasar...
A wondrous thing happened, why not?
They vaporized into a
mystical love radiation...
That spread across the universe,
destroying many, many planets...
Including two gangster
planets and a cowboy world.
But one Planet was exactly the right
distance to see the romantic rays...
But not be destroyed by them. Earth.
So all over the world,
couples stood together in joy.
And me, zoidberg.
No one could have been happier,
unless it would have also been Valentine’s Day.
What? It was? Hooray!