Marie!
No! Please!
[ Shrieking ]
Oh, God!
[ Crying ]
[ Scully ]
Mulder was dying...
It's all right here.
For a year he was going
to doctors.
There's a clear record
of his decline.
[ Doggett ]
How well did you really know him?
Howfar would Mulder go?
How far would he go for what?
The truth... his truth.
Whatever you and I may
differ on...
I'll fiind him, Agent Scully.
You must be
Special Agent Doggett.
I'm Sheriff Frey.
Just call me Kurt.
I appreciate
the help, Kurt.
Shame to have
you drive
all the way up here
on a Saturday.
Hate to say you're
wasting your time.
Not if you confiirm
what you told me before.
Yes, sir. Agent Mulder
was here, all right...
last spring.
You said on the phone
Agent Mulder was investigating
a missing woman,
Marie Hangemuhl.
Well, she wasn't
exactly missing.
He wasn't exactly
investigating, either.
I'm not following you.
It was a false report.
Marie never even
left the house.
The only reason Agent Mulder
found out about it was
because Marie's sister got
all excited about nothing.
There.
See for yourself.
Say, I've got some hot coffee
and a Danish here
if you're interested.
No, thanks.
You know, if you don't mind me asking,
Agent Doggett
what's your interest?
I mean, I was
actually surprised
that one FBI agent gave
this case a thought.
It's not so much the case
as it is the agent.
Agent Mulder disappeared
last May.
Sorry to hear that.
I still don't see what
that has to do with us.
Did Agent Mulder have
a personal connection here--
something that might not be
in your report?
No, I don't think
he'd ever been to Squamash
before, as far as I know.
I have cell phone records
showing that
Agent Mulder came back here
the week before he disappeared.
What for?
That's what I want to know.
It's my job to fiind him.
[ Knocking On Door ]
Kurt?
Paul, this is Agent Doggett
from the FBI.
He'd like to ask you and Marie
some questions.
Marie, can you come out here
a minute?
This is an FBI agent.
He wants to ask us
a few questions.
What's this all about?
A colleague of mine, Fox Mulder,
questioned you last spring.
Come on, Kurt.
This again?
Look, this was a personal matter
that's been blown
way out of proportion.
He's not
investigating you, Paul.
He's investigating Agent Mulder.
If you could tell me what you
and Agent Mulder talked about.
You told your sister
you were going to disappear,
Mrs. Hangemuhl. Tonight.
[ Paul ]
I told you already.
We had a fiight, she was going
to leave, not disappear.
I'm talking to your wife.
Mrs. Hangemuhl.
It's what he said.
My sister lives
out of state.
I was going to go...
I didn't want
her to worry.
You told your sister a story,
a story you were afraid of?
This is crazy.
There is no crime here!
I don't think you
were going
anywhere tonight
Mrs. Hangemuhl.
I think someone or something was
coming here.
And I think maybe it still is.
We had a fiight.
We patched things up
and that was the end of it.
The sheriff s report says
thatAgent Mulder
spoke to you
on Saturday, May 6th.
Yeah, I-I guess so.
Did you see Agent Mulder
again that night?
No, he never came back.
According to his cell phone
records, he did.
To this area, anyway.
What's that there?
Is that
a dialysis machine?
My wife suffers from end-stage
renal failure.
She's a very sick woman.
Anything else?
One thing.
This someone or something Agent
Mulder said might be coming?
I just told my sister I was
afraid of the stories.
That's all, I didn't mean...
Let me ask you something,
Agent Doggett.
Was this Mulder guy sick?
Sick in the head,
I mean?
Is that why you're checking
into this?
What stories, Mr. Hangemuhl?
An Indian folk legend
about a creature who lives
out in the woods.
I've heard these stories
since I was a kid.
So your colleague
twisted it
into a theory that she was going
to disappear, all right
'cause this creature was
coming to eat her.
Eat her?
Alive.
Like I said,
Agent Doggett
I hate to waste
your Saturday.
The Hangemuhls own
a gun, Kurt?
No, I don't think so. Why?
I saw three holes
plastered over
in their living room wall.
Gunshots?
Possibly.
You want to go back
and ask'em?
No.
Kurt, they told me
you were out here.
I just can't believe it.
Is it true?
That's what
I'm here to fiind out.
Were you aware Mulder carried
a second weapon, a Walther PPK?
Yeah, in an
ankle holster.
I found it hidden
under his sink.
The clip was three rounds shy.
What's this about?
Three shots
were fiired in a house
where Mulder investigated
a case last May.
He never fiiled
a report on the case
or the discharge
of his weapon.
Do you know any reason why?
If Mulder did these things,
he would've reported them.
Mulder submitted
case reports, all right
but they indicate
he was here in Washington
on days his cell phone records
prove he was in Pennsylvania.
Are you calling Mulder a liar?
This is the muzzle
of Mulder's pistol.
You see that there?
It's blowback.
Macrospatter
of dried blood
in a semi-circular pattern.
Which indicates Mulder fiired
close-range at something
or someone.
I've heard enough.
Where are you going?
It's where
you're going, Agent Doggett.
You're trying to
build a case that what?
Mulder killed a man and then
made himself disappear?
That's not what happened.
I told you before, he
was abducted. I saw it!
Agent Mulder signed
falsifiied case reports.
Oh, come on,John, this isn't
about Mulder, it's about you!
Your career.
You give the FBI a narrative
for Mulder's disappearance,
you're off the X-Files
and back on the fast-track
to the directorship.
I'm just trying
to fiind the truth.
You want the truth?
AskAgent Scully!
I can't do that.
Why not?
Because she...
She signed those
case reports, too.
You take that story to OPR
the accusation alone
could cost Scully her job.
I'm not taking it to OPR.
I'm taking it to you.
[ Barking ]
Hold back.
We're giving you two minutes
to bring it outside!
Then we're coming
in to get it!
Where is it?
It's dead.
You know that.
Dead and buried.
It's here.
We've come for it.
You lied to us!
[ Rustling ]
[ Moaning ]
Please, don't!
Don't do this!
Don't do this to him!
Sheriff Frey.
Back again?
This is Assistant
Director Skinner.
We drove up when we couldn't
reach you on the phone.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I went hunting
and turned off my radio.
So.
You fiind something?
You might say that.
You fiiled this
death certifiicate
at the county
seat, Sheriff.
We're hoping you
might be able
to tell us something about it.
Yeah. Yeah, last spring.
An unidentifiied transient.
Local woman found the body
in the woods.
You got no
suspects?
No motive?
No, why?
You get a lot
of shootings around here?
That why you failed
to mention this one, Kurt?
What are you insinuating?
The body was found dumped
outside this woman's cabin
on Sunday, May 7--
the morning after Mulder
saw the Hangemuhls.
Okay, so I didn't make
the connection. So what?
Three rounds were missing
from Mulder's weapon.
So Mulder came back
to town to kill this man
and now the Hangemuhls
are lying about it.
Maybe I am, too.
Pretty much.
This theory is even nuttier
than the one Agent Mulder
came to town with.
Where's the evidence?
Where's the body buried?
You're on pretty shaky ground
here, Agent Doggett.
Something happened
here that night.
But you're forgetting
one thing--
Fox Mulder
wouldn't do this.
Look, somebody
shot this man.
Somebody fiired
Mulder's weapon
and Mulder was
here that night.
And you trying to prove
that Mulder's a murderer
is going to help
you fiind him?
Maybe he's not.
I'm not saying that
he did this. Not yet.
But he was here
for a reason
and then he
disappeared.
Why would these people,
people he'd never met before
try to cover it up?
That's the question, yeah.
Earth is fresh.
Sheriff must've dug it up
this afternoon after I left.
What would he want
with the body?
I don't know that he found it.
Looks like there's
another way out.
Are you telling me
the man inside that
casket did this?
Looks pretty deep.
A man doesn't
get shot three times
and then tunnel out
of his own grave.
The sheriff said this transient
was unidentifiied, right?
That's right.
Then why'd somebody leave
these on top of his grave?
[ Car Approaching ]
[ Car Door Opening ]
We've got to move fast.
She's not ready yet.
Then she better get ready.
I can't do this.
You've got to do this.
We don't have
another choice.
Paul?
Marie.
[ Car Approaching ]
[ Ragged Breathing ]
I'll be waiting for you.
[ Gun Cocking ]
[ Low Growling ]
No!
[ Moans Softly ]
[ Moans ]
[ Screaming ]
Our Father,
who art in heaven...
Hallowed be thy name...
[ Screaming ]
What is it now?
Mind if we
come in?
What do you
think you're doing?
Looking for
the sheriff.
He was here,
wasn't he?
Look, I've had a long day
and I want to go to bed,
so if you don't mind...
Agent Mulder
came back here that night
and shot a man
in this room.
You know why,
and so does your wife.
I want you guys out
of my house, now.
Hey, did you
hear me?!
Mr. Hangemuhl, we'd like
to speak with your wife.
Where is she?
Where is she, Mr. Hangemuhl?
Something happened here
and I'm going
to fiigure out what it is.
Agent Doggett.
Looks like
you missed a spot,
Mr. Hangemuhl.
[ Echoing Screams ]
[ Gagging, Choking ]
[ Screams And Moans ]
[ Groans And Vomiting ]
[Three Gunshots ]
[ Skinner ]
Agent Doggett.
Hangemuhl says his wife
must've coughed up the blood.
He insists he didn't harm her.
Of course he says that.
Maybe he didn't.
What are you talking about?
You said it before
Mulder wouldn't do this--
shoot a man in cold blood.
Unless he was trying
to protect Mrs. Hangemuhl.
From who?
From the man that's supposed
to be buried in that coffiin.
The county police found
something you ought to look at.
Mr. Hangemuhl must've just
used water to clean this.
Thank you.
Otherwise...
we might not
have found it.
Look familiar?
We learned
what we could.
This is somewhat short
notice, of course.
[ Frohike ] And a little outside
our area of expertise.
Plus the fact we were sleeping.
You wearing pants, Langly?
Uh...yeah.
We don't have much time.
What did you fiind?
Thought you'd never ask,
big guy.
The pattern you
described to us
is most likely
a medicine wheel.
It's a symbol for healing
usually associated with
North American shaman.
Now, the circle
represents the continuum
between life and death.
The journey is separated
by two roads
one for happiness
one for sorrow.
Lakota Indians teach that
all these elements--
life, death,
sorrow, happiness--
are all one.
But it takes an enlightened mind
to see it.
Why paint it on a door,
or mark it on a grave?
[ Langly ]
Well--
that's the part that takes
some conjecture there,
Agent Dogbird.
We don't know what Mulder
was doing out there.
But legends date back hundreds
of years of a sin-catcher shaman
also known as a soul eater.
A soul eater?
[ Langly ]
They minister to the sick--
legend has it
they consume their illnesses.
The symbol might
be placed on a grave
as a sign of respect.
Or on a door as a summons.
A summons for what?
To indicate a sick person
lives there
someone in need of
the creature's healing gift.
Thanks for your help, boys.
[ Sarcastically ]
Yeah, you're welcome.
Marie Hangemuhl
suffered from a kidney disease.
Agent Doggett?
That wasn't a transient
buried in that grave.
Sorry to disturb you
at this hour, ma'am.
I'm Agent Doggett with the FBI.
May I come in?
The sheriff s
report last May
said you found a body
in the woods out here.
Look, the people of this town
are keeping a secret
about that body--
about who it is.
There was an FBI agent
who came here
because he believed
that it was some kind of
a ""soul eater.''
Maybe it is.
You believe it, too.
You put those stones
on top of his grave.
The things you're asking about--
they've been this way
for hundreds of years.
You can't change them.
A colleague of mine came here
to try and kill this thing
last spring.
I believe he was trying
to protect a woman
named Marie Hangemuhl.
I need your help.
You've got it all backward.
[Thumping ]
I'm going to get you
out of here.
Agent Doggett.
How is she?
She feels fiine,
you believe that?
The doctor says
Mrs. Hangemuhl's kidneys
have spontaneously healed.
She's a healthy woman.
Explain that.
You're going to
have to explain it.
The sheriff s waiting
to take your statement.
The sheriff knows.
He's known all along.
So's her husband.
Known what?
That this soul eater
took her to cure her.
I thought Mulder shot this man
to protect Marie Hangemuhl.
But it wasn't her
he was trying to protect.
Where are you going?
Something happened here.
It just wasn't what we thought.
To understand
what this thing is
you have to understand
what it can do--
its gift.
People hate it
because they need it.
It looks the way it does
because of their sickness.
You care for this man.
Someone always has.
Because you believe it?
That it can
cure people's sickness?
Not cure.
Consume.
Mulder came to see you
last year.
Not to save Marie Hangemuhl.
To save himself.
Mulder was dying,
but he kept it a secret.
He had an undiagnosed
brain disease.
He was a sick man,
desperate to fiind a cure.
They all are.
[ Gasping ]
Mulder didn't do it.
Agent Mulder
saw how it suffered.
He saw it in its eyes.
I knew what needed
to be done.
I just couldn't bring
myself to do it.
Mulder killed it.
He couldn't bear
to add to its pain.
So he came back
here that night
to take its pain away.
They buried it.
It wanted to die.
It still does, but it can't.
All these months
I've kept it here
in secret.
But now that they
know it's back
it'll keep suffering.
[Whimpering Softly ]
Sheriff, as
a federal offiicer
I'm asking you
and your men
to get out of my way.
You can't take it,
Agent Doggett.
It belongs to us.
This is a man.
He doesn't belong
to anybody.
We have sick people.
Sick people who need
what it has.
We're taking it.
You're free to go.
No, sir.
I'm driving
this man out of here.
[ Gunshot ]
[Woman Screams ]
[ Man ]
Sheriff.
It'll come back.
It always does.
[Woman ]
All these years
we didn't know
what it could do.
It took your death.
You freed it.
A.D. Skinner,
you're here late.
So are you.
I wanted to fiinish
my case report
before Agent Scully
comes in tomorrow morning.
Have you?
I don't even know
where to begin
or how to explain it.
Only thing I do know is
is I'm no closer
to fiinding Mulder now
than when I started
this thing.
You got inside of his head,
Agent Doggett.
You understood why Mulder
did something
I wouldn't have thought
him capable of doing.
You want some free advice?
Don't write that report.
You turn that in
you open up a world
of trouble for Agent Scully.
And yourself.
She didn't know anything
about this, sir.
Of that I'm certain.
How many months
will be lost proving that?
How much damage done
to her good name?
And Mulder's?
And to yours?
For what?
The truth.
You and I both know
what happened
out there, Agent Doggett.
No one else needs to.
[ Child ]
I made this.