It is Friday, December 8...
and you're tuned in to WXOP,
Baltimore's news radio...
serving all of Maryland...
and the greater
Chesapeake region, 2 4-7.
We've got your Friday morning
trouble spots:
a two-car pileup with
a fatality, on the 97 at...
[ Buzzer]
It's time.
John!
Press got word
you're taking him...
out the Groves
Street exit.
It looks like
Woodstock out there.
I suggest you
postpone the transfer.
We can get him out later
once the crowd disperses.
Transfer me where?
No, they'll
camp out for days.
We're going ahead with it.
John.
John,
what is going on?
Mr. Wells! Mr. Wells!
Why did you do it?
All right, back up!
Give him some room.
Come on, clear out.
Back up.
Al.
Down!
Weapon!
[ Yelling ]
[ Voice Echoing ]
Somebody call a medic!
[ Heartbeat ]
[ Heartbeat Slowing ]
[ Heartbeat Stops ]
[ Buzzer]
John...
Do you recognize
this, Mr. Wells?
Have you
seen it before?
Um... yes. Who are you?
Don't even...
- Martin.
-John, what am I doing here?
I'm in this cell,
I don't know where I am...
or how I even got here...
and everyone's acting like...
Swear to God,
on top of everything else,
do not play this with me.
I will not be party...
to some half-assed,
1 1 th-hour insanity defense.
What? John...
It's time to start
telling me the truth!
This key card, Mr. Wells...
You do recognize it.
Is that correct?
Yes, it's the swipe card...
that they use
at the apartment building.
For all I know, it's mine.
It is yours.
It was found in the dumpster
behind the Strand Hotel.
You tossed it there,
didn't you?
You had just enough time...
to drive to Baltimore
and commit the murder.
Wait. Murder? What murder?
Then drive back to D.C.
toss the key card.
That way, you could
claim it was stolen.
Make it look like
you spent your whole night...
watching pay-per-view
in your hotel room.
Right?
Please...
What murder?
What is he talking about?
Well, maybe this will
jog your memory, buddy.
Vickie.
My wife.
This isn't happening.
This is not happening.
Court van is waiting.
All right... dignity.
That is your strong suit.
Play it.
Don't lower your eyes.
It makes you look guilty.
Now, we drew Judge Kinberg.
What's your relationship
with him?
Benjamin?
First-name basis.
Excellent.
[ Bailiff]
All rise.
I would remind the
members of the gallery...
to turn off all cellular phones
and paging devices.
Al?
What?
He shot me.
Who?
Your father-in-law?
What are you
talking about?
Circuit Court, Department 6-B
is now in session...
the Honorable
Benjamin Kinberg presiding.
Thursday,
the seventh day of December.
Thursday?
It's not Thursday.
Shh!
It's Saturday.
Yesterday was Friday and...
Today is Thursday.
There's no court
on Saturday.
You know that.
Martin, do you feel all right?
[Judge Pounds Gavel ]
Case Number 8ABX03:
District v. Martin Wells.
Charge of
first-degree murder.
The defense has requested
a hearing on bail?
Yes, Your Honor, we have.
As I'm sure you'd agree,
Mr. Wells' status...
as a prosecutor
makes him a target.
The court puts
his life in danger...
by keeping him
in custody.
Your Honor,
I have the assurances...
of the Baltimore
Department of Corrections...
that Mr. Wells' safety while
in custody is not a concern.
Furthermore, as Your Honor
will certainly agree...
Mr. Wells is an upstanding...
citizen and a respected member
of the Maryland Bar...
held in high esteem
by all his peers.
Your Honor, with cold
calculation, Martin Wells...
brutally stabbed his wife
in their own home.
He poses a threat to the public
and should be denied bail.
He doesn't pose a threat
to anyone, Your Honor...
and he has two small children...
who need him at home.
Why?
Because their mom's not around.
Ms. Carter.
Martin, I can't tell
you how sorry I am...
to see you on that
side of the aisle.
I hope you'll forgive me
when I do exactly what you...
as a prosecutor, would demand.
Bail is denied.
I will, however...
order Mr. Wells transferred
to a more secure...
facility in the interest
of his safety.
Transferred?
No, Ben.
You can't do that.
I can't be transferred.
He'll kill me.
Tomorrow morning--
if today
is really Thursday--
then tomorrow is Friday...
and that's
when he's going to do it.
He's going to shoot me
as I'm being transferred.
Bailiff.
You don't understand!
It'll happen!
Judge, listen to me!
Ben, it'll happen!
He's going to kill me! Ben!
Mr. Wells...
we understand that you had
an interesting morning in court.
What is it that you'd like
to speak with us about?
You'reJohn's partner?
For God sakes,
Martin.
Agent Scully. You know that.
You met her yesterday.
Yesterday?
Yeah. Yesterday.
Wednesday.
Wednesday?
Are you saying
that you don't remember?
What is the last thing
that you do remember?
Being shot by my father-in-law.
You're wasting our time.
Listen.
I don't know
what I experienced.
But what if
it was a premonition?
A glimpse of the future.
I mean, you do hear
about these kind of things.
Yes... you do.
Mr. Wells,
this shooting aside...
is there anything else
that you remember before that?
Um... I was in D.C...
uh... for a sentencing hearing.
I was staying at
the Strand Hotel like you said.
That was three days ago,
Mr. Wells.
Are you telling us that...
you don't remember
anything else?
Not the murder of your wife?
No.
Out of the blue.
Charged with murder.
You wake up one morning...
and you can't
remember a damn thing.
Martin, you
haven't offered us...
one scrap of evidence
to support your story.
Now, as your friend,
I'm going to listen...
to anything you have to say,
but I will not be lied to.
I'm not lying to you.
You're talking to me
about key cards.
I'm sitting in a jail cell.
I don't understand any of this.
But I did not...
kill Vickie.
If you truly don't remember...
then how can you be certain
that you didn't?
Courtney! Haley!
Hey, guys!
Oh!
It's so good to see you.
Wh...?! Come on!
Come on, give Daddy a big hug.
Hug your father, ninas.
Mmm...
How are they holding up?
Good. Good, Mr. Wells.
They want to know
when you're coming home.
Oh. See, um...
Daddy has some things
that he has to do--
very, very
important things.
That's why I have
to be here...
right now, but then,
guess what?
I'll be coming home.
Grandpa says they won't
let you come home.
Oh...
[ Gasps ]
Trina, I need you to get me
something out of the apartment--
something from the girls' room.
Thank you.
Why didn't you mention this
to me before the bail hearing?
I hadn't even met you
before the bail hearing.
Nanny-cam.
Oh, Martin, I wish you'd talked
to me about this before.
I really don't know
if this is a great idea.
This tape may have
the murderer on it.
Whatever happens to be
on that tape...
you know that I
am an officer of the court.
I have to share this
with the prosecution.
You think I'm guilty?
Let's... let's clear
this up right now.
Here.
My apartment.
That... that's the girls' room...
and this must be
the police investigation.
What time did
the murder occur?
The official report
has the police arriving...
at your apartment at
6:20 a.m. Monday morning.
Your key card
was used at 4:1 7.
Which means the killer
is somewhere in-between.
Wait.
There's your wife.
Um... we must
have missed something.
Right there.
Martin, that's you.
[ Door Buzzes ]
I'm not going.
How's that?
I told you. This is the day.
If I go, I'll get shot.
You cannot transfer me.
I don't plan to.
Your lawyers want to see you.
[ Whispers ]
There's my favorite client.
Martin, you holding up
all right?
Brent, uh...
I've been better.
We're going to beat this thing.
Guaranteed.
Martin, I have here
one of the finest...
criminal defense
specialists in the country.
I want you to meet...
We met. I've been thinking
all night about the tape...
and I don't see you having to
turn it over to the prosecution.
I'm sorry?
I obviously showed you that tape
in a good faith effort...
to clear my name,
not as an admission of guilt.
Um...
Mr. Wells,
I'm Janet Wilson.
I don't think we've met.
Martin, what is
all this about a videotape?
The... nanny-cam tape.
That's why you're here, right?
I'm here to introduce you
to your new attorney.
We met yesterday at the bail
hearing. Don't you remember?
Martin, the bail hearing
is set for tomorrow.
[ Martin ]
What day is this?
What... day of the week...
is this?
Wednesday.
Wednesday the sixth.
Yesterday you told me
it was Thursday.
The day before that
it was Friday.
It's backwards.
Everything's going backwards.
Martin, I think we should
have you speak to someone.
You're under a hell
of a lot of stress.
Being locked up in this cesspool
really doesn't help.
We can have you out of here
by tomorrow afternoon.
The prosecution's case
is weak to say the least.
They have no physical evidence
tying you to the crime scene.
Plus, they don't have
the key card...
that was used to access
your apartment building.
[ Exhales Sharply ]
The key card.
Without it,
they've got nothing.
[ Man ] Oh, yeah.
[ Laughs ]
Somebody likes you,
my brother.
[ Chuckles ]
Come on, man.
I'm just messing
with you.
What, you ain't got
no sense of humor, counselor?
Do I know you?
No, you don't know me.
Damn sure put me
in here, though.
Possession with intent.
And concealed weapon.
Mm-hmm.
That concealed weapon
was a pipe wrench.
I was on my way
to my baby's mama's house...
to unstick the Pepsi caps from
out her garbage disposer...
but I told you all that!
''Concealed weapon'' added six
months to my sentence, man.
You remember my name?
No, I don't remember
your name.
All I needed to know about
you was that you broke the law.
I broke the law.
Well, then, I guess that
makes you ''Wife Killer, Esq.''
[ Laughs ]
Yo! Pick 'em up...
you stumbling bitch.
[ Prisoner]
Come on.
[ Screams ]
[ Basketball Bouncing ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Buzzer Sounds ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Door Closes ]
Aw, geez, Martin.
Your face.
It's all right.
Appreciate your coming
to see me.
Agent Scully, I especially
wanted to talk to you.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm sorry it's not under
better circumstances.
This is the day we meet.
Something is happening to me...
something I need to try
to explain to you both.
I'm moving backward in time.
Every morning I wake up,
it's the day before.
For me, yesterday
was Thursday...
the day before that was Friday,
only it's all new to me.
Every single morning I wake up,
I can only remember...
what's happened
the following day.
Agent Scully, would you
mind taking a closer look...
at his injuries,
maybe check his scalp?
I know this all sounds crazy.
But I'm telling you the truth.
This cut, for instance.
It was on my cheek
when I woke up yesterday.
I woke up this morning,
it wasn't there.
But then this afternoon...
I got cut.
I killed a spider
in my cell yesterday.
First thing this morning,
I woke up, it's back again.
Because it happened
the day before.
I haven't actually
killed it yet.
Mr. Wells, are
you saying that...
you don't remember the day that
your wife was murdered?
I'm talking about
two days ago, Monday.
No, I don't... remember it...
because for me,
it hasn't happened yet.
You do realize that, uh...
you're not going to be able
to prove this, right?
I mean, if, uh...
if tomorrow
is really the day before today...
then we won't
have had this conversation.
Oh, for crying out loud.
It means you're going to have
to tell us all over again.
Yeah, well, uh...
make sure I skip
that freaking meeting.
Mr. Wells, let's say
that all this is true.
Why do you think
it's happening?
I don't know.
There has to be a reason.
What reason?
Something...
I'm meant to understand?
Although I don't know
what it could be.
Maybe you already have
the answer within you.
[ Buzzer Sounds ]
[ Door Closes ]
I'd really prefer to stay
while you do this.
Martin.
I can take you through
the chain of evidence.
I think I've done this before,
thank you, Ms. Wilson.
Mmm-hmm, looking for some
loopholes, huh?
Yeah, man, get yourself
out of here.
They just praying that you find
that one little technicality...
so they can let you go.
I'm not looking
for technicalities.
Well, what are
you looking for, brother?
The truth.
The truth?
[ Laughs ]
You better stick
to the technicalities!
The truth is going
to keep you in here...
and make you
somebody's bitch...
that's what the truth's
going to do.
So put on that
engineering hat, CaseyJones...
because you've got a whole lot
of trains to be pulling...
[ Laughs ]
[ Imitates Train Whistle ]
[ Imitates Train Chugging ]
The truth!
[ Sobs ]
[ Cries ]
I know who did it.
[ Reporter] ...claims he arrived home
from a business trip...
to discover the body of his wife
in their living room.
Apparently, Wells
is now in seclusion...
at the home of a friend.
Baltimore Police
are giving no indication...
whether he is a suspect
in the murder...
or if there are indeed
any suspects at this time.
However, Channel 9 News has
learned police are focusing...
their investigation
on the whereabouts...
of an electronic key card,
much like this one.
The card in question
belongs to Martin Wells.
It was used by the killer
to enter the Calvert House...
apartment building
through the garage entrance.
Wells claims no knowledge of the
whereabouts of his key card...
Not something
you want to wake up to.
- ...and suggests
it may have been stolen.
- [ Clicks ]
How you feeling?
Disconnected from reality...
but I guess I'd better
get used to it.
Oh, um... thank you.
I assume you... let me
spend the night here, right?
Thank you.
Like I said, no problem.
So that makes today--
Tuesday...
the day after the murder.
John...
I know who did it now.
You know who killed Vickie?
Mmm. Latino, maybe 40,
five-ten, 1 85 pounds.
He's got a tattoo
of a spiderweb on his left hand.
Martin, last night you told me
you had no idea who did this.
Yeah, now I do.
Well, trust me. I mean,
I-I don't know his name...
but you can find him
in the Baltimore City lockup.
Call them. They can I.D. him
based on what I just told you.
[ Remote Control Clicks ]
[ Al ]
I just want to say...
my daughter was
an exceptional person...
[ Sighs ]
...one who was loved
by everyone who knew her.
[ Reporter] Sir, have the police
identified any suspects...
in your daughter's death?
They're not telling us much.
What about rumors that your
son-in-law is the prime suspect?
What are your thoughts on that?
Reporting from
the Calvert House Apartments...
this is Brian Blakley.
Back to you in the studio.
No prisoner fitting
that description...
has been processed
in the past 36 hours.
He's in there.
He's got to be there.
Sorry, Martin, he's not.
It must be too soon.
He must not get arrested
until later today-- Tuesday.
That's how he could have been
with me in lockup on Wednesday.
Martin, you have
seriously lost me.
If you're trying to admit
something to me or to yourself...
I want you to just
come out with it.
There's a reason all this
is happening.
Maybe I already have the answer.
Well, how's that?
There's something
in my apartment that
you need to see,John.
Where is it?
Uh, the girls'
bedroom, right there.
[ Glass Shattering ]
[ Screams ]
Martin?
Is this it?
My daughters were at their
grandparents'... thank God.
Their bedroom door was open...
with a clear view
of the front hallway.
The nanny-cam is
motion-activated...
so it should have caught anyone
coming in or out of the house.
[ Tape Rewinds ]
There I am.
Nobody else on the tape
between my wife and the police.
I don't understand it.
I'd say this makes you look
more innocent than guilty.
Look, there-- in the mirror...
...the sun.
Your wife comes home...
before the murderer enters
the building at 4:1 7 a.m.
Her time of death is
fixed shortly after that
well before sunrise.
You came home later,
when the sun was already up.
The killer turned off the tape.
The only question is how?
There's a remote control
for the nanny-cam.
It's in a drawer
by the front door...
but nobody else knew
about it except for...
Vickie...
and me.
Are you sure about that?
[ Knocks On Door]
FBI!
I saw your curtains move.
I know you're in there.
[ Door Unlatches ]
M-Mr. Wells, I...
Trina, you knew about
the nanny-cam, didn't you?
You told the
killer about it.
You must have given
him my key card, too.
Mr. Wells, I-I-I wasn't
even there that night.
First thing you're supposed
to say is: ''What nanny-cam?''
Is this your guy?
[ Trina Crying ]
I'm so sorry, Mr. Wells.
He said
he'd hurt my family.
He made me give him
your key card.
[ Trina Sobbing ]
[ Door Closes ]
His name is Caesar Okompo.
He's got a full sheet--
assault and narcotics.
He knows the drill.
He's a clam.
We'll have Trina's
testimony against him.
Or maybe we won't.
He's got her so scared
we can't count on her.
[ Phone Rings In Distance ]
John, let me go in
and talk to him.
Please.
He says he only wants
to talk to you.
[ Door Opens ]
Why?
You don't know?
You got my name, my record,
and you can't figure it out?
Caesar Okompo--
I don't know you.
I never prosecuted you.
Hector Okompo, my brother.
What was the charge?
Possession with intent.
$50 worth of rock.
It was his third strike,
remember?
Yeah, I remember.
I did my job.
You sent him up for life!
I did my job!
I do it ten times a week
every week of the year...
and for this,
my wife was murdered?
You take away my dignity,
my reputation, my life...
because your dirtbag brother
is where he belongs?!
Brady v. Maryland.
Hey, you know
what I'm talking about.
Brady v. the State of Maryland.
Prosecution's got to turn over
exonerating evidence.
You had the word of three people
that wasn't Hector's rock.
It was in a jacket
that wasn't even his...
left beside him in the club.
You knew that.
You knew that and you
suppressed the evidence.
Are you trying to tell me
that your brother
is not a drug dealer?
My brother was a busboy
when you sent him up.
He had two strikes on him.
He wasn't dealing no more.
You sent him up
for who he used to be...
and 'cause it was easy.
You broke the law.
I tell you what we'll do.
You're going to be
convicted of my wife's murder
one way or another.
Plead out now and I'll look
into your brother's case.
Maybe I'll find a way to
recommend a reduced sentence.
Time served.
You want justice?
So do I.
My brother is dead.
Hung himself in a jail cell
a couple weeks ago.
Martin... a word.
I'm sorry, Martin.
I tried to talk them out of it,
but they think they have a case.
Sir, turn around, please.
Martin Wells,
you are under arrest...
for the murder of Vickie Wells.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used...
against you in
a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
[ Mumbling ]
Come on, honey, pick up.
[ Ringing ]
Pick up!
[ Vickie ]
Hey, there.
Vickie...
This is the Wells' residence...
home of Martin, Vickie,
Courtney and Haley.
We can't come to the phone
right now.
So, please leave a message.
[ Beeps ]
Honey, this is Martin.
Pick up the phone.
Vickie, pick up the phone.
Pick up the phone!
It's not 4:00 yet.
Vickie, please,
when you get this...
get out of the apartment,
go to your parents' house...
and wait for me to call.
I'm on my way back to the city.
[ Dog Barking Nearby ]
John, I need your help.
Martin?
Vickie's going to be murdered
inside of two hours.
Vickie? You
mean your wife?
I called the Baltimore Police
but I can't tell...
if they thought
I was a crank.
I need you to call them.
Now, I can describe the suspect,
his name... everything.
Well, how do you
know all this?
No time to explain.
You wouldn't believe it anyway.
Now, Martin, you see,
now, that's a bad sign...
because it's two-
something in the morning.
I haven't seen you
in three years.
You got to give me
something more to go on.
This is all happening
for a reason.
I... I'm being given
a second chance.
A second chance
to do what?
I prosecuted a man
named Hector Okompo.
I suppressed evidence.
See, he was innocent of
the crime he was charged with.
Martin, anything
you say to me...
You have to report.
I put him away,
he died in prison...
his brother wants revenge,
and it is as simple as that.
You could be disbarred for
what you're telling me.
You could go to prison,
lose everything;
do you understand?
I understand
that I can save Vickie.
Hold on a minute.
[ Dial Tone Buzzing ]
[ Phone Tones Beeping ]
[ Indistinct Radio Chatter]
[ Panting ]
[ Relieved Sighing ]
You got here in time.
Are you Martin Wells?
Yeah. Vickie?
Vickie?
There's nobody here.
We checked.
What exactly are
we looking for?
My wife's going
to be attacked here tonight.
It happens...
The killer's going
to use my key card
to enter at 4:1 7.
It's 4:20 now.
I don't understand.
Where is she?
Tell you what.
We'll take a few sweeps
through the neighborhood,
keep our eyes peeled.
We're a phone call away
if you need us.
[ Phone Beeps ]
[ Speed-dialing ]
[ Ringing ]
Come on.
Come on!
[ Al ]
Hello?
Al, it's Martin.
Martin?
What time is it?
Al...
[ Clears Throat ]
is-is Vickie there?
No. The kids are here.
Vickie left hours ago.
- [ Bumping ]
- Isn't she home yet?
[ DoorknobJiggles ]
Martin?
[ Phone Drops In Cradle ]
[ DoorknobJiggling ]
[ Panting ]
[ Screams ]
Martin, you scared
the hell out of me!!
Honey, why aren't you
in D.C.?
What the...
Where have you been?
I-I got a flat
on the way back from my...
Honey, you're scaring me.
What's wrong?
- We're in trouble. We have
to get out of here now.
- What?!
[ Whispers ]
Vickie!
Get in the bedroom.
Lock the door.
You call the cops...
and don't come out
till I say it's okay.
[ Both Yelling ]
Come on!
[ Both Grunting ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Crashing ]
[ Grunting ]
Oh, my God, Martin!
[ Vickie Screams ]
Martin!
No!
[ Grunting ]
[ Screams ]
Martin!
[ Panting Heavily ]
[ Crying ]
No!
[ Gunshots ]
[ Sobbing ]
You said something
about a second chance.
Was this it?