We live in a darkness
of our own making...
...blind to a habitant world all
but unseen by us.
A world of beings traveling
through time and space...
...imaginable to us only as
flights of fancy.
Who are these beings we dare
to imagine but fear to accept?
What dark work goes on inside
their impossible machines...
...cloaked from us by
invisible forces?
If they know our secrets, ...
...why can't we know theirs?
Stop it! Please!
Let me go! Stop it!
Let me go!
Let the boy go!
Let him go, Mulder!
Let him go, or I will be
compelled to use my weapon.
Now, I don't want to do that,
Agent Mulder. I don't want to shoot.
Now, are you armed?
Come on, damn it.
This is just stupid, Agent Mulder.
Don't turn this into a movie.
Just tell me if you've got a gun.
It's too hot for this B.S.
All right, then, lie down.
Lie down on the ground.
Keep your hands out.
Lay down on your belly there.
For crying out loud,
what are you doing?
Agent Mulder, stay there!
He went over!
Over the edge!
Who?
Mulder.
Right, I'll talk to Scully.
You guys head back to the school.
Where is he?
Where's Mulder?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
I heard an agent say over
the radio that you saw him.
Oh, yeah, I saw him. I saw him
back right off that cliff there...
...and I saw him fall
right over there.
- Then where is he?
- He's gone.
- Come on, he can't be gone.
- Yeah, he can't be, but he is.
That cliff there?
He fell from there?
It's impossible a fall like that.
A cop sees things.
A man drops five stories, dusts his
hat off and goes back to work.
An old lady gets shot point-blank
in a Chinese restaurant, ...
...plucks the slug out of her
egg foo young.
But even if Mulder survives this,
what he does then is too much.
You got your point of impact
there where Agent Scully is standing...
...clear and identifiable.
And a set of tracks here
leading down to the wash.
Look at these tracks.
What do you see?
Mulder was running.
It wasn't Mulder.
That's the one thing I'm sure of.
It may have looked like Mulder,
but it wasn't Mulder.
I told you I knew Mulder.
Okay, maybe I didn't know him
that well.
But I know who it was up there,
and it was Fox Mulder.
I'm sure it did look like Mulder, ...
...and you have every reason
to believe that it was him...
...but it was not Mulder.
I told you that I've seen things...
Things that I can't explain.
Well, I have seen what
looks like a man...
...transform into another man.
What looks like a man,
but who's not a man?
- So, what is he?
- You don't want to know.
He's not a man?
What the hell is he?
Hey, don't turn your back on me.
I'm asking you a legitimate question.
He's alien.
He's a bounty hunter.
Looking to collect a bounty on...?
On Gibson Praise...
...because he's part alien.
He's a human anomaly.
So, this alien bounty hunter...
...he disguised himself as Mulder
to come out here and grab the boy?
To take him back to his ship...
...where we believe Mulder is.
You know,
Agent Scully you're, uh, ...
...you're starting to remind me a lot
of Agent Mulder yourself.
Well then, you explain it to me.
If it's true or possible, ...
...what you're saying--
that there's someone like this out there, ...
...this bounty hunter--
he could just become anyone.
You, me, any damn one of us.
I think that it is true.
And possible.
And wherever Mulder is right now...
...he better damn well be smiling.
Right. They're here.
Any sign of him? Mulder?
Not according to these people.
We went through the school.
- You're better than this.
- Sir?
He's got to be here somewhere.
Let's search the school again.
Hello?
Sorry, I thought you were...
I thought they cleared
you out of here.
Find something?
No. Let's keep looking.
- Administration building is clear.
- Copy, check it again.
What I want to know is
how Doggett got out here.
How did he even know
where we were going?
I don't know.
But he's going to turn this place
upside down looking for the wrong person.
What happened to Gibson Praise?
Whatever happened to him,
he's long gone.
Wherever he is,
he's three steps ahead of us.
Don't look now but we've
got a pair of eyeballs on us.
Just start walking,
I'll be right behind you.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
You shouldn't have come here.
You shouldn't have come.
You'll lead them to me.
I'm here to protect you, Gibson.
I know you know that's
the truth.
I know you know my thoughts.
I know they took the man
you work with ... Mulder.
And now, they've come to take me.
The only reason they want
to take you, Gibson...
...is because you're a special boy.
They want to take you
because of what you are.
I'm sorry. I didn't know that
someone was following me.
My friend Thea knows.
She's the only one
at school I've told.
She says the FBI is
looking for me, too.
She's afraid for me.
She has a right to be afraid.
We don't know who to trust now.
I fell when I was running away.
I think you might
have broken it, Gibson.
If they find me,
they'll take me. I know it.
I've always known it.
I'm going to make you
a splint, Gibson, okay?
I can set your leg,
but, uh...
I'm going to need a car
to get you out of here.
I'm going to come back
for you.
I promise.
I'm not going to let anything
bad happen to you.
You said that to me
once before.
Yeah?
Deputy Director, for you.
Yeah, this is John Doggett.
Agent Doggett,
I'm getting reports from Arizona...
Yes, sir.
...That you found Agent Mulder.
I'm afraid somebody jumped the gun
on that. I saw him, sir, but I...
What do you mean,
you saw him?
What the hell is going on
out there?
Well, we're 'round the
clock here.
I've got local SAR, a rolling
ground cordon and an eye in the sky.
- We're on top of the situation.
- How does the FBI...
...find a man and then lose him
in the middle of the desert?
'Cause I'd like to know.
- Agent Doggett, are you there?
- Yeah. I heard the question.
I put you in charge
out there, Doggett.
Now do the damn job.
This amuse you?
I amuse you?
No.
It just made sense to me.
How you found your way out here.
Who led you to Gibson Praise.
You think I was spying on you?
No, but I think our new
Deputy Director was.
You're being made a pawn
in a rigged game.
All right, you've painted me the picture,
now put it in a frame.
All right.
You've got a good rep,
Agent Doggett.
You don't compromise,
you don't quit.
You're a damned good FBI agent--
best of the best.
Lot of guys put you in the
Director's chair one day.
Which is why you've been
set up to fail.
There's no amount of search and
rescue or rolling cordons...
...or eyes in the sky that are
going to turn up Mulder.
It's just the wrong approach.
It's not a question of approach.
It's the only approach I got.
The only way you're going to
find Mulder is to give into the truth.
To listen to Scully.
But even then...
say you did find him, ...
...even then you lose.
You put anything about
aliens or...
...UFOs or alien bounty hunters
in your report...
...Kersh will ruin you.
I'm betting that was his plan.
Is Agent Scully here?
Where's Agent Scully?
I need someone who's with
Agent Scully to put her on a radio.
Someone... with Agent Scully.
Anyone got a twenty
on Agent Scully?
Is anyone out there with her?
I'm with Agent Scully.
Then who's this?
Go for Agent Scully.
What?
Give me the radio.
- You're with Scully?
- Right across the room from her.
From who? From me?
Where?
- What room? Where are you?
- Bunkhouse.
We're in the dorm.
Tell him to hold her.
Tell them not to let
her out of his sight!
Hold Scully.
We're coming to you.
Agent Scully--
There she is.
Do you see her?
Where did she go?
Did you see her?
No.
She ran right back here!
I saw her!
You saw her!
Agent...  Can you breathe?
He thinks it was me.
He thinks that I did
this to him.
How is that possible?
It's someone in this room.
Agent Scully?
Where are you going?
Get out of the car.
Agent Scully!
- Who are you?
- Who am I?
Drop your weapon and
turn around.
- I'm not gonna turn around.
- Just do it!
I know how it works--
Kill shot to the back
of the neck.
Scully, you're pointing
your weapon at a friend.
Turn around, ...
...or I'm going to assume that
you're not who you say you are.
Scully, it's me!
Skinner!
I can prove it.
I know your secret--
who else knows it?
Okay...  then tell me.
You tell me.
How do I know it's you?
I don't like pointing guns
at pregnant women...
...any more than I like them
pointing guns at me.
This has gone too far, Scully.
No.
That's what's wrong here.
It hasn't gone far enough.
I need those car keys.
And what do you think
you're going to do?
Look, we are being
hampered here by the FBI, ...
...by John Doggett, by doubt,
by our own mistrust.
Whatever it is, it is working...
as long as we let it.
You told me Mulder wouldn't
allow it.
Wouldn't let me ruin my career
over this. Over him.
But what about you, Scully?
I mean, my God,
you've got even more at stake.
I can't take the chance that
I'm never going to see him again.
Mulder could just come walking out
of the dark-- we don't know.
Look... we've got one last
chance here...
...waiting for us out there
in the desert--
Gibson Praise.
It may just be who
gets to him first.
Get in the car.
I'll drive.
Gibson!
He's not down there.
I told him to stay here.
He was supposed to stay here.
I found him.
What are you doing
out here?
Why didn't you answer me, huh?
He's here.
I hear him.
What are you talking about?
Mulder.
He's somewhere out there.
He's got a really bad fever.
I think his leg might
be infected.
All right, we got to get you
to the hospital, okay, buddy?
You're so close now.
I'll carry you.
Put your arm around
my neck. Watch your legs.
Agent Scully.
- You take him to the hospital.
- What about you?
I got a boy here who needs
emergency medical attention!
What?
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
It's okay, Gibson,
lie down. Lie down.
Oh, my God.
For someone who claims
he's not following me, ...
...you sure have a knack.
- Hey, you're where the action is.
- What does that tell you?
That I'm crazy or that I'm right?
Wandering around in the desert
in the dead of night, you call it.
You say you want to find Mulder
but you won't do what it takes.
- You're afraid that I'm right.
- I'm not afraid of anything.
Except that maybe Mulder's got
even you believing in this crap now.
You've seen this crap
for yourself now.
How do you explain what
took place today?
Let me ask you something
hypothetically.
If you were to find him
out here...
...or this ship or this
alien bounty hunter, ...
...what would you do then?
I know what Agent Mulder would do.
- He'd do whatever it took.
- You mean lie.
Like you've been lying to me.
And flout orders like
you've done...
...every step of the way
on this thing.
Is that what it takes, Agent Scully?
Give a little, get a little,
Agent Doggett!
You knew where the kid was, ...
...you knew where the kid was
and you wouldn't tell me-- why?
- What kid? I don't see any kid.
- You're lying to me again!
Assistant Director Skinner took
him from here to the hospital.
How do you know that?
There's one thing I know
for sure in this case...
...and that's that Mulder is
after this boy Gibson Praise.
Why? It beats the
hell out of me.
But when he goes after that kid,
my men are going to be waiting for him.
Your men... followed
Assistant Director Skinner?
Hey, where you going?
- Agent Scully, where you going?
- Your men are at the hospital?
They got it controlled.
Nobody goes in or out of that
building without them knowing about it.
How do you know that
they're your men?
Where's the boy?
Door at the end of the hall,
with AD Skinner.
Are you certain about that?
Why don't you get yourself
a visual in the exterior window.
The night nurse has been checking
the boy every 20 minutes-- he's fine.
We have hospital personnel going
about their business.
We're just laying back,
waiting for Mulder.
Yeah, every minute that you wait,
that boy's in danger.
He's exposed.
No one's getting past us,
Agent Scully.
No one's gotten past us.
You believe that, Agent Doggett?
Hey, if something tries to rip
your throat out, I got you covered.
A.D. Skinner...
This is John Doggett.
What the hell is this?
- What the hell is going on?!
- There's no one in that room.
I'm looking for a patient,
a boy, 12 years old.
He may still be in this building.
The window doesn't
even open.
How's a grown man and a boy get out
of the room except by that door?
Agent Scully.
It's okay, I've got him.
Gibson.
How did you get here?
How did you get him
out of that room?
We went up through the ceiling.
I don't know who to trust.
Where is he?
He's right here.
They're going to find him.
Agent Scully!
An agent needs help!
I said an agent needs help!
The best I can say is it's lucky
it all happened at a hospital.
Very lucky, yes, Sir.
I assume the hazardous
materials or chemicals...
...which caused this must
have been medical.
That has not yet been determined, Sir.
So much here is undetermined...
...as remain the whereabouts
of Mulder.
But some of your ... facts...
...like "a man falls from the
cliff and disappears..."
"An agent has his throat crushed
by an assailant...
...who vanishes into thin air."
This reads like a piece of
pot-boiled science fiction.
You mean it reads like an X-File.
But that's what you intended,
wasn't it, Sir?
When you assigned me to the case.
I'll ask the questions, John.
You just give me some
damn answers.
Don't come back until you do.
My dad always said it's
not who wins or loses...
...it's who takes the worst
beating that counts.
That supposed to cheer me up?
I thought so.
But then I never did get
to see your opponent.
And you never will.
You still don't believe me.
What I don't believe is how long
they're keeping you here.
Oh, it's just some things they
have to check out...
...make sure of.
Well, I've got some things
I thought you'd want checked out.
A.D. Skinner is in stable condition, ...
...resting comfortably and awaiting
diagnosis and further study.
Ditto Agent Landau, his throat.
Gibson Praise is right now a
ward of the state...
...but I asked for special protections, ...
...as I assumed you would yourself.
What are you doing here,
Agent Doggett?
Keeping you apprised of the case.
That's not your job.
It is, actually.
And officially.
I'm...
...assigned now to the X-Files.
Whatever you and I
may differ on, ...
...I'll find him, Agent Scully.