Dr. Longenhahn,
here's the body.
They weren't kidding,
were they?
They said they did about
the best they could...
considering he was all mashed
in with that garbage.
( grunts )
How mashed up is he?
Basically, it's hamburger.
Oh.
And they want me
to do what exactly?
The order was to establish
and confiirm real fact of death.
I'd say he's dead.
How about you?
- Yes, sir.
- Good. I'm going home.
You fax me the paperwork by 9:00,
I'll sign it, everybody's happy.
Oh, cryin' out loud.
See this?
They left some garbage
in with it.
Looks kinda like a vertebrae,
only metallic.
Note it on the report.
Then fax me.
Oh, God.
I was hoping
this was all a dream.
- When'd the sun come up?
- About six hours ago.
- Somewhere back in North Carolina.
- Where are we?
We just crossed
into Georgia.
A long way from home,
Agent Scully.
Under the circumstances.
Right.
We can't be too safe.
Are you all right,
Agent Reyes?
I should ask
how you're doing.
I mean, you're the one
who's gonna have this baby.
That's it, isn't it?
What you're really
worried about?
Aside from whatever
danger we're in...
where we're going
doesn't sound like...
there's all that much
in the way of a facility.
You know what I mean?
I-- I've never
delivered a baby.
Well, I've never had one.
That makes us both beginners.
MULDER: This is a videograph
from the D.C. Morgue.
- It's Billy Miles.
- How can that be?
It can't be.
It's impossible.
Yeah, it can't be,
but it is...
walking out of the morgue
lookin' like a new man.
His body was taken to the morgue
in a little box, for God's sake.
Like I told ya,
you can't stop him.
Yeah, you know, you keep
saying that, Krycek.
Why don't you explain it
to us because I'm having
a little bit of a hard time...
understanding it myself.
Billy Miles was scraped out of
the back of a garbage truck.
I saw him go in.
I saw him come out.
Well, I don't know if I can explain it
in any technical sense, but...
that's Billy Miles
without a doubt.
You're sitting there for one reason,
Krycek, because you can't explain it.
I told you
he's a human replacement.
Some new kind of alien...
created to aid in
the repopulation of the planet.
- Which Scully's a threat to.
- If she has that baby.
I don't care who he is or what
you think he's made of...
there's no way
he's gonna fiind her, no way.
Well, maybe he's not, but there
are others out there just like him.
And it's only a matter of time
before they will.
( knocking )
Agent Doggett?
See you a moment?
There's someone here
to see you.
CRANE:
The name is Knowle Rohrer.
He says you know each other
and what he's here for can't wait.
End of the road.
Yeah, literally.
If anybody fiinds us out here,
it really will be a miracle.
- Where exactly are we?
- Democrat Hot Springs.
According to Agent Doggett,
this is where people used to
come for their waters...
until the springs dried up
and they quit coming.
- He was born here.
- Really.
Well, that's comforting.
I guess.
- So where do you want to set up?
- Over here.
Any particular reason?
I think I told you I feel these energies
about people and stuff...
and places.
I found it works best
to go with my instincts.
I'm getting
a feeling myself.
( squeaks )
Well, there's no water
from this rock.
We're gonna need some water
and a place to boil it.
Along with sterile supplies
and a clean place to do this delivery.
I'm a little stiff
from the drive.
Okay.
It's not like you, Knowle.
Comin' to see me when you make me
work so hard to see you.
This couldn't wait,John.
It's about this thing you're pursuing.
- This thing?
- This man you're after.
I think you know
what I'm talking about.
I think I'm confused,
Knowle...
if it's a man
or it's a thing.
This is military,John.
Goes all the way to the top.
I can't overstate
the sensitivity.
Let me say there was a rumored
program out of the Cold War...
planned to create
a super soldier.
Well, this kid I'm talking about
was pretty damn super.
Got right up out of a gut bucket
and hit the ground running.
The kid wasn't exactly
what I'd call military material.
In fact, they say
he was an alien abductee.
- You got it half right,John.
- Which half?
What you're chasing...
is a prototype.
Uh-huh.
And this
so-called prototype...
- what is he after?
- I think you know that too,John.
He's after
your partner Scully.
You may not be aware that
she was part of a program herself.
Six years ago, Agent Scully was
taken in a military operation...
staged as an abduction.
They put a chip in the back
of her neck to monitor her.
It was also used
to make her pregnant...
with the fiirst organicversion
of that same super soldier.
( chuckles )
What do you want from me?
Help us catch him
so we can put him down...
before he fiinds her.
You assume
I know where she is.
Who does, your superior?
Whoever knows,
his life is in danger too.
I want you to know.
( bell dings )
Sit down, Krycek!
Hey, what did I tell you?
Hey!
SKINNER:
Krycek!
Krycek, hold the door!
Hold the door, Krycek!
Krycek!
( elevator whirring )
Mulder.
You heard
about this, right?
- How is he?
- He's got a concussion.
They're gonna keep him here
for observation.
Where were you
when this all happened?
In my offiice, talking to somebody
who warned me this might happen.
Who?
( sighs )
Skinner could have been killed.
He's lucky he wasn't.
He's an old friend. He tells me
stuff I'm not supposed to know.
- I didn't wanna believe it.
- What exactly did he tell you?
He said that Billy Miles
isn't what you think he is.
He's a product of a government program
lookin' to build a super soldier.
He said Agent Scully's
a part of that program too.
And her pregnancy was triggered
by a chip they put in her neck.
I want to know who the hell
you've been talking to!
Who this trusted source of yours is,
who's been spinning this fantasy.
His name's Knowle Rohrer.
He's deep inside U.S. Intelligence
- I don't know much more than that.
- Did he ever lie to you?
Give you bad information?
False leads?
- You have to think about it?
- He said Scully's in danger.
He wants to stop this guy. How's that
so different from what we're saying?
You didn't tell him
where she is, did you?
No. But I'm beginning to think
that the fact that I know...
is gonna catch up with me
if A.D. Skinner's any indication.
You don't tell anybody where she is.
That's the deal, right?
Not even me.
What if something
happens to me?
This, uh, trusted source
of yours...
told you he knows
how to stop Billy Miles.
Did he happen to tell you
how he plans to do this?
- No.
- Right.
What do you say you and me go fiind
out how trustworthy he really is?
Dana, come see
what you think.
Oh, my goodness!
Look at this.
Look at you.
Wow!
I found them folded up
in a cabinet upstairs...
and a nice porcelain basin
and a whole box of candles.
Do we have matches?
- I've got a lighter.
- Yeah.
Now all we need
is some mood music.
- Like ""Whale Song.""
- ""Whale Song""?
They've got these recordings
of whales talking to each other,
calling back and forth.
( imitating whale calls )
I-I don't know, it's like,
it's almost metaphysical.
You're looking at me like--
I don't know.
I probably sound like a goof.
No, no, it's not that.
Um, I was thinking that you reminded
me of someone that I was close to.
- My sister.
- You're not close to her still?
Uh, she was killed
about fiive years ago...
in my home.
It was a terrible time.
Well, it's, uh, it's okay.
I want to thank you.
Thank you for...
putting this together.
It's not what I planned,
but, um, it's very nice.
What?
There's someone out there.
Stay here.
Get out of the car!
I'm a federal agent!
I don't care who you are.
Let's start by putting
that weapon away.
Just point it down now.
- I'm a federal agent.
- I heard you the fiirst time.
Just let me see
some identifiication.
Dana?
I'm sure this looks untoward,
but my life is in danger.
And my baby's.
There's a man who's pursuing us
and it is very important
that he not fiind us here.
We get hunters in here...
taking deer and game
off-season.
I've heard every excuse in the book,
but this one's far too original.
You don't plan
to have it here?
It's not as crazy
as it sounds.
I mean, I hope it's not.
She's a doctor. She can coach me.
And what if something goes wrong?
If you're a doctor, you know the risks.
- You're unprepared here.
- This man...
he's extremely dangerous.
I got a fiirst-aid kit
in my truck.
It's pretty basic,
but better to have than not.
I'll be back with some towels
and the proper swaddling.
Thank you.
and then when we want to reach him,
all of a sudden, he's unreachable...
- nowhere to be found.
- Maybe he got wind.
Maybe he got spooked.
But I'm beginning to think it doesn't
make a damn bit of difference.
You told me that he told you
he knew how to stop Billy Miles.
Are you telling me now
that you think he's a liar?
He is or he isn't. What the hell
difference does it really make?
It doesn't make
any difference at all...
unless you wanna protect
Scully and that baby.
And then what?
How long can you
keep this up?
How long until the next Billy Miles
rears his head? The next threat?
The next phantom?
Do you ever stop
to ask yourself?
All the sacrifiice,
the blood spill.
You've given nearly
a decade of your life.
Where the hell
is it all gonna end?
I don't know.
Maybe it doesn't.
( tires squealing )
- Start the car.
- What?
- Alex Krycek just pulled in.
- ( car engine starts )
What the hell's he doing here?
How did he get security clearance?
Do you recognize
his passenger?
Yeah, it's Knowle Rohrer.
Thank you.
I have to say, with everything
I know you must be feeling...
you look amazingly
beautiful, Dana.
And what about
what you're feeling?
Any vibrations, Agent Reyes?
- I don't know.
- What?
I don't know if I'm
just being paranoid...
but something feels off.
We need some more water.
( gunshot )
( gun cocks )
Go back inside, Dana!
Who is it?
Dana, it's okay.
He's dead.
No, it's not okay.
What do you mean?
Exactly what I said. Now go on inside.
We'll take care of this.
They said that
he couldn't be stopped.
Dana, he's got no vitals.
He's lost too much blood.
Is this the man
you're afraid of?
How did he
fiind you out here?
I do have to
report this thing.
- No, you can't do that.
- I don't have any real choice.
No, I mean,
I-I just felt a contraction.
Something's happening.
- Where's he going?
- Not to see you, that's for sure.
Who the hell's
he going to see?
You go ahead.
I got Krycek.
( elevator bell dings )
( knocking )
( chattering )
Agent Doggett?
( hangs up phone )
- What are you doing here?
- They let me out of
the hospital tonight.
What are you doing here?
I got Mulder down in the parking
garage watching Alex Krycek.
What the hell
is Krycek doing here?
- That's what I'm trying to fiigure out.
- ( phone rings )
- Yeah?
- He's here with Agent Crane.
Agent Crane? How the hell
does he know Agent Crane?
That's a damn good question.
He doesn't.
You been wondering who's getting
these guys past security, how
Billy Miles is in the F.B.I.?
Agent Crane is in on this
with your friend, which means
he's in on it with Krycek.
- They've been in on it all along.
- I don't understand. In on what?
Fooling us, Agent Doggett.
Into chasing after Billy Miles.
Into believing we could protect her.
- Scully?
- Yes, they know where she is.
- No, no. Only I know where she is.
- You and Agent Reyes.
You called her from a phone
inside the F.B.I., didn't you?
There's no way Crane
can tap calls in here, Mulder.
He'd have to have access
to the communications system.
- Skinner's here with me.
- Maybe this goes even higher.
Listen to me,
I got to get to Scully.
You gotta tell me where she is,
where you sent her.
Look, we can nail these guys here,
Mulder. We can put an end to it.
No, you listen. You gotta get out
of there. You got no guarantee...
that these guys
aren't alien replacements too.
Northern Georgia. A place called
Democrat Hot Springs.
Mulder!
( cocks gun )
Get out of the car.
Doesn't seem fair now.
Doesn't seem right.
Coming down to this.
What do you know about fair or right,
Krycek? You're a coward.
I could've killed you so many times,
Mulder. You gotta know that.
I'm the one
that kept you alive.
Praying you'd win somehow.
Then there
really is no God.
You think I'm bad,
that I'm a killer.
We wanted the same thing, brother.
That's what you don't understand.
I wanted to stop them.
All you wanted was
to save your own ass.
No.
I tried to stop them.
Tried to kill Scully's baby
to stop them.
It's too late.
The tragedy is that you--
you wouldn't let it go.
That's why I have to do this.
'Cause you know
how deep it goes.
Right into the F.B.I.
You wanna kill me,
Alex, kill me.
Like you killed my father.
Just don't insult me
trying to make me understand.
- ( gunshot )
- ( groaning )
( breathing heavily )
( screaming )
( groaning )
It's gonna take more bullets
than you can...
ever fiire
to win this game.
But one bullet...
and I can give you
a thousand lives.
Shoot Mulder.
I'm going to go to the airport. I need
that location from Agent Doggett.
- Skinner, are you with me?
- You just go. I'll get him.
( car engine starts )
( groaning )
They're two minutes apart now.
It's not going to be long.
- How's this?
- That's great.
( elevator bell dings )
Right there!
Both of you!
I'm prepared to use force!
- Come on. Come on!
- Agent Doggett.
Here you go.
Thank you.
- ( screams )
- Move!
Agent Reyes, what?
Move out of here!
What's happening?
Who are you?
This baby will be born.
SCULLY:
Agent Reyes!
The Blazer!
Get Mulder on the phone.
( tires squealing )
What's happening?
Huh? What?
- It's okay, Dana.
- What? No!
- It's going to be okay.
- No!
( breathing heavily,
screams )
Get him off!.
- This is my baby!
- You gotta push, Dana!
( grimaces )
Please don't let them take it!
- Come on, Dana. Push!
- God!
SCULLY:
Please don't let this happen.
- Dana, push!
- It's mine!
Hold on!
- ( yelling )
- Harder! Push, Dana!
- Keep breathing, Dana.
Keep breathing.
- Please don't let them take it!
Push! Push!
- Push, Dana, push!
- ( screams )
( baby crying )
( baby continues crying )
Down there.
Get me down there.
Scully. Scully!
Where is she?
Scully!
- Where is she? Tell me where she is!
- Mulder!
- How is she?
- She's inside.
She needs to get
to the hospital.
I'm to take
this story seriously?
These incidents
at the F.B.I.
This account
of Agent Scully's birth.
I'm to submit this report
as quality investigative work?
As representative
of actual fact?
I signed
the report there, sir.
Yeah, I see it,John.
And I see her signature here too.
On an X-File.
I'd like to know when you
assigned yourself, Agent Reyes?
Agent Doggett
assigned me, sir.
Agent Doggett cannot just assume
the authority of this offiice.
I assume it because this offiice
is under investigation...
for the late-night meeting
between you, Agent Crane...
and an intelligence operative
named Knowle Rohrer.
Both men were presumed dead,
but are now missing.
In actual fact.
You investigate
what I tell you.
And you put me
on the X-Files.
That's what
I'm investigating.
- Get some rest.
- Yeah.
- We didn't hear you come in.
- We were just dropping off gifts.
- We just wanted to--
- See it with your own eyes.
It's incredible, you know?
You arriving in time to save Scully.
- Getting her to a hospital.
- We still don't know how you did it.
Speaking with Agent Doggett,
he said they never reached you
with specifiic coordinates.
There was a light.
I followed it.
Guess we got
our next headline.
How's everybody doing?
We're doing just fiine.
- Hey, now.
- ( baby crying )
- None of that.
- ( baby gurgling )
Hi.
What are you
gonna call him?
William.
After your father.
Well, I don't know.
He's got your coloring
and your eyes...
but he looks suspiciously
like Assistant Director Skinner.
I don't understand, Mulder.
They came to take him
from us.
Why they didn't--
I don't quite understand
that either.
Except that maybe he isn't
what they thought he was.
That doesn't make him any less
of a miracle though, does it?
From the moment
I became pregnant...
I feared the truth...
about how... and why.
And I know
that you feared it too.
I think what we feared
were the possibilities.
The truth we both know.
Which is what?
CHILD:
I made this!