[ Breathing Heavily ]
Pick up!
Pick up the phone!
Look, I don't know
what that bitch told you...
but I'm solid!
She's lying to you.
Check her right-hand
desk drawer.
It's all there,
the whole story.
Pick up, man!
Call him off and let's talk
about this, all right?
Give me a chance to explain--
[ Footsteps ]
[ Panting ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Man Panting ]
Help me!
Somebody wants to kill me!
Who wants to kill you?
- He's out there!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa--
Hold it! Hold on!
Don't do that, guy!
- Now you calm down--
- Please, we've got to stop him!
- Who?
- He's out there!
We have to get him
before he gets me!
Anthony!
Take him down,
take him down!
Let me up!
He's gonna kill me!
Take it easy.
Relax now.
Settle down.
No!
This isn't enough!
[ Pounds On Door ]
I'm not safe in here!
Hey, buddy, you've never
been safer in your life, okay?
Just relax--
He can get me in here!!
I'll go call
Social Services.
Right.
[ Pounds On Door ]
It's not enough!!
He can get...
to me! He--
They've identifiied it as nine
millimeter pistol ammunition--
Teflon-coated armor piercing.
It's a single round.
He was shot,
there's no doubt about that.
So I assume the million dollar question
is, ""How?''
Yeah.
Well, what do we know
about the victim?
Carlton Chase, age 39,
well-to-do realtor, single...
lived in the area
all his life.
Nothing but parking
tickets on his record.
Came tearing in here
last night...
saying someone was going
to kill him.
He was right.
Except I don't see any
bullet holes in the walls.
Well, the round looks
to have entered...
through the top
of his head.
Agents.
Thanks for coming
down so quick.
- Al Triguero.
-John Doggett.
Nice to meet you.
Agent Scully.
- Agent.
- Hi.
I'd appreciate any help
you can give us.
We got this much...
fiigured out so far.
Bullet came through
the air vent.
Yeah, that's how it's looking.
There's a little burr
on this louver right here...
where the bullet passed through.
You can barely see it,
but it's there.
So, I'm thinking...
this is where
the killer hid.
He somehow crawled into this
ventilation system, and from here...
he had a clear line of sight
to shoot Chase below.
Did anyone hear a gunshot?
Seems pretty likely
you'd hear one.
Even with a silencer, it's going
to echo through the ductwork.
What's directly above this?
I don't understand.
How could someone
make that shot...
from here?
They didn't make it
from here.
Can I use your pencil?
Sure.
Captain,
we're going to need...
your crime scene investigators
up here.
You got it.
So, lucky shot?
Very.
But this victim here stated that
he was going to be killed...
just moments before
he was shot.
Which doesn't sound lucky
at all.
Guess I can't argue
with that.
What you got there?
The old Godfather trick.
Wrap a towel around a pistol
to muffle the sound.
The killer was up here,
all right.
So how in the hell
did he make that shot?
Well, there's thermal imaging
technology...
which can pick up body heat...
through walls.
Maybe that's...
what allowed him to aim.
We fiield-tested
that in the Marines.
It weighs close
to 90 pounds...
and has to be cooled
with liquid nitrogen.
I can't quite see somebody lugging
it up that ladder we just climbed.
Either way, the rooftop...
of a police station?
That's a pretty ballsy
place for a hit.
[ Chase On Answering Machine ]
Pick up!
Pick up the phone!
Look, I don't know what
that bitch told you...
but I'm solid!
She's lying to you.
Check her right-hand
desk drawer.
It's all there,
the whole story.
[ Man ]
What are you doing?
My, um...
printer cable is loose.
And that's more important
than coffee?
Any messages?
No.
Well, the light's blinking.
Looks like
a message to me.
You going to play it
or what?
Stupid ain't cute, Tammi.
I don't care what
your mama says.
[ Man On Answering Machine ]
Yeah, uh... I got, like, rats... again.
I need you to get them all...
this time.
1806 Brook Valley Turnpike...
last name Allesandry.
You've been here before.
Dwight?
Yeah, I got it.
No, uh...
did you hear the news
this morning?
Carlton Chase?
Well...
I-I just thought
it was pretty scary news.
Try and get Randall
on the phone.
[ Door Slams ]
[ Door Opens ]
Randall?
Your brother
wants to see you.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Loud Thud ]
Randall?
You avoiding me?
Tammi told you I wanted
to talk to you, right?
You want to tell me what
happened last night?
Look, Randall, I'm not mad
at you necessarily.
But I need to know
exactly what happened.
Look, anytime you decide
to do something...
without telling me fiirst...
you could get us
both into trouble.
I saw him stealing.
Carlton stealing from me?
Yeah.
He was skimming.
So where's the money
that he was skimming?
You see, the thing
of it is, Randall...
you get the money,
then you do your thing.
It's a simple equation.
That's what I'm talking about...
when I say you need
to talk to me fiirst!
It'll probably be okay.
But in the future...
let's keep
the communication lines open.
One hand talks
to the other, right?
Here, I brought you
a sandwich.
Meat loaf
the way you like it.
Go ahead, take it.
It's got mayonnaise
and ketchup.
We going out tonight?
Police station's less
than a mile from here.
Chase ran it on foot.
He says that somebody
was after him.
This is probably where
it all started.
Huh.
What's that?
Chase did a lot of business
with an exterminating company...
called AAA-1 Surekill.
Six jobs in one month.
Well, I know...
that's a requirement
of selling a house.
Agent.
It's a .45.
The bullet that
killed Chase...
at the police station
was a nine millimeter.
You know, Elvis used to do this
to his hotel rooms.
I think Carlton Chase did this.
So who was he shooting at?
If it was someone in this room,
he damn sure would've hit them.
Unless it was someone outside.
I got three keys.
You got the cash?
What's this look like?
Who the--
Evening.
What?
You lost?
Nope.
I think this must
be the place.
What, you a cop?
Oh, hell, no.
No, your secret's safe
with me, fellas.
But, uh...
I will be taking that money
off your hands.
And the dope.
Oh, you're funny.
Now, you know what?
Chris Rock is funny.
And you?
You're just dead.
Yeah, cap his ass.
Bang.
[ Muffled Gunshot ]
Bam.
Bang.
[ Door Opens ]
The fiifth. Yeah, I got it.
Nine millimeter--
Sulfuric--
No, I don't need you
to spell it.
All right, thanks.
So which kind of
shooting was this:
lucky, coincidental or
some third alternative?
Well, it's precision marksmanship,
that's for sure.
These holes line up
perfectly...
with the three victims
behind there.
which tells me that
the shooter was standing...
right here
behind this wall.
And consequently wouldn't be
able to see...
what the hell he's aiming at.
Unless he could see.
The light our eyes can register
is only one small portion...
of the electromagnetic spectrum.
Other wavelengths...
from infrared to gamma,
have other properties.
X rays, for instance, can pass
through solid objects.
Walls, for example.
So you're saying this guy used
some kind of x-ray machine.
Wait, you're not saying
this guy has x-ray vision?
I'm remarking that these...
wavelengths exist...
and that the only thing that is
stopping us from seeing them...
if you will, is the biochemical
structure of our eyes.
I'm conjecturing...
that if this structure were
somehow different...
we'd have the ability
to see things that we don't.
Call in Clark Kent.
Okay, so you explain it.
Well, I can't...
so I'm sticking
with what I do know.
Which is?
That this was
a drug rip-off.
Furthermore, it's the
fiifth drug rip-off...
in this area in
the past two months.
Somebody's making a living
capping local drug dealers.
And how does a dead real estate
agent fiigure into that?
Well, that I don't know yet.
But I did fiind out
one more thing:
sulfuryl fluoride.
You got a moment
to see me in my offiice?
Dwight, I need to get
this to the bank.
It can wait.
[ Door Opens ]
Can't you tell
your brother...
to get some lunch
or something at least?
He's practically
right outside the door.
I'll keep the noise
level down if you will.
I just feel like he's
always watching me.
Well, how's he
watching you now?
[ Door Shuts ]
Hello?
Anybody here?
Yeah.
Agents Doggett...
and Scully, FBI.
Dwight Cooper.
What can I do for you?
Mr. Cooper,
do you recognize these?
Well, I don't recognize
much of anything...
except shapes.
Tammi!
Come look at this.
I got bad peepers--
legally blind since birth.
This look familiar?
They're ours.
Last month's billings
for Mr. Chase.
Oh. Carlton.
He was one of
my best clients.
I sent him a ham
every Christmas...
till he fiinally told
me he was a Jew.
[ Laughs ]
He's a nice guy.
We found some evidence
at a crime scene.
A piece of fabric
on which we found...
traces of a chemical--
sulfuryl fluoride.
It's an insecticide used
only by licensed exterminators.
Yeah, it's good stuff.
We use it...
along with about 200 other
outfiits in central Mass.
You've done time, haven't you?
Yeah, a long time ago.
Now my brother and I are
actually members...
of the Worcester Chamber
of Commerce...
if you can believe that one.
[ Chuckles ]
Anything else?
Yeah. Why did Carlton Chase call
this offiice...
14 minutes before
he was murdered?
[ Scully ]
8:34 p.m.
We found a call
to your offiice...
billed on
Mr. Chase's calling card.
It was made from a pay phone...
not far from where
he was murdered.
Wow.
I don't know
what to tell you.
We're all gone home
by that time...
and there wasn't any message
on our machine.
All right.
We'll be in touch if we have
any further questions.
Tammi.
What do you know about that?
About Carlton calling here?
Well, he--
I guess he must've left
a message.
What did it say?
I didn't hear it.
I was reaching
for the play button...
and I hit the erase button
by mistake.
I should've told you.
I was just afraid...
that I lost us
some business maybe.
Come here, baby.
You know, I can't see
worth a damn.
I just want to have
a look at your eyes.
The eyes are the
windows of the soul.
They tell you
everything you need...
to know about a person.
So tell me...
are you lying?
[ Faltering ]
No, Dwight.
That's all I needed to know.
[ Scully ]
Dwight Cooper, arrested in 1986...
for grand theft auto.
Right.
How does a legally
blind guy steal a car?
Well, I assume that he had
a partner who did the driving.
The brother he mentioned...
Randall Cooper.
They were arrested together.
Although Randall apparently
didn't serve much time.
They share the same birthday.
They're twins.
I hate twins.
Twins never rat each other out.
Well, maybe there's someone
in that offiice who will.
Hey, Tammi.
You're here early.
You know you accidentally
left your car running?
You must have been in
a real hurry to get in here...
and make the coffee.
What you got there?
Can I see?
Dwight Cooper. FBI.
Dwight Cooper,
warrant to search.
Have someone...
read it to you.
What the hell...
are you looking for?
Evidence related
to the murder...
of Carlton Chase, et al.
What's in the box?
You got me.
What's the combination?
I don't remember.
So much for
the easy way.
You owe me for that.
I run a clean
business here.
You're not going
to fiind anything...
that's going
to say otherwise.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Can you explain these,
Mr. Cooper?
So, Mr. Cooper, you want to tell
me about these invoices?
Okay, Randall...
let's talk about your
exterminating company.
It's just the three
of you, right?
You and your brother
and Tammi Peyton?
So, how is it...
that your little company billed
over $700,000 to Chase Realty...
last year?
$700,000.
That's a lot of dead rats.
I think...
that you and your brother
and Carlton Chase...
were in a whole
other business together.
Man, I got to get
into the bug business.
I had no idea...
you could make
so much dough...
killing things that
creep around behind walls.
You are quite the entrepreneur.
I'm just a regular Joe,
providing a public service.
Randall?
I'm just a regular Joe
providing a public service.
Is that what your brother
just said to Agent Doggett?
You know why I said that,
don't you?
Because somehow...
you can see through that wall.
You can see your brother
behind me...
and you can read his lips.
I don't know what
gives you the ability...
but I know
how you use it.
You shoot drug dealers...
from places where
they can't see you...
and then you...
and Dwight rob them.
That's how you make
all that money, isn't it?
No. We're exterminators.
Yeah.
You certainly are.
And talking to you now...
I think that the whole thing
is Dwight's idea.
It's time to be your own man,
Randall.
It's time to think for yourself.
You tell them anything?
No. I said what you said.
Well, we got a problem.
It needs to
be taken care of.
I just keep the books.
You keep the books...
on a whole lot
of blood money...
going through that offiice.
We're supposed to believe...
you didn't know
what was going on?
The drug rip-offs,
the murders?
I didn't know about any of that.
Dwight doesn't tell me anything.
I just book the cash receipts.
I don't ask where they're from.
I know not to ask.
Look, here's where
I get confused...
and I'm hoping that
you can help me out.
Carlton Chase.
We think Chase...
was Dwight's fence.
He sold the drugs
your boss stole.
Together, they had
a good thing going.
So why, then,
was Chase killed?
It seems like bad business.
Unless the reason
wasn't business.
Unless it was personal.
Am I under arrest?
[ Deep Sigh ]
Tammi Peyton's phone records.
Found something interesting.
Calls to Carlton Chase.
All of them late night.
What do you
want to bet...
they weren't discussing
escrow accounts?
[ Scully ] So Dwight Cooper learns
that something's going on...
between his girlfriend
and Carlton Chase.
And he kills him.
Or he orders him killed...
assuming Randall's
the triggerman.
[ Scully ]
Maybe not.
[ Doggett ]
What do you mean?
[ Scully ] Maybe Dwight's
not the one who's jealous.
I know it was you.
I still need help, Randall.
You go wait for me.
It's right over there,
the Big Sky Express.
I'll be back right
after I get the money.
I know you took that book
to protect me from Dwight.
I need my book, Randall.
I can't get my
money without it.
[ Gasps ]
I'll be back
in a half an hour, okay?
I'll meet you by the bus.
Randall--
Well, you know
I'm coming back.
You saved me from Carlton.
I owe you.
Randall.
I'll meet you by the bus.
Clothes are gone.
Tammi left in a hurry.
Maybe she thought
someone was after her.
Someone's after you,
you don't pack.
You leave with
what you're wearing.
You think she planned to go?
I do.
The question is, where?
Who are you calling?
Whoever Tammi called last.
Welcome to Concordia Bus Lines.
Our menu options have changed.
For reservations, press one.
- Tammi.
- Dwight!
Is this what you had
in your little secret box? Hmm?
A safety-deposit key.
Looks like you had
a lot of my money in there.
Dwight.
Shut up and drive.
Drive!
So this is how you did it, hmm?
You kept two sets of books.
Huh.
You've been ripping
me off for months.
There's a hundred thousand
dollars difference here.
That's why you were in
such a hurry the other morning.
- Dwight.
- Shut up!
Randall should've
killed you, not Chase.
Or maybe you and Carlton
were working together?
It wasn't like that.
When Carlton found out about
the money, he blackmailed me.
He made me...
do things.
Oh, I bet you
put up a big fiight.
Wait a minute.
If Carlton wasn't
stealing from me...
then why did Randall kill him?
Dwight, you don't understand.
No, no, no. I do understand.
My brother was sweet on you.
He killed Carlton
because he knew...
what was going on
between the two of you.
No!
Where the hell you been?
Hmm?
I got something
for you to do.
[Tammi Whimpers ]
Randall, get over here!
Dwight. No.
Take it.
She ripped us off, Randall...
and you knew it.
No, Randall--
What did you think?
That the two of you...
were going to run off
into the sunset together?
She used you.
Look at me, Randall.
I'm the one who loves you,
not her.
Not anybody else.
Because we're blood.
That's thicker than anything.
I'm going to walk away now...
and I'm going to think hard
about how I can forgive you.
You know what you got to do.
Randall.
You're not going to do this.
[Whimpering ]
Randall, please.
I was coming back for you.
No, you weren't.
Randall!
No!
[ Gunshot ]
[ Doggett ]
Agent.
Has he said anything?
Well, a county D.A.
came in...
and he declined representation.
Aside from that,
he's been uncommunicative.
APB on Tammi Peyton's
a wash so far.
The Bureau in Montana's
on alert.
He watched her every day...
wherever she was.
A man who can look at
anything in the world...
and he chooses her.
He must've seen something in her
she couldn't see in herself.
Well, if you're suggesting he could
see into her heart, Agent...
I think we're out of FBI
territory on this one.
I'll be out front.
[Child ]
I made this!