Previously on Caprica...
Daniel Graystone stole my
technology and killed my men.
For that he must pay.
Eventually, I will
destroy your company,
but before that you have
so many precious things.
Until the debt is paid.
I've been seeing my dead
brother everywhere.
I don't know what's going on.
There was a crash
in the city,
And I thought I saw
my brother there.
He led me to this poster.
There.
That's where it happened.
The accident,
that's where he was killed.
Tamara's out there
in v-world.
I'm getting her back.
Who are you?
I go by emmanuelle.
Heracles said
you were easy to find.
Look for the cube
wandering all alone.
All right,
start guiding.
I can't let my dad know
I'm inside the robot.
I don't trust him.
Hi, daddy.
You're an avatar,
A virtual representation
of Zoe.
What are you doing to her?
Stop it, dr. Graystone!
Stop!
I know this robot can work.
And Zoe is the key.
Caesar, go!
Zoe.
Come on, it's bad enough
you got me wearing
This ridiculous getup.
Now I gotta watch while you
take some fake drugs.
Believe it or not,
That hat
is better camouflage in here
Than that businessman special
you were scanned in.
And as for this,
it's not fake,
And it's not for me.
Are you kidding me?
What?
You're not paying me
to entertain you, counselor.
Now we've got to make it
all the way across town.
We could take the lev,
But in he that's
a guaranteed death sentence.
No wheels,
so we're hoofing it.
It's called "amp."
Think of it
as a hack that bypasses
The holoband's safeties,
Interacting with
the visual cortex
To heighten a player's
senses and reflexes.
In here, you're either
quick or you're dead.
Take your pick.
So how do I...just...
You've taken
eye drops before, right?
Yeah, sure.
It's the same thing.
Just hold it up close
and squeeze.
Okay. Now?
Yes.
Okay.
Welcome back.
Sorry I had to shut you down
for so long,
But I was just
a little stunned
And flabbergasted.
See, up until last night,
I was convinced
that my daughter's avatar
Had been lost or melted
or destroyed.
But now I'm convinced
that you're in there.
And you're free to talk to me.
Give me a sign.
Anything?
No?
Okay, so it's not that
you can't talk to me.
It's that you won't
talk to me.
I...I...
I can't imagine
what the last few weeks
Have been like for you.
This certainly wasn't what
you were expecting, was it?
Must have scared
the crap out of you.
I can understand that.
I'm sorry,
but you have to understand
That this was always
just a temporary place
Just so we cou get you
back in our lives.
And if you can't handle it,
you just let me know,
And I will take you
out of this
And find a way to make you
a more human body,
Whatever you want.
You just...
just have to let me know.
Okay?
Can you at least look at me
when I'm talking to you?
Can you look at me, please?
U87, look at me.
So...
You'll only respond
as the robot, huh?
Okay.
I see.
Okay, so you're giving me
the silent treatment.
Okay.
This might be hard on you,
But it's going to be
all for the best.
Don't worry!
Just another amphead.
A junkie?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You mean the stuff
you gave me was addictive?
But I thought holoband...
Were designed to be
non-addictive. Right.
But amp's are like jamming
a wire
Into your brain's
pleasure center.
Okay, hey,
so addictive drugs,
Senseless sex.
It's a heck of a game.
How do you win?
It depends on who you ask.
Ah, so no rules?
Sounds like a scam.
Well, there's no rule book
in life, right?
You ask me, that's what
keeps it interesting.
Gotta figure out for yourself
what's important.
Move.
I hate that thing.
Just remember to keep
your finger off the trigger
Until you're ready to shoot.
And then be ready to shoot.
Oh, you're a real-life
nicky casino.
You think this is real life?
You think this is what
I look like in real life?
Wait a minute.
Then who are you really?
Someone who's being
paid to help you.
So keep quiet and keep alive.
Great.
Now do it again.
You don't mind if I smoke,
do you?
Zoe hated my smoking.
Actually, she hated anything
at all to do with fire
Ever since our old house
burned down.
Remember that
ramshackle place?
Wood beams.
Wood paneling.
Not the best idea
when you're working
With powerful computers.
Do it again.
They said it started
in my first-floor office,
Got into the walls
and crept upstairs
While we were sleeping.
By the time I woke up,
choking,
The fire was, as they say,
Fully engaged.
Do it again.
Zoe was five.
We had just
moved her upstairs,
Her very first big-girl room
up in the attic.
She loved it up there.
We could hear Zoe's screams.
But we couldn't get past
the flames on the stairs.
Let's do it again.
But that sound.
That sound.
The flames and...
My little girl screaming.
Do it again.
Could hear her screams.
But we couldn't get to her,
Past the flames on the stairs.
Do it again.
I tell you,
That was the longest
seven minutes of my life.
I can only imagine what
it must have been like for her,
Trapped up there
all alone,
Watching the flames
climb the walls,
Melting all the little
glow-in-the-dark stars
That she glued
to the ceiling.
Trapped in a box
of living fl...
Well...
Look at that.
He had me doing
all this soldier stuff,
Basic military crap
That the robot already knew.
And then he started
barking orders at me
Like some
crazy drill sergeant
From one of those
tauron war movies.
Doesn't sound
like much of a test.
Yeah, I know.
But he just kept it up,
Making me do things
over and over again.
You knknow, it just
pissed me off so much,
I wanted to reach out
and snap him.
What?
My God!
I'm such a frakking idiot.
Don't you see it, Lace?
That's exactly
what he wanted me to do.
He wants you
to break his neck?
No, no, no, to react.
He knows that I'm never gonna
admit that I'm in the robot.
So he's trying to trick me
into revealing myself.
Zoe, are you still sure
That it would be
the worst thing if you did,
You know, come out to him?
Yes.
Are you kidding?
Lace, the man lied to me
when he put me in the robot.
If he really thought of me
as his daughter,
He would've never have done
the things that he did.
But it doesn't matter,
because at the end of the day
He just used me to save
his fat military contract.
Business first,
same old daddy.
And you know what,
if I were to tell him
That I was in there now,
he would just use me again.
Maybe in ways
that were even worse.
Okay, so you know what,
he can't know.
Okay.
Okay, so what
are you gonna do?
Well,
what am I supposed to do?
Follow every order
no matter how stupid,
Refuse to
I have to turn me off,
Just be the robot.
Can you even
do that anymore?
This is my place.
At least it's the game's
version of my place.
It's locked.
Someone's taken possession.
Tamara?
Maybe. Try knocking.
Tammy?
Tammy!
What?
Who the frak is it?
I'm Joseph Adama.
Who the frak are you?
Adama, Adama, Adama.
Uh, you know,
That doesn't mean
frak-all to me.
No, no.
Bye-bye.
Don't let him take
his holoband off.
Come here!
What is this?
No, no, let me go.
Let me go.
Sit down.
Put your frakkin' hands down,
all right?
And don't even think about
touching your holoband.
Okay, okay, you got it.
Whatever you say.
All right.
All right?
Hands down...
you're gonna sit down,
And you're gonna
answer my questions.
I got it, I got it.
What the frak have
you done to my place?
Clear.
There's no one else here.
No, no, of course not.
It's just me.
That's...look, you want
my stash, right?
All right,
you take my stash.
I don't want any trouble.
I don't want your drugs.
I'm looking
for a young girl.
Oh, well, you just
should have said something
In the first place,
because I could get you
A really sweet piece
of tail.
She's my daughter,
you motherfrakker.
All right, look,
I told you,
I would absolutely
help you if I could.
This girl,
have you seen her?
Oh, frak, yeah, yeah.
This is, uh...
this is the dead girl, right?
This is the dead girl.
The dead girl?
Well, yeah, I mean, that's
what all the players call her.
She's like a new part
of the program,
New character.
You can't kill her
'cause she's already dead.
Very bad mojo, you know?
Where can we find her?
I don't know.
Come on!
They said they saw her
at that club.
What's it called?
Mysteries.
Maybe. Mysteries.
Where the hell's it at?
What's it to you, pops?
They just busted in,
just now.
They just busted in here, man.
They just busted in.
I'm just looking
for my daughter.
And how could the dead
chick be your daughter?
Doesn't compute,
'cause she's part of the game.
Well,
if you help me find her,
I'll pay you.
We don't play
for the cubits, man.
Your bitch-ass daughter
took out two of my friends.
Hey, watch your frakkin'
mouth when you talk about her!
You're not gonna have to
listen to it much longer.
Hey, you guys
got a beef with him,
Just leave me out of it,
all right?
I was just looking to score,
And this jagoff
said he could help me.
All right.
Just step away.
We'll deal with you later.
Sure. Absolutely.
Whatever you say.
Sorry, pops.
I'll be sure to say hi
to your daughter,
Your little girl if I...
Frak you.
Damn it!
Are you all right?
No, I'm not all right.
I got shot,
and it frakkin' hurts.
It's just a graze.
I'm not gonna de-rez.
Now get out.
What?
Get your pink newbie cheeks
out of this game
And don't come back in
Until you've got
your frakkin' head on straight.
No, but my daugh...
I gotta get my...
Yeah, you're no good to her
if you're gonna freeze
Every time some dirtbag
shoves a gun in your face.
I thought taurons
had bigger stones.
Did the cabbie see him?
No, it was just me.
Are you sure
it's the same car?
Yes, I'm sure.
It was the same car
that I saw in the city
Wrapped around the tree
the other day.
Well, that's just not possible
unless, I mean...
I know, unless I'm frakkin'
nuts, right, Clarice?
No, I'm just saying
that there's probably
Lots of cars out there
that look like that
And lots of drivers too.
And I think that it was
perfectly acceptable
Given everything
that you've been through.
You know, I think it's
all really about Zoe.
Did you ask Daniel
about the avatar?
Yeah.
He said that the code
was unstable or something,
That...
That it wasn't her, that...
You know what, it's the last
thing I need anyway,
Is to start seeing
more dead people.
No.
And now I feel terrible.
I don't think
you should be alone.
I'm fine, really.
I'll be okay.
Um, look,
I've got to go.
It's...we're having
a barbecue.
I'll call you later.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
Oh, look at that.
It certainly is
a beautiful day, isn't it?
Isn't it?
You know what a tell is?
It's an unconscious gesture,
A look or a twitch,
that gives away
The strengths or the weaknesses
of a cardplayer's hands.
It's inconspicuous, but a good
player knows to look for it.
And you showed me yours,
as much as yelled at me,
"I'm in here, daddy!"
So why are we still
playing this game?
I know it's you.
But if you want to keep
Hiding behind a quarter ton
of metal, fine.
Just don't kid yourself.
Don't think for a second
It's because of anything
that I did.
Because I kept
my side of the bargain.
I took you out
of a virtual playground
And brought you
into the real world.
But I guess you can't
handle that, huh?
However brilliant you may be.
Maybe deep down inside,
You're still just
the same, scared little girl
That you always were.
Your mother and I,
We set the bar pretty high.
And maybe you were scared
you couldn't measure up,
So you had to condemn us.
I understand that,
that's only natural,
But the entire
big bad adult world?
Was it really easier to blow up
a train of innocent people
Than to face up
to your own biggest fear,
Which, let's face it,
is life itself, isn't it?
'cause life is scary
and brutal and unpredictable,
And you gotta make
choices like that.
And sometimes you make
the wrong ones.
Maybe I've made
some wrong choices too.
But you keep moving on.
And if you're lucky,
Maybe you get to create
something that lasts,
Has some meaning.
I still love you.
No matter what you did,
no matter what...
No matter what you are,
Crazy as this.
I know you're
not really even her.
You are all of her
That I have left.
So please...
Talk to me.
Please.
All right, I didn't want
to have to do this.
I know what
the robot's tolerances are.
I'm betting
they exceed yours.
Now if you want this
to end at any time,
All you've got to do
is take four steps forward.
And walk out of the circle.
And then I'll know...
For a fact that it's you.
All right?
Because meanwhile...
I'm ordering
the u87 to stay.
Guess you
don't knock, huh?
Stopped about the same time
you stopped answering.
She always signed
her name like that.
That's a little flower.
What the hell,
let me see that.
Hey.
You gave
the ferryman the coins,
You sent her on her way.
Shannon too.
Tell me, Sam.
What goes through your head
when you kill someone?
I'm sorry, what?
I...
How do you do what you do?
I mean, murder someone
in cold blood?
Are you frakking
kidding me?
What the frak
kind of question is that?
How do...
Is this about the
Graystone thing again?
No!
Because that's done.
You're safe.
No, please. Sam, I promise.
Then what is this about?
No, I just...
you just what?
Forget it.
You tell yourself
it's not real.
Why?
Look, I'm only
telling you this because
If you need to know,
you better know.
You tell yourself
it's not real.
And then...
Then they're not people
shooting at you anymore,
They're...Targets.
And the whole thing
becomes just a game.
Guess that's the place, huh?
According
to our junkie friend.
Do you really think
she'd be here?
That's what
the junkie said.
Look, there's
a stage act inside.
The host fires riddles
at the audience.
Avoid him.
Just follow my lead
and be cool, okay?
Fine. Let's go.
Check your guns first.
No weapons
allowed in the club.
Come on!
You don't have to tell me
That a good man is hard
to find.
But there's got to be
one brave soul amongst you
Who's willing to risk
the ultimate price
For the possibility
of the ultimate reward.
An epiphany.
A privileged peek
into the mysteries
That could show our hero
how to win
This crazy game.
All you have to do
Is answer tonight's
riddle.
What?
No takers?
Well, then...
How about you, sir?
What do you say, folks?
Is this stranger
our new prometheus?
Stranger, stranger, stranger.
Boys!
No, no, no.
Hey, hey.
Take it easy, guys, come on.
Listen, I'm sorry, I don't know
what this is all about.
I just...
why, this is all about you.
Right now.
Well, I'm just
looking for someone.
Aren't we all?
I'm...I'm trying
to find a girl.
It's my daughter.
Pretty.
Wish I had her hair.
Maybe we can
help each other out.
Answer tonight's riddle
and all will be revealed.
Well, what if I don't
answer your riddle?
Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm.
There's a price for failure.
But such
a reward for success!
Come now, don't you wanna
find your little girl?
The sacred vessel, please.
Hey! Lay off!
"as the gods
overthrew the titans,
"so has man
overthrown the gods.
"but when man visits
his sins upon his children,
How shall he be repayed?"
Come on.
Say something.
What, you didn't hear it?
Tick, tock, tick, tock.
Um, okay...
Look, I don't have an answer
for you, I'm just...
Won't you even try?
The ultimate reward
for the ultimate risk.
No, I'm just want
to find my daughter, that's all!
Please, folks.
Tammy?
Tammy!
Baby!
Tammy, please.
Pity.
The stench of
a coward offends me.
Hey.
Take him away.
Get off of me.
Get off of me!
Tammy!
All right, all right.
Okay, let me go.
Let go of me!
Don't come back.
Motherfrakkers.
What'd I say about
staying cool, counselor?
You know, you're lucky
we're both still alive.
You want your gun
back or not?
Oh, yeah.
Hey...
Hey, who drew that flower?
Who drew that?
I don't know what
you're talking about, man.
That's tammy's sign.
She was here.
You sure?
Frakking amp heads.
What are you doing?
Like you said, in here,
You're either quick
or you're dead.
I'll be quick.
You freeze.
Anybody else wants
to stay in this frakking game
Better clear out now.
I said now!
♪ time after time ♪
♪ it's the same old story ♪
Where is she?
Where's my daughter?
Look at this place.
Deader than a doornail,
and on a Saturday night.
Where is she?
Where's my daughter?
You freak!
She was here.
Okay?
In fact,
she's the only reason
We've been drawing
a crowd all month.
What?
What are you talking about?
She was right here
on the stage,
Seeking answers
to the afterlife.
Came right up,
unlike her daddy.
When she answered
the riddle wrong,
We discovered she had the power
to transcend life and death.
It was quite a show.
Maybe she's found
the answers
That everyone's
searching for.
Or maybe she is the answer.
But if you find her...
If you find her...
Tell her I'll give her
star billing
If she comes back.
Hell, I'll even pay her.
Real cubits..
The game speaks through
all of us differently.
Changes us in ways
that we can't expect.
Stick around long enough,
it'll happen to you.
Let's go.
Back door.
Come back anytime.
Happy hour's on wednesdays.
I don't get it.
How could she be opening
secret doors in here?
What's happening to her?
Maybe the other
players are right,
She is a part of this place.
No.
She wasn't meant to
be part of some sick game.
She's my daughter.
She's my little girl.
My gods...
They're all her signs.
Wh's happening to her?
Seems like your daughter
has found a home.
Maybe it's time
you went back to yours.
Excuse me, Amanda.
You have a visitor.
Dr. Thomas vergis.
Vergis?
Tell him Daniel's
down in the lab.
He's asking for you.
I told him you were busy,
but he was very insistent.
All right, show him in.
Welcome, dr. Burgess.
Dr. Graystone.
How can I help you?
Are you familiar
with tauron customs?
I noticed your gloves.
I suspect that
you're also in mourning.
Some might
call it mourning, yes.
Two of my employees
were murdered.
Beaten to death
during a break-in at my plant.
Oh, my gods,
I didn't know.
I am so sorry.
The thieves took
something called an mcp.
It's a key element in a
Caprican defense contract
That my company's
competing for.
It's a contract
for a robotic soldier.
And just days later,
the contract was awarded
To Graystone industries.
It seems that Daniel
had suddenly developed
An identical mcp
of his own.
Well, look at that.
Caesar really likes you.
Tell you what.
We'll do one more test.
And then we'll call it
a day.
Scanner up.
Now here's the deal...
I love my dog.
But I love
my daughter even more.
And if there's
even a slight chance
That some small
part of her is tangled up
In your alloy skeleton,
I've got to know.
Are you trying to say
that my husband
Stole your mcp
And murdered those people?
No.
Not personally, no.
He doesn't have
the courage for that.
This is my husband
that you're talking about.
If you knew him,
you would know that
This is not
even remotely possible.
The question is
is do you know him?
I don't give a frak
who you think my husband killed.
He's my husband.
Get out of my house.
So...
U87, take the gun.
And I'm gonna count to five.
And I want you...
To shoot the dog.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five.
You didn't miss.
They were blanks.
U87, shut yourself down.
Sweetheart?
On.
I can't believe it.
He actually
made you shoot caesar?
With blanks.
The funny thing is...
As soon as I picked
up the gun, I knew.
The robot knew.
The weight was off
by a tiny fraction,
Quarter rounds
instead of full.
Well, thank gods.
You wanna
know something?
If they were full...
I might've
pointed the gun at him.
Zoe, he's your father.
At least he's...Yeah.
Get me out of here, Lace.
Before I do something
I really regret.
Sync by fant0m
www.addic7ed.com