Sync by honeybunny www.addic7ed.com
Man: Come on!
Is she there?
Right down in front.
It's not their fault,
you know. They just...
they don't know what they're doing.
Guys, we should leave
before we get caught.
It's happening.
Don't they ever get tired
of this? It's so sick.
Don't worry, this will all change.
And she's gonna help change it.
- Man 1: Come on! Do it!
- Man 2: Do it! Come on!
Man 3: Yeah. Come on.
Woman: Go, Lindsay!
All: Kill! Kill! Kill!
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
Damn it! What happened?
She derezzed. She
flipped out or something.
She must've defaulted
back to the last copy.
I guess she's not as strong as you yet.
I have faith in you.
She'll be perfect,
'cause you're perfect.
Graystone. What a surprise.
Go frak yourself, Caston.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Anything happen after I left?
Some more blood and guts.
I logged off a couple
of minutes after you.
So, did you check on our
girl after she disappeared?
No. Frakkers confiscated my holoband.
I can access her from home.
From home?
We're not splitting for
Gemenon until tomorrow.
There'll be plenty of time for tweakage.
Ben: But, Zoe...
No buts.
Not ever.
For the one true God knows
all and directs us all.
So say we all.
Out! What?
It was as out as can be.
Do we need to turn on the line sensors?
That's exactly what we're
going to do, cheater-girl.
Serge. Serge: Yes, sir.
Activate the line sensors, please.
And the auto-umpire.
Serge: Of course, Amanda.
Come on, miss cheater.
Honey, don't go all immature on me
just 'cause you know
I'm better than you.
What's that, cheater? Sorry,
I can't hear you, cheater.
Gods! If only the worlds
knew what a baby you are.
Serge: Excuse me, Daniel.
There's an urgent
message for you and Amanda
from the athenian academy regarding Zoe.
Here we go again.
Let's not prejudge this.
We don't even know what
we're dealing with yet.
Amanda: Holobands at school?
- Cutting class? Defiance!
- Daniel: Let's all just take a deep breath, here.
Zoe: Guess you better lock me up, huh?
Daniel: Now what did I just say, honey?
Amanda: You think that's funny, do you?
Well, maybe you'll think this is funny.
No car privileges, no phone, no holoband
and you're grounded for a month.
Hey, hey, hey. Come
on, now. Can we just...
We got a big day tomorrow.
Z, your building, remember?
Oh!
Daddy, I'm sorry, I can't
go. See, I'm grounded.
Well, we're going to make an exception.
It's not every day you get
a building named after you.
Well, there's something
to be excited about.
Having your name on the side
of the new computer-science wing
at Apollo university 'cause your
daddy donated about a billion cubits
to the alumnI fund.
You're on thin ice already, little girl.
Come on, like I even want to be associated
with you and the filthy science...
Hey, that dirty science put a
roof over your head, young lady.
That's enough!
You are so lucky,
and you have everything in the
worlds that you could possibly want,
and all you do is
complain about this family.
You have no idea what it
means to build something
or to work hard for anything.
It's all just been handed to you, Zoe.
I guess I'll have to learn
how to marry into money.
You are gonna regret that
for the rest of your life.
I can't believe I did that.
Well, I think it's okay. She
knows that you didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
I just couldn't.
When he pulled out that
knife and started to...
Hey. Relax.
Why do they think watching
something like that
is fun?
Because they're asleep.
No, that's too easy an answer.
I saw their faces. They definitely
knew what they were doing.
And they loved it.
You sound just like me.
Gee, I wonder why.
So now what?
Now, we have to make sure that
you don't derez on us again.
I thought I'd solved that in the
fai l-safe protocol, but clearly not.
Just don't make me
go back in there again
and you won't have to worry about it.
It really got to you, didn't it?
Yeah.
I mean, I knew that wasn't real.
Nothing in here is real.
It was the way that
people were watching,
the way they Drew strength
from what was happening.
It's all right. It's all right.
I won't make you go back there.
People are really like that?
I mean, on the outside, are they really?
Some. But that's all gonna change.
And you're gonna help bring that change.
I thought the whole
idea was to travel light.
Yeah, well.
Zoe: Do you have the passports?
Uh...
Yeah.
Hey, just checking on your ETA tonight.
Joseph: I'm thinking about 7.00.
You always say that.
Oh, it shouldn't be
much later than that.
The party starts at 7.30.
I know. I know.
Hi, dad?
You can't be late. It's his birthday.
Do you want to put willie in
therapy for the rest of his life?
All right. Like I
told your mom, sweetie,
I'm headed to court and I should
be done no later than 7:00.
- No, daddy, no. That's unacceptable.
- That's the best I can do.
You need to promise me
you'll be there on time.
- Then you'll be there.
- Unacceptable?
- So do I hear a promise?
- All right.
All right, your honor. I promise.
Now, put your mother back on for me.
- Hey, we're getting on the lev.
- What?
Can't hear you. Talk to you at home.
No, no, wait a minute.
Sweetie, I want to tell
you something. I... hello?
Frak.
Zoe: Hurry up, Lace.
Come on, Lacy.
I'm sorry.
I can't!
Look, it's okay. I promise, okay?
They're gonna welcome us on Gemenon...
It's not like it is here on Caprica.
We'll have a whole new family.
I'm sorry.
I knew she'd back out.
She won't tell anyone
before we're off-world.
She won't.
Yeah. Whatever.
Relax.
You're more keyed up than I am.
- Tamara: Okay, remember that guy?
- Okay, yeah.
This little creep actually comes up to
me and is like, "she smells like a Tauron.
You can smell them the
second they walk into the room
'cause they're dirt eaters."
Shannon: I hope you walked away.
I did. After I kicked him in the balls.
Tamara, you didn't.
He deserved way worse.
Are you going to be like this
all the way to Gemenon, or what?
Ben?
Ben!
I'm sorry, zo.
It's God's will.
What?
No! Ben, wait!
The one true God shall
drive out the many.
Man: What happened?
In this senseless tragedy,
it's important that you know
that the government of Caprica
takes matters of terrorism seriously,
and that this case will be pursued
until justice is served.
Agent duram.
Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
On behalf of the prime minister,
let me take this opportunity
to express your government's
deepest sympathy.
This is what we know.
A group known as soldiers of the
one is responsible for the bombing.
Now, while this organization has
been dormant for the past 10 years
and we still have a lot of
evidence to sift through,
everything points to their involvement.
Now, as I'm sure you all know,
the sto espouses a monotheistic
religious philosophy,
advocating the worship of a single,
all-knowing, all-powerful God.
Hey, you need a light?
Thank you.
I've never seen you smoke on tv.
No, well...
Company image and all that.
I quit a few years ago, actually.
Started up again last week.
Been trying to quit myself.
Joe Adams.
Daniel Graystone.
Oh, sorry.
Oh! No.
Gloves are symbolic.
They're to keep us away from
the world during mourning,
or something like that.
I don't even know why they
do it. It's an old custom.
Well, at times like these,
old ways are supposed to help, I guess.
I...
I lost my daughter.
Me, too. And my wife.
I could use a cup of coffee.
There's a coffee shop around the corner.
Clarice:Zoe walks with our
mother goddess Athena now, Lacy.
She will be cared for and loved
and cherished for all eternity.
It's not very comforting, is it?
Truth is, it doesn't
do much for me, either.
Zoe's gone.
And all the scriptures, all the prayers,
all the sacrifices
offered in the temples,
none of these are gonna bring
her back to us. Are they?
I am angry.
At the gods?
At whoever did this. It's not right.
No, it's not.
To be cut down when her life
was full of so much promise.
I should've been on that train.
No.
I should be with Zoe.
I should be dead.
No.
It wasn't your time.
The gods weren't ready
to call your spirit.
They have another purpose for you here.
Me?
Zoe was somebody special. A genius.
The things she could
do with a computer...
She just seemed gifted that way.
If you knew of any particular
work that Zoe was doing,
any work that you could find,
then perhaps that would be a way
for you to reconnect with her,
to find comfort in discovering
her in a different way.
Reconnect?
Mmm.
Serge: Amanda?
Yeah?
Lacy.
Hi, Dr. Graystone.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I know this is gonna
sound kind of weird, but
I was just wondering if I could
sit in her room for a while.
Allow entry Lacy Rand.
Welcome, Lacy Rand.
Thank you.
Stay as long as you like.
Listen, I should be going.
Thanks for the coffee.
Are you okay?
Sorry. Yeah.
Sorry. No, no.
Hey, listen. I understand.
In about five seconds,
I'm jumping off a bridge myself.
I needed this, you know.
Daniel: Just to sit and smoke...
It's the easiest job I've had all day.
Can I offer you a ride home?
Uh, no, I live in the city.
Hey, do you follow pyramid at all?
I've been known to lay a
few cubits on the bucks,
much to my misfortune.
Yes, they have had better seasons,
but I've got courtside seats.
Any interest?
Uh...
Listen, I've got
an 11-year-old boy.
Is there any chance he could join us?
Absolutely.
Listen, this is my private number.
Why don't you give me a call, and
we'll set up the details, okay?
Thanks.
Sir.
Lacy?
Is that you?
Yeah.
I'm glad you're here.
Something terrible has happened,
hasn't it?
So I'm dead?
She's dead.
Yes.
Where did all this blood come from?
I don't see any wounds on your body.
I don't know.
Maybe the bombing.
The bombing?
But you weren't even there.
You couldn't have been there.
I know,
but still I felt it.
Zoe was working on a
biofeedback protocol.
She wanted me to feel what she felt
in real time.
She never got it working
exactly, but something happened.
It's like I felt her death.
Zoe is dead.
What happens to me?
She had some kind of plan for
you once we got to Gemenon,
but I don't even know what that was.
We're not going to
Gemenon anymore, are we?
No.
What am I without her?
She's me. I'm her.
I'm all that's left
of her. Help me, Lace.
Make me understand. What
am I supposed to do next?
I don't have the answers you want, okay?
I didn't even know for sure if you
were gonna still be here once Zoe died.
You're scared
of me.
- Why?
- I don't know you.
You grew up with me.
I grew up with Zoe Graystone.
You're something she
created. You're just a thing.
Zoe promised me I'd see
the real world one day.
And the crazy thing is,
I already knew what the
real world feels like.
I remember it,
just like I remember
growing up with you.
No.
It's true. I've never
been to your house,
never played in your room,
never put on your make-up,
or tried on your clothes.
I'm not a person.
I know that.
But I feel like one.
It's gonna be okay.
Somehow.
I promise.
Lacy?
Dr. Graystone.
What... what are you doing?
I...
I... what?
I gotta go.
Lacy, why are you here?
How does the defendant plead?
Not guilty, your honor.
The clerk will set a date
for trial within the month.
Bail will be set at 10,000 cubits.
Your honor, the defendant
is a known member
of the ha'la'tha crime syndicate.
There is a serious
flight risk to Tauron.
The state strongly recommends
that bail be denied.
I thank the state for
its input. Ruling stands.
Ten thousand cubits for the
bail and 20,000 for the judge.
The Guatrau is very grateful
for the work you've done for him.
He has pledged to help us find the
nothos that killed Shannon and Tamara.
Tell the Guatrau I said thanks, but no.
We're on Caprica now.
Caprica. What has this frakking
planet ever done for us?
I've got a deposition in an hour.
No, no, we cannot let this pass, Joseph.
We need to find them.
Let me grieve in my own way.
Whatever you say, my brother.
But I will pray to mars and all the
gods for a swift and terrible vengeance
to come to those who have torn your
wife and daughter from this world.
There are no gods, Sam.
Cyrus: Evaluation protocol 42.
Independent identification, acquisition,
resolution and execution of conflict.
I had a conversation with the
minister of defense this morning.
The prime minister's
getting a lot of heat.
The media is playing up the fact
that we're five years behind schedule
and half-a-billion
cubits over budget.
He's getting a lot of pressure to yank
the cyber combat unit contract from us
and go off-world with it.
They're talking about going to Vergis.
Man: Evaluation demonstration,
proceed in three, two, one.
I'll be out for the rest of the day.
No calls.
- Let's go. They're waiting for us, sweetie.
- Willie.
How was school today?
All right.
I got off of work early and thought
maybe we could walk home together.
- All right. Okay.
- Stop off for a shaved ice, huh?
- You like that?
- Yeah, sure.
All right.
You know, I met a man who offered to
take us to see the Buccaneers play.
What do you think?
Sure.
I thought you liked pyramid.
Sort of.
Courtside seats.
Could tsattie come with us, too?
You know, I think I want
to give grandma a night off.
It's a guys' night out.
We haven't been spending
much time together lately.
Ever.
William: Do you think
they still feel pain?
Sorry?
You know, mom and
Tamara, where they are.
Do you still think they hurt?
- Daniel: What?
- I know you said no calls.
Tomas Vergis is on Caprica.
He's meeting Defense
Minister Chambers today.
Obviously he's making a
play for the U-87 contract.
I hate to say I told you so.
His company is years behind us.
Word is, Vergis has developed
a met a-cognitive processor.
We've been trying to crack
that technology for a decade.
Suddenly he's got it? I don't think so.
Vergis is going to tell Chambers
that he has an MCP, that much I know.
If it's true...
I mean, if they really have a viable,
independent artificial brain...
Can't be.
Then the only thing they need
- is a robotic body to put it in.
- I know.
I know. First thing is,
find out if it's true.
Saying you've got the MCP is one thing.
Actually having it is another.
See what you can find out. Okay.
And, Cyrus...
Did you ever hear of these virtual
nightclubs for kids, teenagers?
You know, they hack the holobands and
create these places where they can go
and do things.
It's only been an underground
phenomenon for about, oh, five years now.
Why?
Just keep me posted on Vergis.
Zoe!
Morning. Morning.
William was up all night. Again.
I know.
I don't know what to do with him.
Let him experience his roots.
Take him home to Tauron.
It's what my daughter would have wanted.
Will was born on
Caprica. This is his home.
Let's not get into this, okay? Not now.
Joseph: Hey, kiddo.
Hey.
Ruth: Good morning. Morning.
- How are you?
- Good.
There's an extra slice of that
cherry cake you like so much.
Awesome.
Hey, tsattie, are you
gonna take me to school?
It's on my way to work. I'll take you.
Okay.
Duram: Dr. Graystone?
Yes.
Agent Duram, Global Defense Department.
I'm wondering if you have a few minutes.
What for?
Well, as you probably know,
I'm investigating the
attack on the mlmt train.
Should I know that?
Sorry. I've been
avoiding the news lately.
That's completely understandable.
May i?
Yes.
It's about your daughter, Zoe.
Was there anything in her
behavior before the incident
that seemed unusual to you?
She was angry, defiant,
rude, vulgar, obnoxious, unreasonable,
just your typical
16-year-old girl.
And how would you describe her circle
of friends? Was there an anti...
Do me the courtesy of cutting
to the chase, Agent Duram.
We have evidence that we believe positively
links your daughter to the bombers.
I'm sorry. You think that Zoe
knew one of the terrorists?
Dr. Graystone, we think that Zoe
might have been one of the terrorists.
My daughter didn't have a
political bone in her body.
Her biggest concerns in life
were partying with her friends
and finding new and creative
ways to piss off her parents.
I understand how upsetting
this must be for you.
We think that was sent from
your daughter's computer sheet.
The message was transmitted
just before the explosion,
but never had a chance
to uplink to the server.
It took a fair amount of digital
forensics to reconstruct it.
It sounds like a last message to me,
like someone who knows the end
is near and wants to make amends.
Get out.
Here's my card.
If you think of anything,
please don't hesitate to call me.
Welcome, Lacy Rand.
May I come in?
Your security authorization
is still valid.
Please enter.
Thanks.
I'm just going to go to Zoe's room.
As you wish.
Daniel: Looking for this?
You'll pardon the way I look,
but I've been up all night trying to
crack one of the better security codes
I've ever run up against.
I've been to the V-Club.
I've seen her.
I saw her go into a room with
an infinity symbol on the door.
Now, I don't have any idea what
this means or how it's even possible,
but I have the feeling that you do.
I'm sorry, Dr. Graystone...
I want to see her, Lacy.
Whatever she is, I need to know.
I need to know.
Guatrau: I'm glad you
came to see me, Joseph.
We grieve for your terrible loss.
Joseph: Thank you for
saying so, Guatrau.
There's a delicate matter
I need your help on.
If I can, you know I will.
There is a man, an important man,
who has conveniently forgotten
how he got to be so important.
Regrettably, he is
embarking on an enterprise
that will cause a
great deal of distress,
not only to my personal interest,
but to many of my colleagues.
This I cannot sanction.
So action must be taken.
You want me to threaten him?
I'd like this matter to be
resolved in a civilized manner,
and I can think of no other Tauron
as civilized as you, tse'jospeh.
And who is this I'm to negotiate with?
Caprica's minister of
defense, val Chambers.
And if this negotiation
does not go well?
It's best not to speak of such things.
May I have some time
to think about this?
Of course. But not too much time.
- Daniel: What goes on here?
- Lacy: Pretty much anything.
No limits. That's the motto.
Down there is the kill zone. Get a gun,
get five guns, walk in and start shooting.
Back that way are the
group sex and drug dens.
Keep going past that and you'll
find the really gross stuff.
Hi.
This is a fight room. You can
frakking beat anyone you want.
Woman: Kill her!
Daniel: So what's this?
Lacy: Human sacrifice.
What?
Virgins.
They offer them to hecate,
goddess of the underworld.
When I created the holoband,
this isn't exactly what I had in mind.
Yeah, right.
The porn sites were the first
ones to license that technology.
Everyone knows that.
But that's different. That's for adults.
Zoe always said you can
rationalize anything.
So what? You and Zoe came here for sex?
At first.
We used the group sex
rooms like everyone else,
but then after Ben showed us
the way, showed us the way,
we saw this place for
what it was. Trash.
The way?
There is good and there
is evil in this world.
There is a right and there is a wrong,
but only through the one true
God can we know the difference.
And Zoe knew. Because Zoe knew God,
and God touched her heart,
and gave her the ability to create
life itself.
Zoe: Why did you bring him here?
He needs you, Zo.
Hi, daddy.
Zoe: I thought that was
you at the club yesterday.
Thought I got away before you saw me.
Guess I wouldn't make a very good spy.
You're an avatar, a virtual
representation of Zoe.
Nothing more.
I'm a little more than that.
A lot more, actually.
I'm sort of her.
Crazy as that sounds,
I am her.
I'm Zoe Graystone.
Zoe is dead.
I know,
and I'm so sorry about that,
more than you can know.
She was like... like my twin sister.
No, that's not right, either.
She was more than that.
We were like echoes of one another.
It's hard to describe.
So,what is this, really?
Did Zoe hack some kind of rudimentary
emulation software or something?
She said it was a combination
of hacks and some...
Okay, that's enough. What
was the purpose of this thing?
I'm not a thing.
I'm not going to argue
with a digital image.
The human brain contains roughly
300 megabytes of information.
Not much, when you get right down to it.
The question isn't how to
store it. It's how to access it.
You can't download a personality.
There's no way to translate the data.
But the information
being held in our heads
is available in other databases.
People leave more than footprints
as they travel through life.
Medical scans, DNA
profiles, psych evaluations,
school records, e-mails,
recording videolaudio,
cat scans, genetic typing,
synaptic records, security cameras,
test results, shopping records,
talent shows, ball games,
traffic tickets, restaurant bills,
phone records, music lists,
movie tickets, tv shows.
Even prescriptions for birth control.
You do not tell the Guatrau you
need time to think about anything.
You say, "yes, sir. Thank
you, sir. May I have another?"
You swore allegiance
to him, Sam. Not me.
You have no problem taking his cubits.
I don't care if he put me
through law school or not.
I'm tired of doing
his dirty work for him.
You just fire me if you don't like it.
You of all people should know that the
ha'la'tha does not fire people, Joseph.
They bury them.
Yeah.
I remember that.
You put me up on your shoulders so I
could see the band as it marched by,
but we were standing under a lamppost,
(laughs)
and I smacked my head
so hard I saw stars.
Took you to the emergency
room just as a precaution.
- I hated that.
- Yeah.
The lights and the doctors
and that smell.
But I remember you holding
my hand the whole time.
You said you wouldn't let go.
She could've programmed
those memories into you.
But it is a lot of detail
for such a minor event.
It's possible she could've found a way
to translate synaptic
records into usable data.
She did.
Yes, but a person is much more than just
a bunch of usable data.
You might be a good imitation,
you might be a very good imitation,
but you're still just an imitation.
A copy.
I don't feel like a copy.
Daddy...
Can I...
May I hold you, Zoe?
What're you doing to her?
Stop it, Dr. Graystone! Stop!
What did you do to her?
I captured the code Zoe
used to create the avatar.
- Why?
- It's time for you to leave.
Serge,
cancel Lacy Rand's security clearance.
Yes, sir.
Sister Clarice, you wanted to see me?
Lacy, I'd like you to meet Agent Duram.
Hello, Miss Rand.
Agent duram has a few
questions he wants to ask.
Lacy, why don't you have a seat?
I understand you were
friends with Ben Stark.
Sure. I knew Ben.
We have evidence to suggest that he
was involved in the attack on the lev.
That's crazy.
I have to agree with Lacy. That's
an absurd allegation, Mr. Duram.
I'm afraid we have forensic
evidence linking him to the bombing.
Were you aware of his involvement
with the soldiers of the one?
Clarice: Ben Stark was
a good and decent boy.
He would never be involved with some
kind of a... of a terrorist organization.
Lacy, did you know
that Ben was involved?
No, and I don't believe it.
What about Zoe Graystone?
What about her?
Were you aware that she was a member
of soldiers of the one, as well?
She's just gone through an
incredibly traumatic event.
Where does the athenian academy stand
on the question of monotheism, sister?
The academy is dedicated to
following the path of the gods,
the goddess Athena being our patroness.
We are, however, open
to all forms of worship,
including belief in a singular God.
And how many of your students
are practicing monotheists?
You know I can't answer that.
It doesn't concern you, sister,
that kind of absolutist
view of the universe?
Right and wrong determined solely
by a single all-knowing,
all-powerful being
whose judgment cannot be questioned,
and in whose name the
most horrendous of acts
can be sanctioned without appeal?
You seem to know a great
deal about the subject.
Know your enemy, Sister Clarice.
Love your enemy, Agent Duram.
That is what we followers
of Athena believe.
I'll be in touch.
You know, I should've remembered
you own the buccaneers.
A fantasy since I was a kid.
Now, William, what'd you think?
I think Jenkins needs more
practise, he's tanking the game.
You know I agree. Why don't
we go tell him ourselves.
Are you serious?
Yeah, tell me what, Dr. Graystone?
This young man would like to discuss
the finer points of midcourt
defense with you, Rod.
Sure, Daniel, no problem.
What's your name, kid?
- Willie Adams.
- Willie, I'm Rod.
I know who you are, Mr. Jenkins.
So, how do you think we did tonight?
Not that great.
Keep it positive. You're
among champions here, pal.
I'd like to speak with your father if
you don't mind hanging out with the team.
Is that okay? Sure.
This is Sean. If you want something,
anything, you just ask him.
Okay.
- Now, you behave, son.
- Okay, dad.
You know, that was the first time
I've seen him really light
up since the accident,
so thank you so much for doing this.
Please, please, it's easy.
And you?
How are you holding up?
You know us Taurons.
We're nothing if not a stoic people.
Do you mind if I ask you a somewhat
strange and personal question?
What would you do if you had the
chance to be with your daughter again?
You don't have to
answer that. I'm sorry.
No, no.
It was a personal question.
I just hadn't thought about it.
Most of my family, including my
parents, died in the Tauron civil war,
so my brother and I
came here as orphans.
When we arrived, they
drove us to this orphanage.
I remember this field of
wildflowers on the side of the road.
It might seem strange to a caprican,
but there are no flowers on Tauron.
Not one.
It was the most beautiful
thing I'd ever seen in my life.
All the colors,
the petals, the softness, and
I wept openly,
for the first and last time.
So I guess that's what I'd tell Tamara,
to find those things in
life that make you cry,
that make you feel.
Because they're what make you human.
I guess that's what I'd tell Tamara
if I could.
Wow.
William, I'm guessing you'd
like to see the game room, yes?
Yeah. Serge?
- Go have fun.
- Serge: Yes, Daniel?
Please escort William
down to the game room.
Show him how to use the equipment.
Right this way, William.
It's quite a place you got here.
I still miss tinkering down in
my parents' basement, you know?
This all seems a bit much.
Ever tried one of these?
Uh...
I'm not much for that stuff.
Indulge me, please.
Sure.
Just step right in here,
if you would. Right there.
This is what happens
when you buy a holoband
at any retail store.
I saw it on the news.
Basically, I'm going to scan
your image for your avatar,
which is, in essence, a
virtual copy of you, physically.
- Now, just stand still.
- Okay.
You're gonna feel a slight
tingling sensation in your skin,
but I assure you, it's not harmful.
You can step out now.
There you are.
I've looked better.
If you will just sit here,
we are ready to go.
Now, just relax, close your eyes.
Remember, it's going to seem real,
very real, but it's all virtual.
Just an illusion.
Okay.
It takes getting used to.
Can I talk?
I guess I can. Where are we?
Inside a very basic computer program.
I haven't had time to do any
decorating yet. Step over here.
Just tell yourself to walk.
What are you doing, daddy?
Working.
Joseph,
this is Zoe,
my daughter.
My gods.
Boo.
Frak!
What the hell is this?
What kind of sick, twisted
thing are you doing here?
There's nothing twisted about it.
And I didn't do it. Zoe did.
Zoe did?
Turns out she was kind of
a chip off the old block.
That's not her.
- Our daughters, they're gone.
- Yes.
You know this.
Yes, but what if they could come back?
You're insane.
Do you know what your brain is, Joseph?
It's a database and a
processor, that's all.
Information and a way to use it.
And what my daughter figured out was...
Was how to harness all the information
that made her who and what she was.
It's genius, really.
She took a search engine and
turned it into a way to cheat death.
No, it's... it's an illusion.
You said so yourself.
Yes. You're right. You're
right. She's a copy.
But she's a perfect copy in every way.
Still doesn't make her your daughter.
There's an axiom in my business,
"a difference that makes no
difference, is no difference."
She looks like Zoe, she talks
like Zoe, she thinks like Zoe,
remembers all the
events of her childhood,
has all the same likes, dislikes,
flaws, strengths, all of it.
Who's to say her soul
wasn't copied, too?
You can't copy a soul.
And you would know that how?
Hmm? How can you prove
or disprove that idea?
Look, I know what I know, okay?
And I know you can't copy a person.
I know that she's my daughter.
I know that she is my daughter,
and I know it in the only
place that matters. Here.
The only difference between her and the
Zoe that lived in this house is just that.
She lived in this house
instead of a virtual world.
I want to bring her here.
Joseph, I want her to live
in this world once more.
I want to hold her in my
arms, and I want to kiss her,
and I want her to feel
the sun shine on her face.
I want her to see the flowers
at the side of the road, Joseph.
But for me to be able to transfer
the virtual representation of Zoe
you just saw in there into
a physical body out here,
I need a very special, very
particular piece of equipment.
- A physical body... what do you mean?
- Yes.
Like a robot?
"Robot" is a crude name for
what we're talking about.
This is a cybernetic life-form node.
It's still a machine!
- It's artificial skin, eyes, hair,
make-up. - It's cold. It's dead. It's...
Yes, but these are surface details.
That's what we always tell
our children, isn't it?
What matters is on the inside.
The device that I need is called
a met a-cognitive processor.
The problem is, there's only
one company that has this device,
and it's not mine.
Okay.
The only one in existence is
owned by the Vergis Corporation.
- Ever heard of them?
- Yeah, sure.
I know your connection to the ha'la'tha.
I know who and what you are.
I also know about the
pit in your stomach.
I know about the sleepless nights.
I know about the wishing and praying
to whatever gods will listen that you
could have everything back the way it was.
Well, I can bring Tamara back.
- I can bring her back.
- Get out of my way.
You can see your daughter again.
Isn't that worth whatever
price you have to pay?
If you leave now, you'll
never know for sure.
You'll always wonder.
You'll walk by her room,
you'll see her pictures on the wall,
and you'll ask yourself every
day for the rest of your life
whether you had a
chance to bring her back.
Now, if I'm wrong,
have me beat up, have
me killed. I don't care.
But if I'm right...
If I'm right and you have a
chance to see your daughter again,
possibly even your wife,
isn't it worth trying?
Good morning.
Hey.
Morning.
What's this?
I made you breakfast.
You made breakfast?
Excuse me. I used to
cook for you all the time.
Eggs a la Graystone,
wild-mushroom sausage,
Rosemary bread and, of
course, your black tea.
Enjoy.
I miss you.
We can make it through this.
We can.
Together.
Just the two of us.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Eat, and maybe later on, I'll give you
a chance to lose to me in straight sets.
Joseph: I need a favor, Sam.
I don't even know if it can be done,
but I need something stolen.
Really? You?
I'm listening. From
the Vergis Corporation.
On Tauron.
Tomas Vergis is a good
friend of the Guatrau's.
I doubt he'd sanction
stealing from a friend.
What if I agreed to deliver
the message he wanted
to Minister Chambers?
Isn't this one of
those big lines of yours
you're always so worried
about crossing, Joseph?
Are you sure you really want to do that?
You're not actually
threatening me, are you?
Minister Chambers, I'm
simply delivering a message.
There's no threat, real or
implied, in anything I've told you.
You Taurons, you've got
stones, I'll give you that.
Are you making a racial comment, sir?
No more than you're making a threat.
Let's be clear.
I don't like your boss,
I don't like your planet
and I don't like your people,
so you crawl under that rock
where your Guatrau lives,
and you tell him that not only will
I not be pressured or blackmailed,
but the government of Caprica is going
to take a very special interest in him,
his business
and his low-life lawyers.
Perhaps you should sleep on it.
Deliver the message, errand boy,
word for word.
Goodbye, Minister Chambers.
Have a safe journey.
I'm not going anyplace,
you frakking dirt-eater.
Hey there, you.
Always in the books.
Missed you at the club last night.
Missed you for two hours.
Sorry.
I haven't been much of
a friend lately, have I?
That's fine. It doesn't matter.
Look,
I found something.
It changed my life. I
want to share it with you.
Changed your life?
Sounds stupid, huh?
Look, it's not. It's real.
Come with us.
To what?
A prayer meeting.
Because I don't go to enough of those.
This one is different.
You pray, Lace,
but your gods don't answer.
You hurt, but your gods don't heal.
You go to the V-Club for sex and sin,
but it doesn't fill
the void in your soul.
There is truth in the world, Lace.
There is a right and there is a wrong.
And there is a God,
a God who knows the difference.
Lacy: That's how it started.
That's how I got involved.
I didn't know what to do, sister,
where to go.
You did the right thing by
coming to see me with this, Lacy.
I, too, used to feel a void in my soul.
I, too, once hungered
to know right from wrong.
But not anymore.
Sister?
You're not alone.
So then, Ben did have something
to do with the bombing.
He was the terrorist.
Labels like "terrorist" are what
this corrupt and decadent culture
calls people who are trying to
fight the real evil in this world.
Ben was eager to strike against all that
was slowly choking this world to death,
and so he did something premature,
something unauthorized.
But was blowing up that
train evil, wrong? No.
He was fighting evil with all his heart.
And Zoe?
You have no idea how
special Zoe was to us.
Or is.
Daniel: Oh!
I gotta hand it to Vergis,
it's an elegant design.
But will it work?
Well, I won't know until I
put it into a cybernetic body
and try and download
Zoe's avatar into it.
How long?
Well, a couple of days, at least.
I do have a surprise for you, though.
Your daughter's avatar is ready.
What?
I used Zoe's original avatar program
to search and download
any data on Tamara Adams.
School records, medical
DNA, you name it.
About 300 megabytes' worth.
You mean, she's in there?
Yeah, the more I work with Zoe's code,
the more I realize she was
nothing short of a computer genius.
I want to see her.
Thought you might.
Baby?
- Baby?
- Daddy?
Tammy?
My gods!
Daddy.
My gods.
It's okay, baby. I'm
right here. I'm right here.
I'm so scared. What is
this place? What's going on?
It's okay.
I feel so strange.
I know, but you're fine.
It's not fine. It's not fine.
This is wrong. This is so wrong. No.
I know, I know, I know. But the
important thing is we're together.
We can be a family again.
I can't remember how I got here.
And I can't remember
where I was before now.
It's confusing. I know.
This is gonna take some time.
This isn't real. This
doesn't feel real, dad!
I don't feel real. I'm
real... this isn't real!
It's not real. Willie
misses you! I miss you!
We can be a family together.
We can be a family again.
- My heart isn't beating.
- I miss you.
Daddy, my heart isn't beating.
Daddy, why isn't my heart beating?
Why isn't my heart
beating? Why isn't it...
My baby. I know.
She couldn't feel her heart.
- She couldn't feel her heart beat.
- She'll adjust.
She's probably very confused by
everything. It's only natural.
No! No, it's not natural.
No, it's wrong. It's an abomination.
Well, define "natural."
These glasses help me to see.
Artificial limbs and organs
help millions to live.
You'd hardly call those aids "natural,"
but I doubt you'd
call them abominations.
That's not what I mean and you know it.
Ah. Uh-huh.
You mean, only the gods
have power over death.
Well, I reject that notion.
I reject that notion!
And I'm guessing that you
don't put too much stock
in those ideas, either.
We have a chance to
have our daughters back.
And your wife. Think of what that
would mean to your son, Joseph.
How much would it mean to William
to be held by his mother again?
You're not right.
You're out of your frakking mind.
Maybe.
Maybe. I've certainly
been accused of worse.
Zoe: Do you really think
this download is gonna work?
This is what I do.
Yeah. This is what you do.
What?
There's a part of me that
doesn't want this to work.
Why?
I don't want to be on Caprica.
But it's your home.
No.
It's not.
It's never been my home,
and it stopped being a home for
the other Zoe a long time ago...
I don't even know what
that's supposed to mean.
Why do you think your daughter was on
a lev train instead of being in school?
Do you think she was
just cutting school?
Going shopping?
She was leaving Caprica,
and she wasn't coming back.
You don't know what she was doing, okay?
You can't know because
you weren't there.
I know where she was going.
She told me she had a plan.
She was going to Gemenon.
And you know why? Because she found God.
The real God. Stop it!
The children of Caprica
are lost, daddy. Okay?
We are all lost if we
don't turn to the light.
Listen to me, okay? We'll
talk about this later.
When are you going to realize
that later is too late?
When did you ever listen,
ever want to listen?
You and mom, you knew it all.
Your arrogance was
killing your daughter.
And that's how you lost her.
Not to some bomb.
Daddy. Daddy.
No.
Oh, no. Oh!
Oh, no.
Zoe!
Hi, dad.
We're gonna make a new
beginning, starting tonight.
You and me.
You know what?
Our family's gonna survive this.
We're gonna get past this.
We're gonna put our
lives back together again.
Mommy and Tamara are gone.
They're dead and
they're not coming back.
So we have to honor them
by continuing to live
as best we can.
I want you to know who you are.
We come from a long, proud
line of Tauron peasants
who knew how to work the
land and still stand proud.
You're named after your grandfather.
Did I ever tell you that?
Nope.
William.
He was killed during
the Tauron uprising.
Our last name isn't Adams.
I changed it after I
arrived here on Caprica.
Our family name
is Adama.
Adama.
And it's a good, honorable Tauron name.
Come here, son.
Demonstration proceed,
in three, two, one.
All targets neutralized.
Program completed by your command.
Dr. Graystone, you've not only
secured a long-term contract
but you've done a great
service to our planet.
Thank you, minister.
The Vergis Corporation have
made certain accusations.
If they really thought they had a case,
they'd have us in court by now.
Yes. But no matter. It
was never our intention
to take this contract
off-world, anyway.
It's been my experience you
can never trust a Tauron.
Deceit is in their DNA.
What'd you call it?
Cybernetic life-form node.
A cylon, minister.
Hmm.
Cylon. Interesting.
We did it, doctor.
Yes, we did.
Daniel: But it's not what I hoped for.
Yeah. Hello?
Lacy?
Who is this?
It's me. Zoe.
I'm here, and I think
I'm gonna need your help.
Sync by honeybunny www.addic7ed.com