My name's Don Konkey.
I take pictures.
My best friend, Lucy Spiller,
runs these two magazines.
I want those photos
on my desk tonight.
She works really hard.
If anything breaks,
I'm reachable.
Guys, have fun.
This is Holt McLaren.
He's a good actor, but he's not hot.
Screw you.
His girlfriend is Julia Mallory.
She's a big star.
You just love me.
She's hot.
I'm Lucy Spiller, Now magazine.
I'm a big fan.
Right.
Lucy got Holt to give her dirt
on this super star Kira Klay.
Kira OD'd.
When Holt found out,
he crashed his car.
But now, he's hot.
Wait!
This is hard for me, because I have
a tenuous grasp on what's real.
Donny! Donny! Donny!
I'm okay.
I'm a functional
schizophrenic.
Lucy helps me.
And I help her.
Don?
Don,
listen to me.
Don.
Are you all right?
Yes, Lucy.
Are you sure?
Do you want me
to call Dr. Shalba?
- No, I was just thinking.
- Okay.
I need a shot of Kira Klay
for the Drrt cover.
She's dead.
I know, Don.
I need you
inside the funeral.
I'm gonna put you
in a suit.
A nice suit.
Okay.
You're gonna blend in
in a suit.
Now, we have a guy
on the inside.
He's got a shaved head
and a pin-striped suit.
His name is Baby.
You hand him your invite.
- Tell him you're Kira's cousin Dan.
- ...I'm Kira's cousin Dan.
What?
- What?
- Something wrong?
No. No, I'm good.
How are you feelin'?
You wanna get outta here?
No, no, I don't.
I...I feel like we should stay.
I just feel like--
No, it's gonna be okay.
I still don't remember anything
about the accident.
Car came out
of nowhere, huh?
It's a blur.
I just miss her.
I know. I know.
Me, too.
I feel like everybody's
staring at me.
Here.
You saved my life
and you nursed me back to health.
Come on.
I was just...
I was just... man.
I was gonna
be a daddy.
And she was
into it, man.
I mean, she was
totally feelin' it.
Yeah.
She was awesome.
When she first moved here,
we hooked up at a party.
Pheww. Awesome.
- Julia looks wrecked, dude.
- Well, she almost died.
Tragic times, bro.
I gotta take a piss.
Just get the shot of Kira.
I know you can do it.
I know you can.
Synchro: Andrea Cooper, pasbel,
Metalmarco, _/Yellow Sub\_
Transcript : Sub-Way
SynchFix: Metalmarco
::ITA-SA:: & _/Yellow Sub\_
Proudly Presents:
Dirt - Season 01
Episode 02 - "Blogan"
We're in a war here.
It may be a war of the absurd,
but it's a war just the same.
First, there was Blaire Marshall,
princess of pop, without
a hit in over a year.
Then there was Logan Hicks,
struggling after the breakup
of his boy band Straight Up Lovin'.
But when Blaire met Logan,
there was a media frenzy:
"Blogan."
- And now...
- Hey, sugar tits...
is that bloat or a blump?
Blump.
No couple has ever been so controlling
about their pregnancy and baby pictures.
Clear a path, grease ball.
Hey, tough guy... why don't you
hold her hand and
give us a damn picture?
It started eight months ago with
their pregnancy announcement
and an unforgettable pap confrontation.
Make my day.
Or maybe they didn't teach you how
to throw a punch in boy band school.
Get outta my face, bitch!
I hope that girlie punch
was worth it to you!
You just bought me
a first-class trip to Bali!
It's the perfect storm
for a cover story.
This baby picture is what
Wal-Mart mommy wants.
And it's gonna be the next cover of Now.
I want some kick-ass
cover lines by lunch.
I don't have time today for pitches.
I'm on my way to Dirt. See ya.
Okay. Let's see what we have.
I think we're close with
the Kira Klay cover.
Now, the other magazines will run
a cover pretty much like this one.
But none of them will run one like this.
I had someone on the funeral photos.
What, is this too hardcore
for you Columbia J-school grads?
This isn't Tiger Beat.
All right, what's out there today?
- Um... celebrity fat farms?
- Do you have art?
More than you would ever want.
All right, I'll put it down for five.
Two spreads and a single.
Keep the text tight.
The photos should sell the story.
All right, tell makeup
to watch the adjacencies.
I don't want Duncan Hines or
Betty Crocker ads opposite the fatties.
I'm so sorry. Gibson Horne.
His car just pulled up.
Your office.
Terry, take over
the meeting.
I want some
great cover tries
and the book on my desk
in five minutes.
Charge it.
Have your ladies
teased the entire week.
Why don't you
have a seat, Brent.
- Hello, Gibson.
- Hey.
Mmm. How're you doin',
sweet pea?
I'm good!
- Are you sleepin'?
- Not so much.
Oh, you are a beauty.
I'm pretty sure you didn't show up
to compliment me.
I wish I could
say you were wrong.
Please, have a seat.
Lucy... are you familiar
with, uh... Tina Harrod?
The one who disgraced
her magazine
by Photoshopping
the cover?
No, the one who got
her news stand up
over 150% in less
than a year.
She's got some very
interesting ideas about our operation.
Are you talking
about bringing her in under me?
Um... instead of you.
See, Brent's been
bringin' me up to speed
on the numbers, and seems to me
your spending's out of control.
Well, if you're talking
about overhead--
Oh, I'm talkin' about overhead.
Efficiencies.
Sell through.
Bein' snubbed at the last five
ASME Awards.
Screw the ASMEs.
I mean, they're just
a circle jerk for editors
to feel good about writing
5,000-word stories on Abu Ghraib.
The Drrt efficiencies
are strong...
and Now
is turning around.
Well, you're gonna make 'em
for less money. Knock off 20%.
- Oh, come on, Gib.
- Lucy,
do not mistake
fondness for weakness.
I will tolerate a lot of things,
but I will not tolerate
someone losing my money.
We'll find a way.
No, you'll find a way.
Or so help me,
I will bury you.
Now, you all have a nice day.
Damn.
I'm tellin' you,
buddy.
She opened her eyes.
She looked at me.
She was beautiful.
No!
No, no!
Oh, she's not
gonna like that, buddy.
She's not gonna
like that at all.
Okay, everybody.
Listen up.
Swag pile.
Between the watches and the phones
and the wrinkle creams
and the free spa vacations, there's
about $20,000 worth of swag here.
Now needs help.
Anybody who can come up
with a really great exclusive on Blogan
gets to pick something
from the pile.
Don!
Lucy?
Don, I've left you
five messages.
Open the door.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- I need to see the Kira Klay shots.
- Mmm. Okay.
- What?
- It's not ready.
- The shots?
- My house.
I don't care
about your house.
I will be sending over
my housekeeper.
Uh, no! E-Everything's
where it's supposed to be!
Okay.
I'm so sorry, Lucy.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's just, it's filthy.
And I didn't
get the shot.
What!?
Jesus, Don, this is not the goddamn day!
What happened?
I--I--I was usin' the lapel camera,
and then when I got to her,
I switched to the ChapStick cam 'cause
I wanted it to be perfect, and it was.
It was perfect. There was a shaft
of light from outside, and...
she was beautiful,
she was perfect.
And then I... guess
there was a light leak
when I've never had a light leak
in a ChapStick camera.
I want that
cover and set.
Do you know if she's
being cremated or buried?
No, Lucy, please.
- I'm gonna make some calls.
- She's not gonna like that.
- What?
- Nothin'.
Okay, Don.
Now, I really need your help.
We've got one more shot
at this if we're lucky.
Lucy's under a lot of pressure.
Okay, Don, sweetheart...
would you look at me?
Okay?
This is just like when we were
in school, on the paper, remember?
Okay? We were the only ones
who could write and shoot.
It's just like that.
It's just
the two of us.
- Now, we can't fail.
- I won't fail, Lucy. I won't.
Okay.
Mind if I cut in?
Hey!
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh!
Call Security and you don't
make it home tonight.
Or else I pull out a Sharpie,
sign a sneaker or some shit,
and they'll load you
in the trunk for me.
It's good to see you.
You look good.
Thought we had something special.
We did. We do.
So special you set me up?
I wouldn't--uhh!
Uhh...
His name's Don.
Unhh!
He lives in east Hollywood.
I have his card.
- Hey, Lucy, I got something.
- What?
Blaire Marshall just made
a seven-figure deal to pose for Playboy.
Two months
after her due date.
Denise Richard's was six.
Two months?
That's impossible.
Uh... excuse me.
Elliott Greene gets to pick something
from the swag pile.
Swag pile.
Hey... Hey, what's my sweet
little nephew doing tomorrow?
Brent, get outta my chair.
Ohhh...
I did it.
Hey, you know somethin'? You should be
kissin' my ass just a little bit more,
considering I probably
just saved your job.
Oh, so after you threaten it,
now you're gonna save it?
Oh, gimme a break.
We both know you want to stay here.
Let me see your little masterpiece.
'Course, editorial's
gonna take the biggest hit.
Well, it's already a wasteland.
Look at these bullshit numbers.
What, y-you're just gonna eliminate
the fact-checking department?
How much crack are you smoking?
You know what I love about you?
Besides, you know... nothing?
It's that can-do attitude.
You know what you can do?
You can get your ass outta my office.
I count a 23% reduction
in overhead right there.
20% of which is in editorial.
This is like
a cheap power grab.
Excuse me. I have
two magazines to put out.
I love your proposal, by the way.
It's so colorful. Gib is gonna love it.
- Excuse me, Lucy.
- Thank you.
Oh, she's like 23.
She's way too old for you.
No, 23's good.
* In my own world *
* Underneath my clothes *
* And I can't get off *
* It's been a long, long way down *
* I do it every day and I don't know *
* If I want to be here anymore *
* Oh, it comes and changes *
I've told you guys a million times,
leave the packages at the door.
Don't ring.
It's Holt McLaren.
What are you doing here?
Well, you told me if
I ever need anything...
Well, you gave me your address.
You could've called.
Well, I didn't.
So, can I talk to you?
It'll just take a minute.
Mm-hmm.
You look different.
I was almost asleep.
What's up?
I--I need a favor.
A favor?
What kind of favor?
For Julia.
Look, uh, I wanna...
I wanna do somethin nice for her.
'Cause she's wrecked.
She's on these painkillers.
She can't sleep.
She doesn't even rember
what happened with Kira
and with the accident.
Well, I'm sure you
filled her in on everything.
Yeah. 'Course I did.
She lost her best friend.
So you want to do something nice
and make it all better.
Oh, come on, Lucy, don't give me
your patronizin' bullshit.
Look. Please.
I'm askin' you for a favor, like...
a little piece in your magazine
to make her feel better.
Just a little better, for a minute.
Julia is a part of
a whole feeding frenzy.
People only want to hear
"poor Julia" stories.
What, so... so that's it?
It is if you don't stop the "Aw, shucks,
I'm from West Virginia" thing.
I've invested way too much
time and energy in you.
You had this heroic moment.
The whole world sees you differently.
You are a star now.
You have power.
- All right.
- Ohh...
Then demand things.
If you don't start using
your power, you will lose it.
All right, so-- so give Julia story.
Do it.
- Does Julia know Blaire Marshall?
- Yeah.
They were in Hell House together.
I need an extra 500 for the wait.
Mm-hmm. Okay.
And just get the face.
I don't want anyone to be
able to see the crematorium.
I'm really sorry,
but I have to take your picture now.
Lucy needs it.
She has to compete
in a very tough market.
She's a good person.
She just has to compete,
'n', yeah. I have-- I gotta help her
because I'm the only one she has, and...
Yeah, I can't fail.
I thought you were great
in From Here to America
and Hell House,
and Made You Look,
and An Earthly September.
That one got five stars,
and your performance
was joyously transcendent,
according to Elvis Mitchell,
The New York Times.
All right. We gotta move this one.
Okay.
Been nice talkin' to you.
Bye.
Excuse me. Hey.
Um... I couldn't help but overhear
that you're in the child care field?
That's right.
We just lost our
wonderful person this week,
and I am just desperate.
You don't have an agency?
Oh, no, no. Of course we do.
It's just, um...
you know, we have to go through
a hundred interviews
before we can find someone who's...
you know, who's discreet enough.
- Oh?
- Well, my husband's...
he's... very prominent
in the entertainment industry.
Really?
And who's that?
I'm--I'm so sorry.
I... can't tell you. Um...
you know how it is.
With security and everything,
it's crazy.
It can be so, um,
so isolating sometimes.
I wish we could live
a normal life. You know?
Well, of course you do, dear.
Oh, I'm so sorry! I--
I don't even know you.
Have a wipe, darlin'.
Now...
- You were sayin'?
- Well, I just thought...
you might know who...
you know, the most
discreet celebrity baby nurses
might be.
There's just a handful, dear.
I know.
You know, I was just, um...
talking to that wonderful nurse
who Blaire and Logan are using,
and she was telling me that she had
a friend who might be available. But...
you know, I can't reach them
because...
they've gone into hiding.
Blaire and Logan's baby nurse.
You mean Gabriella.
Yes!
Yes! Yes, yes. That's right.
That's right. Gabriella.
Mm-hmm.
Um... Lucy?
Hey. I got something
on the baby nurse.
Yeah?
Um... name,
number, rates,
a little history, hometown,
immigration status.
Nice. You can pick something
from the swag pile.
Oh... no, thanks.
"No, thanks"?
Well... it sounds
kind of stupid,
but, um...
I do it for the story.
Here, check this out.
What is it?
It's a still from the Altman film
where Blaire played a pregnant runaway.
Wow. She really
looks pregnant.
She really does.
So?
So... she's not
having a baby?
But she made a deal with People
to take her first baby pictures.
- Black market?
- No.
If she's too vain
to carry a baby,
she's way too vain not to have
a little Blogan.
Surrogate.
Find out where
this pregnancy pad is.
And check into all
of our fertility clinic sources.
Willa, listen to me.
If this gets out
in any way,
they get onto us,
the whole story's over.
Whether she's carrying
a baby or not,
this girl's
my next cover.
Do you understand?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay.
Oh. Oh.
I'm--I'm sorry
- That's okay.
- Okay.
So, there was a
break-in last fall
at the Universal
wardrobe house.
They claimed a couple of pieces
of costume jewelry and a clown suit.
And...
three of the pregnancy
prosthetics
built for Blaire Marshall
for the Altman film.
Let me guess.
One for each trimester.
- You got it.
- Oh, this is great.
Okay, just keep
following this story.
Don't leak a word,
not even in-house
I want you to create a secret
edit queue and file your stuff there.
I want only dummy text
and gray space
up on that wall.
- You know what really pisses me off?
- What?
I was the first person
to report this pregnancy...
and she played me.
God, I really don't
appreciate that.
- Stick around.
- Okay.
Also, Willa, I'm gonna
want you to write
some copy
on a fashion piece
that we're doin'
on Julia Mallory.
It's a many-looks retrospective
kind of thing.
She's gonna be coming in and sitting
with you and one of our photo editors.
I--I thought we were sticking
to the tragedy angle on her.
Yeah, well, we're gonna
go a little counter to that...
see how that plays.
Okay.
Holt!
Hey, dude.
Hey.
Look at you, man...
lean and mean.
What are you here for,
a meeting?
Yeah.
- Which one?
- Angry Inch.
Right.
- Passed on it.
- 'Course you did.
Your teeth
look really white.
Did you get veneers
or something?
No.
I gotta go.
Yeah, I heard you got
the Fincher movie.
How's it goin'?
It's okay, thanks.
Yeah. I was up
for that shit.
Thought it fell apart
in the second act.
But when I sat down
with Fincher...
I was, like...
"Holt McLaren could be really awesome
for this part,"
so...who knows?
- Maybe I got you the part.
- Listen, Johnny.
You didn't get me
the damn part.
In got the part.
I got the part
because people want me.
You're the punch line to a half
a dozen jokes in this town.
And the only reason no one has told you
what a total blight you are to humanity
is because you make
$5 million a movie.
Dude!
What is your damage?
Oh, yeah... and I made seven mil
for Subliminal Velocity.
Enjoy it while
it lasts, dude.
Say hi to Julia
for me, will you?
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Gabriella.
I wanted to come here
in person to tell you that
I don't want anything
from you.
I don't want
to be famous.
And I'm not interested
in your magazine.
And I don't
betray my clients.
Okay. Well, thanks,
anyway, for coming in.
Is that it?
Um... yeah. Willa, you want
to walk her out?
Oh, do you want
your parking validated?
Oh, no. I didn't
park in your--
I mean, certainly,
if you're going
to remain loyal when you're
getting paid half the going rate,
then there's nothing
I can say.
What do you mean,
half the going rate?
The Tom-Kitten
baby nurse?
95 an hour.
That's a 12-hour
minimum.
24 when they travel,
and, uh,
plus the confidentiality
clause, that's, um--
I don't know.
You do the math.
- But they--they--
- Kyle and Deb?
80.
And they're nowhere near the
stars that Blaire and Logan are.
They told me this
was the top rate.
And yet you remain loyal.
I think that's fantastic.
And what if I didn't?
Well, um...
I know that you don't want
to be a star.
But, um, I also know
that you're from Flor de Mayo
and that your mother and sister are
there with other family members.
- How do you know about my--
- I'm a journalist.
And I know that you worry about
them and their standard of living.
And if I help you?
Well, there's a farm
with some acreage and a very
nice house next to your mother
that's for sale
for about $200,000, U.S.
I think that
if you help us...
that could be
a very realistic goal.
Now, the insiders
are reporting that
she's going to induce at the
superstar suiteat Cedars.
They're all camped out there, but
I--I don't think they're
gonna go to Cedars.
No, I think there'll be too many
unanswered questions there...
you know, due to the nature
of the pregnancy.
Don't you think?
I think you are right.
But they don't tell me
the location.
When the baby comes,
they will call,
and then
they will send a car.
Okay, well, why don't you
let us worry about that?
Allyouneed to do
is take that baby
to the window
for a shot
of California sun.
You know how the babies
get jaundice.
It's the house...
plus 100,000, U.S.
I want half the money upfront,
nonrefundable.
And the other half
if you get your picture.
Congratulations
on your new home.
Here, I'll walk you out.
Hey.
- Hey, I can't see the screen.
- Sorry.
Babe?
Yeah?
I was thinkin'.
We should, um...
we should send somethin'
to Blaire and Logan.
You know, some kind
of baby gift?
I--I know. Totally.
Where they havin'
the baby?
I should get
the address.
Wait, wait. Wait, wait.
Yes!
Level five.
- What?
- The address.
Oh, I know,
you have to call
her mom 'cause they're
hiding out there until it's time.
Um, it's in my book.
It's under "B.M., mom."
Cool.
Hey...
- I love you.
- I loveyou.
I love you.
- Well, was that--
- It was great.
But... you didn't...
No.
Nothin'?
No, no, no.
I didn't say nothing
- Oh.
- No. No.
I just didn't come.
Sorry.
Oh. No, it was nice.
Well... maybe you could give
me some direction.
I could draw you a map.
It's not gonna happen.
Listen, it's not you.
Okay, I just--I have
better luck alone
Oh. So...
a vibrator?
You know, they say
you can get, like, desensitized.
Yeah. Well, maybe I was never
sensitized to begin with.
What about, um...
Did you...
Did you come
the last time?
So... what am I doing here?
I had a really
nice time.
There's that word
again, "nice."
And "had." So...
does that...
that mean it's over?
I do have
a lot of work to do.
Mmm. So... essentially,
I'm a booty call.
Well...
yeah.
Yeah. I don't know why I'm having
such a problem with that.
You know how many times
I've wanted a chick
to turn into a sandwich
when I was done?
I'm a rock musician.
Booty call's
are my stock in trade.
Well, then, if anybody
understands, then...
Right. Right.
I'll just...
grab my stuff.
Yeah. Right.
You know, I make pancakes from scratch.
Mmm. Carbs.
Or I could
get out my guitar
and play you some Bon Jovi
sounding bullshit ballad...
tell you
I wrote it for you.
I've got, like, two more
hours of work to do tonight.
Wow.
You're like a guy.
You really are.
See you later.
- This is surreal.
- What?
I don't know. It just seems like we do
a lot to avoid these magazines.
Yeah, but this'll be good for you.
All right? It's gonna get you
back in the public eye.
You're right.
It's still surreal.
Hi! Hi. Thank you guys so much for
coming down. I'm Willa McPherson.
- Julia Mallory.
- Holt McLaren.
'Course I know who you both are.
You're my favorite Hollywood couple.
Sorry. Um, follow me.
So, our idea is to do a sort of
"many looks of Julia Mallory" piece.
We're gonna pull a bunch of really great
red carpet shots and some candids
and, you know, different haircuts
'cause readers love that kind of thing.
And, the art department is this way.
Hello.
Oh. This is our
editor-in-chief Lucy Spiller.
- Hi.
- How are you?
Thank you so much for doing this for me.
Oh, no. Thank you for your
willingness to be a part of the story.
And you, the hero.
I know. I wouldn't be here to do
this story if it weren't for him.
No, you wouldn't.
Well, we should, uh,
we should probably do this.
Right? She's gotta get
home and get some rest.
Oh, okay. Bye.
I'll introduce you guys
to the photo editor.
Come on. Come on.
Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
- What're you-- Prince Tyrese!
- Yeah, that's right!
I'm, uh, a big fan.
Bullshit! You set me up
with that skank!
Those pho-- Those pictures,
those were great.
You-- You were in the hot tub and the
chaise lounge and the whipped cream.
And then the strap-on
right in your butt--
You wanna talk about that anymore, huh?
Why don't you say that shit again
and see what happens!
No.
Who you workin' with?
I'm a small businessman.
- Who hired you for those pictures?
- Nobody! Just me.
You lyin' nutbag!
You hold the third-highest
all-time rebound record.
But your free throw percentage
is hurting the team.
In the first three games of the season,
you averaged 22 points a game.
That went up to 26 points by game four.
Then you fouled out.
You son of a bitch!
You're bent.
Technically, I'm schizophrenic,
but-- I function.
So beautiful.
- What?
- So beautiful.
He was my buddy here,
but he's gone... Gone.
Crazy little cockroach.
This shit ain't over!
Okay.
There they are!
Cedars will be a zoo.
We'll send some shooters there
to throw people off.
Now, the competion
is going to be insane.
But that's okay because
we've got the right information.
Our intel says the baby's going
to be born somewhere else.
Blogan! Blogan!
Come on, Blaire. Blaire, over here.
Blogan! Get him to turn around.
Blaire! Here!
They're gonna be using decoys
and imposters to evade us.
But we are gonna be in the
right place at the right time.
Come on, that's not the shot.
- Yeah, I got it.
- Yes.
Yes!
I'm counting on you, Danny;
I thought that was obvious.
Yeah. Lakeside. Thursday. Love to Katie.
If Tina Harrod can beat that,
he should give her the job.
How's that feel?
To be the first tabloid editor
to put a dead star on the cover?
- It feels great.
- Oh, yeah?
Great, like... like pornographer great?
Well, you call it what you want.
Just about every news outlet in
the world has picked up this story.
The media bloggers are going ape-shit,
and you think that cover's
not gonna pop?
I told you to up the draw.
And people made a deal for 1.5 million
for the baby Blogan pictures.
We scooped 'em for expenses.
No doubt about it. You're the queen.
And you were the only one
who nailed the Blogan thing.
God.
God. I mean, too vain
to carry your own baby.
And the exclusive with the surrogate.
It's a great touch.
So... what are you gonna do
next week, your highness?
- Maybe I'll get lucky.
- Oh, yeah?
You know somebody else
who's gonna die?
Some other big celebrity
couple who's gonna
fake a baby we can steal pictures of?
'Cause those are the only kind of covers
that are gonna keep us
out of debt every week.
Well, thanks for your concern,
but that's my problem.
No, it's not. As of tomorrow,
it's Tina Harrod's problem.
Unless you accept my cuts.
Holy shit.
Hi. I want you, Terry, and Janice to
meet me in the office in 15 minutes.
- They did a nice job, huh?
- Yeah.
Looks awesome.
You wanna go out?
Are you feelin' up to it?
- Yeah. Why not?
- All right.
I'll get dressed.
HOLT MCLAREN IS READY
FOR HIS CLOSE-UP
Oh, this better be good, sweet pea,
'cause what I was dreamin',
ooh, is illegal in most states.
Let me just say this, Gibson.
Whatever happens tonight...
you will never forget this moment.
This is what we both live for.
You want to cut your overhead by 20%?
How about 50?
We combine the magazines--
one monster publication.
The credibility of Now with
all the lurid fun of Drrt.
Well, it's a glossy tabloid.
No. It is more than that.
No, this is People magazine with
a healthy dose of "screw you."
It's The National Enquirer without
the penis enlargement ads.
Wal-Mart mommy will love it,
and so will the rich sorority girls.
You know, when
I bought Now magazine,
I thought I paid my way
into legitimacy.
I bought an institution.
Now magazine brought America through
the second half of the 20th century.
It was solid, and it was
dependable, but it is over.
It's culturally irrelevant.
Well, then I'm culturally irrelevant.
No.
Not if you change. Not if
you charge the old with the new.
Look at Blaire and Logan.
These are two has-beens that became
huge because they joined forces.
We have the chance to
shape American culture.
Is this the shape we want
for the culture?
You're the one who always says,
"Let the market place decide."
This is what the marketplace wants.
You need this.
No. You need this.
If I do this for you...
You name it.
I'll do anything.
I know this will succeed.
I know it. I can feel it.
Brent Barrow know anything about this?
I came straight to you.
Vision is not a part of his job.
He won't be pleased.
I don't give a shit.
I don't work for him.
And God help you if you're wrong.
I won't be.
You see?
Told ya...
* You know what you do before, *
* it was better to be following me. *
* Yeah, 'cause I could see clearly *
* Occasionally *
* Oh, put your faith in me. *
*Follow, follow... *
* I relieve your duty *
* Dutifully *
* I will take your butter *
* If you won't butter me *
* Follow me down this hole Darlin' *
Morning, sweetheart.
* Follow me a little blindly *
::Italian Subs Addicted::
[www.italiansubs.net]
_/Yellow Sub\_