Prevously on Kyle XY...
You took me.
You took Amanda!
- She won't remember a thing.
- You feeling okay?
It's just this stupid headache
I've had all week.
I hope I didn't embarrass myself
at the after party.
- You weren't at the after party.
- We were there. Weren't we?
Are you going to make me
ask you out?
Your dad technically holds the
keys to my future in his hand.
But I could ask him first.
One hundred percent, absolutely
not, over my dead body, no!
Sara just left?
I would never do that to you.
I know that.
I want you
to come home with me.
You're gonna
have to trust me.
Did everything work out
the way you wanted?
Exactly.
The psychic said your soul
mate would be in danger.
After all was said and done,
it wasn't me who needed saving.
It was Jessi.
Okay, you got plenty of room.
Watch out!
To the left.
Good. Straighten it out.
You got it.
Keep going.
We can put a bed here,
maybe get her an armoire.
Are you sure you want
to give up your space?
Well, I don't have much choice.
No, not unless you know
a family dying to
adopt a teenager grown in a pod.
It's the right thing to do.
And it's gonna be okay...
right?
It's gonna be okay.
This is so not okay.
Right when I can finally put
this room to good use,
I get a roommate.
Will you look
at the big picture here?
Jessi, 24/7,
it's in the house.
We're so screwed.
Try not screwed.
What?
For one thing, Andy's out of town,
and for another
I thought she said she was
never having sex with you again.
She'll change her tune.
Like she's gonna resist this.
We're smart people.
We can deal.
It's gonna be okay.
Hi
Sorry.
This is gonna be a disaster.
6th Race - XY
BelXander, MiniBen314,
Ologele, Sniper2410
Saison 03 Episode 03
Electric Kiss
Forom.com & U-sub.net
The first time I met Amanda,
I was drawn by the sound of her music.
It was like her soul was
calling out to me
and mine was answering.
I never questioned what it meant,
this indefinable connection.
I just knew
she was the one.
What should I do?
What?
- Do I help cook or...
- Jessi, your job is to eat.
I don't eat eggs.
You want a waffle?
- I'll take a waffle.
- Just eat your eggs.
How'd you sleep, Jessi?
Good, I guess. It's a cot.
- At least you've got your own room.
- Give it up, Josh.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Has anyone seen my cell?
Did you check outside?
Maybe you left it out there when
you were talking to Mark last night.
Mark? You were talking to Mark?
I told you...
A different Mark, Dad.
It better be.
This different Mark
must be really funny.
You were giggling a lot.
So, Josh, when does Andy get back?
Not soon enough.
Two more days,
and the wait is killing me.
Is she gonna do it?
Do what?
You know, reopen the store and
be generous with the merchandise.
That's what you said on the phone.
You're like a human wiretap.
I guess privacy in this house
is a thing of the past.
Kyle's doing it, too.
He's listening
to Amanda play right now.
I'm sorry, what?
You were listening to Amanda.
Except she stopped playing.
You're right, she stopped.
You fainted.
I'm calling 911.
No, Mom, please, I stood up
from the piano too fast.
There's no reason
for everyone to hover.
Why now?
Your audition is in two days.
Is there anything
I can get you?
- I'm gonna make you something to eat.
- I'm fine!
She didn't have breakfast
this morning. No appetite.
Something
was upsetting her.
Maybe it was you.
How long are you going to
be staying with the Tragers?
As long as she wants to.
It's turned into
a regular orphanage.
You look really pale.
So, is this how it's gonna be now,
the two of you
rushing over to protect me?
Maybe we wouldn't have to if you were
capable of taking care of yourself.
- I can take care of myself.
- I know that.
Thanks.
You can go home now.
Yes, I'll go back
to our house.
I hope you feel better.
- She means well.
- Does she?
Honestly, Kyle, I am preparing
for the most important
concert of my life.
The thought of you two
living together...
It's not like that.
She needs a place to live,
a family.
I know...
You're the only one for me.
There's nothing to worry about.
Now go home.
Seriously, I have to practice.
If I'm not absolutely perfect I won't
be able to win that scholarship,
which, as my mom keeps reminding me,
is the only way I'm paying for college.
Want me to stay and listen?
You'll distract me.
Go home.
Amanda's concentration's just off.
Don't worry, she'll get it back.
I don't know.
It's not like her.
It's nerves.
It happens to everybody.
Trust me.
Last year I couldn't hit an outside shot
for three straight games.
Suddenly, I'm nailing every one.
I just wish Jessi could have
moved in after the concert.
Right, hottie in the house. Of course
your girlfriend's freaking out.
I have to keep reassuring Amanda
while trying to make Jessi
feel more comfortable.
Sounds like a high-class
problem to me, dude.
High-class?
I want them both to be happy.
Sorry, I've got no advice when
it comes to managing women.
I think my current situation
speaks for itself.
So, is...
Lori seeing that Mark guy now?
Stephen told her he was off limits.
Like that's not gonna drive her
straight to him.
Are you slumming
in college town now?
I'm just passing through.
Really?
Sure. I mean,
I know we're not allowed
to go out with each other, but,
as far as I know there's no
rule against accidental run-ins.
Is that what this is?
A hundred percent purely
accidental run-in. Scout's honor.
I don't know. Something tells me
you weren't a Girl Scout.
Not even remotely.
It is nice,
accidentally running into you.
Would you like to do it
again here tomorrow?
See, now you're pushing it.
Is that a yes?
Well, it's not like
you can prevent an accident.
- Do you want a ride?
- How about another game?
They're both gonna be there, Kyle,
no matter what time you get home.
I'll walk.
- Thanks.
- Later.
Somebody likes you.
Here.
What's wrong,
not a big fan of the canine?
It's not the dog
I have a problem with.
Look, I want to apologize.
Okay?
We could have handled
things a lot better.
I told them. I said,
"If we want to make
a good first impression then
abducting you and your girlfriend,
probably not the best way to go."
You're lucky no one called the police.
Could have.
Wouldn't have found anything.
Our membership is very exclusive.
Careful.
I'd like to keep things
just between us.
Kyle, hang on.
Can we start over?
Who are you?
Michael Cassidy.
What do you want?
Okay, to put it bluntly,
you are our greatest achievement.
And we want to make sure
we have a relationship with you.
A relationship to do what?
Anything and everything.
Come see what we are about.
We are making state of the art advances
in science and technology.
Right.
A group of visionaries and
humanitarians. Scientists.
No, mate.
I don't have the smarts.
I'm more of a front man.
Scientists,
terrible social skills.
Anyway, they sent me to convince
you to give us
a second chance.
Let us show you we're the good guys.
- I'm not interested.
- I'm hoping you'll change your mind.
Humor me.
You've been
a very bad girl, Amber.
Haven't you?
Dad!
What the hell are you doing?
I mean, I know
what you're doing but
what the hell are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm going crazy.
Andy's been out of town
and you know, I miss her.
I get that you miss your
girlfriend but this is not okay.
When the bill for this program
comes in, you're paying for it.
Is there a charge?
I unscrambled the channel.
Why would you do that?
Josh asked me to.
Grounded for a week?
Two.
Nark.
Dude, you gotta
do something about Jessi.
She can't keep a secret for 5 minutes.
She totally ratted me out to Dad.
She's not used
to living with a family.
Remember when I first
moved in here?
I told Stephen I took that test
for you, but you forgave me.
Give her time.
Well...
She did provide me with
a fairly excellent dose of porn.
You really miss Andy, don't you?
I thought I was thirsty before.
But now that I've had my first taste...
With her gone,
I'm totally dehydrated.
So, Andy's a drink
that doesn't quench your thirst?
No, she does.
She did.
It's just... Since we went
there, to that place,
I'm going crazy.
That's all I think about.
You had that accidental run-in
with Jessi in the bathroom.
Why aren't you messed up?
Why would I be messed up?
You saw her boobs
and they're right downstairs.
Both of them.
I love Amanda.
She's my soul mate.
Your soul mate?
That's intense.
I felt it from the first time
I saw her.
We just
connected,
as if we were meant
to meet each other.
Amanda's always been
the one for me.
You still haven't gotten it right.
Coming in every second isn't helping.
Great. Broke a string.
I keep messing up in the same place.
It's like I can't hold
the piece in my head.
That's never happened before.
You'll get it. You always do.
What if I don't?
I need this scholarship.
Done.
It's like I'm carrying this
stress in the back of my neck.
Here, let me.
Feels good.
Good.
It's been one thing
after another lately.
- What do you mean?
- First the headaches,
now this pain in my neck.
Forgetting my music...
- You're just nervous.
- I guess
You know, now that I think
about it, I just...
... haven't felt like myself
since prom.
We know that Latnok
sedated her.
It must have been
a very strong dose.
So strong that she's still having
side effects two weeks later?
- Why is there pain in her neck?
- Stress?
- She's nervous about her concert.
- What if it's more than that?
What if they did
something to her?
Kyle, I think
you're being paranoid.
They kidnapped us!
It was all a sick game. Who knows
what else they're capable of?
Let's say you're right,
they did something.
Now what?
Amanda keeps getting stuck
at the same place in her music.
As if her memory's misfiring.
It could be neurological.
Well, it's not like you can just
scan her brain to find out.
Okay. You could
figure out a way.
This never would have happened
if it weren't for me.
I have to make sure
she's all right.
Anything for
your precious Amanda.
Fancy meeting you here.
What a wonderful coincidence.
For me?
I just like to keep them on hand
in case of accidental run-ins.
That's so nice of you.
Why do you sound so surprised?
No, it's just, people don't
buy me flowers very often.
Well, then you've been dating
the wrong people.
I mean accidentally running into
We're really doing this,
aren't we?
I'm willing to take the risk.
I mean, that's assuming
that you want to.
I took three buses
just to get here.
Of course I do.
It's just never been
this easy before.
No games, it's so direct. Just...
honesty.
Well... No.
It's not easy.
I mean, we're being bad.
Secretive.
Downright duplicitous.
We are so evil.
Would you care
to be evil over pizza?
I would love to.
Best accidental run-in ever.
- Is that what happened to my Xbox?
- I needed to wire this controller.
- What do I get out of this deal?
- Knowing that you helped Amanda.
That's no reward for me, either.
Do you see her? I need to install this
scanner under the piano.
I don't want her to see us.
Oh, yes, you know,
that would be terrible.
You wanted to help.
I'm here, aren't I?
Amanda's next.
Better fire up that scanner thingy.
Find a place backstage
for the receiver.
- What should I do?
- Make sure we don't get caught.
Right.
Excuse me.
Are you a performer?
Performers only in the stage area.
- But I'm just...
- Who are you?
I'm sorry, but you're not
allowed to be here.
- Please leave.
- Oh, my God!
This is the wrong piece!
This is Tchaikovsky and
I wanted Spandus Strapopovich.
Mother! Where are you?
How could you do this to me?
I hate you!
- Young man...
- Are you in charge here?
- I am.
- This is completely unacceptable.
You need to come with me.
What are you doing here?
Wishing you luck.
It's a closed rehearsal.
And I need to focus.
Okay. Well, then...
good luck.
- The device is working perfectly.
- Great.
We make a good team.
Thanks for helping.
- Leave me alone.
- Amanda, I just want to help.
By showing up with your housemate?
You know how that makes me feel,
especially now.
- I shouldn't have brought her.
- No, you shouldn't have
But somehow,
she's always around, helping.
Let me ask you something.
What?
That night,
after prom,
when you went looking for me...
Yes?
Was Jessi there?
- Why would you think...
- Just answer the question.
Jessi helped me find you, yes.
I knew it.
Look, I know that night
must seem very strange.
Strange? It's this big
giant question mark,
and now that I know she was
there it makes it all even worse.
- Wherever you go, she goes.
- I know it may seem that way...
No, that's how it is!
And honestly, Kyle, I can't take it!
I've got to nail this audition
and I can't be worrying about
what is and what is not going on with
the two of you all the time.
- I just can't!
- There's nothing going on.
Then maybe you could try
not spending every second with her!
See how that goes.
Oh, cool. You got it to read
the data from the rehearsal.
This is all
of Amanda's brain activity.
- Were you up all night?
- Not all night.
Maybe most of it.
You know, you could have
used your computer.
It wouldn't have bothered me.
This one's fine.
Well, call out the numbers.
I'll input them in the program.
I should do this by myself.
Why?
It's just...
maybe you should go see
what everybody else is up to.
It's Amanda, right?
She hates me.
She doesn't hate you.
She just thinks that we spend
too much time together.
- I've only been trying to help.
- I know.
But she doesn't know the real story,
so it looks different to her.
It must be hard, being with someone
when you have to keep so many secrets.
It is.
I wish I could
tell her everything.
Then why don't you?
I think about
how worried she'd be.
Who knows how much more danger
I'd be putting her in.
I feel like she'd be more protected
if she didn't know the whole truth.
I know the whole truth.
Thankfully, you can
take care of yourself.
Yeah, I guess.
Oh, my God.
There's something there.
You were right.
They put something
in her brain.
- What did you do to Amanda?
- What?
- You put something in her head.
- Kyle, you're being really...
Tell me what it is.
Okay. It's something new
we've developed. It's safe.
Instead of typical sedative you
use an nanoscopic neuro-blocker.
Attaches itself to the receptors
on the brain stem.
Why would you do that?
So she wouldn't remember
anything from that night.
- It should have dissolved.
- Well, it hasn't.
She's having side effects
and I need to get it out.
We can't get it out.
But we might be able
- to disintegrate it.
- We?
You mean Latnok?
I'd like to help.
Kyle, don't try anything
on your own. You could hurt her.
- Let me make a phone call.
- You've done enough.
Hilary, where are you
when I need you?
Where are you off to?
Amanda's concert?
Crap. You can totally tell
when I'm lying, huh?
Just like Kyle.
You're going to meet Mark.
Listen...
Let me break it down for you.
When it comes to living in this house,
I know we all gather round
the kitchen island and yuk it up
and we're all smiles and hugs
and touching moments,
but underneath, it is us versus them.
Everyone under legal voting age
is honor-bound to keep each
other's secrets.
- Well, I can keep a secret.
- Great.
- That's it?
- As long as you don't rat me out
- to Mom and Dad, you're in.
- I won't.
- Fine.
- Good.
You know, you should
wear your hair down.
Long healthy hair helps signal
a prospective male
to your reproductive potential.
Okay, thanks.
That's good to know.
How's it going, man?
Good, man. Really good.
I'm close to a breakthrough on
the three dimensional algorithm.
Glad to hear it.
Look.
I heard through the grapevine you've
been spending time with Lori Trager.
I guess.
She's a great girl.
No doubt.
But...
you know how we like
to keep things confidential.
And...
Our goal is to get our guy
back in the fold.
You were never supposed
to make contact with his sister.
I know. We met by accident.
It was just a...
I'll keep things separate.
I mean, we're just hanging out.
Not anymore.
- Jessi, hey!
- Your pants are down.
Oh, look at that.
What are you doing?
I... was just thinking of...
- Hey, she's pretty.
- Don't look at that!
Are you okay?
Knee...
broken.
Leave.
Out!
Good. I need your help
figuring this out.
I thought you couldn't
be seen with me.
I don't have time for that.
What we saw is a neuro-block
which hasn't been dissolved.
It's keeping Amanda's memory of what
to play from getting to her fingers.
But I think I can eliminate it
with an electrical charge.
How do I do it
without electrocuting her?
That's a risk
I'd be willing to take.
I know.
You don't have time for this.
- That's Amanda's head?
- Right.
It's empty.
You don't have to be here.
Except this is my room now.
I have to regulate the voltage
and apply the right amount
to disintegrate the block.
But without hurting her.
- That's not enough.
- I know.
You need more power
if you want it to work.
I know.
Let me concentrate.
That's it.
You're doing it.
More.
I think I need to touch Amanda
to control the electrical flow
more precisely.
She'll feel it and
know what you're doing.
Not if I can distract her.
While you're zapping her?
Does someone want to explain
why my laptop just fried
like my brain on drugs?
I must have caused a power surge.
Sorry. I'll fix it later.
Later not so good for me. I was
in the middle of something important.
Charlotte Cam Live.
See, it's you.
You are the problem.
Eavesdropping, barging in without
knocking, blowing out electricity.
- That was me.
- Fine.
Then you get the assist.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't get a minute alone.
Why don't you go
somewhere else, then?
Because this is my house!
Not yours!
Does he think I don't know that?
When I first moved in,
nobody wanted me here
except for Nicole.
But I had nowhere else to go.
They'll come around.
It'll just take time.
How much time
before Josh isn't mad at me?
Probably until
Andy comes back tonight.
A welcome home kiss from her,
he'll forget why he's upset.
- Kyle, that's it!
- What?
How you can help Amanda without
her knowing what you're doing.
Pass the electricity
through a kiss.
I won't know how much power to give her.
If I'm wrong I'll electrocute her.
Then you'll have to practice.
On what?
Me.
Are you all charged up?
Ready?
- Either of you seen Lori?
- No.
She's been out all day.
- Did she say anything to you?
- Nothing at all.
What was that?
What was what?
You just gave her a look. That was your
"I know you're lying" look.
I don't have that look.
Did Lori ask you to lie?
I knew it. She's with Mark.
There you are.
I thought you ran off
with a girl your own age.
I'm sorry. I got held up.
Lucky for you
I'm not high maintenance.
Do you want me to come to you?
Listen, Lori...
I don't even know
how to say this.
Is this the part
where it's not easy anymore?
Look, my future's really
important to me
- and I don't want to jeopardize it.
- I got it.
Now, Lori, come on.
This isn't about you.
Mark, I said I got it.
And now I'm going to hang up.
- Look, I'm sorry.
- Goodbye.
- This is weird.
- It's science.
I know, but I've never
kissed you before.
- You've seen me naked.
- You're not helping.
Sorry.
I shouldn't be kissing anyone
other than Amanda.
Fine.
Go kiss Amanda.
Give her your best guess
about the voltage.
Maybe you'll be right
and you won't kill her.
Sorry.
You need more practice.
Hi.
- I think Kyle's in his room.
- Actually, I wanted to see you.
But if you're on your way
out the door...
That's okay. Please.
I was hoping you could teach me
some relaxation techniques.
You nervous about
the concert tonight?
The entire scholarship committee
from U-Dub is gonna be there.
Watching and judging.
I haven't been able to get
through the piece in weeks
and my mom's all over me.
Sometimes parents don't realize
the pressure they're adding.
It's not just her.
I'm off my game.
It's not the easiest thing
in the world to have
Kyle and Jessi
living under the same roof.
I can see how that would bother
you, but you can trust Kyle.
I know.
I guess I don't trust her.
Is that awful?
Amanda, you and Kyle have
a very special connection.
He would never do
anything to hurt you.
Trust that.
I don't want to hurt you again.
I can take it.
Maybe if I touched you.
Use my hands
to complete a circuit,
any extra current
will flow back through me.
It's worth a shot.
Do you have enough
charge left to try again?
I think so.
How's that?
That's not bad.
I feel
warm.
It tingles a little.
Are you ready?
Just try to be gentle.
I can hear your heart beating.
Yours, too.
Amanda, wait.
- Let me explain.
- You are always trying to explain!
Explaining why you keep secrets,
explaining why you didn't tell me
what happened on prom night.
But there is no explanation
for why you were kissing Jessi!
There is.
I'll tell you everything.
I don't even care anymore,
because none of it matters.
It does matter.
It'll help you understand why
all of this is happening.
The only person who doesn't understand
what is happening is you.
Please.
I'm late for my recital.
I've ruined it.
I've ruined us.
I'm so sorry, Kyle.
She's gonna get to that section of the
music and she won't be able to play it.
I can't let that happen.
I have to help her.
Is there any other way
than kissing her?
Then I guess
you have to go make it right.
Thanks, Jessi.
Comfortable?
I need to clear my head.
The tub always works for Kyle.
I thought you'd be with Andy.
Isn't tonight the big homecoming?
Her mom's extended their vacation
rental for another three weeks.
Sweetie.
I'm sorry.
I know you're frustrated.
I just want to see her.
I thought it was for
you konw, other reasons,
but today I got all mad
at Kyle and Jessi
and all I could think of
was telling Andy about it.
I just
really miss her.
The Jessi thing,
you know it's not gonna be easy, right?
I know we all got used to Kyle
and that turned out great.
I just hope we can get used to her.
So do I.
Is everything okay?
Fine.
You've been gone a while.
Do anything exciting?
Not really, no.
How about I phrase it this way.
See anyone exciting?
Actually, no, Dad, I didn't.
And thank you, Jessi.
I knew you couldn't keep
your mouth shut.
Jessi didn't have
to say a word.
I'm sure she was
a real pillar of secrecy.
I'll just go.
This isn't her fault.
Oh, that's good. Stick up for her.
Let's see how else
you can destroy my day.
I didn't destroy your day.
No? Because it was
going pretty well
until Mark told me he won't date me
because he's afraid of his future.
Good. He should be.
Why do you get to decide who
I can and can't go out with?
Because I'm your father
and you live in my house!
Real original, Dad.
Does it feel good to be
a walking parental cliché?
You want a cliché?
Go to your room!
You are not allowed back here.
I need to see her.
I don't know what you did to her,
but my daughter is back there
crying her eyes out.
- I've never seen her like this.
- I can help her.
- Please.
- Don't you think you've done enough?
Keep him out.
Two minutes.
What are you doing here?
I couldn't let you perform without
trying to make things better.
It's just...
I feel so sad.
I did this to you.
Amanda, I'm so sorry.
I trusted you.
And I broke that trust.
I hurt you. I never thought I'd do
anything to hurt you, but I did.
I love you so much, Amanda.
I love you, too.
That's why it hurts so badly.
It's not that you kissed her.
It's that I can feel what's
happening between you two.
- There's nothing.
- You don't see it. But it's there.
I can't be with you
when I know I'm losing you
to someone else.
You'll never lose me.
I already have.
I'm sorry.
One minute.
I can't do this.
I can't go out and play.
Let me help you.
I know how to fix your problem.
How?
If you have any trust
left for me at all,
let me show you.
You're on.
You have to go now.
Amanda's music
had brought us together.
We had connected that first
time I heard her play.
And now,
somehow our connection
had been severed.
Though she had never
played better,
it broke my heart to know that
because of what I had done,
she would be playing on
without me.