Previously on Kyle XY...
- The thought of you two living together
- It's not like that.
She needs a place to live, a family.
- I know, but...
- You're the only one for me.
- I never caught your name.
- Jessi.
I'm Cassidy.
I've counseled a lot of
teenagers over the years.
I have never given up on any of them.
I'm not giving up on you.
I heard you've been spending
time with Lori Trager.
- We're just hanging out.
- Not anymore.
There you are.
- I don't know how to say this.
- Mark told me he won't date me
- because he's afraid for his future.
- Good. He should be.
Why do you get to decide who
I can go out with?
Because I'm your father
and you live in my house.
I thought you'd be with Andi.
Her mom extended their vacation
rental another 3 weeks.
I just really miss her.
With Kyle I'm just a sidekick.
But out here I'd sink 'em half
the time with my eyes closed.
What did you do to Amanda?
You put something in her head.
We might be able to disintegrate it.
I'd like to help.
- You've done enough.
- Kyle, that's it.
Pass the electricity through
a kiss. You'll have to practice.
- Are you ready?
- Just try to be gentle.
- Amanda, let me explain.
- You are always trying to explain.
But there is no explanation
for why you were kissing Jessi!
I can feel what's happening
between you two.
But I can't be with you when I know
I'm losing you to someone else.
- You can never lose me.
- I already have.
The call it heartache,
a hurt so profound
it becomes hard to breathe.
I had never felt it before,
and I wondered,
will it ever go away?
I know you're hurting over Amanda.
But you have to stop obsessing.
And I have just the distraction.
The allure of a new woman.
See? Many new women.
Two dimensional, yes,
but still satisfying.
It's a safe, easy escape
with someone you love.
You!
Let music be your relief,
your way out.
You're wallowing in sorrow,
you're depressed.
You're pining.
You need A minor.
Come on, now.
With more feeling. Commit.
Great.
Trust me, you're not
the first guy to get dumped.
Think of it as a rite of passage.
Mine was tenth grade,
Beth Ann Johnson.
Beautiful, adventurous, a gymnast.
Deadly.
Stick with me, now.
I'm ready.
What are you doing?
Wiping Amanda from Kyle's memory.
Could you give us a minute?
- But I'm all charged up.
- Jessi, please.
Fine. I'll just go
zap someone else, then.
I'm kidding.
She is kidding, right?
What you're going through takes time.
But it will take even longer
the more you lay around here
and feel sorry for yourself.
It's time to get up, or man up,
whatever the phrase is these days.
- Man up?
- Out of the tub. Now.
Either that or fill it with soap
and water because you stink.
Come on.
6th Race - XY
BelXander, MiniBen314,
Ologele, Sniper2410
Saison 03 Episode 04
In The Company Of Men
Forom.com & U-sub.net
- We should go.
- Sit.
I thought Amanda
didn't work on Fridays.
You know her schedule?
That's so co-dependent.
I've been reading
some of Nicole's books.
Like it or not, you're gonna see her.
She lives next door,
so get used to it.
- If you want my advice...
- We don't.
I can't believe
he came in here with her.
- Who?
- Please. I saw your jaw clinch.
By the way, don't grind or
you'll get really bad TMJ
and have to eat creamed spinach
the rest of your life.
- Do they look like a couple?
- Pumpkin, don't torture yourself.
Just look over there and tell me.
I see a decided lack
of chemistry.
Nothing like what
Ky-manda exuded.
- She just looked over here.
- She did?
Don't look back. She'll see you.
- Where should I look?
- Anywhere. Here, look at me.
Yeah. Yeah, look deep into
Trager's eyes.
That's not weird.
Kyle, look at me.
I don't think that's a good idea.
As a matter of fact,
maybe you shouldn't be
sitting next to me.
Maybe I should just sit
at another table.
I'll make it easier for you.
Jessi, wait.
Feeling better?
Are you using your car?
What? I couldn't hear you.
Could I borrow your car, please?
For?
I want to go out.
Where to?
I'm not sure.
What, you just gonna
drive around aimlessly?
Can I borrow your car or not?
Josh has it.
Josh has the car?
Josh has a car.
His radiator's busted
so he took mine.
You couldn't just say that
in the first place?
And be straight with you? Like
you were when you went to see Mark?
Passive-aggressive
doesn't really suit you.
- You lied to me, Lori.
- You gave me a good reason to.
Jessi, is that you?
Come on in.
I was just looking at these colors.
Any preferences?
For the walls.
Not really.
Any color's fine.
It's gonna be your room.
I want you to feel comfortable.
Something bothering you?
I'm sorry.
- I shouldn't...
- Why are you sorry?
Habit.
Being in this room, I guess,
trying to get people to open up.
Just know you can talk to me
whenever you want to.
In this room or not in this room.
- I feel...
- That daughter of yours!
This green's fine.
- I should talk to her.
- Bad idea.
- I could explain.
- What? Why you kissed another girl?
Right in front of her?
You can't take that back.
You're finished, Kyle.
It's over.
Way to lift his spirits, dude.
Come on.
We're getting out of here.
- Where are we going?
- I've got just the cure.
Good magazine?
If by good you mean
trashy and trivial and
completely devoid of journalistic
value, then yes, it's fantastic.
I'll leave you alone.
Wait.
You don't have to.
It's not you.
Who is it?
My father. He's unbelievable.
He's got this bug up his ass
about Mark.
A bug?
He's pulling this big
power trip on me.
And now I am stuck here,
carless
with no place to go.
I wish I had a place of my own.
I do.
The apartment.
I still have the keys.
What are we waiting for?
There's really nothing
to do there.
It doesn't matter.
It's not here.
Are you coming?
Is this spot OK?
It's fine.
I parked here a million times.
Where are we?
Kyle, my friend,
we're at a Seattle landmark.
Little-known watering hole,
tradition passed on from generation
- to generation of teenagers.
- What is it?
A bar that doesn't check IDs.
Isn't that illegal?
Tonight isn't about technicalities.
It's about letting loose,
it's about seeing how much fun
life can be post-Amanda.
So, why are we at a bar?
You don't even have cable ?
I told you
there's nothing to do here.
Hi, Jessi. How are you ?
How are you doing ?
What are you two ladies
up to this evening ?
What did you have in mind ?
I was gonna go meet a friend
for coffee. Any suggestions ?
Try the Rack.
God, no.
It's totally lame.
Check out.
Actually, their lattes are amazing.
Well, we have to go.
Cool. Maybe I'll see you later ?
Maybe.
What's the matter with you ?
Ladies, looking good.
You want to take it down a notch ?
Ladies.
That girl keeps smiling at me.
- She likes you, dude.
- She doesn't even know me.
She feels the heat.
See ? Everyone's having
a great time.
I don't think so, little man.
- You're kidding me, right ?
- Your dad would kill me.
You're our designated driver.
This sucks.
What are you doing ?
I just...
Are you calling Amanda ?
Dude, you're missing the point.
Forget Amanda.
Forget her ?
Dude, you've been in that room
for days. You've got tub sores.
You're in pain.
Forgetting her is a good thing.
This will help.
Wait.
I tried that once
and I did not like it.
You didn't do it right.
Just do it. Come on.
And the wife says,
"That's not a pig."
And the guy says,
"I wasn't talking to you."
I don't get it.
What are you talking about, man ?
It's ingenious.
- What ?
- Everything is vibrating or something.
- Really ?
- Yes.
I feel a distinct hum.
- Dude, you're buzzed.
- Buzzed ?
Alcohol's kicking in.
I'm buzzed.
This is cool. Just us guys,
bonding over lady trouble.
What kind of lady trouble
do you have ?
Dude, Andy's been out of town
for two weeks.
And when she's here
she can be a real ball buster.
Talking about ball buster,
try your sister.
Please. I've had to live
with that for 16 years.
Why would you ever
be with her by choice ?
Her dining habits alone.
The way she slurps...
You ever watch Hilary eat ?
Tiny nibbles. She, like,
flosses after every bite.
Andy doesn't wear deodorant.
There. I said it.
What do you have on Amanda ?
I haven't thought about Amanda
for 6 minutes and 14 seconds.
It's working !
They called it male bonding.
An exercise in forgetting our problems.
And the girls
who had caused them.
I wasn't sure why I had to drink myself
full of chemicals to achieve it,
but they clearly felt
like I needed the help.
Dude, the head.
The head ?
I love you guys.
I love you, too.
No, you gotta add the guys, man.
Guys.
I love you.
Ladies.
I'm drinking
to forget my girlfriend.
Come on, it'll be fun.
Oh, my god.
And that British accent.
He was totally laying on the charm.
How could you not be into him ?
- Isn't he too old ?
- Good old, not gross old.
Popcorn.
Jessi, there is a foreign hottie out
there who seems really into you.
So ?
Do something about it.
You're available.
I guess.
You guess ? Is there a romantic
interest I'm not aware of ?
Only Kyle.
Rewind. Kyle ?
- Is that a problem ?
- Huge.
Here we go.
I think we should
get Kyle out of here.
- He's fine.
- People are starting to stare.
Now I'm making some serious dime.
OK, do you want
to win your money back ?
Nothing or double.
Double or nothing.
That's what I said.
See this glass ?
Somebody over there, catch.
Put that glass onto the bar.
I'm going to bounce this quarter
off of this table,
onto the countertop,
off of that neon sign,
off of that hanging light
and skipping it off the handle there.
- Beer tap.
Thank you.
And into the glass.
- I'll take that bet.
- You will lose.
Sir.
Just do it.
Pay up.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I've enjoyed bonding with you.
I love you.
How long have you been
into Kyle ?
I guess I've always felt
a special connection.
Aren't you guys like,
brother and sister ?
No.
But you guys both have the same
you know, no belly button thing.
That doesn't mean we're related.
You sure seem like you are.
No, it's...
more like we're from
the same village.
Is everybody
in a small town related ?
In some parts of the country.
Look, I can't help it if I think
Kyle and I are soul mates.
- I just do.
- Soul mates ?
Does Kyle know about any of this ?
He's never said anything.
But I think he feels the same way.
Or he will eventually.
Jessi, Kyle is totally,
hopelessly in love with Amanda.
But they broke up.
That doesn't mean
he's not still hung up on her.
You saw him. He's been mired
in Wallowtown for days.
Well, when will that end ?
There's no exact time.
It could take months, years,
forever to get over someone.
Meanwhile, there's an exciting
international man of mystery
who wants to have coffee
with you at the Rack.
Well, what about you ?
What about me ?
I'll be fine.
Hot older guys
always have hot older friends.
Watch this.
Do you have one of those
clappers like they sell on TV ?
Kyle, you really
shouldn't do that.
Mr. Grumpy.
Please don't do that.
What else can you do ?
Well...
Not good.
This is not good.
Where the hell is Declan ?
You're like,
a magician or something.
Nope. I was born in a pod.
I'm a science experiment.
You're funny.
- Whoa. You're bald.
- Josh, do you mind ?
- We gotta get Kyle out of here.
- Not now.
Hello.
My name is Kyle
and I am the result
of a science experiment.
Hang on.
It's Tom Foss.
- Hello, Foss.
- Kyle, I've been trying to call you.
You've been trying
to call me what ?
Are you drunk ?
Maybe.
- Yes.
- Kyle, listen to me.
Not now.
I just hung up on Foss.
Anyway, what was I saying ?
So, Latnok took an embryo
and put it in a pod with
all these X and Y chromosomes,
which is why
there's no umbilical cord.
Yes !
That is my name !
- Gotta stop, buddy.
- No.
I cannot stop.
Because I'm Kyle.
I'm Kyle XY.
Now can we leave ?
This is a disaster.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Bringing Kyle home like this isn't fine.
Kyle, are you OK?
Can't you do something like,
I don't know, alter the polarity
of your liver to process
the alcohol or something?
I can't believe
you did this to him.
Me? You were into this too
until I cut you off.
About that. I think I
have ginger ale poisoning.
No way.
Please tell me
we parked someplace else.
You lifted me
so I could reach the peaks
You made me drink
so I could hardly speak
What can I get for you?
I hear your lattes are exceptional.
I wouldn't go that far,
but they don't disappoint.
I'll have one of them, then.
Nonfat.
Sorry. Have we met?
I don't believe
I've had the pleasure.
One latte, nonfat.
- I'm Lori, by the way.
- Michael Cassidy.
- Here's my friend.
- A friend.
- I want you to meet him.
- Absolutely.
Thanks for the ride.
No problem.
Thank you.
Man. Now my butt smells
like cabbage.
What else is new?
The window.
Hey, man, our car got towed
in front of the Wild Coyote.
It's my dad's SUV.
Your have daddy's car towed.
You guys might lose your Xbox
for a few days.
I need to see your driver's
license and your registration.
The registration's in the car.
- That's a problem, isn't it?
- Come on, man.
Do you...
understand the absurdity
of the conundrum that you presented?
How is that?
You asked us to show you
our registration to retrieve our car.
But our car
is locked behind a fence
that you won't let us get to.
That is incredibly stupid.
Are you calling me stupid?
No, sir.
Not at all.
Can we just work something out,
or...
Sure. I'll tell you what.
You give me 200 bucks, I'll let you
go back and get your registration.
See, yeah, I don't...
I don't have $200 on me.
Well, you know, I guess
you're gonna have to call Daddy.
You're good boys, aren't you?
What the hell are you doing?
Why would you invite Lori Trager
here if you knew you were meeting me?
I don't see the problem.
Is there a problem?
You told me not to see her.
Change of plans.
- A change of plans?
- I changed my mind.
I thought you'd be happy about it.
Whatever.
- Are you purging?
- Yeah.
I just tossing out everything
dated last century.
So you realize
all the kids are out?
I want to finish.
Are you mad at me?
Just busy.
You are mad at me.
Why?
I'm not mad.
It's just...
here I was,
trying to reach out to Jessi,
something I rarely
get a chance to do.
And you barge in here
with the same nonsense
about Lori and her bad attitude
or whatever it is you call it.
- She lied to me.
- I know that.
But there was no good reason
for you to object to her seeing Mark.
- Mark's two years older.
- You're four years older than me.
She's in high school
and he's in college.
He's smart, he's responsible.
The kind of boy
we want her to be with.
But you laid down the law
and she broke it.
- So you got all puffed up.
- Puffed up?
She didn't do what
you wanted her to do,
and your ego took a hit.
Is that all?
That's all.
Almost there.
Why are we doing this again?
To get your registration from the car.
Am I bleeding?
Your turn.
- Show off.
- Just look for the car.
I can't believe we're doing
this. This is all..,
My fault. Acknowledged. I was just
trying to make Kyle feel better.
I don't. I feel terrible.
- It'll pass.
- I don't feel better about anything.
Are You gonna start in on me too?
You should have let me call
Amanda when I wanted.
Fine. You know what? Go ahead,
call her. Beg for forgiveness.
You'll probably pull it off,
too, 'cause you're Kyle.
Perfect Kyle. You always know
just what to do.
- What was that about?
- I don't know.
I feel sick.
Don't leave me, buddy. Come on.
I feel really sick.
Holy crap.
What did you do?
I altered the polarity of my liver
to return my body to homeostasis.
That's what I said.
- You stole the car?
- It's your car. Get in.
- Get out!
- What?
You're drunk. I'm not getting in
the car with you. Get in back.
- Stay where you are!
- We're all gonna die.
Get back here!
Great. Just great.
At least I got your car back.
You've been really awesome
tonight. Thank you.
It's just a flat tire.
We can fix it.
Kyle can twitch his nose
or channel his chi or something.
We all know you're the man.
You're the savior. I'm the screw up.
- What are you talking about?
- What am I talking about?
Just... Just fix it.
I will.
What's taking so long, huh?
Come on, work your magic.
- Why are you acting like this?
- You got a problem?
Stop.
Come on.
You guys should be looking after
me, not the other way around.
This is crazy.
I'm the sober one.
I'm the designated driver.
I'm refereeing the fight.
And giving girl advice.
When you think about it,
I'm the only one with a
successful, functioning relationship.
What am I doing with
you two losers?
So, what are you doing
with your life now?
Are you going to college
or you working?
I'm not that old.
You are very mature.
I've had to learn quickly.
It shows.
I haven't seen you
around the apartment.
My mother...
she left.
She left me.
I'm sorry.
I'm all right.
It's OK if you're not.
You will be.
- Let me explain.
- What?
How you like jerking girls around?
Becaue, one minute you're into me,
then suddenly you're not.
We play the whole
"accidental run-in thing."
And then you gave me a kiss,
which from my vantage point
you seemed to like a whole lot.
And then, boom, suddenly
you don't want to defy my father
or jeopardize your future
or some other lame-ass excuse.
- But it's...
- Let me finish.
I thought we had something,
but clearly you don't.
And the least you could have done
was been man enough to be honest.
Excuse me.
Did I do something?
Why are you so angry?
If you ask me,
he's still hung up on Lori.
It's not about Lori or Hilary.
It's not about girls at all.
- You're not, uh...
- It's about my ankle, you idiot!
I went to see a specialist
the other day.
Top foot guy around.
Treats the Seahawks
and the Sonics.
Turns out there's
this little bone.
Talus or something.
Anyway,
mine's been fractured
for like, years, he said.
Maybe if they would
have caught it...
They didn't.
So I've been playing on it.
Never healed right.
What about the surgery
you had before?
It's a different part of the ankle.
Just one of those things.
Diminished function,
I think they call it.
Basketball's history.
I should have cracked a book
once in a while, I guess.
I'll uh, get the spare.
- Are you in pain?
- Some.
Is that why you wanted
to get drunk tonight?
To forget?
Maybe, yeah.
You step up and face your problems,
but me, I run away.
For once I guess
I wanted you to do the same.
When I saw you like that tonight,
it made me feel so bad
about my life.
I understand.
Guys, I don't think
we have a spare.
Your father drives around
without a spare?
Guess so.
Now I've got to call him.
What am I supposed to say?
"Hey, Dad!
You want to come pick us up?
We just did some serious
underage drinking.
And then, after Kyle's
humongous ralph,
we shredded the back tire
breaking out of an impound lot."
Thanks for driving, by the way.
You should have seen this guy
back at the bar.
- He picked up a bald chick.
- You did?
She wasn't bald.
Her head was shaved.
There's a difference.
Cue ball.
I don't really remember that much.
You don't?
Why? Did I do something?
Nothing, really.
Gentlemen, our luck
is about to change.
Now you are gonna pay for what
you did back there, boy.
I'd like to. Eighty-five dollars
for the impound fee
and whatever
it costs to fix the fence.
I don't want your money.
What the hell are you?
All right. Keep it.
I got something better.
I don't like that she lied.
I don't either.
But I guess my
ego did come into play.
- But I didn't get all puffed up.
- How about slightly inflated?
I'm sorry I interrupted you
and Jessi earlier.
I'll get another chance.
I'll tell Lori
it's OK to see Mark.
I just hope it's not too late.
I knew Jessi was good
for something.
Mother relationships
are a tricky business.
Believe me, I know.
Did yours leave, too?
Maybe I'll tell you
more about it someday
when I know you better.
We're supposed to be closed.
Is there anything else?
Oh. Sorry, love.
Here you go.
She's a bit icy, isn't she?
I kissed her boyfriend.
Oh, really?
We always had
a special connection.
- You and her boyfriend.
- Yeah.
It's hard to explain.
But it's there.
It's like we speak
the same language,
have the same thoughts.
That is a rare thing to find.
Yeah, well...
For some reason he thinks
he's meant to be with Amanda.
Have you told this boy
how you feel?
It's complicated.
I'm living in the same house now.
Listen, Jessi,
you are a very special young lady.
You're brilliant,
beautiful, unique,
From what I've seen, that
Amanda girl has nothing on you.
And if you really do sense that
special bond between you and Kyle,
you should act on it.
How did you know his name?
I never mentioned it.
There's a lot of things
I know about you, Jessi.
A lot more than you think.
And many that you don't know
about me.
I don't understand.
I think it's time I explained.
Man, I feel like I've been hit
by a truck.
Me, too and I didn't even drink.
Is Amanda's light still on?
I can't help it.
You could always get drunk
every night.
I don't ever want to get drunk
like that again.
I don't want to forget
how much I care about Amanda
and why she's so important to me.
So, you happy being miserable?
I'm gonna have to work through it.
Nothing I can do or say
is gonna help her understand.
Except the truth.
What?
Josh is right.
Why not tell her everything?
- I can't.
- Why not?
- You told us the truth.
- It's not the same.
- Kyle!
- It's totally the same.
- Bro, I don't understand.
- Go for it, man.
I can't!
It's not the same.
Amanda loves me
and if I tell her everything...
I don't want her
to stop loving me.
You've already lost her.
You've got nothing to lose.
You know, I rarely agree
with this guy here,
but he's right, Kyle.
Nothing to lose
and everything to gain.
Seems too easy.
Sometimes the best solutions are.
I'm gonna tell her.
Dude, you made a breakthrough.
Go now.
Before you lose your nerve.
I love you guys.
After a night of mistakes
and valuable lessons learned,
I finally understood male bonding.
It's not using your friends
to forget.
It's remembering how lucky
you are to have them.
All right, go.
So.
You can give me a lift home.
Let's go.
- Foss, I can't talk right now.
- Kyle!
- I've been trying to reach you.
- I was with my friends.
Yeah. Getting drunk!
When I call you it's important.
- I'm sorry.
- You answer the phone
- and you stay on it!
- Hey!
I needed you and you were gone.
- There's been a lot going on.
- Listen to me.
- Adam Baylin...
- What?
- What about him?
- He's been deteriorating.
And I've been moving him
from location to location.
- Staying on the run.
- Why?
What's been going on?
- He wanted to see you, Kyle.
- Tell me!
Adam died today.
He died?
You may not realize it yet,
but this changes everything.