Previously on Kyle XY...
- Why are you acting so weird?
- Nicole says it's 'cause I like you.
- Don't you like me?
- Yeah, I do.
You make fun of me, you put me down, and
you always have to have the last word.
- I thought that was our thing.
- We have a thing?
- I'm Adam Baylin.
- What do you want from me?
- What would you like to know?
- Zzyzx was my conception, Kyle.
You're saying I was gestated
inside one of those tanks at Zzyzx.
So you created me.
I worked security at Zzyzx for years!
I know every in and out.
- There are innocents!
- They'd kill Baylin, they'll kill you!
- Kyle, what's wrong?
- That's him.
I am the only one that you can trust.
- What did you see?
- Adam was there?
- Baylin?
- He gave me this.
The important thing now is trying
to figure out what the message is.
Foss, I need to talk to you.
What's going on?
- Who the hell was that?
- Declan.
I never thought I'd see
you deal with anything like this.
Look, some coward jumped me. I'm not
gonna let him get the best of me.
I think you can let
yourself freak out a little.
- Her sole focus should be Kyle.
- She's been willful and defiant.
She's a computer with a glitch.
Bring her in. We'll fix her.
- Why did we come to your office?
- To get you some help.
- You remember Mr. Ballantine?
- Hello, Jessi.
I got your message.
- You're back.
- Anything come up?
Where were you?
You just took off and cleared
everything out of here.
Well, I wasn't gonna
leave it just lying around.
What is it?
What happened?
She was attacked two weeks ago.
Attacked?
You think...
You think I did it?
I wouldn't hurt her.
Did you leave that warning for Declan?
Only to keep him away, to protect you.
By threatening my friend
and hurting my sister?
I said I didn't do it.
And how could you think that I would?
That's from Baylin.
Why would he leave that?
I've been struggling with
that same question myself.
You expect me to trust you?
Tell me where you went.
Let's get back to work.
Wait!
This is it?
Just gonna walk on out?
After everything?
I'm sorry.
- Transcript : swsub.com -
- Projet-SG.net | SeriesSub.com -
Season 2 Episode 9
- The Ghost In The Machine -
There's the genius at work.
What kind of genius
plays with human life?
Adam, you're trying
to better human life.
At the cost of too many innocents.
If this one doesn't survive
the extraction process,
I'm shutting us down.
Just like that?
I'm sorry, Brian.
I know how hard you've worked
to make this happen for me.
You're damn right.
I'm not gonna let you give up.
This one's different.
That boy of yours will be our salvation.
Salvation.
Your Bible is showing.
Yeah, well ... old habits
die hard, right?
Look, your friend Kern has, um,
finally lost it.
I already told you
I can't let you in there.
- What are you talking about?
- I will not allow you
to extract the subject.
The subject is a person,
William! A child!
You're letting your
emotions cloud your science.
I thought I taught you better than that.
- Adam.
- Get your hands off me.
This is my company!
Well, you're the only ones
- who still think so.
- What?
Let's just say your backers are
a little more motivated by my plan.
Your plan?
You were a frustrated
academic worried about tenure
before Adam brought you in here.
What I know is that
781227 is more valuable
to this company if it remains inside.
You can't keep him in
there like he's some machine.
He is a person!
A human being!
Well, that's not how I see it.
Then you and I have a problem.
Foss' words kept ringing in my head.
He'd done so much for me,
and we'd been through so much together,
it was hard for me
to accept his betrayal.
So how'd it go ?
- We're done.
- Good riddance.
Foss was bad news.
- I know you don't like him, but...
- What?
He threatened to hurt Lori
and then she gets beat up.
Then Baylin, the guy you said
had the answers
-  to everything leaves you a warning.
- Okay.
I get it.
We got a bigger problem anyway.
Lori's got this screwed-up idea
to drive to a spot in the woods
where some hunter was killed.
Why?
I think she's trying to prove
she's not traumatized
by what happened at the dance.
So she found the scariest
thing she could get into.
That sounds like a terrible idea.
You haven't heard all of it.
That spot in the woods?
- It's right where Zzyzx used to be.
- We're not going.
- Excuse me?
- Declan told me where you wanna go.
I'm going.
If you guys wanna flake, fine.
Whatever it is, me and Andy are in.
No one invited you.
- Rude.
- I meant "you" as in "him." No offense.
None taken.
Wait a minute.
Dad's away on business.
So that typically means a night
of watching old musicals with Mom.
So I may have to show her my Lori file.
And I have to warn you,
I have photos.
Welcome aboard.
That's Amanda.
- Hey.
Yo. Amanda. You should get
the scoop about tonight's big event.
- What big event?
- Lori Trager's excellent adventure!
No one's going anywhere.
Don't be such a buzzkill.
She's in there.
Listen...
I need you to do me a favor.
I want you to read Andy's mind.
I don't know. Note her sweat
glands, analyze her aura.
Work your extraterrestrial mojo.
What are you talking about?
I think I like her...
in that "I wanna be alone with
her in a dark place" sort of way.
Oh.
And I need to know
if she feels the same way about me.
Your sister said
since you have a job now,
you're paying for the gas.
Tell her no... and feel free
to slap her upside the head.
She thought you'd say that.
She said to mention how your dad might
like to know who crashed his laptop.
Blackmail runs in the family.
We need serious munchies.
We should find someplace else to go.
What would be creepier
than the scene of an actual murder?
My mom's been on the warpath lately.
You guys can go, but I better stay here.
Come on, Amanda.
Where's your sense of adventure?
Whoever killed that hunter
could still be out there.
That sounds really appealing.
Trager, this is lame.
We're not 12-year-olds at summer camp.
Hey, Kyle.
Hey, Jessi.
What's up?
How did you get in here?
The door was open.
Well, we were just leaving.
- Can I come?
- You don't even know where we're going.
Because we're not.
Great.
I'll just stay here with you, then.
New player on the field.
What are we waiting for?
- Amanda, I though you said...
- I changed my mind.
You coming?
- All right.
- And then there were seven.
Come on, you guys, keep up.
Whatever, bossy.
This is the murder site.
I looked it up online.
Lori, are you okay?
You keep drinking.
I really appreciate the whole
"concerned brother" thing, but...
let's skip the
After School Special routine.
What's this?
Don't worry.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
Then why can I see them?
You guys! Get over here! Hurry!
It's Lori!
I saw her go down there.
Trager, quit messing around!
Lori, get out! It's not safe!
What's wrong?
Zzyzx. That's a way in.
Lori, get the hell out! Now!
Cool! What is this place?
RESTRICTED AREA KEAP OUT
Get your candy asses down here!
- I have to go get her.
- I'll go with you.
Wait!
- What?
- She's your sister!
And following her into a porthole to
hell isn't part of my job description.
However, I will contribute.
Everyone stay here.
We'll be back as soon as we can.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
It's just a little... tight.
I'm sort of claustrophobic.
Careful.
Fire doors. They work on gravity.
We don't want those to come down.
How did you know about that?
I don't know, I just do.
This isn't a game
of hide and seek, boys.
This isn't a game, Trager!
Did you see that?
I suddenly found myself
transported to the Zzyzx of the past,
as if I were reliving a memory.
But how could I remember this and why?
I realized Adam
couldn't hear me or see me,
but I could watch the memory unfold.
Take him out, now!
It was Professor Kern.
Was this the moment he betrayed Adam?
Get off me!
Get off me! You're making a mistake!
Let me go!
- You can't do this.
- It's already done. Move him out.
You're not gonna get away with it, Kern.
Run!
Kyle! What is it!
Why'd you rush in here?
I think there's something here.
How'd you know that was there?
I think a ghost showed it to me.
It's not that hard.
Pick a character from the show.
Let's see.
I'm funny, likeable,
and, dare I say, philosophical.
- I'll going with Shaggy.
- Wrong. You're Velma...
with a Daphne overlay.
Kyle's totally Fred,
minus the blond hair and the scarf.
Which character are you, Jessi?
I've never seen Scooby-Doo.
What? The Mystery Machine?
Scooby Snacks?
Subversive plot references?
- Where are you going?
- To find Kyle.
But he told us to stay here.
Do you always do
what people tell you to?
I just thought it'd be
safer if we all stayed put.
Then stay put.
Catfight.
Alone at last.
- Think you can get a fire going?
- Not a problem.
What if Zzyzx is haunted?
There's no such thing as haunted.
People hear scratches at the window,
it's just a tree in the wind.
- Foss.
- What?
I followed Foss and once
again stepped into the past.
When I saw the pod,
I realized this is the room where
I spent the first 16 years of my life.
As I looked at myself,
I wondered what they
were doing to me all those years.
Did anyone care what I was feeling?
I don't know why
you insist on playing that.
It can't comprehend it.
I'm prepping for a data
input retention test.
Don't let anyone through the door.
Data input retention test.
Do your job.
You know, one of these days,
he's gonna tell you what
you can do with your tests.
What was a data input retention test?
And why was Foss so concerned?
We're losing the sun here.
How's that fire coming, Prometheus?
I almost got it.
I thought you'd be better
at rubbing wood.
I need a breather.
I can't believe you brought
Sour Patch Kids but no matches.
Such a wimp. It's not that cold.
Where are they already?
Kyle's with them. No worries.
What's to worry about?
All of our friends just disappeared
into a big black hole
in the middle of nowhere.
- What?
- Nothing.
Then stop staring at me like that.
I wasn't. I was just
thinking about that...
drainage pipe.
Where does it lead to?
A government LSD lab?
A secret prison where inmates
fight to the death to be set free?
You play way too much G-Force.
- All right. What do you think it is?
- How about a drainage pipe?
Okay. I get it.
You're scared, so you mask it
- with extra-strength sarcasm.
- I'm not scared.
Being afraid of
things is a big waste of time.
You're staring again.
This seemed like such
a good idea four beers ago.
Lovely.
Are you a natural blonde?
Excuse me?
I heard blondes have more fun.
I guess it depends on the blonde. Why?
Kyle likes you.
I thought that was the reason.
My hair color?
Why else would he like you?
I don't know, really.
Maybe there isn't a good reason.
Do you always just say
what you're thinking?
I guess.
Does he like that you're so...
good all the time?
If you're so interested in why
Kyle likes me,
why don't you just ask him yourself?
- All right.
- No! I mean, why do you care so much?
Listen, just so you know,
Kyle is with me!
It's not supposed to be that way.
Well, that's how it is!
Once we get to know each other,
he'll understand.
Oh, I wouldn't count on it.
Kyle doesn't go for the
emotionally tortured type.
Kyle and I have a connection.
What are you talking about?
Last week, you were all over Declan!
Declan? I don't want Declan!
I want Kyle.
Trager!
Where the hell have you guys been?
Lori, get out of there!
Kyle! Declan! Can you guys hear me?
Oh, my God!
Hello?
Lori!
Declan!
Kyle! Can you hear me?
Kyle! Declan! Can you hear me?
Okay... don't panic.
You have a flashlight.
You have got to be kidding me.
Okay.
Okay, Trager, stay calm.
Please don't be a crazy guy with an axe.
No. No. No. No. No.
Son of a...
Stay here. I'll check it out.
Where am I gonna go?
What do you mean
"It's not giving back the information"?
It depends on what we ask.
Math problems are fine.
We input the question,
he outputs the answer
just like he's supposed to.
Is that correct?
Yes, that equation would take
our most advanced mathematician
- two weeks to solve.
- So what's the issue?
For one, it won't process any of
our strategic warfare scenarios,
almost like it's making judgment calls.
I'd somehow rejected the information
they wanted me to process.
It can't make judgment calls.
It's like saying
my toaster has a conscience.
When your toaster malfunctions, you go
out and buy a new, but 781227 costs...
I know what it costs.
Yeah, it's Kern.
781227 is no longer cooperating.
Yeah.
Too bad they don't have merit
badges for porn or video games.
You'd be an Eagle Scout by now.
Thanks for the vote of confidence.
It's getting late.
We should go after them.
I'm more worried about us.
This is exactly how those movies start.
They kill the impishly handsome
young comedy relief first.
Only comedy going on here
is you trying to start that fire.
Let's go back to the car.
It'll be warmer in there.
I'm not that cold.
Says the girl with two jackets on.
Dead end.
Perfect.
I could tell his fear was growing,
and I tried to keep his mind off of it.
I have a question about girls.
Don't ask me.
I just got blown off by
the weirdest one I know.
I don't get it. One minute
you think she's weird, and...
the other you're sorry she's gone.
Yeah.
I don't get it, either.
Declan was hiding another fear,
just like the one I had about Foss...
betrayal.
- You're worried Jessi likes me.
- No.
You think she does?
I don't know, but if she does,
Don't worry,
I wouldn't do that to a friend.
I kissed Amanda.
I knew it.
You had this weird morning-after vibe.
I just can't figure out if...
...we're a couple or not.
What you need is the kiss test.
This first kiss is the stuff of
romantic comedy endings.
The second kiss?
That's the one that defines
the relationship.
- So all I have to do is just...
- Amanda?
- What are you doing down here?
- Looking for you.
We told you not to do that.
- I know, but Jessi went down...
- Jessi's down here, too?
I'm sure she's fine. She's a lot scarier
than anything else down here.
Stop it!
What is that?
It's methane gas.
Must be a natural pocket beneath us.
We have to get out of here fast.
How much time do we have?
Gas could have been released
all over the complex.
There's no way to estimate
how much is leaking in.
Great. I'm gonna die
like a canary in a coal mine.
What way do we go?
There's gotta be a map or something
on one of these walls.
Complete with a "you are here" sticker?
I'm trying to get us out of here,
Trager.
Why don't you ask the ghost
to show you the way?
I was kidding.
Declan was right.
I didn't know how or why,
but I suddenly saw an escape.
Go down the hallway. Make the first left
you can. There's a door in the corridor.
That's the way out.
There's no fire doors between us and
that point, you shouldn't have problem.
- Follow me.
- Wait, aren't you coming?
- I have to find Jessi.
- I'll come with you.
I need you to be safe.
Come on.
Kern, 781227's lab.
- What happened?
- It's the cool memory matrix.
The entire Zzyzx data bank.
All research, everything we've ever done
or recorded.
- It's been copied.
- Copied? Where?
Finally, I understood.
I had copied all the data
from the Zzyzx mainframe,
including every frame of surveillance
footage their cameras had ever recorded.
I hadn't been seeing ghosts.
I'd been seeing the past.
It can't do that.
It can't make decisions
and act on its own.
That's exactly what it's doing, sir.
Well, then disconnect it now.
Kern!
Disengaging neuron...
I had spent my whole life fearing them,
when in reality, they feared me.
I was the ghost...
the ghost in the machine.
Begin protocols for termination.
I won't let you do this, Kern.
Kern wanted me dead.
But I knew somehow...
Foss had saved me.
So...
it's a nice night out here.
I'm just saying.
Despite...
everyone we know may be
perishing underground right now, it's...
a nice night out... here.
I can't take it anymore.
What is up with you?
And don't say nothing, because we both
know you've been rambling all night.
Even more than usual.
And you've had zero tolerance
for my witty banter.
If you've got something to say,
forget the jokes.
Man up and say it.
Okay.
I have a proposal.
I mean, idea.
Let's count to three
and both say what's on our minds
at the same time.
What, are we 12?
Forget it.
Okay.
Okay, I'm in.
Here goes.
One.
- Two.
- Three.
- I have cancer.
- I like you.
What?
Help!
Josh! Andy! Help!
Holy...
- Kyle!
- Jess!
Is she breathing?
I'm okay. We got to her.
You're okay. You're gonna be okay.
Hang on.
How did you...
- Where'd he go?
- He went back in.
Why?
I knew I couldn't survive
in this gas much longer.
But I had to have
what was in Baylin's safe.
As I struggled to open the lock,
I heard a voice...
Baylin's voice.
Find the answer.
You already have it.
As the gas overpowered me,
I feared I'd never make it out alive.
And I'd already died in Zzyzx once.
If I fell, I knew
I wouldn't be able to get up.
And this time I didn't have Foss
here to help me.
So I called upon everything
he had taught me,
and how he had sacrificed everything
so that I could live.
Now it was my responsibility to survive.
Come on!
Come on.
No matter how afraid
I might be at times,
I could never give up.
Oh, God.
Say something if you're okay.
I'm so sorry about tonight.
I guess I should have let you give me
your "After School Special" routine.
That's okay.
Forgiving is what concerned brothers do.
I'll be right back.
Some night, huh?
It sucks, doesn't it...
when the person who turns you on
turns you off?
Did I ever tell you about
the healing power of song?
I have a feeling you're about to.
Feeling better?
When we were down there,
I saw things...
strange things... happen
and I think it was because of me.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I think the gas was just messing
with all of our heads.
I know you have to go...
but I want to say something.
You came back for me.
When you reached out for me
and took my hand,
it was the first time
I didn't feel alone.
Anyway...
thank you for saving my life.
About what you said...
Forget about it.
How am I supposed to do that?
Easy.
When you feel the urge
to talk about it... don't.
And do me a favor.
Don't tell anyone.
- Andy...
- I'm serious.
You okay?
Yeah.
I guess.
Everyone was really impressed with
the way you held it together tonight.
Lori said you were the most
responsible one there.
Responsible.
I should have been more like you.
I almost killed myself going back for
something I ended up not getting anyway.
I could have lost everything.
I could have lost you.
Is this what you wanted?
I had to pry it out of your hands.
Seems important, so I kept it.
How am I to thank you?
Does this mean you're
impressed with me now, too?
I'm always impressed with you.
Come on, I'll walk you home.
You're up late.
What's all that?
The... That message from Baylin.
I can't figure out how, but somebody
must have tampered with it.
You spent all day working on it.
Well, he had no reason not to trust me.
Neither do I.
You've always been there for me.
You're the reason I'm alive.
This was Baylin's.
Can't get it open.
We'll figure it out.
Being in Zzyzx, I was able to free
myself of the ghosts
that had haunted me.
But I still hadn't seen the real danger
hiding in the shadows.
If someone had tampered
with Adam's message,
it was someone who wanted me
to lose faith in Foss.
I had searched the information I had
acquired at Zzyzx, hoping for a clue.
Take him out. Now.
Come on.
Get your hands off me.
Get off me!
This was the moment that Kern
betrayed Baylin all those years ago.
- You can't do this.
- It's already done.
Move him out.
But I was still missing the answer.
You're not gonna get away with it, Kern.
Run!
That was a little dramatic,
don't you think?
I had to be sure he bought it.
Betrayal seems to come easy to you.
It's necessary.
I only wish that I could help
him understand
that this thing is bigger
than all of us.
You know, one of these days
we're gonna have to take care of him.
I'd like to see you try.
I realized then that my instincts
were right about Foss.
The man not to be trusted wasn't him.
It was Taylor.