Previously on Kyle XY...
Then no good-byes.
- Just like "See ya. "
- See ya.
You've proven you can keep my secrets.
If there was anything to tell,
don't you think I'd bring you in on it?
I'm Adam Baylin.
You're saying I was gestated
inside one of those tanks at Zzyzx.
- So you created me.
- Yes.
You have to condition yourself,
or you're gonna die too young
before you've even had a chance to live.
This is Brian Taylor.
- Nice to meet you.
- You as well.
I've heard a lot about you.
- He's been shot!
- Zzyzx will kill him. I'll go tonight
- and eliminate the threat.
- You'll do nothing.
You'll harm no one.
- They're innocent!
- They're not innocent!
They killed Baylin and they'll kill you!
Kyle, you can't go back to the Tragers.
I lied so that I could leave,
and now I'll lie so that I can return.
I'll do everything in my
power to live by the truth.
Why do you wanna go back,
complicate your life?
It's not complicated. It's simple.
I love them.
- Oh, Kyle...
- This is great.
It's so good to see you again.
- How long can you stay?
- What are you doing here?
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
Did your parents come with you?
Let's give this guy a chance
to catch his breath here.
Are you okay?
I'll never forget that
look on their faces,
the joy and relief.
They seemed so happy to see me.
I wanted to tell them the truth
about everything that had happened,
but I wanted to be at home
with them even more.
Is that your folks?
And that meant playing
my part in the charade.
- Mr. Trager ?
- Yes.
My name's Brian Taylor.
I'm the attorney for
David and Julia Peterson.
Attorney?
- Well, come on in.
- Thank you.
Is everything all right?
I'm sorry to have to tell you this, but
David and Julia were killed
in a car accident last week.
My God.
What are you doing?
Thank you.
It's not even my birthday.
The hell?
No belly button?
No, no, no. Don't be scared, sweetheart.
We can be friends.
You want some?
Here.
Warm you up.
Go on.
There. Yeah.
That wasn't very nice.
Now, you gotta be nice.
You wanna play?
Let's play.
Give me the knife.
Give it to me!
Why you little...
- Transcript : swsub.com -
- Projet-SG.net | SeriesSub.com -
Season 2 Episode 2
- The Homecoming -
Get me Hollander.
According to the police report,
David lost control of the car and it
plunged into a canyon.
The gas tank was punctured and the...
- car caught fire.
- Oh, that's horrible.
But for the grace of God, Noah decided
to sleep in that morning.
Otherwise, we would be having
a far more difficult conversation.
And you say this happened a week ago?
That's right.
Well, I'm just surprised that Kyle...
Sorry, we'll still not used
to his real name.
Oh, I understand.
Why didn't he contact us sooner?
Well, he missed you terribly.
And to be honest, I...
Well I had to insist
that he come here at all.
He was rather reluctant to involve you
and your family again.
Why?
He felt that he'd already
been enough of a burden.
Kyle's never been a burden.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
See, Julia and David named you
as his permanent guardians.
His... guardians?
It's not that we don't want Kyle.
We went through so much
when we lost him the first time.
If he stays here and another relative
comes to take him away again...
There are no other relatives,
Mr. and Mrs. Trager.
It's a lot to take in.
I understand. You need time to think.
We're staying at a
hotel near the airport.
Would it be all right
if he spent the night here?
I'm... I'm sure he'd like
that very much.
I'm planning on leaving
town tomorrow evening.
Really the only question
for me is whether
I'm buying one plane ticket or two.
Mom was having a symbolic moment.
A way of letting you go.
Well,
I always knew you'd be back.
You did?
Not like this...
but, yeah.
Kyle, are you okay?
I mean...
I'm sorry. I know that sounds lame.
No.
I don't know what else to say.
You don't have to say anything.
So, is it weird
being back here?
A little.
There.
That's better.
Glad to see it?
Very.
Welcome, Emily Hollander.
Ms. Hollander, you've handled some...
unusual assignments for us before.
I like unusual.
This case is no exception.
In fact, it's a highly sensitive matter
that requires the utmost discretion.
Well, now I'm intrigued.
Madacorp is like an iceberg.
Most of its interests lie
beneath the surface.
As did Zzyzx,
one of our research facilities.
I say "did" because Zzyzx
was fire bombed this week.
By whom?
That's unclear at the moment,
but there is a...
much more pressing concern.
Zzyzx experimented
with artificial reproduction
and produced two primary assets.
The first was a male called "XY."
He was terminated sometime
last year for reasons unknown.
The second is a female, XX.
She apparently survived the bombing
and escaped.
Escaped?
I take it the subject
has outgrown her petri dish.
She's fully-developed.
Human, yet not human.
She's had no contact
with the outside world.
Consider her dangerous,
unpredictable, and disoriented.
She's likely still wandering
around the woods near Victor Falls.
And I assume
that you don't want her to go camping.
I want her here.
There's no telling what she might do
and we can't
risk any exposure to the company.
Shouldn't be too much
of a challenge for you.
I know what you accomplished in Iraq.
I'll find her for you, sir.
I wish you'd let us know.
We would've flown out there
to be with you.
Everything happened so fast.
Well, you're here with us now.
It's okay, you know?
It's normal if you...
feel some anger
or a sense of injustice...
Injustice?
You finally reunited
with your parents and...
Things don't always turn out
like you expect them to.
Well, you need anything else?
No.
Thank you.
Sure.
It's so good to see you again.
Good night.
I couldn't help but think back to
the last night I'd spent in this room.
It was the beginning of my secret life,
before I left with the Petersons.
And now I was home,
hiding even more secrets.
I could only hope
that whatever fate had in store for me,
it would be kind and forgiving
to the people I loved.
What a day.
I'm exhausted.
It's just so hard to believe.
I know.
You kept sensing something was wrong.
I never dreamed of anything like this.
You're not feeling guilty are you?
I can tell you're happy
that Kyle's home...
miserable about the reason.
When did you become
the psychologist in the family?
I learn by osmosis.
I missed Kyle so much...
and I'm thrilled that he's here, but...
I don't want to lose him again.
You heard the lawyer.
Yeah, there are no relatives
that he knows about.
I mean, there's still so much
that we don't know.
What about those years
when Kyle was missing?
We still don't know
what happened to him.
Yeah, well...
I guess we're always going
to have questions.
The only one we could answer
right now is, do we want him to be...
part of our family?
Okay, just remember, Kyle's been
through a lot, so be extra sensitive.
- Why you looking at me?
- Cause you're such
a model of tact and compassion.
Fine. I won't speak.
Can we have that in writing?
Guys, stop.
The point is Kyle needs our support.
But don't press him.
Let him deal with this in his own time
in his own way.
- Good morning.
- Morning!
- Sleep okay?
- I haven't slept so well in days.
Nothing beats a cold slab of porcelain.
Sorry.
- Are you hungry?
- I'll make pancakes.
I missed your pancakes.
I think we're out of syrup.
- Who finished the syrup?
- I didn't know we were rationing.
- It's okay.
- I'll go get some more.
No, wait.
You don't have to be so nice.
Just be yourselves.
You know what I mean.
You're all trying to make me feel better
and I appreciate it, but the truth is...
just being here is enough.
Excuse me.
- Hello?
- How did it go?
Fine.
- Are they there right now?
- Yes.
We need to talk.
So meet me later like we agreed.
Okay, I will, good-bye.
Was that Mr. Taylor?
Cool phone.
- You know, I could use a new one.
- Good. Go buy one.
- Seriously?
- Sure.
Just as soon as you get
that after-school job to pay for it.
Check the job board at The Rack.
I'm meeting Declan there for lunch.
How is Declan?
An eternal ray of sunshine.
He's in a gunk.
A what?
A guy funk. Totally gender-specific.
You should come with.
Maybe you can shake him out of it.
If a guy funk is a gunk,
then what's a girl funk?
Redundant.
It's Hollander. I found our girl.
Or at least what she left behind.
Where are you?
In the woods, east of the Zzyzx complex.
How long ago since she was there?
By the looks of things, it couldn't
have been more than four or five hours.
Is there anything
I should be concerned about?
Not unless you count the dead guy
covered in pink goo.
Clean it off.
So nothing can be traced back
to the company.
What the...
What is it?
Hold on.
She must be exceptionally strong.
You forgot to mention that.
As I told you, I have no idea
what she's capable of.
Find her before she kills again.
Is that clear?
Crystal.
What's the trick?
Once you teach your mind to alter
the positive and negative polarity
of the cells in your body...
The glass will move.
Not the glass. The water inside it.
What are you doing?
Oh, hey, Josh.
- Why were you zoning out like that?
- Was I?
You were staring at that glass.
I was thirsty.
Right.
Come on, did you learn some new tricks
while you were away?
I don't do tricks.
You forget I kept records, okay?
And I'd be more than happy
to bust out that file
if you've got something new
you want to show me.
Okay, I do have something.
But we have to concentrate really hard
if we want it to work.
Absolutely.
Face the glass.
- Close your eyes.
- Close my eyes?
Do you want it to work?
Open them.
I made the water disappear.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Welcome back.
It's good to see you.
You don't look any different.
You don't look like you're in a gunk.
A gunk?
Lori thinks I'm depressed.
Are you?
No...
but you've had me
freaked out and worried.
There's no reason to be.
Right, because being
the keeper of your secret code
and good-bye message
shouldn't have given me any anxiety.
You should forget about that box.
Forget it?
It's been torturing me for months.
Everything's fine now.
No, everything's not fine.
Come on, you can't come back out of
nowhere and not tell me what happened.
Sorry, I have to be somewhere right now.
Where?
I just gotta go.
Not cool, Kyle.
After everything?
Just not cool!
What is she wearing?
Come on, now.
We need to go.
Get the ball.
Can I have my ball back?
I appreciate you seeing me.
It's my pleasure.
I understand you've got a very
weighty decision to make.
No, we love Kyle.
I mean, that's not the issue.
It's just that...
he left here with
so many questions unanswered.
Well, I'll do my best
to answer them for you.
That five-year period when Kyle was lost
and the Petersons were looking for him,
he couldn't remember any of it.
Well, he did through therapy
in Connecticut.
He was abducted
by a man named Adam Baylin.
Adam Baylin, that was the...
name of the grad student
who looked like Kyle.
Apparently,
Noah...
bore a striking resemblance
to Baylin's dead son.
He kidnapped him.
Clearly deluded, he...
raised him as his own
for the next five years.
Now, the good news, if there can be any
in these circumstances,
is that he treated him very well.
Noah said that they spent
most of their time together with
him teaching him.
Teaching him? Teaching him what?
Mathematics, physics.
Baylin was a scholar.
And as you know,
Noah's very talented in those areas.
How did Kyle end up wandering
in the woods that day?
Baylin was a very tortured soul.
He took his own life,
leaving Noah...
alone,
distraught.
Eventually, he just wandered off.
I believe that's where you came in.
Noah has come to terms with this.
He wants to put the past
to rest and move forward.
My hope is that he can do that
with the love and support
of your family.
Female Caucasian, hair black,
blood-stained shirt only.
Behavior erratic, considered dangerous.
Sighted on MacGowan,
north of Juniper Park.
You made it.
What's all this?
Baylin's belongings.
His journals and his books,
his research.
You'll understand it better than I can.
How'd it go with the Tragers?
It's hard...
not telling them the truth.
I'm going to tell Declan.
No, you're not.
I need to. He already
knows a lot of the story.
How?
Before I left, he was helping me.
There was no one else who understood.
What, and now...
And now you're back
and he's asking questions?
- I can explain it to him.
- No, you can't.
For the same reason you can't
explain to the Tragers.
- He already knows more than they do.
- Well, that's your mistake!
What were you thinking?
He's my friend. I can trust him.
You're the one who said
you wanted to come back!
You said you understood the way
things were going to work.
There are consequences
for my decision. I know that.
But you obviously don't!
Because the only logical move
is to shut him out.
I need someone I can talk to.
Then you know what?
Go ahead. Tell him...
Tell him everything.
Tell him all.
Tell him about the experiments
and the murders and the lies
that you've been perpetrating.
We'll wait and see how long it takes
before somebody else
catches wind of who you are
and what you can do
and drags you out of there!
Is that what you want?
That's... That's...
what we're here to explore.
And that's why you can't explain,
because that...
that is unexplainable.
This smoothie has chunks.
Chunks are good. They add texture.
- Hey, is that your...
- My Kyle file?
Still that alien trip?
Not unless he does something
notebook-worthy again,
which, thus far, nada.
His parents just died.
I don't think his mission
is to amaze you.
He could throw me a bone...
start speaking in tongues,
run a two-minute mile,
predict a tsunami or something.
He's only been back a day.
Give him time.
I just hope Kyle is still...
Kyle.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Hey.
How's the job search going?
I still haven't found
my ideal work situation.
Which is?
Sitting around, eye-groping
unattainable cheerleaders.
Which he does here.
Here.
You're a genius.
Please. I don't even think
you could work a blender.
Yo, you're hiring?
Anything interesting?
Oh, my God!
Kyle, what are you doing here?
I'm meeting Josh and Lori.
No, I don't mean here.
I mean here as in in town.
I got in last night.
I can't believe it.
How long are you staying?
Still trying to figure that out.
Well, make it as long as possible.
We've got so much to catch up on.
Well, let's catch up now.
I can't. I'm waiting for Charlie.
Charlie?
Yeah, you know, tall, dark,
perpetually late boyfriend?
- You're still together.
- Yeah, why wouldn't we be?
Anyhow, can we catch up later?
How about tonight?
We're going to a concert.
Believe me, I'd love to bail,
but Charlie waited in line for,
like, two days to get the tickets.
But promise me you'll find time.
I promise.
Then I know it'll happen.
I'm so glad you're here.
Me, too.
Hello?
I'm not here to hurt you.
Do you understand?
I'm here to take you home.
Okay,
I'm coming in now.
Don't do anything crazy.
Anything crazier than this.
All right.
It's okay.
Easy, now.
You're okay.
God, you're just a kid.
Hi.
My name's Emily.
That's it. Don't be afraid.
I'm here to help you.
I'm your friend.
You like the light? Yeah.
You're just going to go
to sleep for a while.
- Ballantine.
- It's Hollander. I've got her.
- Where are you?
- We're in a dockyard
about six miles west
of the interstate on Route 16
in a shipping container
near the back fence.
Well, bring her in.
Yeah, there's something here you're
going to want to see for yourself.
Kidnapped?
I know.
- It's tough to hear.
- It's horrible.
His amnesia helped protect him
until he was ready
to deal with the experience.
Fortunately, Kyle seems
to have made peace with it.
Josh? You okay?
Yeah, but a kidnapping.
It's just so...
ordinary.
Yeah, it's great that Kyle's okay,
but this completely blows my alien
abduction theory out of the water.
There is something
seriously wrong with you.
Look, we just wanted you both to know
everything before we make
our final decision.
When Kyle first came here, everything
about him was a mystery and
now it's all clear.
And what we're left with is a boy.
A remarkable boy who has no one else
in the world but us.
And once we sign those custody papers,
he'll be one of us.
Here to stay.
Of course you should sign.
Kyle's still the man.
Even if he is ordinary.
Tough day?
What are you doing here?
Listen, man, I get
that whatever you have to say
is gonna be a little off
the chart of normal,
but I can take it.
I really can't talk about that.
- Why?
- Because I don't want to lie to you.
- Well, then, tell me the truth.
- That's not possible.
I don't understand any of this.
That guy Tom Foss hid
cameras in this house.
Someone came after you with a gun, Kyle.
It's all been taken care of.
What are you... What are you
talking about? By who?
Do you have any idea what I've had
to deal with, keeping your secret?
I've been lying to Lori for months,
I can't focus, my grades are screwed,
my dad is all over me...
the only thing
that's kept me remotely sane
was knowing that one day you would
tell me what the hell you got me into
and it would all be worth it.
Look me in the eye
and tell me all of it was for nothing.
It wasn't for nothing.
And I can't say any more.
Our girl's been busy.
They offer art classes at Zzyzx?
Must be all the people that she came
into contact within the last 48 hours.
Can't be.
Who is he?
The other asset.
XY?
Thought you said he was terminated.
That's what I was led to believe.
But if she saw him out there...
Your next assignment, Ms. Hollander...
has just begun.
- Boy, I'm starving.
- That looks good.
I didn't hear you come in.
Everything all right?
I know my coming back here
hasn't been easy.
The last thing I want to do
is make trouble for you.
You never brought anything
but love into this house.
Would you like to tell us something?
Noah.
We know about Adam Baylin.
You do?
Mr. Taylor told me everything.
And we understand
you want to move on, so
we'll just take our cue from you, okay?
Okay.
And we'd like to sign those custody
papers and make it official.
Thank you.
Can we make one more thing official?
What's that?
My legal name is Noah...
but I'll never be anybody but Kyle.
My name is Kyle.
We'll take care of it.
They believed our story.
This is your home now.
They think Adam Baylin abducted me.
Another lie.
My lie.
I had to put the puzzle together
so that they could put the puzzle away.
I hope I did the right thing
coming back here.
You have what Adam always wanted...
a family.
Adam may no longer be here,
but his dream still lives in you.
He believed that
you could be a shining light
in a world full of darkness.
So do I.
The question now is...
can you believe in yourself?
I can.
But the secrets that put me here
are the last I'm willing to keep.
Well, then, you're already
a better man than most.
Adam wanted me to give you this.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
It's a ring.
It's beautiful.
What's the symbol?
Never seen it before.
When Taylor left,
I hoped that the lies
I had to tell left with him,
and that from then on,
I could live safely and honestly
with my family.
Kyle, come on. I'm starving.
You'd better sit before things get ugly.
So, here we are.
Here we are.
Back to normal.
Too normal.
Josh.
Let's eat.
Phone's about to ring.
The phone... it's about to ring.
How did you do that?
I'll tell you how.
He's Kyle.
- Nobody phones Josh.
- It's probably for you anyway.
They'll call back later.
Projet-SG | http://projet-sg.net
Seriessub | www.seriessub.com