Previously, on Kyle XY.
So let me understand.
The boy has no family that you know of.
He doesn't communicate, and he was
found wandering alone in the city.
But there is one more thing
we should see.
- No belly button.
- I have a new patient,
and I'm bringing him here
for a little while.
- You don't know him.
- Don't want he touches my things.
He's a very sweet, very special boy.
He's this super brain... with amnesia.
He can't understand the simplest things,
but does calculus like it's 2 plus 2.
He barely knows what
you're saying sometimes,
but somehow speaks Chinese?
Mom, I'm telling you, Kyle is not human.
781227.
Spelling out your alien birthday?
It's you!
1985?
The guy in the photo.
It's Adam Baylin.
Adam Baylin has been
missing for 20 years.
You gotta stop asking questions!
If you don't, you're gonna put
your family in danger.
- Who are you?
- It's Mom.
The Peterson's live in Connecticut.
I'll be ready to go by tomorrow.
Now that I know, I'm ready.
You're not telling me something.
You've proven you can keep my secrets.
If there was anything to tell,
don't you think I'd bring you in on it?
- Thanks for everything.
- Take care, kid.
I'll take care of 781227
and Adam Baylin.
In the meantime, 781228
is in excellent condition.
What did you tell him?
To go with the Petersons, it was the
only way to keep Tragers out of danger.
You two are very good liars.
It's our job.
I'm Adam Baylin.
- What do you want from me?
- What would you like to know?
Everything.
He's home.
Home?
With his parents.
It's okay. It's just another dream.
I have a...
bad feeling.
Kyle's okay.
There's nothing to worry about.
Come on.
- Transcript : swsub.com -
- Projet-SG.net | SeriesSub.com -
Season 2 Episode 1
- The Prophet -
Every story has a beginning.
Every life has meaning and potential.
But I didn't know my story's beginning,
nor realize my true potential,
until a few month's ago
when I first met Adam Baylin.
I've waited a long time
to meet you Kyle.
There's so much that I want to tell you.
There's so much that I want to know.
I'll answer all of your questions...
at least the ones that I can.
I want you to feel at home here.
Are you hungry?
Would you like something
to drink after your trip?
Thanks.
Try again.
What's the trick?
There is none.
The magic is in your mind.
You only need to discover
and release it.
Teach me.
We'll have to start at the beginning.
Are you familiar with
Einstein's contributions?
I've read about him.
He was a genius.
No question.
Why do we think Einstein's was capable
of such brilliance and innovation
when his peers must have worked
just as hard?
He had a gift?
Or...
a head start?
The typical gestation period
for a human being is 40 weeks.
Einstein spent several weeks
longer in his mother's womb.
His brain had more time to develop.
That's why he was smarter?
Well, not just smarter.
Einstein believed it was why
he perceived the universe differently.
There've always been rumors
that Einstein conducted
a series of secret
experiments in the 1920s.
Allegedly, he tested the idea
of extending natural pregnancy,
mostly on primates,
hoping the animals would
develop superior brains.
But when the experiments failed,
they say that Einstein
abandoned the project,
although
other scientists were still intrigued.
They resurrected the experiments
in the 1950s,
this time without Einstein
and under tighter secrecy.
They decided to implant human embryos
in surrogate human mothers.
Did it work?
After many failures, there was
one successful pregnancy.
A healthy 13-month gestation.
13 months?
Unfortunately, the surrogate mother
died when the child was born.
What happened to the child?
You're looking at him.
Okay, here's the deal.
Mom and Dad really need this trip,
so you can't do anything
to stress them out while they're away.
I'm planning a weekend
of quiet reflection.
Seriously. If you have your
loser friends over, don't be total pigs.
And keep them out of my room.
Don't want their little hands
in my underwears.
That was one time
in sixth grade. God, let it go.
Okay, I think we have everything.
We don't.
Well, Lori is in charge.
Not more than one friend
over at a time, and no one
spends the night.
If you're referring to Declan,
I don't think that's a concern.
Why? Is everything okay with you guys?
We're fine...
I guess.
It's hard to tell what
he's thinking nowadays.
Forget about things here.
Enjoy your weekend.
Yeah. Just go. Have fun.
It's not like you're counting
the minutes or anything.
I'm down to seconds.
All right. We'll call you later.
If you hear from Kyle,
make sure he knows I have my cell.
And give him the number of the hotel.
What?
Can we go?
Sweet freedom.
Give me half.
Sorry. Bank's closed.
You drew this symbol.
For Zzyzx.
Zzyzx was my conception, Kyle.
My hope at the time was to create
children with more sophisticated brains,
children who could enlighten the world
and advance civilization.
So I continued the experiment.
Even if it meant harming
more surrogate mothers?
I didn't.
I worked years on developing
an artificial womb.
Finally, I designed a chamber
that I believed could work,
and I invented a fluid
that would provide oxygen
and nourish the embryo placed inside.
So there was no need
for a natural mother...
and obviously,
no umbilical cord.
And as a result,
the child would not have a belly button.
You're saying I was gestated
inside one of those tanks at Zzyzx.
A carefully monitored chamber.
So you created me.
Yes.
My first memory
is waking up in the forest,
fully grown, covered in
that pink fluid you were talking about.
How long was I kept inside that chamber?
Your whole life.
All the fine ladies showed up
tonight.
Check it out!
Party of the year!
The party's over.
Such a tragedy, Kyle.
Ever since you left,
the rowdy queen of rebellion
has become a total buzzkill.
I'm attempting thoughtful,
sober, and restrained
until Mom and Dad
get over you being gone.
Dude, you should be here.
It's, like, the whole school.
Hey, I was talking to Kyle.
- Actually, I should go.
- Wait. I want to hear how you are.
Sorry. We'll talk later.
He's always doing that.
You cut it too close.
I told you.
I'm responsible for the security here.
Two minutes, Kyle.
Two minutes...
or Zzyzx can trace the connection.
I've been careful.
You gotta stop pretending that you're
living with your parents in Connecticut.
Stop contact with the Tragers.
It's too dangerous.
It's an unnecessary complication.
It's necessary for me.
If you didn't like dinner,
you could have just said so.
What happened?
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
I just tripped over the table.
His IQ's off the charts.
His ability to avoid furniture,
well, gets him every time.
Kyle, this is Brian Taylor,
an old friend of mine.
Very old.
We grew up together.
Nice to meet you.
Me as well. I've heard...
a lot about you.
Really?
Yeah.
He tells me everything.
Almost everything.
All right, I'll check in on you later.
I'll be inside
if you need me, all right?
Kyle...
living here alone, I've...
relied on both of them over the years.
Taylor's managed to turn
my dreams into reality.
He brings any useful ideas
I have to the outside world,
and it's Foss' job
to protect me from it.
From Zzyzx?
Yes.
I sent him there to work.
He's my eyes and ears.
Why did Zzyzx order my termination?
I don't know. Years ago, I realized
that some of my backers
had other plans for the experiment.
I protested.
They tried to kill me.
- So I just disappeared.
- But you left me there.
Every time that I tried to remove
a subject from the chamber,
the subject died.
You mean the child died.
I'm sorry. It's just that...
I'm the subject.
I'm the child.
The original purpose
of the experiment was noble
and good.
It was supported by
a secret group of visionaries,
great humanitarians
known as Latnok.
Latnok?
It's Hungarian. It means...
The Prophet.
Ready to get started?
Change within,
change the world around me.
That's right.
Once you teach your mind
to alter the positive and negative
polarity of the cells in your body...
- The glass will move.
- Not the glass,
the water inside it.
The glass is just a container.
It's the content that matters.
The content.
Take a shot.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
It took me 20 years to master this.
Give yourself at least 5 minutes.
Free your mind.
And concentrate.
All the evidence of the festivities
has been eliminated.
You actually made a list?
I'm taking no chances here.
Dumped the empty bottles
in our neighbors' bins,
glued the broken picture frame,
and got the stains out of the couch.
The only thing left is making sure
you don't narc on me.
I won't say anything.
They're still gonna know.
There's always one
little thing you overlook.
No way. I've got it all covered.
Except that.
Oh, crap!
Nice save.
Hey, guys, we're home.
Hey. How was San Francisco?
Oh, we had a great time.
Just what we needed.
Yeah. How'd it go here?
Everything's cool.
No major damage?
It was quite dull, actually.
- Did a lot of reading.
- Have you heard from Kyle?
- Just a quick chat on-line.
- How's he doing?
Who knows? He signs off
so fast all the time.
Well, he didn't call us.
I hope he's okay.
Maybe he sent an e-mail.
What's this?
I had nothing to do with it.
Josh, start talking.
I had a few friends over.
Okay. How long am I grounded?
Why don't you go get
next year's calendar.
I don't know. What do you think?
We just got home.
Let's deal with this later.
What are you doing?
Trying to imagine what
it was like inside the chamber.
Must be why I like the tub.
You must have seen me
when you worked at Zzyzx.
Yeah, I saw you.
Did I know what was happening?
Was I aware?
You were in some kind of sleep state.
Did I look comfortable?
You seemed to be, yeah.
So I just stayed there
asleep the whole time?
Look, I... I don't know
what they were doing to you.
You saw me.
A person floating in a tank
year after year,
and you never bothered
to ask what was going on?
I did my job.
- Your parents are home.
- The door's closed.
Which is technically
against their rules.
If I don't break a few rules
soon, I'm gonna explode.
It's not easy being the good girl.
Well, here's your chance to corrupt me.
What is it?
Nothing.
Come on. Where's the guy who used to
crawl through my bedroom window?
I guess I'm... just distracted.
Yeah... ever since Kyle left,
just like my mom.
Comparing me to your mom.
That's not good.
Well, we all miss him, but you can't
sit around and brood all the time.
It's just... it was
pretty wild how he left.
I know. So fast.
No time for closure.
Hey, he should come visit, right?
Good luck with that.
Why are you being so negative?
Kyle's gone.
He's not coming back.
Can't hurt to ask.
Hey, Kyle. How are you?
I'm fine. How's it going with you?
No, not this time.
Tell me what's happening with you.
How are things in Connecticut?
It's all good.
Are you going out?
A little bit.
- Meeting people?
- A few.
Getting along with your parents?
Things are going well.
- Well, things here kind of suck.
- Why? What's wrong?
We're all basically craving
some Kyle-time.
So here's the plan.
Use our frequent-flyer miles
and catch a flight to Seattle.
You want me to come to Seattle?
It'd be so great if you
could surprise everyone.
- Well...
- My mom would flip out, in a good way.
Will you come?
I take that as a "no. "
I just stumbled.
No.
Something's wrong. Tell me.
The two of us share a gift, Kyle.
Our minds can enable our bodies to do
extraordinary things, like...
Swim faster. Jump off a roof.
You jumped off a roof?
I didn't know I wasn't supposed to.
Foss told me you had a seizure.
I was trying to hear
a distant conversation.
Well...
you put too much strain on your mind.
I've spent years challenging myself,
testing what I could do...
at a great cost.
My mind is stronger than ever,
by my body is failing me.
Failing you?
Your mind's potential is...
far greater than mine,
and so is the toll
it can take on your body.
You have to condition yourself
or you're gonna die too young...
...before you've even
had a chance to live, Kyle.
The timer.
It's hard,
you know?
You feel like...
everyone looks to you for support so...
You try to be strong,
as usual. You try to...
go on and...
smile like everything's
back to normal, but...
inside, you know it's not.
It's like you've made
this strange and...
powerful connection with someone,
and then suddenly, he's gone.
And you can't just...
get on with your life.
Not when you feel this void...
and this terrible sense
that something is wrong.
It just...
I really miss him.
You know, I...
I feel like I've lost
one of my own children.
You just let me know if
anything else comes up.
I will. Just keep me
in the loop on things.
Sorry.
Kyle. It's okay. Come on in.
Are you turning Adam's
latest dream into reality?
Something like that.
I heard he tripped again
the other night.
Must have scared you.
It did.
How about that, huh, Adam?
Someone else cares about you besides me.
Well...
I feel like I'm seeing double.
- Talk with you later.
- All right.
I hope I didn't alarm you.
I'm still worried about the timer.
Let me worry about that.
We should tell Foss.
No, we can't. He's too cautious.
He'll want us to leave here,
and there's still so much to do.
I want you to remember this moment.
After I'm gone,
all of my experiences,
everything I've studied and learned
will be yours.
Your mind is a powerful tool.
Develop it,
protect it.
Use it wisely.
But more important than your mind,
it's your soul that touches people.
You can touch the world, Kyle.
It's who you are.
It's who you're meant to be.
How about Shanghai Garden?
- If I see another lettuce wrap...
- Well, I can't live on pizza.
Hey, guys.
Dad, you and me :
mushroom, garlic, pepperoni.
I had that for breakfast.
Compromise: We go for sushi.
An invitation to hell.
Here's an idea:
Mom could actually make something.
What? She has time now.
She stopped working.
Look, I know your mom
hasn't been as focused lately.
Focused?
I throw this awesome rager
while you're out of town,
and she still hasn't
said a word about it.
Swift, Josh. Remind them to punish you.
And we will, believe me.
We just have to discuss how.
Make me sweat it out, huh?
Well, it's not working.
It's totally working.
Anyway, Mom's been in such a funk
since Kyle left, I asked him to visit.
- Kyle's coming?
- I don't know. I mean
I invited him but
he basically cut me off.
I haven't heard from him since.
It's gotta be tough he's trying to
connect with his real parents
while staying in touch with us.
So, what, we can't talk to him?
Well, I just think...
if we're all gonna move on
we have to let each other go.
- Ready to try again?
- I can't do this.
Well, I told you.
It takes time.
No. I don't want this.
I didn't ask to come here.
I had people who I loved,
who loved me.
I had a life.
You'll have an extraordinary life.
I don't want to hear about Latnok
or their experiments or how
I was locked in a tank.
I'm a human being.
How could you put me in there?
Why did you create
me in the first place?
I had no one.
No real family.
No one whose mind worked like mine,
who could experience
the world the way that I did.
I always felt different.
And I thought if there
were another person...
You didn't want to be alone.
I hope in time you can forgive me, Kyle.
What is it?
He's been shot!
Get inside.
- Now!
- I won't leave him!
I'm here.
Please.
There's still so much
you have to teach me.
The briefest connection can make the
strongest, most indelible impression.
Adam encouraged and inspired me
and helped me unravel
the mystery of my past
But without him,
my future seemed more uncertain
and dangerous than ever.
Zzyzx will kill him.
They had the opportunity,
and they didn't.
- They'll be back.
- Then we have to
- get him out of here.
- And then what?
And then Kyle runs
for the rest of his life?
You build him a prison
to hide like you did for Baylin
- Well, you tell me the alternative
- I worked security at Zzyzx for years
I know every in and out.
I'll go tonight
- and eliminate the threat.
- You will do no such thing.
What are you talking about?
"Eliminate the threat?"
What does that mean?
Zzyzx killed Baylin
because he knew too much about them.
You know too much, too.
No!
I have an obligation to protect you.
- Not by eliminating anyone.
- They'll come after you
- I won't let them find me.
- They'll target the Tragers
to draw you out. Do you wanna be safe?
Do ya? Do you want them safe?
Then I need to do this.
You'll do nothing.
You'll harm no one.
Have you heard from Kyle?
Not lately.
Would you know if he's traveling
somewhere with the Petersons?
He never said anything.
Well, the last time
you talked to him, did he
seem all right?
What did he say?
You know Kyle. He's a man of few words.
Do you realize that was the longest
conversation we've had in weeks?
And what a surprise.
It was all about Kyle.
- Josh, I'm worried about him.
- You're worried about him?
Right.
I threw a party while you weren't home.
There was unsupervised minors
messing around in our house.
There was underage drinking and...
inappropriate behavior and...
probably a few illegal
substances I didn't know about.
And you busted me for it.
You actually found out.
And then you did nothing.
Nothing.
By why should you?
I only live here. I'm only your son.
Feels strange not having him here.
Yeah, it does.
It seems Adam planned for everything.
He was always ten steps ahead,
preparing for every contingency.
You mean he expected...
To be killed?
He had to live with that possibility,
that fear.
As will you now.
I'll manage, like he did.
You have to disappear for a while.
We have to keep you as
far away from Zzyzx as we can.
Foss thinks they'll find me.
You let me worry about Foss.
Where is he?
I never thought I'd hear
Josh begging to be punished.
It was more than that, and you know it.
Look, I'm concerned about Kyle.
That doesn't mean I'm not attentive to
Josh or anyone else in this family.
Who are you kidding?
Do you think you're fooling anybody
and you're not concerned about Kyle.
You're being completely
stressed out and obsessed.
Steven, I can't help feeling
that something is wrong.
Well, get over it.
He's not ours to worry about anymore.
I know how much you miss him.
I know
that you can't stop caring
about him. We all do.
But Kyle is not here, we are.
We just need to feel
that you're here with us.
The heart rate is stable.
We'll move on to the next phase
as soon as possible.
- What did you do?
- Get in.
- They're innocent.
- They're not innocent!
They killed Baylin! They'll kill you!
No!
I did what needed to be done.
And you feel nothing now?
- People died.
- I know that.
- We're responsible.
- No.
No.
I'm responsible.
Those people,
they ordered you terminated.
They saw you as inhuman,
as...
expendable.
The waste product
of a failed experiment.
It's...
Keep learning what
Adam had to teach you.
Get stronger. Condition your mind
and body like he said.
He kept everything
organized, but there's just...
there's so much of it.
I just don't know where we should start.
We?
I'm gonna stay here
and read his notes
and see if I can help.
Why would you do that?
You think I'm just gonna
walk away from you now?
Sometimes
the connections you make
with other people sneak up on you.
You share experiences.
You have a history.
You form a bond.
I should take a picture.
You better do it fast. It's not gonna
last long. The natives are hungry.
Dinner's my choice tonight.
I think not.
Excuse me? I can still taste
that chili you ordered yesterday.
- Good. So you've already eaten.
- Let's not order in.
- I'm with you. Let's go out.
- No, actually,
I'd like to cook tonight.
What, is that such a scary thought?
No, no. That sounds great.
Absolutely.
And one more thing.
No phone,
no Internet, no video games for a week.
Plus,
you're getting a job.
You need to take on
some real responsibility.
Harsh.
It wasn't your fault.
Adam knew you couldn't
protect him every minute.
I hope you know that.
We should get started. You've
a lot to learn.
I won't be able to, not in this house.
Kyle, you can't go back to the Tragers.
If I stay here, safe but shut in,
I might as well have stayed
inside that tank.
I won't be able to touch
the world like Adam said
if I'm not part of it.
- You don't know what you're asking.
I know I can't tell them about
the experiment or the people who died
without making them accomplices.
I know I'll have to keep
my past a secret.
You'll be lying to them, every day.
No.
I lied so that I could leave.
And now I'll lie so that I can return.
But beyond that,
I'll do everything in my power
to live by the truth.
Why do you wanna go back there
and complicate your life?
It's not complicated. It's simple.
I love them.
Taylor will provide all the details.
I understand.
Well, you got what you wanted.
I expect you to honor our agreement.
I will.
It took a lot to get you here.
I won't let you waste your potential.
Thank you
for doing this,
for everything you've had to do.
Be worth it.
You made our favorites.
Well, I'm making up
for a lot of missed meals.
Welcome back.
Is it ready yet?
Almost!
- It smells so good!
- I know. I'm dying here.
Dinner is served.
Oh, my God.
In that moment,
all the things I'd learned about myself
all the gifts I need to develop
and all the secrets I promised to hide
didn't matter.
All that mattered was being
home with my family,
feeling that connection again...
and knowing that I wasn't alone.
Projet-SG Team
http://projet-sg.net
SeriesSub
www.seriessub.com