Prevously on Kyle XY...
We'll have to start at the beginning.
Einstein spent seven weeks
longer in his mother's womb.
That's why he was smarter.
I worked years developing
an artificial womb.
It was supported by a secret
group known as Latnok.
When you first came here,
everything in the world was new.
Adam created me,
but you are my family.
I saw you kissing Jessi.
It just wouldn't be appropriate.
It won't happen again.
When you kissed me, I felt such
a rush. Didn't you feel it?
My heart says there's
still something there.
As much as I want us to be
together, we can't.
- My Mom's changed our plans.
- Josh doesn't know?
This is our last night together.
No heartfelt goodbyes.
Tonight is about you and me.
You're going straight to bed.
- Who are you?
- Michael Cassidy.
They put enormous pressure
on me to bring you in.
They wanted their greatest
achievement on their side.
Why the interest in Cassidy?
I don't like him.
The guy creeps me out.
You know what I would like to
hear about? My mother.
I think it's beholding upon me
to tell you what sort of person
you have living under your roof.
After the explosion,
she came across a man camping.
And she killed him.
- Oh, my God.
- It's in her nature.
He murdered my mother.
She knew I was Latnok.
She was gonna kill me.
Baylin's experiment...
we're starting it up again.
Sarah found out.
I'm already a murderer!
- How did it go at the Rack?
- Just like we wanted.
- Kyle's still out there with Cassidy.
- Kyle can handle him.
You saved my life. I will take
care of this. Do you trust me?
I do.
Ruse.
Charade.
Deception.
No matter how you define the words,
they begin and end with a lie.
Here you go, mate.
My mum always said
tea was medicine for the soul.
How are you feeling?
How should I feel?
It's going to take some going through.
You've been through a lot tonight.
What are you going to
tell everyone else at Latnok?
This group here don't need
to know anything other than
what you're gonna tell your family
about Jessi running away.
But the senior
members, they know.
- You told them already?
- It's my job, mate.
Got to keep them up to speed.
But they're not even
care that Jessi's dead?
You have to understand.
You're their guy.
You always have been.
Come on.
I want to show you something.
- Was this mine?
- The one and only.
Took a little maneuvering
to rebuild it after
the explosion at Zzyzx, but,
but that's why our young
geniuses come in so handy.
They rebuilt this?
Not exactly.
They built it in pieces.
Mark's algorithms.
Nate's hoverboard magnets.
Everyone contributed something.
You tricked them.
Their inventions had
practical applications.
- That's all they needed to know.
- What did I give you?
I'm sure you can figure it out.
The growth accelerant
that Nate and I developed.
- Helps with muscle growth.
- Why didn't you just tell me
that this is what
you were doing when you brought me in?
How would you have
felt about that?
If Zzyzx had their way,
I would have spent my entire life
in this pod as some
type of bio-computer.
That's not the kind of technology
you want falling into the wrong hands.
There's your answer.
They knew you wouldn't approve.
They were right.
But...
you don't really have a choice
in the matter, do you?
Unless you want everyone you know
to know the truth about
what you did to Jessi.
Is that what this is?
More blackmail?
I like to think of it
as self-preservation.
We gonna have
a problem with that?
Look, in a couple of days,
Latnok are gonna have a
warehouse full
of specimens in gestation
to keep them occupied.
They already have
everything they need?
I have everything they need.
I give it to them...
they leave you alone.
Consider this your freedom.
My gift to you.
My lies had brought
me an offer of freedom.
But now Adam's misguided experiment
was in the hands of a blackmailer...
a murderer.
I knew I wouldn't truly be free
until I stopped him.
6th Race - XY
BelXander and MiniBen314
Saison 03 Episode 10
Bringing Down the House
Forom.com & U-sub.net
Thank God.
You're okay?
It worked. I got him
to tell me everything.
- What did he say?
- I'll explain it all, I promise.
But I need to see Jessi.
I need to know that she's okay.
I'm okay.
Your
arms are growing.
They are?
They're at least a half-centimeter
bigger in circumference.
Have you increased
your exercise regimen?
Maybe a little.
Your...
Your pectoral
muscles are also expanding.
What?
Your hand...
feels nice.
Does
this one, too?
Did you just shock me?
No. Why would I shock you?
I don't know. I...
I felt a charge
go through my body.
- That's your libido.
- What?
No it isn't.
I would have felt that before.
You never felt a charge with Amanda?
I felt other things.
Well, maybe there was a power
surge in the area.
Maybe.
So, how did you sleep
last night?
I didn't.
Neither did I.
I'm sorry you had to
go through that.
I'm sure it wasn't easy...
confronting Cassidy
about Sarah.
I was acting.
I'm fine.
I promise.
There's that power surge again.
Josh is still asleep, but I talked
to Lori about what's going on.
I'll finish getting dressed
and be right out.
I'll be in the other room,
pretending to be dead.
I'm not happy about this.
I'm sorry. Jessi came in,
and things got weird. But,
- It won't happen again.
- Not that. Well,
yes, that. But more importantly,
I don't like this game
you guys are playing with Cassidy.
It's dangerous.
I don't like it either.
I've given you a lot of leeway
in the past,
but this just feels different.
There's something about it.
Something about Cassidy...
He scares me.
I'm going to take care of it.
I promise.
I need it to be over.
We can't keep doing this
to our family.
Hide and seek with parents
downstairs is not cool.
Straight to voice mail?
Not cool.
Leaving without saying
goodbye? Even less cool.
What's wrong with you?
Call me back.
Can anyone help me figure out how to
throttle my girlfriend long-distance?
- Why long-distance?
- Because she left.
Vamoosed. Hitched a ride
on the a-train to Cleveland.
She didn't even have the
courage to tell me in person.
She left this on my pillow.
On your pillow?
Ask Dad.
Oh, I will.
Mom?
Are you okay?
You know what?
Yeah.
If she's just gonna up and
leave like that, forget her.
I'm fine.
Dandy.
Copa-freakin'-cetic.
She was probably
afraid to say goodbye.
Then she's a coward.
Good riddance.
Josh, I'm sorry.
But there's something else
we need to talk about...
Here's what I have so far.
Leave it open.
Well...
In order to fill,
say, 100 pods,
Cassidy would need at least
5,000 gallons of formula on hand.
Not to mention the space
he'd need to house the pods.
I ran a search,
and there are over 5300 warehouses
in Seattle that are big enough.
The formula would have to be
kept at a certain temperature
in order to sustain its
nutritional elements...
probably a few degrees
below body temperature.
That's a way to narrow it down.
We can access the city
police's thermal imaging scans,
like how they find the
people growing the weed.
- The weed?
- Yeah, the...
The blaze.
The herb.
The chronic.
- Where did you pick that up?
- Cable.
Once we find where
they're hiding the formula,
we need to sabotage it
so that it doesn't work.
And destroy any way of
re-creating it.
What about the pods?
How do we destroy them?
We won't need to. Without the
formula, they're useless.
Where?
I hear her heartbeat.
You're still listening
for her heartbeat?
It comes naturally now.
She's coming to the window.
You've gotta go. She can't see
you. You're supposed to be missing.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
I know this is weird,
but I really need to talk to you
and I don't want
anyone else to know about it.
What happened?
Here, come in.
- I think you were right about Nate.
- What did he do?
I found all this odd
research in his dorm room.
You were in his dorm room?
I saw the number from
the Ouija board.
When you asked
what your birthday was?
7 8 1 2 2 7.
There were drawings
of these chambers...
that could carry a baby without
a birth mother. Or an umbilical cord.
Your father's name,
Adam Baylin, was everywhere.
I know you have secrets,
and I try not to pry, but Kyle,
- it's like he was studying your life.
- Does he know you saw all of this?
You said there were people
who would use
those you care about to get to you.
Is he one of them?
I think he might be.
Why do I always do this?
Why do I always get involved
with the lying, cheating jerks?
I'm sorry.
Amanda, I need you
to stay away from him.
I can't guarantee it's safe
to be around him.
What?
It's you.
The Charlies,
the Nates of this world...
those are the real jerks.
You,
no matter what,
are one of the good guys.
I always knew you were.
Even when I thought I didn't.
I try to be.
You are.
Kissing Amanda, I felt
a rolling flutter deep inside.
I'd heard the term before,
'butterflies.'
How was it possible to feel
electricity for one person
and butterflies for another?
I think Cassidy has
Adam's data stored
on an isolated server
at the university.
I saw the system last night.
If I can get back in there,
I can swap it out with a dummy drive
and figure out if he made any back-ups.
I need to get rid of all of them.
Don't you think Cassidy
would be watching you closely?
I'll need some sort of distraction.
You can't go.
- You're dead.
- I know.
And dead girls
get stuck in the house
doing thermal scans of
Seattle's industrial district.
I almost hate to suggest it,
but what about Mark?
We don't know
if we can fully trust him yet.
I do.
I mean, based on my little
recon mission last night,
we know he's no fan of Cassidy's.
And I know it's not my life
we're talking about, but,
your secret is my secret, too.
It's all of ours.
Do we have to spend the rest of our
lives not ever letting anyone else in?
This situation is too extreme, Lori.
No matter how much you care about him.
The problem is,
we don't have anyone else
who has an excuse to be in Latnok.
That's not entirely true.
What is this, Bring
Your Mother to Work Day?
I'm sorry, Michael. I hate
to bother you like this, but,
can I speak to you?
It's about last night.
I know I wasn't the best dinner guest,
but I didn't think my behavior
- warranted a house call.
- No, it's Jessi.
She never came home.
I see. I'm sorry.
Come in.
Thanks.
So, she wasn't at her apartment?
First place I checked.
I don't know why I thought
she might come here,
especially after
your confrontation. But,
I didn't know where else to look.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
Oh, please, no.
It's not the first time
she's run away, unfortunately...
- Where did she go the last time?
- The woods.
It's a long story, and yes,
we've already looked.
She's had a rough go of it.
You used to counsel her, didn't you?
Is there a problem?
No, not at all. It's just...
It's a bit of a sore subject.
I received a warning for taking her in.
I almost lost my license.
Well, she was very lucky
to have had you helping her.
Thank you.
It's nice to feel appreciated.
You've done an
amazing job with Kyle.
All I know,
you mean a lot to him.
He means a lot to us.
Are you cleaning?
In a manner of speaking, yes.
I am cleaning my life.
I have too many things that remind
me of Andy. I am purging...
And please don't touch anything.
It's all exactly where I want it.
Staphylococcus aureus.
No. That is in fact a cup.
Inside the cup. The bacteria.
How long has this been here?
Could be this morning...
Could be last month...
Your room is the perfect
environment for it to grow.
It's warm, dark,
and a little...
- Manly?
- Dank.
Why am I letting you stand in my
room and insult me?
- Because your dankness...
- Manliness.
Just gave me an idea of how
to disable the formula.
I needed to burn Adam's journals
to erase his records of the experiment.
But I knew I was also burning
the only real connection I had
to the man who had given me life.
And the way he had given it.
Thank you for earlier.
I'm just glad it's over.
According to the hard drive,
he made a single backup of data.
I think I saw the disc in his
safe when I found Sarah's ring.
He'll have moved it by now.
Maybe to his apartment.
Now you're breaking
into his apartment?
If I don't destroy every trace
of this formula,
he'll just re-create it.
I have to make sure
that doesn't happen.
I can't help wishing you'd just
taken him up on his offer of freedom.
They're re-starting the experiment.
They're playing God!
And if Cassidy is any indication
of the kind of people they are,
- I don't want them to have that power.
- I understand.
I do. But the deeper in you get,
the more it's changing you.
- Changing me?
- You fake Jessi's death.
You're lying,
you're sneaking around,
breaking laws...
This just isn't you.
At least it's not
who you used to be.
- Thanks for coming with me.
- Are you kidding?
Being your lookout,
breaking into someone's apartment...
It's like the old days.
I'd be pissed if you hadn't asked me.
This is it.
I have the keys
to Jessi's apartment.
I'll go in there, climb through
the air-conditioning ducts,
and then drop down into Cassidy's.
Or, I could just pick the lock.
Don't ask.
Isn't that breaking and entering?
It was okay when you
were just entering?
Let's see what we find.
Cassidy's passport
and birth certificate.
- In case of a quick getaway, I guess.
- He's not using his real name.
It says Michael Cassidy Kingsley.
Mother, Grace.
Father, unknown.
Grace Kingsley.
Why does that name sound familiar?
Grace Kingsley...
Grace Kingsley was
in Adam's notebooks.
She's a member of Latnok.
Easy, killer.
It's just a game.
It's not just a game.
It's our game.
Mine and Andy's.
I thought making things explode
would make me feel better,
but it only reminded me
of how much this sucks.
It does suck.
Believe me, I know.
Lori didn't move thousands
of miles away
while you were still both in love
and leave you without saying goodbye.
All she did was reject
your sorry ass.
I have an idea.
Death by porn?
Just give me a few minutes.
I have to make a call.
If his mother knew Adam,
then she must have known Sarah.
I wonder if she knows
her son is a killer.
This is everything on the disk.
- That's the formula for the fluid.
- You found it.
- It worked.
- What did?
The thermal imaging.
That facility is storing
a large amount of something
at the temperature we were tracking.
Let's assume we're right,
and the existing formula is there.
I'll go,
add your bacteria to the fluid,
then get out before
anyone knows I was there.
I wish I could go with you.
I do, too.
We should see what else is on
the disk before we destroy it.
The pod schematics.
Step one.
Genome insertion.
Step two.
Clone development.
Clone? I thought they
used human embryos.
That's the way
it's always been done.
They must be using someone's
genetic sequence to create a clone.
- 7 8 1 2 2 7.
- That's impossible.
Latnok isn't planning
to gestate babies in those pods.
They're making clones...
of me.
- You've got to be kidding me.
- Is that even possible?
It never was before.
Now with the pods and the formula,
the development process is a
more regulated environment.
I can't even wrap my head around
the breach of scientific ethics.
It's even worse than just cloning.
Jessi and I were in gestation
for sixteen years.
That's what allowed our brains
to develop the way they did.
Without all that time,
we'd be just like everyone else.
So in order for them to create
more children like you...
They would have to be
in the pods for years.
But why just you?
Why not both of you?
They think I'm damaged.
I think we've already
established how wrong they are.
Still, Kyle is special.
It's understandable why they
would want more like him.
If I'm special, it's not because
of how I came into this world.
It's what happened
to me once I was in it.
You took me in.
You loved me like I was
one of your own children.
Having you in my life...
that's what makes me special.
But this, what they're planning, it's
robbing someone of their childhood...
their connection to a mother...
a family. I can't allow that.
Which is why we have to make
sure it doesn't happen.
- Is that mold?
- No. Mold is a fungus.
This is a bacterial agent
that will compound
exponentially when
introduced into a live organism.
It'll basically suffocate any
nutritional elements growing
in the formula,
so it won't allow anything to grow.
Of course it will.
I have to get going.
Just... Be careful.
Please.
I'll be home soon.
Are you sure
you don't need back-up?
We can't risk anyone seeing
you until this is all over.
When it is over,
what happens with your life?
What do you mean?
We'll destroy the experiment.
And then we can focus on Cassidy.
But one day soon, if we're successful,
your life will just return to normal.
I'm starting to realize
my life can never be normal.
But it would be nice to get back
to some type of constant.
Does constant mean Amanda?
I don't know what it means.
Sorry, Jessi.
I wish I did.
I wish I could understand how I could
have feelings for more than one person.
You're saying you
have feelings for me?
Why would you even have to ask that?
- What are you looking for?
- Nicole.
Why?
Good luck.
- What happened?
- The lamp blew out.
I'll fix it.
- I rock.
- Why do you rock?
And why aren't we making
me feel any better yet?
Maybe this will.
Hi.
Jackie told me how to hijack
the car's navigational system
and walk Andy through linking
up a video camera.
So even though she's on the road
in the middle of the country,
you get to see your girlfriend.
Don't understand that at all, but...
thanks, man.
Really.
You're welcome.
Where are you?
Some rest stop in North Dakota.
Declan totally hacked into our
minivan's GPS. You're lucky we have one.
Your moms are lesbians.
How could they not?
Are they... listening
to me right now?
Lucky for you, they took
my brothers in to pee.
Good, because you are in
big trouble, young missy.
I know. I totally suck.
You totally do.
How could you not say goodbye?
I chickened out.
I couldn't say goodbye to you.
I still can't.
Well, then it doesn't
have to be goodbye.
It can be hello with
a lot of miles between us.
In that case,
hello.
Hi.
You know what?
We can say hello every day
until I get to see you again.
And then every day after that.
This should only
take about 20 minutes.
Just need to cable the system
and run a quick diagnostic.
No problem.
I imagine you're not
dropping off another lasagna.
- I'll come back later.
- Sorry. But you can't leave.
- Why?
- Because you've seen me.
- Not following.
- I'm supposed to be missing
and if you tell your new boyfriend
that I'm not, you'll ruin everything.
He's not my boyfriend.
He's not anything anymore.
I told Kyle I'd stay away from him,
but he still has all that stuff
about him in his dorm room.
- Why didn't you just take it?
- I don't know.
- Because that would be stealing.
- But Nate stole it in the first place.
I guess it just didn't occur to me,
all right?
- I'm not as smart as you.
- That's true.
I just came to say that Nate's
working until ten tonight,
so if Kyle wants to get
into the room, he can.
- Kyle's not home.
- Then you do it.
- I can't go anywhere.
- You still haven't explained that.
And I don't plan on it.
Look, unfortunately,
you're gonna have to do it.
Do what? Break into his
room and steal his files?
I was thinking firebomb, but okay.
Almost done.
It's just...
You don't have to watch.
Unless you just like... lurking.
Ninety-six percent.
Ninety-seven.
- Can you hear me?
- Yeah, I can hear you.
I'm going to ghost his system.
So, basically it'll be like
I'm sitting right where you are.
Less chance for operator error.
Okay. Open up the systems file.
I need you to get his IP address.
- If you know...
- I know what that is.
Save the sarcasm.
Type it into the "share host"
box down at the bottom.
And change all the
settings to "allow."
Perfect.
There's a lot of stuff
here Nate's been collecting.
About Kyle?
See for yourself.
I've wanted to know
his secrets for so long...
Here it all is.
Yeah, well take a good look.
No. When he's ready to tell me,
then it'll mean something.
For now, this is just weird.
Always the good girl.
Not all of us can be
as wild as you, Jessi.
Apparently, you can.
Amanda?
What's wrong?
Nate...
This is Cassidy.
I caught Kyle's girlfriends
going through my stuff.
- Girlfriends?
- Amanda and Jessi.
Jessi. That's impossible.
She's... missing.
Well, if she was,
she isn't anymore.
Find out what they know.
Shut it down.
Mr. Cassidy wants everyone out of here.
- I haven't finished yet.
- We have orders.
We need to check the perimeter.
What are you doing?
What is this?
A bacteria.
- A bacteria? Why would you...
- Mark. We don't have much time.
Do you have any idea what
you've been helping Cassidy do?
Computerized in-vitro
gestational chambers.
For women who
can't give birth naturally.
I wish that's what it was.
- What are you talking about?
- Cassidy has been using you.
Latnok is not what they say they are.
And that I need your help.
I need you to trust me.
Please.
I'll distract them.
Just do what you
need to do and get out.
Hello?
You're very anxious, for someone
who's looking for a dead girl.
- I told you, I didn't see anything.
- I wish I could believe that.
I really do.
- Why did you do that?
- I thought you could use the help.
We have to get the files
and get moving.
- He's not gonna be out for very long.
- Why not?
Because you don't hit hard enough.
Better?
Where are they?
What did you do?
Relax.
They're on their way to the Rack.
To meet you, actually.
I may not be a genius, but I
know how to clone a cell phone.
Speaking of, you've put me in
quite a bind with your little tricks.
Latnok's gonna
think I failed them.
Failed them?
Or failed her?
- What?
- You know what I'm talking about.
So you found out about my mum.
You know,
if she had her way,
you wouldn't still be
living this life of yours.
Latnok would have complete
control over you, and believe me,
it's only a matter of time before she
figures out how to get what she wants.
I was going to convince her
to let you go.
All because I thought
you saved my life.
Who knew what a clever
little liar you would be?
I had no choice.
We all have choices.
Like how I
am choosing to forgive you
for what you've done
and give you a chance to fix it.
Then no one need be any the wiser.
Even if I knew how to do that,
I wouldn't.
Oh, you know.
It's all up there
in that head of yours.
Forgot about that, didn't you?
I can think of a few people
who probably haven't.
But they went about it
the wrong way in the past.
Anyone with a brain knows there's
only one way to get you to cooperate.
You figured out what
I did to get rid of Sarah.
So you know what I'm willing
to do to get what I want.
We're okay. Nate's still out cold.
That ring... looks a lot like
the one Kyle wears around his neck.
Nate stole it from Cassidy.
It belonged to my mother.
So I guess you kind
of helped me find it.
And you saved me, so...
I guess we're even?
Look, I know we've never
really gotten along, but...
I don't know.
I feel like we might be a
little bit closer than before.
So I think it's only
fair that I tell you...
Tell me what?
I'm going to tell
Kyle I want him back.
You really have
the nerve to say that?
After everything
that happened tonight?
Like I said, fair warning.
You deserve it.
You're a lot braver than I thought.
Origin...?
What is it?
I don't believe it.
You still wear Adam's Latnok ring.
How awfully sentimental.
And lucky for me.
- Why are you doing this?
- Because that is what they want.
That's what she wants.
And if you try to stop me,
I'm just gonna have to keep
hurting you.
Then,
I'm gonna hurt Jessi...
until she wishes
she had really died.
And then,
just when you think
it couldn't get any worse,
I'll hurt everybody that
ever mattered to you.
Starting with Amanda.
How you feelin' about that, mate?
Nicole had been right when she said
she didn't recognize
the person I had become.
The person I had been before
would have never done this...
- You won't do it.
- What makes you so sure?
Because Grace Kingsley, my mother...
What about her?
She's your mother, too.
I'm your brother.
Merci d'avoir suivi Kyle XY avec nous.
Espérons tous une suite !!!