Freeze!
Don't move!
Drop the knife.
Keep your hands where I can see them!
Drop it!
In a gadda da vida, baby
don't you know that I'll always be true?
All right.
I figure we'd hit tucumcari by lunch,
then head south,
hit bisbee by midnight.
Sam wears women's underwear.
I've been listening. I'm just busy.
- Busy doing what?
Reading e-mails.
E- mails from who?
From my friends at Stanford.
You're kidding.
You still keep in touch with your college buddies?
Why not?
Well...
What exactly do you tell them,
You know, about where you've been,
what you've been doing?
I tell them I'm on a road trip with my big brother.
I tell them I needed some time off, after Jess.
Well, so you lie to them.
No.
I just don't tell them
everything.
Yeah. That's called lying.
Hey, man, I get it.
Telling them the truth is far worse.
So what am I supposed to do,
just cut everybody out of my life?
You're serious?
- Look, it sucks.
But in a job like this,
you can't get close to people.
You're kind of antisocial.
You know that?
Yeah. Whatever.
God.
- What?
This e-mail from this girl, Rebecca Warren,
one of those friends of mine.
Is she hot?
I went to school with her and her brother Zach.
She says Zach's been charged with murder.
He's been arrested for killing his girlfriend.
Rebecca says he didn't do it,
but it sounds like the cops have a pretty good case.
Dude, what kind of people you hanging out with?
No, man. I know Zach.
He's no killer.
Well, maybe you know Zach as well as he knows you.
They're in St. Louis.
We're going.
I'm sorry about your buddy, okay?
But this does not sound like our kind of problem.
- It is our problem.
They're my friends.
- St. Louis is 400 miles behind us, Sam.
Oh, my god. Sam.
- Well, if it isn't little Becky.
You know what you can do with that "little Becky" crap.
I got your e-mail.
I didn't think that you would come here.
Dean, older brother.
- Hi.
Hi.
We're here to help.
Whatever we can do.
Come in.
Nice place.
It's my parents'.
I was just crashing here for the long weekend
when everything happened.
I decided to take the semester off.
I'm gonna stay until Zach's free.
Where are your folks?
They live in Paris for half the year,
so they're on their way home now for the trial.
Do you guys want a beer or something?
Hey.
- No, thanks.
So...
tell us what happened.
Well, um, Zach had came home,
and he found Emily tied to a chair.
And she was beaten up and bloody, and she wasn't breathing.
And so he...he called 911.
And the police, they showed up, and...
and they arrested him.
But the thing is,
the only way that Zach could have killed Emily
is if he was in two places at the same time.
The police, they have a video.
It's from the security tape from across the street.
And it shows Zach coming home at 10:30.
Now, Emily was killed just after that,
but I swear he was here with me,
having a few beers until at least after midnight.
You know, maybe we could see the crime scene,
Zach's house.
We could?
Why?What could you do?
- Well, me, not much.
But Dean's a cop.
A detective, actually.
Really? Where?
Bisbee, Arizona.
But I'm off duty now.
You guys, it's so nice to offer, but I just...
I don't know.
Beck,
Look.
I know Zach didn't do this.
Now, we have to find a way to prove that he's innocent.
Okay.
I'm gonna go get the keys.
Oh, yeah, man.
You're a real straight shooter with your friends.
Look,
Zach and Becky need our help.
- I just don't think this is our kind of problem.
Two places at once?
We've looked into less.
You're sure this is okay?
Yeah.
I am an officer of the law.
Beck, you wanna wait outside?
No. I wanna help.
Tell us what else the police said.
Well...
there was no sign of a break-in.
They say that Emily let her attacker in.
And the lawyers are already talking about a plea bargaining.
Look, Beck...
if Zach didn't do this,
it means someone else did.
Any idea who?
Um, there was something.
About a week before, somebody broke in here
and stole some clothes
Zach's clothes.
And the police,they don't think it's anything.
I mean, we're not that far from downtown.
I mean, sometimes people get robbed.
You know, that used to be the sweetest dog.
What happened?
He just changed.
Do you remember when he changed?
I guess around the time of the murder.
So the neighbor's dog went psycho
right around the time Zach's girlfriend was killed.
Animals can have a sharp sense of the paranormal.
Maybe Fido saw something.
So you think maybe this is our kind of problem?
No. Probably not.
But we should look at the security tape just to make sure.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
So the tape, the security footage?
Think maybe your lawyers could get their hands on it?
I just don't have that kind of jurisdiction.
I've already got it.
I didn't want to say something in front of the cop.
I, um,
I stole it off the lawyer's desk.
I just had to see it for myself.
All right.
Why do they always have to send you?
Because I'm the best.
I know.
That's why I want you to stay home.
It's just Kansas city.
I'll be home tomorrow night
and make it up to you.
Here he comes.
22:04 That's just after 10:00.
You said time of death was about 10:30.
Our lawyers hired some kind of video expert.
He says the tape's authentic.
It wasn't tampered with.
Hey, Beck, can we take those beers now?
Oh, sure.
Hey, uh...
maybe some sandwiches, too?
What do you think this is, hooters?
I wish.
What is it?
Check this out.
Maybe it's just a camera flare.
That's not like any camera flare I've ever seen.
A lot of cultures believe that a photograph can catch
a glimpse of the soul.
Right.
- Remember that dog that was freaking out?
Maybe he saw this thing.
Maybe this is some kind of dark double of Zach's
something that looks like him but isn't him.
Like a doppelganger.
That would sure explain how he was two places at once.
Honey, it's me.
Client canceled at the last minute.
I called.
Why didn't you answer?
Lindsay?
Lindsay?!
Oh.
It's okay, Lindsay. It's me.
Please, don't hurt me any more.
Leave me alone.
All right.
What are we doing here at 5:30 in the morning?
I realized something.
The videotape shows the killer going in but not coming out.
So he came out the back door?
Right,
so there should be a trail to follow,
a trail the police would never pursue.
'Cause they think the killer never left.
They caught your friend Zach inside.
Still don't know what we're doing here at 5:30 in the morning.
Blood.
Somebody came this way.
Maybe the trail ends. I don't see anything over here.
What happened?
He tried to kill his wife.
Tied her up and beat her.
Really?
I used to see him going to work in the morning.
He'd wave, say hello.
He seemed like such a nice guy.
Hey.
Remember when I said this wasn't our kind of problem?
Yeah.
- Definitely our kind of problem.
What did you find out?
I talked to the patrolman who was first on the scene.
He heard this guy Alex's story.
Apparently the dude was driving home from a
business trip when his wife was attacked.
So he was two places at once.
Exactly.
Then he sees himself in the house.
Police think he's a nut job.
Two dark doubles attacking loved ones in exactly the same way.
Could be the same thing doing it, too.
Shapeshifter?
Something that can make itself look like anyone?
Every culture in the world has a shapeshifter lore;
legends of creatures who can transform themselves
into animals or other men.
- Right, skinwalkers, werewolves.
We've got two attacks within blocks of each other.
I'm guessing we got a shapeshifter
problem in the neighborhood.
Let me ask you this.
In all this shapeshifter lore,
can any of them fly?
Not that I know of.
- I picked up a trail here.
Someone ran out of the back of this building,
headed off this way.
Just like your friend's house.
Yeah.
And just like at Zach's house,
the trail suddenly ends.
Whatever it is just
disappeared.
Well, there's another way to go.
Down.
I bet this runs right by Zach's house, too.
The shapeshifter could be using the sewer system to get around.
I think you're right.
Look at this.
Oh.
Is this from his victims?
You know, I just had a sick thought.
When the shapeshifter changes shape,
maybe it sheds.
That is sick.
Well, one thing I learned from dad
no matter what kind of shapeshifter it is,
there's one sure way to kill it.
Silver bullet to the heart.
That's right.
This is Sam.
Where are you?
We're near Zach's.
We're just checking some things out.
Well look Sam, just stop, because I really don't need your help anymore.
What are you talking about?
I told the lawyers that we went to the crime scene.
Why would you do that?
I told them that we were with a police officer.
And they checked it out,
and they told me there is no detective Dean Winchester.
Beck
I don't understand why you would lie to me about something like that.
We were trying to help.
Oh, trying to help?
Do you realize that that was a sealed crime scene?
This could have just ruined Zach's case.
Beck, I'm sorry, but...
- No. Goodbye, Sam.
I hate to say it, but that's exactly what I'm talking about.
You lie to your friends because if they knew the real you
they'd be freaked.
It's just
It'd be easier if...
- If I was like you.
Hey, man, like it or not, we are not like other people.
But I'll tell you one thing.
This whole gig...
..it ain't without perks.
I think we're close to its lair.
Why do you say that?
'Cause there's another puke-inducing pile next to your face.
Oh, God.
It looks like it's lived here for awhile.
Who knows how many murders he's gotten away with?
Dean!
Get this son of a bitch!
All right. Let's split up.
All right. I'll meet you around the other side.
Hey.
Anything?
No. He's gone.
All right. Let's get back to the car.
You think he found another way underground?
Probably.
You got the keys?
Hey, didn't dad once face a shapeshifter in San Antonio?
That was Austin.
And it turned out not to be a shapeshifter.
It was a thought-form
a psychic projection. Remember?
Oh. Right.
Here you go.
Don't move!
What have you done with him?
Dude, chill.
It's me, all right?
- No, I don't think so.
Where's my brother?
- You're about to shoot him.
Sam, calm down.
You caught those keys with your left.
Your shoulder was hurt.
Yeah. It's better.
What do you want me to do, cry?
You're not my brother.
Why don't you pull the trigger,then, hmm?
Because you're not sure.
Dude, you know me.
Don't.
Where is he?
Where's dean?
I wouldn't worry about him.
I'd worry about you.
Where is he?
You don't really wanna know.
I swear, the more I learn about you and your family...
I thought I came from a bad back ground.
What do you mean, learn?
He's sure got issues with you.
You got to go to college.
He had to stay home.
I mean I had to stay home
with dad.
You don't think I had dreams of my own?
But dad needed me.
Where the hell were you?
Where is my brother?
I'm your brother.
See, deep down...
I'm just jealous.
You got friends.You could have a life.
Me,
I know I'm a freak.
And sooner or later, everybody's gonna leave me.
What are you talking about?
You left.
Hell, I did everything dad asked me to, and he ditched me, too.
No explanation. Nothing. Just... poof.
Left me with your sorry ass.
But still, this life,
it's not without its perks.
I meet the nicest people.
Like little Becky.
You know Dean would bang her if he had the chance.
Let's see what happens.
Oh, hi.
I know what you're gonna say.
- Oh, you do?
Well, no. Not exactly.
But I can take a guess.
"Get off my porch."
That's about right.
I admit it, we lied.
Thought I'd try to explain myself.
Sam told me not to come.
But
I thought, "what the hell? I have to try."
Damn it.
That'd better be you, Sam, and not that freak of nature.
Yeah, it's me.
He went to Rebecca's,
looking like you.
Well, he's not stupid.
He picked the handsome one.
So you're saying that there's something out there
that made itself look like my brother?
Mm-hmm.
What'd you call it?
- A shapeshifter.
Yeah,
maybe we're crazy.
But what if we're not?
I mean, look. You said it yourself.
Zach was in two places at once.
Tell me how that could happen.
Okay. So
this thing,
it
it can make itself look like anybody?
That's right.
Well, what is it, like a genetic freak?
Maybe.
Evolution is about mutation,
right?
So maybe this thing was born human
but was different.
Hideous
and hated.
Until he learned to become someone else.
Yeah, that's the thing.
He didn't just look like you. He was you.
Or he was becoming you.
What do you mean?
I don't know. It's like he was downloading your thoughts and memories.
You mean like the vulcan mind-meld?
Yeah. Something like that.
I mean, maybe that's why he didn't just kill us.
Maybe, he needs to keep us alive
a psychic connection.
- Hands.
Yeah.
Come on. We got to go.
He's probably at Rebecca's already.
Come on. We got to find a phone, call the police.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,whoa, whoa.
You're gonna put an apb out on me.
Sorry.
This way.
It's funny.
I kind of understand him.
He's all alone.
Close to no one.
All he wants is for someone to love him.
He's like me.
Everybody needs
a little human touch now and then.
It's so hard to be different.
You should go.
You are disgusting! Just get the hell out of here!
Rebecca, just calm down.
- Oh, calm down?
What is wrong with you?
- What's wrong with me?
What's wrong with you?!
- I'm calling the police.
Give me your hands.
Shut up!
You're a nice girl, Rebecca.
I mean, I liked you.
Believe me,
it makes it harder.
But I got to do what I got to do.
I wish I would've met you
now it's a little late
Freeze!
Drop the knife.
Drop the knife!
Come on! Come on!
They think that your early ending was all wrong
for the most part, they're right but look how they all got strong.
That's why I say, hey, man, nice shot..
Good shot, man
That's why I say, hey, man, nice shot
An anonymous tip led police to a home in the central west end,
where a S.W.A.T. Team discovered a local woman bound and gagged.
Her attacker, a white male approximately 24 to 30 years of age,
was discovered hiding in the home.
Shots were fired.
It's not even a good picture.
It's good enough.
Aw, come on!
They said attempted murder. At least we know...
- I didn't kill her.
I'll check with Rebecca in the morning to see if she's all right.
First I want to find that handsome devil and kick the holy crap out of him.
We have no weapons.
No silver bullets.
The guy's walking around with my face.
It's a little personal. I want to find him.
Okay.
Where do we look?
We could start with the sewers.
We have no weapons.
He stole our guns. We need more.
The car?
I'm betting he drove over to Rebecca's.
The news said he fled on foot. I bet it's still parked there.
Oh, the thought of him driving my car.
- Aw, come on.
It's killing me.
- Let it go.
There she is.
Finally, something went right tonight.
This way.This way!
You go. I'll hold them off.
What are you talking about!
They'll catch you.
They can't hold me! Just go. Keep out of sight.
Meet me at Rebecca's.
Dean, stay out of the sewers alone!
I mean it!
Don't move.
Keep your hands so I can see them.
I'm sorry, Sam.
You know me.
I just can't wait.
So say this shapeshifter is real.
By the way, you know,you're crazy.
But, um,
say it is real.
How do you stop it?
Thanks.
Silver bullet to the heart.
You are crazy.
What happened?
I- I was walking home, and everything just went white.
Someone hit me over the head,
and I wound up here just in time to see that thing turn into me.
I don't know. How is that even possible?
- Okay. Okay.It's okay.
Come on. Can you walk?
Okay. We got to hurry.
Sam went to see you.
What are you gonna do to me?
I'm not gonna do anything.
Dean will, though.
They'll never catch him.
Oh, doesn't matter.
Murder in the first of his own brother.
He'll be hunted the rest of his life.
I must say.
I will be sorry to lose this skin.
Your brother's got a lot of good qualities.
You should appreciate him more than you do.
Cheers.
Not bad, little brother.
You're not him.
Even when we were kids,
I always kicked your ass.
Hey!
So this is what you do?
You and your brother, you hunt down these kinds of things?
Yeah, pretty much.
- I can't believe it.
I mean, I saw it with my own eyes, and...
Does everybody at school...
Nobody knows that you do this?
No.
Did Jessica know?
No, she didn't.
It must be lonely.
Oh, no.
No, it's not so bad.
Anyway, what can I do? It's my family.
Well, you know, Zach and me and everybody at school,
we really miss you.
Yeah. Me too.
Well, will you call sometime?
It might not before a little while.
So what about your friend Zach?
The cops are blaming this Dean Winchester guy for Emily's murder.
They found the murder weapon in the guy's lair,
Zach's clothes stained with her blood.
Now they're thinking maybe the surveillance tape was tampered with.
Yeah, Becca says Zach will be released soon.
Oh, oh, oh
Sorry, man.
About what?
I really wish things could be different, you know?
I wish you could just be
joe college.
Aw, it's okay.
You know, truth is,
even at Stanford, deep down, I never really fit in.
Well, that's because you're a freak.
Yeah. Thanks.
Well, I'm a freak, too.
I'm right there with you all the way.
Yeah, I know you are.
You know, I got to say,
I'm sorry I'm gonna miss it.
- Miss what?
How many chances am I gonna have to see my own funeral?