You boys really screwed up this time.
Where is he?
You're never gonna see your father again.
They've got dad.
Meg?
- What did she say?
- I just told you, Sammy.
Okay.
What are you doing,
Dean?
We got to go.
Why?
Because the demon
knows we're in Salvation, alright?
It knows we've got the colt.
It gots dad.
It's probably coming for us next.
Good. We've still got three bullets left.
Listen, tough guy, we're not ready.
Okay? We don't know
how many of them are out there.
Look, we're no good to anybody dead.
We're leaving... now.
I'm telling you, Dean,
we could've taken him.
All we need is a plan.
They're probably keeping dad alive.
We just have to figure out where.
They're gonna want to trade him
for the gun.
- What?
- Dean, if that were true,
why didn't Meg mention a trade?
Dad...
- He might be...
- Don't!
I don't want to believe it
any more than you,
but if he is...
All the more
reason to kill this damn thing.
We still have the colt.
We can still finish the job.
Screw the job, Sam!
Dean, I'm just trying to do
what he would want.
He would have wanted us to keep going.
Quit talking about him like
he's dead already!
Listen to me.
Everything stops until we get him back.
You understand me?
Everything.
So, how do we find him?
Maybe we go to Lincoln.
Start at the warehouse
where he was taken.
Come on, Dean. You really think these demons
are gonna leave a trail?
You're right.
We need help.
Here you go.
What is this... holy water?
That one is.
This is whiskey.
Bobby, thanks.
Thanks for everything.
To tell you the truth,
I wasn't sure if we should come.
Nonsense. Your daddy needs help.
Yeah, but the last time we saw you,
you did threaten
to blast him full of buckshot.
You cocked the shotgun and everything.
Yeah, well, what can I say?
John just has that effect on people.
Yeah, I guess he does.
None of that matters now.
All that matters
is that you get him back.
Bobby, this book...
- I've never seen anything like it.
- "Key of Solomon"?
It's the real deal, all right.
And these uh... these protective circles,
they really work?
Hell yeah!
You get a demon in one,
they're trapped.
Powerless.
It's like a satanic roach motel.
The man knows his stuff.
I'll tell you something else, too.
This is some serious crap
you boys stepped in.
Oh, yeah?
- How's that?
- Normal year, I hear of
say, three demonic possessions,
maybe four, tops.
- Yeah?
- This year, I heard of 27 so far.
You get what I'm saying?
More and more demons are
walking among us.
- A lot more.
- Do you know why?
No, but I know it's something big.
The storm's coming,
and you boys, your daddy...
you are smack in the middle of it.
Rumsfeld.
What is it?
Something's wrong.
No more crap, okay?
I want the colt, Sam.
The real colt.
Right now.
We don't have it on us.
We buried it.
Didn't I say "no more crap"?
I swear... After everything I heard
about you Winchesters,
I've got to tell you,
I'm a little underwhelmed.
First Johnny tries to pawn off a fake gun,
and then he leaves the real gun
with you two chuckleheads.
Lackluster, men.
I mean, did you really think
I wouldn't find you?
A ctually,
we were counting on it.
Gotcha.
You know,
if you wanted to tie me up,
all you had to do was ask.
I salted the doors and windows.
If there are any demons out there,
they ain't getting in.
Where's our father, Meg?
You didn't ask very nice.
Where's our father, bitch?
Jeez. You kiss your mother
with that mouth?
Oh, I forgot. You don't.
You think this is a freaking game?!
Where is he?!
What did you do to him?!
He died screaming.
I killed him myself.
That's kind of a turn-on...
You hitting a girl.
You're no girl.
Dean,
- you okay?
- She's lying. He's not dead.
Dean, you've got to be careful with her.
Don't hurt her.
- Why?
- Because she really is a girl.
- That's why.
- What are you talking about?
She's possessed.
That's a human possessed by a demon.
Can't you tell?
Are you trying to tell me there's an
innocent girl trapped somewhere in there?
That's actually good news.
Are you gonna read me a story?
Something like that.
Hit it, Sam.
"regna terrae,
cantáTe deo,
psáLlite dóMino"...
An exorcism?
Are you serious?
We're going for it, baby...
Head spinning,
projectile vomiting,
the whole nine yards.
"tribuite virtutem deo".
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna rip the bones
from your body.
No, you're gonna burn in Hell.
Unless you tell us where our dad is.
Well, at least you'll get a nice tan.
"exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus,
"omnis satanica potestas,
"omnis incursio infernalis
adversarii, omnis legio,
"omnis congregatio
et secta diabolica3"...
He begged for his life
with tears in his eyes.
He begged to see his sons
one last time.
That's when I slit his throat.
"ergo"...
For your sake,
I hope you're lying.
'cause if it's true,
I swear to god,
I will march into Hell myself,
and I will slaughter each and every one
of you evil sons of bitches,
so help me God.
"perditionis
venenum propinare.
"vade, satana,
inventor et magister omnis fallaciae,
"hostis humanae salutis.
"humiliare sub potenti manu
dei, contremisce et effuge,
"invocato a nobis sancto
et terribili nomine,
quem inferi tremunt".
Where is he?
You just won't take "dead"
for an answer, will you?
- Where is he?!
- Dead!
No, he's not!
He's not dead!
He can't be!
What are you looking at?
Keep reading.
"ab insidiis diaboli,
libera nos, domine.
"ut ecclesiam tuam secura
tibi facias libertate servire,
te rogamus, audi nos".
"ut inimicos sanctae ecclesiae
humiliare digneris,
te rogamus audi"...
He will be!
Wait! What?!
He's not dead,
but he will be
after what we do to him.
How do we know
you're telling the truth?
You don't.
- Sam!
- A building!
Okay?
- A building in Jefferson city.
- Missouri?
- Where, where? An address.
- I don't know.
And the demon, the one we're looking for,
where is it?
I don't know. I swear.
That's everything.
That's all I know.
Finish it.
What? I told you the truth.
I don't care.
You son of a bitch.
You promised.
I lied!
Sam?
Sam!
Read.
We can still use her,
find out where the demon is.
- She doesn't know.
- She lied.
Sam, there's an innocent girl trapped
somewhere in there.
We've got to help her.
You're gonna kill her.
What?
You said
she fell from a building.
That girl's body is broken.
The only thing keeping her alive
is that demon inside.
You exorcise it,
the girl is gonna die.
Listen to me, both of you,
we're not gonna leave her like that.
She is a human being.
And we're gonna put her
out of her misery.
Sam, finish it.
Finish it.
"dominicos
sanctae ecclesiae.
"terogamus audi nos.
"terribilis deus
de sanctuario suo deus israhel
"ipse tribuite virtutem
et fortitudinem plebi suae.
benedictus deus.
gloria patri".
She's still alive.
Call 911.
Get some water and blankets.
Thank you.
Shh, shh, just take it easy,
all right?
Come on. Let's get her down.
Sorry, sorry.
I've got you.
It's okay. It's okay.
A year.
What?
It's been a year.
Shh, shh, just take it easy.
I've been awake for some of it.
I couldn't move my own body.
The things I did...
It's a nightmare.
Was it telling us the truth
about our dad?
- Dean.
- We need to know.
Yes.
But it wants... you to know
that... They want you
to come for him.
If dad's still alive,
none of that matters.
Where is the demon
we're looking for?
Not there.
Other ones.
Awful ones.
Where are they keeping our dad?
By the r-river.
Sunrise.
"Sunrise"?
What does that mean?
You better hurry up and beat it
before the paramedics get here.
What are you gonna tell them?
You think you guys
invented lying to the cops?!
I'll figure something out.
Here. Take this.
You might need it.
Thanks.
Thanks... for everything.
Be careful, all right?
Just go find your dad.
And when you do,
you bring him around, would you?
I won't even try to shoot him this time.
You've been quiet.
Just getting ready.
He's gonna be fine, Dean.
Dude, what are you drawing
on my car?
It's called a devil's trap.
Demons can't get through it
or inside it.
So?
It basically turns the trunk
into a lockbox.
So?
So we have a place to hide the colt
while we go get dad.
What are you talking about?
We're bringing the colt with us.
We can't, Dean.
We've only got three bullets left.
We can't just use them on any demon.
We've got to use them on the demon.
No, we have to save dad, Sam, okay?
We're gonna need
all the help we can get.
You know how pissed dad would be
if we used all the bullets?
Dean, he wouldn't want us to bring the gun.
I don't care, Sam!
I don't care what dad wants, okay?
And since when do you care
what dad wants?
We want to kill this demon.
You used to want that, too!
Hell, you're the one who came
and got me at school!
You're the one
who dragged me into this.
I'm just trying to finish it.
Well, you and dad are a lot more alike
than I thought. You know that?
You both can't wait to sacrifice yourself
for this thing.
But you know what? I'm gonna be
the one to bury you.
You're selfish, you know that?
You don't care about anything
but revenge.
That's not true, Dean.
I want dad back,
but they are expecting us
to bring this gun.
They get the gun,
they will kill us all.
That colt is our only leverage,
and you know it, Dean.
We cannot bring that gun.
We can't.
Fine.
- I'm serious, Dean.
- I said "fine," Sam.
Hey, hey.
I think I know
what Meg meant by "sunrise".
Son of a bitch.
That's pretty smart.
If these demons can possess people,
they can possess almost anybody inside.
Yeah, and make anybody attack us.
And so we can't kill 'em...
A building full of human shields.
They probably know
exactly what we look like, too,
and they could look like anybody.
- This sucks out loud.
- Yeah, tell me about it.
All right.
So, how the hell
are we gonna get in?
Pull the fire alarm,
- get out all the civilians.
- Okay,
but then the city responds in...
- what, seven minutes?
- Seven minutes, exactly.
Hey, what's happening?
Is it a fire?
We're figuring that out right now, sir.
Just stay back.
I got a yorkie upstairs,
and he pees when he's nervous.
Sir, you have to stay back.
I always wanted to be a fireman
when I grew up.
You never told me that.
This is the fire department.
We need you to evacuate.
Hurry up!
Dad.
He's still breathing.
Dad, wake up.
Dad!
- Wait. Wait.
- What?
He could be possessed,
for all we know.
What, are you nuts?
Dean, we got to be sure.
Sam?
Why are you splashing water on me?
Dad, are you okay?
They've been drugging me.
- Where's the colt?
- Don't worry, dad,
it's safe.
Good, boys. Good, boys.
Hey, buddy,
You can't go in.
Go!
Back, back!
Sam, let's go!
Sam!
Sam, come on.
Come on.
Come on,
we've got to get out of here.
How is he?
He just needed a little rest,
that's all.
How are you?
I'll survive.
Hey, you don't think
we were followed here, do you?
I don't know.
I don't think so. I mean,
we couldn't have found
a more out-of-the-way place to hole up.
Yeah.
Hey, uh...
Dean, you, um...
You saved my life back there.
So I guess you're glad
I brought the gun, huh?
Man, I'm trying to thank you here.
You're welcome.
Hey, Sam?
Yeah?
You know that guy I shot?
There was a person in there.
You didn't have a choice,
Dean.
Yeah, I know.
That's not what bothers me.
Then what does?
Killing that guy, killing Meg.
I didn't hesitate.
I didn't even flinch.
For you or dad, the things I'm willing
to do or kill, it's just...
This scares me sometimes.
It shouldn't.
You did good.
You're not mad?
For what?
Using a bullet.
Mad?
I'm proud of you.
You know, Sam and I,
we can get pretty obsessed.
But you...
You watch out for this family.
You always have.
Thanks.
- It found us. It's here.
- The demon?
Sam, lines of salt in front of
every window, every door.
Already did it.
- Check it, okay?
- Okay.
- Dean, you got the gun?
- Yeah.
- Give it to me.
- Sam tried to shoot the demon in Salvation.
- It vanished.
- It's me. I won't miss.
Now, the gun. Hurry.
Son, please.
Give me the gun.
What are you doing, Dean?
He'd be furious.
What?
That I wasted a bullet.
He wouldn't be proud of me.
He'd tear me a new one.
You're not my dad.
Dean, it's me.
I know my dad better than anyone,
and you ain't him.
- What the hell has gotten into you?
- I could ask you the same thing.
Stay back.
Dean?
What the hell is going on?
Your brother's lost his mind.
- He's not dad.
- What?
I think he's possessed.
I think he's been possessed
since we rescued him.
- Don't listen to him, Sammy.
- Dean, how do you know?
He's different.
You know, we don't have time
for this.
Sam, if you want to kill this demon,
you've got to trust me.
Sam?
No.
Fine.
You're both so sure.
Go ahead.
Kill me.
I thought so.
What a pain in the ass
this thing's been.
It's you, isn't it?
We've been looking for you
for a long time.
Well, you found me.
But the holy water?
You think something like that works
on something like me?
I'm gonna kill you!
Oh, that would be a neat trick.
In fact,
here.
Make the gun float to you there,
psychic boy.
Well, this is fun.
I could've killed you a hundred times
today, but this...
This is worth the wait.
Your dad...
He's in here with me,
trapped inside his own meat suit.
He says "hi," by the way.
He's gonna tear you apart.
He's gonna taste the iron
in your blood.
- Let him go, or I swear to god...
- What?
What are you and god gonna do?
You see, as far as I'm concerned,
this is justice.
You know that little exorcism of yours?
That was my daughter.
- Who, Meg?
- The one in the alley?
That was my boy.
You understand?
- You've got to be kidding me.
- What?
You're the only one that can have a family?
You destroyed my children.
How would you feel if I killed your family?
Oh, that's right.
I forgot. I did.
Still,
two wrongs don't make a right.
You son of a bitch.
I want to know why.
Why did you do it?
You mean why did I kill
mommy and pretty little Jess?
Yeah.
You know, I never told you this,
but
Sam was gonna ask her
to marry him.
Been shopping for rings
and everything.
You want to know why?
- Because they got in the way.
- In the way of what?
My plans for you, Sammy...
You...
And all the children like you.
Listen,
you mind just getting this over with, huh?
'cause I really can't stand the monologuing.
Funny,
but that's all part of your m.o.,
isn't it?
Mask all that nasty pain,
mask the truth.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
You know, you fight, and you fight for
this family, but the truth is
they don't need you.
Not like you need them.
Sam...
he's clearly John's favorite.
Even when they fight,
it's more concern
than he's ever shown you.
I bet you're real proud of your kids,
too, huh?
Oh, wait, I forgot.
I wasted 'em.
Dean!
No!
Dad!
Dad, don't you let it kill me!
Dean!
Dad, please.
No!
Stop.
Stop it.
You kill me,
you kill daddy.
I know.
Dean? Dean? Hey.
Oh, god,
you lost a lot of blood.
- Where's dad?
- He's right here.
He's right here, Dean.
Go check on him.
Dad?
Sammy!
It's still alive.
It's inside me. I can feel it.
You shoot me.
You shoot me!
You shoot me in the heart, son!
- Do it, now!
- Sam, don't you do it.
- Don't you do it.
- You've got to hurry.
I can't hold on to it much longer.
You shoot me, son!
Shoot me!
Son, I'm begging you!
We can end this here and now!
Sammy!
Sam, no.
You do this!
Sammy!
Sam, Sam...
"Bad Moon Rising"
by Credence Clearwater Revival
I hear hurricanes a-blowin'.
I know the end is comin' soon.
Look, just hold on, all right?
The hospital is only 10 minutes away.
I'm surprised at you, Sammy.
Why didn't you kill it?
I thought we saw eye-to-eye on this.
Killing this demon comes first...
before me,
before everything.
No, sir,
not before everything.
Look, we've still got the colt.
We still have the one bullet left.
We just have to start over,
all right? I mean,
we already found the demon...