Can't keep kids out of this place.
What is it anyway?
I forgot you're not a local.
You don't know the legend.
Legend?
Every town's got its stories, right?
Ours is Roosevelt asylum.
They say it's haunted with the ghosts of the patients.
Spend the night,
spirits will drive you insane.
Hello?!
Police officers!
You tell me these kids brought bolt cutters?
Come on.
Let's split up.
All right.
Hello?
Come on out.
Kelly, you copy?
Jeez!
Where the hell you been?!
In there.
What was it? See anything?
No.
This is patrol 1 4. We are clear, we return to the station
Hey.
So, what?
You're still not talking to me?
Walt.
I said I was sorry about before.
How many times do I have to say it?
No, dad was in California last we heard from him.
We just thought if he comes to you for munitions,
maybe you've seen him in the last few weeks.
- Just call us if you hear anything.
- Okay.
Thanks.
Caleb hasn't heard
from him?
Nope.
Neither has Jefferson or pastor Jim.
What about the journal?
Any leads in there?
No. Same last time I looked.
Nothing I can make out.
I love the guy, but I swear
he writes like freaking Yoda.
And maybe we should call the feds,
file a missing person's out.
We talked about this. Dad would be
pissed if we put the feds on his tail.
I don't care anymore
After all that happened back in kansas,
I mean...
he should have been there, Dean.
You said so yourself.
You tried to call him and nothing.
I know.
I loose my cellphone.
You know, he could be dead
for all we know.
Don't say that.
He's not dead. He's...
He's what? He's hiding? He's busy?
I don't believe it.
What?
It's a-a text message.
It's coordinates.
You think dad was texting us?
He's given us coordinates before.
The man can barely work a toaster, Dean.
Sam, this is good news.
It means he's okay, or alive.
Was there a number on the caller I.D.?
Huh, it said "unknown."
Okay, well, where do the coordinates point?
That's the interesting part.
Rockford, Illinois.
Okay, and that's interesting how?
I checked the local rockford paper.
Take a look at this.
This cop, Walter Kelly,
comes home from his shift,
shoots his wife,
then puts the gun in his mouth,
blows his brains out.
Earlier that night, kelly and his partner
responded to a call
at the Roosevelt asylum.
Okay, I'm not following.
What does this have to do with us?
Dad earmarked the same asylum
in the journal.
Let's see.
Here.
"Seven unconfirmed sightings, two deaths"
till last week, at least.
I think this is where he wants us to go.
This is a job.
Dad wants us to work a job.
Maybe we'll meet up with him.
Maybe he's there.
Maybe he's not.
May He could be sending us there
by ourselves to hunting thing.
Who cares?
If he wants us there,
it's good enough for me.
This doesn't strike you as weird...
the texting,
- the coordinates?
- Sam.
Dad's telling us to go somewhere.
We're going.
You're Daniel Gunderson,
right, you're cop?
Yeah.
I'm...
Nigel Tufnel
with the chicago tribune.
Do you mind if I ask a couple questions
about your partner?
Yeah, I do.
I'm just trying to have a beer here.
I just want to hear
the story in your words.
A week ago, my partner
was sitting in that chair,
and now he's dead.
Are you gonna ambush me here?
Sorry,
but I need to know what happened.
Heyn buddy! How about leaving
the poor guy alone, huh?!
The man's an officer! Why don't
you show a little respect?!
You didn't have to do that.
Yeah, of course I did.
That guy's a serious jerk.
Let me buy you a beer, huh?
Two?
Thanks.
You shoved me kind of hard
in there, buddy boy.
I had to sell it, didn't I?
It's method acting.
Huh?
Never mind.
What did you find out from Gunderson?
So, Walter Kelly was a good cop.
Head of his class, even-keeled.
He had a bright future ahead of him.
What about at home?
He and his wife had a few fights. Like everybody.
But it was mostly smooth sailing.
They were even talking about having kids.
?All right, so how the kelly had some deep see the crazy way in the bus * ???
- or something else did it to him.
- Right.
What did Gunderson tell you about the asylum?
A lot.
So, apparently,
the cops chased the kids here...
into the south wing.
South wing, huh?
Wait a second.
South wing, south wing.
"1972,
three kids broke into the south wing.
Only one survived."
The way he tells it, one of his friends
went nuts and started lighting up the place.
So, whatever's going on,
south wing seems like the heart of it.
Yeah, but if kids are spelunking the asylum,
why aren't there a ton more deaths?
It looks like the doors
are usually chained.
They could have been
chained up for years.
Yeah, to keep people out.
Or to keep something in.
Let me know if you see
any dead people, Haley Joel.
Dude, enough.
I'm serious. You've got to be careful. Right.
I told you, it's not E.S.P.
I just have strange vibes, sometimes,
weird dreams.
Yeah, whatever.
Don't ask, don't tell.
Do you get any reading
on that thing or not?
No. Of course,
it doesn't mean nobody's home.
Spirits can't appear during certain hours of day.
The freaks come out at night.
- Ya.
- Hey Sam
Who do you think
is a hotter psychic
Patricia Arquette,
Jennifer Love Hewitt or you?
Man.
Electroshock,
lobotomies. They did
some twisted stuff to these people,
kind of like my man Jack
in "cuckoo's nest."
So, what do you think?
Ghosts are possessing people?
Maybe.
Maybe it's more like Amityville
or the smurl haunting.
Ah, spirits driving them insane,
kind of like my man Jack
in "the shining."
Dean...
When are we going to talk about it?
Talk about what?
About the fact that dad's not here.
Oh, uh, let's see, never.
I'm being serious, man.
So am I, sam.
Look. He sent us here.
He obviously wants us here.
We'll just have to
pick up the search later.
It doesn't matter what he wants.
See, that attitude right there,
that is why I always got the extra cookie.
Dad could be in trouble.
We should be looking for him.
We deserve some answers, Dean. I mean,
this is our family were talking about..
I understand that, sam,
but he's given us an order.
So what ? We've got to
always follow dad's orders?
Of course we do.
Sanford Ellicott
You know what we got to do?
We've got to find out
more about the south wing,
see if something happened here.
Sam Winchester?
That's me.
Come on in.
Thanks again for see me last minute.
Dr. Ellicott?
Ellicott, that name.
Wasn't there a dr. Sanford Ellicott?
Yeah, he was a chief
psychiatrist somewhere.
My father was chief of staff
at the old Roosevelt asylum.
How did you know?
Huh, well, I'm sort of
a local-history buff.
Hey, wasn't there an incident
or something in the...
in the hospital, I guess,
in the south wing, right?
We're on your dollar, Sam.
We're here to talk about you.
Oh, okay, yeah, yeah, sure.
- So?
- So.
How's things?
Uh, things are good, doctor.
Good.
What you been doing?
Uh...
same old. I've just been on a...
on a road trip with my brother.
Was that fun?
Loads.
Um...
You know... We...
met a lot of...
interesting people.
Mm-hmm.
Did a lot of, uh...
a lot of interesting things.
Uh...
You know,
what was it...
exactly that happened in the south wing?
- I forget...
- Look,
if you're a local-history buff,
then you know all
about the Roosevelt riot.
The riot?
- Well, no, I know, I'm just curious --
- Sam.
Let's cut the bull, shall we?
You're avoiding the subject.
What subject?
You.
Now, I'll make you a deal.
I'll tell you all about the Roosevelt riot
if you tell me something honest
about yourself...
like, uh...
this brother you're road-tripping with.
How do you feel about him?
Dude.
You were in there forever.
What the hell were you talking about?
Just the hospital,
you know.
And?
And the south wing,
it's where they housed the real hard cases,
psychotics, the criminally insane.
Sounds cozy.
Yeah, and one night in '64, they rioted,
attacked the staff,
attacked each other.
So, what, the patients took over
the asylum?
- Apparently.
- Any deaths?
Some patients, some staff.
I guess
it was pretty gory.
Some of the bodies
were never even recovered,
including our chief of staff, Ellicott.
Cops scoured every inch of the place,
but I guess the patients must have...
stuffed the bodies somewhere hidden.
- That's grim.
- Ya.
So they transferred
all the surviving patients
and shut down the hospital
for good.
All right so the * we've got a bunch of violent
deaths and unrecovered bodies.
Which could mean
a bunch of angry spirits.
Not good times. Let's check out
the hospital tonight.
Check this out.
Creepy...
yet terrifying.
I thought we were going to a movie.
This is better.
It's like we're in a movie.
I can't believe you call this a date.
Come on. That'll be fine.
That's look around.
Come on!
- What was that?
- Ugh!
Hey, look.
Come on, let's check it out.
I don't want to.
Let's just go.
Come on.
Okay.
Okay. You can wait here.
Gavin, no.
I'm just gonna be a minute.
Nothing's gonna get you, I promise.
Damn it.
Hey, sweetie,
couldn't take it, huh?
Hey.
Gavin, where are you?
Gavin.
Getting readings?
No, big-time.
This place is orbing like crazy.
There's probably
multiple spirits out and about.
And if these unrecovered bodies
are causing the haunting?
We got to find them and burn them.
Just be careful.
The only thing that makes me
more nervous than a pissed-off spirit
is a pissed-off spirit of a psycho killer.
Dean!
Shotgun!
Sam, get down!
That was weird.
Yeah,
you're telling me.
No, Dean, I mean, it was weird
that she didn't attack me.
It looked pretty aggro from where I was standing.
She didn't hurt me.
She didn't even try.
So she didn't want to hurt me,
then what did she want?
It's all right.We're not going to hurt you.
It's okay.
What's your name?
Katherine.
Kat.
Okay.
I'm dean.This is sam.
What are you doing here?
My boyfriend, Gavin...
is he here?
Somewhere.
He thought it would be fun,
try and see some ghosts.
I thought it was all just...
you know...
pretend.
I've seen things.
I heard Gavin scream, and...
All right, Kat, come on.
Sam's gonna get you out of here.
Then we're gonna find your boyfriend.
No, no.
I'm not gonna leave without Gavin.
I'm coming with you.
It's no a joke around here, okay.
It's dangerous.
That's why I've got to find him.
All right, I guess we're gonna split up, then.
Let's go.
Gavin!
I've got a question for you.
You've seen a lot of horror movies, yeah?
I guess so.
Do me a favor.
Next time you see one,
pay attention.
When someone says a place is haunted,
don't go in.
Gavin?
Hey, gavin.
Hey, it's okay. It's okay. I'm here to help.
Who are you?
My name is Sam.
We found your girlfriend.
- Kat?
- Yeah.
Is she all right?
She's worried about you. Are you okay?
I was running. I, uh,
I think I fell.
You were running from what?
There was...
There was this girl. Her-her face...
it was all messed up.
Okay, listen, listen,
this girl, did she try to hurt you?
What? No, she, uh...
she what?
She kissed me.
Um, but she didn't hurt you physically?
Dude, she kissed me.
I'm scarred for life.
[ Chuckles ] Trust me, it could have been worse.
And now, do you remember anything else?
She, uh...
Actually, she tried to whisper something in my ear.
What?
I don't know. I ran like hell.
You son of a bitch.
It's all right. I've got a lighter.
Ow. You're hurting my arm.
What are you talking about?
Let me out!Please!
Kat, hang on!
What's going on?
She's inside with one of them.
Help me!
Kat!
Get me out of here!
Kat, it's not gonna hurt you.
Listen to me. You have to face it.
You have to calm down.
She's got to what?
I have to what?
These spirits, they don't try to hurt, they're trying to communicate.
You've got to listen to. You've got to face it.
You face it.
No. It's the only way you're gonna get out of there.
No!
Look at it.That's all.
Come on.You can do it.
Kat?
Now, I hope you're right about this.
Yeah, me, too.
Oh, Kat.
1, 3, 7.
Sorry?
It whispered in my ear
1, 3, 7.
Room number.
All right. So if these spirits aren't trying to hurt anyone.
then what are they trying to do?
Maybe that's what they've been trying to tell us.
I guess we'll find out.
All right.
So,
now, you guys ready to leave this place?
That's an understatement.
Okay.
You get them out of here.
I'm gonna gofind room 137.
So, how do you guys know about all this ghost stuff?
It's kind of our job.
Why would anyone want a job like that?
I had a crappy guidance counselor.
And Dean? He's your boss?
No.
All right.
I think we have a small problem.
Let's break it down.
I don't think that's gonna work.
Then a window.
They're barred.
How are we supposed to get out?
That's the point. We're not.
There's something in here.
It doesn't want us to leave.
Those patients.
No.
Something else.
This is why I get paid the big bucks.
"Patients journal."
All work and no play makes Dr. Ellicott,
a very dull boy.
Right. I've looked everywhere.
There's no other way out.
So, what the hell are we gonna do?
For starters, we're not gonna panic.
Why the hell not?
Hey.
Sam, it's me.
I see it. It's coming at me.
Where are you?
I'm in the basement. Hurry up!
I'm on my way.
All right. Can either of you handle a shotgun?
What?! No!
I can.
My dad took me skeet shooting a couple times.
Oh, I heard.
It's loaded with rock salt.
Now, it might not kill a spirit,
but it will repel it, so if you see something,
shoot.
Okay.
Dean!
Dean?
Don't be afraid.
I'm going to make you all better.
Hey, Gavin.
Yeah?
If we make it out of here alive,
we are so breaking up.
Did you hear that?
Something's coming.
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Don't shoot! It's me!
Sorry. Sorry.
Son of a...
what are you still doing here?
Where's Sam?
He went to the basement. You called him.
I didn't call him.
His cellphone rang.
He said it was you.
Basement, huh?
All right.
Watch yourselves.
And watch out for me.
Sammy?
Sam, you down here?
Sam!
Man...
Answer me when I'm calling you.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You know that wasn't me who called, right?
Yeah, I know. I think something lured me down here.
I think I know who
Dr. Ellicott.
That's what the spirits have been trying to tell us.
You haven't seen him, have you?
No.
How do you knowit was him?
Because I found his logbook.
Apparently, he was experimenting on his patients.
Awful stuff.
Makes lobotomies look like a couple of aspirin.
But it was the patients who rioted.
Yeah. They were rioting against Dr. Ellicott.
Dr. Feelgood was working on some
sort of extreme-rage therapy.
He thought if he could get his
patients to vent their anger,
then they'd be cured of it.
Instead it only made them worse and worse
and angrier and angrier.
I'm thinking, what if his spirit
is doing the same thing?
To the cop,
the kids in the '70s
making them so angry they become homicidal.
Come on.
We've got to find his bones and torch them.
How?
The police never found his body.
The logbook said he had some
hidden procedure room down here
Somewhere where he'd work
on his patients. So,
if I was a patient,
I'd drag his ass down here
do a little work on myself.
I don't know.It sounds kind of...
Of crazy?
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
I told you I looked everywhere.
I didn't find a hidden room.
Well, that's why they call it hidden.
You hear that?
What?
There's a door here.
Dean.
Step back from the door.
Sam, put the gun down.
Is that an order?
That's more of a friendly request.
'Cause I'm getting pretty tired
of taking your orders.
I knew it.
Ellicott did something to you, didn't he?
For once in your life,
shut your mouth.
What are you gonna do, sam?
The gun's filled with rock salt.
It's not gonna kill me.
No.
But it'll hurt like hell.
Sam.
We've got to burn Ellicott's bones,
and all this will be over,
and you'll be back to normal.
I am normal.
I'm just telling the truth for the first time.
I mean, why are we even here?
'Cause you're following dad's orders
like a good little soldier?
'Cause you always do
what he says without question?
Are you that desperate for his approval?
This isn't you talking, Sam.
That's the difference between you and me.
I have a mind of my own.
I'm not pathetic like you.
So what are you gonna do? Huh. You gonna kill me?
We're no closer to finding dad today
You know, I am sick of doing what you tell me to do.
than we were six months ago.
Well, then here.
Let me make it easier for you.
Come on.
Take it.
Real bullets are gonna work
a hell of a lot better than rock salt.
Take it.
You hate me that much?
You think you can kill your own brother?
Then go ahead.
Pull the trigger.
Do it!
Man, I'm not gonna give you a loaded pistol.
Sorry, Sammy.
Oh, that's just gross.
Soak it up.
Don't be afraid.
I'm going to help you.
I'm going to make you all better.
You're not gonna try and kill me, are you?
No.
Good.
'Cause that would be awkward.
Thanks, guys.
Yeah, thanks.
No more haunted asylums, okay?
Hey, Dean.
I' sorry, man. I...
...said some awful thingsback there.
You remember all that?
Yeah.
It's like I couldn't control it, but I didn't mean it
any of it.
You didn't, huh?
No. Of course, not.
Do we need to talk about this?
No.
I'm not really in the sharing and caring kind of mood.
I just want to get some sleep.
Dean.
Hello.
Dad?