The Master is Prime Minister.
And these are my friends.
They're called the Toclafane.
What?!
Tell us who he is. He's a Time Lord.
He's cannibalised the TARDIS,
it's a Paradox Machine.
We meet at last, Doctor.
Stop this, stop it now!
We can't stop him.
Down you go, kids, remove one tenth
of the population. I'm coming back.
And the Earth was no more.
'Spacelane traffic is advised
to stay away from Sol 3,
also known as Earth.
'Pilots are warned Sol 3 is
now entering Terminal Extinction.
'Planet Earth is closed.
'Planet Earth is closed...'
What's your name? Tom Milligan.
No need to ask who you are,
the famous Martha Jones.
How long since you were
last in Britain? 365 days.
It's been a long year.
What's the plan?
I must see Professor Docherty,
can you get me there?
She works in a repair shed, Nuclear
Plant Seven, I'll get you inside.
What's so important about her?
The more you know,
the more you're at risk.
A lot of people depend on you.
You're a legend. What does the
legend say?
Martha Jones, she's
gonna save the world.
Bit late for that. How come you can
drive, don't you get stopped?
Medical staff. Used to be in
paediatrics in the old days.
Gives me a licence to travel,
I help out at labour camps. Great.
I'm travelling with a doctor(!)
Story goes, you're the only person
on Earth who can kill him.
That you alone can kill the Master
stone dead.
Let's just drive.
Citizens rejoice!
Your Lord and Master stands on high!
Playing Track Three...
SCISSOR SISTERS: # I can decide
whether you should live or die
# Oh, you'll probably go to heaven
# Please don't hang your head and cry
# I wonder why
my heart feels dead inside
# It's cold and hard and petrified
# Lock the doors and close the blinds
# We're going for a ride
# Oh, I could throw you in the lake
# Or feed you poisoned birthday cake
# I won't deny I'm gonna miss you
when you're gone
# Oh, I could bury you alive
# But you might crawl out
with a knife
# And kill me when
I'm sleeping, that's why...
# I can't decide whether you should
live or die
# Oh, you'll probably go to heaven
Please don't hang your head and cry
# I wonder why my heart feels dead
inside
# It's cold and hard and petrified
# Lock the doors and... #
It's ready to rise, Doctor.
The new Time Lord Empire.
It's good, isn't it?
Anything?
No? Anything?
Ohh, but they broke your heart,
didn't they? Those Toclafane.
Ever since you worked out what they
really are. They say...
Martha Jones has come back home.
Now why would she do that?
Leave her alone. But you said
something to her.
The day I took control.
What did you tell her?
I have one thing to say to you.
You know what it is...
Ohh, no, you don't!
'Valiant now entering
Zone One airspace. Citizens rejoice.'
Come on, people! What are we doing?
Launch Day in 24 hours!
Morning, Tish!
Ah! Smell that sea air!
Makes me long for good old British
fish and chips.
And what do I get?
Cold mashed swede. Some hotel!
Last time I book on the Internet.
All over the Earth, those things.
He's even carved himself
into Mount Rushmore.
Best to keep down.
Here we go...
The entire south coast of England.
Converted into shipyards. They
bring in slave labour every morning.
Break up cars, houses,
just for the metal.
Building the fleet out of scrap.
You should see Russia.
That's Shipyard Number One.
Black Sea to the Bering Strait,
100, 000 rockets ready for war. War,
with who? The rest of the universe.
I've been out in space.
Before all this.
And there's a thousand civilisations
with no idea of what's happening.
The Master can build weapons
to devastate them all.
You've been in space?
Problem with that? Nope! No, just...
Wow. Anything else I should know?
I've met Shakespeare.
Identify, little man.
I've got a licence! Milligan,
Peripatetic Medical Squad,
I may travel.
I was just checking for...
Soon the rockets will fly!
And everyone will need medicine!
You'll be so busy!
TOCLAFANE LAUGH
But...they didn't see you.
How d'you think I travelled
the world?
The Master set up Archangel that
mobile-phone network, 15 satellites.
It transmits a low-level psychic
field. That's how everyone
got hypnotised into thinking he was
Harold Saxon. Feels like years ago.
But the key's tuned into the same
frequency, makes me sort of...not
invisible, just unnoticeable.
I could see you. That's cos you
wanted to. Yeah, I suppose I did.
Is there a Mrs Milligan?
No. No, what about you?
There used to be someone.
Long time ago.
I must find this Docherty woman.
We'll wait till the next work shift,
what time is it?
It's nearly three o'clock.
Time for my massage!
Who shall I have? Tanya!
Lucy, have you met Tanya?
She's gorgeous!
Tanya, when we go to the stars,
I'm going to take you to the
Catrigan Nova. Whirlpools of gold.
You two should get to know each
other. That might be fun!
Oh!
What the hell? 'Condition red,
condition red!'
Ohh, I see. I told you.
I have one thing to say...
Ohhhh, here we go again.
Isomorphic controls.
Which means, they only work for me.
Like this!
Say sorry! Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Didn't you learn anything
from the blessed Saint Martha?
Siding with the Doctor
is a very dangerous thing to do.
Take them away!
Move! Come on. OK, gotcha.
There you go, Gramps.
Oh, d'you know,
I remember the days when the Doctor,
oh, that famous Doctor, was waging
a Time War, battling Sea Devils,
and Axons,
he sealed the rift at
the Medusa Cascade, single-handed!
And look at him now.
Stealing screwdrivers.
How did he ever come to this?
Oh, yeah! Me!
I just...
need you to listen...
No, it's MY turn. Revenge!
Best served hot! And this time...
It's a message for Miss Jones.
Professor Docherty? Busy!
They sent word, I'm Tom Milligan.
This is Martha Jones.
She can be the Queen of Sheba, I'm
still busy. TVs don't work any more.
Oh, God, I miss Countdown.
Never been the same since
Des took over. Both Deses.
What's the plural? Desii?
Deseen? But we've been told
there's going to be a transmission.
From the man himself.
There!
'My people!
'Salutations on this,
the eve of war.
'Lovely woman.
'But I know there's all sorts of
whispers, stories of a child,
walking the Earth.
'Giving you hope.
'But I ask you...
'how much hope has this man got?
'Say hello, Gandalf!
'Except...he's not that old!
'But he's an alien.
With a much greater
'lifespan than you stunted little
apes,
'what if it showed?'
What if I suspend
your capacity to regenerate?
All 900 years of your life,
Doctor. What if we could see them?
Older and older and older...
Down, you go, Doctor!
Down, down, down the years.
Doctor...
'Received and understood,
Miss Jones?'
I'm sorry.
The Doctor's still alive.
The Archangel network seems to be
the Master's greatest weakness...
15 satellites, all around the Earth,
still transmitting.
That's why there's no resistance,
it's broadcasting a telepathic
signal that keeps people scared.
We could take them out.
We could, 15 ground-to-air missiles,
got any? Any military action,
the Toclafane descend.
They're not Toclafane.
The Master made that up.
Then what are they? That's why I
came to you. Know your enemy.
I've got this...
No-one's been able to see a Sphere
close up, they can't even be damaged.
The lightning strike in South Africa
brought one down. By chance. I've got
the readings. On this.
Oh! Whoever thought we'd miss
Bill Gates?
Is that why you travelled the world?
To find a disc? No, just got lucky.
I heard you walked the Earth to
find a way to build a weapon.
There! A current of 58.5
kilo amperes,
transferred charge of
510 mega joules precisely.
Can you recreate that?
I think so. Easily, yes.
Right then, Dr Milligan.
We're gonna get us a Sphere.
He's coming...you ready? You do your
job, I'll do mine.
Now!
That's only half the job.
Let's find out what's inside.
I'm gonna kill him.
If I have to wait a hundred years.
I'm going to kill the Master.
One day, he'll let his guard down.
One day.
And I'll be there.
No, that's my job.
I swear to you,
I'd shoot that man stone dead.
I'll get him.
Even if it kills me.
Don't say that. I mean it.
That man made us stand on deck and
watch the islands of Japan burning.
Millions of people.
I swear to you. He's dead.
Tomorrow, they launch.
We're opening up a rift in
the Braccatolian space.
Won't see us coming. Kind of scary.
Then stop.
Once the Empire is established,
and there's a New Gallifrey in
the heavens...
maybe then, it stops.
The drumming.
The never-ending drumbeat.
'Ever since I was a child.
I looked into the Vortex.
'That's when it chose me. The
drumming, the call to war.'
Can't you hear it?
Listen. It's there now, right now.
Tell me you can hear it, Doctor.
Tell me. It's only you.
Good.
Tomorrow, the War!
Tomorrow, we rise, never to fall!
You see?
I'm doing it for them.
You should be grateful.
After all, you love them.
So very, very much.
There's some sort of magnetic clamp,
hold on... I'll just trip the...
Oh, my God...!
THEY GASP
It's alive!
Martha. Martha Jones.
It knows you. Sweet kind Martha
Jones. You helped us to fly.
What d'you mean? You led us to
salvation.
Who are you?
The skies are made of diamonds.
No... You can't be him.
'The skies are made of diamonds.'
We share each other's memories. You
sent him to Utopia. Oh, my God.
What's it talking about?
What are they? Martha.
Martha, tell us. What are they?
They're us. They're humans.
The human race, from the future.
I took Lucy to Utopia.
Isn't that right, sweetheart?
Trillions of years into the future.
To the end of the universe.
Tell him what you saw. Dying.
Everything, dying.
The whole of creation falling apart.
And I thought...there's no point.
No point to anything. Not ever.
And it's all your fault.
MARTHA: I'd sort of worked it
out with the Paradox Machine.
The Doctor said the day before the
Master came to power...
When he stole the TARDIS, all I
could do was fuse the coordinates.
I locked them permanently.
He could only travel between the
year one hundred trillion and the
last place the TARDIS landed.
Which is right here, right now.
The Master had the TARDIS, this time
machine. But the only place he could
go was the end of the universe.
So he found Utopia.
You should have seen it, Doctor.
Furnaces. Burning.
The last of humanity,
screaming at the dark.
The Utopia Project was the last hope.
Trying to find a way to escape
the end of everything.
There was no solution. No diamonds.
Just the dark and the cold.
Human invention that had sustained
them across the aeons turned inward.
They cannibalised themselves.
We made ourselves so pretty.
Regressing into children.
But it didn't work. The universe
was collapsing around them.
But then the Master came.
With his wonderful Time Machine!
To bring us back home.
But that's a paradox!
If you're the future and you've come
back to murder your ancestors,
you should cancel yourselves out,
you shouldn't exist.
That's the Paradox Machine.
My masterpiece, Doctor,
a living TARDIS, strong enough
to hold the paradox in place.
Allowing the past and the future
to collide in infinite majesty.
But you're changing history.
Not just Earth. The entire universe.
I'm a Time Lord.
I have that right.
But even then.
Why come all this way
just to destroy?
We've come backwards in time
all to build a brand-new empire!
Lasting one hundred trillion years!
With me as their Master.
Time Lord and humans combined.
Haven't you always dreamt of that,
Doctor?
What about us? We're the same
species. Why d'you kill us?
Because it's fun.
SPHERE LAUGHS
Human race -
greatest monsters of them all.
Night, then.
It's time we had the truth,
Miss Jones.
Legend says you travelled the world,
to find a way of killing the Master.
Tell us. Is it true?
Just before I escaped.
The Doctor told me...
The Doctor and the Master, they've
been coming to Earth for years. And
they've been watched.
There's UNIT, and Torchwood,
all studying Time Lords in secret.
They made this. The ultimate defence.
I can shoot the Master with this.
You can put that down now.
It's not easy to kill a Time Lord,
they can regenerate.
Literally bring themselves back
to life. Ah, The Master's immortal!
Wonderful(!) Except for this!
Four chemicals in the gun, inject
him...
Kills a Time Lord, permanently.
Four chemicals? You've only got
three.
Still need the last one, the
components were kept safe, scattered
across the world.
And I found them. San Diego,
Beijing, Budapest...and London.
Then where is it?!
An old UNIT base, north London, I've
found the access codes. Get me there.
We can't get across London at night,
it's full of wild dogs.
Tomorrow we can go with the medical
convoy. You can stay here.
We can get halfway, stay at the
slave quarters in Bexley. Professor,
thank you. And you.
Good luck. Thanks.
Martha.
Could you do it? Could you actually
kill him?
Got no choice. You're many things.
But you don't look like a killer.
Let me in, it's Milligan.
D'you bring food?
Couldn't get any. And I'm starving.
All we've got is water.
Sorry...
It's cheap. Pack them in, hundred in
each house, ferry them off to the
shipyards every morning.
Are you Martha Jones?
Yeah, that's me.
Can you kill him? They said you can
kill the Master, can you?
Tell us you can do it, please.
THEY SPEAK OVER EACH OTHER
Come on, leave her alone...
she's exhausted.
No, it's all right.
They want me to talk. And I will.
Access Priority One.
This is Professor Alison Docherty.
'State your intent.' First of
all, I need to know about my son.
'State your intent.'
Is my son still alive?
I have some information
for the Master.
Concerning Martha Jones.
Guess what?!
I travelled from the ruins of New
York, to the Fusion Mills of China,
right across
the Radiation Pits of Europe.
Everywhere I saw people like you,
living as slaves.
If Martha Jones became a legend,
that's wrong, because I'm not
important.
There's someone else.
The man who sent me. The man
who told me to walk the Earth.
And his name...is the Doctor.
He never stops, he never stays,
he never asks to be thanked.
But I've seen him. I know him.
I love him.
And I know what he can do.
It's him! Oh, my God, it's him!
The Master! He's here!
But he never comes to Earth! He
never walks on the ground! Hide her!
He walks among us,
our lord and master. Martha?
Martha Jo-hones?
I can see-ee-ee you.
Out you come, little girl.
Come and meet your Master.
Anybody? Nobody? No? Nothing?
Positions!
I'll give the order.
Unless you surrender.
Ask yourself.
What would the Doctor do?
Oh, yes!
Oh, very well done!
Good girl! He trained you well!
Bag! Give me the bag!
No, stay there, just throw it!
And now, good companion...
your work is done.
No!
But you...when you die,
the Doctor should be witness. Hmmm?
Almost dawn, Martha,
and Planet Earth
marches to war.
'Citizens of earth,
'rejoice and observe.'
Your teleport device.
In case you thought I'd forgotten.
And now.
Kneel.
Down below,
the fleet is ready to launch.
200, 000 ships,
set to burn across the universe.
Are we ready?
'The fleet awaits your signal.
Rejoice!'
Three minutes to align the Black
Hole Convertors! Counting down!
TICKING
I never could resist a ticking
clock! My children! Are you ready?
SPHERES: We will fly and blaze
and slice! We will fly and blaze
and slice!
At zero, to mark this day,
the child, Martha Jones, will die.
My first blood.
Any last words?
No?
Such a disappointment, this one.
Days of old, Doctor,
you had companions who could absorb
the Time Vortex! This one's useless!
Bow your head.
And so it falls to me, as Master of
all, to establish, from this day,
a new order of Time Lords.
From this day forward...
SHE LAUGHS
What...What's so funny?
A gun?
What about it? A gun, in four parts?
Yes, and I destroyed it.
A gun, in four parts, scattered
across the world... I mean!
Did you really believe that?! What
d'you mean?
As if I would ask her to kill.
Oh Well! It does not matter, I have her
exactly where I want her.
But I knew what Professor Doherty would do.
The resistance, knew.....
About her Son.
That's why I came to you.
Know your enemy.
I told her about the gun so she'd get
me here. At the right time. You're
still gonna die.
Don't you want to know what I was
doing?
Tell me. I told a story. That's all.
No weapons, just words.
I did what the Doctor said. I went
across the continents.
And everywhere I went, I found the
people. And I told them my story.
He saved your lives so many times
and you never knew he was there.
I know him. 'I told them about the
Doctor.' I love him.
I told them to pass it on. So
everyone would know about the Doctor.
Faith and hope? Is that all?
No, I gave them an instruction.
As the Doctor said.
'Use the countdown.'
I told them if everyone thinks
of one word at one time...
Nothing will happen!
Is that your weapon?
Prayer?! Right across the world.
One word, just one thought,
at one moment...
But with 15 satellites.
What? The Archangel Network!
A telepathic field binding the
human race together,
with all of them, every single person
on Earth, thinking the same thing at
the same time.
And that word... is "Doctor".
Stop it. No, no, no, no, you
don't...
Doctor. Doctor.
Doc...?
Doctor.
THEY CHANT
Stop this right now! Stop it!
Doctor.
Doctor. Doctor.
MASSES CHANT: Doctor!
I've had a year to tune into the
psychic network and integrate
with its matrices.
Doctor. Doctor. Doctor.
Doctor.
The one thing you can't do.
Stop them thinking.
Tell me the human race is degenerate
now,
when they can do this.
No!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Then I'll kill THEM!
You can't do this!
You can't do this! It's not fair!
And you know what happens now.
No!
No! No...
No! No!
You wouldn't listen. No! Because
you know what I'm going to say...
I forgive you.
My children!
Protect the Paradox!
Captain! The Paradox Machine!
You men! With me! You stay here.
No!
Now it ends, Doctor!
Now it ends!
SIRENS
We've six billion Spheres
heading for us!
We've got control of the Valiant,
you can't launch. I've got this.
Black Hole Convertor inside every
ship. If I can't have this world,
then neither can you.
We shall stand upon this Earth
together as it burns!
Can't get in. We'd get slaughtered.
Yeah. Happens to me a lot.
Weapon after weapon after weapon,
all you do is talk and talk
and talk, but over all these years
and all these disasters, I've always
had the greatest secret of them all.
I know you.
Explode those ships,
you kill yourself.
That's the one thing
you can never do.
Give that to me.
Everyone! Get down!
Time is reversing.
The paradox is broken.
We've reverted back, one year and
one day, 8.02am.
'This is UNIT Central, what's
happened? We saw the President
assassinated!'
After the President was killed,
before the Spheres.
Planet Earth restored.
It never happened. The rockets, the
terror. It never was.
What about the Spheres? Trapped at
the end of the universe.
But I can remember it.
We're at the eye of the storm. The
only ones who'll ever know.
Oh, hello! You must be Mr
Jones, we haven't actually met.
Whoa, big fella.
You don't want to miss the party.
Cuffs.
So, what do we do with this one?
We kill him. We execute him.
No, that's not the solution.
Oh, I think so.
Cos all those things.
They still happened.
Because of him. I saw them.
Go on! Do it!
You're better than him.
You still haven't answered the
question. What happens to me?
You're my responsibility, from now
on. The only Time Lord
left in existence.
Yeah, but you can't trust him. No.
The only safe place
for him is the TARDIS.
You mean you're just
gonna...keep me?
Mm. If that's what I have to do...
It's time to change. Maybe
I've been wandering for too long.
Now, I've got someone to care for.
Put it down. There you go...
I've got you, I've got you...
Always, the women. I didn't see her.
Dying in your arms. Happy now?
You're not dying. Don't be stupid.
It's only a bullet. Just regenerate.
No. One little bullet, come on.
I guess you don't know me so well.
I refuse.
Regenerate, just regenerate, please,
please just regenerate, come on...
And spend the rest of my life
imprisoned with you?
But you've got to! Come on!
It can't end like this!
You and me!
All the things we've done.
Axons! Remember the Axons, and the
Daleks... We're the only two left.
And no-one else.
Regenerate!
How about that? I win.
Will it stop, Doctor?
The drumming? Will it stop?
NO-O-O-O!
Just to say... I don't blame you.
But who are you?
Time was, every single one of
these people knew your name.
Now they've all forgotten you. Good.
Back to work.
I really don't mind, though.
Come with me. Had plenty of
time to think, that past year.
The year that never was.
And I kept thinking
about that team of mine.
Like you said, Doctor.
Responsibility. Defending the Earth.
Can't argue with that.
Hey, I need that!
I can't have you walking round
with a time-travelling teleport,
you could go anywhere. Twice.
Second time to apologise.
And what about me? Can you fix that?
Will I ever be able to die?
Nothing I can do.
You're an impossible thing, Jack.
Been called that before.
Sir.
Ma'am.
But I keep wondering,
what about ageing?
Cos I can't die,
but I keep getting older,
the odd little grey hair, y'know?
What happens if I live for a
million years? I really don't know.
OK, vanity, sorry, yeah.
Can't help it.
Used to be a poster boy!
When I was a kid,
living in the Boeshane Peninsula,
tiny little place,
I was the first one ever to be
signed up for the Time Agency.
They were so proud of me.
The Face of Boe, they called me.
Hmm!
I'll see you.
No. Can't be.
No. Definitely not. No.
No!
Yeah, could you put me through?
Hi, I'm looking for
a Dr Thomas Milligan.
Yeah? Hello?
Hello?
Right then! Off we go.
The open road! There is a burst of
starfire, right now, over the coast
of Meta Sigmafolio, the sky is like
oil on water, fancy a look?
Or...back in time, we could...
I don't know, Charles II?
Henry VIII?
I know, what about Agatha Christie?!
I'd love to meet Agatha
Christie, bet she's brilliant!
OK. I just can't. Yeah. Spent all
these years training to be a doctor.
Now I've got people to look after.
They saw half the planet slaughtered,
and they're devastated.
I can't leave them. Course not.
Thank you.
Martha Jones, you saved the world.
Yes, I did!
I spent a lot of time with you,
thinking I was second best.
But d'you know what? I am good!
You going to be all right?
Always, yeah.
Right, then. Bye.
Cos the thing is, it's like my
friend Vicky, she lived with
this bloke, student housing,
there were five of them, all packed
in, and this bloke was called Shaun,
and she loved him, she did,
she completely adored him, spent
all day long talking about him.
Is this going anywhere? Yes!
Cos he never looked at her twice.
I mean, he liked her, that was it!
And she wasted years pining
after him, years of her life,
cos while he was around, she
never looked at anyone else.
And I told her, I always said to her,
time and time again, I said,
"Get out."
So this is me.
Getting out.
Keep that.
Cos I'm not having you disappear!
If that rings, WHEN that rings,
you'd better come running, got it?
Got it!
I'll see you again, mister.
HORN BLARES
What?
But... What?!
BELL TOLLS
What?!
Subtitles Ripped by
Mighty_Marvel