HE COUGHS
Sorry.
ORGAN PLAYS OPENING BARS
OF THE WEDDING MARCH
SHE SCREAMS
PEOPLE GASP
MURMURING
WOMAN: Where did she go ?
What ?
What ? Who are you ? But. . .
Where am I ?
What ? What the hell is this place ?
What ?  !
You can't do that, I wasn't. . .
We're in flight. That is physically
impossible, how did. . .  ?
Tell me where I am. I demand
you tell me, right now, where am I ?
Inside the TARDIS.
The what ? The TARDIS.
What ? The TARDIS.
The what ? It's called the TARDIS.
That's not a proper word.
You're just saying things.
How did you get in here ?
Well, obviously,
when you kidnapped me.
Who was it ? Who's paying you ?
Was it Nerys ?
Oh, my God,
she's finally got me back.
This has got Nerys written all
over it. Who the hell is Nerys ?
Your best friend !
Wait a minute. What are you
dressed like that for ?
I'm going ten-pin bowling. . .
Why do you think, dumbo !
I was halfway up the aisle !
I've waited all my life for this.
I was just seconds away,
and then you. . .
I dunno, you drug me or something.
I haven't done anything.
I'm having the police on you !
Me and my husband,
as soon as he is my husband,
we're gonna sue
the living backside off you !
No, wait a minute,
wait a minute, don't. . .
You're in space,
outer space.
This is my. . .spaceship.
It's called the TARDIS.
How am I breathing ?
The TARDIS is protecting us.
Who are you ?
I'm The Doctor. You ?
Donna. Human ?
Yeah.
Is that optional ?
It is for me.
You're an alien ? Yeah.
It's freezing
with these doors open.
I don't understand it,
and I understand everything !
This can't happen.
There is no way a human being
can lock itself onto the TARDIS
and transport itself inside.
It must be. . .
It must be some sort of
subatomic connection,
something in the temporal field.
Maybe something macrobinding your
DNA with the interior matrix. . .
Maybe a genetic. . .
What was that for ?
Get me to the church !
Right ! Fine,
I don't want you here anyway !
Where is this wedding ?
St Mary's, Haven Road, Chiswick.
London, England.
Earth. The Solar System.
I knew it.
Acting all innocent,
I'm not the first, am I ?
How many women have you abducted ?
That's my friend's. Where is she
then, popped out for a spacewalk ?
She's gone.
Gone where ?
I lost her.
Well, you can hurry up and lose me !
How do you mean, "lost" ?
Right ! Chiswick !
No, she didn't run away.
We're not talking jitters,
she literally vanished,
now go and check the house.
Oh, Angelica, that's not helping,
is it ? Now smarten up.
Lance, any sign ?
I've looked all round.
Where the hell did she go ?
Showing off. First day at school,
she was sent home for biting.
It's a bit more serious than that.
She's never disappeared before.
She didn't disappear !
It's a trick, it's one of her silly
little "look at me" party pieces.
Oh, what if she's dead ?
Oh, don't say that.
I said St Mary's.
What sort of Martian are you ?
Where's this ?
Something's wrong with her.
The TARDIS, like she's. . .
recalibrating !
She's digesting.
What is it ? What's wrong ?
Donna,
is there anything
that might have caused this ?
Anything you might've done ?
Any sort of alien contact ?
I can't let you go wandering off,
not if you're dangerous.
Have you seen lights in the sky,
or did you touch something, like,
something different,
something strange, like something
made out of a funny sort of metal. . .
Who are you getting married to ?
You sure he's human ?
He's not a bit overweight with
a zip round his forehead, is he ?
Donna !
Donna ? Leave me alone.
I just want to get married.
Come back to the TARDIS.
No way, that box is too weird.
It's bigger on the inside,
that's all. Oh, that's all !
Ten past three, I'm gonna miss it.
Can't you phone them, tell them
where you are ? How do I do that ?
Haven't you got a mobile ?
I'm in my wedding dress.
It doesn't have pockets.
Who has pockets ? Have you ever seen
a bride with pockets ?
When I went to my fitting,
the one thing I forgot to say
was, "Give me pockets !"
This man you're marrying,
what's his name ?
Lance. Good luck, Lance.
Oi ! No stupid Martian
is gonna stop me from getting
married. To hell with you !
I'm not. . . I'm not from Mars.
Taxi ! He had his light on !
There's another one.
Taxi !
Oi !
There's one.
Why aren't they stopping ?
They think I'm in fancy dress.
Lay off the sauce, darlin' !
They think I'm drunk.
BOTH: You're fooling no-one, mate !
They think I'm in drag !
Hold on, hold on.
HE WHISTLES
St Mary's, in Chiswick,
just off Haven Road.
It's an emergency, I'm getting
married, just. . . Hurry up !
That'll cost you, sweetheart,
double rates today.
Oh, my God. Have you got any money ?
Um. No. Haven't you ?
Pockets !
.And that goes double
for your mother !
I'll have him. I've got his number,
I'll have him.
Talk about the Christmas spirit.
Is it Christmas ?
Well, duh ! Maybe not on Mars,
but here it's Christmas Eve.
Phone box !
We can reverse the charges.
How come you're getting married
on Christmas Eve ?
Can't bear it, I hate Christmas.
Honeymoon, Morocco,
sunshine, lovely.
What's the operator ?
I've not done this in years.
What do you dial, 100 ?
Just call direct. What did you do ?
Something. . .Martian.
Now phone ! I'll get money.
Oh, answer the phone !
Hello ? Oh, now the battery's gone
dead, has anyone got a charger ?
Could you try the hotel ?
Hello ? Hello ?
Vikram, is your phone working ?
I've got one wedding about to arrive
and another wedding refusing
to leave, so it IS a police matter.
Mum, get off the phone and listen !
I'm in. . . Oh, my God,
I don't know where I am.
It's a street. . .
and there's a WH Smith.
But it's definitely Earth !
MACHINE BEEPS
Excuse me. I'm begging you,
I'm getting married, and I'm late,
and I just need to borrow a tenner,
and I'll pay you back, I promise.
THEY PLAY: "God Rest Ye
Merry Gentlemen"
Taxi !
St Mary's, Chiswick.
Thanks for nothing, spaceman !
I'll see you in court !
Donna !
I'll give you the rest
when we get there.
Oh, I look a mess.
Hurry up !
Hold on a minute, I said Chiswick !
You've missed the turning.
Excuse me ?
We should've turned off, back there.
We're going the wrong way !
What the hell are you doing ?
I'm late for the wedding.
My own wedding, do you get that ?
METALLIC THRUMMING
Turn around ! Turn this cab around
right now !
Are you deaf or what ?
Oh, my God.
Help me !
Help me ! Help me !
Help me ! Get me out !
Help me !
Help me, I'm being driven
by a robot !
Behave !
You are kidding me.
Open the door !
Do what ?
I can't ! It's locked !
Santa's a robot !
Donna, open the door.
What for ?  ! You've got to jump !
Am I blinking flip jumping !
I'm supposed to be getting married !
Listen to me, you've got to jump !
I'm not jumping on a motorway !
Whatever that thing is,
it needs you.
And whatever it needs you for,
it's not good !
Now come on !
I'm in my wedding dress !
Yes, you look lovely. Come on !
I can't do it !
Trust me.
Is that what you said to her ?
Your friend. The one you lost.
Did she trust you ?
Yes, she did. And she is not dead.
She is so alive. Now jump !
SHE SCREAMS
THE DOCTOR COUGHS
Funny thing is, for a spaceship,
she doesn't do that much flying.
We'd better give her a couple
of hours. You all right ?
Doesn't matter.
Did we miss it ?
Yeah.
Well, you can book another date.
Course we can.
You've still got the honeymoon.
It's just a holiday, now.
Yeah. Yeah.
Sorry.
It's not your fault. Oh.
That's a change.
Wish you had a time machine.
Then we could go back
and get it right.
Um, yeah, yeah.
But. . .even if I did, I couldn't go
back on someone's personal timeline.
Apparently.
God, you're skinny.
This wouldn't fit a rat.
Oh, and you'd better put this on.
Oh, d'you have to rub it in ?
Those creatures can trace you.
This is a biodamper,
should keep you hidden.
With this ring. . .I thee biodamp.
For better or for worse.
So come on, then - robot Santas,
what are they for ?
Your basic roboscavenger.
The Father Christmas stuff
is just a disguise.
I met them last Christmas.
Why, what happened then ?
Great big spaceship,
hovering over London ?
You didn't notice ?
I had a bit of a hangover.
I spent Christmas Day over there,
the Powell Estate, with this. . .
.family.
My friend, she had this family.
Well, they. . .
Still.
Gone now.
Your friend. Who was she ?
The question is, what do camouflage
robot mercenaries want with you ?
And how did you get inside
the TARDIS ? I dunno. . .
What's your job ?
I'm a secretary.
Weird. I mean, you're not special,
you're not powerful,
you're not clever,
you're not important. . .
This friend of yours, just before
she left, did she punch you
in the face ? Stop bleeping me !
What kind of secretary ?
I'm at HC Clements.
That's where I met Lance.
I was temping. . .
I mean, it was all
a bit posh, really.
I'd spent the last two years
at a double glazing firm.
Well, I thought, I'm never
going to fit in here.
And then he made me a cup of coffee.
I mean, that just doesn't happen.
Nobody gets the secretaries
a coffee.
And Lance, he's the Head of HR,
he didn't need to bother with me.
But he was nice, he was funny.
And it turns out he thought everyone
else was really snotty too.
So, that's how it started,
me and him.
One cup of coffee and that was it.
When was this ?
Six months ago.
Bit quick, to get married.
Well. . .he insisted.
Will you marry me ?
And he nagged and he nagged me.
Oh, just think about it.
We'd make a great couple,
and I'd get rid of the dog, and
we could do out that back bedroom.
And he just wore me down. And
then finally I just gave in.
Please.
Oh, please.
Please, please, please, please,
please, please.
What does HC Clements do ?
Oh, security systems. Y'know, entry
codes, ID cards, that sort of thing.
Ask me, it's a posh name
for a locksmith's.
Keys. . .
Anyway, enough of my CV. Come on,
it's time to face the consequences.
Oh, this is gonna be so shaming.
You can do the explaining,
Martian Boy.
Yeah, I'm not from Mars.
Oh, I had this great big
reception all planned.
Everyone's going to be heartbroken. .
MUSIC: "Merry Xmas Everybody"
by Slade
MUSIC STOPS
You had the reception without me ?
Donna, what happened to you ?
Hello, I'm The Doctor.
They had the reception without me !
Yes, I gathered.
Well, it was all paid for, why not ?
Thank you, Nerys.
Well, what were we supposed to do ?
I got your silly
little message in the end.
"I'm on Earth" ?  ! Very funny.
But what the hell happened ?
You vanished ! How did you do it ?
What's the trick, cos I know
it's an illusion. . .
BABBLE OF VOICES
DONNA SOBS
Awwww !
APPLAUSE
# I have wandered, I have rambled
# I have crossed the stratosphere
# I have seen a mess of problems
# That I long to disappear
# Now all I have's
this anguished heart
# For you have vanished too
# Oh, my girl
My girl, my precious girl
# Just what is this man to do ?
# So reel me in, my precious girl
Come on, take me home
# Cos my body's tired of travelling
# And my heart don't wish to roam
# Yeah, reel me in, my precious girl
Come on, take me home
# Cos my body's tired of travelling
# And my heart don't wish to roam
# No, no
# Well, you took me in
# You stole my heart
I cannot roam no more
# Cos love, it stays within you
It doesn't wash up on a shore
# And a fighting man
forgets each cut
# Each knock, each bruise, each fall
# But a fighting man
cannot forget. . . #
Oh, I taped the whole thing.
They've all had a look. They said
sell it to You've Been Framed.
I said, more like the news !
Here we are.
It can't be. . . Play it again.
Clever, mind.
Good trick, I'll give her that.
I was clapping.
But that looks like. . .
Huon particles.
What's that, then ?
That's impossible.
That's. . .ancient. Huon energy
doesn't exist any more,
not for billions of years.
It's so old that. . .
It can't be hidden by a biodamper !
Donna !
Donna ! They've found you !
You said I was safe !
We've got to get everyone out.
My God, it's all my family.
Out the back door !
Maybe not !
We're trapped !
Christmas trees. What about them ?
They kill. Get away from the trees !
Get away from the Christmas trees !
Everyone get away from the trees !
Lance. . .  ! Turn the music off. Listen
to me - stay away from the trees.
Stay away from the trees ! Oh,
for God's sake, the man's an idiot.
What harm is a Christmas tree
gonna. . .  ? Oh.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
SCREAMING
Oi !
Santa ! Word of advice.
If you're attacking a man
with a sonic screwdriver. . .
don't let him near
the sound system.
FEEDBACK SQUEALS
It's all right, Stan,
you'll be all right.
Michael ? Connie ?
Oh, Sunita, do something useful.
What is it ? What were they ?
Just stop wittering, just help 'em !
Remote control for the decorations,
but there's a second
remote control for the robots.
They're not scavengers any more.
Someone's taken possession.
You're a doctor.
People have been hurt.
Nah, they wanted you alive, look.
They're not active now.
All the same, you could help.
You've got to think of the bigger
picture. There's still a signal !
Donna, who is he ?
Who is that man ?
There's someone behind this,
directing the roboforms.
But why is it me ? What have I done ?
Find the controller,
and we'll find that out. Ooh.
It's up there.
Something in the sky.
Clever, clever, clever boy.
CHUCKLES
Eat you up all snicker-snacker,
little travelling man. . .
He shall come to me,
and the beautiful bride.
Such secrets to unlock.
I shall descend this night.
I shall descend upon this Earth
and shine !
I've lost the signal ! We've got to
get to your office.
I think that's where it all started.
Lance ! Is it Lance ?
Lance, can you give me a lift ?
To you lot this might just be
a locksmith's, but HC Clements
was bought up 23 years ago by the
Torchwood Institute. Who are they ?
They were behind
the Battle of Canary Wharf.
Cyberman invasion.
Skies over London full of Daleks ?
I was in Spain.
They had Cybermen in Spain.
Scuba-diving. That big picture,
you keep on missing it.
Torchwood was destroyed,
but HC Clements stayed in business.
I think someone else came in
and took over the operation.
But what do they want with me ?
Somehow, you've been dosed
with Huon energy.
And that's a problem,
because Huon energy hasn't existed
since the dark times.
The only place you'd find
a Huon particle now is a remnant
in the heart of the TARDIS.
Y'see, that's what happened.
Say that's the TARDIS,
and that's you.
The particles inside you activated,
the particles magnetised and whap !
You were pulled inside the TARDIS.
I'm a pencil inside a mug.
Yes, you are. 4H. Sums you up.
Lance, what was HC Clements
working on ?
Anything top secret, special
operations, do not enter ?
I'm in charge of personnel,
I wasn't project manager. . .
Why am I even explaining myself ?
You make keys, that's the point -
and look at this !
We're on the third floor.
Underneath reception,
there's a basement, yes ?
How come on the lift there's
a button marked lower basement ?
There's a whole floor which doesn't
exist on the official plans.
What's down there ?
Are you telling me this building's
got a secret floor ?
No, I'm showing you this building's
got a secret floor. It needs a key.
I don't.
Right, thanks, you two,
I can handle this. See you later.
No chance. You're the man
who keeps saving my life.
I ain't letting you out of my sight.
Going down ! Lance !
Maybe I should go
to the police. . . Inside !
To honour and obey.
Tell me about it, mate. Oi !
The bride approaches.
She is my key.
Where are we ?
What goes on down here ?
Let's find out.
D'you think Mr Clements
knows about this place ?
The mysterious HC Clements.
Oh, I think he's part of it.
Oh, look. Transport !
SHE LAUGHS
Wait here, I just need to get
my bearings. Don't do anything.
You'd better come back.
Couldn't get rid of you if I tried.
Donna, have you thought about this,
properly ?
I mean, this is serious !
What the hell are we gonna do ?
Oh, I thought July.
Thames Flood Barrier !
Right on top of us.
Torchwood snuck in
and built this place underneath.
What, there's, like,
a secret base hidden underneath
a major London landmark ?
I know. Unheard of.
Oooh, look at this.
Stunning !
What does it do ?
Particle extrusion. Hold on. . .
Brilliant !
They've been manufacturing
Huon particles.
My people got rid of Huons, they
unravelled the atomic structure.
Your people ?
Who are they ?
What company d'you represent ?
Oh, I'm a freelancer.
But this lot are rebuilding them.
They've been using the river,
so they've got the end result. . .
Huon particles in liquid form.
And that's what's inside me ?
Oh, my God.
Genius ! Cos the particles are inert.
They need something living to
catalyse inside, and that's you !
Saturate the body, then. . .
Oh ! The wedding !
Yes ! You were getting married !
Best day of your life. . .
Oh, your body's a battleground.
It's a chemical war inside -
adrenalin, acetylcholine, wham go
the endorphins. Oh, you're cooking !
You're like a pressure cooker,
a microwave, all churning away.
The particles reach
boiling point, shazam !
What did I do this time ?  !
Are you enjoying this ?
Right, just tell me,
these particles,
are they dangerous ? Am I safe ?
Yes !
Doctor.
If your lot got rid of
Huon particles,
why did they do that ?
Because they were deadly.
Oh, my God.
Whatever's been done to you,
I'll reverse it.
I am not about to lose someone else.
Oh, she is long since lost.
I have waited so long,
hibernating at the edge of
the universe
until the secret heart was
uncovered and called out to waken. . .
Someone's been digging.
Oh, very Torchwood.
Drilled by laser.
How far down does it go ?
Down and down. All the way
to the centre of the earth.
Really ?
Seriously ? What for ?
Dinosaurs. What ?
Dinosaurs ?
What are you on about, dinosaurs ?
That film, with dinosaurs.
I'm trying to help.
That's not helping.
Such a sweet couple.
Only a madman talks to thin air,
and trust me, you don't want
to make me mad. Where are you ?
High in the sky. . .
Floating so high on Christmas night.
I didn't come all this way
to talk on the intercom.
Come on ! Let's have a look at you !
Who are you, with such command ?
I'm The Doctor.
Prepare your best medicines,
Doctor-man,
for you will be sick at heart.
Racnoss.
But that's impossible.
You're one of the Racnoss.
Empress of the Racnoss.
If you're the Empress,
where's the rest of the Racnoss ?
Or are you the only one ?
Such a sharp mind.
That's it - the last of your kind.
The Racnoss come from the
dark times, billions of years ago.
They were carnivores, omnivores,
they devoured whole planets.
Racnoss are born starving -
is that our fault ?
They eat people ?
HC Clements, did he wear
those black and white shoes ?
He did. We used to laugh, we used
to call him the Fat Cat in Spats.
Oh, my God !
My Christmas dinner.
You shouldn't even exist.
Way back in history, the
fledglingempires went to war against
the Racnoss. They were wiped out.
Except for me.
That's what I've got inside me,
that Huon energy thing. Oi !
Look at me, lady, I'm talking !
Where do I fit in ?
How come I get all stacked up
with these Huon particles ?
Look at me, you !
Look me in the eye and tell me !
The bride is so feisty !
Yes, I am !
And I don't know what you are,
you big. . .thing,
but a spider's just a spider. . .
and an axe is an axe,
now DO IT !
LANCE LAUGHS
That was a good one. Your face !
Lance is funny.
What ? I'm sorry. Sorry for what ?
Lance, don't be so stupid - get her !
God, she's thick !
Months I've had to
put up with her, months !
A woman who can't even point
to Germany on a map !
I don't understand.
How did you meet him ?
In the office. He made you coffee.
What ?
Every day, I made you coffee.
You had to be dosed with liquid
particles over six months.
He was poisoning me ?
It was all there in the job title.
The head of human resources.
This time, it's personnel.
But. . .we were getting married.
Well, I couldn't risk
you running off !
Then I was stuck with a woman
who thinks the height of excitement
is a new flavour Pringle !
Oh, I had to sit there and listen
to all that yap yap yap. . .
"Ooh, Brad and Angelina. . .
Is Posh pregnant ?
"X Factor, Atkins Diet,
Feng Shui, split ends, text me,
text me, text me. . ."
Dear God, the never-ending
fountain of fat, stupid trivia !
I deserve a medal !
Is that what she's offered you ?
The Empress of the Racnoss ?
What are you, her consort ?
It's better than a night with her.
But I love you.
That's what made it easy.
It's like you said, Doctor.
The big picture.
What's the point of it all
if the human race is nothing ?
That's what the Empress
can give me -
the chance to go out there,
to see it, the size of it all.
And I think you understand that,
don't you, Doctor ?
Who is this little physician ?
She said, Martian.
Oh, I'm sort of homeless.
But the point is, what's down here ?
The Racnoss are extinct. What's
gonna help you, 4, 000 miles down ?
That's just the molten core
of the earth.
I think he wants us to talk.
I think so too.
Well, tough. All we need is Donna.
Kill this chattering
little Doctor-man.
Don't you hurt him ! No, it's
all right. No, I won't let them.
At arms !
Ah, now. . .except. . . Take aim !
I just want to point out
the obvious.
They won't hit the bride,
they're such very good shots.
Just hold on. . .
Hold on just a tick,
just a tiny little. . .just a tick. . .
If you think about it,
the particles activated in Donna,
and drew her inside my spaceship.
So, reverse it. . .
and the spaceship comes to her !
Fire !
And off we go ! The key !
My ke-e-e-ey !
TARDIS THRUMS
Oh. D'you know what you said
before, about a time machine ?
Well, I lied.
And now we're gonna use it.
We need to find out what the Empress
of the Racnoss is digging up.
If something's buried
at the planet's core,
it must've been there
since the beginning.
I've always wanted to see this.
Donna, we're going further back
than I've ever been before !
If a key is lost,
then another must be cut.
At a-a-a-a-arms !
We've arrived.
D'you want to see ?
Suppose.
Hold on, scanner's a bit small.
Maybe your way's best.
Come on.
No human's ever seen this.
You'll be the first.
All I want to see is my bed.
Donna Noble. Welcome. . .
to the creation of the Earth.
We've gone back 4.6 billion years.
There's no solar system, not yet.
Only dust and rocks and gas.
That's the sun, over there.
Brand new.
Just beginning to burn.
Where's the Earth ?
All around us.
In the dust.
Puts the wedding in perspective.
Lance was right, we're just. . .tiny.
No, but that's what you do,
the human race,
make sense out of chaos.
Marking it out with
weddings and Christmas
and calendars.
This whole process is beautiful,
but only if it's being observed.
So I came out of all this ?
Isn't that brilliant ?
I think that's the Isle of Wight.
Eventually, gravity takes hold.
One big rock, heavier than others,
starts to pull other rocks
towards it.
All the dust and gas and elements
get pulled in, everything piling in,
until you get. . . The Earth.
But the question is,
what was that first rock ?
Look. . .
The Racnoss.
Now I have measured the bride's
catalysis,
I can force-feed it.
Drink the particles,
become the key !
Hold on, the Racnoss are hiding
from the war. What's it doing ?
Exactly what you said !
Oh ! They didn't just bury something
at the centre of the Earth !
They BECAME the centre of the Earth.
The first rock.
EXPLOSION
What was that ?
Trouble.
My wonderful key !
Now, my servants, bind him !
What the hell's it doing ?  !
That little trick of mine,
particles pulling particles -
it works in reverse.
They're pulling us back !
Well, can't you stop it ?
Hasn't it got a handbrake ?
Can't you reverse,
or, warp, or beam, or something ?
Back-seat driver !
Oh ! Wait a minute.
The extrapolator !
Can't stop us,
but should give us a good bump !
The bride shall join her groom -
what a wedding there shall be.
Now !
We've gone about 200 yards
to the right. Come on !
She is close,
the holy bride in white !
Find her ! Find her !
What do we do ?  ! I don't know !
I'm making it up as I go along.
But trust me, I've got history.
But I still don't understand.
I'm full of particles,
but what for ? There's a Racnoss web
at the centre of the Earth.
My people unravelled their power
source, so the Racnoss were stuck.
They hibernated for billions
of years, frozen, dead, kaput !
You're the new key -
brand-new living particles.
They need you to open it. And you
have never been so quiet. Oh !
I hate you. Yeah, I think we've gone
a bit beyond that now, sweetheart.
My golden couple.
Together at last,
your awful wedded life.
Tell me, do you want
to be released ?
Yes ! You're supposed to say, "I do."
No chance.
Say it !
I do. I do.
I. . .don't !
Activate the particles !
Purge every last one !
And release !
The Secret Heart unlocks
and they will waken
from their sleep of ages.
Who will ?
What's down there ?
How thick are you ?  !
My children !
The long-lost Racnoss,
now reborn to feast on flesh.
The Webstar shall come to me.
My babies will be hungry.
They need sustenance.
No. . . Perish the web.
Use her, not me, use her !
Oh, my funny little Lance.
But you were quite impolite
to your lady-friend.
The Empress does not approve.
NO-O-O-O-O !
It's Christmas !
Harvest the humans !
Reduce them to meat !
SHE SCREAMS
My children are climbing towards me
and none shall stop them !
So you might as well unmask,
my clever little Doctor-man.
Oh, well, nice try.
I've got you, Donna.
I'm gonna fall ! You're gonna swing !
I've got you.
SHE SCREAMS
CLANGING
Ooh, sorry.
Thanks for nothing.
The Doctor-man amuses me.
Empress of the Racnoss,
I give you one last chance.
I can find you a planet, I can
find you and your children a place
in the universe to co-exist.
Take that offer, and end this now.
These men are so funny !
What's your answer ?
Oh, I'm afraId I have to decline.
Then what happens next
is your own doing.
I'll show you what happens next !
At arms !
Take aim !
And. . . relax.
What did you do ?
Guess what I've got, Donna.
Pockets !
How did that fit in there ?
They're bigger on the inside.
Roboforms are not necessary.
My children may feast
on Martian flesh.
Oh, but I'm not from Mars.
Then where ?
My home planet is far away
and long since gone.
But its name lives on.
Gallifrey.
They murdered the Racnoss !
I warned you.
You did this.
No ! No ! Don't !
NO-O-O !
No ! NO !
NO-O-O-O-O !
NO-O-O !
NO ! My children !
SHE SCREAMS
My children !
Doctor !
You can stop now.
My children !
EMPRESS SCREAMS
Come on. Time I got you out.
Transport me !
Oh, they will suffer, so suffer.
This planet shall be scorched.
But what about the Empress ?
She's used up all her Huon
energy - she's defenceless.
Orders from Mr Saxon. Fire at will.
FIRE !
DONNA SQUEALS
There's just one problem.
What is it ?
We've drained the Thames.
SHIPS' HORNS SOUND
There we go, told you she'd be
all right. Survive anything.
More than I've done.
No, all the Huon particles
have gone.
No damage. You're fine.
Yeah, but apart from that.
I missed my wedding, lost
my job, and became a widow
on the same day. . .sort of.
I couldn't save him.
He deserved it.
No, he didn't.
Better get inside.
They'll be worried. Best
Christmas present they could have.
Oh, no !
I forgot, you hate Christmas.
Yes, I do.
Even. . .if it snows ?
I can't believe you did that.
Basic atmospheric excitation.
Merry Christmas.
And you.
So. . .
what will you do with yourself now ?
Not getting married, for starters.
And I'm not gonna temp any more.
I dunno, travel.
See a bit more of Planet Earth.
Walk in the dust.
Just go out there and do something.
Well, you could always. . . What ?
Come with me.
No.
OK.
I can't. No, that's fine.
No, but really.
I mean, everything we did today. . .
D'you live your life like that ?
Not all the time.
I think you do.
And I couldn't.
You've seen it out there.
It's beautiful. And it's terrible.
That place was flooding,
and burning, and they were dying,
and you stood there like. . .
I don't know.
A stranger.
And then you made it snow.
I mean, you scare me to death.
Well, then.
Tell you what I will do, though.
Christmas dinner.
Oh, come on !
I don't do that sort of thing.
You did it last year, you said so.
And you might as well, because
Mum always cooks enough for 20.
Well. . .
Oh, all right, then !
But you go first - better warn them.
And don't say I'm a Martian.
I just have to park her properly,
she might drift off
to the Middle Ages.
I'll see you in a minute.
TARDIS THRUMS
Doctor ! DOCTOR !
THRUMMING STOPS
Blimey, you can shout.
Am I ever going to see you again ?
If I'm lucky.
Just. . .promise me one thing.
Find someone.
I don't need anyone. Yes, you do.
Cos sometimes. . .I think
you need someone to stop you.
Yeah.
Thanks, then, Donna. Good luck.
And just. . .
.be magnificent.
I think I will, yeah.
Doctor ?
Oh, what is it now ?
That friend of yours.
What was her name ?
Her name was Rose.
I'm The Doctor.
Me too, if I ever pass my exams.
What was your name ? Martha Jones.
Rose. Not that you're replacing her.
Never said I was. .
EVIL CACKLE
SHOUTING AND SCREAMING
It's started.
Let her go !
The Globe Theatre.
Mr Shakespeare, isn't it ?
What are you standing there for ?
Come on !
Very well dressed for a hitch-hiker.
NO-O-O !
Don't let go !
Tonight, I am going to perform
a miracle.
I am 76 years old.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd 2006 for BBC