I'm Chuck.
Here are some things that you might need
to know, or maybe you just forgot.
- I'm not who you think I am.
- You're Orion.
- My father invented the Intersect.
- No hug for your old partner?
I'm been looking for you
for a long time.
Put him on the helicopter,
and kill his son.
I overheard them say that they're
moving your father to Black Rock.
Black Rock is a code name
for a secret Fulcrum base in Barstow.
I'm shutting down this project.
Chuck's going into lockdown.
Operation "Moron" is over.
They're gonna take you underground.
We have to run.
Your dad is still out there.
You're committing treason.
You could go to jail.
I know.
According to the coordinates,
this should be Black Rock.
It doesn't exactly look like
a Fulcrum compound now, does it?
Maybe your flash was wrong.
No, they had to have just moved
my father.
These beer are fresh.
There's still ash on the cigarette.
- Could have been kids having a party.
- Great.
We've got to start all over again.
Chuck, we're AWOL.
It's why we ditched the car.
If Casey finds us, I go to jail,
you go to a padded cell
with 24-hour surveillance.
There is no going back.
Don't give up, Charles.
Cute couple.
- If anything happens to them...
- What are you going to do?
You going to kill me?
You going to beat me to a pulp?
I'm sure you can come up
with something more creative.
No, you...
you had it right. I'll kill you!
Forgot about that.
I'm sorry. I'll tell you what.
As long as the new Intersect
is operational by tomorrow night,
- your son will be fine.
- Hold on.
There's still a ton of diagnostics
to run, simulations...
I can't guarantee
I can finish it by then.
Well then, I can't guarantee
your son's safety.
The safety of the Intersect
is no longer my main concern.
I want you to hunt Agent Walker
and the Asset down.
- Bring them back. Dead or alive.
- Understood, General.
Once the Intersect is in our possession,
this mission will be over
and you will have your pick
of assignments.
Your country thanks you...
Colonel Casey.
Congratulations.
You've earned it.
Got it.
What are you doing here, bro?
Chuck hasn't been showing up.
I was looking for some clues
where he might be.
- Chuck, I just heard from him.
- Really? He just called?
He left a voice mail not 5 minutes ago.
Our wedding is this weekend
and he decided to go out of town.
Good. Glad to hear...
hear he's safe.
Sorry, nervous Nellie, I guess.
Have a nice day!
Babe,
we've got to get
a lock for that window.
I need emergency satellite
tracking on an unregistered line
that dialed the following number
5 minutes ago.
As you can see...
just the one bed.
A little presumptuous, I guess.
Should I have asked for separate rooms?
No. It's fine.
As long as we're on the lam,
I can't let you out of my sight.
I'm going to take a shower.
I'm going to assume that that whole out
of sight thing doesn't really apply now.
Right.
I'm at the motel
a mile south of the base.
They just checked in.
You want me to kill them?
Vincent,
I may need them for leverage.
When the tests are complete,
feel free to use
whatever despicable acts of violence
are in your nature.
You could eat them if you want.
I'll sleep on the floor.
No, it's okay.
Why are you doing this?
Because the floor is gross,
and I'm not going
to make you sleep on it.
No, why are you here,
risking everything
that you worked so hard for?
Because,
after everything
that you've done for this country,
you deserve to find your father,
to get the Intersect
out of your head
and to have a chance
at a normal life.
- Thank you.
- You don't have to thank me.
It's my job to protect you.
What about when it's not your job?
What happens to us then?
One mission at a time, Chuck.
Telecom tracking complete.
Location verified.
Gotcha.
The Yvonne's Team presents:
Season 2 - Episode 21
Chuck Versus the Colonel
Sub-way.fr (v1.00)
Friends?
I wish people in our line of work
could afford friends.
That's just one of the sacrifices
of upper management.
Big Mike is my friend,
and I never would have betrayed him
- if you hadn't tricked me.
- Really?
Do all your friends give your mother
urinary tract infections?
Listen, Grimes.
I am offering you a cup...
up the corporate ladder.
- Dude...
- Now...
I need a new assistant manager.
Will you be my Ass Man?
Are you kidding me?
No. Never.
And as far as friends go,
I have Chuck, that's all I need.
Don't move.
Don't breathe.
Just stay there.
Stay. Stay.
I'm going to kill you, Morgan.
Dead man walking.
What do you want?
I want to speak to Michael.
I want to clear the air.
Come closer.
Mike, I know that this...
this whole thing is my fault.
I never knew Emmett
was trying to take over the store.
Truth is,
I just wanted you
to stop dating my mother.
You should be so lucky that a man
of his stature would defile your mother.
- Sorry.
- Never take sides
- against the family again.
- Understood.
What can I do to make it right?
I'll do anything...
stepfather.
Michael, there's a mess that needs
cleaning in bathroom stall 3.
No, let me do it.
I'll handle this.
We all have to clean up
our own messes in this world, son.
This can stop anytime you want.
All you have to do
is accept my offer.
Don't move.
I'm going to be right back.
I have very sensitive sinuses.
9 millimeters of hot lead
should clear that right out.
You really think you could
run away from me? Let's go.
What?
Sarah had nothing to do with this.
What's going to happen to her?
Sir,
we have an issue.
I told her not to move.
- Chuck, let's go.
- Sorry, Casey.
God.
Fulcrum is here.
We can't leave Casey.
- They're going to torture him.
- If we go back he's going to arrest us.
Yes, I know.
But we can't leave him.
Okay, fine.
One condition: you stay in the car.
Deal.
Going somewhere?
We came back here for you
because Fulcrum's here.
- Then we better get out of here.
- I'm not leaving without Sarah.
- You drive or I end you.
- End me? How're you going to do that?
You have no gun.
You don't think I could kill you
with my thumb or my elbow?
- Nerd bludgeoned by radiator?
- You can't kill me with that radiator.
It is far too confined here
for you to get the appropriate torque.
I could strangle you
with the handcuff chain.
You could maybe do that.
Too late.
They got her. Let's go.
I told you.
I'm not leaving without Sarah.
Stay down!
Drop it!
Can't do that, John.
Guys!
Let's just take a beat here.
Remember, we are a team.
Stay in the car!
Technically,
I still have one foot in the car.
How far you think
you're going to get?
Until we rescue Chuck's dad.
You're out of bullets.
It's over.
On the ground.
You two mind taking that outside?
We're in a bomb shelter.
I'm sorry, Sarah.
You didn't do anything wrong, Chuck.
You trusted somebody
who you thought cared about you.
Look outside, Chuck.
Look out the window.
"Tron."
"Tron"! Did you see that?
My father signaled me!
Did you just flash?
Come on. A midnight screening of Tron?
My father had to have written that.
Come on. We got to go back there!
My father's there!
Casey, please!
I don't care.
Something weird is going on.
Have you seen Chuck? He didn't
come home last night, Casey came by,
said he was worried about him.
I'm sure. Can't live without
his precious Chuck.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- The guy's obsessed with him,
a classic perv.
- No offense.
- Obsessed how?
You want to see
something really freaky?
Dude keeps a Chuck diary.
Bathroom visits...
and duration.
Keys,
duct tape,
high-grade chloroform...
From one stalker to another,
I'm impressed.
You guys think this has something to do
with Chuck missing?
I don't care. No clue.
You mind if I...
get right?
Casey, please!
Excellent work.
- Thank you, General.
- A CIA team is on their way
to take Agent Walker
and the Asset back to Langley.
- What about my father?
- Chuck received a signal from him.
He believes there may be
a mission tonight.
We'll look into it, Ms. Walker.
In the meantime,
enjoy your last few moments
in Burbank,
Colonel Casey.
Now I get it.
Now I understand
why you would betray your own team.
I would never betray my team!
You went AWOL.
You betrayed me.
Don't you ever forget that.
So sorry, Colonel.
But congratulations on that
chicken franchise you always wanted.
- Keep talking...
- Stay on Beckman.
It might be too late by midnight.
Just make sure
we don't give up on Chuck's father.
If your dad's there...
we'll keep him safe.
You have my word.
It's your neighbor, Devon Woodcomb.
Door was unlocked.
This is creepy.
Is that Chuck's bedroom?
Freakburger...
I hate this whole family.
Boss Man calling Ass Man.
Radio check.
The new automated have arrived,
if you could please
have Mike unload them.
Hold on a second.
You said that if I agreed...
Into the headset.
You said that if I agreed
to be your Ass Man,
you wouldn't make Mike do
any more humiliating jobs.
- And you wouldn't fire him.
- Get it done.
Good luck using automated checkout
machines with no power.
- Where'd you get that?
- Casey's locker.
Morgan's really turned
into Emmett's stooge.
This will show them
who's really in charge.
We did it.
That way! Go!
For whatever it's worth...
if I have to spend the rest of my days
in a dark, windowless room,
I can't think of a better person
to spend it with.
That's not really how this works.
We can't request a cozy little two-bed,
two-bath cell?
Two-bed?
Electrical interruption.
Auxiliary power activated.
Quick,
before the power turns back on.
Is that Awesome?
Ass Man!
We are under siege!
Shoot to kill!
Well... Hey, there, Emmett.
It is a good thing I installed
those emergency generators.
I underestimate you.
That was awesome!
- Fire them.
- Move! Move!
I saw you on the security cam!
Stay calm.
How're you doing?
What are you doing here?
We need to talk.
I get it, dude. You know,
there was a time in my life
that I didn't have
a lot going on either.
Dead-end job, no girl...
- Really?
- Well, no, John.
But this is not the answer. Okay?
You need help, bro.
You need serious psychiatric help.
What are you doing, man?!
Put the gun away, dude!
Take another step
and I will drop you.
Not bad for a frat boy.
- Don't you move.
- What the...?!
What the hell is going on here?
Don't freak out.
This is crazy.
We've got to call the police.
We can't do that.
Here, drink this.
He tried to kill me!
- Why can't we call the cops?
- Because I am the cops.
Moron.
I am a high-level CIA asset
and these are my handlers.
For the past 2 years,
they've had to protect my every move.
He can handle it.
You can handle this, right?
Tell me you can handle this.
You're being serious?
- He's being serious?
- I need you to help me.
I need you to be cool about this.
I need you to cover
for me with Ellie.
I need you...
to be Awesome.
Can you be Awesome?
You're a spy, Chuck?
Yeah, more or less, yeah.
This is...
Awesome!
I knew you weren't a loser
who worked at the Buy More.
"Loser's" a little...
that's a little harsh.
Here's the thing...
the Buy More actually is real.
But here's the most important thing.
I need you to do this for me right now.
I need you to go home
and handle Ellie.
That is your mission.
Can you do that?
I got your back, bro.
Right, right.
- A spy!
- Keep that on the D.L.
Impersonating a military official's
a federal offense, numbnuts.
- Put it on the list.
- Don't you leave me here
We got to go.
You walk out that door,
you're a dead man.
I don't care.
You will care.
I smell bacon.
Anyone else smell pig?
I seem to detect the faint odor
of the forbidden meat.
Knock it off. Listen to me.
You need to apologize to Emmett
for blowing the power, otherwise
- he's going to can you.
- Nice try.
Get us to apologize
so we look like asses.
Lose all our street cred.
You're going to have
to accept 1 concept.
What's that?
No one on this planet
is as dumb as you are.
I'm trying to help you guys.
- Are you?
Why are you taking all this crap
from everyone?
What choice do I have?
Emmett is trying to fire
the entire store,
I am the glue that holds it.
Why do you care
if this store holds together?
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
don't you have some goal
in this world outside the store?
Even Jeff and Lester
have their ridiculous band.
Don't you have a dream?
Of course, I do. It's just...
What?
It's crazy and you'll laugh at me.
I promise, I won't laugh.
Promise?
I'd like to be a Benihana chef...
in Hawaii.
I know. It's stupid.
It's not stupid.
It's totally attainable.
No, it's not.
You have to train for,
like, years, okay?
I'm way past my prime,
I am not Asian
and I don't even know
where to get the knives.
Ass Man, I need you.
Ass Man on his way.
We ran a thermal satellite scan
of the coordinates,
and activity was present.
It seems Fulcrum has moved
their operation underground.
Bartowski was right. We sending in
a team to rescue his father?
We don't have time for that.
I've ordered F-16s
- to annihilate the site.
- But I gave my word.
I have not come to this decision
lightly.
We have no other choice.
Chuck's a spy.
Stay cool.
There you are.
Did you learn anything
about Chuck at the Buy More?
He's supposed to pick up
your parents at the airport.
Honey? Why are you
just looking at me like that?
It's a really simple question.
Have you talked to Chuck?
- He's fine, yeah.
- So you spoke to him?
Definitely not.
Someone else spoke to him?
Who?
Honey.
I need you to focus, okay?
No wedding day jitters!
We've got company coming any moment,
my father and my brother are MIA,
so I just need you
to pull it together.
Can you be Awesome for me?
Good.
You focus! Focus!
I need your A game.
- No gun for me?
- No. You get to stay in the car.
The whole stay in the car bit?
Aren't we past this?
I think I'm perfectly capable
of handling myself on a mission.
What, Agent Imbecile?
- Drop it.
- You drop it.
No! I've come this far.
If he stop me, he'll have to kill me.
Beckman called an air strike.
It'll be here in 20 min.
What? Casey, my father is here!
You said you would rescue him.
You gave me your word.
But that didn't meant something.
I guess I have a lot to learn.
Yeah, you do.
You made three crucial mistakes.
You don't realize you were being trailed
for last half hour,
you didn't bring nearly
enough firepower,
and you didn't ask me to join.
Would you like to help us
rescue my father?
Your father served the country honorably
and deserves to go to the wedding.
- It's a yes?
- But,
he stays in the car.
- Agreed.
Done.
The team's back together again!
Group hug!
- One more step, it'll be your last.
- In the car I go.
Aces, Charles. Aces.
How's my favorite underachieving,
reclusive, kidnapped scientist?
It's done.
There's your Intersect.
You're a dream.
There is...
one request.
Anything that won't inconvenience me
is fine, I don't care.
Leave my family alone.
I'm not invited to the wedding?
- How did you know...?
- I'm in a conglomerate of bad guys.
Few details escape me.
Stevie, this works,
you have nothing to worry about.
It's a little tart in here.
I'll send down some air freshener.
Definitely staying in the car.
I had no idea Tron was so popular.
Welcome!
I see you all found your way.
Directions were good.
You have all have been
carefully selected by Fulcrum
to be the next generation
of Intersect agents.
More capable than any computer.
More efficient
than any spy in history.
Welcome to the future!
Can you dig it?
That's not what I was hoping for.
My God!
He's using the Intersect
to build an army.
Can you dig it?!
The program will begin
in three minutes.
3 minutes.
You fellas have a cigar for me?
- Don't you hate smoke?
- I figure if I'm gonna die,
I might see
what all the fuss is about.
Keys.
Go! There's an air strike
headed this way.
Three minutes to target, general.
Prepping weapon systems.
"Gone to stop Roark.
Be back in five. Chuck."
I'm gonna kill him.
Don't worry, Agent Casey,
we'll take care of that.
The prodigal son returns.
Thank you for saving me
the trouble of hunting you down.
My pleasure.
Move it.
Great, the gang's all here.
It's only fair that a son should see
the results of his father's labor.
Of course if this doesn't work,
I'm afraid I have to go back
to that bit where I kill everybody.
- If it does work?
- If it does work,
Same result, but,
you should root for it.
I mean, nobody likes a cynic.
Let's get right to the countdown,
shall we?
Five... four...
Three... I'm excited.
Two...
Casey! Sarah! Shut your eyes!
Keep them closed.
Chuck, look at the screen.
No, Dad, I don't want a refresh.
I want this nightmare to be over.
I know, that's why I made this for you.
It's all for you.
Trust me, son.
What a rush! What a rush!
I got to flash.
I'm not flashing. I'm not flashing!
It's not working!
There must be a glitch.
I'll have to take it back to the lab.
No more labs!
A deal is a deal!
Your son is dead! Get him up.
What's that?
I've got Chuck.
Let's get out of here. Come on!
Chuck, are you okay?
I feel...
I feel different. Lighter.
It worked.
- What worked?
- This.
I programmed it to remove
the Intersect from Chuck's head.
What do you mean "remove"?
The Intersect is out.
It's over, Chuck.
You're free, son.
Colonel Casey,
am I to understand
that you rescued Mr. Bartowski,
recovered the Intersect cube
and destroyed
Fulcrum's operation base?
- That's correct.
- I should be promoting you to general.
Actually,
Walker's the one responsible
for the success of the mission.
She pretended to go AWOL.
Used herself and the asset as bait
to lure Fulcrum out
so we could secure their location.
She risked her life
to the integrity of the mission.
If anyone deserves a commendation,
it's Walker.
Actually, General, I never...
Never thought she could be so cold.
I mean, I didn't, certainly.
She used me as bait,
like Casey just said.
Treated terribly, you know.
She cuffed me,
I had chaffing on my wrists.
I was malnourished.
It was... it was... horrific.
Well, then, Colonel Casey,
now that the "Intersect project"
is over,
I assume you want to command
your old unit?
Sorry, I just want to make sure
I didn't misinterpret anything.
Did you just say "over"?
That's correct.
We have the Intersect cube,
Fulcrum is defeated,
your mission complete.
Mr. Bartowski,
you are free to return to...
whatever it is you do.
General, I'd...
I'd just like to say
that although I know we've had
our share of ups and downs,
this has been an incredible,
dare I say,
life-changing experience...
that you don't feel quite
as strongly about. I get it, you busy.
Government... It's a little rude.
Why are the Brothers Imbecile
still working here?
Can we just give them
one more chance, please?
You know what, Grimes,
I'm gonna ask you
a very important question.
And I want you to think very long
and hard, about it.
Do you want to be a loser
the rest of your life?
Excellent question.
If you had asked me that
this morning,
I probably would have said yes.
Now, I'm not so sure.
Then do what needs to be done.
Yes, sir.
Big Mike, in the old country,
if a man did the honorable thing
and he fell on his own sword,
- his family was looked after.
- That was a good break.
Real nice deal.
- Will you look after my mother?
- I will.
Gentlemen,
it's been a pleasure
serving with you.
If you retell the story,
do me a favor
give me a better physique.
What are you doing?
Morgan out.
Will you come to Hawaii with me,
where I will learn
the ancient art of hibachi?
Morgan, I thought you'd never ask.
This is so great.
One second, hold on.
- A little hot in here, buddy?
- It's a bit chilly but...
- worth it.
- Is everything okay?
Yeah. No, dude, actually,
for the first time,
everything is fine.
It's all over.
God, I admire him.
You're free, Morgan!
You're free!
Babe,
we are late. We have to go.
I can't.
We have a rehearsal dinner
full of people waiting for us.
I knew that my dad
would disappoint me,
but, not Chuck.
I don't know, it must be in the DNA.
I know it's difficult without Chuck,
but he wants to be here,
I know he does.
Your dad leaving
shook him up pretty bad.
Ellie, he'll be back.
Trust me... he loves you.
So do I.
Chuck, where have you been?
I was getting your wedding present.
Dad...
Are you staying?
I'm not going anywhere.
I got your back, bro.
I was wondering if you...
wanted to come
to my sister's rehearsal dinner.
The Intersect's out, Bartowski.
- You don't need my help anymore.
- I'm not asking you as the asset,
but as a friend.
Okay, well, I tried.
Open bar, I hope.
I'll go warm up the Vic.
- You look amazing.
- Thank you.
- Very dapper.
So how does it feel?
It feels great, actually.
Like everything is finally real.
It is real.
Where you headed?
Got a wedding to go to.