***
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:Max  –°“∞»ÀÕı
Chuck
Season 1 Episode 2
hi.My name's  charles
bartowski,but you can call me  uck.
Those are my shoes.
This is my life.
It's filled  with spies,car chases,computer-stealing
ninjas  and me saving the day.
Oh,wait,wait. I o ed tgo back.
I work at the buy more.
It used to be pretty boring.
Chuck! Get overhere! Now!
Look at this. What happened?
Well,wayto go,jeff.
You do realize we don't
workfor large mart.
They're our competition.
Can you imagine the shameif sommarge rt fiend or
costco stoogeput out a display on our buy more green?
So this has tocome down,right?
Yesterday.
I now present to youthe
magic... of morgan.
this is my best friend,morgan.
He is not a magician.
Voila!
See,everything changed  when I got an e-mail
from my old college buddy  bryce larkin.
You see,bryce had been working for the cia when
he stwhe a ole bunch of government secrets--
big important secrets,really
scary,nasty,get-killed-for-having-them secrets.
Next thing I know,these ecpersrets
are downloaded into my brain,
which means every moment lf myife...
is in danger.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
The nsa sent their top
agent to protect me.
That's casey. He's pretty scary.
He works at buy more now,cas aover.
So now I must defend the
country from assassins...
no,casey!
...Terrorists...  ...
and shoplifters.
Casey,casey,casey. No,no,no,no,no.
No,no,no,no. It's just a video game,okay?
Lives are not in danger,and
the countryis still safe.
This guy's been here24 hours and he's
taking the job waymore seriously than me.
That's becausehe's crazy.
Tell me somethingI don't know.
Oh,hey,dawg. Nice to
see you again,pal. Huh?
You're not so tough now,are you?
Oh,youdon't like that,huh?
Sarah?
The cia sent their tot,agen too.
Oh,yeah,I know. Believe me.
She told me to trust her.
But just like any
woman,she's got a past.
and... she's posing  as my girlfriend.
sarah,what,uh... at
awhre you doing here?
I work here now,chuck.
Oh,damn.
I burned another batch.
Why are you working here?
Surveillance.
I can monitor the buy more
from here while you work.
It's just a cover.
Right,yllh,a part of the plan.
'Cause there's a plan,right?
I mean,uh,you making gourmet wieners isn't
exactly the reason why you joined the cia,
and casey isn't a natural-born appliance salesman,and the
whole kinda government-secrets-locked- in-my-brain thing,
uh,that's,I'm sure,not really a boon for national security,so I'm
hoping,I mean,I'm hoping that you'll tell me that there's a plan?
We have a plan.
There is somebody who can help.
We can discuss it further tonight.
How about another date?
I can pick you up at 8:00.
Yeah. Yeah,that sounds... I'd like that.
That sounds great. I'll,uh,I'll see you.
chuck is in.
Send the doctor.
Hey,sis,what do you think of this shirt?
Another date with sarah.
This is very exciting.
-Well,see,it's not that big a deal.
-Yes,it is. Hey,she is hot.
Jeepers.
I'd go with the first shirt,too. It
looks really nice with your skin tone.
Oh,yeah?
Wait a minute-- morgan
has met her,and I haven't?
Well... yeah,he confides
in me,ellie. You know?
He-he tells me his deepest,darkest
secrets,which,you could,too,by the way.
Here's one: I loath you.
That's not a secret.
I need to meet this girl.
Tomorrow night. Dinner. Here.
A little too soon to be seeing
the tron poster,don't you think?
Not exactly a natural aphrodisiac.
Dinner. Perfect. I'll clear my schedule.
Our most valuable secrets
have been sent to an idiot.
Well,at least they
weren't sent to his friend.
"Operation chuck.
" I can't believe this.
I spoke with agent walker.
She'll deliver chuck to
the rendezvous tonight.
Good. Dr.  Zarnow's
on his way to L.A. Now.
He is our best,nsa's top scientist.
Well,I hope he can fix this.
Get in.
Wienerlicious really pays well,huh?
Uh,what are we,uh,what are we doing? We're
going to,uh,like,a movie or some dinner?
Not exactly.
What,what does,what does
"not exactly" mean,exactly?
So.
Here we are on ourdate at the buy more.
Is this all partof the plan or a
chance for meto clock in some overtime?
There's a doctor comingto see you,chuck.
He worked on theencoding process for the intersect,the
computerthat bryce destroyed,the one that'sin your head.
He's comingto examine you.
Uh-huh,uh,and-and doesthis examination involve,say,I
don't know,needles orperhaps probing of some kind?
The doctor is our best
shotat helping you.
It's what you want,right?
To get the secretsout of your head.
Yeah. Yeah,of course.
But you-you still... you're still being very vagueabout
the probing,and I'd liketo know the answer to that.
We've rewired the hometheater
room for this test.
When the images start,just
say what they are.
That's it?
I'm sure you'll finda
way to screw it up.
The doctor's here.
- When do I getto meet him?
-You don'T.
It's importantthat he doesn't
see you. You're too valuable.
Thanks. I'm flattered
and totallyfreaked out.
Dr.  Zarnow?
Agent casey.
Agent walker.
Thank you for meetingus
at a neutral site.
Let's begin.
I don't understand whyI
can't see my patient.
For your safety,we're
keepingpatient x's identity a secret.
Does patient x work here?
Patient x--who knows all the
intersect secrets--works in a buy more?
Ridiculous. Of course.
After the tone,the test will begin.
uh... dog.
Uh,hippopotamus.
Fat guy.
Ugly building.
Really beautiful womanat the beach.
Cardinal oneis the top moscow spy
in the white house office of...
the plot to assassinatepresident
carter was orchestrated by...
northrop davis voting computers has
been approved  by the dnc,rnc and cia.
Oceanic flight 815 was shot downby
surface-to-air...  work on subterranean...
beneath denver international
airport has reached phase four.
Benedictine agents within the vatican report...  ...assassin
still active...   ...been approved by the dnc,rnc and cia.
scenario five is... okay,well,that'sjust
a picture of a turtle.
Your patient is phenomenal.
We never imagined this.
What didn't you imagine?
One person seeing
allthe intersect images.
All our secrets in one mind.
Can you remove the secrets,doctor?
Yes. I think I can.
So,did I pass the test?
You did great,chuck.
And this doctor guy--he
can fix me or...?
Uh,he's hopeful,yeah.
Okay.
Oh,uh,I almost forgot.
Uh... dinner tomorrow nightwith my
sister and her boyfriend captain awesome.
She really wanted to meet you.
Okay,well,that's a good idea.
Meeting the family'skind of a big step
if our relationshipwere remotely real.
so,uh,if this wholeexamination thing,if it
works out,then I guess...we're through,huh?
Uh,yeah. Mm-hmm.
-Okay. Well,good night.
-Good night.
Oh,and,uh... just so you know... um... tonight wasprobably
the best... only second dateI've been on in years.
Drive safe.
Did you see this?
Atwh?
Did you know thatbryce was dead?
No. No,I didn'T.
Well,are you okay?
I don't know.
Um... yeah,I don't know. It's crazy.
I,uh,I spent somuch time hating him
for getting mekicked out of stanford,
I don't know,really,how to feel,but
it's hard to bemad at him now.
I'm reallysorry,chuck.
Yeah,ey's cas. I'm at the scene.
No sign of zarnow's
body. Probably vaporized.
I guess those secrets are
staying in chuck's head.
Well... no sign of anything here.
It looks like we're sending
thegood doctor home in an ashtray.
Okay,well,I've got hot dogs to fry.
And I've got some toastersto sell.
Feels like a cia job to me.
Keep your eye on agent walker.
And don't let chuck out of
your sight. He could be next.
The strong barsare getting
a little sticky. On... on one.
On theother one,it's
fine,but on the second...
you can't trust her.
-Chuck. John.
-Big mike. Big mike!
How's customer service training?
-Fine.
-Super.
Glad to hear it.
The better my employees,the
less I have to work.
Very inspiring words,sir.
Regular call to arms.
Well,go make 'em better.
Show me you're
assistantmanager material.
Chop-chop! I got a napin an hour.
-Good-bye.
So,uh,this isthe hand-held scanner.
Very expensivepiece of equipment.
So is a stealth fighter
andsomehow I managed to fly that.
Right,uh,and the gun,you
know,kind of works like A...
-gun?
-Uh-huh.
And it beepswhen you scan the barcodes.
well,if screamed out
loud,I'd be right at home.
:N't I dowant you to have any more
private meetingswith sarah,hmm?
Um,is there...is there a problem?
No problems,only solutions.
well,that... sounds very much likethe buy more customer
policy that I've noticedyou have some issue with.
Anowyou kn,uh... you know what
I thinkwe're gonna do about that?
We're gonna dosome role-playing,and work
on that attitude of yours how about that?
-Hey,morgan.
-Hi,yo.
Ah,hey,there he is. There's
myjohnny-on-the-spot.
Morgan and casey,you
guysare gonna do some stuff.
You're gonna be a shopper,and you're
gonna bethe sales rep,like you are.
And,uh,I'm gonnatalk to big mike and-and work onsome
stuff 'cause I know he's got otherthings in store.
Got it from here.
there you go.
so,chuck,no private
meetingswith casey today.
What? What is it upwith you guys?
Did he tell youthe same thing?
Right,of course he did.
Hold on a second. Is something wrong?
The doctorfrom last night-- he was killed
in an explosionsoon after he left us.
Wha-what?
The doctor who wassupposed to fix me?
Tell me what this is.
A... a nasty...
nsa incinerator.
Special issue designed
toeliminate all biological traces.
That's what killed the doctor.
And guess who worksfor the nsa?
-Why... why,why would casey...
- he's a killer,chuck.
It's what he doesfor a living.
He tried to kill us,and he'll
probably try to do it again.
Maybe it was orders.
Maybe he didn't like  the
way zarnow looked at him.
Oh,that's nice. I feel
much better now,sarah.
What am I supposed to do?
You go back in there and you
pretend likeyou know nothing.
Go. You can do that,chuck.
I know nothing.
I know nothing,I... got it.
All right,so I'm gonna try again. Ready?
Do you have any ramones?
No,don't say no. It's
not gonna...listen,okay.
Uh,excuse me,john. How you doing?
Do you have any ramoneshere,dude?
Don't tell meyou don't have any.
Casey,the...the correct response
is "can we order youthe ramones?
" Ramones,man,ramones. Okay,just
lookingfor the ramones,man.
Do you have ramones?
'Cause I love ramones... ow!
That's a "no"on the ramones,I guess.
Okay,I don't thinkthat's
in the buy more manual.
What did sarah tell you?
I know you talked to her.
It's what I dofor a living.
oh,no,here it is,on the
bottom shelf: Ramones.
-There you go.
-Thanks.
-Bye.
-I love you.
What did you tell chuck?
That you're a
cold-bloodedkiller. Was I lying?
No.
The way I figure it,the only two people that
knew the doctorwas coming are right here.
Since I didn't cap
him,you're under arrest.
quick,take a pic.
She's so hot. Did you get it? Come on.
Let's go put iton the internet.
-Mr.  Bartowski.
-Hi lester.
Uh,code zebra.
Linux install at afactory
off ventura. 142 euclid.
Uh... I'm sorry. Why-why
can't you and jeff go?
linux,pcs? We're,uh,we're mac
guys,chuck. We're... we're it artists.
Okay. Yeah. Uh... fine,whatever.
I'll be back in half an hour.
And,uh,just tell
caseythat I'm on my cell.
You tell him. I'm not your servant.
-Okay,youknow what...
- no,no,I mean,I'm gonna tell him.
I just,you know,I mean,in
general,I don't always...
absolutely,I'm going to...
right now,should I tell him?
-hello?
-Pull over.
Well,I can't pull over.
-I have a home install at,uh...
-142 euclid?
Guess who called that in?
Oh,my god. It was you!
You killed the doctor,and
now you're here to kill me!
are you out of your mind?
What... what... what...
what happened to you?
Your girlfriend happened.
-What,who,sarah?
-She's rogue,chuck.
She killed the doctor,then
she tried to kill me.
Is she okay?
Yeah,I'm golden. Thanks for asking.
No,no,no,why should I believe you?
She showed me the bomb.
She saidyou did it.
Nsa incinerator,right?
It's a niceexplosive easily
purchasedon the black market.
What do you really
knowabout sarah,chuck,huh?
Think.
She's cia.
She workedwith bryce.
He was rogue. Maybe she is,too.
She found you in L.A.
,But she couldn't grab
you because I was around.
So she had to wait her chance.
Dr.  Zarnow screwed that up.
He could pull those secrets out of your head,then
she loses the intersect,so she had to act fast.
let's go. Come on.
thought I turnedthat off.
Well,it's not me. Is it yours?
no.
nsa incinerator! Run!
casey! Casey!
You're nervouscooking,babe. Relax.
Devon,this dinnerhas to go well.
It's going to be awesome.
You don't know chuck.
He freaks outwhen he likes a girl.
Yeah,ain't thatthe truth,huh?
You know practicemakes perfect.
How did you get in here?
Uh,chuck's window.
Or,as I like to callit,the morgan door.
I got to lock the window.
I wonder wherechuck is.
Still thinkit was me?
:Why would sarah do this?
She's cleaningthe operation.
:Cleaning?
Eliminating everyoneshe's
come in contact with.
You know where she is?
We have to get back to my house.
She's having dinnerwith us tonight.
No,kid,you're on the
next plane to washington.
-But my sister...
- doesn't have a super computerin her noggin.
You're the priority.
It's casey. Put me
through to general... hey!
Hey!
Chuck!
well,it's about time.
Chuck.
Where have you been?
Why?
You,uh,you surprisedto see me?
What?
-Where's casey?
-I don't know.
Maybe he's havingsome car trouble.
Everyone okay?
Yeah,just a little
hungry,dude. You're late.
And dirtyfor my taste.
And your girlfriend has been
just nothing but mean to me.
Look out for her.
So I'm glad everyone'sgetting
along so well.
Yeah,your sister is awesome.
Indeed.
Hey! I've got an idea.
Why don't we actually go
out,huh,for pizzaor something,
someplace public,with lots
and lotsof people around?
Uh,chuck,I've beencooking all day.
Yeah,cooking pot
roast,dude,which is my favorite.
Manzoom,manjo. Let's eat.
Sit down,okay? It'll be good.
Lady. Looks great,baby.
This looksdelicious,ellie.
Oh,it was nothing.
So,sarah,let's turn this
up a notchpersonal style.
Tell us somethingabout yourself.
Well,I'm originallyfrom
D.C. I just moved here.
Oh,chuck hada friend from D.C.
A former friend.
You know,former because a: He was
a jerk,and b: He'S...well,he's dead.
The girl chuck wasdating
before you-- he stole her.
Ugh,I just don't know howanyone
could choose bryce over chuck.
hi. I'm john casey. I just moved inupstairs.
I thought I mightbring something over.
Ow,come in.
Chuck,you didn't tell meyou're
bringing another friend.
Hey. Hi. Yeah.
It totally slipped my mind that my friend,john
casey,was coming over,and we work atbuy more together.
Morgan,you know johnfrom buy more.
I was telling him we weregonna have a get-together
and that,you know,the more,the merrier.
You pull a stuntlike that
again,I'll kill youbefore she can.
You kidder.
Chuck,we're goingto need another chair.
Okeydokey.
You know what? I'mcrashing the
party. Maybe I should...I'll get it.
Strange.
nsa ran a checkon sarah walker to see what we
had... two years ago,she posedas a french diplomat.
Infiltrated the
innercircle of an arms deal.
Killed the entire circle.
With a bomb?
We don't know.
Her alias was elana truffaut.
Eyth were poisoned.
-At dinner.
-Wonderful.
hey,sis...chair. Ta-da!
So...thank you.
Chuck.
I mean,I knew that you had it in you,butshe
is... oh,she is...wow,she's really great.
Yeah. She'S... unpredictable.
Hey,listen to me.
You have no reasonto be nervous. Okay?
Now,you have agreat girl out
there. I mean,she evenmade dessert.
-Dessert?
-Yeah.
Oh,dessert. Dessert. Poison.
Don't freak out.
Stop!
We... uh,we didn't do a toast... yet.
Which I... whichI'll do right now.
Uh... so,I'd like topropose
a toast. To my sister.
To my sister,and-andto... to
a meal that looks so great.
And devon,you're great.
And sarah. And sarah
for a great dessert.
And to john casey and-and his... and his...and
his mini quiches,which areequally as great.
And what aboutme,chuck?
For what?
And to morganfor his great comic timing.
Thank yo  sir.
Cheers.
Well,you know,that
soufflÈdoes look amazing.
You're right,honey. I can't even resist.
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait.
-Who likes magic?
-I do!
I know a trick.
Chuck... oh,chuck,what are you doing?
Voila!
0whoa,chuck,that was... 0I
knew you could do it,man.
Flamb?
chuck!
Chuck,look,no matterhow stressed out you
are,it is never okay to murdera woman's souffl?
Um,you know what? Let me talk to him.
Casey,hey,maybe,uh...
tell me exactlyey cas said.
Nothing. Everything's okay.
makeup sex. Nice.
what did he tell you?
That you killed Dr.  Zarnow and
poisoned a bunchof french diplomats.
They're blaming me for zarnow?
If you're planning on
hurtingme,even to prove a point,
I think you should know I have
a very low thresholdfor pain.
And you believe casey?
Tell me aboutthe french diplomats.
They were french assassins,and they
were after me,but I got to them first.
And you know what? I'm
kinda glad that I did.
Chuck,do you really
thinkthat my name is sarah?
I never asked youto believe
me. I asked youto trust me.
This doesn't make sense.
If casey didn't kill zarnow,then...
what are you doing?
I have to go right now.
Uh,I'm sorry.
I have to go,but dinn won wasderful.
Gotta go.Be back.
Yeah,well,I betterbe going,too.
This has beengreat.Thanks.
Uh... you're welcome.
I think that went well.
You know,not great,but
I think it went well.
So,uh,I'm gonna makea little doggy
bag and head out my morgan door.
How about that?
Sounds good? Super-duper.
Sarah,wait!
You stay inside.
Do what I say.
Do you think we were wrong?
Casey!
hey,don't move.
Zarnow?
good to see you again,agent casey.
oh,my god.
Yep,we were wrong.
Casey,he's got sarah.We've
got to save her.
Brilliant deduction,nancy drew.
Now pull out the tranq dart!
Oh,I have a very
strongaversion to needles.
Do it!
Okay,uh,here we go.
that was the doctor,right?
He's probably not dead?
And the sun sets in the west.
Nothing gets by you.
One,two,three.
what's he gonnado with sarah?
He's gonna torture her until
she tells himall about you.
Come on.
If we hurry,we can catch him.
All right,where are we going?
I laced my quicheswith microbots.
You're not kidding,are you?
I don't kid about quiche.
We can trace himusing the car's tracker.
Yeah,I think that only
comeswith the sports package.
We made some enhancementswhen
your car was in the shop.
Got a signal.
Let's go.
Hey,casey,casey.
Wait a minute.
Why,why would hebring sarah here?
I don't know.
You wait here.
damn tranq dart.
come on.
Oh,god.
hey,wait,you idiot!
It's morgan.
He ate your quiches.
We're onthe wrong trail.
Come on.
I got nothing.
What do you meanyou got nothing?
Then what do we do?
It's over.She's gone.
No,no,no,no,no.
Okay,this is our fault.
We didn't believe her.
Now we have to save her.
Look,if you were a bad guy,what
would you do,fly sarah outon a plane?
Would you use a
boator a-a-a what?
Chopper.
Small airfieldnear the water.
The closest I could find.
Then do-do a satellite
searchusing the touch screen
and then maybe limit thatto airfields
that are withina certain range of us
and then maybe limit that by if
there's activityon the ground?
That's not bad.
Thanks.
Yeah,I was just kindof,you
know,spitballing,just kind oftop of my head.
I was thinking...found it.
Port of los angeles.
Floor it.
Okay.
This is how this is gonna work.
I'm gonna go over there,rescue sarah,
and capture Dr.Zarnow,shoot
anybody who gets in my way.
You,you're gonna stay here.
So,in this planI basically do nothing?
Yep.
Let's do this.
All right,all right.
Now we wait.
Stay in the car.
Do not leave the car.
Do not leave this car.
sarah,are you okay?
:What are you doing here?
Stupid question.
Okay,uh,should I...?
Sorry.
Chuck,you have to get out of here.
No,I'm here to save you.
You shouldn't even be
here;you're too valuable,
and,besides,I have this well in hand.
Uh-huh,yeah,'cause
it looks well in hand.
Just find me somethingto pick this lock.
I don'T... okay,here.
go,go,go!
The tape,the tape.
The helicopter's ready,agent walker.
This is your last chance.
We're going toa special facility
where they're goingto torture you.
Really torture,not this child's play.
Or you couldjust tell
me who is patient X.
Somethingfor the flight.
Oh,crap.
Run!
I know you.I know your secret.
You-you've been feedingamerican
science to north korea for years.
Ah,patient X.
To think that my secretsare
in that head of yours.
It's an honor,really.
Of course,to hell with honor.
I'm here for the impressivedollar
figure the human intersectwill fetch.
Who will I offer you to first?
sarah... sarah...
don't worry,agent walker.
I'll take goodcare of him.
No,casey,don't shoot.They have chuck.
Proceed to bravo coordinates.
The ship will bewaiting there.
It's about ten miles offshore.
15-minute flight.
Don't move!
You must be kidding.
I want you to landthe
helicopter right now.
It's heavier than you thought.
What?
The gun.
It's heavy.
Don'T... don't!
Give me back the gun.
I'm not giving you the gun!
you shot the pilot,you idiot!
I didn't mean to do that.
What's happening?
Who's flying this thing?
You're goingto kill us both.
Come on,chuck.
let me go.
get your hands off of me!
Get off of me!
oh,god.
That's a crane.
Oh,my god,casey,I thinkchuck's
flying the chopper.
Yeah,I'm here.
I told you to stay in the car.
You know what? Forget about the car.
Tell me how to fly a helicopter.
All right,there's a
collectivein the cyclic control.
What?
One's the stick.One looks
likean emergency brake.
Grab 'em both.
Okay,okay,I got it.
This is not working!
Push the stickjust a bit forward while
doing the same thingwith the emergency brake.
ground--
not good.
Pull up! Pull up!
Pull up on the emergency brake!
Level off.Level off!
I don't know how.I don't
know how to level off!
Listen,moron,you want to die?
Casey,put sarah on the phone.
Give me thephone,casey.
Here.
Okay... uh,chuck,you're goinge to bokay.
Now,I need you to focus.
Uh,have you ever playedany
flying games before?
Flight simulators? Yeah.
Flight simulators?
Yeah,sure,I've done those,yeah.
Okay,which ones?
Uh,maverick of the skies...
uh,stealth fighter elite...
uh,apache chopper patrol.
Great.
Okay,now rememberthat last one.
I want you to pretend likeyou're
playing that game,okay.
You're just in your bedroom,you're
playing a game,and none of this is real.
it's just a game.
It's just a game.
Okay,I can do this.
I can play this game.
Easy,chuck,easy.
Uh... uh,is thisone of those
helicopters that can turn into a boat?
No,it isn'T.
Just ease tothe right
and goose the brake.
They designed the game
exactly like the helicopter.
I got it.
Almost there.
A little more to the right.
Keeping right.Keeping right.
Goosinakthe brE.
It's just a game.
A big scary video game.
oh,thank you,god!
oh,yes!
You are wonderful.
And that is how...I do... that!
That's how we do that.
Go,team.Sarah... see sarah.
Up top on that one.
Palms are a little sweaty,but...
what the hellwere you thinking?
Clammy hands,got it,no good.
Chuck,the secrets that you
knoware incredibly important.
You compromised everything
when you stoppedtrusting me.
And when you gotout of the car.
Listen,I'M... I'm sorry,okay?
No,it is not okay.
How could you thinkI was the double,huh?
You know,I am not bryce.
Bryce betrayed
everythingthat I believe in,
and if you ever accuse meof
that again,then I will walk away.
Mission over.We all
go back to washington.
And you do not want thatto happen,chuck.
That you should trust me on.
Way to go,ace.
Dad's suit?
Yeah.
It's my only one.
I'm quite certain
hewouldn't mind,though.
You realize that you don'thave
to go to bryce's funeral.
Yeah,yeah,I guess.
It's just we had a lot of history.
Even if he did get mekicked out
of school and steal my girlfriend.
Well... you've moved on
to bigger andbetter girls.
I don't really mean
biggerlike,literally bigger.
I just mean that,um...
that I really like sarah.
And I hope you guys work things out
before the next dinner party,of course.
I don't know...I don't know,sis.
I... I... look,I reallythink I blew it.
Chuck,just try apologizing.
It goes a long way.
Sarah's special.
She's different fromyour
stanford friends.
He flew a helicopter?
Your report was
ratherterrifying,major casey.
Do we really havethe situation in hand,or
should Mr.Bartowskibe in our care full-time?
Well,you know how I feel,general.
But for now,we're in control.
Then chuck stays where he is.
But,uh,don't gettoo comfortable,casey.
The new intersect will be
upand running in six months.
And what happens to
chuckwhen this is done?
Well,you'll dowhat you do best.
knock,knock.
Hey,chuck.
How is everything?
I saw youat the funeral.
Oh,yeah,I had to go.
After everything bryce
did,he was still my partner.
Look,I'm not accusing
youof anything... today.
Yesterday,yes,I may havelaid it on
a little thick with the accusing.
But I'm really sorry about that.
Instead of not trusting you,I should
have been thanking youfor saving my life
and protecting the
countryand-and-and...
and making really tastygourmet wieners.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
It was our first fight.
You know,it's a big step,if our
relationshipwere remotely real.
You know,with Dr.Zarnowgone,chuck,those
intersect secretsaren't going anywhere.
That means moremissions,more danger,more secrets
that you can't tellyour sister or your friends.
I know that.
Some people want to be heroes
and others have to be asked.
So... chuck,are you ready?
good.
I hope we're notinterrupting anything.
Uh... by the way,I thoughtwe'd give
that dinner another shot,maybe here.
We knew you'dforgive him.
Right,and you realize thatyou
all have to eat my cooking.
Give me the 411on the corn dogs.
What do youthink,man?
What do you recommend,buddy?
Sarah?
Holy... okay.
Cheers.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: YTET- max –°“∞»ÀÕı