Stu Brewster here,
and I'd like you all
to meet Jeffery Barnes, the new
Missile Command world champ.
SAN FERNANO VALLEY, 1983
VALLEY VIDEO GAME
CHAMPIONSHIPS
Thanks for
joining us, Jeff.
My pleasure, Stu.
Now, Jeff,
you've dedicated the last
three years of your life
to playing Missile Command.
You've managed
to take a video game
and raise it to a level
that can only be
described as an art form.
So let me ask
the question on
everybody's mind:
What's next
for Jeff Barnes?
What's next? Uh...
I hadn't really, uh...
How can I make up my mind
when I've got
so many tasty options?
I've got so many tasty options.
SAN FERNANDO VALLEY
25 YEARS LATER
Jeff, please.
There we go, buddy.
Score.
Powwow on the
sales floor.
And one of you two idiots better
light a fire under Bartowski.
He's late.
Aren't you
forgetting something?
It's only the most important
meal of the day, bud.
Of course!
Breakfast.
Thanks.
What did I... What is that?
What did I just drink?
It's a ginseng
protein shake.
Been used
thousands of years
in the East
to promote Yang energy.
And let me tell you, brother,
it does wonders
for your wang energy.
Great, thanks.
Hey, where were you last night?
We heard you come
stomping in at, like,
4:00 in the morning.
Yeah, oh, yeah, it was a...
it was a crazy night.
Morgan and I stole a car,
and then we drove around
shaking down liquor stores
and smacking around hookers.
Relax, it's a video game.
Oh, good... video games.
Come on, El.
I mean, what's one night
- of blowing off a little steam?
- One nights have
a funny way of adding up.
I mean, what's cool
when you're in college...
We were just wondering...
what happened
to all your big plans, bro?
All that talk about
backpacking across Europe,
or finishing
your college classes?
You know, I just have a lot on
my plate at this precise moment.
Well, like what, precisely?
Chuck, we were happy when you
decided not to move out,
but shouldn't your life
be moving somewhere?
It's time for you people
to get moving around here.
Show some initiative!
Well, I've got
just the guy to help.
I'd like you to meet
Emmett Milbarge.
Emmett here's an efficiency
expert, and he's been sent
by Buy More corporate
to tighten your slack-asses up.
Thank you for your very kind
words of introduction, Michael.
I'll be in my office.
Well, it is just
so nice to be here in...
Burbank.
Burbank, California.
Just a real pleasure
to meet all of you
in the flesh.
I personally am
looking forward
to spending more time here
in the Buy More trenches,
getting to know
the rank and the file.
Unfortunately,
my visit here
isn't going to be all fun.
I'm going to be
interviewing you,
and I'm going to be evaluating
you on your performance,
And, perhaps, even...
trimming the fat.
So... who would like
to go first?
We'll just start out simple.
Why do you
belong at the Buy More?
I satisfy a quota.
My dad's part Indian.
The cool kind of Indian,
though, not like Lester.
I used to be
in management, myself,
so I know how
to grease the store's... cogs.
- "Cogs"?
- Make sure they don't...
squeak.
If you know what I'm saying.
ASS-KISSER
Why do I belong at the Buy More?
You know, I'm going to have
to think about that.
I'm going to go
grab a soda.
And... You want one?
'Cause it's my treat.
I'll gr- I'll grab you one.
And I'll be back in a jiff.
UNTRAINABLE
I speak more than one language,
binary code.
Zero, zero, zero, one,
one, zero,
one... zero.
PROSTITUTE?
What would I do?
I'd just ask W-W-C-D?
- "What would Chuck do?"
- Chuck?
The chain of command?
Well, there's, like, Chuck,
and then there's, like,
the rest of us.
Oh, and then there's Jeff.
Sometimes I... W-W-C-D-N?
"Wonder what Chuck's doing now?"
Who represents
the Buy More ideal?
Who makes the trains
run on time?
Who provides your moral compass?
Who holds
the team together?
- Chuck.
Lester... no, Chuck.
- Well...
I'm looking forward
to meeting this Chuck fella.
If he ever decides to show up.
Chuck, you picked one hell
of a morning to be late.
- Yeah, crazy night, Morgan.
- Lover's tryst?
Say no more.
Unless you care to infuse
your story with a more
tawdry level of detail?
You don't. Okay, listen,
there's this efficiency guy
who's been looking all over
for you, all right.
So if he asks, you have
gallstone issues.
- That's a thing, right?
- Morgan?
Well, I had to think
on my feet here, Chuck.
This Emmett guy's
been busting my...
preconceptions.
And helping me see the Buy More
in a whole new...
Hey, hello!
This is him... Chuck.
We finally meet, Chuck.
Hi.
SOMALIA TRAINING CAMPS
DIRTY BOMB TRADE
NUCLEAR WEAPONS TRAINING
Are you feeling all right?
No- yes!
Yes, I'm fine.
Actually on second thought,
I think my gallstones
are acting up, so...
Hi.
Do you know this man?
No. No, never
seen him before
in my life.
Wait a minute.
Is that one of the sweat hogs
from Welcome Back, Kotter?
He is a Buy More employee.
You know, he doesn't work
at this store.
But you should check out
one of our other
13 convenient
Southern California locations.
Hmm...
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
CHUCK 205
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴:我爱狮心小s
Farrokh Bulsara,
CLASSIFIED
born in the Asir Province, 1974.
The past ten years,
he's been hopping
between training camps
from Syria to Somalia.
What does a global terrorist
want with a nerd like Jeff?
Insightful question,
Bartowski.
It's why we have
an Intersect.
We want you to approach
Jeff socially.
Get to know him
better and see
if you can get
him to open up
about his past.
You want me to hang out
with Jeff?
It's either that, or we throw
him in the back of a van
and have an agency interrogation
team go to work on him.
Great, so it comes down
to either torturing him
or torturing me?
Looks like we got a bogey.
Sarah?
Is that my sister?
Ellie, what a surprise.
Yeah, I was just driving around
I thought it'd
be nice, uh...
I thought it would be nice
if you and I could talk
without Chuck, actually.
Oh, okay.
Not polite
to spy, Chuck.
I would hate it if he found out
that I was going
behind his back
like this.
Oh, well, your secret
is safe with me.
Do you know if he has any plans?
Tonight?
Uh, actually, I think he is
hanging out with Jeff.
Nerd Herd, creepy, serial-killer
Jeff?
Yeah.
I think it's time
that you and I had a talk.
I hope you enjoyed
your fro-yo?
Ha. Yeah, I was,
uh, just seeing my girlfriend.
Girlfriend? Oh...
I, too, have
a special lady friend.
Henrietta.
She works in our Ontario branch,
accounts payable.
She's a real tigress.
Well, now that
we've gotten the topic
of our love life out of the way,
perhaps you'd like to sit
down for our interview.
How is tomorrow?
'Cause I'm really more
of a morning person.
I'll be the judge of that.
Hey, buddy.
Where are you going?
What'd I do?
Nothing! No.
You know... nothing.
Just... you know, we never
really get the chance to talk.
How about we grab a beer?
No, thanks.
I could be enticed
to grab a dozen beers, however.
It's a date.
We can kick it at my place.
You're going
to love Roscoe.
He's my ferret.
Ooh... you know what?
I'm actually allergic
to any and every member
of the polecat family.
So maybe we can kick it here?
Sure.
- Hmm.
- Hmm...
Following a thorough inspection
of the branch,
there seems to be no sign
of intelligent life.
May I present
tonight's feature entertainment.
You made an Anna music video?
You like?
Wow.
It's really-
I know, man.
She's my muse.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
I'm going to slip
into my drinking pants.
Look at that!
Abort mission.
Extraction required.
The Intersect
has been compromised.
Negative.
Perimeter is secure.
I'm talking about the weirdo
inside the Buy More!
I'm starting to think
that there's something
going on with my brother.
Oh.
Why?
What do you mean?
It's just
everything seemed
to be moving along
just fine for Chuck.
And you had everything
to do with that.
Oh, thanks,
but, uh, I-I can't
take the credit.
Then, I don't know,
it's like...
it's like he's slipping
back into old Chuck mode.
You know, no
confidence.
No direction.
It's-
it's the Morgan
Years revisited.
I mean he went to
Stanford, for God's sakes.
Did you know that he's 12
credits short of graduating?
12 credits short of a real life.
I know that I sound
like his mother.
Just tell me that I don't have
anything to worry about
and I will lay off.
Pound! Pound! Pound!
Go! Yes!
Pound! Pound!
Quit being such
a lightweight!
Resuming dictation.
Yes! Yes!
I'd like to report the following
violation of Buy More policy:
misappropriation
of the home theater room,
after hours
consumption of alcohol.
And lewd use
of a musical montage.
I'm going hohome at once
to file this report.
Crazy thing happened today.
Uh, some dude came into the
store looking for you.
He had this goofy,
old picture and
everything.
Only a matter of time, I guess.
What?
You mean you
know the guy?
I'd imagine...
he's one of my fans.
You want to see something
I've never shared with anyone?
Please don't be a porno.
- Please, please don't be a porno.
- And I'd like you all
to meet Jeffery Barnes.
The new Missile Command
world champ.
Missile Command?
I used to kick ass at that game.
Well, I was the best.
By breaking the all-time record,
you've won $100 in quarters
and a year's supply
of Slim Jim's.
This prize will be presented
by none other
than Mr. Morimoto, CEO
and chief engineer
at Atari games.
Dude, you are
so wasted.
FACIAL SCANNING
COMPLETE
FARROKH BULSARA
What is it
about bad guys and vans?
Okay.
Okay, Chuck,
party's over.
Hey, hey,
I- I flashed! Some guy
on the TV. He's a video...
Later, Chuck. We have guests.
Out the back door. Now!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, what about Jeff?
- What about him?
- We can't just leave him here.
- He's deadweight.
You weren't kidding.
Go! Go!
He pukes on my
upholstery,
he's gonna wish we left him
with the terrorists.
Search the place.
Should I be worried about him?
You know, um, Chuck is, uh...
Chuck is like a duck.
Sometimes
it seems like
he is just gliding along,
but beneath the surface,
his, uh... his little feet
are-are just
paddling away like crazy.
Deep down,
I really think
Chuck is an incredibly mature
and responsible guy.
Chuck?
Oh!
- Oh,
- is he okay?
Yeah. Don't worry.
This guy's feeling no pain.
Ouch.
Here we go. Here we go.
Big boy. Big boy.
What's up, ladies?
You take the brunette.
I'm gonna take a crack
at the blonde.
???
Oh...! Jeff!
I'm, uh, supposed
to give this to you.
MY NAME IS JEFF AND I'M LOST
Okay.
Is that your address?
- Yeah.
- All right, we're gonna get you a cab.
Already have.
Already here. Thank you.
Great. Awesome.
Come on, Jeff.
That was a great
time last night, huh?
You got smashed
and passed out,
and we just watched, and
it was really awkward.
Okay, here
you go, buddy.
Get home safe.
Chuck.
We're about to have one of
those conversations, aren't we?
Well, if I wasn't
worried enough,
last night's
performance was...
Not... Not one of
my proudest moments.
Uh-uh.
I feel like you left
all those back at Stanford.
I'm sorry. I just...
You were so close to graduating.
You know, maybe if you just
went back and finished,
you could move on
to the next phase.
I mean, if the world
were gonna end today,
- why would you want to...?
- I- I hear you.
I really do.
But all those goals
I used to have-
I still have 'em.
Okay.
Hey, sis?
The world's not gonna end today.
I have very reliable sources.
Wild night,
huh, buddy?
Nah. Pretty
standard Tuesday.
This is bad.
This is very bad.
Can't you see
that we're losing them, man?
I'm your best friend, Jeff.
No, I'm your best
friend, Chuck!
Oh, isn't life grand!
Maybe we should form
an alliance.
You and me could be
best friends?
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, dude.
Let's not, uh...
Let's not panic
here, okay?
Thanks, man.
Well, you know...
It was very
comfortable.
Sure.
Excuse me.
We need to talk.
My sister thinks
I'm an idiot, I know.
Actually, we just got
some fresh intel
on your favorite
video game designer.
There were a few things
Morimoto left out of his bio.
Yeah. Guy secretly worked
for Japanese military.
In 1980, they
launched Morimoto's
first-generation
weapons satellite.
The guy who created
Missile Command
commands
actual missiles?
Via satellite.
It's still up there-
dormant,
but presumed operational.
Anyone knows how
to fire that puppy up,
it's Morimoto.
And you think he's working
with Farrokh and the terrorists?
Well, he hasn't been seen
in years.
We captured this image
outside Morimoto's office
about an hour ago.
What about Jeff?
How is he supposed
to be involved in all this?
The only way
to find out is
to get into
Atari headquarters.
Security's going to be tight.
But if we don't
secure the satellite,
then Jeff's safety is gonna be
the least of our concerns.
So how do you want to do this?
Guys...
I have an idea.
All right, be
cool, Casey.
Have you seen
what I'm wearing?
Just let me do
the talking, okay?
These are my people-
programmers, nerds.
And right now, their
network is being attacked
by a particularly
nasty virus.
Back at Stanford, we called
it the Bartowski special.
Yeah, real cool
there, Chuck.
Damn computers are out
all over the building.
Gentlemen,
excuse me.
What do you want?
We heard you're having
a computer problem.
Someone
called. Bill?
Bob... I can't
remember,
exactly; it was a
very common name.
- Yeah, we got it covered.
- Mind if I take a peek?
Look, nerd,
Atari has
more Ph. D.s
than friggin'
Microsoft.
Yeah. Why don't you help
some old lady log onto AOL?
Nice one. Ooh!
Plan B.
Hi.
I hear you're having
a computer problem.
See, if I could just get
onto that terminal, I could
set off the fire alarm,
I couldcrash the power,
create a diversion.
Or we could just
take the stairs.
Looks like
Agent Walker's
got the diversion
pretty well covered.
Sarah doesn't even know
how to fix a computer.
The second she touches
that machine, our cover's blown.
The CPUs have been
massively overvolted,
but we may be able to ghost
the drive on another system.
The more elegant solution
would be to flash the BIOS
and swap out
the cooked CPU.
What are you guys waiting for?
Okay. I'm gonna
see if I can find
another way into
the penthouse.
You wait here
where it's safe.
This place is creepy.
So creepy.
Well, if it isn't my friend
from the Buy More.
What a funny coincidence
finding you here.
Yeah, it's
freakin' hilarious.
What a small world, right?
I got a... I got a
call about a computer
that was acting
up here, and so...
In fact, is this
the right floor?
I don't even
know if it's...
You have the correct floor.
- This way. Please.
- You know if you're busy,
I can come back
another time.
Uh-uh. You're timing
was perfect.
I hope
the machine doesn't give you
too much trouble.
* What you say
about his company *
* Is what you say
about society *
* Catch the mist,
catch the myth *
* Catch the mystery,
catch the drift *
You should not be here.
Um, uh...
* The world is,
the world is... *
Mr. Morimoto?
You listening
to Rush?
You are too late.
He took the code.
Who are they, terrorists?
I knew I should've
never hidden
the numbers inside
the machine.
You hid the satellite code
inside a game of
Missile Command?
Every game, hidden
in the final board.
The kill screen.
A secret level
only I could achieve.
The mathematics underlying
the final board
are too advanced.
It's like the music
of the universe.
Hands up.
I am sorry, I
cannot do that.
- What's going on here, Chuck?
- Wait.
Wait, if the bad guys
have the code,
why are you still
playing the game?
Uh-oh.
We're running out of time!
SAVE YOURSELVES!
- Let's get out of here, Chuck.
- No, we can't just leave him here.
- Not this time.
- No, no, no, wait!
Go, go, go!
It's a... wait, wait!
THE END
General, we're
sorry to report
that Farrokh and his
team have the code.
That, and they murdered
Morimoto.
That means that your duties
are no longer required
on this operation.
Casey,
we're turning this matter
over to the 30th Space Wing
at Vandenberg.
Wait, you're launching an ICBM?
You think you can shoot
down that satellite
before it
shoots us?
Morimoto's satellite
will be passing
over California in four hours.
Best case,
we shoot it down
off the coast before its own
missiles are armed.
The satellite
falls to Earth
with acceptable
civilian casualties.
Wait a second, acceptable what?
I'd like to hear
the bad version.
We miss.
What happens then?
Farrokh uses
Morimoto's satellite
to start World War III.
Hey, what about the...
what about the kill screen?
- Excuse me? - Missile Command - Morimoto said
that the code is hidden
in every arcade game.
If we can get to the kill
screen, we can get the code,
and then we can take control
of the satellite.
We'll have our engineers
take a...
No, look, the only way to get
the code is by beating the game,
and the only person
who can beat the game...
- Is
- burned to a crisp.
- I was talking about Jeff.
- So was I.
Casey, you coordinate
with the Air Force
while Mr. Bartowski
pursues his...
contingency plan.
But I promise you,
one way or another,
I am bringing
that satellite down.
You want me
to come out
of Missile Command
retirement?
You're serious?
Deadly.
I don't know, man.
Come on, what's
the problem?
I guess I'm just cool
with resting on my laurels
- and whatnot.
- But Jeff...
you could be
the first guy
to ever get to
the kill screen.
Listen, it doesn't exist.
The kill screen's just a myth.
I promise you, it's real,
and you're the only one
who can do it.
I'm a little out
of shape, mentally.
Jeff, it's just a
stupid video game!
That's where
you're wrong, Chuck.
It's more
than a game.
Besides, what do you care
whether I play or not?
I guess I was just really moved
by what you said last night.
- Huh?
- Oh, you remember.
Come on.
How you were
sick and tired
of busting your ass
at this stupid store.
How you had this
incredible gift
that you couldn't wait
for the world to see.
Really? I said that?
Sure you did, Jeff.
About Missile Command?
You were very compelling.
Okay, I'll do it.
- I'll play.
- Buddy...
But first,
I'm gonna need provisions.
I need two bottles
grape cough syrup,
one pound M&Ms, no brown,
and my lucky arcade game from
the Gas 'N Sip in Tarzana.
Done.
Really?
I want Anna
wearing a hula skirt
fanning me with a palm frond.
- HUH?
- I sweat profusely when I play.
And finally,
I need a crowd.
- I want you to get some of my old fans back.
- Come on.
The people that were into that
game are in their 40s now.
They have jobs, and wives,
and kids and...
Hey, hey, hey-
Morgan, buddy.
Can you give me
a hand with this?
Why don't you just
go ask your buddy, Jeff?
He's in the break room.
We're putting together
this like video game
exhibition-thingy
this afternoon.
Jeff's gonna make a run
at the all-time
Missile Command high score.
- Whoa.
- Hey, where are you going?
Sounds like you two guys
got it all worked out.
Morgan, I desperately
need your help, okay?
If Jeff doesn't break
the Missile Command record...
What, Chuck?
The world's gonna end?
Look, all I know
is that I need your help.
Okay, I can't do this
without you, buddy.
I can't.
Hey, hey, was Jeff...
was Jeff the president
of his high school
audio/video club?
Doubt it.
Was Jeff a roadie
for Mamma Mia
for four
straight summers?
Does Jeff own
his own smoke machine?
- No, but I do. Okay.
- Huh?
Jeff is a loser, dude.
I'll see what I can do.
You're the best, buddy.
Oh, and I'm gonna need
to borrow your girlfriend.
- Oh, dude, she's all yours.
- Great.
JEFF BARNES TO PLAY EXHIBITION!
MISSILE COMMAND
THE GREAT ONE RETURNS
JEFF BARNES AT BUY MORE ASAP!
Jeff! Jeff! Jeff! Jeff!
Jeff! Jeff!
I'm here at a Burbank
electronics store
where a local man
prepares to break
the Missile Command record.
BLAST FROM THE PAST
A FADING STAR SEEKS NEW GLORY
Now for those of you
who weren't around
a quarter century ago,
Jeffrey Barnes
first made his mark on...
...way back in 1983.
Sarah, Sarah-
I know where Farrokh is.
The terrorists are using
a television station
to control the satellite;
they're here in L.A.
Chuck flashed.
He knows where they're
controlling the satellite.
There is still time
before the satellite
is in range.
Maybe Chuck's right,
but there's nothing you can do
to stop it without the code.
Well, I'm going to go
to the news station.
Knock yourself out.
I have my orders.
33 minutes and five
seconds, this finger
gonna push
that button.
Hmm. I'll call you
from the road.
- Agent Walker.
- Yes.
Who do you trust to bring down
a rogue satellite more:
some burnout loser
playing a video game
or an Air Force ICBM?
I trust Chuck.
Jeff! Jeff! Jeff! Jeff! Jeff!
I'd like you all to meet
Jeffrey Barnes.
Uh...
Missile Command
world champ.
I don't feel so hot.
What? No, no, no.
You're gonna be great.
You look great.
You're gonna
kill it, buddy.
What was I thinking, man?
No one can get
the kill screen.
I can't handle the math.
You've dedicated three years
of your life to playing
Missile Command.
It's too heavy.
It feels like my brain
is about to...
What's next for Jeff Barnes,
Missile Command world champ?
Get up for
a second.
Hey.
I'll get some water.
Hey, we-we-we need
to take care of this.
Yeah.
Here I come.
Hey, hey.
Come on, buddy,
come on!
Wake up, buddy!
You got to play!
You got to get the kill screen,
you got to get the code.
If we don't stop that
satellite, they're gonna launch
some crazy missile into
space and then-then...
then it's World War III.
Acceptable civilian casualties.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Chuck, what's up?
Hey, I was thinking,
why don't you guys
get out of town, maybe
Palm Springs, you and Awesome
just get out of town.
Now, actually,
would be a great time.
Trip's on me, you know.
- Early wedding present.
- Wait a minute.
Are you trying to get rid of me?
No, no, I just
thought it'd be nice.
What's gotten into you?
I don't know.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I- I know I've been a bit
of a disappointment lately.
I- I-I want you
to be proud of me.
I just... I ran out of time,
that's all.
Why don't we talk about this
when you get home?
I got to run.
I love you, Ellie.
Honey,
do you think my brother's
on drugs?
That'd explain a lot.
They're going nuts
out there, okay?
These nerds are gonna
tear this joint apart.
You got to do
something.
What am I supposed to do?
Well, they came to see
video game greatness.
Someone better deliver.
Ladies and gentlemen...
or Gentlemen,
let me introduce you
to the challenger.
Hailing from the City of Angels,
the Master of Disaster...
What's going on?
...the King of Sting,
the Dancing Destroyer,
Charles Irving
Bartowski!
Who is this guy?
Where's
Jeff Barnes?
Who authorized this?
This is an abomination.
THE END
You suck, Bartowski.
Are you listening to Rush?
Music of the universe.
Missile Command.
The mathematical pattern
underlying the game
is exactly the same as-
Morgan.
Hey, uh, buddy,
do, do we carry any Rush CDs
in the store?
No need, I got 'em
all on my Zune.
You have a Zune?
Are you kidding me? No.
No, I'll grab my iPod.
Good, good, good,
I have, I have
a very,
very special request.
On my mark.
Three, two, one.
Mark!
* A modern-day warrior-
mean, mean stride *
* Today's Tom Sawyer-
mean, mean pride... *
* Though his mind is not
for rent *
* Don't put him down
as arrogant *
* His reserve, a quiet defense *
* Riding out the day's events *
* The river... *
WEAPONS SEQUENCE INITIATED
Welcome to Strategic Air
Command, Major Casey.
* What you say
about his company *
* Is what you say
about society *
* Catch the mist,
catch the myth *
* Catch the mystery,
catch the drift... *
Engaging telemetry.
Arming warhead.
And opening silo door.
* No, his mind is not for rent *
* To any God or government *
* Always hopeful,
yet discontent *
* He knows changes
aren't permanent... *
Give me the code.
It was destroyed.
I'm gonna do this.
No one can stop
the satellite now!
Tell me what
the target is.
- What's the satellite aimed at?
- Why?
It doesn't matter.
No one will remember
who threw the first stone.
- Oh, my God.
- Gentlemen,
we have a kill screen.
I got this.
Target's to range.
Releasing synchronized safeties.
On my mark.
Three,
two, one, mark.
CONGRATULATIONS, MR. MORIMOTO.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO PLAY AGAIN?
YES              NO
NO
OZPGSB
Fire when ready, sir.
Chuck, what's happening?
Sarah, I did it!
I did it, I beat the game.
I got to the kill screen.
I got the code!
The game- it follows a pattern.
It's just like
Mr. Morimoto said-
the music of the universe.
Chuck, just give me the code.
Oscar...
Zelda...
Penguin...
Gamma...
Sector...
Bob...
WEAPONS SEQUENCE TERMINATED
Oh, my God.
Satellite's powering down.
Terminate launch sequence.
This bogey's
bugging out
and going home.
Damn.
You did it, Chuck.
It worked!
How does it feel to be a hero,
Mr. Bartowski?
Oh. Oh.
Looks like you fools had
one hell of a party.
Congratulations,
Bartowski.
That's quite
an achievement.
And in light
of today's events,
I'd like to announce
there's a new assistant
manager amongst us.
What'd I tell you, man?
It's all coming up
Bartowski.
You all remember
Mr. Emmett Milbarge.
Mr. Milbarge has
volunteered to stay on
for...
well, as long as it takes.
That's right, Michael.
I'm afraid this
branch is sick.
And not the kind of sick that
can be fixed with a Band-Aid.
What this Buy More needs
requires a surgeon.
Someone who doesn't mind
getting up to their
elbows in guts.
Mmm.
And that's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna reach in,
wrap my fingers
around the disease,
and rip... it... out.
How you feeling, buddy?
- Better.
- Good.
Thanks.
So...
Missile Command champion.
I got lucky.
You know.
Congrats.
I'm glad it was you.
I mean, you're sure
you're not...
Me? Uh-uh.
I'm cool.
Being number one
is a real bitch.
Feels like the whole world is
gunning for you, sometimes.
I can imagine.
So, what was it like?
The kill screen?
Forget it.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Oh,
I am so proud of you!
Hey, relax.
It's just a video game.
Granted, I am the best Missile
Commander in the world.
I'm not talking
about a stupid video game.
I'm talking about this.
Sarah told us
what's inside.
My diploma?
Well, don't act
so surprised.
You sly dog.
Sarah also told us about
what you've been doing
behind our backs.
She did?
Really?
Yeah. No wonder you've
been such a mess
- this past year.
- Why didn't you
tell us that you were
taking online courses?
Oh!
Oh, right... that.
You two kids have some
celebrating to do.
She's waiting
out back.
You'll thank me for that ginseng
shake in the morning.
You really surprised me,
Charles.
Well, thanks for
my fake diploma.
- What do you mean?
- I get it.
You know, you had one
of your CIA pal's
doctor it up to get
Ellie off my back.
It's real, Chuck.
Come on.
I'm serious.
You graduated.
What about my last
12 credits?
Well, Casey and I decided
that your exceptional
field service
ought to count
for something
and Stanford agreed.
Huh.
And by exceptional,
you mean, like, uh,
I don't know, decrypting
weapons-satellite codes?
Electrical Engineering.
Or running away from
exploding games
of Missile Command?
Physical Education.
You earned it, Chuck.
Thank you.
You see that star out there
on the horizon?
That's the Air Force
bouncing Morimoto's satellite
off the atmosphere
and burning it up.
Make a wish.
It's yours.
Hey, bud.
Let's party.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入