Hi.
Joshua Gomez.
Welcome to Chuck.
Do me a favor.
Put on your 3-D glasses right now.
Wow!
That's cool.
That is pretty amazing stuff.
Chuck.
Chuck, wake up.
Sarah, what are...?
What are you doing here?
Okay, uh, Sarah?
Yes, Chuck?
- This is a dream.
- No, it isn't.
Come on. Who are we...
Who are we kidding here, huh?
This is... This is clearly
my-my subconscious at work.
And on behalf of my conscious self,
I'd-I'd like to apologize.
I'm normally much more respectful
of women even in my dreams.
It's just that, you know, anxiety
and fear can-can really, um...
... affect your dream life.
And what are you afraid of?
I watched you kill that
Fulcrum agent in cold blood.
Sarah, I am...
I am not like you, okay?
I might have all these
government secrets in my brain,
but that does not make me
a real spy.
I need to tell you this
in reality, not in my dream.
Chuck.
This isn't a dream.
Oh, what is it?
It's a nightmare.
That's not the way
that dream was supposed to go.
- Chuck, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I'm absolutely 100% on it.
Why?
Dude, you were totally
screaming last night.
- Like a little girl.
- Honey.
It was crazy how high it was.
I'm sorry about that,
but, yeah, I'm fe.
Bro, you're a tense coil
of stressed-out negativity.
- We don't mean to pry, but...
- Actually, we do. We do.
What's stressing you out?
Nothing... particular.
You know, it's a little hectic
at work and stuff.
I didn't realize life got
so hectic at the Buy More.
Well, Chuck, maybe
what you need is a day off.
Good prescription, babe.
Chuck, that's exactly what you need.
You need to blow off some
steam, have some fun.
Take a day off, Chuck.
Dude,...
we got the day off.
What? What? What is...
What is going on?
- Tyler Martin is coming here.
- Tyler Martin?
The Tyler Martin?
Rock star Tyler Martin?
Rock star, legend, poet.
I've never actually heard him,
but apparently, he had this huge
promotion over at Large Mart,
and they pulled the plug because
of the whole sex tape thing.
- Have you seen it?
- No.
Well, anyway, Big Mike heard
about it, and offered them our store.
- Thank you, Big Mike.
- That's what I'm saying.
This place is gonna
be so packed to the gills,
no one's even gonna notice
that we're doing diddly squat.
Get over here!
Have fun.
Grimes,...
got a job for you.
Old football buddy of mine,
Jimmy Butterman, just got paroled.
I told his PO
that we'd give him a job here
at Buy More so he could get back
on his feet.
An ex-con, sir?
I-I just...
Is that such a good idea?
He's a teammate, Grimes.
Teach him everything you know.
I will.
When you say prison, though,
are you talking, like, bars
and-and guards and, uh, showers?
- Get out!
- Get out. Getting... Okay.
Attention.
Attention!
Oh, thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
when my personal friend,
Mr. Martin, enters the store,
there is to be
no flash photography...
... no approaching of Mr. Martin
of any kind,
and most importantly,
no touching!
Consider yourself warned.
Sarah, Casey, there's a situation
in the Buy More.
- There is a guy with a grenade.
- I'm heading toward the store now.
Where is he?
- He's gone.
- Where is the grenade?
Go!
Don't open it!
It's a grenade.
It's gonna blow anyway, idiot.
I'll take it out front.
We can't take it out front.
There's people out there.
We got to take it out the back.
- You stay here.
- Casey!
Hey, that's my Tyler Martin display.
He is a hero of mine, Chuck.
Sorry, Lester.
Emergency.
Nobody treats Lester like that.
Jeff, let go!
Throw it.
Chuck!
Interception!
Why are we playing keep away?
Come on...
Oh, Grimes.
See you've met Mr. Butterman.
The other half
of the Defense of Death.
Blow it up!
What did we win?
- Good morning, Sarah.
- No time to diffuse it.
I got an idea.
Here.
Hold on. Open the door.
Get down!
Good morning, Chuck.
The Subbers in Black presents...
Season 2 - Episode 12
Chuck Versus the Third Dimension
Transcript: www.tvsubtitles.net
Synchro: Job22
www.subbers-in-black.com
Agent Walker, Mr. Bartowski.
I'm sure you're wondering why would
someone want Tyler Martin dead.
Not really.
Have you heard his music?
It's overly produced, the lyrics
are completely banal.
I mean, Facebook even has a group
called I Want To Kill Tyler Martin.
Not that I'm a member.
I wouldn't ever...
That's just wrong.
Why don't you just share with General
the intel about the grenade
- that you flashed on?
- It was an IG-88 thermite charge.
That's military.
Commonly used by North African
intelligence units.
Interestingly, Tyler Martin recently
completed a tour of Africa.
I want you to find out who was
behind this attempt and why.
Well, the only way to do that
is to question Tyler Martin.
Then bring him in.
It can't be that hard
to get him alone.
All right. All right.
Hello, Cleveland!
Yeah.
This is Burbank.
Dude.
Whatever.
Now, I would like to thank
all of the humanitarians
that have affected my work.
Mother Theresa, Nelson Mandela,
God rest his soul.
And my personal favorite,
Angelina Jolie.
As a thank you
to all my beautiful fans
who still buy Cds.
I've included this,
a ticket, a golden ticket...
- A golden ticket?
- Golden ticket!
... inside these.
My new CD.
It is a backstage invite
to a benefit concert
I'm having tomorrow night.
All right, we'll see you later.
That was great, Tyler.
This is gonna be huge for the
Tyler Martin brand, you realize that?
How are we supposed to grab
a rock star in broad daylight?
I mean, security's crawling
all over the place.
This is going to be easy.
- What...?
- Catch you later, Gavin.
What's gonna be easy?
I'm such a fan, Mr. Martin.
I'm a big fan of yours, too.
- So, are you, uh, a
- model, actress?
Massage therapist?
- Maybe a
- acrobat?
I can be whatever you want.
Idiot.
I think we got a pervert.
Oh, daisies.
Nighty-night, Tyler.
How much tranquilizer did you use?
It's a high grade at a heavy dose.
Mr. Martin should be out
for 12 to 24 hours.
Jet lag is brutal.
Rock star metabolism.
All the better
for seeing you, darling,
you know.
- I feel like a daffodil.
- Time for the road trip.
Road trip? Wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where you going?
The Buy More parking lot camera
has a match on the car
- the suspect drove this morning.
- What about Tyler here?
Check his mouth every 20 minutes, make
sure he doesn't choke on his own tongue.
Hang on a second.
You're-you're gonna go,
and you want me to stay here
and be on tongue watch duty?
Well, you don't have plans, do you?
Would it be so crazy
if I did have plans?
Plans that involved something
other than fixing a computer
or playing hot potato
with a thermite grenade?
Yes.
So, what's with Chuck?
The guy's got a point.
He hasn't had a day off.
If you ask me, we're lucky
he didn't melt down months ago.
No, I think it's something else.
He's been acting
- strange since the holidays.
- Hold that thought.
We got a real fan boy, huh?
No, no,
there's something wrong here.
This is too neat.
It's too orderly.
Beckman was right.
We're dealing with a pro.
Golden ticket's got
to be in here somewhere.
I don't know, guys.
I mean, you think this is right?
This golden ticket's supposed
to be for Tyler Martin fans.
- Hey, I am a fan.
- So am I.
Yeah, so am I.
So, Mr. Butterman,
could you settle a bet?
Say it's our first day in prison.
Who do you think would be
considered the weaker gazelle?
You put anything in my mouth...
I will bite down hard.
- That's it.
- The golden ticket!
- Oh, my God, Morgan!
- Please, please.
- I am so happy for us, buddy.
You don't want me to hurt them.
Fellas... please.
This ticket only entitles me
to a plus one,
okay, so we are gonna
have to settle this...
the Buy More way.
This ticket is Lester's...
and... and Butterman's.
What?!
No, hey, hey, excuse me.
This may be the most impressive
restroom I've ever seen in my life.
That ceiling looks just
like the night sky.
That's because that
is the night sky.
- Have I made a mistake?
- No.
Better question.
Where am I?
- Who are you?
- I'm Chuck, my name is Chuck.
And I...
- I work for the label.
- My record label?
Yes, yes, your record label.
There was a death threat
against you earlier today,
so we thought it might
be good to move you
- to this secure location.
- All right, well...
- I'd better go.
- Um, um, Mr. Martin,
you actually have
to stay here for the night.
The night?
No, no, no, Jack.
- Chuck, actually.
- I get death threats all the time, OK?
Besides...
it's party night.
- It's Tuesday.
- Exactly.
- I've got to go.
- Um, you know what?
Hey, hey, how about... I'm just
gonna call my bosses real quick.
Chuck, the record company
got you this phone, right?
Sure.
- Okay.
- Why...
I'll get you a new one.
Chuck...
in case you haven't noticed yet,
I just asked you to party...
with me.
Come on.
Yeah.
What a night.
You got money, right?
'Cause I don't hold cash.
First, a little liquid nourishment.
Then, we'll get on
to the heavy drinking.
I'm actually more of a beer guy.
Something amber complected?
Not tonight, Chuck.
I may be a rum-soaked narcissist,
but I am also the best wingman
you will ever have.
Drink it down, mate.
See you guys in the emergency room!
Hello.
Gavin, you old slapper.
No, I'm with the rep
from the label.
Chuck!
- Never heard of you.
- I've never heard of him.
He's never heard of you!
No, never mind.
See you later.
Who's for another drink?
Ladies, tonight, all the drinks...
on the record company.
To determine who will be
the plus one of my golden ticket,
we will settle this with
Morgan's special triathlon.
First up...
the Molly Ringwald
underpants challenge.
The first of you to present to me
women's underpants is going to...
I'm a man.
For God's sake, I'm a man!
I'm actually going to accept these.
You know, a ticket's not
that important to me.
I need some ice.
Look, if you're worried about Chuck,
I can talk to him, scare him straight.
- I'd actually enjoy that.
- Uh, no, it's okay.
I'll get him under control.
Too late.
So I said, "I'll give you
the dog for the trousers."
That's how I got the trousers.
Hey, Chuck.
I'll tell you what you need.
- Aspirin!
- A tattoo.
Oh, no, no, no!
I'm not crazy about needles.
Ladies love a little bit of ink.
Whenever I do something amazing,
you know, feed the starving,
help the homeless,
rescue some emaciated refugee,
I map it out here on my body.
- How do you know what they all mean?
- Well, this here means...
serenity.
It's not...
it could be bliss.
I don't know Gavin,
my manager, sorts it all out.
You know, you got to kind
of trust the artist.
- Are you Tyler Martin?
- Yes, I am.
And this here is Chuck.
Chuck is in my band.
Yeah...
yeah, I'm in his band all right.
Drummer just laying the beats down.
Like a little drummer boy.
Come, they told me.
Pa-rump-a-pum-pum.
- Um... you guys want to dance?
- Yes.
- No.
- Yes, we do.
No, I'm not really
a dancer, you know?
Unless it's, like, some ballet or...
but this isn't a ballet place.
You know, I'm
much better at ironic dancing.
What happened to your accent?
Sorry.
I don't really have one.
I don't really care.
Round two.
The Subway sprint.
There's only one thing you got
to ask yourself, Butterman.
Do you like succulent chicken oozing
with bacon and ranch dressing?
I love succulent chicken.
I am in your head, sir.
Let's use this... Are you ready?
Set... Consume!
Oh, keep it down
or you're disqualified.
Keep it...
down.
Attaboy...
get to work.
Come on.
Come on, man.
We have a winner.
Winner!
Winner.
The signal is weak,
but I still have a trace on Chuck.
He's somewhere in the club.
Casey, it's him.
Damn it, he made me.
Go.
- Freeze!
- Halt!
Get on the ground.
You'll want to be
more gentle with me.
Get your hands up...
do it!
I'm going to walk away from you now.
- I'd rather we all go up.
- Casey, be careful.
Then, you should know that
Mr. Martin is still in danger.
I have some friends set to meet him.
So, by all means, stay here and die.
- Or you can go save him.
- Casey.
We gotta get Chuck come on.
Chuck!
We got a problem.
These girls want to take us upstairs
and do despicable things to us.
Tyler, Tyler, that's...
that's not such a great idea.
All the best nights of my life
have begun with that very sentence.
Which brings us to the final leg
of our triathlon.
- Good lord, is that...
- Yeah, Butterman, it is.
May I present
to you the urinal cake.
Okay, here's the deal.
The winner will be
the first one of you...
- Ah, come on.
- That's disgusting.
Dude, seriously, are you kidding me?
What is wrong with you?
You were just supposed to touch it.
I still win, right?
All right, who stole
the urinal cakes?
I splashed myself silly.
Welcome to Castle de Orlando,
Spanish conquistador.
So, I think we should
maybe just head...
Tyler, Tyler, I need
to talk to you, buddy.
- In a minute, Charles.
- No, no, it's very important.
- I need to talk to you right now.
- Ladies, I'm so sorry.
If you just go make yourself
comfortable right inside,
then maybe we could have our talk, and
then we'll join you in just a second.
- How does that sound?
- What?
Thanks so much.
Listen to me very carefully, Tyler.
These women are very,
very dangerous.
Don't worry.
I always use protection.
- Good looking out.
- That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm begging you, just once,
deny yourself this pleasure.
- You're right.
- That's totally selfish of me.
- Oh, good, lets go.
- You need this much more than I do.
No, no, Ty, no,
I'm not talking about...
Please don't, please...
Hey.
- I'm...
- Where's Tyler?
That's an excellent question.
T-Tyler, Tyler just...
he stepped away for a second, but
he's gonna be right back, I promise.
I guess you'll have to go first.
Go first where, go first what?
Why... where am I going first?
Why do I have to be first?
First is the worst,
second is the best, and third...!
Oh, h-hi.
Those are my shoes; I need those.
I need those shoes, I need those...
no, those are my pants!
I think that you have overestimated
my prowess as, as,
as a lover and a man.
Just looking at you,
I can feel that you require a...
a real rock star, so...
Tyler.
What happened
to not leaving your wingman?
Sarah.
Where are you?
Top floor, Tyler's suite,
or more specifically,
the roof outside of it.
Things have gotten
a little out of hand.
Aah!
This is so romantic.
The perfect second honeymoon.
Could you push the button
for the lobby, please?
No, no, n-no, the lobby, the lobby!
Where you going,
where you going?
No, lob-lobby!
Don't...
Ladies.
Ladies, you ready for me?
Tyler, run!
Sorry, I must be going.
Get 'em, Sarah!
Lobby, please.
Chuck, what were you thinking?
You know, I gave you clear
instructions to keep him here.
And instead you take him
to a nightclub?
Interesting tactical decision there.
Time-out, listen, he woke
up and I couldn't stop him.
Okay, I don't have a knockout
karate chop like you guys.
- That's not part of my skill set.
- Where am I?
- And how was I?
- Mr. Martin, we're with the government.
We're here to protect you.
Wait, there was an elevator.
Chuck, you were there.
T-Two girls.
One of them had a gun.
I-It was pointed at me.
Tyler, Tyler, it's all right. Just like
Casey said, we're here to protect you.
- I need to call my manager.
- No, Mr. Martin, I don't think that's
a good idea because
we don't know who's involved.
I have to call my manager.
Good show.
Casey, what is wrong with you?!
You can't do that!
You're going to give the guy
brain damage or liver problems.
Too late on both counts.
I know why they're trying to kill him.
I know why they want him dead.
- What?
- His back, the tattoo on his back.
It's not, it's not Arabic philosophy.
It's actually a very clear message
about a private reactor
that's being built in North Africa.
His manager is bringing in
the tattoo artists.
Of course. He's a rock star,
he travels the world.
Manager is using him
to move secrets.
Idiot never even knew
what the ink meant.
You're wrong about Tyler.
He's actually a pretty good guy.
He's an idiot, Bartowski,
just like you.
Should have never left
the two of you alone.
You know, Chuck, Casey is right.
You could have
gotten yourself killed.
What exactly were you thinking?
What was I thinking?
I'll tell you what I was thinking.
I was thinking like I wasn't a spy.
Okay? I was trying to have
a little bit of fun,
and I knew the second I called
you two, it would all be over.
But Chuck, you are a spy,
and you should know better than
to put yourself in a dangerous
situation where I can't protect you.
Is it really so wrong
for me to want a night off?
I was having a really good
time, too, until the assassins
stole my pants and tried to kill me.
I've earned it.
I deserve it.
I'm losing consciousness.
Casey!
My ears couldn't take it.
Either that or I shoot him.
You ready for a taste
of the sweet life tonight, buddy?
- Yeah, sure, sure.
- Backstage passes.
You know what that means, don't you?
No, I've never been
backstage.
That ticket's our
passport to freedom.
Not only is there
free beer backstage,
but there are women
that haven't been sober for years,
and we're allowed in,
so the ladies assume we're not losers.
Wow... it sounds like a fairy tale.
Poor Butterman.
The guy's been trapped
in an 8x10 cell for years.
He ate when they said "Chow time,"
and he slept when they shouted
"Lights out!"
Now look at him.
Broken.
The man had a choice of five sodas,
a choice we take
for granted every day,
a choice he's been
denied for far too long.
I'm sorry, Jeff, this ticket
doesn't belong to us.
This ticket belongs to Butterman.
The man deserves
his passport to freedom.
You and I,
we're going to give it to him.
I'll make it up to you.
I'll buy you a keg.
What do you like?
It's called Beer.
- Done... done.
- Beer brand.
Your flash turned
up good intel, Chuck.
The man you confronted
last night is Achmed Gambir,
a top foot soldier in
a private army in North Africa.
We've been trying to infiltrate
their ranks for years.
I want you to capture Achmed
at tonight's concert.
He's the key
to bringing down this merc army.
What... wait, wait.
You want Tyler onstage as bait?
General, Mr. Martin knows there are
people after him and he won't go on.
Well, then convince him.
Wait, no, no.
No, no, guys, hey,
this is way too dangerous.
Tyler could get killed.
Those are nightmares
tattooed on his body, Chuck.
- We have to take Gambir down tonight.
- Okay, okay, fine, fine,
you go in there and tell him
he has to put his life on the line
because he was a pawn
in someone else's game.
He won't listen to us.
So you want me to do it?
No, absolutely not.
What do you mean no?
We have orders.
Chuck, what is the matter with you?
This is about more
than just taking a night off.
Maybe.
Um, I... you know, I'm a little
off my game right now.
I'm not, not really sleeping.
I don't want to get into it.
Chuck, lives are
on the line right now,
and if Tyler doesn't help us, then
he will never be free of those people,
and if you don't help us,
then Achmed Gambir gets away.
And the world becomes
a more dangerous place.
I don't know what happened
to you, but this is our job...
not only to protect Tyler but the country
and anybody else who needs protecting.
We do whatever it takes
no matter what.
Did you forget that?
That I definitely didn't forget.
We don't have time for this.
Wait.
I'll do it.
I'll convince him.
Hey, man.
You okay?
No.
No, I'm not okay.
Don't know where I am,
how I got here,
and someone's trying to kill me.
On the plus side, your friend's
tranqs are out of this world.
Yeah, it's one
of his few good qualities.
I've never been in a situation
like this before, life...
or death.
Pretty much live my life
avoiding anything this real.
It takes some getting used to.
What do you want me to do?
We would like for you
to perform tonight
at your special concert.
That's madness.
People are trying to kill me.
Yes, and you can help us catch them.
You can help the world, the entire
world, by doing this, for real.
You could go back
to living your life again.
One night of bravery
for an entire life of normalcy.
I can't even tell you
what I'd give for that.
How do I know I can trust them?
Your people?
Because I do.
They're the best.
I stake my life on it every day.
I got one thing to say.
- Hello, Cleveland.
- It's Burbank.
Right.
I'm dyslexic.
You boys have given
me back hope. Thanks.
You deserve a taste
of the sweet life, man.
Enjoy it for all of us.
- Do us proud, Butterman.
- Thanks.
There you go.
Dude, how could you just sell
the golden ticket like that?
Sorry, guys.
I found out how much these
things are going for online.
But your freedom, man.
Was it worth the price of freedom?
Price of my freedom is 800 bucks.
Same as my ticket to Zihuatanejo.
See you never.
Enjoy hell.
Get busy living, or get busy dying.
True that.
Well, back to work.
20 minutes till
Tyler Martin takes the stage.
- Chuck.
- Yeah, I'm here.
Don't let Tyler take the stage
till we give the okay.
Okay.
Got it.
Sarah, made the mark.
Get on my six and intercept him.
Who are you?
Why you wearing this?
Some guy gave me free tickets.
He just said I had to wear
this stupid jacket.
- He's ahead of us.
- Which one is he?
Sorry, buddy, no one allowed
to see Mr. Martin.
- Oh. Ha, ha.
- Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Let me get that.
Yeah, you get it, Chuck.
Open this door.
- It's him. It's him.
- Who?
The guy who's trying to kill you?
Here?
I thought you said we were safe.
- I know you're in there, Mr. Martin.
- Oh, I need another drink.
That's a good idea.
No, that's... no. No.
- Hey, get in there. Get in there.
- I said open this door!
- What about you?
- I'll be all right.
Just, just stay in the closet.
Wait.
Take off your shirt.
Just trust me.
- Sarah, it's Chuck.
- Chuck. What is it?
Achmed. Achmed's right outside
the dressing room.
I don't know what happened
to the guards.
OK, Chuck, stay right where you are.
Look, I didn't need the night off.
You were right,
it's something else. I should've
told you. I should have....
Chuck?
Chuck, can you hear me?
Move.
Excuse me. Go!
I think maybe,
maybe you have the wrong room.
Tell me where he is?
Tell you where who is?
Oh, where where
he is where Tyler is.
Right. He, you know, he... he
skipped out. I don't know where he is.
So sorry.
I don't know. He's gone.
He's in the closet.
Excuse me.
Move!
Coming through.
Move.
Okay, you got us. Yeah, worse plan ever.
But I know about the tattoo.
I know what it means.
You and your private
army enriching uranium,
selling it to unstable countries.
Using Tyler's manager and his tattoos
to pass the info off to your buyers.
You take one more step,
I send this e-mail
and everyone knows.
Proving that the cell is
mightier than the sword.
Or, or a very large knife,
as it might be in this case.
Go! Excuse me.
Move!
Put it down.
Put it down!
No!
I can't let you do this
for me Chuck.
Actually, my plan was
working very well.
- No!
- Follow me.
- Tyler, what's going on, man?
- Gavin, you're fired!
- Sarah, we're running to the stage.
- He's right behind us.
- Chuck, are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, just get us out of here.
- Tyler! Tyler! Tyler!
Everybody give
it up for Tyler Martin!
Help.
Los Angeles.
What do we do now?
- Jump.
- What?
Jump.
Chuck!
Jump!
It's all good, it's all good,
Chuck, relax.
Come on, take it easy.
Okay, okay.
Stephanie, right?
Stephanie.
Yeah!
You think I look mad,
wait till you see her.
A little too much to drink
there, huh, pal?
- Uh, let's get you some coffee.
- We got him! Ha, ha, ha!
- See? I told you they were the best!
- Yeah, that's it, all right.
Now back to the stage.
Come on, I want to sing now.
All right, like he said,
back to the stage.
Who the hell are you?
Grimes?
Where's my boy Butterman?
He kind of took off suddenly.
Can't say I blame him. Man's gotta run
free after being locked up so long.
Yeah, yeah, well, um, Big Mike,
do mind if I ask you what Butterman
was in the can for?
I mean, you talking robbery? Drugs?
- Murder?
- Butterman?
- Yeah.
- God, no!
Bank fraud, insider trading.
The man's a white-collar criminal.
Why? He take you fools
for some money?
- He said he was going somewhere.
- Zihuatanejo?
That's Mexican for Philadelphia.
I knew I should have
learned Spanish.
I can't believe
my manager's going to jail.
Think about it.
No privacy.
It'd be like hell on bloody earth.
Yeah.
Tell me about it.
You understand why you're gonna have
to get your tattoos removed, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I hear you're the bro to talk to
to get more of those
tasty tranq darts.
Philistine.
- Thanks, Chuck.
- Oh, hey, it was nothing.
No, no, it was everything.
You taught me to put people
in front of myself.
Felt kind of wonderful.
I can strike that off the list now.
If you ever want to party,
you know where to come.
Yeah, actually, I don't think
that's my scene.
Smart man, Chuck.
Smart man.
All right.
- Take it easy.
- You, too.
- Hello, Mr. Martin.
- Your limousine is waiting outside.
You know my name.
Have we made love before?
No.
Daddy's got to go.
Sorry. Later.
You did a great job, Chuck.
Thanks.
Look, if-if there's something
bothering you,
then please tell me.
I know part of your job is to have
all these secrets in your head,
but you're not supposed
to keep them from me.
I know. I know.
I saw you shoot that
Fulcrum agent on Christmas Eve
after they took over the Buy More.
- And when I asked you about it...
- I lied.
Yeah.
- Chuck, I have to protect you.
- I know that. I, I...
I know that you do.
And you were protecting me.
You were protecting all of us.
He had threatened
my family, my friends,
and you were just doing
your job... I get that, but...
Sarah, the guy was unarmed
- and, and you just...
- I did what I had to.
He knew who you really were.
Your whole family was in danger.
And I'm sorry.
Sometimes I forget that
you never asked for all of this.
There's parts I'm not sure
I'll ever get used to.
Well, you deserve a break.
So, take tonight, tomorrow
whatever you need, it's yours.
Seriously? Really?
Yeah, no missions,
no cameras, no Casey,
no thermal satellite
surveillance and no me.
- You guys use satellites?
- Yeah.
And Chuck, when you're ready again,
we'll be here, waiting.
Hey, what's this?
What's going on?
- Lock and load.
- A new mission.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Wait, a new, a new mission?
What kind of mission?
It's fine, Chuck.
We've got it.
What, what kind of mission?
Ah, finally,
a mission without Bartowski.
I'm going to enjoy this.
Okay, guys.
Where are we going?
Well, come on, Casey. No time
for a break, we've got work to do.
www.subbers-in-black.com