My name is jane vasco.
I could use you on my team.
I work for a secret government
agency that hunts neuros.
People who can do dangerous
things with their minds.
On my first assignment...
Something a little weird happened,
okay, something really weird.
Until I get some answers
I'm getting on with my life,
doing my job.
Stocking up on aspirin,
because let me tell ya,
pain's a bitch !
Riley, what's happening ?
System is down,
backed up and secure.
We going somewhere ?
Nice if there were a neuro
or two in maul.
I don't think you'll be sipping
a lot of mal-tais in hungary.
No cracks.
I didn't say anything ?
It's a pre-emptive strike.
I do have a life above ground.
Clearly.
What's the 911 ?
We have an emergency
situation at nico.
Morgan informs me
there's been a break.
How many ?
Six that we're aware of.
When ?
We don't know.
There have been administrative
problems at nico for months now.
Morgan's thinks they've
been sweeping things
under the carpet.
In any case, I can't tell you when
because no official
report was made.
Morgan picked this up
from other sources.
Can't the locals handle it ?
There are no locals.
These neuros have been chipped,
so there's minimal security.
The other staff are
administrators, doctors, nurses.
The flight leaves at 0600.
That's four hours from now.
Pack light.
Seth, I'm going to need riley
where we're going
so there'll be no one here
to run security.
I'm going to get joe
to do a lock up here.
I'll be at the hospital
if you need me.
Thank you.
Farber air force base at 0500.
Let's roll.
Nice to meet you, agent mcbride.
Make yourself comfortable.
I do understand why you're
here and I assure you,
you and your team will have
my full cooperation.
That won't be necessary.
We're planning on performing
a thorough house-cleaning.
Just how thorough
are we talking about ?
From the top down.
Cozy.
Oh, yeah, all we need
is some villagers and torches.
Roger armstrong.
Andre mcbride.
We've been expecting you.
And let me assure you,
you and your team will have
my full cooperation.
I would expect nothing less,
mr. Armstrong.
I'll gather my team after
they've had a chance to settle,
and we'll reconvene
in your office in one hour.
Transcript : swsub.com
Synchro : bbd1980
I used to dream of
traveling as a kid...
Places like hawaii,
the caribbean...
White sand beaches,
toes digging in the sand,
a cute guy to my side.
I thought this might be
the year I'd make that happen.
Guess I was wrong...
Again.
We first became aware of
the situation
at evening bed check.
We have a very strict curfew.
Obviously, not strict enough.
We have a limited security
staff, agent mcbride.
Most of our residents,
having been chipped,
are well-behaved.
Why didn't you report
the situation ?
We had hoped we could
bring them back
without causing concern.
I take full responsibility
for what happened.
Oh, it's already been
assigned to you.
My orders are to locate
and contain the escapees.
At the same time,
the entire operation
will be evaluated.
From security to management.
Expect changes.
It's 1125 hours.
My team will need to be briefed.
15 minutes.
This is alex rawlings,
head of security.
I've read the intel
report you compiled.
Not much detail about how
the escapes were accomplished.
You know everything that we know.
There's no evidence whatsoever
that they breached the perimeter.
I find it highly unlikely that
they walked through the walls.
Yes, sir.
I'll need blueprints,
from the roof to the basement,
and the surrounding property.
I have them digitized,
if you'd like...
Riley, download it to your rig,
I want to keep it portable.
It gives us an edge
for security purposes
plus we may have to roll with it.
I'm on it.
Go on.
I've arranged for dr. Phillips,
head of medicine,
to show you
the rest of the facility.
He's better qualified
to answer your questions.
If there's nothing else...
Not for the moment.
We run quite a number of
tests and experiments.
An inmate would be placed
depending on what phase
of testing he or she is in.
What kind of tests ?
Everything from mri's to cat scans.
We do perform some
invasive surgeries.
The main focus of our research
is to determine etymology.
We still have no idea
where, how or why
the phenomenon began to
appear in the population.
You let them walk
around like this ?
They're human beings, agent king.
And, having had the good
fortune to have been chipped,
quite harmless.
I don't like it.
Hell, they know who we are.
And probably aren't too happy
about seeing us again.
This is yellow sector.
These are our longest
term residents.
Most have been through
the complete battery of tests.
This is our minimal
security section,
primarily for containment.
And still well-covered
with security cameras.
Yes, every sector is covered
and the cameras run 24/7.
What's blue, doctor ?
Our central core is at
the end of that corridor.
Every section extends off
the core like spokes on a wheel.
It's also our path
lab and safe room.
Safe room ?
Yes, just in case.
What makes it safe ?
We've discovered during
our research
that an extremely amplified
ultrasonic wave
can interfere with the aberrant
neurological activity...
Limiting its range and efficacy.
Like a chip.
Yes, very much like a chip but
not localized to the individual.
If there ever were to be some
sort of threat to the staff,
if a chip were to fail
we can surround that room
with an ultrasonic barrier
that would, in effect,
prevent their "special talents"
from getting through.
Have you ever had a chip fail ?
No, not to date.
Why not use the ultrasonic
throughout the entire facility ?
A number of reasons.
The power involved to generate
the frequency and amplify it.
That, and the intensity of
the frequency could be harmful
to the physical structure
of the building.
That section has been reinforced.
This is red sector.
It's our highest security section.
The inmates here, albeit chipped,
are considered dangerous
and anti-social.
Have you found any
connection between
their behavior
and their condition ?
Nothing consistent.
Apparently, the aberration
itself does not cause
anti-social behavior.
I believe these people
would have been incarcerated
in the outside world,
even if they did not possess
their "special talents".
Well, well, well...
This place is looking
better already.
I told you I'd kill you
if I ever got the chance,
you sonuvabitch.
Ahhh !!!
I remember you.
You're the pyro freak who likes
to set fire to schools.
You bit me !
And last time I checked
I had rabies.
What's the green sector ?
Maintenance.
Generator, hospital supply rooms,
nothing of any real interest.
) Dr. Phillips, please, dr. Phillips.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Yes, I'll be right there.
What've you got ?
I've been over the security
tapes and reports.
On the night of the escape,
none of the entrances or exits
were breached.
Still leaves us nowhere.
Not exactly.
There's a tunnel that
runs below the facility.
Where does it lead ?
To an old convent about
two miles from here.
A few centuries back,
this place was a prison used
to house religious prisoners.
The tunnel was built
as a means for them
to communicate with and
escape to the outside world.
And you didn't think
it was worth checking ?
No need.
It was sealed almost 200 years ago
when it was discovered.
When we took possession,
the closure was reinforced.
It's been filled with
a few tons of concrete.
No exits breached,
the tunnels are blocked.
How the hell did
six neuros escape ?
You've been quiet.
Something on your mind ?
One guard I saw was
carrying a chip gun.
Wouldn't you ?
Why? Everyone here is chipped.
Dr. Phillips said he'd never
heard of a chip failing
but they built a safe
room just in case.
Even so, the guard I saw was
coming from a maintenance area
of no real interest.
You're thinking their
full cooperation
might not be so full.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
rawlings said
the tunnel was sealed.
What do guys expect
we're going to find here ?
No dates for this weekend,
that's for sure.
I wasn't expecting visitors today.
My name is andre mcbride.
I am mother superior.
My team and I are doing
historical research in the area
and we were wondering
if we could check out
the building and the grounds.
If it doesn't interfere with
the sisters, I see no problem.
This place is amazing.
How old is it ?
It's been here
for almost 400 years.
We understand there is a tunnel
that runs under the property.
Yes.
Do you have any idea
where it leads ?
Someplace that used to be a prison.
Would you mind if
we took a look at it ?
Of course.
The walls are completely sealed.
No way anyone came
through that tunnel.
Hey boss.
Thank you.
No, I'm working.
What do you got ?
I've officially confirmed
the names of the escapees.
Luckily, these people are chipped.
Because they'd make an
all-star team of neuros
if they weren't.
First there's jakob
baumgartner, shape shifter,
who I believe we all rember.
Then there's jerry williams.
Neuro ability; the man can
move at extremely high speeds.
Marilyn smith, neuro ability,
she can emit highly-focused
lasebeams
produced from a region behind
the optic nerve.
Bill davis, can cause a magnetic
force between objects.
Tom sampson, can create
ultrasonic vibrations.
And last, but not least,
roger hanley,
a levitator.
We're on our way to you now.
No worries, boss.
Three other break-ins have
occurred since the escape.
Oversized drill bits
stolen from a machine factory,
several boxes of
c-4 explosive taken
from a ming factory, nothing else.
But check this out;
a cache of guns
and ammo were stolen
from a highly secure military
munitions storage shed.
Given the details,
those escaped neuros
could've pulled this off.
How ? they're all chipped.
Maybe.
Andre, you said they've
been experimenting
with de-chping here.
It's not a secret.
But it's not a known
fact that they can do it.
Not known to us, anyway.
Might explain what we were
talking about earlier.
Worth discussing with armstrong.
Doesn't track.
If you managed to get
out of this place,
would you stick around ?
Personally, I'd get my
ass as far away from
here as possible.
Unless escaping isn't
the only thing on their mind.
You are correct, agent mcbride,
we have experimented
with de-chipping.
But those experiments were
discontinued long before
they garnered results.
I've got a list of burglaries
that could have been committed
by those neuros
had they been de-chipped.
You have my answer, agent.
And you have mine.
We could be looking at an
attempt for a full-scale breakout.
Until otherwise notified,
I'm putting nico on 24/7
lockdown.
No one other than my team comes
or goes without my permission,
that includes you.
Don't you think
you're overreacting ?
I'm just getting started.
Beautiful night.
What did I do to deserve this ?
I thought I might welcome you
to some hungarian generosity.
Unless I'm interrupting.
Darlin', it's what you're starting
that I don't want interrupted.
You tried monarchia ?
I can't even pronounce it.
If you like it, I have another
bottle back at my place.
Must have been that
trip to the convent.
Thank you.
To the second bottle.
The second bottle.
Hey, aren't you going to...
Huh ?
Good evening, father.
Welcome, father.
I hope all is going well.
We need to talk.
I don't have much time.
It'd take a team of
munitions experts
and bulldozers
to pull these burglaries off.
Or six unchipped neuros.
Armstrong and phillips,
both claim that
the experimental surgeries
were discontinued before
yielding any results.
You believe them ?
At this point, no.
If there are any plans in the works
for an assault on the castle
I'll know about it.
I've linked into what little
there is of their system.
Hey, did you get anything off
those tapes rawlings gave you ?
Nothing.
You with us, or what connor ?
Just barely.
Trust me, be careful if
you sample the local wine.
What'd I miss ?
I thought you might have
something to report
besides the local wine.
Why would I have
something to report ?
I passed out in my room last night.
Oh, really ?
This is time-coded just
after 1900 hours.
Right off the cameras
at the main entrance.
I swear, boss, I never left.
That is me, isn't it ?
I checked the odometer on the suv.
Between the time connor
says he didn't drive out
until the time he
didn't get back...
Someone racked up
just over six miles.
Just about enough for
a round trip to the convent.
What about baumgartner ?
The man can shape shift
into pretty much anyone.
He is on the list of escapees.
Why come back to the place
you escaped from ?
Not that big a risk
if you can impersonating
anyone you want.
Come and go as you need.
We keep him high on the list.
At this point, we have
to proceed assuming
that armstrong and phillips
are lying to us.
And if that's the case,
that "maintenance area"
which is supposed to be
of no particular interest
could turn out to be
very interesting.
I'd like to run
ultrasonics on the tunnel.
It's still our best bet.
Alright, we reconvene in two hours.
I want everyone to carry.
Armstrong ?!
access denied.
I was not in your room last night.
I was in the lab
until my shift ended.
I clocked out at 1800 hours.
You can check
with security to verify.
I never should've turned
down that job at microsoft.
retinal imprint, failed.
Nice place.
I think I found something.
Check this out.
This is a density
readout on the tunnel.
You can see that the ends are solid
about three feet deep.
Probably concrete like they said.
But if you look here,
you can see that except for
this solid area in the center,
once that's cleared,
the tunnel would be passable.
You find your woman ?
We found the woman.
Well, I've got something.
I was just explaing to jane...
Hey !!!!
Move !! over there!! Go !!
Andre.
I assume that one of you
is jakob baumgartner.
The only question is,
which one ?
There's a way.
Shoot both of us.
It's a win-win situation.
She's right, boss.
Our girl'll just get up
like nothing happened.
Last chance, mr. Baumgartner.
You could've shot me in the leg.
Ah !!
Armstrong's dead.
When ?
I'm not an m.E. But given
the condition of his body,
I'd say he was dead
before we arrived.
Baumgartner's been busy.
And that maintenance area
isn't a maintenance area.
I only got as far as the morgue
but there seems to be
another facility beyond that.
I couldn't get through.
Time we had a talk
with dr. Phillips.
If it ever was dr. Phillips.
Riley, call security.
Have them get rid of this body.
It's time we find out what
they don't want us to know.
I'm the computer tech.
It's you guys that are supposed
to get hit on the head.
You might want one of
the doctors to check that out.
I think it's baumgartner
who's checked out.
I have a pretty good
idea where "I'm" going.
As I started to explain to jane...
Well, baumgartner...
Whatever.
This concrete is
only a few feet deep.
The same is true at the other end.
And except for a few
feet that're still
blocked in the middle,
the ends are like corks.
Blow'em out, clear the middle
boom, you have free access.
From the convent and the hospital.
It would explain the stolen
c-4 and other equipment.
If the freaks are planning to
break their friends out of here,
then they have to be working
it from the convent side.
You think the mother
superior lied to us ?
I'd say if it's mother superior,
she could be an escapee.
No, I don't think so.
Why not ?
She doesn't match any
of the profiles.
They could be controlling her.
Baumgartner's not going
to give up the game
and he knows he's under pressure.
If they're going to move,
they will move soon.
What would it take
to force a cave-in
and seal the tunnel ?
Same as they're planning
to use to clear the concrete.
A small truckload of c-4
just placed differently.
Can you do it ?
I guess, given the supplies
and chemicals around this place,
mixed in the right
proportions... Maybe.
How long ?
Less time if I get started now.
Good.
Riley, you work this
end with connor.
You and I better get
to the convent.
If baumgartner's going to move,
he may not want
to leave any witnesses.
Great, down here again.
Still think she's an innocent ?
Tough play to call.
Best bet is to chip both of them.
She might actually
be a mother superior.
If she's not a neuro,
the chip won't hurt her.
It's your afterlife.
I'll take baumgartner.
Cuff him.
You have no right...
I have every right.
I don't think you realize who
and what we're dealing with here.
You mean a man who's been given
an extraordinary gift from god.
You're attempting
to protect yourself
from things you don't understand.
This man and the others
like him are simply trying
to protect themselves
from imprisonment and butchery,
ignorance and fear.
I think you have been
sold a bill of goods,
mother superior.
We only want to understand them.
Who they are, why they are.
No one wants to harm them.
You have to expect him to lie,
cover-up the truth.
He's one of them.
What truth is that ?
Ha!
Please, miss vasco.
The de-chipping, the experiments.
Cutting into us as if
we were nothing more
than laboratory rats.
Leaving some of us
crippled and blind,
and those are the lucky ones.
You really don't know, do you ?
Then perhaps it's time
you were introduced
to the dangerous escapees
you've been working
so hard to apprehend.
Alright.
Just how powerful is this stuff ?
It's enough to finish the job.
But not enough to take
the whole place down, right ?
Let's go!
Guess we're gonna find out ?
On my mark.
3, 2, 1.
Your vicious band of
criminals, agent mcbride.
Is dr. Phillips responsible
for all of this ?
Yes.
This is his handiwork.
The people we hope
to set free are not
as "fortunate" as these.
And you're their appointed savior.
Why ?
Because, agent mcbride,
though it might come
as a shock to you...
I do possess a conscience.
Months of work
and only seconds to destroy it.
This tunnel, it saved
countless lives in the past.
We'd hoped it could serve
that purpose again.
can you really let this continue
and allow these people to suffer ?
The ball...
as they say,
is in your court, sir.
any one of those
people could have been me.
And, in less enlightened times...
You.
I don't think these
people will give you
any further trouble.
I'll see that they're
taken to their rooms.
You may have pressed your
luck this time, jakob.
Alright, let's go.
It seems as if it's your luck
that has changed, doctor.
You didn't chip them ?!!
You must to stop this!
I thought you were
going to chip them.
No, agent, I distinctly
recall giving you that order.
Well, we seem to have
a real problem on our
hands, don't we ?
You would agree,
wouldn't you, doctor ?
This is something of a problem.
What're you doing ?!
Maybe now, you'll be inclined
to tell us the truth !
Unless you'd like to wait there
while we retrieve our chip guns.
You know,
I can't seem to find mine.
Do you know what's happened
to yours ?
I'll tell you whatever you want.
Just get them out of here.
No, doctor, I think it best
that they stayed and listened,
after all, who'd better to
call you on your lies than them.
I should have let them kill you.
Are your hands so clean ?
This is your work,
doctor, not mine.
If I had known...
If you had known, what ?
Single-handedly you would
have put a stop to it ?
What did you people
think was happening here?
Not this.
How nice to be able
to choose to be so blind.
You loathe me for doing
your housekeeping.
It's always nice to have
clean toilets,
just don't inquire as to how
the job was accomplished.
That's a bit simplistic,
don't you think, doctor ?
Is it?
Ever since the first
aberration surfaced,
we've been under orders and
pressure to find the source,
understand the nature
of the mutation.
You, as well as anyone, should
understand, agent mcbride,
they want results, not excuses.
At any cost ?
Don't be naive !!!
Had I come up with the answers,
discovered a cure,
I'd have been given
a medal of honor
and a parade to go along with it.
Are you even vaguely aware
of what's gone into medical
research over the years ?
Research, that in the end,
has saved millions of lives.
And that makes it okay !!
It makes it necessary!!
As much as you don't want
to know, miss vasco,
you are part of this.
We work on the same team,
toward the same end.
No, no, not anymore we don't !
That team is about
to change, doctor.
In fact, my team will stay here
until this entire facility
is either cleaned up
or cleaned out.
You will give me full access
to your records.
I want the name of
every individual involved.
Are there any physicians on
this staff that can be trusted ?
Dr. Newman.
I'll have him form a new team.
Hopefully, it's not too late
to help some of these people.
Let's get out of here.
Agent mcbride.
I misjudged you.
Thank you.
Dr. Newman is attending
to the crew.
Some of them may survive.
Phillips was right.
My hands aren't so clean.
We all live to learn, jane.
It's learning that we can
wash our hands that matters.
Compassion ?
When we last met,
I was rather ill-behaved.
But things have changed.
Have they ?
Haven't you always
suspected that in the end
we are more alike than different ?
I'm not too sure of that.
Clearly, you're not
the only one of us
who can survive a gunshot
to the chest.
We're family.
You've known it for some time.
I suppose I have.
I've spoken with dr. Roberts.
And I know you two finally
had the chance to meet.
He and randall hyde, you and I,
it appears we have a great
deal in common.
You said that you weren't
part of phillips' experiments.
You were never de-chipped ?
No.
Maureen chipped you
when she apprehended you.
How are you able to continue
to use your abilities ?
When dr. Roberts told you that
he'd perfected his process,
he was telling the truth.
Chipping has no effect on us,
any of us.
The people you sent to nico,
are the result
of earlier experiments.
But you still wanted to help them.
As did you.
Perhaps there's more
to dr. Robert's vision
of an improved species than
simply the ability to heal.
What happens now ?
You'll learn that soon enough.
There's an old phrase...
Be careful what you wish for,
you just might get it.
The people I work for have
been desperate to understand
the neuro phenomenon...
How it works, where it started.
In time, they may get that answer.
But at what price ?
And ever since I can remember,
I've always wished to feel
part of something.
Now it seems, after
all these years, that I am.
The price for that, too,
might be more than
I'm willing to consider.
Beautiful night.
It might turn out to be.
I feel I owe you an apology.
I don't know why.
According to everyone the "you"
that came to my room wasn't you.
Then perhaps you'd like
to share some wine
with the real me.
Not monarchia ?
Definitely not.
I'll guarantee you'll like
what I have for you much more.
Y'know, if you are baumgartner,
this could get strange.
You have nothing to worry about.
Do you really think
you'll need that ?
I'm a firm believer in safe sex.
-=www.seriesub.com=-