My name is jane vasco.
I could use you
on my team.
I work for a secret government
agency that hunts neuros.
People who can do dangerous
things with their minds.
On my first assignment...
Something a little
weird happened,
okay, something
really weird.
Until i get some answers
i'm getting on with my life,
doing my job.
Stocking up on aspirin,
because let me tell ya,
pain's a bitch!
Make it stop!!!
We've got a problem here !
What are you waiting for?
Not here.
Not in this house.
Make it stop!!!
This is special field
agent leslie jackson.
Put me through to cooper.
Coop, it's lj.
Whatever it is with
this damn house...
It looks like it's
starting all over again.
What the hell
is your problem?
Transcript : swsub.com
Presync : IceFre@k
A daily ritual.
Cleansing ourselves.
We wash our hair,
our bodies,
our hands and our teeth.
But with all the lotions,
soaps and shampoos,
none of it seems to reach
below the surface.
So we do our best
to cover up
whatever we're
trying to hide.
But with
so much concealed,
...i often wonder what
it will be like
when it cracks.
And what lies underneath
comes rushing out,
unable to
be contained.
A shot of confidence,
i'm out the door
to face neuros, pain
and unanswered questions
about my special condition.
Seventeen maiden lane.
In the dunbar district.
It's an odd little place.
On the market for years.
odd, you mean haunted.
When it wouldn't sell,
the f.b.i. Picked
it up for a song
and reprovisioned it
as a safe house.
Since that time,
four year ago
there have been
several "incidents."
what exactly is
an "incident?"
show up at
my place tonight
and i'll demonstrate.
Oh, you mean
a minor incident.
Oh.
Several witnesses being
held at the location
experienced some sort
of mental breakdown.
So much for "safe" house.
None of the effects
were permanent.
The victims all recovered
shortly after
leaving the premises.
The bureau's
been thorough.
They've pretty much eliminated
most of the obvious.
Radon.
Mold.
Gasses.
All of it... Eliminated.
So, now the press has this story.
Senator moreland is requesting
a special committee
to investigate the bureau's
handling of suspects
and witnesses.
They think
the bureau's responsible?
The f.b.i. Has been
accused of using drugs
and "mind control" tactics
to get people to talk.
When they don't give
people the answers,
they will fill in
the blanks.
Think there's
any truth to it?
My contacts at
the bureau say no.
So obviously no one
scanned for neuros.
Obviously, until now.
) if we are dealing
with a neuro,
we're gonna have
to consider proximity.
Riley's downloaded
the city zoning maps.
We've eliminated all
the surrounding neighbors.
Well, I got a map
for the entrances
to the main sewer
lines, if that helps.
Alight, you guys cover inside.
We'll take the perimeter.
Just in case something
goes bump in the night...
...you'll be outside so
i have nothing to fear.
Did you feel something?
Yeah, a draft.
Upstairs or down?
Up.
I'll check down here.
Basements.
Mom?
Nothing out on the perimeter,
anything here?
Uh, no.
Not that I can find.
Where's maureen?
She's downstairs.
You alright?
Yeah, yeah, i'm fine.
and... and that's when you
came up behind me.
And... whatever
it was that I saw...
Wasn't.
What do you mean?
The room was...
as it was as it was when
i first came into it.
Why didn't you tell me
this on site?
I was a little freaked
out at the time.
a-and I didn't know what
the hell was going on.
Do you know now?
No.
But i know what i saw.
Ok so the woman
that you saw,
did you see her face?
No, no.
It all happened so fast, and...
She was gone.
Is this her?
Picked these up off
of nsa's satellites.
This was time-stamped
when the last f.b.i.
"incident" occurred.
No, that's not her.
I thought you said you
didn't see her face.
Yeah.
I didn't but...
I'm just saying the coloring
and the shape, it's, it's not...
sue me, alright?
It's not the woman i saw!
Anyways,
i'm running her against the
facial recognizance database.
Nothing so far.
She might've been
just passer by.
Almost makes you start
believing in ghosts.
Well, whatever is
going on in that house
and we're not going
to solve it from down here.
Boss, if you give me
another day...
No, the FBI is under
a lot of pressure.
Hope you didn't make
plans for this weekend.
Pack for a few days.
We're moving in.
I told you what i saw.
I don't know why it warrants
a special interrogation.
Is that what you
think this is?
It's what it feels like.
Given everything
you told me,
i have the distinct impression
that you haven't told me everything.
I told you what i saw.
But there's more,
isn't there?
What you saw meant
something to you.
Yeah, maybe that
i was losing my mind.
It's so simple,
just tell me what you're
not telling me.
I'm pretty good at
reading my people.
Well, maybe you should try
reading one of these.
Because you're certainly not doing
a very good job reading me.
You're off the case, jane.
What?
Why?
Because i believe whatever
you saw in that house
affected you deeply.
So deeply you can
scarcely talk about it,
and that makes
you unreliable.
Hey, i'm the one that heals
and recovers quickly, remember?
Only on the outside.
Get some rest.
You're sitting
this one out.
the kitchen's fully
stocked if anyone's hungry.
This feel to you guys like
one of those movies
where everybody goes in the old
house and nobody survives
because they all just get...
Riley, whatever's
going on in this house
has a rational explanation.
Yeah... That's exactly what
the scientist always says.
You know what,
he's also always wrong.
We secure here?
Just have to finish
up in the basement.
Then do it.
That's great,
just great.
Sure, riley,
we need you on site.
Why don't you just go down
to the basement
set up some
wires and die.
Great idea.
Thanks andre.
These guys ever
watch movies ?
Who the heck goes down
into the basement alone?!
The first guy to get it,
that's who!
Nothing down here,
that's good.
That's easy,
that's easy.
It's fine, it's fine,
it's fine...
The spirit of a dead child.
That's the worst.
That's always the worst.
Security breach in
the kitchen, security breech!!!
I'm on it,
backdoor.
It's okay.
I don't eat much.
We're a team, mcbride.
If you think it's worthy
of a court martial,
go for it.
But i'm in.
Every entry and exit
is covered.
If anyone comes in
or leaves...
They'll activate
the alarm.
These clasps will keep any of
us from activating the system.
We'll work
the "buddy system."
two to a room,
one on watch.
Do we get to draw
straws for our buddy?
Riley, you're
on first watch.
Great!!!
It's always the second
guy that gets it.
If you see or hear
anything...
I know...
Just scream.
It won't
be too difficult.
God.
On a serious note,
i pulled an i.d.
On that woman who was
in front of the house
when the f.b.i.
Agent lost it.
Anna robeson.
She's been near
or around this house
since the incidents began.
This is the first image i
have of her at this site,
captured four years ago.
But this man,
her husband,
karl robeson.
Protected witness?
If he was, the bureau claims
to know nothing about it.
I mean, I've been through
their database.
I can't find
one record,
not one that he was
ever brought here
or held in custody.
You think the
bureau's covering up?
Or someone on it.
Riley, give me a
closer look here.
Mean something to you?
It might.
Riley, what else do you
have on karl robeson?
The guy is off
the radar completely.
All i could come up with
is that he did time
at havenhurst for
grand theft auto.
You have a local
for anna robeson?
Still working on
a current address.
I mean...
I don't know
if she's indigent or what,
i'm striking out.
So the broad's a neuro.
Could be.
You find anything
else on anna robeson,
you let me know right away.
Yeah, of course.
Okay, people.
Let's turn in.
Nighty night, don't
let the bed bugs bite.
Good night.
Don't let
the bed bugs bite.
You sure this is
the right way, lieutenant?
The map says
east, lieutenant.
Yeah,
the map says east, lieutenant.
I think you got
this one wrong, boss.
Should of checked the map.
Should have checked the map.
I checked the...
NNoooo!!!!
Side servant's entrance!!!
Alright, what do we got?
Side entrance breech.
Send connor...
They're already on it.
Okay.
You alright?
Yeah !
Look what we
found sneaking around outside.
Anna robeson.
Why are you here,
mrs. Robeson?
Why do you keep
coming back to this house?
Because my husband...
Because karl is here.
There's no one
here besides us.
The day those two men
came to take karl...
I followed them.
They brought him
to this house.
I never saw karl after
they brought him here.
They said that they were
investigating him
about a kidnapping.
Karl would never
hurt anyone.
The f.b.i. Disagreed.
Karl was different.
And he worked for the people
who lost their daughter.
But if you knew him...
What do you mean
"different?"
it's hard to explain.
Try.
He could take my hand...
And instantly, i'd experience
what karl was feeling.
Joy, pain, sorrow...
Even anger.
Husbands and wives
often have those feelings
of being connected.
I know what
you're thinking.
But this was different.
And it wasn't
just with me.
I remember once when we
were out together...
It was a beautiful,
wonderful day.
We came across a homeless
man, asking for money.
But one look in his eyes,
you could see that his life
was lacking more than money.
Karl handed the man
five dollars.
But he held onto his
hand for a moment.
You could see
the change immediately.
It was as if this
man lit up inside...
His hope was restored.
Karl gave that to him.
It's beautiful.
This son of a bitch sounds
like a chip candidate to me.
Karl would never
hurt someone's child.
Or anyone.
Mrs. Robeson...
I'm afraid you're going to
have to spend the night here.
We're in the middle of an
investigation and right now...
You're a suspect.
I know why you're here.
The things that have
happened in this house.
Karl is here.
Maureen,
would you be so kind
as to take mrs. Robeson
up to your room.
Keep an eye on her.
Well, we know she's
telling the truth
about her husband being
brought here.
Why would the bureau
lie about that?
That's something we'll
have to find out.
I want every scrap of
information you can give me
on karl robeson.
You gotta consider that
broad has been around this place
every time something bad
has gone down.
That's right.
Why risk it?
I say we chip her
and ship her.
I do not believe that
she is our neuro.
E.s.p.?
No, she was right here
with us.
She could have had any
one of us at any time.
Why take the chance?!!
Why risk it?
Because i think she
knows something.
Something she's
not telling us.
Jane, would you mind
going upstairs,
help maureen keep an eye
on that woman.
If you're right and
she's not a neuro,
what she said about
her husband...
How when he
touched people...
I know.
Yeah.
Had enough of
connor as a roomie?
Just wanted some
time to myself.
You want
to talk about it?
Not really.
Sounds like
you do.
What'd you see?
Saw enough to help
me understand
part of what's going on
in this house.
Which is?
Which is specific
to the individual.
Whatever he or she
fears most.
I've been going over
the documented cases in my mind.
It was a woman.
The last woman,
she was supposed
to be a witness
in an organized
crime case...
A hemophobic...
That means she fears
of blood...
She saw blood coming
out of the walls.
An agent,
arachnophobic.
Could have sworn he saw
scorpions crawling out
from under the bed covers.
And you?
I saw men...
Under my command...
Dying.
because I made a mistake.
Something from your past?
Not specifically.
But something i live
with every day.
You can't take
responsibility for what
happens to us.
You don't believe
a word of that.
You know if you were
leading this team,
you would feel exactly
the same as i do.
You still haven't told
me what you saw.
I'm not sure
i understand it.
Enough to support
my theory?
When i know,
i'll let you know.
What are you doing here?
How did you find me?
What do you want?!
No!!!
no sign
of connor upstairs.
And mrs. Robeson?
Apparently slept
through the night.
No,
i've checked the entire
basement and the outside.
When was the last time
anyone saw connor?
Last night when we took
mrs. Robeson upstairs.
You try his comm?
Nothing.
Did an
ultrasound sweep.
Come on, people!!!
Well, where
the hell did he go?
He didn't just
vanish into thin air!
I got him.
Picked up connor's
comm set via gps.
Can you force a connect?
I could do that while
i was still in diapers.
You're hot.
Connor.
You already know what it's
like to sleep
in a four by six
cinder block room.
You gunning to go back?
I'm here, what's up?
What's up?
Isn't that my question?
Technically, you're awol.
Now, I want to know why.
Because hanging around
that house,
waiting for ghostly
apparitions to appear
is a waste of time.
That's my call.
) well, i made my own.
I can do a lot more
in the field
than i can hanging
around that house,
tucked in
with the rest of you.
I think the old broad
was onto something.
There's something
i need to check out.
You saw something
in the house.
What did you see ?
Connor!
Damn!
I lost him.
He's off the map.
I'm making a fresh pot.
Dr. Carpenter should be
here in about an hour
to pick you up for analysis.
What is it you
people are afraid of?
We just want him
to check you out,
make sure you're in
good health.
You're a bad liar,
miss bowers.
But whatever it is you
want me to do, i'll do.
Maureen!
I've got something.
I'll be right back.
Is everything alright?
What ?
Hey, mo,
not tomorrow.
Now!
Miss bowers.
Everything alright?
Bowers.
You alright?
What's wrong?
Maureen?
Andre!
You okay?
No,
i feel like
i'm losing my mind.
It's alright.
It's just the house.
Mom?
I thought you
were at school.
I don't go to
school anymore.
I'm grown up now.
This is always
my favorite time.
When i have
the house to myself.
Your father's gone
and you're gone.
And i get to be alone.
You like being alone?
It gives me
time to think.
What do you think about?
I think about you.
And wonder what's
so wrong about you.
I don't understand.
Can you imagine what it's
like to have a child...
A beautiful child..
Only to find
yourself frightened
by the very thing
you love the most?
You're frightened by me?
You were never like
the other children.
Even before
you could talk,
i knew you were different.
All the dreams we
had for a child...
...only to discover that i
was the mother of a freak.
Jane.
Tell me what you saw.
I don't wantto talk about it.
It isn't real.
Whatever you saw,
it's this house.
It's not real.
Some wounds don't
heal so quickly.
I understand.
But maureen's right.
This house has a way
of getting inside us.
The fear is real...
What you saw is not.
Is there any difference?
Yes.
We can conquer...
Or at least learn to live
with our fears.
I'll be alright.
I never doubted it.
yeah, yeah...
I'll let him know.
Connor's coming in.
He says he's
got something.
And he's bringing it
here for show and tell.
Jane...
Before you freaked...
I mean before
what happened...
What did you touch?
What're you talking about?
What'd did you touch?
Did you plug something in?
Turn on a light switch?
I don't know.
I suppose i turned
on the light.
Why?
Andre?
I was making some notes...
I turned off the light
and went to bed.
I was in the kitchen
with anna making coffee.
Is everything all right?
I knew it!
I am right again!
I am right again!!!
You going to have
a parade for yourself
or tell us
what's going on?
I just confirmed
with connor.
That his mp 3 player
plugged in
and he was listening
to music.
Wow, that really
explains it riley.
Don't you see,
Whatever it is...
it is in the electricity,
in the circuitry of the house.
So it seemed brilliant
to ask,
how come whatever is
in here didn't touch me?
I mean, with all
my equipment plugged in,
the drawing power.
There had to be
a logical explanation.
Look at this.
Come here.
Andre and jane were upstairs
when whatever
happened, happened.
But me and connor...
I'm getting to that.
The light switch
in jane's room,
the lamp in andre's,
the outlet connor used,
they all work
on the same circuit.
The house was re-modelled
at some point
and there was too much power
to draw from one circuit
so they split it off.
The coffee machine
works on
the same damn circuit.
Except for this
room and my gear.
Riley, you're out on a
pretty big limb with this.
Think about it.
Why does chipping
work on neuros?
Because neurological
activity is...
Electrical.
Electrical...
Exactly.
The chip can
interferes or shortcircuit
a connection in the brain.
All the wiring goes to a breaker
box located in the basement.
Hell, guys,
it's worth a look.
Okay...
It should be here,
right along this wall.
It's hollow.
It's just painted drywall.
It looks like a door
that's been boarded up.
Help me get this
thing out of the way.
Alright, get back.
Whoa.
Different circuit.
What do you
make of this?
It's an
interrogation room.
Crude, but familiar.
I see you found
camp's playground.
This is russell camp.
Assistant special
agent in charge
of the northeast
division of the f.b.i.
Who are you people?
I thought i told you that
we're asking the questions.
Alright connor,
what's going on?
I saw something
last night.
Something from my past.
Someone i hurt.
Which helped me rember
who this piece of garbage was.
You know him?
I know of him.
When i was
in the joint,
cops would be investigated
by the bushel.
Campy here was
working local p.d.
And was accused of
some very bad things.
What kind of things?
Let's just say
that his interrogation
techniques were...
Unconventional.
This is the agents
who brought anna's husband
to this house.
He and his partner,
dwight elkins.
Why lie about it?
Isn't it obvious?
He and elkins wanted to get
away from f.b.i. Headquarters
so they could conduct
their interrogations
so no eyebrows
would be raised.
A five-year old
girl was missing.
We didn't know if she
was dead or alive.
Robeson wanted
to lawyer up.
So you tortured him.
We were trying to
extract information.
Alright...
What happened?
He said he didn't know anything
about the kidnapping
and we let him go.
Look at this!!
You better talk,
you son of a bitch!!!
There was a girl's life
at stake, for godsake!
Here we go.
Alright!!! Alright!!
Nobody...
Nobody thought anything
was going to happen to him, ok?
We roughed him
up a little.
Dwight gave him a jolt
from the charger.
Nobody knew his heart
was going to stop.
We didn't know.
So you killed him?
He died, yeah.
You and elkins...
You got rid of the body,
walled the place up,
you didn't tell the f.b.i.
That you'd even
questioned the man.
They ended up catching
the kidnappers.
Two weeks later.
Still had the
kid with him.
Robeson had nothing
to do with it.
Given your future,
he might've made
the right choice.
Connor, call the f.b.i.
And tell them to pick
up this piece of garbage.
Congratulations, pal,
you are first in line
for the senate
investigation committee.
I love you, anna.
Everything anna robeson
described about her husband,
how he could pass on
his moods and emotions...
Sound like a neuro to me?
Alright, let's say he was.
So in his last moment,
he's electrocuted.
All his pain, his fear,
his last emotions...
All which are
brain activity...
And electrical...
Passed into the circuitry
of this house.
So you're saying
the house is a neuro?
I don't know.
But it seems everyone who came
in contact with that circuit
seemed to experience their
own pain and fear...
As if karl robeson was still
able to transmit emotion.
So what?
You're saying we should
chip the house?
This is nuts.
You have a better
explanation?
Wait, at the end...
That wasn't camp's voice.
I'll bet even money that
whatever was wrong
with this house,
isn't wrong anymore.
Carl robeson escaped this
house through camp,
the man who killed him.
Alright, are you willing to put
your money where your mouth is?
Yes, i am.
Let's go.
Follow me.
After you.
Keep talking.
Alright,
you fill my wallet.
You just turned
it on, right?
Flicked the switch.
Alright.
Oh, no!!!
Oh God !
Oh God ! Anything but that!
Riley !
Anything but that !
What is it ?
What's wrong ?
What's wrong?
It's...
It's decaf!
I hate decaf.
I will get you for that.
I'm sorry.
A president once said,
"we have nothing to fear
but fear itself."
andre, one of the
strongest men i know,
admitted his fear to me.
Even maureen admitted her
fear of losing control,
i think my greatest
weakness is the fear
that i'll be seen as weak.
But i have to wonder,
if the vulnerable
aren't the strong.
And if those who wear
their strength like a shield,
the weak
and frightened.
Hey.
I think
i am ready to talk.
Come on in.
www.seriessub.com