My name is Jane Vasco.
I could use you on my team.
I work for a secret government agency
that hunts Neuros.
People who can do dangerous
things with their minds.
On my first assignement
something a little weird happen,
Okay, something really weird
Until I get some answers,
I'm getting on with my life,
doing my job,
stocking up on aspirin,
Because, I got to tell ya,
pain's a bitch.
This is beautiful.
You like it?
Absolutely beautiful.
She's just talking about
the tag, Riley !
I know !
I love salamanders !
It's not a salamader,
it's a chameleon.
It's the underground cop
of the reptile world.
Always blends in.
Can't be pinned down.
It's perfect for you
So what's gonna be for you, Lady?
Maybe a puma.
Cunning, dangerous,
Ever quite know, it's going on beyond nice
Hey, I ain't got nothing for a while, thanks
Hey, come on.
It would be great right in here, ya
Right there.
Yeah, but who?
Ah no, I don't know, I'll pass, Thanks.
Truly a shame.
Now, you're telling me
All right, so what do you think I should get?
Right here
All around here
Definitely not that hangover you're
gonna have tomorrow morning buddy
We should heu...
pack'in up!!
No it's early, it's early, right?
Seing, it's early !
No, actually Mo, it's quite late.
Why don't you, heu, paid him ?
Do you accept good "two it is" ?
Never said no before !
I think our friends has had a little bit too much to drink
I dare say that yes !!
Okay !
Jane, that man is an artist.
And you're clearly
a patron of the arts.
So, whatta you say?
The three of us?
My place?
One of us has
to take him home.
You girls could flip for it.
That was easy.
C'mon ri,
get in the taxi.
You coming?
No, i've got a ride.
Oh, right.
C'mon cinderella.
We better get home,
before i turn
into a pumpkin.
I think you passed
that critical line.
So your place or mine?
Ri, you are really
going to feel terrible
in the morning.
Five more, Five more minutes.
Dr. Pearson to
maternity,please Dr. Pearson
to maternity.
What?
No!!
Hello?
Is anybody here?!!!
Transcript : swsub.com
Presync : IceFre@k
Hospitals,
not exactly one of the top ten
vacation destinations.
Sterile surroundings,
intimidating machines.
And lab coated doctors
rattling off critical data...
They make indigestion
sound like some flesh
ravaging disease.
Then there's the worst part...
The food.
But the question of the day
isn't what's on the menu,
but what the hell was
I doing here?
Hey, you're awake.
Who are you?
What happened?
Where am i?
How did i get here?
I'm shelly.
I'm your day nurse.
You're in the hospital.
Why am i tied down?
The doctor will
be in, in a minute.
Why can't you tell me what
the hell's going on.
I'm sorry.
The doctor..
No, no, please.
You'll pul
your lines out.
Take it easy,
just try and keep still.
Okay, okay...
It's for your
own safety, jane.
I'll take over,
thank you.
I'm sorry about
the restraints.
But last night...
What about last night?
You don't remember anything
about last night?
Of course i do.
I was out
with my friends.
I took riley home
then i went home.
At least i thought i did.
That's all you remember?
Well, clearly there's
something i can't rember.
So why don't you tell me
what's happening to me.
I'm your doctor.
Jakob baumgartner.
As for your memory loss...
Don't be too concerned.
A certain amount of
memory loss is to be expected.
To be expected from what?!
Was in some kind
of accident?
Some of the treatments
you've received have been..
Rigorous.
Treatments?
How long have
i been in here?
Why don't we have
this conversation
after the effects of
the sedatives have worn off.
Why don't we have it now?
Because i'd prefer that
you were clear and focused.
And less agitated.
We'll bring you
some breakfast.
Some strong coffee.
We'll talk afterwards.
Why can't you tell me
what's happening to me?
Do this for me.
Have some breakfast and
some faith that i have
the best
interest at heart.
I promise, all your
questions will be answered.
I'll be back soon.
How's our patient vasco?
Pretty much what
we expected.
Disoriented.
Angry.
Confused.
You reassured her,
of course.
Gained her trust.
Yes.
But as i told you from the outset,
vasco isn't a simple case.
Dr. Baumgartner.
I was wondering about your
orders for patient vasco.
No more restraints?
No, not at present.
Any special orders
for staff, then?
Do we need to be
on suicide watch?
No, i don't expect that
to be a problem.
Thank you.
Okay.
No sudden movements,
that's how you pull
these things off.
Sorry.
The doctor said he'd be
back to speak with me.
That was over
an hour ago.
I'll let him know.
Soon, please.
Seth?
Dr. Carpenter.
Were we expecting you?
I'm concerned
about jane vasco.
Of course you are.
That's to be expected.
How is she doing?
She hasn't recovered from
her coma yet,
Dr. Baumgartner is
encouraged though.
Her vitals are strong.
If i could just
look in on her.
There's really no
point right now.
I'm sorry you
wasted a trip.
If there's any change, I assure you,
we'll let you know.
Seth!
Jane!
I don't know why they're
lying to you
or what's going on but we've got
to get out of here.
Seth, we've
got to go, now!
Security! Guards!
What are you doing?
This is no way
to behave, jane.
What are you
talking about?
Why are you
doing this to me?
What did you expect,
jane?
How should we treat you
after you killed riley?
What?!!!!!!!
Get off of me!!!!!!
It is impossible !
I don't believe it.
That's not going
to bring jensen back.
It doesn't make any sense?
Why would i do that?
When was this supposed
to have happened?
Is this another thing you
claim not to remember?
Andre...
I honestly don't rember.
You want to play this game,
jensen had too
much to drink.
You walked to his place.
He was found dead
the next morning.
Why don't you tell
me what happened!
What set you off?!
How am I supposed to tell
you what happened,
when i don't even
believe this!!
You don't believe it?
Really?
You believe that?
Is that yours?
Looks like it is.
Does that jog your memory?
Riley, you're really
going to feel terrible.
It doesn't make any sense.
I made a bad call
with you, vasco.
I should've
turned you in.
What are you
talking about?
Your healing powers,
jane.
What did you think
that was all about?
Your dna has tested
neuro positive.
Why didn't you tell me?
Would it have
changed anything?
The question is,
why didn't i report it
to my superiors,
if i had jensen
might be alive today.
In that sense,
i own this
as much as you do.
And this place?
What is it?
If I am what you say I am,
why not just chip me
and take me to the lab at
the internment center?
Where the others go.
Chip you?
With your abilities?
As for
the internment centre,
we'd get no
answers there.
Nico has been
a complete failure.
And this place?
Baumgartner?
Baumgartner was head
of research at nico.
Fought an uphill battle for two years
to change procedures.
But we still sent
neuros there.
No alternative.
Not until
baumgartner quit.
Nico's no more
than a warehouse.
They've cut funding
to almost nothing.
The place is a toilet.
The only one who seemed
to care was baumgartner
about research
about finding answers.
And maybe a cure.
that's beautiful.
You think he can help me?
Help you.
Do you think i give a damn
if he could help you.
As far as i'm concerned,
you're here to help him.
An intact neuro.
Unchipped, powers
fully functioning.
There's a lot
he can learn from you.
Things i should have
but didn't.
I'll be taking marrow
samples along each leg.
I'll need ten intraosseus
1.27 mm needles.
Did you say ten?
In a single session?
I should up
the dosage of tetracaine
or else she'll feel pain?
You won't need
an anesthetic.
For bone marrow extrusion?
Protocol calls for
a 5 mig minimum, doctor.
Anything less and she'll
be screaming in agony.
We're setting new
standards, nurse wells.
I don't understand.
I don't need you
to understand.
I need you to assist.
First needle please.
- If you need something you should tell me now.
- I don't need anything...
That's all, nurse,
you can wait outside please.
Okay, jane, just relax.
I don't give a damn
about what happens.
As far as i'm concerned
you are here to help him.
Hey, how are you doing?
I'm still alive.
So not doing so good.
Well...
Dr. Baumgartner seems
quite sure of his methods.
Even if they seem
a little unconventional.
I'm &just going to sterilize the entry sites,
it'll only sting a little.
I must've misunderstood.
There're no points
of entry.
Didn't they...?
Didn't they tell you?
I'm different.
Is there anything
i can get for you?
Are you in pain?
What's it going to be for you, lady,
maye a puma...
What i need,
you can't get for me.
We have a visitor.
I'll send her in.
Hey, kiddo.
How you doing?
Mo,
did i really
do those things?
Did i really kill riley?
I loved riley.
I don't know
what's happening to me.
You'll be okay.
I don't even know
who i am anymore.
What did andre say to you?
He told me what happened
and what i have to do.
Follow doctor's orders.
Baumgartner.
Let me ask you something.
What's your take
on that guy?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
It's just
this whole thing.
Why?
Before you, before
any of this happen,
did you ever hear any discussion
that nico was failing?
Andre probably thought it
was none of our business.
Maybe.
Or maybe he has
something to hide.
It's a chameleon, always blends in.
You?
The fact that he has someone
like you on our team.
You mean a neuro.
That's not
been confirmed.
Apparently you missed
the morning edition.
Mo, what're
you getting at?
I don't know.
It's more questions than answers.
It's just...
I don't know, baumgartner.
Keeping you away from
the internment center
could be andre's way
of covering his ass.
That doesn't
sound like andre.
No,
but killing riley
doesn't sound like you.
I want to look
into this,
if i find any answers...
Trust me.
I want to be the
first to know.
So hang in there, okay.
I'll be back.
Nurse wells,
bring me the bone marrow
results for patient vasco.
Perhaps i left it
in my office.
I found them,
dr. Baumgartner.
Good.
I'll be in room c examining
the results.
Seth...
You shouldn't be out of your
room without permission.
I just needed
to take a walk.
To think.
I understand.
Next time, though,
ask for permission.
This is a hospital,
not a prison.
It's for your
own safety, jane.
What happened, seth?
What would make
me hurt riley?
I don't know.
There's still a lot we
don't know about...
Neuros?
Your condition.
And you think this is
the best place for me?
Maybe the only place.
But why not nico?
I thought all the research
was centered there?
I thought andre told you.
Nico's become an
embarrassment.
They've given up trying to
do anything
but store the people
we send them.
That's why baumgartner left.
Exactly.
Jakob baumgartner is the
foremost expert in this field.
He authored the first
paper describing
the neuro aberration.
He's done nothing since
but study the phenomenon.
He resigned from nico when he
saw their changed priorities.
Do you trust him?
I do.
Sorry, jane.
I'll look back
on you tomorrow.
Connor, am i glad
to see you!!
You got to know what's
going on here.
Shhh, it's okay.
Don't do this.
Listen to me!!!
Why would i listen to anything
a damn neuro has to say?
Are you part of this, too?
Face it, lady, you had us
all fooled for a while,
but you're just another
chip candidate.
And what're you, connor?
You and seth?
All of you.
You just march step to whatever
Andre tells you to do ?
Mcbride didn't kill riley.
You did.
So yeah. right now, i'd
follow him into hell.
And being here with you...
It looks like
i'm already there.
How is she?
She feels cut off
and abandoned.
Alone and isolated.
She found the nico report
as we expected she would.
Then we're almost there.
Yes.
I prefer speaking with
you face to face.
Any word on vasco?
Is that concern i hear?
So i like the broad.
I just want to find her so
I can bust her chops.
I'm sure she'll
be flattered.
Riley?
Tell me you got something!
Look, I got feelers running into every
system in the known universe.
Airports, hospitals,
everything's running a blank.
No credit card
use, no atm hits.
Nothing.
You two,
i need a complete timeline of
everything you did that night.
Every bar you stopped at,
every joker
who offered you a drink.
Boss...
What?
We've been over
this ten times.
We'll go through
it 10,000 times
until we find her,
is that clear?!
I want security footage
from every red light camera,
bank lobby, every wired
parking ramp you might
have passed on thursday night.
You think we
had a stalker?
It happens.
Wrong kind of guy sees a
couple of chicks out drinking,
faculties impaired maybe...
Follows his favourite
one home, for
the snatch and grab.
How "impaired" was jane?
A few beers.
Tequila.
A few tequilas.
Connor, emergency
rooms in person.
Every jane doe, every female admitted
in the last two days.
Done.
Wait a minute!!
If she'd been hurt,
she would have
healed out by now.
Theoretically, yes.
But we have to check
all possibilities.
If she's hurt and not healing,
we can figure out why later.
After we find her.
Connor..
You should check
the morgues, too.
I think we're ready to
move to the final phase.
She's convinced that i'm a fraud
and that her only hope
lies in getting
to nico.
Jakob, you understand
failure is not an option.
You were quite
clear about that.
It's crucial that i find
the location of that center.
And she's the only one
who can take me to it.
All that's left is to throw her a lifeline,
which is?
The one person she
really trusts.
This is good.
Good evening.
Good evening, doctor.
I'm afraid i was
right about andre.
I found out some things.
That makes two of us.
I found a report.
The nico report.
I managed to tap
into riley's database.
I found the same thing.
Then you know that
baumgartner's full of crap.
I should be at nico.
The doctors there are
onto something.
That's why i'm here.
If andre finds out...
The hell with Andre.
We've got to get
you out of here, jane.
Thanks, mo.
I owe you.
You do.
And you'll pay.
Just lay low,
i got to figure things out.
I'll be back in
the morning.
And we'll get you
to nico.
I'd like to check on the state
credentials of a dr. Jakob baumgartner?
Yeah ok, I'll hold..
Hi, tomorrow...
Can i call back in
the morning then?
Perfect.
Thank you very much.
Jane.
- Here you are !
- What are you doing here?
They told me they moved
you tonight...
I have to talk to you.
What is it?
Whatever's going on here...
Baumgartner...
He's not a... He's a..
He's a...
- What ?
- He's a...
I don't know what he is.
I'm not even know
if he's human.
But this hospital,
this whole place...
What they're
doing to you...
It's all a lie!
Okay, jane,
it's a lie.
What do you mean?
There are no patients
here, none.
And no other doctors.
Whatever's going on...
It's all about you.
I know.
I don't understand.
I saw something earlier.
I don't know how
to explain it.
But the doctor...
Somehow he changed...
I know it sounds insane
but he's some kind of monster who
can change his appearance.
I don't know what he is.
That's okay..
That's okay
We're called
neuros, shelly.
How are you feeling?
Little bit woozy,
must have given me something.
If we're going to do this,
we're doing it now.
Let's go.
What are you doing
out of your room?
Get down!!!
Everybody stay down!!!
No one will get hurt!!!
Stay down!!!
Put it down!!
Put it down!
Damn it jane,
my gun's jammed!
No!!
Mo!!!!
My ankle!
Where's the car?
Go! Go!! Go!!! Hurry!!!
I am!!
Are you okay, mo?!
Yeah, i'm okay.
Brought your clothes
to change into.
Aren't you relieved
you'll be at nico soon?!
You always had my best mo,
i appreciate it.
Hey Mo, you know what ?
I heu...
I officially
forgive you
for stealing todd engels
right out from under me
the first year
at the academy.
Hey, what did you expect.
He was there.
I wasn't really
into him anyway.
Thanks for driving,
my ankle still killing me.
Don't talk to me
about your ankle,
i'm the one who got
shot in the back.
let's get out of here.
Fill it up, we don't
want to stop again.
We're attracting
too much attention.
Hand me my wallet out of my purse
and i'll pay you when we get going.
Have you got cash?
I don't want anybody
tracking us by my cards.
Good thinking.
Thanks.
Jane's credit card!
$23.47 for gas.
How soon before
we get to nico, jane?
We won't get there
until tomorrow.
You planning
to drive all night?
I could use a break.
How's the ankle?
Not good, actually.
Want to stop
and take a rest?
I just want to get there.
How'd you girls
like your food?
It was fine.
Best hash browns
in the state.
Great.
I get you anything else?
No, i think
we're gonna head out.
Just the check.
Do you have enough cash?
Meet you in the car.
Your foot better?
You want to drive?
It's a little sore but if you're
sick of it, I can try.
It's fine,
i'll do it.
Thanks
Thank you!!
Bless your hearts!
No problem.
What can i say,
i'm a good tipper.
Another hit.
$23.47 again.
$23.47...
How's the ankle?
Still a little swollen.
Hope you don't mind driving
the rest of the way to nico.
No, we're almost there.
Excellent.
This is it.
This is it?
This is nico?
Why?
I just expected...
Don't you recognize it?
This is where you live.
No, that's not
exactly right.
This is where i live.
You forgot one
small detail, doc.
Maureen just
got a new tattoo.
And you didn't realize i saw
you walking without a limp.
As my father
always says...
What you don't
know can hurt you.
Are you okay?
I will be.
What?
I never thought i'd be so
happy to see the real you.
Where's riley?
He's back
at the command centre.
Connor...
Want to get this garbage
in the car, please.
You got my messages.
Guess i did.
I don't think we ever had
a shape-shifter before.
The guy did a pretty
good "you."
never as good as
the real thing.
Really?
You took a hell
of a risk, vasco,
even if you didn't
believe maureen.
How did you know the rest
of us weren't real.
To be honest, i had my
doubts about you, too.
I mean baumgartner's
version of you.
He kept referring
to riley as jensen.
You never do that.
Smart.
So once i figured out maureen wasn't
maureen, the rest fell into place,
besides you would never had been caught
with someone like todd engels.
Who?
Exactly.
Mo, i officially forgive you
for stealing todd engels.
What do you expect,
he was there.
Rember that little dude from
first year at the academy?
Oh, the dorky guy who was
always quoting mark twain?
No.
I figured wherever you guys were,
you'd be looking for me.
And i knew that if
anyone could find me..
It would have to be "the best."
I brought donuts.
Sweet!!!
Riley!!!
They told me i killed you.
I could think of
worse ways to go.
I got it right away.
$23.47 for gas.
$23.47 for breakfast.
I told him
i was using cash
but i knew you'd pick up those
hits on my credit card.
Of course.
Hey, it was big tip.
Everyone knows you're
not that big a tipper.
Good thing you
remembered my address.
Good information.
Don't even think about it.
So what was it about?
Did baumgartner
give anything up?
Not a thing.
Obviously he wanted
the location of nico.
He has it now.
Hope you had a good
vacation, vasco.
But we've got work to do.
Vacation?
Yep, I'm home !
We often take our friends for granted
until something happens
and makes us appreciate
them more than ever.
Like being there for us when
we break up with our boyfriends.
Or when we realize
they don't want to be
dissected in medical experiments
and locked up for killing
one of them.
Absolutely nothing.
Not a scrap of paper.
It's like no one
was ever here.
According to riley,
there's no record
of any recent tenants.
I can try to track something down
through utilities
or moving services, but
I'm not holding
out much hope.
This was a pro job.
Whoever did this
has skills and money
Give me a minute.
When i was in this room,
i thought my friends
had turned on me.
I thought i deserved it.
I was never happier to find
out it wasn't true.
To be honest...
There's a part of me stil
waiting for it to happen.
Ready?
Yeah.
There's nothing here.
They've accepted me as part of their
team, even with my gift.
But i'm still not sure that
gift isn't really a curse,
and it's just a matter of time
before they realize it.
Okay, i have trust issues,
sue me.
www.seriessub.com