My name is Jane Vasco.
I could use you on my team.
I work for a secret government
agency that hunts Neuros.
People who can do dangerous
things with their minds.
On my first assignment...
something a little weird happened,
okay, something really weird.
Until I get some answers
I'm getting on with my life,
doing my job...
stocking up on aspirin...
because I gotta tell ya,
pain's a bitch!
"TRISTATE NATIONAL BANK"
So, what do you think he's gonna hit first,
the teller or the vault?
- That remains to be seen.
- Or not.
Federal agents! Everything is
under control! Connor, get the car.
- Who the hell are you guys?
- Let's go.
You're gonna tell me what this is about?
Well, you're on your way
to the Freak Zoo Palace, pal.
Not bad, that's the house.
Is that what this is to you? Sport?
Well, it is us against them, darling, so,
yeah, as long as we're winning, I'm good.
What the hell!
Something's up with the Freon.
It's overheating.
Stop the car.
- Stop the car!
- I can't.
Move this damn thing over!
We're not overheating guys.
Hang on.
Halt! Stop! Stop!
- Stop where you are!
- Connor!
Stop or I'll shoot!
You guys want to tell me
what the hell has just happened?
That guy was chipped.
PAINKILLER JANE 1x15 "THE HEALER"
Subtitles subXpacio and TusSeries
Ok, I've performed over two dozen tests
including a postmortem...
I've found no variation
from the standard Neuro positive.
So how do you explain a chipped Neuro
still able to function.
I can't. However,
is merely an assumption...
that this man was responsible
for what happened to the vehicle.
Half the engine block was melted.
Trust me, doc, that's a hell of a lot
more than just a bad transmission.
Ok, according to this man's chart,
his ability was cellular.
Invisibility involves reorganizing
the cellular structure...
to absorb rather than reflect light.
Which has nothing to do
with melting the engine.
Exactly. To date we've never encountered
a Neuro with multiple abilities.
You think we're witnessing
some kind of mutation?
Even if we were, and I saw no indication
of that, the man was chipped.
Or maybe the chip failed?
My test confirmed
that the chip was functional.
Besides, if it failed, wouldn't he
have used his invisibility...
when he attempted to escape?
Something hit that truck, doc.
Sure; or someone. But
whatever or however it was,
it was not the man you apprehended.
Thoughts?
Yeah, freak show
is getting freakier by the moment.
Constructive thoughts?
If the man did possess multiple powers,
maybe they resided
in different parts of his brain,
and when we chipped him,
we only brought half of them down.
That's a good thought, but Seth
would've found some indication of that.
So, right now we have no idea
what we're dealing with.
Riley, any update on that Neuro
we are looking for? Jennifer Town?
She's off the radar. No credit card hits,
bank withdrawals, cell phone use...
She's got a removal
a prescription for "Glucofash".
No hits on the pharmacy either.
- Anything off the Comsat?
- Flat line. Nothing.
I've got a whole lot of people
giving me a whole lot of nothing.
I'll let you know when I have something.
Easier to find real men with real weapons.
None of that's easy.
As for our invisible Neuro, I still think
we can't rule out a mutation.
Which Seth won't be able to identify
which put some another step ahead of us.
Well, look at the bright side,
you could've been a lawyer.
I better take off.
You still owe me that incident report
form the Forrest case.
Which is still sitting on my desk.
As you can tell paperwork
is not my favorite thing.
You don't have to like it,
Jane, you just have to do it.
Brian and I have plans tonight.
It's sort of an anniversary.
One more day?
What would that be,
the third one more day?
Go ahead. Someone at least
will get something out of this day.
- Thanks.
- Have fun.
Some times you need a shower
after a rough day.
Not just to cleanse the body but
sometimes the mind.
Not to say mine's particularly dirty,
although I do have my moments,
I'm talking more about the conscience.
Bri, what're you doing here?
You want to try that again but
this time with...
Bri! Hey, this is great!
I thought you were out of town and...
I'm so happy that you came
back a day early just to see me.
Of course I'm happy to see you.
But...
I didn't know you were coming...
and have this report due...
and I promised to have it in
tomorrow morning.
- So, what's another day?
- It's my job.
All right, it's all right. I understand.
I don't suppose there's another
beautiful, brilliant woman in town who...
wouldn't mind a surprise visit.
I promise I'll make it up to you.
- But the report comes first.
- Only tonight.
I had to make sure my nose
wasn't too close to Brian's face...
or I might have poked his eye out.
When it comes to lying,
Pinocchio has noting on me today.
Who was it that said:
"No matter how bad you feel,
guilt makes it worse.
No wait, that was me.
Hi. Thanks.
- I'm working on it.
- News flash!
Our paralyzer Neuro. I've got her.
Jennifer Talon. I think she finally
took a chance and used her cell phone.
- I hope it was important.
- Location?
The Marina.
I'll work in SatCom now to narrow it down.
All right, let's roll.
Go at Jennifer Talon from a distance.
I'm not an idiot, boss.
Long range night scope with a chip rifle.
Silencer too, for her pleasure.
That's good. We get too close to this woman,
we don't know what she's capable of.
Well, if we get too close to her...
Adequate.
The cruise was wonderful, thank you.
I hoped to be in many more.
Sorry, I...
Don't fight it Adam...
It won't do any good.
I know, it must be a disconcerting feeling
experiencing complete paralysis.
The mind fully functioning.
aware of what's going on but...
the body just won't respond.
It must be just awful.
You did tell me I was priceless.
You're wrong.
- Riley?
- Sector right, last boat.
Got it.
- All right, careful boss.
- Thanks, kid.
It's right in front of you.
This leap succeed.
The effects of the paralysis
will wear off once I leave.
You might be a little sore.
Take two aspirin.
Don't call me in the morning.
- You're ok?
- I'm fine. Keep going.
- Connor is down!
- I'm on my way.
- Take it.
- I'll be ok, keep going.
Pressure.
I know, I can be a real bitch sometimes.
Come here.
- You ok?
- Is that Jennifer Talon?
Wasted talent.
Yep, you're all right.
Get him back to the subway. Have
Seth look him over. I'll clean up here.
What are you gonna do with me?
We'll take you some place where there
are a lot of other people just like you.
All right, you're all done.
- So, what's the damage?
- Besides his face?
The cut was strong. I will have
the stitches out in a few days,
Just try not to put
too much strain on that area.
Thanks doc, I'll mention that
to the next Neuro who tries to kill me.
We were fifty yards from that boat.
There's no way she could've seen us coming.
Try telling that to my spleen.
She must've spotted us.
I don't think so.
It's like the last one. Jennifer Talon
had the ability to induce paralysis.
That is not what went down in the dock.
You think this is the same mutation?
- Twice in a row?
- A bit of a coincidence.
- What then?
- I think we've got a second Neuro.
He'd harassed you this morning,
hit us in the Marina this afternoon.
I can help up with that.
Some of the damps the dock was very
similar to what happened to our transport.
What are you saying, we have
some lunatic Neuro stalking the team?
Starting to look that way.
They'd need access to our Intel.
They've got that.
A leak.
Not from my system.
I could not happen.
They did, Riley. I need you to double
and triple check your security.
- Look...
- Just do it.
The leak could be human, not systems.
- Even one of us.
- No, Outside. Morgan's people.
- I'll handle that end.
- And our end?
It doesn't make any sense. Everything
that's happened has put us at risk.
Besides, I trust you people with my life.
Something troubling you?
We've been working
together for five weeks now.
Has there been any change with you?
I don't know.
I think I'm just gonna wind up
a freak that heals with a high IQ.
- And that scares you.
- Shouldn't it?
Strange, eh?
Someone who comes to a healer
hoping he can help her not heal.
God chooses different paths
for his children.
We see killing most
when we stray from that path.
Something else is bothering you.
I told you previously that I have
misgivings about my work.
That I'm not always sure
that we're doing the right thing.
And...
I'm not supposed to be talking
about it with anyone.
Now you've assured me
that whatever we discuss...
- ...is completely confidential.
- And it is.
Do you trust me?
Yes.
You're still getting the headaches?
Maybe all I really need is some sleep.
I'm gonna head out.
Can I trouble you with one
more thing before I go?
- A hug?
- Of course.
I'm available whenever
you feel is necessary, Jane.
Thank you.
This better be important.
I don't like wasting my time.
It is Morgan, we have a leak.
- Single instance?
- Multiple.
- Consequences?
- Casualties, none fatal yet.
- Fix him before there are.
- That's why I'm here.
I don't appreciate what you're implying.
Rest assured my plumbing is very
sound. If there's a leak,
it's coming from your own kitchen.
Until this is resolved
I'm taking my team in dark.
- People in the dark tend to step their toe.
- They won't.
Do it, but watch your step.
You're still here!
Of course I'm still here!
The man said double
and triple check my systems.
You can't go over the blueprints of
the pyramids and get home by 5 o'clock.
Sorry I asked.
- Is Seth still in the lab?
- Isn't he always?
Double and triple check your systems.
Unbelievable.
What you got there?
You scared me.
- I'm sorry, I...
- That's fine.
What are you into so late?
Just a theory I'm working on.
- Tell me about it.
- Really?
Really. What's up?
Ok, Neanderthal.
- Neanderthal?
- Indeed!
One the $ 10.000 questions in genetics,
well, in evolutionary biology
in general, is...
what happened to Neanderthal?
I don't know. What did happen to it?
No it, them. I don't know either,
but the question is very exciting.
It's just a hobby of mine.
So far I surmised that...
Neanderthal DNA maybe somehow
hiding inside the human population.
- Hiding?
- Yes.
- Fascinating.
- Yes!
Would you like to see
the genome structure?
You know I absolutely would, Seth,
but I've...
I've got this report do and...
- Maybe another time.
- Yeah, absolutely.
Oh, actually, could you...
do me a favor?
Hairs? Human?
Unless they're Neanderthal.
I'm just kidding, Seth.
Would you mind running a
DNA test for me and...
keeping it between us.
Andre has to authorize all the tests.
Right, that's right.
The ones he knows about.
This is US government equipment, Jane.
All the tests have to be authorized.
Even with my hobby, Andre sings off.
I'm not asking you to do anything
outside of the box here, Seth.
DNA testing is a very important part
of what we do.
- Yes, it is.
- So, we're not doing anything wrong here,
and if the results come back
Neuro positive,
I'll tell Andre right away.
Jane, where did you get this sample from?
Seth, I'm asking you to do me...
a personal favor, ok?
I mean, we got to have something
over the Neanderthals, right?
You see, we are smart enough
to know when we can...
alter the rules.
Ok.
Thank you.
Seth!
What kind of person are you?
What's it, do you think you're
above the rules, or what?
- Riley. Let me tell you, it's all me.
- Jane. Jane, Jane, Jane, Jane, Jane.
Let Seth explain it himself.
- I don't know what to say.
- Cause there's nothing to say.
Seth...
when you finish the last cup of coffee...
you put on a new pot.
You put on a new pot.
Plain and simple.
- I think what I said.
- Yeah, look
- ...call me with the results.
- Immediately.
- Hello.
- Jane, it's Seth.
I just thought you'd be glad to know
that the sample tested Neuro negative.
Thanks.
Okay. I just want to thank you...
Jane! Congratulations
on you new promotion!
I heard you authorized
a DNA test yesterday.
- Yes.
- I want chapter and verse.
Who? What? When?
Why?
A while back I went out a window.
Cut off 46 stories.
All the way down, I thought it was over.
Obviously, it wasn't.
But it's been bugging me
ever since that...
the meaning of life and all that.
What I am.
Is this you attempting
to answer my question?
- What do you know of the fate of yours?
- Not as much as I want to.
Right, I felt the same way, but this guy,
Joseph Grace is different.
Joseph Grace?
You know this guy?
Well, yes, he's been the subject
of some controversy in the literature,
involving cases of terminal cancer that
went into remission. That sort of thing.
You're saying he's for real?
Well, that depend on what you mean.
Do I think people may have healed
under his influence? It's likely.
There's a recognized,
perceivable effect in the body.
I'd attribute half of his supposed miracles
to that, the other half to exaggeration.
All right, I want you
to find out more about this guy.
You, with me.
I'm sorry, I thought he knew.
I thought he knew.
And you've been seen this man
for over a month?
Yes.
And when we found
we had a leak you had to wonder...
if this was the Neuro stalking our team.
When Joseph uses his healing on me,
I feel something.
Like an energy passing through me.
I suppose I had to consider the possibilities
that it wasn't all God given.
- You told him things.
- Nothing that would compromise the team.
Joseph is a good man
and he did test Neuro negative.
And if he hadn't?
I suppose this would be the last
conversation we'd be having.
Is it?
Don't ever go behind my back again.
You have a problem, you come talk to me.
Right.
Eh, Riley, what do you got on this guy?
Joseph Grace. He's not criminal record,
never been sued,
Doctors they think he's full of it
but they can't prove anything.
Doesn't mean he's not full of it?
Not to the nine documented cases of cancer
remission he's had in the last five years.
Look, whatever healed this people
wasn't this bozo?
What's Jane to heal her for anyway? I mean,
it might be the one thing
she doesn't need help with.
She can heal the wound
but she cannot heal the pain.
Did you make that up yourself?
- I read it in a fortune cookie.
- Oh, hey Connor,
- ...you're not feeling well.
- What?
Yeah, you're feeling kind of sick,
you make an appointment with Joseph Grace.
- See what you can find out.
- Look, I already know what I'll find out.
The guy tested Neuro negative.
I'd be wasting my time.
Humor me.
If he lays his hands on me...
This means spiritual pace is pretty good.
Hello, I'm Joseph.
Thank you for coming.
Won't you come in?
Constant pain.
And they say nothing can be done.
I've tried everything.
This is my last resort.
Faith. Is our faith
that keeps us close to the creator.
I try and play a small part on that.
Do you thing you can help me?
Relax.
Close your eyes.
Clear your mind of worries...
of questions...
Give me your hands.
I'll give them back, I promise.
Now, just relax.
Hear boss,
We've to talk. Either this guy is a Neuro,
or he's the real deal.
Copy.
- What do you got, doc?
- Ok.
These images are from a medical
investigation into Joseph Grace...
conducted at Mass General.
This is a broken femur that healed normally.
This is femur that was ravished
by bone cancer that was...
quote, unquote, healed by Joseph Grace.
Doctor, I have no idea
what we're looking at here.
Ok, that's the normally healed bone.
This is the other one.
They're different.
Yes, they're different, but
what this shows is that Joseph...
actually has a real effect.
He's actually healing people.
- I'm astonished.
- So was Connor.
Apparently his wound has already healed.
Really? I'll look into that.
Doctor, tell me something.
Could this healing have
a potential downside?
Could it be dangerous?
To the average person?
Not that I can tell. Heal the cells but...
these are from Jane.
That's from before,
that's from a couple of days ago.
It's the same. I mean, all I can see here
is that Joseph healing effect on Jane...
- ...is the same as the others.
- Yes, but...
you have to remember that Jane
isn't like another people.
Hey boss, what are you doing?
No, no, no. It's all right.
I've doing this all night.
I've got a beat on that Neuro
has been ambushing us.
It's time we turn the tables.
Did you find out how he's getting
access to inside information?
No, we chip him first, ask questions later.
It's what I've talking about.
I've got this surveillance shot
off the FBI database.
He's a mercenary.
Works for the highest bidder.
Seems pretty able to elude
FBI surveillance at will.
We got it at the scene
of every ambush so far.
I know exactly where and when
to find you, son of a bitch.
Connor?
Yeah, I'm in position.
No sign of the subject.
- Vasco.
- In position.
Got nothing either.
Riley, talk to me.
Subject’s vehicle has entered the vicinity.
Unless he's been tipped and it's a decoy.
No, no. Play it through.
I've got him.
Entering the park from the East.
I do not have a clear shot.
I got him.
Holly!
He's moving!
Don't bother.
This is Edward Small.
A friend of mine.
Go, will you?
You're just gonna let him go?
- He's the one who's been attacking us!
- No Jane, you are.
There's no doubt in my mind.
There should be. I would never do
anything to put this team in danger.
You would never do anything consciously.
I've discovered how
Joseph healing ability works.
Basically he's somehow able to energize
each cell stimulating it to repair itself.
Then that energy creates
an attractive force...
bringing the organ
or tissue together with hope.
- But?
- But your constitution is not typical.
Tell me about it.
Applying Joseph energy to someone
like you, the results are unpredictable.
Even so, how is this connected
with my sabotaging the team?
Jane, you have more than once voiced your
doubts about what it is we have to do,
and let's be frank; on several occasions
you've deliberately disobey my orders.
Yeah, but during those attacks,
I was in as much danger as you and Connor.
You think I'm trying to take myself out?
We believe that Joseph's energy
affected you or your mind in such a way...
that your doubts began
to manifest themselves...
and they started to work against the team.
You don't believe this.
Jane,
your current genetic profile is something
that we don't fully understand.
you heal rapidly,
you IQ is increasing steadily,
there's really no saying
what you're capable of.
Even trying to undermine my own team?
There's something else.
Joseph Grace has tested Neuro positive.
How is that possible?
- Seth told me that...
- When Seth ran the first test,
-  ...you were in proximity.
- First test?
We tested again
with a sample that Connor acquired.
And with you out of the picture,
he tested positive.
So, wait a minute,
you're telling me that...
somehow I was able to wield
the sample I brought you to change?
- I don't believe that.
- No, I didn't think you would.
Jane, I have told no one else...
about your condition,
no one outside this team.
- Thank you, your point?
- I made a mistake.
I don't blame you,
but it's clear you've become a liability.
Now, I would prefer
not to have to restrain you.
Convincing enough for you?
Seth seems fairly certain that
once you stop seen Grace,
you'll recover from whatever it is
that happened to you.
I'll heal from the healer.
We need to eliminate the source.
Whatever Joseph effect has been on me
he didn't do this. I did.
All he's ever done is try to help people.
Jane, that is a voice inside your head
trying to justify why a part of you...
interfere with this. Joseph is a Neuro.
You have first hand experience of how
his healing can have disastrous results.
Yeah, on someone like me.
We have to chip him.
All right, then let me do it.
It's unnecessary.
No, I have to overcome this.
Let's get it over with then.
When you phoned it sounded important.
Are you all right?
I think it's time you learned
about my work.
For some unknown reason,
a neurological aberration has
appeared in our population.
This aberration allow people
to make things happen.
Some of these things are pretty fantastic.
while other are very dangerous.
I've seen people make
others jump off buildings.
Or start fires, by will alone.
Even raise people from the dead.
Good Lord.
We call these people Neuros.
My job is to go and find these Neuros...
and implant them with a chip that...
neutralizes their abilities.
Joseph, you're a Neuro.
My gift is God given.
Whatever form it takes, who are you
or anybody else to take it away?
The diseases that you heal are God given.
We might not be meant
to tamper with any of it.
If I run?
I don't think you will.
Will it hurt?
I don't know.
Come on, this way buddy.
Good news.
The cellular anomalies caused by Joseph
healing appear to have cleared up.
Great.
So, I'm back to my
normal, abnormal self.
I wonder if you'll ever
find a cure for that.
Is that why you were going to see Joseph?
You said that the anomalies
had cleared up.
Does that that me that, whatever it was,
that last entrapment inside of me
has cleared up too?
You want the truth?
Probably not.
I'll catch you later, doc.
Yes, Sir. Right away.
That was Morgan!
We're all getting raises.
That was Morgan and we have a problem.
- Another one?
- Do they ever end?
You know anything about this?
When it comes to Morgan's business,
I don't want to know.
Have been receiving Intel that we may
have problems at the internment zone.
NICO is 5000 miles away.
How does that concern my team?
If my information is reliable,
somewhere keep people at NICO
may have been compromised.
The only physician in my team is Seth.
I can't imagine...
While the problem may extend
to the medical staff,
our primary concern
is security and administration.
You can't be sure who if any
of the locals can be trusted.
I'll keep you informed as our
intelligence develops but for now...
this is strictly need to know.
Is not to go beyond us.
Someone once said
we are our own worst enemy.
Their job probably didn't involve
going against neurological aberrant,
but after these past few days...
I just may have to agree with them.
Is bad enough dealing
with your own inner turmoil,
if that manifested itself
in the physical plane...
I can't even imagine what
this world would look like.
Transcript and synch
by subXpacio and TusSeries