±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
¡¶àºçòğöµü¡· µúîå¼¾µú1¼¯
-=Ææàãğü×öä»×é=-
·­òë:
ğ£¶ô:
ê±¼äöá£ºêø»¤ììê¹
lucas: sometimes,it feels like it was yesterday -
graduating high school, saying goodbye.
that feeling that you get at 17 or 18
that nobody in the history of the world
has ever been this close,
has ever loved this fiercely
or laughed as hard
or cared as much.
Okay. We're not gonna do this.
We're not gonna get sad. Nothing's gonna change now.
We'll all be friends forever.
I know it.
Look,in four years, we're gonna be right back here.
You know,done with college or wherever we go.
Right?
Yeah.
sometimes,it feels like it was yesterday.
and sometimes,
it feels like someone else's memory.
Four years later
Nathan: where did he get the hoop?
His uncle lucas gave it to him.
I don't want him playing.
Nathan,he's 4 years old. All he wants to do is be like his dad.
Why don't you go out there and show him -
I said i don't want him playing.
Jamie,come on,sweetie. Mama's got to go to work.
Good morning,clothes over bro's. Please hold.
Can you call prime and make a dinner reservation,please?
Make sure i get the table in the wine room.
Any night next week will do.
Um,you're booked every night next week.
Okay,then the week after. This looks great.
Can we make this about a quarter-Inch wider? Great.
And we've got to send something funny with a card
To conan o'brien.
Cheese. He likes cheese.
You want me to send conan o'brien cheese?
Manchego. No,send gouda.
Gouda's a funnier cheese, and don't forget to remind me
About the conference call with macy's.
Guys.
Absolutely not.
There is no way she gets on the cover of my magazine
Unless she gains 10 pounds, minimum.
She looks unhealthy.
We were just brainstorming.
Brainstorm better. Anorexia is a disease.
It is not a fashion statement.
What do i smell?
Um,it's your coffee. Mocha double latte,extra foam.
Is there foam? Last time there was no foam. I like foam.
Extra foam.
Okay. What time is the premiere?
8:00, red carpet at 6:00.
I'm gonna do the red carpet and then skip the movie.
Let's call one of the nicks
And find out if they'd like to go.
Okay, which knick do you prefer?
There's stephon marbury, jamal crawford...
Oh,david lee is really cute.
Not the new york knicks, you goof.
The nicks - Nick lachey, nick zano,nick reid.
Whoever.
And tell victoria to wait for me in the limo.
She's not gonna like that.
Well,she works for me.
Oh,i must have the wrong office.
No,that's me - John knight,label president.
Last i knew, you were peyton sawyer,
Assistant to the assistant of the label president,
And your desk was - Where is your desk?
I'm sorry,i was just arranging your trades
And delivering the online download report,
Updating your call sheet, and admiring your view.
Also,mr. Knight,i have a couple unsigned bands
That i would really love for you to hear.
Peyton,i'm losing my hair, i'm hung over,
I have two different alimony payments due
And seven lines ringing.
Of course.
Sawyer?
Yes.
You look good.
Drop a button on that top and i'll let you sit in
On the morning new-Music session.
One button, one song.
And get me some aspirin.
Man,they do grow up fast.
Uncle lucas!
J. Luke!
Hey.
You in high school already?
No,i'm only 4.
Hmm,4 going on 40.
What you drawing?
You can't see it. It's not done.
Yeah,trust me, i understand that one.
I take it the writing's not going l?
The writing... is not going at all.
How about you? How was the last day of student teaching?
Great.
Trying not to freak out about next week when it's just me.
You're gonna be great, hales.
Did you get a nanny yet?
No,not yet.
Well,you know,you can't babysit him forever,hales.
And by him,i mean nathan, not jamie.
Well,it's only been four months,so...
announcer: seattle is on the clock right now.
we'll get to the commissioner coming up
in regards to their pick.
they going big? They going small?
it's been unpredictable so far.
here's the commissioner.
man: with the 10th pick in the nba draft,
the seattle sonics select...
We're moving to seattle, mama!
It's gonna be seattle.
My agent just called. He said we got a guarantee -
I'm going 10th pick to the sonics!
Oh,baby, i'm so proud of you!
You have worked so hard for the last four years!
You believed in it,and now it's actually happening!
Why are we buying a house in tree hill
If we're moving to seattle?
We should buy a house there.
Oh,we're going to. A big one.
With a pool?
More like a moat and a drawbridge.
And a dragon?
Yes,and a pet dragon for jim-Jam.
Hales,we're gonna have all kinds of houses,
But tree hill is home.
And,besides, this isn't even my salary.
This is just shoe-Contract money.
It's money from the shoe,mama! Let's get it!
Oh,baby,i don't know.
The little man's spoken.
And he's right. We should get the house,hales.
You know why? Why?
Because we did it together. We made it happen.
And we're gonna have to get used to the fact
That this is what life's like when your dreams come true.
The tar heels land another blue chip prospect,
And we've got the scoop.
I'm marvin mcfadden -
Junk: pass it,pass it,pass it! Pass the ball!
Yeah,he is. He's passing it to my guy.
Can you guys keep it down? I'm working on my demo.
For what? A job.
I'm gonna send audition tapes to all the local stations.
Sorry,mouth. Go ahead,man,do your thing.
The tar heels land another blue chip prospect,
And we've got the scoop.
I'm marvin mcfadden -
No,no,no,no,no,no!
That's how you go down the lane!
Sorry. Sorry.
The tar heels land another blue chip prospect,
And we've got the scoop.
Pizza!
I'll pause it.
Junk and fergie play video games,drink beer,
And eat pizza.
I'm mouth mcfadden, and i'm still unemployed.
So,six months ago when they asked us to fix this mess,
What the hell were we thinking saying yes?
Well,well,well, if it isn't skills taylor,
New assistant head coach of the tree hill raiders.
Hey, if you could afford me...
So,how great is this,huh?
Lucas scott,head coach. Local boy makes good.
Local boys made good.
You're a big part of this, skills.
I hope so. Man,we blew this place up.
Hey,how many games they won
Since we hung that state championship banner?
Not many.
But i do know one thing - Losing's over.
Oh,no doubt.
She's got a hit tv show.
Great potential for crossover marketing and promo.
But the songs are terrible.
John,she's young, she's hot,
And her social life's a train wreck.
We could ship this thing platinum.
Um,i have a band.
Well,why not? It can't get any worse.
Okay,well,they're called low versus diamond,
And they've already built a strong internet following,
And the songs are great.
We'll go with the actress.
All right?
Why don't you go get us some lunch menus?
Ladies and gentlemen, the n.S. 23.
Let's see it. Barry,thank you so much.
Seattle's gonna be drafting a hell of a player,nate.
Baby,it's awesome. I have to go relieve the sitter.
But you guys should stay and celebrate.
It's the night before the draft.
You sure? Yeah.
Thank you guys!
Hey,no driving tonight, okay?
Take the limo and get the car tomorrow.
I promise. Okay.
Hook it up.
Check it out.
Lucas: "and like the river court signatures
"Of their younger selves, weathered now,faded.
So,too,were they."
"I...
...suck."
Tell me you are writing the best pages of your life.
Well,hi to you,too.
If not the best pages of your life,
At least a bunch of okay pages?
I've written a few sentences.
Uh-Huh.
And deleted them because they sucked.
Luke,this is serious.
I can't be your editor if i don't have anything to edit.
My butt is on the line here.
Tell me you have something, anything.
Uhh... lindsey?
Luke?
I don't know. You know, i think it's an earthquake.
Lucas scott!
Somebody needs to do something about the paparazzi.
They're totally out of control.
We pay them a lot of money to talk about the brand.
I hope you were nice. I was nice.
Nick, did you enjoy yourself?
I did. I thought the movie was -
Driver,can you pull over, please?
I'm sorry,darling. You were saying?
Nothing. I liked the movie.
Thank you very much,
And enjoy the rest of your evening.
Right. Okay.
I just - I just thought that maybe...
Yes,we know what you thought,nick.
You thought you'd have your way with my designer.
A little fondling, a little tongue-Kissing,
Something a little dirty but not too freaky.
Uh,no, i just thought that -
It's clothes over bro's, nick.
We want the tabloids to think that she's sleeping with you.
She's not actually sleeping with you. We're all set.
Call me!
Taxi!
You are unbelievably rude.
Well,it's been a long day. But tomorrow's even longer.
You have a 9:00 a.M. Interview about taking the company public.
I'll be there for the finer points.
You just need to look beautiful and talk about your passion
And your creativity and blah,blah,blah.
And i've made a change to the model lineup
Due to the additional scrutiny from the press.
Oh,but you forgot -
She's not on the list.
She's my friend.
She's not your friend.
She's an employee.
I'm not sure i'm comfortable with that.
Brooke,clothes over bro's is a multimillion dollar company.
Yeah.
A company that you've entrusted to me
To make executive decisions like these.
We have to cut her loose.
You're gonna fire her?
No,i'm not gonnfire her. You're gonna fire her.
It's your company,my dear. I just work here.
Hey,it's me.
It's not gonna work out for the fashion show.
No,it's actually not gonna work out at all.
I'm gonna have to let you go.
It's nothing personal. It's just business. I got to go.
Postcard for jamie scott!
Another one? Yeah,man.
Where are they now?
Well,aunt karen and cousin lily are in ireland.
Now,that's right across the irish sea from england.
You remember where england is?
The one with the clock!
You are a genius. Are you sure you're not my kid?
All right.
You think we'll ever see them again?
Oh,yeah,of course we will,man.
So,listen.
I'm gonna go talk to your dad, and then we'll go,okay?
Okay. All right.
Haley keeps the alcohol out of reach.
At least,she tries.
It's a little early, don't you think?
So,how's physical therapy going?
How's your second book coming?
Ouch.
So,you know,haley told me that the doctors say
You'll be up on your feet any day now.
Pretty lucky,nate.
Oh,yeah,that's me. Mr. Lucky.
I'm just saying you'll be back to normal in no time.
Luke,i'm never gonna play basketball again.
That's not exactly normal,okay?
Luke,damn it! Don't be a dick,all right?
You want it? Walk over here and get it.
Why don't i walk over there and kick your ass,huh?
Kicking. Kicking's good. Let's see it.
Give me that bottle right now,
Or dan's not gonna be the only scott to kill his brother.
James: ready,uncle lucas?
Real nice,nate.
Luke...
Come on,jamie. Let's go.
Bye,daddy.
Bye-Bye.
So,none of you guys know who ate my pizza?
Nah,man.
Amazing. So,my pizza just ate itself.
Hey,i was working on my audition reel.
Hey,that's good. 'Cause you owe me for the rent.
And you two knuckleheads owe me for a pizza.
There he is!
Big game james. Hey,yo,big game.
I got something for you.
Cool!
You want to try it on?
All right.
Put your arms through, and there we go.
It's perfect!
Let's see what you got, baller.
Darn it,uncle skills, you always do that.
You ever gonna let him score?
Shorty shouldn't be in the paint. He got to learn.
Dude,he's 4.
What do you think, sawyer?
I think you were right about the act we signed today.
Her songs blow. So why'd you sign her?
How long have you been in los angeles,peyton? From...
From tree hill,north carolina. Four years.
Four years. Why'd you come?
I wanted to discover
And sign bands that could change someone's life,
Like the bands that changed mine.
I figured you were one of them.
I used to be,too.
Then i figured it out.
it's called show business for a reason.
We're here to make money.
Even if the product sucks.
Especially if the product sucks.
I hate to be the one to break it to you,
But rock 'n' roll can't actually save the world.
See,i disagree.
Walk into any club on the strip tonight
And just look at the kids, look into their eyes.
They're all looking for something to believe in.
I think that music can be the thing that changes their world.
That is why you are still the assistant to the assistant.
They're not out there to get their world saved.
They had a bad day.
They went out to get drunk and get laid.
Peyton,you're as smart and as talented
As anyone at the label,but you'd be so much further along
If you could just accept the business side of what we do
And play the game.
I'm just not really interested in playing the game.
You already did.
You dropped a button to get into that meeting.
Drop a few more,they'll probably give you my job.
Well,i will have your job one day,john.
Just not that way.
Have fun in the clubs tonight,
Assistant to the assistant.
substitution for the clippers. J. Luke.
Down by 2,and it looks like they're bringing in a rookie.
Clock running down, time for one last play.
All right,jamie, this is what we're gonna do.
When i tell you,i want you to hit the green button. Okay?
Don't do it,jamie. Pass it to your pal junk.
Kid's got the ball clock running down.
Jamie, i'll give you ice cream.
Shoot it!
No,no,no,no,no!
Oh!Oh! Oh!Oh!
That's it, you lost the ice cream.
Oh,oh,oh,oh,oh!
Jamie! Oh,oh,oh!
Hi, upside-Down boy.
Hey,mama! We won!
Oh,wow. We were just...
Oh! Here you go.
What are you wearing?
Uncle skills gave it to me.
Well,wasn't that nice of him, making you look all krunk.
Did you say thank you?
Mm-Hmm.
Uh-Huh.
Okay,go say goodbye to the guys.
So,look,i kind of gave nathan some grief today
About not being on his feet yet.
Oh,well,you know,i know he's a little dark right now.
You got to push him, hales.
????
Okay,mom,i'm ready.
Okay.
Whoa, what about me,jamie?
Bye,uncle lucas.
Oh,bye,buddy. I love you.
I got to go home now, and anyway,
You should be writing.
I don't want to hear it.
So,we caught up with brooke davis,
Young,hot designer of clothes over bro's.
Now,brooke, let me ask you this.
Do you ever miss just being young?
I am young.
But acting young.
Not being the boss of this huge corporation,
But being brooke davis, 21-Year-Old girl?
Sure,i miss it.
Thank you. We have to move on.
Clothes over bro's is my dream come true.
This is what i wished for.
Oh,baby...
Why don't you go upstairs? I'll be up in a minute,okay?
I can't.
We can't be like this,nathan.
Your son needs you.
Please don't become your father.
Nathan: my father is in prison.
So am i.
Well, you can walk out.
Lucas on recording: chapter three.
Peyton sawyer is destined for greatness.
Actually,she's already great,
Because peyton sawyer has a thing called integrity,
And nothing or no one is ever going to change that.
I remember the first time i met her.
you have 47 messages.
all messages deleted.
Hi. It's peyton.
Yeah,i'm sorry. I know it's late there,i just -
What happened to us, you know?
I don't know who i am anymore.
Or how i got here.
I miss who i used to be.
I want to have a home again, you know?
And real friends.
You know,
The kind of friendships we used to believe in.
I miss that.
And i miss you.
I guess i just miss all of it.
No,i have the uncorrected proofs.
I need the corrected ones.
Okay,i have to go.
Thanks. Bye.
Hi.
Look,before you start yelling at me,i'm sorry.
I know i've missed my deadline again,
And i know you have a lot of people to answer to,
And it's not fair to you.
I remember the first time i read it.
I was a junior editor, just out of college,
Missing my friends.
I took two dozen manuscripts home for the weekend,
Just like i did every weekend, hoping that this time,
Something would speak to me.
And it did.
It was a great first novel,luke.
It brought you to me.
But a writer's career is about a body of work.
It's about the second book and the third and the fourth.
Lindsey -
It's been two years.
And that wouldn't scare me if i thought you were writing,
But you're not.
So what am i supposed to do,luke?
Well,you could give me a little bit more time
Because i'm handsome.
Close the door,luke.
Not being the boss of this huge corporation
But being brooke davis, 21-Year-Old girl.
That is not the face of a happy girl
Who got everything she wished for.
A lot of things, but not everything.
Well,are you counting the trip to milan?
The trip for work. Come on.
Let's see the face of a girl who gets to go to italy tomorrow
To approve the textiles for her fall line.
But it's not everything.
no,dear. It is everything.
And if you've lost sight of that,
You have lost your way, brooke davis.
Milan,tomorrow.
Smile.
Okay. Let's do lunch.
Sawyer!
What's the name of that sushi place i like?
You were wrong yesterday
When you said the kids in the clubs
Were just there for decadence.
I think it's more like romance and hope and inspiration
And that feeling that you get
When other human beings pick up basic instruments
And make sense of your world.
And the day that i think it's just about making money
Is gonna be the day
That i've betrayed everything i believe in about music
And life and myself.
Was that a sushi place?
I quit,john. I'm going home.
You're making a mistake.
No. I'm fixing one.
I think you drink too much.
I think you're right.
Haley: jamie,come on.
Hey,come on.
Okay,your boarding pass and itinerary are in your bag.
The car service will pick you up in milan.
If you have any problems, i gave you my home,cell,
And parents' house number.
Millicent,you are a great assistant,okay?
Try and have some fun while i'm gone.
You're only young once.
announcer: seattle is on the court right now.
????
are they going big? They going small?
they've been unpredictable so far.
here's the commissioner.
man: with the 10th pick in the nba draft,
the seattle sonics select -
????
Hey. Hey,man. Uh,can i get an autograph?
Yeah,sure. Thanks.
Yeah,just write,uh,"to greg, portland's biggest fan.
Seattle sucks, and so do i."
Hmm.
"To greg...
"Enjoy losing to us next year.
Your pal,nathan scott."
There you go,buddy.
Whoa. You got a problem,man?
No,no,no. Walk away. You've got too much to lose here.
Come on,man. Let's see what you got!
You got too much to lose here, okay? It's not worth it.
That's it. Listen to your girlfriend.
Come on,nate. Wait.
Look,we shouldn't be driving, all right? I'll get the limo.
Come on,nate. We'll just grab barry,take the limo.
You're not driving.
All right. You're right.
Greg: i have witnesses. You all saw it.
He hit me. I'm gonna sue that punk.
Hey,man, i never touched you.
And if i'd have hit you, you'd be out cold right now.
Too late,seattle boy.
You should have left with that fat-Ass wife.
Oh,my god. Nate. Nate,you all right?
I can't feel my legs,man.
What? I can't feel my legs!
with the 10th pick in the nba draft...
Help!
Somebody help!
the seattle sonics select mouhamed sene from senegal.
Okay,it's time for bed. Come on.
Mama, why is daddy so sad?
Um,it's just a really tough time for daddy right now.
But,uh - But he loves you.
You know that,right?
Uncle lucas loves me.
Hi.
How long's it been?
Two years.
It's been longer than that.
God,luke,i missed you.
I have someone.
I'm with someone.
Postseason hardball, preseason hoops,
And regular season football.
I'm marvin mcfadden, and sports is coming up next.
Hi. It's peyton.
Yeah,i'm sorry. I know it's late there,i just -
What happened to us, you know?
I don't know who i am anymore.
Or how i got here.
Lindsey: hey,you.
Come to bed.
Hey.
Sorry about yesterday.
It's just,they only agreed to let me split time here
Because i promised them i'd get you back on track.
I know. It's okay.
I still love you.
I love you,too, lucas scott.
Peyton: i miss who i used to be.
I want to have a home again, you know?
I miss that.
I miss you.
Jamie.
Son...
Daddy's sorry, for everything.
Come here.
I guess i miss all of it.
Does any of that make any sense?
That makes all the sense in the world,peyton.
Four years ago,it all seemed so clear,didn't it?
Conquer the world, save the world,
Live happily ever after.
Are you happy,brooke?
Sometimes.
Not always. Are you?
No.
Okay. Then let me ask you something.
What is gonna make you happy,peyton?
Is it how you look or the car you drive
Or the people you know?
Is it money or celebrity or power or accomplishment?
Because i have all those things,
And - And i don't think it's enough.
Well,then,what is?
Love,i think.
And that love can be for a boy or a girl
Or a place or a way of life or even for a family.
But where you find it is up to you.
So where are you gonna find that love,peyton?
I think i need to go home.
I was hoping you'd say that.
I missed you, brooke davis.
I missed you, peyton sawyer.
We're home now. It's gonna be okay.
Come on.
ææàãğü×öä»×é
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
»¶ó­¼óèë