Previously on "one tree hill"...
I stripped naked,
And that boy didn't even flinch.
I'm sorry.
What did i do ?
What you didn't do is tell me
that ho bag got naked for you.
Oh, that.
You... couch.
You... fired.
Did you go home with that guy
last night ?
Yeah.
Nathan doesn't want us hanging out,
And i, uh, i have to respect that.
How'd you like
to stay the night tonight ?
Like old times.
That's up to you, isn't it ?
I'd been given only days to live.
That was 14 months ago.
I have a proposition for you.
Nathan's your son.
It could ruin him.
He's doing this
because he wants to bury nathan.
And the deeper nathan is buried,
The more money he'll have to
pay you to dig himself out.
Okay.
I'm in.
They're excited.
And i didn't even have to
pay them this time.
It's gonna be a big show.
Dan, you reached out to nathan,
and he hung up on you.
He was never gonna
forgive you, anyway.
Sometimes the truth is all we have.
Skills is gonna take jamie
for the day,
Just to keep him away from the tv.
Yeah.
You know, the first memory i have
Is sitting on my father's lap
holding a basketball.
He spent my entire life
trying to get me into the nba.
Now he's gonna take it away.
What are you looking at, goof ?
How you doing ?
Uh, you didn't tell me
that this show was live.
Oh, it's better this way.
Bigger audience, bigger ratings.
After today,
everyone will know your story.
I'm nervous.
Don't be.
Just speak from your heart,
and don't forget to smile.
You'll be fine.
Mr. Scott ?
Yeah ?
What happened
between you and nathan ?
I murdered his uncle...
Among other things.
I'll see you out there.
This should be the last of it.
I'm so sorry about all this.
It's fine.
No, it's not fine.
You've been amazing
about everything,
And it just...
I'm sorry.
I'll talk to him.
These aren't mine.
Awesome.
Are you coming to watch the show ?
No, i need to watch it here.
I told nate i'd call him after.
Okay.
See ya.
Drive safe.
Thanks.
Hey, clay ?
I hope everything turns out okay.
You and nathan
are both really great guys,
And you deserve better.
So do you, quinn.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
So, let's run down the list.
There's blondie from
the body-wash commercial.
She has a name, you know.
It's kylie.
Of course it is.
There's the actress who can...
be in your bed in 20 minutes.
Make it 30.
And there's this one,
Nathan's sister-in-law.
It's a little early for a beer,
isn't it ?
You know what i want ?
Grape kool-aid.
Stop it.
It's okay if you like her.
No, it's not.
Why not ?
Because she's somebody's wife.
So ? I was your wife.
Yeah.
But you left me.
Things change, clay.
She's beautiful...
And you like her.
She's not you.
Look, i have to watch
nathan's and my career
Possibly end
on this nightmare tv show.
You can go if you want.
No, don't be silly, babe.
I'm not going anywhere.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, here.
Thanks.
Oh, what is all this ?
David dropped off some of my stuff.
In the garage ?
Not exactly.
Look, hales, i thought
i'd just watch from my room,
You know, to give you and nathan
some space.
But i'm here if you need me.
I know, quinny.
Thank you.
Okay.
Nathan...
Hey, um, it's gonna start soon.
It's been a good life, huh ?
Yeah.
It's been a wonderful life.
You know, when this show is over,
It's still gonna be a wonderful life
Because i love you
and your son loves you,
And nothing that happens
in the next hour
Is gonna change that.
God, i needed to hear you say that.
Good.
I really needed to say it.
My guest tonight's
grown rather infamous
Over the last few weeks.
Her name is renee richardson,
And she's nearly 4 months pregnant.
And she claims that this nba player
Is the father of her unborn child.
That player happens to be my son.
They say that truth is the best
vindication against slander.
So what is the truth ?
Is she lying,
or am i about to become
a grandfather again ?
We'll meet her and hear her
story when we come back.
Believe nothing
just because a wise man said it
or you read it in a book
Or it's of divine origin
Or simply because
your mother told you.
It doesn't make it true.
Believe only what you yourself
can test and judge to be true.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Please welcome my guest,
renee richardson.
Here we go.
Hi, renee. Hi.
Thank you for having me.
She's pretty.
Crazy-looking as all hell,
but... pretty.
We're gonna talk
about a lot of things tonight,
But just to set the stage,
Can you tell us a little bit
about the night
Of the alleged affair,
the first time you met nathan ?
Um, we had been to a lot
of the same parties and clubs,
But we hadn't really
been introduced.
And that was, what,
nearly four months ago ?
Um, that's right.
Uh, i remember because it was
the night of the memphis game,
And nathan scored
his season high that night.
35 points, 11 assists,
and six boards ?
You killed it tonight !
Here is to your contract year
And to making my job
a hell of a lot easier.
Cheers.
Excuse me ?
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to bother you,
but could we get a picture ?
Absolutely.
Just give us one second.
Dude, having you around
is so much better than a puppy.
But seriously...
I'm proud of you,
And i love you,
and you absolutely deserve this.
Oh, yeah, that's the one.
All right, let's do this.
Nathan scott, the girls.
The girls, nathan scott.
Hi. Nathan.
Nice to meet you.
How you doing ?
Nathan.
All right.
Mmm.
Somebody smells good.
That's the rainstorm body spray.
All right, let's make it look sexy.
And on the count of 2.
1... 2.
We were really hammered that night.
It was the longest road trip
of the year.
You were lonely.
I'm always lonely.
On the count of 2.
Whoo !
That's a long way down.
Thanks.
That really helps me right now.
Sorry, i'm... i'm just not
a huge fan of heights.
Yeah...
You know, beer bongs i can do.
I think they are
a beautiful college tradition.
Streaking through the quad...
that's another one.
Well, i could do that.
Yeah ?
Man, did i pick the wrong school.
I'm clay.
Hi. I'm sara.
How about we do this together ?
On the count of 2.
Wait !
On the count of 2 ?
Nobody goes on the count of 2.
Yeah, i know.
I'll be our thing...
Something we can tell
the grandkids about.
Well, i'm gonna tell them
about streaking on the quad.
Yeah, nobody wants to hear that
from their grandparents.
Actually, i take that back.
Everyone would love hearing
that from their grandparents.
Attagirl. You ready ?
You okay ?
On 2.
1...
2.
See ?
How badass were you ?
Tell that to the grandkids.
Let's back up a little bit
to when you were younger.
We did our research
and found out you were once...
A cheerleader...
Uh, yes.
... and a homecoming queen...
And, more recently,
a hostess in a club.
Uh, yes, but there was no nudity
or anything.
I understand.
My wife was a stripper...
a little nudity.
Have you ever been married ?
No.
But you knew nathan was married.
I-i felt bad about it.
I mean, obviously,
i-i wish that he wasn't,
But... i was attracted to him.
And attraction is not a choice.
It just is.
Have you ever been in love, renee ?
Yes.
It feels good, doesn't it ?
Falling in love is the easiest
thing you're ever gonna do.
It's the most exciting thing.
It's the most powerful thing.
That's why falling out of love
hurts like hell.
But falling in love...
there's nothing better.
It's the best it ever gets.
Mm.
Did i ever tell you
how amazing you are ?
You're amazing...
and beautiful...
And talented.
And one of these days,
i'm gonna get you a real darkroom,
Not just some cramped
apartment bathroom.
Stop. Come here.
Look at this.
Look how happy you are.
I don't need a big darkroom.
I just need you
to always be that happy,
'cause you deserve that.
How'd i get so lucky with you ?
Technically, you haven't
gotten lucky just yet.
But i think you're about to.
We got to get a bigger darkroom.
And then you kissed.
Yes.
And the kissing escalated.
When we come back,
We're gonna talk a little
about love and loss
And how we're sometimes
our own worst enemies.
And then we're gonna find out
if renee is telling the truth,
After this.
You awake ?
Depends.
Good news or bad news ?
That video position came up
at work again.
And i took it.
David, why ?
Because i'm tired of being poor.
We're not poor.
We're frugal.
Mrs. Padilla said she's been
driving you to work.
It's just sometimes the car
won't start.
How do you get home ?
I catch a ride or i walk.
Quinn.
I like walking.
Baby, what about your documentary ?
I stopped at the library
and got the grant forms.
It's what we've talked about.
It's what you've always wanted.
And i'll still want it
a year from now.
But this is good money, quinn.
I want to get you a house...
And that darkroom.
I don't need those things.
I need you to be happy and inspired.
Well, this will make me happy.
And you'll keep me inspired.
Please ?
Say it's okay ?
Say, "okay." Okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay.
Promise me
you'll fill out the forms.
Of course. And if something comes up,
then, that you'll take it.
Of course, of course,
of course, of course.
I promise.
Okay.
I love you, you know that ?
I love you, too.
Falling in love is easy.
But a lifetime of love...
now, there's a miracle.
You know i love you.
And you know i fired alex,
But you're still working with her.
I like her script, brooke.
You like her script
or you like her ?
Relationships aren't always easy.
I should know.
I'm on my second marriage.
Yep.
How many of you are divorced ?
Divorce doesn't just happen.
And relationships
don't just end in an instant.
What'd you do with your ring,
anyway ?
Your wedding band.
Where is it ?
I don't know.
You don't know,
or you don't want to remember ?
Hey, sara...
What do you think ?
I think you look like a boy
playing dress-up.
Come on.
This is my shot.
I got to get in the mailroom,
i become an assistant,
They make me junior agent,
And i'm in.
And you're in.
Help.
The person interviewing you...
it's a woman, right ?
Yeah.
Jeans and a button-up shirt,
and go heavy on the boyish grin.
You sure ?
Hey, it got you me, didn't it ?
You don't think
that will be too casual ?
Here.
Married says mature,
stable, and dependable...
Everything they'll want to see
in a future agent.
Only i'm not married.
Then marry me, you knucklehead.
Yes.
Yes !
Well, there's that boyish grin !
We all want to be loved,
to be happy.
So why aren't we ?
Because we've become experts
At sabotaging our own happiness...
... feeling like victims,
when, in fact,
It's the choices we make.
The bad habits, the vices,
The inability to show love
and compassion...
These are the things
that tear us down.
We're not...
Victims.
We're assassins when it comes
to love and happiness.
Renee is beautiful,
And she's smart,
and she wants love in her life,
And yet who did she choose
to sleep with ?
Allegedly.
A man who was unavailable to her.
Now, she may be telling the truth...
And she may deserve compensation,
But she is no victim.
Oh.
We applaud the sentiment,
but we don't change.
Why ?
Because we want what we want.
So we do it, we say it, try it,
And we victimize ourselves,
and we hire an attorney,
And it has to stop.
Renee...
You say nathan scott,
My son, is the father
of your unborn child, right ?
Yes.
I believe you.
I think you're telling the truth.
And more than that,
i'm going to prove it...
With the help of
this lie-detector machine...
... when we come back.
This is just...
This is unbelievable.
Two minutes, guys.
What is this about ?
What's what about, honey ?
No, i-i didn't agree to this.
Relax.
It's great television.
No, you don't... here's the thing...
If you're lying, science
will prove it eventually,
And if not, you have nothing
to worry about.
Don't forget to smile.
Nathan.
Do you believe this ?
Do you realize how ridiculous
this is ?
The guy shot his brother
at point-blank range,
And now he has a hit tv show.
He's rolling out some rigged-up
lie-detector machine,
And i have to sit 3,000 miles
away and just take it.
Screw him.
I mean it.
Let's not even watch
the rest of the show.
It's a nice day.
It's a nice life.
How can you be so strong ?
It's a question of character.
It's really about
who has better character.
Is it renee...
or nathan ?
And if you sign with me,
I promise you
that the energy and resources
That i'll dedicate to you
and your career
Will be unmatched.
Okay. I'm in !
Can i give you my two cents ? Sure.
This is all still about
that wide receiver, right ?
Yeah.
I think...
... you can do better.
Babe, this guy is a big deal.
I mean, he can change
everything for me.
But you said it yourself...
he's a bad guy.
And if i only represent good guys,
I may have no clients at all.
No, i don't believe that.
I don't think you do, either.
The guy is great, sara.
He's not great.
He's just a great player.
And the man i love
knows the difference.
That's what's gonna make you
a great agent.
You'll find players
that you can believe in
And clients that become friends.
You'll find someone
Who has integrity
and character and heart.
And that will change everything
for you.
And that's the man
i fell in love with.
I love you, you know that.
I know.
You really hurt my feelings
When you said
we weren't getting married.
When did i ever say anything
about marriage ?
When your dad came to town.
You said we weren't getting married
Like it was some sort of
completely ridiculous notion
To you.
No.
Brooke, i was venting.
It had nothing to do
With the actual concept
of marrying you.
I think about that all the time.
Really ?
Yeah.
Well, good, because that's what
i wrote in the sand.
That night you said you were gonna
take that movie in new zealand,
I-i wrote "marry me" in the sand,
And then i didn't tell you
Because you said you were leaving.
Surprise.
David ?
David.
What is this ?
Surprise.
I know this is a surprise,
But we have an expression
on this show...
Step into the light...
and get yourself right !
... and get yourself right.
During the break,
We hooked renee up
to a lie detector,
And here's how it works.
I'll ask renee a question,
and depending on her answer,
The words "true" or "lie"
Will appear on the screens
behind me.
For instance,
is your name renee richardson ?
Yes.
Excellent.
Let's begin.
Did you, in fact,
meet nathan scott at a party,
As you described earlier ?
Yes.
Did you flirt with nathan scott ?
Did nathan flirt back ?
You smell good.
That's my rainstorm body spray.
Yes.
Believe only what you yourself
test and judge to be true.
Renee, is nathan scott, my son,
The father of your unborn child ?
Yes.
Hey, it's Clay.
It's my third time calling, buddy.
Look, i'm watching the show
right now,
And i, um... i just want
to talk to you.
So, please call me back, all right ?
Hales ?
Nathan ?
Hey, david, do you know where...
Hey, babe.
Uh... what is this ?
Okay, okay, i-i know it's expensive,
But i just had a thought...
Screening room.
Okay.
I'm just saying...
I go to work, i come home,
i sit here...
I'm happy.
Remember that old car that we had...
And the futon ?
We were really happy then.
Yeah, that futon sucked, baby.
I love this picture of you.
Really ?
'cause that guy was struggling,
foolish, and broke.
That's not true.
Quinn...
... you've got some crazy,
romantic notion
of who i used to be,
of who we used to be.
We were just naive kids.
God forbid i ever go back to that.
Can you hand me
a phillips screwdriver ?
It's in the box over there.
Sure.
How great is this room, by the way ?
No windows.
It's perfect.
It's a really dark room.
Did you mean it when you proposed ?
I did that night.
But not anymore.
I don't know right now.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
I'm sorry i hurt your feelings.
Sometimes we fall short of
the people we are meant to be,
And sometimes people do things
they're ashamed of.
Thank you, renee.
And usually,
after the guilt sets in,
We make things worse.
My son, nathan scott, is a good man,
But sometimes people do funny things
In the face of pressure
and desperation.
And the truth...
Well, truth is an absolute,
And the truth can set you free.
My name is dan scott.
I love my wife, rachel.
What is he doing ?
My son, nathan, loves me.
I'm president of the united states.
I'm santa claus.
I didn't kill my brother.
Hey, you guys got to get in here !
Life is funny, isn't it ?
Sometimes bad things
happen to good people,
And it isn't fair.
This is a still frame
of the moment i told you
We were gonna do
the lie-detector test.
Your pupils are dilated.
Your eyebrows are arched.
It means you were surprised.
This is a still frame of the moment
After you said nathan
had slept with you
And the monitors said "true."
You were surprised again,
weren't you ?
Sometimes bad things happen
to good people.
I think you're a good person, renee.
I think something bad
happened to you,
And you were clever enough
to see a way out.
All right.
Mmm.
You smell good.
Oh, that's the rainstorm body spray.
All right.
Let's make it look sexy.
Okay... ooh, easy.
Not too sexy.
That'll cost us $20 million
next year.
On the count of 2.
1... 2.
I don't think you wanted to.
I think you were afraid...
and lost and desperate.
You knew nathan
was in a contract year,
And you knew he had
too much to drink that night.
Maybe someone lied to you,
Maybe someone took advantage
of you, or maybe...
Being a good person
just wasn't paying off.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I know.
But here's the good news.
You can stop it...
Right here, right now.
You wanted to get some money,
some security.
What's so little
to someone who has so much ?
And then you got angry,
and then the press got involved,
And then there was no turning back.
Renee...
We have a team of experts backstage
Who study body language
and heart-rate response
And all of it.
You were at that party that night,
And you had sex, didn't you ?
And you got pregnant.
But you didn't have sex
with nathan scott,
and you never had sex
with nathan scott, did you ?
No.
Well, what do you know ?
Character changes everything.
It's okay.
It's over now.
It's over.
Thanks.
He says she's dropping everything.
I'm so sorry
you had to go through this.
I shouldn't have been drunk
at that party, haley.
I just...
You...
You're still young.
We both are.
I think...
I think we just forget
that sometimes.
What are you listening to ?
You know.
I never changed it.
Play it.
I can't.
For me ?
I love this song.
You look beautiful.
Well, thank you, handsome.
Dance with me.
You know what i want ?
What ?
Grape kool-aid.
You know what i hate ?
I hate these pens.
It's either way too much fluid
Or not nearly enough,
But it's never the right amount.
And they cost, like, a fortune.
What are you looking at, you goof ?
Sara, hey.
Hey, sara ! Hey !
Sometimes i can't see you anymore.
I forget things about you,
And i'm afraid that i'm losing us.
Like the way you smelled and, uh...
The sound of your voice
and how you felt in my arms,
And, um...
If you let someone in,
you'll erase me.
You won't.
I can't.
Open the door, clay.
Clay...
It's okay.
On the count of 2.
1... 2.
I think you need to go home.
Oh, okay. I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was a bad time.
To david.
I think you should go home to david.
And i'm sorry, too.
I love you so much,
my beautiful wife.
"A team of experts backstage" ?
Nice touch.
So how'd you know she was lying ?
He's still my son.
I raised him.
I know what kind of man he is.
Besides...
Takes a con to know a con.
It was a good show.
I love you.
Yeah.
You okay ?
No.
I need to know that you feel
the same way that i do,
That you can... see yourself
doing this with me forever,
Because if not, what am i doing ?
What... what are we doing ?
What...
Hey.
Who are we ?
Hey. Look at me.
We're us, brooke.
You're the girl i love
with all my heart,
And i'm the boy who's gonna be
with you forever.
We don't have to rush into anything.
Forever is a very long time.
It's not fair.
We were supposed to have more time.
And you still do.
I don't want you to be alone, honey.
You like her... quinn.
Why'd you send her away ?
I don't want to lose us.
No, you can't erase who we were
or what we had.
No one can.
We burned so bright together.
You won't lose that.
I loved you so much, sara.
You were perfect with me...
And you always will be.
But now it's time to let go.
It's okay, honey.
I love you.