Previously on one tree hill
???
?????
??????
We'll stop her heart,
and then i'll do the repairs.
It's not me that has to make
a decision about lucas.
It's you.
Go home and read his book.
Young man: so we're all
just gonna shoot 3s, coach?
Yeah, for the most part.
Who's gonna
get us the ball?
Me.
I need to fix it.
I need to fix all of it --
You, us.
I need that peace
before i die.
Let me help you with what little
time i have left.
Don't deny a dying man
his last wish.
I can never forgive you --
Not now, not ever.
???
??????
Out of bout
warrior ball.
What?!
You're kidding me.
On the street, that's assault.
You're not even gonna call
that a foul in fere?
Brooke.
Hey, mom? Oh!
Man: hi, i'm calling
from dr. Copeland's officefor brook bravis.
Brook, it's urgent
that you call us --
Hello? Uh-Huh.
Yeah, no, sure, just --
Brooke!
It's angie's surgery!
Okay, tell me again why angie's
surgery is so last-Minute.
'Cause it's all done
on a volunteer basis.
E surgeons
donate their services,
So it depends on
when they have an opening
And the right medica
and everything.
I just didn't think
it was gonna be today.
Well, what can i do?
You're doing it.
Thank you.
But would you mind
calling lucas for me?
He's justten
so attached to angie,
And i think
he's gonna want to know.
Yeah. Sure. I'll be back.
Okay.
Hey, come on.
Lucas: hey, coach.
Hey.
Uh, thanks for the coffee.
What's up, man?
Uh, you know, i was thinking
maybe we could go over tonight's game plan one more time.
Look, it's gonna work,
bro.
N't, they'll just fire the head coach
and hire me, right?
Win-Win.
So, what else
is bothering you?
Nothing. Why?
'Cause you got that "something
else is bothering me" look.
Come on, keep it real.
Ta to your boy.
Nothing just --
I haven't heard from lindsey
in a while,hi
You know, maybe a week,
and i --
I mean, it's one thing for her
to give me the key back, but...
I mean, she's still editing my book.
I think she's ducking me.
Nah, she's ain't ducking you,
bro.
She's probably just busy.
Yeah.
I just wish she'd call,
you know?
It'll be okay,
But until then,
you know what heals a broken heart more than anything?
Hmm?
Bacon.
Smell that?
Thank god for millicent.
Come on, man.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
A dad who's gonna leave
without you
donif drag
y boneout of bed.
No, it's okay.
I'm ready.
I can see that.
????
Knk, knock. K
Who's there?
Ya.
Ya, who?
Yahoo! There's a ravens game
met.
????
Okay, i just
got to get my cape.
Brooke.
Hi.
Big day huh
How yoholding up?
Nervous.
Please tell me you're not --
You're not nervous.
She's gonna do great,
okay?
So are you.
Dr. Copeland,
we're all set
Okay, this is gonna take
a little while,
But as soon as i'm done, i will
come out and let you know, okay?
Okay.
Nurse lee is gonna
take angie now.
Okay.
Hey. Hey, sweet girl.
The nice nurse is gonna take you
for your surgery now, okay?
But nothing isonna happen
to you. I promise, okay?
They're just gonna take you
and make you better.
You're gna be better,ok?
Dr. Copeland.
What's your name?
Your first name?
Just try to relax, brooke, okay?
She's in good hands.
Okay.
How you doing, dad?
Hanging in there.
Good'cause it feel i
we kind of slowed down.D
Nah, we're good.
Maybe we should turn around
and go back.
Why? You don't think i can
make it up this hill?
I'm not supposed to lie,
right?
Watch your old man work.
Come on dad!
You do it! Mush!T!
We made it halfway up.
Well, almost halfway.
I don't know, james.
I've got a long way to go
if i'm ever gonna play basketball again.
I keep trying to do the things
i used to do,
And my body's just telling me
i can't.
I think you can.
Thanks, buddy.
You want to borrow
my cape?
Yeah, you know what
i think i might need tt.
All right, thank you.
U know welse
i'm gonna need?
That scooter!
Hey!
You get back ere.
How long's it been?
About an hour.
T
last time i aske
I know, honey.
You asked like 30 seconds ago.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Hey, i know you're nervous.
She's gonna be fine.
Yeah.
You should get going
Mnh-Mnh. I'm good.
Peyton, i know you have
a big day today.
Okay. Well, then, tomorrow
will just be a bigger day.
I don't even know
his first name.
Dr. Copeland.
I hope it's something nice --
Not like a last name
for a first name...
You know, like "monroe"...
or "madison."
Lucas.
Yeah, really.
No, i mean lucas is here.
Oh.
Brooso sry. S
I left my cellphone at home.
How's she doing?
I don't know. They -- They said
it was gonna take a while
And that they'd let me know as
soon as she was out of sur
Okay, well, then, uh...
I'll just wait here with you
if that's okay.
Yeah, thanks.
I'd like that...
Considering peyton
has to go.
Brooke, i --
P.Sawyer,
I love y,
But i know your day's insane, and...
I will feel better if at least one of us
getting shing donebesides iting, so...
Please? For me
All right, you cme
rst thing.
I will.
Thank you.
Bye, peyton.
Bye, luke.
Over the next couple
of months,
You're gonna
start to feel sluggish.
It's important
not to push it.
There is some good news,
though.
What? I've got seven months
to live instead of six?
Use  your physical size
and bloo
You're number two
on the donor recipient list
for a compatible heart.
Y this pager with youyo24 hours24ay.
If a heart
becomes available,
We'll have about six hours
tolace it.
Number two, huh?
What's it gonna cost for me
to get to number one?
Well, i'm pretty certain
reverend carter
isn't willint  barter
with his life.
He's in pretty bad shape.
Good man, too.
Good man?
What's that supposed to mean --
"Good man"?
We're not allowed
to discriminate
when it comes to saving lives, dan.
If the hifs, my job is to
place it into whoever needs it.
Oh, i see.
It doesn't matter if they're
miracle workers or murderers.
Hey, sorry.
It's okay.
How's brooke?
Um, scared to death
but trying to be brave.
I feel like i should
go by and see her.
??? I already told you,
You are underict orders
not to go anywhere
Until you have recorded
at least one song.
All right, fine.
??????
Maybe i just
don't like peyton.
Oh, damn.
Was that talkback on again?
You want to take care of that
for me, baller?
Grandma -- Uh, i mean,
nanny deb will do it.
Dude, nanny deb
is not your maid.
Actually,
she kind of is.
??????
Recycling --
Now, you little knucklehead.
This is so great, you guys.
Look at you go, peyton.
Me? Look at you .
You've sold nearly
100,000 copies, dude.
Well, hey, man, that's you and haley
and that creepy label guy from l.A.
That you have some sort of weird
sexual tension with.
Ew. No, i don't.
You kind of do.
What about you, rock star?
You got any flings we can scold you about
whilsecretly wanting to hear more?
No, u know how it is,
hay.Haley.
It's a dferent city every
night and press in the morning.
I can't even imagine
having a date,
Let alone
an actual relationship.
Uh, well, you have
plenty of time for boys.
You are, what,
like 18 years old?
Oh, speaking of -- Do you want
to do a psa for rock the vote?
Hell, yes.
That's so cool.
All right, cool.
We'll set it up.
Come here
?????
You, too.
You coming, haley?
Yeah, i'll --
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Oh, you naughty man.
Hey, mom. Oh!
Damn it, mom!
Doesn't anyone
knock around here?
Geez.
Geez, mom, what if jamie
had walked in?
I thought the door
was locked.
Besides, you said
you were going for a run.
Well, jamie got tired.
Okay, fine, i got tired,
but that's not the point, mom.
What were you doing?
I met someone online.
Ugh. Who?
I don't know exactly.
We've never seen each other.
Well, he's s
parts of me, but --
Stop, okay?
Mom, you're chatting with some
stranger on the internet.
He's very romantic.
He's sensual.
We're arranging to meet soon.
Come on, mom.
This is just weird.
What is so weird about it?
You don't think it's weird
that you're hiding in my spare bedroom flashing some webcam?
I wasn't hiding.
Besides, all those times
you locked yourself in the
bathroom when you were 12?
Okay, stop.
I knew what yowere doing.
Mom.
You were in there
all the time.
Where is jamie, anyway?
I don't know.
I guess i lost track of him
when you blinded me.
Ugh. Jamie!
Jamie
James lucas scott,
what are you doing out on the street alone?
I never told her
i love her.
I just...
I never said it.
Look, i'm sure when angie's
in your arms, she knows it.
Most of time,
Love doesn't really need words,
you know?
Yeah.
So, um, what's going on
with y and owen?
Nothing, apparently.
What's going on
with you and lindsey?
Nothing, apparently.
I don't know.We...
Haven't spoken
for over a wk.
She hasn't
returned my calls.
That sucks, luke.
I'm sorri'
You should get out of here.
You've got that game tonight.
I'm okay
for a little while longer.
Okay.
I'll go get us
some coffees.
She'll be in touch.
Lindsey.
I wouldn't read
too much into it.
Yeah.
I'm okay
for a little while longer.
I'm sorry that i didn't mail
your card to your grandfather.
I was just tings
to protect you, buddy.
God.
You might be mad
at me for that,
Or you might not
understand i but...
Dan is a bad person.
I'm sorry, buddy.
I just wanted him to know
that he still had a friend.
Everyone
should have a friend.
That big cloud
oks like a sheep dog.
I kindooks
like cotton candy.
You shouldu e
toama.
I know, buddy.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
I promise i will try to explain things better
from now on? Okay.
Ok
Love you, son.
I know.
I love you, too.
Brooke...
...the opetion went verysmoothly. Angie
He gonna be okay?
She's in recovery now. We are assisting her breathing,
but she's stable,
And all indications are
she's gonna be just fine.
Thank you.
Brooke?
She's gonna  okay.
Dr. Copeland...
Thank you for fixing her.
Welcome.
You too.
This year was a year
of firsts for me --
First tour bus,
first single on the radio,
And the first time
that i got to vote,
And that pretty much rocked.
People tel
that my voice is a gift.
Well, so is yours
So use it, let it be heard,
and rock the vote
You were perfect.
And, by the way,
great album.
Thanks
thanks, guys
So, ng otour buses,
it with  --
The starburst thursday night
concert series.
The starthrst thursday n
cories,
Which is what?
Which is a summer tour
at six flags. It's cool.
They've got a lot of really good
ed --
I love starburst,
and i love roller coasters.
Exactly.
It is very you.
Unds awesome.
What color you want?
Orange.
Hey millicent
What
Yeah, no,
i'll be right there.
Haley, don't do it!
You've got too much to live for!
Dude, millicent calls
Says you're depressed-Looking,
you're headed to the roof.
I get all freaked out.
What's going on, foxy?
I found my 5-Year-Old son
walking alone on the st today.
You know why?
'Cause i lied to him.
I'm worried i'm wasting your
time with this record, peyton.
No, haley,
the record's gonna be great.
Well, i hope so,
but what about after that?
Mia said that her life
is so nomadic
That she can't eveag'te
having a
Let alone
a serious relationship.
I have a husband and a son
who need me
???
Okay, haley, it's not wrong
for  wananot mia.U want.
????
But i used to be.
Do you remember how hard
that was on my relationship?
All right,
so this time it won't be.
This time you'll do it
differently.
And this time
i'll help you.
I like your water balloon.
Yeah, lucas and???
???
On who?
?????
You'd be surprised at how good
mak feel.
Well, speaki
of mn people...
We were just kids then, right
Yes,matu to be
doing that stuff now.
But i'm not.
Dude, the gu, s gonn, ve
a hent.
He's gonna drop dead.
You didn't tell me that!
But you were r
it really was fun.
My god.
You wantedu e me,
sir?
I hear the ravens might be
playing quentin fields tonight,
Broken wrist and all.
I think so.
Should be a big game.
So grab a camera
and go get me a story.
Really?
I mean, thank you, sir.
Uh, marvin...
We've decided give you a shot here.
Don't let usown.
I won't.
You can count on me.
Hey, scott.
You really gonna play a kid
with one hand
Against the best backcourt
in the conference?
All right," let's go.S got!
Let's go, let's go!
Full-Court press!
Pick them up
on defense!
Come on, now.
They can't defend us full-Court.
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Yes! "D" up! Full-Court!
Go, go, go
????For long.
There .Ght ther right there.
I told you. I told you.
Subs.
What is this, hockey?
No, it'sour worst nightmare.
Check the records
for 3-Point field goals
Attempted and made
in a half.
10 seconds.
Defense! Defense!
Come on, defense!
"Q," how you doing?
Man, who came up
with this crazy plan anyway?
'Cause i like it.
Good game, gentlemen.
Let's go, fellas.???
Yeah, team, keep it up.Ahe
What he said.
"Q," great half. Strong play.
Let's go, baby.
We can win this.
You guysone more half.
Lindsey
Hi
No, i mean, i'm at halftime
of a game, but...
I'm just so glad you called.
Yeah, we're...
We're up by 7.
Oh,  you so much.
Oh.
Come on, defense,
move your feet!
????
"Q", you got to get there!
Coach, i can barely
breathe right now.
Yeah, well, pick it up, or i'll
find someone that wants to play!
Luke.
Unbelievable.
Time-Out!
All right, look.
I know you're tired, okay?
But nothing in this life
comes easy, you hear me?
Nothing.
So suck it up.
Now, we got 3 minutes left, and
we're up by 9 points.
Finish it!
You hear me?
We are not gonna lose this game.
"Ravens" on three.
No.
"Bear creek sucks."
1, 2, 3...
All: bear creek sucks!
You hear that?
They're taunting you.
And they're right.
Their point guard
only has one hand.
Yeah, but it's a good hand,
coach.
All right, then,
here's what we're gonna do.
Whenever he gets the ball,
you foul him.
He'll eitherss h free throws
Or we'll break his other hand.
???
????
1, 2, 3...
All: four-Nine!
Ref, tt's flagra
No, sir.
It's one and one.
Skills: hey, they're playing
hack-A-Shaq.
They gonna send "q"
to the line
And make him shoot
left-Handed free throws.
Re nice.
Come on, "q."
Nice shooting, "q."
Let's go, baby.
One more.
Ronnie, come here.
Take out that wrist,
ronnie.
I got it.
Out of bounds.
Warrior ball.
What?!
You're kidding me.
On the street, that's assault.
You're not even gonna
call that a foul in here?
Technifoul.
Oh, you're gon
"t" me
You blow the call,
and you're gonna "t" me up?!
You're gonna get tossed,
son.
You need to throw
his dumb ass out.
How do you like it,
punk?
Luke,
what the hell happened?
That kid intentionally tried
to hurt "q," and you saw it.
I know, but, luke,
you grabbed him, man.
I should have
knocked him out!
God!
This is really bad, luke.
She's seeing someone else.
Lindsey.
She called at halftime.
I...
I can't believe it.
She's supposed to
come back to me.
Luke, i know
you don't want hear this, but...
What if she doesn't?
What ishe's not going to?
You can't wait around
forever.
Maybe it's --
Maybe it's time to te on.
She's supposed to
come back.
Brooke: hi.
Did you win?
I don't know.
What?
How's angie?
She's stronger
than i am.
She's breathing
on her own.
They said
she's doing great.
That's good.
That's really good, brooke.
Listen, i appreciate
that you came by,but...
They said
i'after hours.E lywho's a
That's okay. I, um...
Lindsey called.
See?
That's great, luke.
You thought
she was avoiding you.
Yeah.
Well...
I'll see you.
Hey, what do you mean
You don't know
if you won or not tonight?
I meant i don't know
if the team won.
But i lost.
I know that for sure.
So, am i allowed to ask what'sgoin
????
There's really not much to say,
you know?
It's not the easiest thing in
the world for him to talk about.
Well, you know what works?
Get him drunk.
Oh, says the 18-Year-Old.
I'm just saying.
You know how it is --
Guys always tell the truth
when they're wasted.
Says the 18-Year-Old.
Jamie: how come uncle lucas
was so mad, mama?
The ravens won the game.
I don't know, jim-Bob.
Uncle lucas won't call me back.
Hey, look,
there's grandpa.
I have an idea.
Why don't you go give your card
to your grandpa?
???
You're my best friend.
Thank you.
Go see your pop, okay?
Thank you, haley.
That wasn't for you.
That was for him.
It's a big story, bill.
We could lead with this.
Yeah. Marvin.
Tell me you got
some great footage
of lucas scott
grabbing that kid.
I, uh --
I didn't get it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I told you he wasn't ready.
Hey. Are you sure
you don't want me to stay?
I want to surprise you.
Des, this wa
in the morning,
It'll be like the cover-Song
elves were here.
Okay, but just call
if you need anything, okay?
Yeah.
Mia?
You had
day today
With, you know, the starburst
tour and rock the vote,
And i really want you to know
i'm so proud of you.
Peyton...
Thank you.
???
For my life. I love it.
Mia, your songs
were always great.
You were always great.
I just pointed people
towards the greatness.
Sing good, rock star.
Luke!
Hey.
Luke.Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Hey, what are you
doing here so late?
Hey. I'm not exactly sure,
actually.
I'm really happy for you,
mia -- All your success. It's just...
I think maybe i'm also
a little jealous.
Really?
Yeah.
That's so weird.
I'm jealous of you.
Yeah. It's like
i look at you and think,
"If, four years from now,
"I have this great guy
and a beautiful son
"And i'm about to make whama
gonna be an amazinn rd,
I'm gonna consider myself
really damn lucky."
Thank you.
Now i know
why i came here.
Okay, look for the rose.
Nobookert?
Debutanteball?
Antwon.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
You said you were older.
Hey, you said
you was younger.
Well, i-I showed you...
things.
Yes, you did.
Mm-Mm-Mmm.
Okay,
this is really awkward.
I mean, obviously,
nothing can happen here,
I mean, because it can't.
You right.
Nothing can happen.
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
Oh, what's one night between
two consenting adults, right?
Oh.
Maybe one night
and the next morning.
Oh, my! Oh!
It's gonna be bad
for coach, isn't it?
Yeah.
It's already bad.
Hi, mama.
Everything okay?
Hey, buddy.
????
You look so handsome.
Hey, you.
Hi, baby.
Hey.
Hi.
You should get some sleep.
Nah, i want to be here
when she opens her eyes.
It's a pretty great feeling,
isn't it?
It's why
i became a surgeon.
Why is that?
To give people
their lives back.
She'll recover and you'll send
her back to her parents, but...
The day she gets accepted
to college,
She'll have you to thank.
The day she gets married,
becomes something great,
Has children of her own,
She'll think,
"brooke davis got me here.
She gave me this."
And dr. Copeland, too.
It's ethan, by the way --
My first name.
Thank you, ethan.
You're welcome, brooke.
S right.
You are in bad shape.
Excuse
it's after hours.
Are you a relative
of reverend carter?
Not a relative, no.
But he's number one
on mst.
Oh, luke.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't want this
for you.
Peyton...
...i hate you.
What?
I wish you never came back.
You ruined my life.
????
??????