Previously on one tree hill...
ain't nobody gonna
give no roster spot
to no fool
with no green elf shoes on.
What are the chances of another
heart becoming available?
This time when it goes off,
call us.
I'm taking that last shot,
or i'm taking a seat.
Take a seat.
Child services keeps showing up,
looking for me.
I probably won't see you
for a while.
I never had
a letterman jacket.
Now you do.
I want you to have this.
It means
we're going steady.
I want a director who can
make the little things
the big things.
And you are just not the guy
to do that.
Pick one ...
if you don't,
i'm gonna choose
your director for you.
Appreciate you meeting me.
What do you want, reese?
I'm directing the movie.
It's done!
You can work your whole
"i'm nathan scott, mr. Big shot,
scoring my touchdowns"
on somebody else,
because ...
i don't even
play football.
Whatever ...  the point is,
at the end of the day,
all your bluster and b.s.
Don't mean anything to math,
because math don't care,
and neither do i.
Well, does english care?
'cause i pretty much
suck at that, too.
Thank you.
Thank you for that.
I like her poncho.
Why am i shirtless?
Yeah, let's do one
where he wears a poncho
and she's shirtless.
He was kidding.
You guys were great.
Thank you.
So,
what'd you guys think?
Really?
Didn't realize julian had
given creative control
to all four of us.
They're the real people.
Don't you think their opinions
may be valuable?
They seemed fine.
Yeah.
I stand corrected.
Let's get the studio
on the phone right now.
Tell them we found two actors
who seem fine.
Why don't you tell them
their director's a jackass
while you're at it?
Okay, we should go,
and i will stop by later
to see how you're doing.
You know, even when
he talks back to me,
i still find him likable.
All right,
lose the shirt, buddy.
Always and forever.
It sucks i can't
stick around for this.
It sucks even more you're
gonna be gone for two weeks.
At least i'll have
all these shirtless nathans
to keep me company.
Oh, i don't think so.
Thanks.
A crib.
Thank you, karen and andy.
Were you allowed to date
in prison?
Some people did.
I opted not to. Why?
Well, there's a girl
at school ...
oh, you like her?
No.
Yes, you do.
You like her a lot.
No, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Anyway, i was wondering
if maybe i could invite her
over to your beach house
someday.
Sure. Why not today?
I'll clear it with your mom.
Well, i never asked a girl
over to play before.
What do i say?
Well, lucky for you,
women have never been able
to turn a scott man down.
So you just flash
your million-dollar smile,
say a few nice words,
and pfft ...
it's like putty
in your hands.
Yeah, that's the one.
Just smile
and say something nice?
That really works?
Every time.
What are you smiling about?
I can't help it.
That was amazing.
No wonder you were so popular
in high school.
Excuse me?
Sex did not make me popular.
I made it popular.
Ohh. Well, either way,
i'm just happy
to be a part of that crowd
for a change.
Please.
With this face,
you were probably mr. Popular.
You might be surprised.
Anyway,
i wish i could stay,
but i'm already late
for casting.
For which character?!
Don't ...  oh!
Peyton sawyer?
Yeah.
Go have a seat
with the other peytons,
and we'll call you
when it's your turn.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm sorry.
You don't understand.
I ...
i am peyton sawyer.
I really appreciate
your confidence,
but you still have to
wait your turn.
What's your name?
Peyton sawyer.
Actresses.
Why do people
always leave?
Hi. I'm here to read for
the part of peyton sawyer.
First of all,
you don't know me.
Second of all,
God, why are guys such jerks?
Too old, but she would
make a great deb.
Um,
she's the real peyton.
Hi.
Did you come to watch?
No.
The baby-proofer's
coming to the house,
and i've got to go register
for our wedding and baby gifts,
and your mother
sent us a crib,
but the instructions
are all in italian.
You're stewed, buttwad.
"Weird science."
I really wish i could help,
but i'm kind of slammed.
No, it's okay.
I just came by to wish you good
luck and to bring you lunch.
Why are you so good to me?
I don't know.
Maybe because
i am a riddle
wrapped in a mystery
inside a bitch.
What woman isn't?
Bye.
You wanted to see me?
Yes.
Take a seat, please.
Do you know
why i called you here?
No.
I guess i'm in trouble,
but i don't know what for.
And i'm sure as hell not gonna
start admitting stuff.
I think you know
exactly what you did.
You won the essay contest,
and, as promised,
you're gonna be published
in the school paper tomorrow.
You suck.
Congratulations,
samantha.
Oh, you're gonna be
a published writer!
That is,
if that's okay with you.
Hell, yes.
She said yes!
That's great.
What time's she coming over?
I don't know.
What kind of food
does she like?
I don't know.
What do you know?
She said yes!
Well, that is
the most important thing.
Now, how do i get her
to like me?
Well,
if she's coming over,
she probably already
does like you.
Now all you have to do
is make sure you're dressed nice
and tell her
how good she looks.
Is that
how you got nanny deb?
That and gin.
Got any gin?
Don't worry. I'll be there
the whole time if you need me.
* still i'm working now
is that your heart again?
Yeah.
I'll be fine.
I wish that beeper
would beep already.
Me too, buddy.
Hey.
Lucas is casting his movie
in here today,
so the studio's
off-limits.
Ohh. Sweet. Snow day.
Later, teach.
Oh, no, no.
Not so fast.
We still have work
to do.
You're kidding, right?
You're italian, right?
Easy, girl.
I saw that.
What?
Did you greet all
the other brookes that way?
No, ma'am. That i saved
just for you.
Oh.
And the guy playing whitey,
who is just so cute.
So, do you want to meet
brooke davis?
Shut up.
She's here?
Yeah.
I just got butterflies
a little bit.
Now i know
how people must feel
when they're meeting me
for the first time.
Missy, this is...
brooke davis!
Yep.
Brooke, this is...
missy me!
Hi! Oh!
I guess we made
the right choice.
Oh, hi!
Oh!
Okay, i want my part
in the movie to be the best.
So anything that you need,
you just ask.
Okay, great,
because i'm a method actor,
so i'm gonna need to know your
likes, dislikes, mannerisms ...
basically be glued to you
until the movie starts.
What do you think?
Sounds...great.
Aah!
Ooh! Hi.
You wanted to see me,
coach?
I did.
I want to ask you something
in confidence.
What do you think
of devon?
In confidence...
...i think he puts up
big numbers,
but he won't win you
any games.
He doesn't care
about the team.
He only cares about
getting himself to the nba.
And you don't want to
get to the nba?
No, i do.
But you're the only reason
i have a shot at it,
so i owe you,
and i'm gonna play my heart out.
Look...
if you started me, you'd be
replacing your star player
with a player that gives you
wins instead of headaches.
You sound like a salesman,
nate.
I believe
in what i'm selling.
So do i.
You're starting next game.
Be ready.
I want to draw something
that means something to someone.
You're always saving me, lucas.
I love you, luke.
But i've chosen darkness.
That was great.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I loved "trouser hound,"
by the way.
He loves you, too.
Thanks.
There's something
about that one.
She wants to
sleep with you?
There it is.
So, we done?
I liked the first girl.
I'm just not sure.
Two things ...
number one, big wedding ring.
Number two,
even bigger nose.
She can lose the ring,
but the schnoz
is gonna need its own trailer.
Okay, there's nothing wrong
with her nose.
Besides, i'm not
casting this movie
based on
who i want to sleep with.
He has no idea
what he's doing.
It's called
having integrity.
It's called being naive.
Look, you have a decision
to make, okay?
Audiences like boobs.
I didn't make that up.
It's just ...  it's the way it is.
Sex sells.
So i say go with the girl
with the nice rack.
Now, if you want to disagree
with me, fine, go ahead.
But just make
a damn decision, man.
Adam, maybe you should
take a break.
You're right.
This place is dead anyway.
"Swingers."
Julian, i didn't get to choose
a director i like.
I'm not making the same mistake
with peyton.
Okay, that's fine.
But reese is right.
You need to come to a decision
you can both live with, okay?
Like it or not,
we have a deadline,
and you have a job to do.
This job sucks.
I don't think
this is right.
It looks fine to me.
Done and done.
Okay, well, then,
what is that for?
I don't know ...
to keep the baby from moving?
Why don't you just
have lucas do it?
Because he's busy, and we are
two strong, capable women.
We can do this.
Hey,
what's chase doing?
Uh, no.
He's busy...with me.
So, i'll see ya.
I mean, arrivederci.
I got it when i was 12,
but i don't know why
you need to know.
How many cigarettes
do you smoke a day
to get your voice
to sound like this?
I don't smoke, and my voice
doesn't sound like that.
How many guys
did you sleep with
in high school?
Gee, i don't know.
I was never very good at math.
Dumb at math.
Got it.
What do you think
of this outfit?
I don't think that brooke
would wear something like this.
I am brooke, and i did
wear something like that.
But don't you think it should be
a little more revealing
or easy to strip off at least ...
you know, brooke-ish?
I don't strip things off.
The outfit is fine.
Julian, what do you think?
Um, it could be
a little sexier.
Should i just go ahead
and put her in pasties?
Come on, brooke. Did you really
wear that in high school?
Yes, i did.
Maybe during
your "clean teen" days.
Just make it a little sexier,
you know? Brooke-ish.
Oh, you totally have a type.
He looks a lot like lucas.
That's another thing you should
know about me for the movie.
I lash out sometimes.
Sorry.
"Part of me is glad
that jack's gone.
"Gone is a place i dreamed of
when i was hiding in a closet
"from whatever drunk parent
i had that month.
But ... "
whose phone is that?
Yours.
Hi.
Is everything okay?
Hey. I just wanted you to be
the first to know.
I'm starting next game.
I couldn't have done this
without you, hales.
I love you.
Tell jamie i'll
call him later, okay?
I love you, too.
He's ...  he's starting!
Sorry, sam.
"But i got lucky."
You must be
lauren's mom.
You must not talk
to many women.
I'm lauren,
jamie's teacher.
He invited me to his grandpa's
house after school,
and i just couldn't turn down
an afternoon
with a cute boy
and a little old man.
You're not
a little old man.
No.
Grandpa dan, aren't you
gonna invite her in?
You look very nice,
miss lauren.
Thank you. It's what i was
wearing at school earlier.
Well, it's very becoming.
Shall we?
Thank you.
So, what did you do?
Nothing. The principal
just wanted to meet with me.
You're probably
in trouble.
With the new princal,
everyone's in trouble.
Mrs. Scott,
could you come in, please?
Am i in trouble,
principal rimkus?
Do you know why
i wanted to see you?
No.
And i'm not gonna start
admitting stuff.
I have a problem
with the essay
you selected
for the school paper.
Oh, sam's essay?
What's wrong with it?
What, you mean besides all the
references to sex and drugs?
She's witnessed some really
horrible things growing up.
I think that's what makes
the essay so important.
Well, that may be.
But i have the students and
their parents to worry about.
I understand,
but with all due respect,
i thought i was in charge
of the school paper
and had final say
on what went in it.
You do.
And i have final say
on whether or not you work here.
Pick another essay.
So, when you stop
to think about it,
where does
the sidewalk end?
You know, i never really
thought about it.
Jamie's always been advanced
for his age.
Right now he's reading
the "time traveler's wife."
Oh, that's one
of my favorite books.
Mine too.
That's great.
How about i refill
your kool-aid?
Well, thank you, jamie.
That is very gentlemanly of you.
We have wine,
if you prefer.
Kool-aid will be fine.
Back off.
Hey, skills.
You looking for luke?
No.
I'm the baby-proofer.
Why didn't i know that?
Who brags about being
a baby-proofer?
Oh, okay.
I mean, i think our house
is pretty safe.
I can spot at least
20 pbis already.
Huh?
Possible baby injuries.
Oh. Like what?
Well, for one,
lamp cord strangles.
Okay.
Outlets electrocute.
And i'm guessing you
probably don't have a
lock on the toilet seat.
Luke barely remembers
to put it down.
Funny. But you know
what's not so funny?
When junk was a kid,
he fell in a toilet ...
almost drowned.
He was dead
for 40 seconds.
I'm ...  no, i'm sorry.
You're right.
That's totally not funny.
Um, i have a lot of work
to do, huh?
Yep.
But you got lucas
to help you, right?
No, i mean, he's over at tric
casting his movie.
But i ha...  i have it.
It's fine.
That's not done,
by the way.
I hope not.
I can see at least 30 pbis
already.
If you need help putting
that thing back together,
give me a call.
I'm also a handyman.
Hey. Heard any word
from jack yet?
Uh...no.
That's kind of
why i hang here.
I figure this
is where he'll show
when he decides
to come back...
if he decides to.
I'm sure he will.
Yeah. I hope so.
Could you really get fired
for publishing my paper?
Where did you hear that?
I've already lost jack.
I really don't want to lose you
to some stupid paper.
You ...
you're not gonna lose me.
And your paper's anything
but stupid, sam.
Well, i better get going.
Don't want brooke to worry.
Listen, haley.
I appreciate it.
I do.
But if i were you, i would just
choose a different paper.
It's not worth it.
Looks like 12's
the new 23.
What's up?
Like you don't know.
Coach cut his best player
to start his best friend.
I didn't know
he was cutting you.
I thought ...
i'm sorry.
Don't be.
I'm going to the nba anyway.
Somehow ...
daddy!
Hey, boo.
There's my team.
Hey. Hi.
Hey,
daddy's gonna be okay.
What you looking at,
12?
You're not the only one
with a family.
Wedding. Wedding.
Wedding.
Baby.
Is there a reason
that we're registering
for the wedding and the baby
at the same time?
Well, they're happening
at the same time,
so why not
register them together?
Because i may have registered
the baby for a boning knife.
That's got to be a pbi,
right?
I swear, i love you,
but are you sure
you would not rather
be doing this with lucas?
No. He is busy.
And there is no one
i would rather do this with
than my best friend
and my maid of honor.
Maid of honor?
Really?!
Well, it shouldn't be
a surprise.
But it's so nice to hear!
Okay!
Ohh.
Want to know
what i think?
I think that nathan
likes tutor girl,
but tutor girl likes lucas,
and i know i like lucas,
and i don't know who
the hell you like anymore.
This is all turning into one big
love rectangle plus one,
whatever that is.
Pretty good, right?
Yeah. Awesome.
Dude,
she sounds like you.
I was never
that anning.
I know how you feel.
I was in tric
earlier today,
and there were 10 peyton sawyers
bitching and moaning.
Oh, so there were 11 of you
bitching and moaning?
I think i like
that other one better.
So, i'm driving jamie home
from school,
and he suddenly yells at me
to stop the car
because orval got out
of the bag.
Oh, and who's orval?
My question exactly.
Orval is his pet rabbit's
imaginary friend.
Oh, that's so cute.
And he insists that orval
has gone into a chuck e. Cheese.
So, since we're already there,
why not grab some pizza?
Oh, he's crafty.
You're making fun of me?
No, i wasn't.
You're trying
to embarrass me
so miss lauren
will like you better.
Jamie.
He was in prison!
Hey, yo, man.
I heard you was casting today.
Hey,
who's gonna play fergie?
Uh, man, uh...
you know, when i turned
the book into a movie,
i had to omit
some of the characters.
Look, i'm really sorry, fergie.
I didn't...
then who did luke hang with
on the river court?
Mouth...and skills.
You gonna play me
like that?
That's cold, dawg.
Look, fergie...
which do you like better?
They look the same,
man.
We're gonna need you to sign off
on a few locations
before we can move on.
Okay...
hey, man, i am trying to wrap my
head around this dan character.
I don't get why he's got
all this hatred for keith.
Reese wants to sign off
on peyton number three.
Are you okay with that?
No!
I like the first one.
Toucan sam?
Peyton's a love interest.
Think about it
with your other head.
I know you have a vision,
lucas,
but maybe you need to trust
reese's experience on this one.
Our table read is tomorrow,
and we can't do it
without a peyton.
I know, all right!
I just need to think about it!
We don't have time
for that.
Well, make...time!
And...scene.
So, which ones do you think
lucas will like?
Whichever ones
you're naked in.
Speaking of naked...
i slept with julian.
Come again?
That's what she said.
She being me ...
it's a joke.
I know.
I get it.
Um, god, why am i just
finding out about this now?
'cause i've been really scared
to tell you.
I know that you said
it's fine,
but i kind of still feel like
it violates girl code somehow,
and i know you're happy
and engaged
and pregnant, and ...
and he's charming.
Brooke, hey, really...
it's fine.
We talked about this,
all right?
Girl code was shattered
years ago.
You promise?
You're not gonna revoke
my maid-of-honor card?
God.
Of course i promise.
Come here.
I mean, you know that's like
three guys we've shared, right?
Lucas, julian.
Um, sex tape?
Ew. Sex tape.
I forgot about that, and i
kind of wish that you had, too.
Oh, no, no, no.
Um, so just how did it go
from being a non-date to sex?
It was the grin, right?
That didn't hurt.
And then he threw in a touch
of sweet and so much sincerity.
And then he threw in
the letterman jacket i made him.
Oh, well, letterman jacket.
That's a good touch.
High-school brooke
did letter in sex.
Hey,
how's the movie biz?
Well, i had
my first diva moment ...
threw a temper tantrum.
No way. Damn. Wish i'd
have been here to see it.
Uh, stick around.
I'm sure i'll have another.
Is it really that bad?
I can't even pick a basketball
much less a peyton
without feeling like i'm making
the wrong decision.
My gut says one thing,
and everybody else
says something else.
Who cares what
everybody else says?
Go with your gut.
Just like that, huh?
Lucas, this was your book,
and now it's your movie.
You know the characters,
and you know tree hill
better than anybody.
You should have some faith in
yourself, for crying out loud.
I love you. I love you.
You know that?
I know.
You know, they should name
an antidepressant after you.
Yeah. Great with
everybody else's problems.
It's my own
i'm a basket case with.
Hmm. All right, well...
psychotherapist luke.
Can i help you
with anything?
Sam wrote this paper
for my class.
It was gritty and harsh
and honest and really beautiful,
and i want to publish it
in the school paper.
And principal rimkus
won't let me.
Well,
what else can you do?
I could publish it anyway.
Kids like sam, they ...
sometimes all they have
is a voice,
and if you take that away
from them,
especially after everything
that she's been through,
then what's the point of
me even calling myself
a teacher anymore?
Well, it sounds to me
like you've already
made your decision.
I'm just not sure
it's the right one.
Man, you got to have some faith
in yourself sometimes.
No, go with your gut.
Come on.
What's the worst
that can happen?
I could get fired,
or at least suspended.
I've been suspended ...
not that bad.
You're pretty good
at cheering me up, too.
Yes!
Go away!
You're mean!
That's why daddy and uncle lucas
don't like you.
That's true.
I was mean.
And they have every reason
not to like me.
But ever since i got sick,
i've tried real hard
to be a better person.
Then why were you
making fun of me?
I would never
make fun of you.
You're my best friend.
Don't you know that?
Actually,
you're my only friend.
I don't even have
an imaginary one.
Miss lauren doesn't think
i'm a joke?
Of course not.
You're her favorite student.
She told me this is one of the
best dates she's ever been on.
She said that?
She sure did.
You should go back in there
and finish the date.
And if i hurt your feelings,
i'm sorry.
I would never do anything
to hurt my best friend.
I forgive you.
Well,
aren't you coming?
You'll be fine
without me.
I just wanted to make sure
i got your signature move right.
What is with you idiots?
This is not
my signature move.
And fyi, i did a lot more
in high school
than just have sex,
okay?
I was
student-body president.
I was the captain
of the cheerleading squad.
I started
a clothing line.
It is amazing that i even
had time for sex!
Sorry.
I didn't mean to offend you.
I was just following
the breakdown.
"Brooke davis ...
gorgeous brunette
"with an amazing energy
and smile.
"Her three
favorite things ...
sex, sex, and sex."
Coach...i wanted to talk
to you about devon.
I didn't mean for you
to cut him.
Well, good,
because it wasn't your call.
I cut devon because
he wouldn't play for me.
And that crap he pulled
the other night ...
that's the last straw.
Okay, well, maybe you could talk
to him about it or something.
Coach,
the guy has a family.
So do you, nathan.
So do i.
Look,
this is a business.
You two aren't the only ones
whose end game is the nba.
I'm certainly not gonna get
there coaching a losing team.
I understand. Okay, maybe
devon and i can work together.
It's done, nathan.
You're my starter now.
I need for you to focus on that.
Who's more important here ...
you or devon?
My family
is more important.
All right, then.
We're done here.
I'll see you in practice
tomorrow.
Stop it!
He already cast me.
Hey!
Excuse me.
It's like "the twilight zone"
in here!
You!
How could you write such
horrible things about me?
You, who called me
your pretty girl
and said that i was gonna
change the world someday?!
Huh?!
What are you
talking about?
Tell me that you
didn't write that!
I didn't write this.
Then who did?
I'll take
the third haley's legs,
the first brooke's fun bags,
and the last peyton's ass.
I take
the real brooke davis.
Here's your stupid jacket.
I should have seen this coming.
You related to my character
in the book,
and you wanted
all my wardrobe to be sexier,
and you gave me
your letterman jacket.
You want high-school brooke?
I have news for you.
I am not that girl anymore.
There is a lot more to me
than just sex.
Brooke ...
high-school brooke
graduated!
Hey, brooke!
Don't worry.
I know where you can find five
more who look just like her.
Oh, hey. You're baby-proofing.
Don't forget the laundry room.
Jamie used to take naps
in the dryer.
Yeah, i got it.
The toilet,
the cupboards, fridge.
What else does a baby
get into?
Your heart.
I love it.
Good.
Thanks.
I saw you registered
for a boning knife,
but i figured that was
more practical for a newborn.
How you holding up?
I don't know.
One minute,
i'm shopping,
and the next,
i feel like i'm gonna cry.
Tell me that's normal.
Just remember, things are never
as bad as you think they are,
even though your hormones
are trying to convince
you otherwise.
I know, i know.
Um, i just ...  i keep telling
everybody that i'm okay.
But doing
all this baby stuff
just really makes me wish
that lucas was here.
I've got this
doctor's appointment tomorrow
that i really
want him to go to,
but he's so busy
with the movie.
Well, if you want him to go,
why don't you just tell him?
I did.
I told him last week.
But with everything
that's going on, he's ...
you know, he's swamped,
and i don't
want to be a nag.
I think you should
nag him anyway.
That boy needs it.
Thanks.
And thanks for being
so good with luke.
You make everything better
for us.
Sorry i'm late.
I'll start dinner.
Or we can order pizza.
Sam, i am not
in high school anymore.
I can make you
a grown-up dinner,
like a salad
or a...roast.
Okay, i was just thinking
maybe we could celebrate?
Okay.
What should we celebrate?
The fact that i finally
ditched my clone
or that julian thinks that
i am a teenage nymphomaniac?
Um, i was just kind of thinking
maybe we could celebrate
me winning
the school essay contest.
Really?
Sam, that's amazing.
"Homeless in high school."
It's about me and jack ...
how rough life can be
on your own.
All that fun stuff.
I am so proud of you.
Thank you.
Can i put it
on the fridge?
Yeah.
Brooke...
i don't know why
you're so mad at julian,
but at least
he's still around.
I would give anything
to have jack back.
Yeah.
But we should be
celebrating that.
So, what do you
want to do?
I want to eat pizza.
Seriously?
Okay.
So thanks for tonight, jamie.
I'll see you in school tomorrow?
Bye.
So, how did the rest
of your evening go?
So-so.
She just wanted to talk
about adult stuff
like a new car
and maroon 5.
Next time, i think i should date
someone my own age.
Or younger.
I'm sorry
i called you mean.
Next time, we should
just do a guys' night.
So, uh...
we still friends?
Best.
Hey, it's me.
Um, god, i'm sorry.
I know you're busy.
Just today has been...
i tried
putting the crib together.
I did.
It just totally sucked.
And every square inch
of our house
needs to be baby-proofed,
or our kid's gonna end up
like junk.
And i don't even know
what we're registered for.
I really just wish
you could have been there.
Um, and i wish
you could be there
for my doctor's appointment
tomorrow,
but i know you're busy,
and i just ...
if you're satisfied
with your message, press 1.
If you would like to erase and
re-record your message, press 2.
Hi! It's me.
Um, i put the crib together.
It's awesome.
So, i just want to call
and say hi and i miss you
and come home soon, okay?
Bye.
You want to know
what i think?
I know what you think.
You want the girl
with the big breasts.
Look, when i was casting
"trouser hound,"
i had a really tough time
trying to decide
who should play miss kittington.
A director friend of mine
told me to close my eyes
during the auditions.
He said
that was the best way
to be able to hear the actress
and not just see a hot girl.
Is that what you do?
No!
I picked the actress
with the best rack.
You just looked like
you needed some advice.
Hi.
Well, hello.
Leave us.
Actually, i want to
speak to both of you.
I really
want to play peyton.
I feel that i identify
with her.
We were both in
the popular crowd in school
even though we felt
like outcasts,
and we both feel that the first
song you hear in the morning
can affect
your entire day.
And i'll totally
sleep with you.
You too.
Well, look at you go.
You just made my decision
very, very easy.
Mine, too.
Playing the role
of peyton sawyer
is miss heidi jay.
Sorry, but the other girl
just wasn't peyton.
I had to go with my gut.
No worries.
She was peyton last night ...
and i was lucas.
Everyone, welcome
to the table read
for "an unkindness
of ravens."
I am adam reese,
your director.
This is lucas scott,
the writer and producer.
Lucas.
All right, here it goes.
"Fade in. Exterior
tree hill high school. Night.
"Steady traffic filters
into the parking lot
"as a solitary figure
enters frame,
dribbling a worn basketball."
"I'm really lucky
to have basketball.
"It's pretty much my shot
at everything from here on out.
If i lose that,
it's over for me."
Well, well.
If it ain't
the jolly green-shoe giant.
Oh, that's right.
You only 6'2", so i guess
that'd make you sprout.
What are you doing here,
nino?
Playing point guard.
Or at least i will be
as soon as you get the
hell up out of my spot.
Hey...
see you on the court, 12.
"When i'm tutoring someone
and they get it
"and that light goes on,
i feel good.
I feel worthy."
"So i put soap
in my foster mom's wine ...
cleaned her mouth out
for a change."
That's so awesome.
Hey, sam, great article.
"I wanted you to fight for me.
"I wanted you to say
there's no one else that
you could ever be with
and that you'd rather be alone
than without me."
Does that look like
mr. Popular to you?
I know you're not the person
you were in high school,
'cause i'm not, either.
And i'm glad,
because that kid
never would have stood
a chance with you.
Were you really
a mathlete?
I was the mathlete.
But i'm not anymore,
and i don't want
high-school brooke.
I'm sorry the breakdown
hurt your feelings.
It was meant to describe
who the character was
before anyone got to know
the real person.
That's a breakdown
describing
the brooke davis
i'm looking for.
"Funny. Intelligent.
"Kind-hearted.
Strong-headed."
"Simple. Complicated.
"Motherly. Childish.
"Tough. Sensitive.
"Beautiful.
Way cooler than she was
in high school."
That girl has been
nearly impossible to find
but worth every second
of the wait.
Are you gonna make sure
missy knows this?
I'm gonna make sure
everybody knows.
"I'm glad you're here.
"I know we kind of lost
each other for a while there,
but hopefully
that's over, right?"
"It's always gonna be there,
isn't it ...  you and me?"
Is the father
going to be joining us?
No.
Yes...he is.
Hey.
How'd you know?
You told me last week.
I'm so happy
you're here, luke.
Are you kidding me?
I wouldn't miss this
for the world.
That's exactly
what i needed to hear.
That's your baby's
heartbeat.
And that is exactly
what i needed to hear.
Beautiful.
"They eye each other,
just a boy and a girl,
alone but together in this place
called tree hill."
Let's make a movie.