www.1000fr.com presents
one tree hill s05e18
season finale
capture:frm@xxy
sync:frs@will
let me take this part.
You're a cute kid.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hey, you.
Whatcha got there?
What's that?
I think you drank too much.
I think you're right.
Nathan: damn.
Think somebody got thrown
through a plate-glass window.
Dude, it seriously smells
like ass in here.
And rotten cheese.
Go away.
Ew, and bad breath.
I said, "go away."
Ho...
Holy crap.
What?
Have you
seen your head?
Not lately.
You have a mohawk.
I do?
Awesome.
Can I get one, daddy?
Sure, if you want to look goofy
like your uncle lucas.
Kind of like he has a tail...
Just on his head.
Jamie, why don't you go get luke
a bottle of water, huh?
Okay.
I thought
we were gonna see you
at that school-board hearing.
Yeah.
They suspended you, luke.
10 games.
There's only 11 left.
Not for you.
Here you go!
All right, jamie.
Let's get going.
Okay.
Bye, uncle lucas.
Cool hair.
Wait for me right there,
okay?
Look, luke...
I know from experience
whatever answers
you're looking for...
You're not gonna find them
like this -- trust me.
I know it sucks
that lindsey's dating,
and it sucks that you grabbed that player,
but don't make it worse.
The darkness doesn't
have any answers, luke.
Okay, you silly rabbit.
We're going to the beach.
Yes, we are.
Just me and my funny bunny.
Did you hear that?
Did you hear what I called you?
Did you hear what mama --
Hello?
Yes, this is she.
But...
There must be some mistake.
She has eight days left.
But she's recovering
from surgery, so...
No, I understand.
Okay. Bye-bye.
They want you to go home today.
But that can't happen.
Oh, well, well.
What...what is all this
not sure.
I would laugh if this whole
thing wasn't such a mess.
What whole mess?
You, your head --
All of it.
You and I
are going for a drive.
But, first, we're gonna fix
the ferret above your face.
why?
We're taking a drive
because I'm your best friend
and you need me.
And we are fixing your...
Very punk-rock haircut
because I have
a 5-year-old son
who unfortunately wants to look
just like his uncle lucas.
so,
How's the comeback going?
It's not a comeback.
Quentin says it is.
Quentin's wrong.
And, by the way,
nobody's sporting
the faux hawk anymore, dude.
I'm bringing it back.
So, what team do you think
you're gonna play for in the nba?
Jamie, come here.
I know you're
really excited about this, but...
I'm probably
never gonna play in the nba.
Sure, you will.
Geez, kiddo.
You're playing
with rolled-up socks?
What happened
to your ball?
I lost it.
I got to go feed chester
I got to ask you
something.
Did you tell peyton
that you hated her?
Maybe.
I was a little wasted.
Luke, you can be
such a jackass sometimes.
She is in love with you.
You probably broke her heart.
Oh, I didn't break her heart.
You're being dramatic.
i'm being dramatic.
Stop here.
The light's green.
Just stop.
All right.
We're sitting at a green light.
Now what?
Just wait for it.
Haley, the light's green!
Wait for what?!
Kind of like peyton's heart,
don't you think?
I'll be right back.
You shouldn't stay here.
Okay.
hey.
You said
it made you feel better.
It's gonna be okay.
All right.
All clear, you goof.
No peyton?
No. You need to apologize
to her.
Hey, remember all the water-balloon battles
we used to have up here?
Don't change the subject.
Actually,
now that you mention it,
it was junior year,
the boy-toy auction.
We had that water-balloon
fight up here,
and you saw my tattoo
of nathan's jersey number for the first time.
You mean your
slutty little tramp stamp.
I am so barely your friend
right now.
Sorry.
The point is,
I was so scared that night.
I was falling in love
for the first time,
and I was so unsure.
But I did it.
And while
it hasn't been easy,
it has bn everything.
We're not kids anymore, luke.
You know...
It really hurts me
to wat what you're doing.
Lindsey said no, hales
I said yes.
Don't give me that, luke.
I'm being honest with you
right now,
and you need to be honest
with yourself.
What do you want?
If lindsey's the girl
that you're in love with, great.
If it's peyton, great.
If it's brooke, just please...
Stop hiding your heart.
I mean it.
Hi. How's your day?
Well, I cleaned the bathroom,
washed the news van,
returned some shoes
for the weather lady
because apparently the straps
cut into her "cankles,"
and they hired
a new sports guy -- steve.
How about
I buy you some lunch?
Come on.
Reverend howard carter.
I did a little research.
Man of faith, lived a good life.
Tough run, though.
Diabetes, stroke.
You know, it's not
exactly benevolent of you
to lie there and take a heart
that could be put to better use.
In fact,
it's really quite selfish.
Don't you agree?
"yeah, I agree.
Yes, I do."
Morning.
Good morning.
The reverend was looking
a little uncomfortable.
Would you like to give him
this pillow?
Actually...
I just might.
Hey, look.
It's my mom
doing the walk of shame.
Maybe we should hire
a nanny for you.
Out with a guy
you met on a porn site.
Not porn -- erotica.
Hey, buddy. Thought you
might want to go for a swim.
No, thanks.
It's been a while.
I don't think I've seen you in the pool
since your accident.
It's okay.
I have to feed chester.
Jamie, are you afraid?
no.
I just don't want to.
Are you sure?
It might be fun.
No, thank you.
Well,
I think I found the problem.
Brooke: you did?
Yes. Uh, you have
an incredibly cute baby here,
and you don't
want to send her home.
But are you sure
she's well enough?
Brooke, angie's tough days
are over, okay?
And she was very brave
about them.
It's time
for you to be brave.
But I was supposed to have
eight more days with her.
We were supposed to go
to the beach.
Well, that's
how the program works.
They take
the first flight available.
Anyway, look, um...
When the silence sets in...
And it will --
Be proud of this.
Okay? You've done
a great thing here, brooke.
But it's time for angie
to go home...
Today.
Yeah.
So you got something for me, man?
Just shut up
and check the ball, "q."
oh.
Crossover's
a little rusty, son.
Huh? Fake this guy.
Ha ha ha.
Where that a.c.c. Game at,
nate? Hmm?
First-team
all-american?
Nba lottery? Huh?
ugh,
Up out of here, man.
Damn it!
The fadeaway, nate?
Really? Are you serious?
The fadeaway is weak,
man! Weak!
Come on, man.
Let's go again.
No, man. I'm not feeling today.
I'm done.
Hey, j. Scott...
Why don't you run out in the hallway
and get us some waters?
Okay.
hey.
You see any hot
psycho nannies out there,
you run back in here,
okay?
Not funny.
What's going on, nate?
I'm just out of shape.
No, man. That ain't it.
That is not it.
Now, every day we do this,
and every day you play soft.
Well, maybe that's because
I can't do this anymore.
Really? Maybe you
just scared to, right? Huh?
Easier to have your dream
taken away than give it a shot and fail, right?
I'm not scared.
Right?
You not scared?
Well, you playing scared.
I'm not scared.
You playing scared!
I am not scared, man!
I'm -- I'm afraid to go
in the pool, daddy.
Yeah, but, uh...
You went in the pool
all the time
before your accident, jamie,
and you loved it.
You know
you can still do it.
I know.
I'm just...scared.
It's okay
if you don't play anymore.
Thanks, son.
Haley:
i'm dying here.
You okay?
Huh? Yeah.
Uh, I-I just got
a weird e-mail from mia
saying she met
this guy out on tour that
said he knew ellie. So it just caught me
off guard.
How come you're dying?
Oh, because I'm having trouble
writing lyrics
for this melody
that you liked.
Okay, what do you got
so far?
So far I've got nothing.
All right.
How about...
"i hate you, bitch.
You ruined my life"?
Does that
do anything for you?
You know what?
I do have some words for you,
even though they're not mine.
Lucas and i, we used to write
our predictions every year
before the school year
started.
Sort of what we hoped
would happen.
Lame.
You know
you're jealous.
Kind of.
Anyway, I'm gonna violate
my friendship rule here
because you're at,
like, code red.
"peyton sawyer
will become peyton scott."
That was, like,
eighth grade.
He got a little cocky
sophomore year.
"make out with peyton sawyer
or more."
And, "this year,
i'll talk to peyton sawyer."
"try again with brooke --
Brooke davis."
Well, that...
But, you know, this is
how much he doesn't hate you.
It's a whole lifetime's
worth.
I know. I know.
That's --
That's what he writes.
But what he says
is a totally different story.
Sometimes people write
the things that they can't say.
Come on in.
It's open.
hi.
This is nice, luke.
Lindsey,
what are you doing here?
Uh...
I needed to talk to you
about something, but...
You wouldn't answer
your phone.
You look good.
You look hung over.
Yeah, well...
There's a girl I almost married
started dating again.
And after that, well,
things just kind of went dark.
The book's done.
Oh, come on.
The -- the ending needs work.
I haven't even written
a dedication yet.
You can e-mail
the dedication.
The book's done, luke.
It's perfect.
So...
I think this is goodbye.
And goodbye shouldn't happen
over the phone.
Lindsey...
Do you ever Miss me?
I should go.
What you doing, buddy?
Looking at your trophies.
You know, someday, you're
gonna have your own trophies.
Think so?
Oh, yeah. I know so.
Trophies, awards --
Maybe even a monument.
And then maybe someday
you'll have a son of your own
that's even greater than
any award or accomplishment.
Come here.
Don't be afraid
to be great, son. Okay?
'cause you are.
And the world isn't strong enough
to beat james lucas scott.
I promise.
We love you.
Hi, I'm steve,
the new sports guy.
Hi, steve.
That's
the better sports guy.
The truth is, I'm scared, okay?
The countdown's on.
And I've got to wait for this damn beeper to go off
before I can get a heart...
After you get one.
You're the one
who's lived a good life.
I'm the one who needs time
to make amends.
So why don't you just take one
for the team, huh?
And if you do...
I'll use my time for redemption.
Okay?
You suck, carter.
I love you, little girl,
and I always will, okay?
You're gonna have
a great life.
Don't forget me, okay?
I'm james lucas scott!
You got my message.
I told you not to come.
I know.
She's gone, luke.
You did it, buddy.
I knew you could. Come here.
All right, you ready?
Yeah!
One...
Both:
two, three.
Okay, carter...
It's up to you.
But sometimes a guy just needs a
sign there's some hope for him,
you know?
Hope.
???
And telling the new sports guy off.
But I should pbably
get back to being shunned.
I'm sorry
it's so hard for you now.
You know something?
I stand by what I did.
Luke was really hurting,
and it just felt insidious
somehow to broadcast that pain.
Mouth, how many men's basketball
championships has ucla --
11.
I don't know
what to do now.
Omaha.
Not without you.
Then I'll go, too.
Really?
U'd go with me?
yes.
I'd go anywhere with you,
marvin mcfadden.
Jamie, you're tracking water
all over the house!
I can't get him
out of that pool now.
Dude, dry off
and get your jersey on.
We're going
back to the gym.
We are?!
Yeah.
Nathan and jamie scott.
Oh, jamie!
You know what?
You still make
my heart race.
You do. I'm serious.
Feel this.
????and love and joy right now
because of you.
It's my other boy.
All right. I'll see you.
I love you.
hey.
Wow. Very peyton.
Lindsey
stopped by today.
She's here?
Uh, not anymore.
I had to go see brooke.
The trifecta.
How nice.
What did lindsey want?
She wanted to tell me
that my book's done.
Well, everything
except the dedication.
She said I could
e-mail that to her.
I'm thinking about...
Taking off for a little while,
you know?
Lucas,
please stop running.
Come on --
You got to let go of this dark weight you're carrying around.
This morning...
Nathan told me the darkness
doesn't have any answers.
He's right.
You saw him
after his accident.
And look at him now.
Yeah.
You know
that romantic notion
that all the garbage
and the pain
is actually really healing
and beautiful
and sort of poetic?
It's not.
It's just garbage,
and it's pain.
You know what's better?
Love.
The day that you start thinking
that love is overrated
is the day that you are wrong
the only thing wrong
with love and faith
and belief...
Is not having it.
Woman: hey, they want to do
a conference call about the lucas scott galleys.
Okay, just, uh,
have them call my cell.
And then you should
take off. Thanks.
Hey, lindsey,
did you tell him?
No. Bye.
???
Hi, luke.
Just got
your dedication...and...
I guess I'm one
of those lost souls because...
I lied to you.
I said I was seeing someone,
and I wasn't.
The truth is...
I was afraid of the immensity
of your love, and I thought...
Well, I just wanted you to know.
You asked me if I Miss you.
Of course I Miss you.
That's all I do.
hi.
hi
They're supposed to call me
as soon as angie's home safe.
Where's peyton?
I don't know.
Probably at work.
I didn't tell her
angie was leaving for sure.
And you told me not to come
to the airport. Why?
I don't like you guys
to see me like this --
Vulnerable.
That's how I always see you,
brooke.
And I think
it's kind of beautiful.
You know, um...
I've been thinking about
all the things you've done for...
Angie and rachel
and me and...
All kinds of people.
You save people,
brooke davis.
It's what you do.
Thanks for letting me
share that.
You call me
when she's home safe, okay?
Hey, luke.
We've been through a lot --
Me and you.
I wouldn't have made it
through today
or a couple other days
without you.
So, thanks.
You're welcome.
This is for you.
I love you, lucas scott.
You know that?
I love you, too,
brooke davis.
Okay, come on, guys!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on, come on, come on!
Rick, where are your pants?!
Coffee accident.
Well, we can get them
at the break.
Jerry, we're gonna lead
with the ucla signing.
Where is it?
Right here.
All right.
Let's get it done.
You're all set.
I'm good.
I got the prompter.
Uh, you sure?
Watch and be amazed.
Okay, guys.
Countdown begins.
In 5, 4, 3, 2...
Cue music.
Go, camera one.
Graphic out.
And cue anchor.
Good evening.
I'm rick hunter.
And this is
the channel 11 evening news.
It's national letter of intent day
for big-time college basketball programs.
Aneve gold is here with news
of a local signing. Steve.
That's right, rick,
big news out of masonboro,
where local phenom shane dorset
has committed????on the west coast at ucla.
Could have been you.
Obviously the local poweouses are disappointed,
but dorset cited
ucla's once-proud legacy --
What's that?
The prompter's down.
Uh, go to rick.
I-I don't think
you want to do that.
Uh, have him fill.
Steve, fill.
Um, as many of you know,
ucla's mascot is a bruin,
um, which is
kind of a cute bear.
Oh, for god's sake!
Where's the prompter?!
It's not up yet.
Bill: should we
go to commercial?
All right,
say exactly what I say.
Dorsetited
ucla's legacy.
Just look at the camera and say,
"dorset cited
ucla's legacy."
Dorset cited ucla's legacy.
The bruins have 11 men's ncaa basketball championships...
...which is more than any other school.
...which is more???
They won seven consecutive titles from 1966o 1974.
They won seven consecutive titles from 1966 to 1974...
A streak that was broken
by north carolina state
in one of the greatest
final-four ges of all time.
Of course,
sports fans may remember
the last big area signing
was tree hill's nathan scott,
who played locally at
tree hill high, gilmore college,
and was ultimate a first-team all-american
at the university of maryland.
...and ultimately
was a first-team all-american...
We'll be back after this.
I'm -- say your name.
I'm say your name.
And we're out.
Thank you.
And for my encore...
I quit.
And it's the same guy
that said he knew ellie.
Oh, mia,
if you see him tonight,
can you have him call me?
Hey, I got to go, okay?
bye.
I don't hate you.
I remember the first time
I ever saw you...
All skinny arms and...
Tanglemess of hair.
It was hard letting you go,
peyton.
You know, it...
It was hard losing you, peyton
and it was hard
seeing you again.
And it's...still...
Really hard.
I know.
While I'm asleep,
I have this dream where...
We're back
in that hotel room in l.a.,
and you proposed to me.
And every single time,
I say yes.
It's just a dream, right?
It's my dream.
I'm sorry. He...
They did all they could.
I'd like to send flowers.
Well, if you want to leave
your name and number...
My name is dancott,
and my number is 1.
Come on, nate.
Nba'a pipe dream, boy.
You might as well
give it on up.
Come on, dad.
You can  it.
My god.
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
I just...
I can do this.
I'm gonna do this.
Oh, got it.
Here you go.
Let me give you
a hand here.
There you go.
You folks be careful.
You could get yourself
killed out here.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
Look, I'm at the airport,
and I've got two tickets
to las vegas.
Do you want to
get married tonight?
season 6 returns in september
welcome to www.1000fr.com