Uh, are these
the pages from my book?
The "comet,"
not "ravens,"
And i cannot be held
accountable, 'cause baby and me
Have gone completely
bed-Rest stir crazy.
What?
Oh.
Great.
I've got permanent bed head,
and you're laughg at me.
Look, i'm - I'm sorry.
I know how hard it is
being cooped up in the house.
"Hard"?
I haveead this month's issue
of b. Davis magazine
Cover to cover
five times.
Just stay and tell me stories
about life on the outside.
I can't.
I'm working on something.
Why have you been so weird
lately?
You're, like, off in the garage,
and yo-
You're making me a present.
Are you making
the baby a present?
Is it a present for me
and the baby?
All right.
Uh, y-You know what?
You're right.
Well, yeah, i'm right,
so just stay and let me guess.
No, no. I mean, you're right.
You're going completely crazy.
Crazy people
should not be left alone.
Funny. I thought vampires
didn't photograph.
Oh.
Sam, remind me to buy you
a garlic necklace.
Good morning, brooke.
Being dramatic, as usual.
I'm not being dramatic.
I'm being a mom.
And that means keeping sam
out of harm's way.
Ah, so i guess i'm "harm."
No. You're "harm's" older,
decrepit sister,
"Emotional damage."
Sam: okay.
We bought you caffeine,
so play nice.
Thank you.
What are you up to?
Nothing.
I like samantha.
She's plucky and dark.
She's going through
a really hard time.
Yeah, i know about jack.
Not just jack.
Sam wants a family.
She is vulnerable, and i don't
want her latching onto you
Just so that you can end up
disappointing her.
I don't intend
to disappoint her.
You never do.
Hi.
Well, hurry along.
We don't tip.
Do you have to be
such a bitch?
I'm wrong when i'm nice. I'm wrong when
i'm mean. I just can't win with you.
No, you can't,
so please stop trying.
I told you, this relationship
is about business,
And that includes sam.
Haley: knock, knock.
Brought you this month's issue
of b. Davis magazine.
Our ceiling fan
does 147 rotations a minute.
Well, that answers my question
about how mama's doing.
How's baby?
Baby is kicking
baby-Growing ass.
The doctor says
we're doing good.
Good. That's what auntie haley
likes to hear.
Good job in there, kiddo.
So, i got an interesting call
from the label this morning.
Oh, let me guess - They want
mia's album like last week,
Which, by the way,
is gonna be fantastic,
Which is unbiased,
even though i am the producer.
Okay.
Call wasn't about mia.
They want to buy
one of your songs.
I guess they have an artist
that heard it
And fell in love with it
and blah, blah, blah.
I never thought about
selling my songs.
Okay, well, from the way
they were raving about you,
You might want
to start thinking about it.
I'll come off the bench.
Hey,
i'll do whatever it takes.
I just want
back on the team.
Devon...
coach.
...you know how
this league works.
There is always someone
right behind you
Ready to do
whatever it takes.
The roster's full.
I am sorry.
Hey, scott.
You're here early.
I'm meeting nino.
We're just gonna run through
some drills before practice.
Good.
Glad to hear that.
You know, you two
have been playing together
Really well
these last weeks.
Thanks.
And i'm not the only one
who's noticed.
Been getting some calls
about you -
Scouts.
Yeah.
Now,
there's nothing concrete yet,
But as i know more,
you'll know more.
Nice work, nathan.
Thanks.
What are you shredding?
Nothing.
Junk mail.
Well,
you have two choices.
You get me the fabric on time,
at cost,
Or your "little start-Up company
that could" - It won't.
What now?
It's the new line.
It's - It's so good.
Fresh.
Some of your best work.
But you've always been
a talented girl, brooke.
Thank you.
Now, would you stop threatening
our suppliers?
It's tacky.
Well,
nice chip at the wall.
Who says i'm trying
to chip the wall?
My daughter
seems sad lately.
What gave her away -
The "kick me, i'm sad" sign
on h prada?
No, it's her designs.
They're so good.
And she built a fashion empire
on a broken heart,
So who's the boy?
Julian.
Cliffsnotes version -
Boy meets girl,
Girl falls crazy in love,
can't admit it,
Boy moves away,
asks girl to come,
Girl says no.
And girl buries herself
in work.
I've read this book before.
I hear bonding.
Back away from the innocent,
victoria.
So, haley still has
to put her mojo on it,
But whato you think?
I love it.
And i love chase for inspiring
the hell out of you lately.
Well, let's just say good
kissing inspires good music.
Yeah,
he is a good kisser.
I mean, that one tiny,
little, inconsequential,
Hardly memorable time
that i kissed him, you know?
You too?
It was twice.
I mean, honey,
It was only to make lucas
and brooke jealous.
Great.
I'm still trying to forget
that he kissed brooke.
B.T.W.,
not going so well.
Honey, why are you so worried
about the kissing part?
I mean, i thought you'd be
more concerned
With the virginity part.
The what part?
And you didn't know that.
So, uncle skills,
it's been a month,
And you still haven't talked
to miss lauren.
Hey, ask her
to the danceonight.
I'm good.
Just trying
to hook a brother up.
Wait, so all you guys got dates
to the dance?
Andre: not me.
Q always said,
"don't bring sand to the beach."
Is the dance
at the beach?
What about you,
j. Luke?
Hey, guys!
Hey, madison.
Hey, jamie.
Madison, you're late.
One lap around the park.
Go.
I bet jamie's
gonna ask madison.
No, i'm not.
Chuck, andre, no teasing.
One lap around the park. Go.
I thought you were
feeling madison.
Well, i'm not gonna be the only
guy at the dance with a date.
Besides, you said all women
are no good.
No, i said nanny deb
was no good.
Is there anything
you don't remember?
Genius.
Who cares
what people think?
I mean,
you're a leader, right?
So if yowant to ask madison,
i say go for it.
My man.
Lucas: open your eyes.
Told you you had
one last graduation gift.
The cure?
Tonight in atlanta.
But i'm supposed to be leaving
for l.A. Today with brooke.
Yeah, i know,
but brooke and chase
Are having their own...
extended goodbye.
Brooke says you can leave
in the morning.
I mean,
unless you don't want to go.
No, no, no, no, no!
I'm going.
And you are gonna get into
a hell of a lot more
Than a concert
with these tickets.
So,
what do you got for me?
Congratulations, nathan.
You got an offer.
From the nba?
It's from a european team,
???
And it's a two-Year deal.
Wait. Europe?
Nathan,
a lot of really good players
Are leaving the nba
to go to europe.
Great.
Give me one of their spots.
Look, i know that this is not
the offer that you were expecting.
But this is still a good offer
from a good team.
Well,
when do they need to know?
They'll move on
another choice tomorrow.
How lame is my life
That my only friends are a
5- Year-Old and my foster granny?
Language, samantha.
Brooke would totally freak if she
knew i was hanging out with you.
Well,
you're a young lady.
You need to look like
a young lady.
Language, victoria.
And as for brooke,
She'll learn she can't pick
her daughter's friends.
That's a lesson i like to call
"the peyton sawyer debacle."
Oh, um,
i can't go in here.
Salesperson
kind of hates me.
Since when?
Since the salesperson
caught me shoplifting.
You got caught
shoplifting?
Do you know how much
clothes over bros lost
In profit last year
because of shoplifting?
Millions.
It's why those prices that
you're always complaining about
Are so high.
Okay.
You are a member
of this family now.
Theft is common.
We don't do common.
Okay.
I don't do it anymore.
Well,
why did you do it at all?
I don't know.
I guess i got a high from it.
Well,
find another way to get high.
Okay, your words.
And as for this salesperson,
If she wants you out,
she'll have to deal with me.
Let's go.
Nice day for carrot sticks,
huh?
Speaking of the dance,
want to go with me?
I'm sorry, jamie.
Chuck just asked me.
Chuck?
Chuck.
Did you know that chase
lost his virginity to brooke?
Yes.
And i'm guessing
from the look on your face,
You did not know that.
Well,
welcome to tree hill.
I challenge you
to find a boy
That did not lose his virginity
to brooke davis.
But she's brooke davis.
And you're mia catalano.
And you're mia catalano,
and i'm getting off this train.
I just feel stupid -
Like, everyone knew but me.
All right,
i can relate to you.
Nathan lost his virginity
to my sister.
Wow, you win.
Look, i know the way chase
lookat you.
He probably didn't tell you
Because he's not thinking about
anybody but you.
Now, chop-Chop.
Let's make a record.
I am
a high-School graduate,
And i can't read
a freakin' map.
Look, atlanta's
just a straight shot down 74,
To 95, to 20, to 75,
to 85- 6 hours.
Show-Off.
You too.
And maybe if you
would have studied more
Instea ???
No way.
I got an a-Plus in backseat.
So, you're the only one
with one more graduation gift.
And i was gonna wait
to tell you till i got to l.A.
In case you freaked out,
but...
I sent copies
of "unkindness of ravens"
To a bunch of publishers
in new york.
You thudded me.
Payback.
And right now, there's
some stuffy old publisher
Reading your words
and falling in love with them.
And he's gonna buy them,
And he's gonna fly you
to new york
And make you very,
very famous.
Thank you
for doing that.
I mean, i wanted to,
but i just...
You were afraid.
Yeah.
I know.
But someone once told me
your art matters,
And i wonder who that was.
I don't know
Off that easy with just a thank-You,
either. And you're not gonna get
I mean, when they turn your
brilliant novel into a movie,
You are gonna have to cast,
Like, a hot, rockin' body,
kick-Ass p. Sawyer.
Yeah,
only if i can play lucas.
Oh!
So, this julian -
Where is he?
Los angeles, and i really think
she wanted to go.
I know i did.
It was the closest
i've ever come to a real family.
I'm sorry
she didn't think of you.
My daughter
can be quite selfish.
Hey, no bagging on brooke.
I told you.
It's my "friendship
with the devil" deal-Breaker.
Really?
You're following us?
I know everything about retail
and who you should be watching,
And it is not us.
It's actually
that girl over there
About to sff that clutch
into her knockoff.
As for samantha...
Sorry about
the shoplifting thing.
It...won't happen again.
Satisfied?
Now you can go back
To being completely and utterly
incompetent at your job.
Why are you such a bitch?
This bitch
just defended you.
A thank-You would be nice.
Thank you.
Now, why are you such a bitch?
Maybe i get a high
from it.
You know what?
I stopped shoplifting.
Maybe you could stop
being so mean.
Brooke:
i said no bonding.
I told victoria to keep her
old-Lady talons away from sam,
And then there they were,
Having a freakin'
tree hill shopping-Palooza.
Look at her face.
She's so smug.
I just want to throw
that magazine across the room.
Okay, um, maybe it is because
i'm hormonal,
Or maybe it's because i've been locked in this room
for so long,
I have completely lost touch
with reality,
But is it the worst thing
in the world
For momzilla
to be nice to sam?
Yes
Okay, what if she hated her?
Wouldn't that be worse?
Yes, but...
...she never
took me shopping.
Am i interrupting?
No, just looking at who i can
pull up to take your place.
Devon.
Did you come here
to talk to me about devon
Or the european offer?
Both, actually.
But first,
i need to ask you a question.
Okay.
Do you think i'm good enough
to make it to the nba?
Are you good enough?
Yes, nathan,
you're good enough.
But it takes more
than talent.
It takes
timing and luck.
Look, you have an offer
on the table,
And a two-Year contract
to play professional ball
Does not come often.
So you think
i should take it.
Yes, i do.
Yeah, no,
that's really great.
I think that adjustment
helps a lo
Cool.
Sounded good to me.
Sorry to interrupt.
The recording light wasn't on,
so i thought i'd just come in.
You're nick lachey.
And you're mia catalano.
See? I told you.
So, what's a guy got to do
to get your song on his album?
Um, wow.
When the label said
they had an artist
Who was interested in recording
one of my songs, i really -
Didn't picture me.
Yeah, at all.
Nick lachey.
You really love using first
and last names.
It's a tree hill thing.
Sorry, nick lachey.
Okay, just go.
Bye.
So,
what are the magic words?
'Cause i really want you
to say yes.
Your song is great,
and trust me -
I've listened to a lot
of new songs for this album.
Yeah, i'm - I'm sorry.
It's just that
"all in my head"
Wasn't supposed to be
one of them.
Just screwed up.
I'm glad they did.
I really am flattered that
you came all the way out here,
But there are no
magic words.
The answer is just no.
What if i told you
i had a really rough flight?
Standby.
Middle seat.
Coach.
I'm sorry.
I'm just not interested
in selling my music.
Oh, but would you sign this
for my son?
He's a big fan.
His name's jamie.
Peyton: can you believe
that nathan and haley
Are married with a baby?
Yeah.
I think they were ready
to get married and have a baby
On their second date.
I think they did.
I really hate that i'm gonna
miss jamie getting bigger.
I mean, by the time
i come home to visit,
He's already gonna be
walking and talking.
Nah,
with nathan and haley,
He'll be reading
and dribbling first.
They are gonna be
amazing parents.
And you are gonna be
an amazing mom.
You should have that
one day.
And you will.
What's chuck got
that i don't?
Better timing,
a date with madison.
I don't get it.
I thought me and madison
had an unspoken connection.
Look, nothing is unspoken
with women.
Now, you can't let this thing
with madison
Ruin the dance tonight.
It's not,
'cause i'm not going.
Jamie, you got to go
to your first dance, man.
I mean,
what happens at your first dance
Becomes the building block
of the rep
That'll follow you
all the way through school.
Me?
My first dance?
I walked in "antwon,"
but i left "skills."
So, what? You st gonna sit
onhis couch?
You sit around
poing about nanny deb.
I'm gonna sit around
and pout about madison.
Cool.
You want to roll like i roll?
Then i'm going to the dance...
now.
Oh, man.
This is killing me.
At least the punch
is good.
My wife
just had a little girl.
I told myself i'd be called up
by the time she got here.
I'm sorry about what happened,
man.
It ain't your fault.
And i wanted
to tell you that.
All me.
So,
what are you gonna do now?
Work harder.
Try and get picked up
and...
If i do...
...i'm gonna do things
differently.
Funny thing is, um...
I told you ???
But i should have been
telling myself that.
'Cause you only get one.
Sam?
Well, the broom's
not parked outside,
So i guess victoria's not here,
either.
Maybe i'll do some filing.
Oh...my...god.
Thank you.
What?
It amazes me
how much you can eat.
It's kind of like
you're eating for two.
Are you eating for two?
Trust me, this will be
just the tip of the iceberg
When i'm pregnant.
And either way,
you said it was our last hurrah,
So how can that
not include
Stopping for
"world's best pie"?
Which, by the way, how do you
think they determine that?
Well,
i'm - I'm sure they do studies.
Damn good last-Hurrah pie.
The way i see it is,
As soon as that car pulls out
for l.A. Tomorrow,
I'm officially an adult,
Which means
no more being spontaneous,
No more shoveling pie.
Well, if this really is our last
hurrah, how about we, uh...
Go out in style?
We can't.
Are you serious?
Oh, yeah.
Dine and dash.
I dare you.
I will see you
on the outside.
There's an extra $5
in it
If you run out behind me
screaming.
Woman: no, no, no!
I can't believe
we just did that!
No, no!
What are you doing?!
Dances suck, huh?
Want to get out of here
and get some ice cream?
Sorry, bro.
I met someone.
Antwon:
aw, come on, now.
There's a lot of girls out there
you could be having fun with.
Why do i have to try?
You're not.
It's not the same thing.
I know you like her.
I think you're chicken.
I am not.
Look, i'm not scared.
Prove it.
Hey, you're home.
You missed jamie on his way
to the dance.
He was so cute
in his little suit!
Looked like
a little lucas.
What's going on?
I got an offer to play...
in europe.
And i don't know, hales,
maybe we should...consider it.
It's good money.
It's a two-Year contract.
But you want to play
in the nba.
I know, but so does
every other person on my team
And every other player
in the "b" league.
Okay, um...
All right, let's say that
you take this two-Year contract
And then the nba
comes calling.
What if i don't take it
and then they never call?
I mean, i've been working
on this...
Comeback
for a long time now,
And maybe
this is my chance
And i'm just too focused on the
fantasy of the nba to notice.
It's not a fantasy.
That's your dream.
There's nothing wrong
with pursuing it.
To what end?
I don't know.
But whatever you decide,
You have a wife and a son
who love you,
And we're behind you 100%.
Thanks.
Yeah.
What do you call this
again?
The chaser.
Really?
'Cause it tastes just like
a bad long island iced tea.
Why didn't you tell me you lost
your virginity to broo davis?
I didn't.
Why,
did she say i was a virgin?
Nice.
Peyton told me,
but it should have been you.
The losing-Virginity topic
Really isn't something a guy
likes to bring up to his girl.
Or himself.
But, then again, your premiere
starred brooke davis.
Stay out of it,
nick lachey.
So, what's brooke been up to,
anyway?
You have really out-Bitched
yourself this time, victoria.
Explain.
Or no.
Don't explain.
I'm sure it'll just be
more of the same
Self-Serving,
manipulative b.S.
Oh, just stop the histrionics.
We could lose samantha.
"We"?
She is not yours to lose.
Samantha and i
have gotten very close,
And that woman gave her up.
She made her mistakes
a long time ago,
And it's a little late
to try to show up now.
I'm sorry.
Are you kidding,
or am i being punked?
This is different.
I never abandoned you.
Not physically.
And maybe that's worse.
You think i'm so bad.
I destroyed those letters
for you, brooke.
I see how much samantha
means to you.
No.
Don't do that.
You have never done
anything for me.
This is about you
trying to have
Some half-Assed do-Over
with sam
Because you screwed up
so completely with me,
And it is so obvious
and so damn pathetic!
Just stop!
And you never
took me shopping.
Okay, wait.
Just hear me out.
You're just in time.
For what?
I have
the instrumental track
For "all in my head"
cued up.
Go sing.
Now?
Hey, joe perry said,
"let the music do the talking."
An aerosmith reference.
I knew i liked you.
I turned down the offer.
Yeah, i know.
I just got off the phone
with the scout.
Nathan, i -
I'm going to the nba,
bobby.
I was going to say
That the european league
missed out on a great player.
I hope the nba doesn't.
Thank you.
Oh, and i want you to know
i told the scout about devon.
He's a good player.
He just made a mistake,
And that doesn't mean he
shouldn't get a second chance.
I told the scout
the same thing.
I'll see you in practice
tomorrow, scott.
I'll see you at practice.
Antwon "skills" taylor
crashing a 5-Year-Olds' dance?
I was hoping to see you.
I wanted to ask you out, but i
was kind of hesitant because...
I just got out
of a relationship.
Me too.
Bad break-Up.
It broke my heart.
So i guess
neither one of us
Should really be dating
right now, huh?
Probably not.
So, you want to dance?
No.
But i could go
for some rebound s-E-X.
I'm kidding.
A dance would be nice.
It was good.
It was great -
The song, i mean.
I know.
Okay,
i'll let you record it.
One condition -
I want to produce.
Hey.
Sorry i've been sneaking around
with your mom.
It's just...
she's not that bad
Once you get past
the royal bitch of it all.
No, she's worse.
You know, she'd really like
another chance.
Sam...
I have a letter for you...
...from your birth mother.
I guess she's been sending them
to the store,
Hoping that i could help her
get in touch with you,
And somehow they ended up
in junk mail.
Yeah, i don't want it.
Sam.
No, she gave me up.
She doesn't want me, right?
What does she want now?
To say she's sorry?
Maybe.
Well, then,
she should have said it.
Every time i sat there
in that coffee shop
Right in front of her...
She didn't even know
that was her own daughter.
So, screw her
and her "i'm sorrys"
Because all that ever got me
was a sucky life.
And there's nothing
she could say to fix that.
Samantha, you've been going
to that coffee shop for months.
You must want something
from her,
E- Even if
it's just closure.
Yeah. Okay.
How about why?
Why wasn't i good enough?
Why didn't she love me
enough?
Why could she just
throw me away?
Maybe...
Maybe she wants
to tell you
Why giving you up
was the hardest thing
That she ever had to do.
Sweetheart,
i have no idea how you feel.
Even on her worst day,
victoria never gave me away,
But if you
want to know why,
She's the only person
who can answer that for you.
I should have told you
about brooke.
Did you love her?
Thought i did.
That's before
i fell in love with you.
???
Really?
I'm sorry i hosed you,
man.
She's waiting for you
over there.
No.
Hello?
This is he.
Yes, sir.
A tryout.
All right, thank you.
Babe...a tryout!
Oh, god.
What if i just gave away
my last chance?
Your chance is coming,
baby.
I really believe that.
I'm gonna be right here.
It's okay.
Peyton.
Hi!
Close your eyes.
I knew you had a surprise
for me.
Open your eyes.
Where did you find this?
It's the best concert
we never went to.
I still can't believe
You pretended to like the cure
all those years.
I never said
i loved the cure.
I said i loved kissing you
to the cure.
This was one of the best days
of my life.
Really good pie.
We had our whole lives
in front of us.
Hey.
We still do.
I know.
Well,
the cure is playing.
Where's my kissing?
I can't believe i kept
those tickets for six months...
...and i lost them
in six hours.
You know what?
Maybe we can just go back
to the doorman
And explain
that we really did have two.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm kind of thinking he's
probably heard that one before.
I'm sorry
about the concert.
Who goes
to a sold-Out show anyway?
And besides, i only have
one last night with you.
Unless you show up tomorrow
with, like, another surprise.
If that's what it takes
to keep you from leaving.
I'm gonna miss you.
You better...
'Cause i have a lot of dreams
wrapped up in you.
And it's kind of hard
to have a happily ever after
All by yourself.
And we're gonna have that,
lucas.
We are gonna get married,
And we're gonna make
a lot of babies
In the backseat
of this car.
I promise.
And i always keep
my promises.
Good...
'Cause i'm gonna
hold you to it.
ææàãğü×öä»×é
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
»¶ó­¼óèë