Previously on "one Tree Hill"...
You were at that party that night,
and you got pregnant.
But you didn't have sex
with Nathan Scott, did you?
No.
He says she's dropping everything.
Maybe we need a vacation.
The Bahamas?
Tree Hill.
It's almost morning. I should go.
Or, uh...
you could stay.
Administrative work is
for fatties, Millicent,
and you are not a fatty.
You...
are a plus-size model.
Honey, I'm home. Let's do this.
I told you it was realistic.
Hey, honey. Alex and I
worked everything out.
Isn't that great?
Hey.
Uh-oh... the look,
followed by the pout.
I just missed you next
to me last night... again.
I know, baby.
Alex and I didn't
finish until 4:00 a.m.
I know. I watched her
leave on my sneaky-slut cam.
I'm sorry.
I'm really trying to be
super-evolved girlfriend,
but it's hard for me
when my boyfriend
spends all of his nights
writing an epic love story
with naked-actress girl.
She's not naked.
She's always naked in my mind.
P.S.... not a good time
to insert obvious
girl-on-girl humor.
Hey.
I love you.
And I know me working with
Alex has been really hard.
Excruciating.
And I appreciate how
understanding you've been.
But here's some good news.
I think we're finally gonna
finish the script today.
"Finish" as in "done"?
As in "no more late
nights with Alex"?
And lots of late nights
with the most beautiful girl I know.
They're offering two
years. I say no deal.
It's not bad.
It's B.S.
Look at your numbers
last season, man.
I mean, all the team is trying to do
is take advantage of the
bad press around Renee.
Okay, so, right now,
her lie is making my
name less valuable.
But not your game.
That's why we're countering.
I'm gonna ask for four
years. We'll take three.
They offered two,
and we ask for four?
It's how the game is played, Nate.
You're sure they won't stop playing?
Buddy, trust me.
They won't.
Just let me do my job.
All right.
It's my job to look good, bitch.
Mils, you've been raping
my closet for two weeks.
You should be wearing
C.O.B., not... M-E.
I've been seen in all my C.O.B.
clothes.
What about the new stuff?
That dress ball and chain
Brooke was working on
would be the shiz on you.
I know, but Brooke
isn't done with it yet,
not to mention super
uber-assistant Calliope
is guarding it like
a virgin's vajayjay.
And since all my old
clothes are so Millie 1.0,
your closet is my only
high-rnd alternative.
Oh, my God. I'm so sleepy,
and you're so talky.
Sorry. Still wired.
Late night, major party...
you totally missed it.
Doubt it.
The party scene is so lame-tarded.
It's the same people,
same paparazzi, same porn.
Porn?
In the VIP's VIP it's way overrated.
You know, I'm starting to
like just hanging with Julian
and working on stuff
people take seriously
other than my tight ass.
O.M. Gucci!
Score me some of what you've
been taking, you skinny bitch.
You totally look
better than me in that.
Really?
Take it off.
Wow. That good?
Hmm.
Good God.
Millie!
"Haley James Scott,
tonight at 8:00"...
And I can't even
utter the last part.
Free. The concert is free.
One more time, and I will
wash your mouth out with soap.
Please explain how
this impromptu concert
is getting your album
completed on shedule.
Only if you explain to me
the deal with "shedule."
Come on, Miranda, I just
wanted to get out of the studio
and, you know, get some
feedback on my new songs.
You'll get feedback in 2 1/2 months,
when the record is done and the
downloads are making the label money.
And then you'll be "free" to perform
at any label-authorized concert.
In the meantime, this one...
is off.
Okay, but you're gonna
have to tell them.
Go on. I'll hold the door open.
Well, Americans will line
up for anything that's free.
Look, we're not talking about
a rookie getting his feet wet.
This is Nathan Scott.
Just look at his numbers,
and I think you'll understand
why we feel that he's
earned a four-year deal.
Yeah.
Or we might consider a three-year
if the price is right,
but a two is not
gonna get us anywhere.
I hope so.
Mmm. Thanks.
Best part of my day.
Me or the coffee?
Maybe a little bit of both.
So, any good news?
Uh, we'll see.
Now I just have to wait.
Mm. How would you feel
about waiting with me?
Come on. I have somewhere
I want to take you.
Grab your office.
It's good to be home.
So, this is your
dirty little secret?
Yeah... I've been helping out here
every saturday for
a couple of hours.
Hales and I used to do it
in high school, you know...
hippie parents, raised to
give back. Hi, miss Quinn!
Hi.
I guess I kind of missed it.
Hey, you let me in. I
just wanted to let you in.
Hey, Miss Quinn.
Hi.
Wow.
Great spiral, great listener,
and now this hot
Mother Teresa thing?
You know, in girl world, you
just called me hot, right?
In an old-nun sort of way.
Oh, okay, yeah.
So, what exactly do you
do here, sister Quinn?
Well...
we make these homemade cameras,
and then we take pictures with them.
You know, the first time
I looked through my lens,
I realized that I could find
magic in unexpected places.
And I want the kids to feel that.
Pretty dorky, huh?
Completely dorky, yeah.
I love it.
Mm. It's just a sample.
It's top-secret C.O.B.
for next March.
I just finished it today.
Here is your super-sassy
rock-star comeback outfit.
I want you to look
so amazing up there.
I mean, you could just let me
wear this one to my show tonight.
I could,
but then I'd have to kill you.
And if you're dead, we can't talk.
And.. .I really need a huge
Haley heart-to-heart right now.
All righty.
Spill.
I think I'm pregnant.
I'm late, and I am never
late. And I'm freaking out.
Why are you freaking out?
You've wanted a baby
since you were 22.
Because I don't know how
Julian's gonna take it.
The last time we
talked about our future,
he basically said "what's the rush?"
I am fluent in boy,
and I am pretty sure
That "what's the rush?" Doesn't
mean "let's have a baby now."
Maybe not, but things
happen all the time...
Unexpected things that turn
out to be amazing things.
I named mine Jamie.
Yeah, but with all the Alex drama,
I just wouldn't want him to
think that I was expecting it.
Oh, Brooke, Julian's not gonna
think you got pregnant on purpose.
Come on, Hales, you have to admit
The timing looks a bit suspect.
No. You know what? Julian loves you.
Stop worrying. Go to the doctor.
It's your turn to be the girl
who gets the baby and the boy.
So, the girl doesn't get the boy.
No. That's what makes
the ending work.
She doesn't need the boy anymore.
Says the boy.
Not that you're the boy... jst a boy
who doesn't get that some
sad girl with bad hair
doesn't want to spend
money on a movie
where the girl doesn't get the boy.
It's not American.
The ending is perfect as is.
Trust me.
Now, a little drumroll, please.
And we're done. That's it.
Fade out. Hit "print."
What about all your
annoyingly good notes?
You did them all.
You've been so focused
these past few weeks.
Now it's just time to kick
the script out of the nest,
see if it can fly.
My dad used to say that.
So, what's next, then, Mr. Producer?
Well, I'll just put out some
feelers, make a few calls,
see if anyone responds
to the material.
Which is, like, a no-brainer.
This script is the bomb.
I'll be sure to lead with that.
Good.
And I'll work on scoring
production offices
with expensive water
and a snobby temp.
We'll be so legit.
Whoa. We got to still
sell the script.
That could take months.
So we won't be seeing each
other every day anymore?
No, ma'am.
You are officially off duty.
Oh.
Sweet.
You have no new messages.
Nice shot.
You got another one of those?
You're good.
You got an agent?
Don't need your charity
today, all right?
So, you staring, or you playing?
Playing.
Hello, Nathan.
It's grandpa Dan.
I saw it on the security cam.
Jamie...
Grandpa Dan!
Hey, there, buddy.
Oh, warm welcome.
Nathan,
you remember my wife, Rachel.
Yes.
Of course.
Well, when you and deb are
tired of my high-School class,
I'm sure I could rummage
Through some of my old
middle-School friends for you.
It's good to see you, too, Nathan.
It's funny... I used to
want you to be my daddy.
And now I'm your mommy.
Nice to meet you, grandma Rachel.
Aww.
I remember when you were
a rumor in third period.
Dad, can I show grandpa
Dan my new room?
Yes. Yes, of course you can, son.
I haven't seen you
around here before.
First time... helping out a friend.
Yeah, I saw you with
the camera lady.
She your girl?
No.
Why not? She's pretty.
You got a lot of questions.
My turn. You got a name?
Nope.
I know what you're doing...
you're letting the poor kid win.
That's what you all do...
show up, volunteer for a few hours,
make yourselves feel
good about whatever.
So, what's your thing?
You a bad dad or something?
I lost my wife a few years back.
What was her name?
Sara.
My mom died, too.
Do you want to talk about it?
What's that gonna do?
I used to think the same thing.
I had a bunch of memories of her,
my own secrets.
And I thought that if I talked
about her with anyone else
that those memories would go away.
I wouldn't have our secrets anymore,
and maybe I'd start to forget.
And did you? Forget?
Not one thing.
Sometimes I feel like
she's still here with me.
She is.
She always will be.
Moms are special that way.
Brooke Davis.
You ready?
I've been ready.
Paul Norris.
Hey, dad. It's me.
Julian.
It's good to hear from
you, son. How are you?
How's Brooke?
She's good. We're good.
I'm happy to hear that.
So, I've been working.
And I found a script
that I really like.
I'm thinking about sending it out.
Ah. Kick it out of the nest.
See if it can fly.
I think you said to me about a
thousand times when I was a kid.
So, dad, listen, I, um...
I wanted to see if you'd
want to produce it with me.
I mean, it's nothing
huge. It's an indie.
But... it's about second chances.
And...
I don't know...
it made me think of us.
I'd like that, son.
Very much.
This is some collection.
Look at this one... Jerry Rice.
Whoa!
I got it for my birthday.
I'm 7 now.
I know.
I'm sorry I missed that.
I'm sorry I missed a lot of
things over this past year.
I forgive you.
I always hoped you were watching.
I never missed it. I
pretended like you never left.
I like that big clock
thing that hangs behind you,
'cause it means you're okay,
even if you're still sick.
I'm glad you're home again.
Me too, buddy.
Surprise!
Rachel.
Uh, what are you doing here?
Waiting for a hello hug
from my favorite boy!
Miss Davis.
I'm... sorry, but the
test came back negative.
E... excuse me?
You're not pregnant.
So, you and mom went to high
school with grandma Rachel?
Were you friends?
Um, I'm not really sure grandma
Rachel was friends with anyone.
Like grandpa Dan?
I'm glad they have each other.
Yeah.
They're a perfect match.
Dad...
I have a secret.
Sometimes I watch grandpa Dan on tv.
I know I'm not supposed to.
I'm sorry.
No, Jamie, it's okay. I
knew you were watching.
And it's okay for you to miss him.
He loves you.
He loves you, too. He
watched all the Bobcats games.
And... Jamie.
Dad, he's different now.
He helps people, like he
helped us with that lady
who was trying to hurt you and mom.
Yeah.
Well, there's things between
us you can't understand, Jamie.
I'm not a little kid anymore.
I understand a lot of things.
I know you do.
I wish you didn't have to.
Dad, it's only three
words... "I forgive you."
Shoot it.
Aw!
So, um...
How's life in L.A.?
It's great.
You can be anybody you want there.
And who are you?
Rachel Scott...
Dan's ex-screw-up of a wife
who has changed her life
with the positive
words of Dan Scott.
It's genius.
So, I guess Dan helped
you step into the light
and get yourself right.
Mm.
Dan helped me step into the light
and get myself a personal trainer,
a driver, and a black card.
Same Rachel, different city.
So, are we gonna talk about Brooke?
I mean, have you seen her?
No.
And I don't want to.
I know I messed up last time,
but she and Victoria
blackballed me in the industry.
Even after I got sober,
I couldn't get a gig.
Then I got unsober and ended
up shaking my ass on a pole.
I'm sorry that happened to you,
but none of it was Brooke's fault.
So, what... you're on her side?
You were her friend.
She went out on a limb for you,
and you repaid her
by stealing money.
So, yeah, I'm kind of on her side.
Go see her.
You owe her that.
I guess I was late
because of stress.
Julian, Alex, the new line...
It's okay.
It'll happen.
When you guys are ready,
it'll happen.
Brooke.
Hey.
You were so meant to be a mom.
You are gonna have a houseful
of very fashionably dressed
little Brooke Davises
running around.
You wait and see.
Yeah.
So, this is your cave?
Yeah, we can't all have
pimped-out beach houses
to hide in.
Says the woman whose cave is
in an nba player's mansion.
Touché.
But I'm thinking about getting back
to my artist roots, you know?
Crampy, old apartments with
character and creaky floors...
they make the best caves.
So you're staying in Tree Hill?
For a while.
You know, it's home. I like it here.
Plus, you know, the
company isn't horrible.
Beautiful.
It is.
This is what I love...
you know,
standing in the pitch black,
waiting for the smallest moment
to reveal itself right
before your eyes.
I have to take this.
I... hope it's what I want to hear.
Oh, you're super agent. It will be.
Hey.
Today?
Are we sure?
Yeah, that's great.
Just keep me posted.
Good news?
Just a rumor, but,
uh, yeah, I think so.
So, I should get going.
Yeah.
But I'll see you tonight
at Haley's concert?
Yeah, I'll see you tonight.
Okay.
Oh.
We're not working tonight, Alex.
I know,
but I just reread the script,
and it totally sucks ducks.
I mean, the main character
is total white noise.
She needs, like, a... a crack habit
or a... a brother with cancer...
something oscar-worthy.
The script is awesome.
Trust yourself. We did good work.
But I... I just... Good night, Alex.
I have plans with Brooke.
But...
I'm just...
never really good at being alone.
Come on. Stop it. Go live your life.
You're Alex Dupré.
Well, well. This is
quite the crowd, isn't it?
Yeah, I can't believe
all these people showed up
after so many years.
I know.
There is a lot of people
out there... just waiting.
Wow.
So... nervous?
'Cause I heard you get
a bit of stage fright.
Oh, no. Actually, I'm
not nervous at all.
I'm just looking forward
to getting back out there.
Really? Because I'd be nervous.
I mean, after all, if
the music's no good,
it'll be all over
Youtube by tomorrow.
And then you'll have to explain
to the label what you were thinking
when you put together this
premature little free concert
that could ruin any good buzz we
have about your up-and-coming album.
Ohh.
See? Now I'm nervous.
Break a leg.
That's funny... "leg" wasn't
my first option for you.
Live your life, Alex.
Mm.
Can I get another?
Hey, baby.
Hi.
I hope that's champagne
you just ordered,
'cause we're celebrating
tonight, remember?
Right... we're celebrating.
I'll be right back.
I told you I'm with Brooke tonight.
No games, Alex.
This isn't a game. I swear.
I found some coke in my suitcase.
What have you done?
Nothing... yet.
But I'm thinking about it.
I don't want to mess up.
Okay, look, calm down.
Please come.
Please.
Okay, just don't do
anything. I'm on my way, okay?
Okay.
What's up, bud? Hey.
I hope that grin means you
had a good day at the office.
I'm hearing good things.
That's awesome.
I don't think I could take
any more bad news today.
What's up?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. It's
just... it's family stuff.
All right.
Chase, my man, I'm in a good mood.
So I'm gonna have one of those
tasty blue brain blasters.
You could have told me they sucked.
Come on. Who said that?
They sucked, and you know it.
And that's why, from now on,
I'm officially just bar manager.
But who's gonna bring
me my shots and beers?
All right. Hey, Grubbs.
Guys, this is Grubbs,
my new bartender.
Clay here wants a drink.
What do you think?
Shot of tequila, chilled,
and a beer, imported.
No... hip domestic.
Nice.
Wow. That's pretty impressive.
Yeah, I know. That guy sucks.
Here.
Thanks, Grubbs.
Well... to you.
Thanks for all the hard work.
And here's to next season
not being a contract year.
Congrats, man.
Cheers.
Hey, Nate. Hey.
Clay. Hey, Quinn.
Oh, hey, check this out.
Grubbs, this is Quinn.
Hey.
She needs a drink.
White wine's gonna
make you both happy.
Wow. He's better than Zelda.
Hey! Oh, my gosh!
I've been gone a long time.
But, uh, I'm back. It feels good.
Anyway, I want to show you
guys some of my new songs.
And, uh... thanks for showing up.
I hope you like it.
What do you mean you're on
your way to Alex's hotel room?
Brooke, I'm sorry. She's in trouble.
And of course she called you.
Well, I didn't really have a choice.
She said she found some cocaine
and she thinks she may relapse.
I... I can't just leave her alone.
She sounded really bad.
She's an actress, Julian!
I'll hurry back. I promise.
Boo!
Hey. Where have you been?
I called, but you didn't answer.
I know. Sorry. I had to
drop by work for a sec.
You like?
You look great. But
you always looks great.
You always say that, Mouth.
You called me "Mouth."
You never call me "Mouth."
What the hell are you wearing?
It's great, Brooke. I love it.
You know that dress is not supposed
to be released until next summer,
so unless I magically
went to sleep for a year,
you need to explain to me
why you're wearing it tonight.
I thought it would be fine.
I mean, I'm the face of C.O.B.
Millicent Huxtable,
that dress needs to
leave this bar right now,
on or off you.
Your choice or your job.
Someone needs to chill out.
It's just a dress.
And there's no one
important in here, anyway.
"No one important"? What's
that supposed to mean?
I mean, it's Tric,
not the Music Awards.
Is that why you're taking pills...
so you can go look fab
at someplace important,
like the Music Awards?
You were going through my stuff?
Your stuff was all over the room.
And that's not what's
important here.
I'm worried about you.
Worried about what?
You're different...
Blowing Brooke off,
messing up at work,
partying all the time,
and now these pills.
So I took a few diet
pills to drop a few pounds.
So what?
Brooke hired you for who you are.
You don't have to change that.
I don't just have to please Brooke.
There's an entire industry.
It's a lot of pressure to fit in.
And for once, I want to fit in.
God, marvin, you told
me you supported me.
I wanted you to be a model
because it made you feel special.
And that's sweet and noble
and one of the reasons
why I love you.
But it's not that simple.
I wish it were, but it's not.
I'm sorry.
Stop saying you're sorry.
You're just the only
one I could call
who wouldn't want to do it with me
or report it to the tabloids.
What about your sponsor from rehab?
Rehab was for publicity.
My sponsor isn't good for anything
besides scoring the best blow.
The only time I stopped doing it
was when I started working with you.
I'm not trying to pressure you.
It's just the truth.
Well, I'll take it and go.
But I could just go
out and get more.
Would you?
I don't know.
Right now, I want it so bad.
Tonight was hard.
I didn't have anywhere to go.
It was so quiet in here.
And I hate myself when it's quiet.
Hey. Alex.
Hey.
You are so much more than you see.
The girl I've been working
with is bright and funny
and independent and
strong all by herself.
She doesn't need that stuff.
I wish I could see her.
Let's just get you
through tonight...
and hopefully you will.
The playbaounds great.
Playback? I recorded a little bit.
You know, I thought we could
"accidentally" leak a song,
get the fans excited for more.
This little concert was genius.
I'm so glad I thought of it.
Yeah, me too.
Studio tomorrow, bright and early.
Where are you headed?
Have you met Grubbs, the bartender?
He's kind of hot, in a...
dirty, "I'm gonna hate myself
in the morning" sort of way.
Ciao.
Hi. Oh, thank you.
You know, I could get
used to being the one
watching from the stands.
No, it's my job.
I'm not giving it up.
Oh. You were amazing, Hales.
Thank you.
When I was up there, I couldn't
stop thinking about how lucky we are
and how we just got
everything we dreamed of...
Jamie and how far we've come,
and it just feels like nothing
can get in the way of that anymore.
Why do we say things like that?
What?
Well, I didn't want to tell
you this before the show, but...
he is the healthiest-looking
dying man I have ever seen.
I guess evil does a body good.
It's everything I took
from you... plus interest.
Well.
Not that I have anything to say
to your thieving ass,
but you took a lot
more than money, Rachel.
And I'm trying to take
responsibility for that, Brooke.
You should, too.
I'm sorry. Is that hair
color seeping into your brain?
What in your twisted, little
head am I responsible for?
You left a envelope full
of money with a junkie.
Says the junkie.
True forgiveness is about
accepting our own fault in things.
You'd know that if
you watched the show.
Now, I have given you
an apology and a check,
and you've given me nothing.
But that's okay. I forgive...
Stay away from me, bitch.
Whiskey... straight up.
Hmm.
I'd have guessed blood.
Interesting choice
for the poster boy
of redemption and clean living.
I know I surprised you today.
I'm sorry about that.
You're always sorry, Dan.
So, why are you back?
What do you want?
A chance.
It's not gonna happen, Dan.
And I'm kind of thinking
you should cancel your
plane ride to ask Lucas, too.
You know, I'd hoped fixing
things between you and Renee
would help thaw the ice a bit.
So you did that for yourself.
No.
I did it for you.
Well, I already said "thank you."
You know...
there's never gonna be a
golden ticket back into my life.
I'll tolerate you for Jamie.
But you're dead to me.
The moment Keith died, you died.
It's like watching an antelope
at the watering hole
in the Serengeti.
This antelope hasn't hooked up
at the watering hole in weeks.
There's a nun that's
been hogging all my time.
Oh, excuse me. I guess I've
been messing up your game.
Eh, it's okay.
The game was getting old.
I thank you for today.
I'm glad that you got
me out of the house.
Those kids were good for me.
Yeah.
I know, right?
It's all about finding
magic in unexpected places.
Yeah.
So, did you get that
call you were waiting on?
Not yet.
But, you know, I've done
a lot of deals like this.
Silence is just one of their tools.
It'll work out.
I hope so.
Yeah.
Well, I should get going.
I have to be up early and bring
coffee to this friend of mine.
He kind of depends on me.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Quinn.
Who says tonight's over?
I just thought you'd be home by now.
Look, me too, but she's all alone.
So am I.
Brooke, you know I love you.
I just don't think I
should leave her yet.
She's...
I'm worried about her.
Well, I'm worried about us.
But you do what you've got to do.
I was stupid to think
he'd let me back in.
Baby, let's go back to L.A.
Let's leave these small
people and this small town.
This small town's the
closest thing we have to home.
And I'm not running from it anymore.
Neither should you.
Who says I'm running?
You are.
We both are.
And I'm not leaving until
I get what I came for.
What's that, Dan?
Redemption.
Come on. You totally can't see it?
Look closer.
I swear that there's
a face on the moon.
Oh, yeah. Look at that. It...
Wow. It's entirely
made of cheese, too.
Oh, yeah, and you totally suck.
And you totally crack me up.
And I... I haven't laughed
so hard in a long time.
You want to go for a swim?
Says the man that knows
I'm afraid of the water.
What if I'm afraid, too?
Okay, I'll play.
What are you afraid of?
To move on.
And to feel something
for someone now.
But I'm tired of being afraid. I...
There are so many reasons
that I shouldn't have done that.
But I've wanted to for so long.
Me too.
You can do it, Alex.
I know.
Wait.
I don't understand.
I do.
You've been lying all night.
Nice performance, Alex.
No, I wasn't lying. I swear.
Julian, please.
It was full.
Why can't you be the girl
who gets the boy and
the baby, Brooke Davis?
Hey.
You know that this thing with Dan...
It's gonna be okay, right?
He can't hurt us anymore.
Yeah, I know.
Good.
So, how about a little
special encore performance
for my sexy-ass husband?
Yeah?
Big news in the nba...
The Charlotte Bobcats
have opened up their checkbook
and capped themselves out,
acquiring Derek McDaniel in
a hush-hush deal late today.
That's bad news for
local star Nathan Scott,
who is going to have to find
a spot elsewhere, if at all.