???
??????
Lucas: lindsey.
She's the first thing
i think about every day.
"How is she?"
"Does she miss me
like i miss her?"
"How do i get her back?"
And then another day
without her begins.
Peyton: lucas.
Jamie: chester.
Brooke.
Oh, my god.
I have to pee.
Skills: what day is it?
What time is it?
What the hell
did i drink last night?
Marvin: "mmm, millicent...
you smell so good."
"I have to go to work."
"Sure, i guess
i can be a little late."
"What do you mean i'm fired?
I wasn't even that late!"
"How am i gonna pay my rent?"
"Would you like fries
with that, sir?"
Jamie.
God my girl is up
Morning.
Morning
You know,
i'm hungry this morning.
I am starving.
Dan: keith.
Smells good in here.
Haley: yeah, i made
some french toast.
Nice.
It's totally good,
daddy.
It's totally good.
That's not what i meant,
but that ss good,
Good morning.
What's your day like?
Mostly just playing.
My day's not bad either.
I'm just gonna finish
grading these papers
And then go over to see peyton
for a little bit,
And then you and i have
to interview the n-A-N-N-I-E-S.
I hate it when you spell.
Don't say, "hate."
Sorry.
I just think it's d-U-M.
Wow.
Add a "b" to the end of that,
or you will be, too.
Jamie, what do you think about
going to practice with me today?
Can i?
I don't know.
It's a big step.
What do you think, mom?
Please be careful.
Sweet!
I'll go get my jersey.
Thanks, mama.
I l-O-V-E you!
I l-O-V-E you, too,
smarty-Pants.
Kid's got your brains.
I just now figured out that
you were spelling "nannies."
Whatever.
They're getting here at 5:00,
by the way.
Okay.
And if you run into quentin
at practice,
Will you t@al himhe's d
with his chapter reports
on "les mis"?
That's good.
Now if only he could figure out
his jump shot.
I'll see ya.
Bye, baby.
That desk
looks good on you, coach.
Welcome back, coach scott.
So, how my boy doing?
Boy's good.
Sorry i was out of touch
for so long.
Hey, you got to do
what you got to do, right?
I just wish i was able
to help you somehow.
You did. You ran the team
for the last month.
How they doing?
You know.
You win some.
You lose some.
And how many "some"
did you lose?
You lost eight games?
Yeah, but we won four.
Well,
three plus the first one,
but you was here
for that one.
Look, i know this is
not what you was hoping for.
And i'm taking
all the blame for this.
But i'm gonna keep it real
with you.
"Q" sucks,
and it's all his fault.
I mean, he ain't hit a shot
since you left.
Because they're doubling him.
No.
His hand is messed up.
I mean,
we ice it constantly,but...
It just ain't been right
since he punched
that knucklehead over at tric.
What's "q" say?
He said
he had it checked out.
All right.
I'll talk to him.
See, that's the thing.
He asked me not to say
nothing to you about this.
He think the injury
gonna cost him a scholarship.
I'll tell you what's gonna
cost him a scholarship --
Playing injured
and going 4-8.
Yeah.
Let's get him in here.
Uncle lucas!
Hey!
There's the man!
I missed you, boy.
Daddy said
you were on a ship.
Did you see any pirates?
Yeah, i saw
a coup pirate ships,
But they didn't want
any part of me.
You want to show me
your jump shot?
All right.
Welcome back, luke.
You good?
I'm working on it.
Oh, my god.
Oh my god
The macy's presentation!
I forgot!
I remembered.
It's all right here.
We just need
your design sketches.
Thank you.
You have really stepped up,
Especially with you-Know-Who
out of the picture.
But...
But what?
Am i in trouble?
No.
I was actually thinking
that
You are way too valuable
to just be
my assistant anymore,
So how would you feel
About a little raise
and a little promotion?
Oh, my gosh!
I don't knowhat to say.
What's my title gonna be?
Something cool, i hope.
We'll figure all that out,
but we have to get you
back to new york first.
Clothes over bro's.
This is she.
Oh.
No.
Absolutely, i can.
I mean, i will.
Yes.
Thank you.
Milly:
brooke, i'm so happy, really, but...
I'm not sure
i can go back to new york.
That's okay.
Change of plans.
I'm gonna need you here.
Oh? Oh, good!
Why?
What's wrong?
I'm gonna be a mom
Brooke, i don't understand.
What do you mean youre gonna be a mom
That was the lady
from the agency.
The horrible woman who
said she wouldn't commend
you for adoption?
She said it's like a special
case, like a foster-Care thing.
Oh, my --
I have to get ready,
and i can't get this in my bag!
Okay. First of all,
you don't need this.
What do you need?
What can i help you with?
I don't know.
I've never had a baby.
I don't know what babies need.
I just --
I have to go, and
i cannot get this in my bag!
Once again,
you don't need this.
Now, just calm down.
Okay, where are my keys?
They're in your hand.
But i'm not sure
you should be driving.
Let me get you some water.
Millicent.
They're giving me a baby.
There's something missing
up on the wall.
There used to be another one.
What was it?
That was
your grandfather's jersey.
Grandpa dan?
Why'd they take it down?
Because of the bad things
he did.
People decided they didn't
want it up there anymore.
You do bad things sometimes,
daddy,
And yours is still up there.
Not that bad.
Quentin:
ho, ho! There he is!
* i said
it's j. Luke scott *
* the boy is hot
* wherever he goes, homey,
that's the spot *
* his name is "q"
* he's better than you
* if the spot is hot,
then he's there, too *
My man.
* i'm the dad
* and i'm not so bad
* i --
Mr. Fields.
Well, well.
The prodigal coach
returns...
And rockin' a tan to boot.
What's going on, coach?
You trying to get
all dark and sexy like me?
It's good
to see you, too.
Aw, man.
Come on, now, coach.
You know how we roll.
Even big game james know that.
Yeah, i know,
but this is how i roll.
Haley: hey, knock, knock.
Hey, foxy, what's up?
I like that outfit.
Oh, thank you.
There are perks to
having a very famous
designer as a roommate.
You get tons of free stuff.
Speaking of,
check out all these demos.
Wow. Looks like
things are picking up, huh?
Well, mostly
because your instincts
are pretty kick-Ass,
haley james scott.
Mia's album is killing it.
And are you ready for this?
She has sold...40,000 copies!
Wow! That's great!
That's really great! She --
She's really the kind of
girl that deserves it, you know?
I know.
Now i just need to find
another one.
Well, i already did --
You.
You deserve all the success
you're getting and more,
And i'm really proud of you.
Thanks, haley.
That really -- That means a lot
to me coming from you.
Actually, that was
just to butter you up,
'Cause i really need
to ask you for a favor.
You are a crack-Up.
What is it?
Anything.
So, you know how you're looking
for the next great artist
And you really trust
my instincts and everyth
Do you have a demo
for me?
I do.
Haley, that's awesome.
Who is it?
Haley james scott.
Yes.
Look, man, the doc says it's
gonna be a little swollen
from time to time.
Why y'all sweatin' it
so hard?
Because we're 4-8.
Maybe that's 'cause
of the coaching.
Easy.
Look, i'm just sayin. Man
One of them
disappeared for a month.
The other one
can't be trusted.
All right.
I want you to palm these.
Please.
[ Chuckles ]
There. You happy?
Not quite.
Palm the balls...
And hold them there.
For how long?
I don't know.
30 seconds?
Shouldn'shbe a problem,
right?
I do this, and
all this nonsense goes away
30 seconds.
You see, the thing is, "q,"
It's not so much
that we're 4-8.
We're 4-8,
and you shooting like trash.
Yeah, that's 'cause
they doubling me, man.
Dole-Teams
never bothered you before.
See, you're one of the best
shooters i've ever seen, "q,"
When you're healthy.
The other ones -- Well,
they're right here in the gym.
Even me, uncle lucas?
Especially you, jamie.
See, you and quentin
are the best shooters we got.
When you're healthy.
Nothing like a second opinion.
And this time,
we'll come with you.
Go.
I have news, boyfriend.
I might be getting a promotion
and staying in tree hill!
and leaving tree hill.
What?
Why?
Before i got the job
with the local stati
I sent audition tapes
everywhere.
There's a good station
in omaha,
And they saw
the ravens feature i did, and...
They offer me a job
In nebraska?
Yeah.
The nearest clothes over bro's
location to omaha is this one.
Yeah, i figured.
Well, is it really
that much better
than where you're at,
marvin?
I mean, like you said, you've
already done one feature here.
Maybe you'll get to do more.
Maybe, but it was really
just 'cause they were in a bind.
This w be
a full-Time on-Air position.
It's a small market,
but it's a great opportunity.
You should take it.
But --
If it gets yloser to your
dream, then you should take it.
I don't think
it's that easy.
Why not?
Because you're part
of my dream, too.
Milly, i know we just started
out, but i love being with you,
And i...
I guess i was hoping
we had a future...together.
Was that too early?
Did i freak you out?
I freaked you out, didn't i?
No.
No, no, no, no.
There is no way those words
could have been too early --
Not coming from you.
Just promise me
that if you do take the job
That i can have your room,
because i'd really like
to find a place to stay
That's not pay-By-The-Day.
What?
I know it's really rough,
but i was thinking --
Yes.
But it's okay if you want --
Will you stop?
The answer is yes, okay?
I've been waiting
for the opportunity
to go out and buy
the next haley james record,
So of course
i want to record it.
It might
be kind of fun, huh?
Well, you did have a major-Label
debut that did pretty good,
So it is good business for me,
but, yes, it's gonna be a blast.
Yeah.
What do you say?
I say it's exactly what i need
right now.
Well, guess what.
Me
What?
I mean, you never know where the
next miracle's gonna come from.
It's brooke.
Oh.
Hey, brooke!
Hey, what's going on?
Brooke: it's a miracle!
Uh, yeah.
We just said that.
What, did you bug my office?
They're giving me a baby!
Um...hold on. Wait. What?
What?
The lady from the agency
called this morning,
And they're sending me --
A purple monkey?
You're adopting
a purple monkey?
No, not adopting
and not nkey.
I'll explain it all later.
Peyton, how crazy is this?
No, brooke, honey,
that's awesome.
God, haley and i
thought we had big news.
Why?
What's your news?
We're gonna make
an album together.
Oh, whatever.
I'm getting a baby.
I have to go.
I'll call you later.
Excuse me.
Wow.
Today's kind of fun.
Listen, "q,"
i know it looks grim,
But, hey, we'll have that thing
off by the playoffs.
Playoffs?
Man, we 4-8.
Hey, we're gonna figure it out.
All right?
Just, uh, hang in there.
Yeah, i'd like to speak
to coach taylor,
If you don't mind...
Alone.
We'll be downstairs.
"Q," keep your head up,
all right?
Listen, kid --
Thanks for nothing, man.
I trusted you, all right?
I put my ass on the line for you
every single night, man.
Quentin, you needed this.
I needed this?!
I -- You know,
i needed a scholarship.
I needed you
to keep your mouth shut.
That's what i needed.
But you went
all uncle tom on me
as soon
as massa lucas got back, huh?
You know what?
When your wrist heals
erything's okay,
I'm gonna let you
take that back.
But for now...
Just consider yourself lucky.
Hi, grandpa.
Hi, jamie.
You boys want to jump me again,
now's your chance.
Hey.
We'rnot ha
ving this.
Not having what, son?
You following jamie around.
I've seen you, okay,
outside of the school.
I've seen you
driving past the house.
And now you just happen
to be at the hospital?
Nathan, stop.
I was in prison
for a long time, okay?
I was just getting
a checkup.
But the truth is,
i was hoping --
No, don't, dan.
Don't hope.
You hear me?
There's no hope for you.
I guess
i just don't understand.
Grandpa dan seems nice.
How come everyone's
always mad at him?
You love chester, don't you?
Well, what if grandpa dan
hurt chester
And took him away so
you could never see him again?
I guess i would be
really mad at him...
And sad, too.
Yeah.
Well, that's how we feel.
I just think that's kind
of an awful thing to say.
Yes, i'm mad.
Oh, you don't think
i should be mad?
I thought i was just gonna have
one baby in my life, but fine.
I have to go.
Holy cow!
Stupid owen.
A little baby talk,
and he totally freaks out.
Well, nothing like
foisting a baby
on a guy
you've almost kissed.
And a confirmed bachelor,
at that.
Whaty?
Whatever.
He's gonna come over later,
And we're gonna talk about it
or fight about it,
But it doesn't matter
Because baby and brooke
are gonna be fine.
Yeah, i think "baby and brooke"
needs a little explanation --
Like who, when, and how,
for starters.
Okay. So, the adoption agency
has this program
Where babies
from other countries
who need major surgeries and
stuff come over to the u.S.
And doctors donate their time
to fix them up
And then they go home.
Oh.
That's great!
It's kind of a "whenever
they can squeeze you in"
sort of thing,
And the agency had a family at
was supposed to host the baby
Drop out, so they said
this could be a great trial run for me.
When does the baby show up?
Is it a boy
or a girl?
And are his parents
coming, too?
Okay. She's a girl,
and she gets here tomorrow.
Her parents
don't come with her,
And they didn't tell me
what's wrong with her.
They're just sort of
gonna hand her over,
And we go from there.
And check it out.
I got her...
A purple monkey
like the one i used to have.
That's so cute!
And did you get her
anything else?
Yeah, i got all this stuff.
I mean, like,
you know...food...
Or, i mean, a crib.
...and stuff.
I got a little sidetracked?
Okay. Why don't we go
to my house
And we'll go through some
of jamie's old things?
Really?
Yes.
Come on,
you purple monkey.
I'm so excited!
Me too.
Hey, what you doin'?
Looking for places to live.
Well, stop, because
i've found you a place.
With me.
I passed on the omaha job.
Marvin...
I feel like i'm good
at what i do, millicent,
And i'll just work hard and
Hope the station
gives me another shot.
Are you sure?
That i'm doing the right thing?
I don't know.
But about us?
Yeah. I'm sure.
I don't want to leave you,
millicent.
But you said you needed
a place to stay,
And i thought...
you should move in with me.
But...i can't.
I mean...
Look, i know it's soon, but
you'll save a fortune on rent,
And you'll get to see me
every day.
I mean, what do you say?
I'd like to,
but i just can't.
Sorry.
But i'm really glad
you're staying.
Haley, thank you.
This is great.
Sure.
Listen, have you given
any thought
to how difficult it's gonna be
to give this baby up
After the surgery? You know you got to fought for her brooke
I know.
But she needs help, right?
Yeah.
Nathan: hey.
What's going on?
Hi.
Hi, aunt brooke!
Hi, best boy ever!
I have a surprise for you.
What is it?
Hey.
I found the car seat.
Surprise.
It must have been good
to spend time with your mom
and lily and andy.
Yeah.
I think we all needed it.
Plus, the view wasn't too bad,
either.
Yeah,
i'm sure it was beautiful.
So, uh, you and haley
are gonna make a record, huh?
That's great.
Actually, i was meaning
to ask you --
I mean, it's totally cool
if you say no,
But, um, i was thinking,
to cut down on studicosts,
Maybe i would build
a small studio in the office.
But it's your space, so...
I think that's a great idea.
I mean, i'll ask my mom,
but, yeah, i think it's smart.
I don't blame you, peyton.
Luke...
at all for any of it.
I feel bad for you,
i feel bad for lindsey,
And i feel responsible
somehow.
And i really hope that doesn't
come off as arrogant, okay?
But i know this hurt you.
She's coming back, peyton.
She loves me.
And i love her.
It's gonna be okay.
I hope so.
It's open.
That kid's a lot hairier
than i thought he'd be.
Very funny.
And "he"
is gonna be a "she."
I guess you talked to owen.
Yep.
How you doin'?
Okay.
A little freak out but okay.
Is he with you?
No.
Weird.
He's coming over soon.
Actually, he's not.
That's kind of why i'm here.
Oh.
Okay.
You know, brooke,
owen's my friend,
And i know he's really into you,
but...
He's just kind of always been
about his independence, too,
you know?
I guess i didn't know.
He's just a little thrttd
with all the baby stuff.
Yeah,
he said that on the phone.
Look, did he send you over here
to talk to me?
Are we in junior high now?
He didn't send me over,
And he's not coming by either.
Then why did you?
Well...
I'm taking off.
I thought i'd say goodbye
and congratulations.
And maybe i want to see
your face one more time.
Probably why owen's
not coming by.
What is that
supposed to mean?
Well, he probably figures
If he looked in those eyes
one more time,
He'll cave
on the whole independence thing.
Anyways, call me
if you need anything...
Someone to talk to,
new carpets...
I don't know, a husband...
I'll see you around.
Hey, brooke?
Don't take the owen stuff
too personally.
I won't.
Yeah, you will.
I know how you are.
It's -- It's just a big deal.
It's kids.
I mean, i know it's just one,
But if you really want a family,
something that's like forever...
"Forever" scares a lot of us.
Yeah.
Hi.
Can i talk to you?
Sure.
Come on in.
What's, uh --
What's wrong?
Um, maybe nothing...
i hope.
Okay, just have a seat.
What's up?
Well, i think i'll stand.
Actually, do you have
something to drink --
Some water or an apple martini with
a cherry, if you have it?
Okay, you're kind of
freaking me out.
The last time someone entered
the apartment like this,
It was skills, and he thought
he'd killed chester.
Jamie's bunny?
Yeah, but it turns out
he was just, like, a really
heavy sleeper, apparently.
Well, it's not that.
It's just i know
i sort of freaked you out
When you asked me to stay here,
and, well, there's a reason.
Great.
I knew it.
What?
I figured this was
just too good to be true.
There's just a reason
we can't sleep in the same bed.
Oh, no.
What?
This is like "the crying game,"
right?
Marvin!
Hairy back?
Marvin.
Well, it's either that
or you're completely repulsed
by me.
I'm a virgin.
Really?
Yes.
And considering your last gross
boss-Lady hookup,
You're clearly not, and
i am just not ready to --
How did i find you?
What?
Such a perfect girl
who's smart and sweet and...
So awesome.
Go on.
Milly, i would never
pressure you about sex.
I just --
I want to be with you.
But --
I mean, we could even get
two beds, if you want...
Although, if i catch you
sneaking into mine,
I'm telling skills.
I am so into you, and...
I want you here.
Will you say yes?
Okay. Yes.
If you think it can work.
It can.
It does.
So, i see you know cpr,
And you're also
a lifeguard.
Yes.
Have you ever kissed any
of the husbands you worked for?
Okay, uh...
No.
Well...
Sorry.
So, nathan...
haley tells me you like
to watch your nanny swim naked
in the pool?
I guess i deserved that.
Hey, brooke.
You okay?
I think i made a big mistake.
I think it's a little late
for that, isn't it?
If i wanted
a "little late for that,"
I would have called peyton.
You are supposed to say,
"no, you didn't.
You're gonna be fine."
No, you didn't.
You're gonna be fine.
It doesn't count now.
So, you got
a purple monkey, huh?
Just like you had.
You remember that?
Of course.
I do know some things about you,
brooke davis.
You're gonna be a great mom.
I'm not even gonna be a mom.
I just fix her up, and
then i have to send her back.
Well, if you didn't do it,
who would?
Owen thinks
i'm being selfish.
He thinks
i just want what i want.
Well, i'd say
it's the opposite.
Right?
I think it's great
that you're willing
to help  little girl
get the care that she needs
And get to the rest
of her life.
So do i.
But what if i do
something wrong, luke?
What if i hurt her?
What if i break her?
I mean, i rushed into this,
and i'm scared.
You know what?
When it comes to single moms,
I had a pretty special one.
And it's good
that you're a little scared.
But you're gonna do great.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming over.
You think she'll like the purple money?
I think that she's gonna love
the girl
who gives it to her.
Yeah.
Jamie's out cold.
I wish
i could sleep like that.
Yeah, tell me about it.
So, i'm sorry
you couldn't find a nanny
that you could trust
around me.
Too soon
The truth is, i just want ja
all to myself right now.
But i also want my job
and i want my music
And i want alone time
with you.
Well, you should take a break
from that.
Let me go
through those things.
I'll try to find a person
that's really ugly
with a lot
of great references.
Actually, you can't,
Because i thought you might
want to get a workout in.
You know, our therapist said that
We should focus on
the things that we love, so...
I think she's right.
I'm probably really gonna suck,
you know.
You are gonna find out sometime right?
Thank you, hales...
For everything.
You're welcome.
Thank you back.
You lucky, man.
I was gonna break
that scoriatitle
and pull that old laundry
up off the wall.
Luck has nothing to doth it.
I'm just better than you.
How you holding up?
How you think?
If somebody would have told me
your old sorry ass
would be back playing
before mine,
I would have laughed
their ass out the gym.
What you trying to do --
Make some kind of comeback?
Trying to make
a free throw.
Let me show you
how that's done, old man.
Left-Handed...
You'rest fine,
"q"...
Even if you have to go
to a junior college first.
That's what i did.
Wow.
And look where it got you.
Let's see what you got.
Come on, nate.
Oh, here we go.
Nathan scott.
Biggest raven of them all.
Look at you, huh?
Heard they clipped
your wings.
What you got, raven?
Nathan scott....
Just like i thought.
Hmm?
They must have put salt
on your tail, boy.
You ain't got no chance
of flying again.
Me, on the other hand...
...i can beat you
with my other hand,
And that ain't
even my shooting hand.
Some comeback,
mr. Jersey on the wall.
Sometimes you got
a big mouth, quentin.
Aw, nate.
Nate!
Come back, man!
Where you going?
Come back.
That's it?
That's a sorry-Ass comeback,
nate.
Nathan scott,
ladies and gentlemen.
Hello, son.
What are you doing here?
Just regjutting it all.
You too, huh?
Thinking
about playing again?
No! All right?!
I'm not thinking
about playing again!
I can't even make
a damn free throw.
At least
your legacy's safe, son.
Just do your best.
Unlike some of us, you have
nothing to be ashamed of.
Hey, man, you got a second?
Just don't come too close
right now, man.
I'm kind of pissed off.
Why?
What happened?
Just some nonsense
quentin said to me.
You know, sometimes that kid's
got a big mouth, man.
What's up?
Uh, millicent is gonna move in
after all.
Fine with me.
Hey, about time we classed up
the place a little bit, huh?
Well, speaking of,
you think we could?
You ow, straighten up a little
and straighten up a little?
Oh, you talkin'
about all the sex talk
And foul language, right?
Yeah.
Good luck with that.
Come on, skills.
I'm not saying
everybody has to be a saint,
But millicent's a girl,
you know?
And she's my girl.
All right.
I'll talk to the fellas.
It's all good, baby.
All right, thanks.
Hey, you think she could walk
around in her --
No.
I didn't think so.
New song?
Yeah.
Nice.
Thank you.
Actually, i think i'm gonna
record that album with peyton.
Really?
Yeah.
That's great, haley.
Yes, it is.
Yeah.
How'd your workout go?
Not so good.
But you know what?
Whatever happens,
we're gonna be fine.
Yeah, we will.
Deb: hello?
Who is that?
That's the new nanny
mama hired.
Did someone call
for a nanny?
Grandma!
What did i
tell you about that?
Grandma deb is way too young
to be a grandma.
Sorry.
Nanny deb!
Oh, i like that
so much better.
Hi, mom.
Hey, mom,
you look great.
Ooh, thank you.
??
It's been said that the saddest
thing a man will ever face
Is what might have been.
But what of the man
who's faced with what was?
Or what may never be?
Or what can no longer be?
You did the right thing,
skills.
And one of these days,
"q" is gonna realize that.
Now we just got to figure out
a way to win without him.
Choosing the right path
is never easy.
It's a decision we make with
only our hearts to guide us.
But sometimes we find our way
to something better.
Hey, brooke, come on.
We got to get to the airport
to pick up that baby.
I think
i need to do this alone.
I'm gonna be okay.
Okay.
Sometimes we fight
through the regret and remorse
of our mistakes --
Our malice and our jealousy
And the shame we feel
for not being the people
we were meant to be.
And that's when we find our way
to something better...
...or when something better
finds its way to us.
???
??????