you saved me.
you saved me, too.
than: i borrowed some money
from these guys,
so they asked me to shave
a few points in the last game.
everyone get away
from the door.
oh, jimmy,
what did you do?
go.
dan: what are you doing here,
lucas?
lucas: i don't think
jimmy killed keith.
keith's dead, okay?
he's not coming back.
open your eyes.
keith: open your eyes, luke.
hey, skills.
you know this girl?
yeah, that's abby.
she was in the tutor center.
jimmy let her go.
sometimes, i wonder if anything
is absolute anymore.
is there still
right and wrong...
good and bad...
truth and lies?
or is everything negotiable...
left to interpretation, gray?
who is it?
um...
my name's lucas scott.
i was wondering
if i may talk to abby.
there's no abby here.
you have the wrong address.
well, no, no, no!
i was just --
thanks for nothing.
sometimes, we're forced
to bend the truth...
transform it...
because we're faced with things
that are not of our own making.
and sometimes...
...things
simply catch up to us.
coach durham, can you address
the allegations of point-shaving
and illegal activity
within the ravens?
look, i'm gonna say this
one time and one time only.
this is the best gro of boys
i've had
in 35 years of coaching.
these are not cheaters.
they're champions --
every one of them.
there's only three things
i'm afraid of losing
in this world, haley --
u, our son,
and the game.
how bad will it get if they
find out aut you and daunte?
they'll take my scholarship
for sure.
i probably
won't play anywhere...
ever.
hey!
[ clears throat ]
sorry.
it's fine.
hey, brooke.
i heard
about that stalker thing.
i tried calling you,
but i never heard back.
yeah, it's...
where's
your clean-teen t-shirt?
things change, you know?
yeah, i know.
hey.
do i have any blood on me?
no, why?
'cause i just saw chase,
and it feels like
i got my heart ripped out.
i think you'll be okay.
do i look insane?
no, why?
i saw him again --
this time in the shower.
peyton, you got to stop
doing this to yourself, okay?
fake psycho derek --
whatever the hell his name is --
he's locked up.
you know that.
yeah, that's what they said
last time -- or what he said.
i don't know.
maybe if i just see it
with my own eyes
that he's
actually behind bars...
maybe.
come on.
hey...
you know what, i'm gonna
have to catch up with you, okay?
okay.
hi, baby.
i knew you'd come.
well, they said
that you wouldn't, but...
i knew that you would.
i want to know why.
why me?
why diyou pick me?
you love me.
no. i don't.
i hate you.
don't you get that?
you're just
a deranged, pathetic psycho,
and i never, ever want
to see you again, okay?
then why'd you come?
have i been
in your head?
you asked me to come into
your life, peyton.
you got undressed
in front of your webcam...
what?
...because you knew
it would make me want you.
you posted those pictures
online.
you are wrong.
am i?
is that why
you're dressed like that today?
are you a tease, peyton?
dressing sexy...
wearing that perfume,
making me...ache for you,
and then saying no?
stop.
are you a tease, peyton?
stop!
because that would
really be disappointing.
i did not do this.
you did this.
no, you did this!
you did this to me, peyton!
it's all your fault!
you did this to me!
you did this!
tease!
nathan:
thought you'd look a lot worse,
considering
the walls are closing in.
what do you mean?
the point-shaving, dad.
right.
what are you hearing?
nothing.
you think it's bear?
no, no. if it was bear, he'd
have pointed them right to us.
sounds like the whispers of
someone who lost a lot of money
but isn't close enough
to know the details.
they're asking questions about
lucas now, and it's not right.
he only missed
those free throws because of me.
okay.
but that's the only time
i ever want to hear you
say that out loud.
look, first, you won
the state championship
and every postseason game
that lucas played in,
so they're grasping
at straws.
you don't think
it's serious?
no, it's serious...
because if they find proof,
your future's in jeopardy.
but i don't think
they're gonna find any proof.
so, what do i do?
you stay cool.
deny everything.
and pray
no one uncovers the truth.
[ cellphone rings ]
i'm sorry. sorry.
i-i didn't mean to scare you.
i didn't mean to scare you.
my name's lucas scott.
we -- we go to school together
at tree hill.
do you know me?
my uncle was keith scott,
and i know that you were
in the tutor center that day,
and i know
that jimmy let you go.
so...
listen...
i have to know
what you saw, abby.
okay?
you got to tell me.
did jimmy edwards...
kill keith?
no.
[ chuckles ]
what is this?
what the hell is this?
look, mrs. brown,
i-i can exp--
get out. get the hell out of my
house, or i'll call the police!
and tell them what, huh?
that your daughter knows the
truth about my uncle's death?
your uncle
was keith scott?
i'm very sorry for you,
but my daughter has been
traumatized since then.
she hasn't been to school.
her life has become
very difficult,
and that is
why i lied to you last night.
listen, abby told me
that jimmy edwards
didn't kill my uncle keith.
did she?
honey, is your name abby?
am i your mother?
are you sure?
now, i'm very sorry
for your loss.
that day changed all of us --
and none of us for the better.
but i'd like you
to leave.
and -- and, lucas,
don't come back.
abby
has been through enough.
hey.
jeez, you look
worse than i do.
yeah.
[ chuckles ]
um, listen, uh,
t-the thing is that, uh...
nathan said this whole gambling
thing's just gonna go away,
and i don't really know,
uh, how much i believe that,
and i just wanted to know
what you thought --
if you t-think
that he's right or --
or do you think
he's right?
no.
it's not going away.
'cause he said that
they're just focusing on you,
and then they're
not gonna find anything,
and nothing's gonna happen.
yeah, but, see,
that's the problem.
you know, yeah, i mean,
i missed a couple free throws,
but i'm a sub.
i played half a season,
15 minutes a night.
no gambler's gonna build
a point-shaving scheme
around a reserve.
okay, so,
what is gonna happen, then?
well, i think that after
they're done looking at me,
that they're gonna start
taking a look at nathan.
i hate to say it, hales,
but when they do...
it's gna end up really bad.
[ exles sharply ]
okay.
okay, um...
how bad is --
is really bad?
well, nathan's
not gonna go to jail.
but he's not
gonna go to duke, either.
ian: [ echoing ]
it's all your fault!
tease.
brooke: peyton?
hey, what's wrong?
i went to see him.
who?
oh, no. derek?
ian.
his name is ian.
i know.
you do?
been hiding these
from you.
there's been a lot of articles
about the attack.
i thought
you were clipping coupons.
i know, honey,
but i hate coupons.
did you leave
the front door unlocked?
no.
i'm sorry.
i have a key.
i-i didn't know
if you were sleeping. sorry.
it's okay.
you locked the door,
right?
yes, i did.
i used to love my room,
and he took it from me.
psycho derek.
it's like i --
i really thought
if we just fought back, like,
if we attacked our attacker,
that he would go away,
but he hasn't.
it's really gonna take
some time, peyton.
you guys went through
something really traumatic.
yeah, but what
if you have finals
and you can't sleep
and you don't have time?
well, then, hopefully,
you have a friend
who's gonna tell you that fe
kicks you around sometimes.
it -- it scares you,
and it beats you up.
but...there's a day
when you realize that
you're not just a survivor.
you're a warrior.
you're tougher than
anything it throws your way.
and you are, peyton.
you are.
and so are you,
hales.
thank you.
and so are you.
i mean it.
thanks.
come here.
i was hoping
for a booty call.
sorry, coach.
what's so important it
can't wait till a decent hour?
it's the investigation.
it was me.
i missed those free throws
in the semifinals on purpose,
and i just wanted you
to hear it from me
before i hold
a press conference tomorrow.
i'm sorry, coach.
you know,
i only took a chance on you
because keith asked me to.
i know.
he would be ashamed of you
right now...
just like i am.
keeping in shape?
yes, sir.
duke's gonna be
pretty rough,
especially
if you're not in shape.
yes, sir.
so, there's, uh...
some reporters asking questions
about, uh...gambling...
point-shaving --
that kind of thing.
you know
anything about that?
no, sir.
well, your brother's name's
not going to be worth a damn
when this whole thing
comes down.
what do you mean?
lucas didn't do
anything wrong.
not what he says.
what?
what the hell
is wrong with you?
you're welcome.
screw that, luke.
we said
we weren't gonna say anything.
we agreed.
so what?
so what did you do?
i...went
and saved your stupid ass
so you could play
college basketball
and have everything
you've ever dreamed about.
you know what?
that's a bunch of crap.
we could have
beat this thing, man.
sounds like you're feeling
a little guilty to me.
yeah, of course
i'm feeling guilty,
but you shouldn't have said
anything to whitey, man.
that was
a stupid thing to do.
you know what?
i don't care.
i'm not going to college
to play basketball anyway.
it doesn't matter.
it doesn't matter
that for the rest of time,
people are gonna talk?
they're gonna say
you disgraced the game, luke.
that doesn't matter
to you?
let them say
what they want to say about me.
it's what they say
about jimmy edwards
that matters to me
and what they say
about keith.
but this?
at least i know
the truth about this.
peyton thinks i'm a martyr.
i can't stop this, luke.
i just --
i'm this close, man,
and i got the baby.
i -- i can't.
you shouldn't have said
anything.
[ drowsily ]
what's going on?
it's a new day.
move your scrawny butt.
i checked the shower,
and psycho ian's not in there,
so you need to be, because,
no offense, you're kind of rank.
thanks a lot.
well, i just call them like
i smell them.
choppity-choppity.
[ sighs ]
what are you doing?
i told you.
we're warriors.
we kicked that idiot's
psychotic ass,
so a new day dawns,
p. sawyer.
yeah, but when i went
to go see him...
brooke,
he said i led him on --
that i led him on with,
like, my podcasts and my webcam
and the way that i dress.
peyton.
so you're saying
that every girl
who wears a little bit
of lipstick and a short skirt
is asking to be assaulted
and raped?
no, of course not, but...
i did give him
full access to my life,
and now he knows
all this stuff about me.
and he uses it, you know?
he uses it to get in.
okay.
then it's time we start learning
a little bit about him.
get up and fight, warrior.
and take a shower.
just the ammo today, sir?
yeah, just the ammo.
the only reason i ask is,
we just got this baby in today.
.45 automatic,
and if you've got
your handgun permit,
you can be
shooting her today.
how'd that feel?
jeez. who knew
there were so many ian banks?
maybe we should add "stalker"
to the search.
really.
so, where's your head at
with chase these days?
i don't know.
i think about him a lot.
you know how it is.
start wondering
if he ever thinks about me,
and if he does,
is it the same?
did he leave
'cause of the videotape,
or was he just looking
for an out?
you know --
same old self-doubt.
oh, wow.
this is him.
he's not from st. flora.
he's from texas.
what?
oh, my god.
his girlfriend looks
just like you, if you --
if i what?
if you were dead.
* a doll's house,
and i'm trapped inside *
* i'll break
these shutters open wide *
* in my dreams,
i walk with you *
you call my name *
* in my dreams,
i talk with you *
nothing remains *
i want
to tell someone, mom.
abby.
i'm tired
of lying about what i saw,
and i'm tired of hiding out
and pretending i'm crazy.
i want
to go back to school, mom.
honey, you can't.
as soon as i make enough money,
wel go someplace different.
we will, but for now,
we have to do it this way.
why?
because i say so.
that's why.
so what, then?
we just hide from our lives?
at least we have lives.
not really, mom.
and you might be afraid of this,
but i'm not.
abby.
abby!
aah!
ohh!
you need
to get out of here.
i want to talk to you.
i said get out!
calm down!
just shut up!
will you shut up?!
just --
okay, look.
i need you to sit down.
just --
just go sit down.
just sit down.
you're abby brown.
look, i don't know what
you think you might have seen.
she didn't see anything.
shut up!
just...
you made a mistake.
abby: no.
i saw you.
i saw everything.
abby.
she's not well.
i know what you did.
and so do you.
my brother keith
was always better than me.
he had a better heart.
people liked him more.
no, they loved him.
karen loved him.
but...
...karen was mine.
she was supposed to be mine.
she was just a girl
who went to school that day.
she's just a girl.
i hope you burn in hell.
so do i.
well, if it isn't tease one
and tease two.
did you come back
for another kiss?
brooke:
not really, derek.
or should
i call you "ian"?
yeah,
we know your real name.
actually, we know
a lot of things about you.
we spoke to all your teachers
at the alton academy
and the girls
you used to date.
you don't know
anything about me.
really?
susanna gold
ring a bell?
you know, a lot of teenage boys
have performance anxiety.
i know a lot of teenage girls
who are teases, too.
is that really
the best that you've got?
'cause we have
a lot more than some podcasts
and a few webcam photos,
ian banks.
whatever.
boyfriend
of maggie watterson.
or should i say
former boyfriend?
you shut your mouth,
you whore.
hey, what happened
to maggie, ian?
i don't know
what you're talking about.
really?
'cause the accident --
you were driving.
it was prom night.
no, it wasn't
my fault!
what happened, ian?
ian?
we were just messing around...
driving fast.
my father never let me
drive that car.
he loved that car.
the road was slippery.
you lost control.
i tried to wake her up.
there was just...
blood.
there was just
so much blood.
her parents said
it was my fault.
they --
they all said it.
i can't be maggie, ian.
i'm not maggie.
we were gonna be together
forever.
she loved me.
she --
she trusted me.
she forgives you.
i forgive you, too.
i'm sorry.
i'm so sorry.
i'm not gonna be
seeing you anymore.
you're not gonna
see us, either...
ever.
goodbye, ian.
i hope you find peace.
we talked
about not saying anything.
lucas --
he was supposed to do nothing.
he's really
just trying to help out.
it's just so lucas, you know?
trying to be the hero.
i'm not gonna feel guilty
about it.
nobody asked him
to do this.
that's not exactly true.
he's doing this for me
because i asked him to.
and if you're not gonna feel
guilty about it,
then i sure
as hell will,
because he is my best friend
and he's your brother
and he's doing this
for all of us --
for you and me
and our son, and, um...
it just really sucks.
damn it.
i'm sorry, hales.
i'm sorry
i put us through this.
i'm sorry i made you ask lucas
to take the blame.
i'm sorry i've bn so weak
about all this.
nathan...
you are about to make every
dream you've had come true.
everybody understands that.
no, it's not worth it.
i mean, what the hell
was i thinking?
we're gonna be parents
soon.
what would we want
our son to do?
what would make us proud?
and what am i gonna say
to him someday
when he asks about this?
that i was dan?
that i put what i wanted
in front of everything else?
nathan...
you're gonna lose it all --
your scholarship,
the game that you love.
i won't lose it all.
i'll still have you,
and we'll still have our son...
and we'll have that feeling
that in the face of all this,
we didn't lose our way.
we still know
right from wrong.
i'm just...
scared for you.
i love you for this,
but...
but it's just not --
it's not my dream that's dying.
it's yours.
it's gonna be hard.
i know that, but...
the people i admire
are the people
that carve a life for themselves
after their dream dies.
my father
could never get past it, hales.
he could never let go of what
he wanted when he was 17...
and look what it did to him.
open your eyes, lucas.
open your eyes.
abby?
i need
to talk to you.
i know what my mom said,
and i'm sorry she lied,
but i need
to tell you some things.
you were hiding
in the hallway.
[ voice breaking ]
i got scared, and i ran,
but i was worried about
the others and jimmy, too.
i saw it in his eyes
when he let me go.
he was just scared, too.
you came back.
and what happened
after that? huh?
abby? come on,
you got to tell me.
please.
your uncle keith --
he tried to help jimmy.
please.
but he couldn't.
and jimmy...
jimmy what?
i'm sorry.
no!
was my uncle keith still alive
when jimmy shot himself?
who shot him, abby?
ohh.
i thought once he realized
someone knew the truth,
he'd come forward,
so i stalked him
with messages and threats.
i thought
he'd turn himself in.
i thought i'd be safe.
but he found me.
who?!
who killed --
who killed my uncle?
your father.
it was your father...
dan scott.
he killed keith.
he was there...
and he picked up
the gun...
and you know i'm right,
don't you?
you know it in your heart.
you have to come forward.
you got to
tell somebody, abby.
abby, you have to
tell somebody!
i did.
i told you.
i'm sorry.
coach.
i don't know how you can look
your brother in the eye, nathan.
this is a damn disgrace.
coach, i lied to you
on the river court yesterday
and during the playoffs.
it wasn't lucas.
i know.
i'm sorry.
so am i...
more than you'll ever know.
[ sighs ]
when i was 2 years old,
i made my first basket.
when i was 6, basketball went
from being a game to a sport.
since then, i've played
7,072 official minutes --
probably
20,000 or 30,000 unofficial.
but for 32 minutes this season,
over the course of two games,
i did not compete
to the best of my ability.
i regret this.
and i regret
that the fear
of losing the opportunity
to continue playing
the game that i've always loved
prevented me from standing up
and taking full responsibility
for this sooner.
i apologize to my coach
and to my teammates
and to all the kids
who look up to me --
especially to the kids.
and while
i never lost a game on purpose,
the truth is still the truth.
and you can spin it
and shade it and bend it,
but there's still right
and wrong,
and i was wrong.
and the truth is,
i've forsaken a game
that's always been
incredibly good to me
and teammates
that have been like brothers...
and a brother
that was a teammate.
to my coach...
my wife...
my father, and my family,
i apologize for the burden
i know this will bring.
i know that the integrity of
the game cannot be compromised.
i regret that my own integrity
was not as steadfast.
i'm deeply remorseful
for the choices i've made,
but i will accept whatever
consequences there might be.
i love this game.
i'm sorry i betrayed it.
* years from now...
brooke...
you loved your room,
peyton.
and, maybe, like you said,
that's been taken from you,
but we're gonna
take it back.
we're gonna
take everything back.
* ...soon enough
* work and love
will make a man out of you *
* through and through
* your gentleman father
* would pray for a daughter
* as he walked
* from room to room
* saying, "women are winning
* "the tournament of hearts
* somebody's got to lose"
* soon enough
* work and love
will make a man out of you *
* through and through...
karen: dan?
i've done
some horrible things.
unforgivable things.
lucas didn't need a father.
he had one.
he had a person who helped him
erase the shame of my cowardice.
everything i've touched,
i've diminished --
deb's life, nathan's talent.
keith.
you're --
you're not without redemption.
i've -- i've seen it.
i see it.
that's not true.
i just want to --
i want to go back, you know?
i just want to go back.
i-i-i want to --
i want to take that little kid
that i used to be
and just grab him and shake him
and say, "you stop. stop!
just stop!"
i want to wake up
from this nightmare, you know?
i-i want
to breathe again.
i want to --
i want to breathe again, karen.
can you help me breathe?
can you help me quiet
these voices in my head
that tell me i've lost you?
because i know that i have.
if oy i would have
stayed with you.
* ...soon enough
* work and love
will make a man out of you *
* soon enough
* work and love
will make a man out of you *
truth is still absolute.
believe that --
even when that truth
is hard and cold
anmore painful
than you've ever imagined.
and even when truth...
is morcruel than any lie.
-- cync by ayssa --
www.1000fr.com