Previously on "One Tree Hill"...
Where did you even get this?
It was e-mailed to me this morning.
Julian, we're being blackmailed.
You filmed us having sex?
You found my computer?
No. But someone did.
And now Julian and his
father are being blackmailed
for 1 million dollars thanks to you!
We just said we were
getting the tape out there.
The plan was never to blackmail
these people for money.
Look, we got to tell Brooke, all right?
She's got no idea...
Look, I told Brooke I was taking a lover.
You just need to relax.
I came home for you because I love you.
It's just, things are different.
Is there someone else?
Maybe.
- Is you, isn't it?
- Yes, but...
Thanks for sleeping with
my girlfriend, buddy.
I'm being deported.
Marry me.
What did you just say?
Marrying me fixes everything.
Somebody bought your portrait.
She's right there.
Remember the tennis player that
wouldn't take no for an answer?
She is the girl who bought
my portrait tonight.
That Katie girl?
Why do you have a photo with her?
Because it's not her.
It's Sara.
Even though she doesn't
show it all the time,
deep down inside, your mom is still
very sad that your grandma died.
Mom's gonna be okay, right?
Yeah, she's gonna be fine.
Welcome to Brooke's spa.
We hope you enjoy your stay.
Oh!
Trust m, it's great for the skin.
In that case...
Seriously?
That thing has been ringing nonstop.
Didn't the shoot just end?
Yeah, but editing just started.
You just did the thing.
What thing?
Whenever you're passionate about
something, your eyebrows tighten up
I saw it a lot on set.
And even though I think it's kind of sexy,
m worried about you.
Why? Because I'll never win
the world poker championship?
No. Because when you're
passionate about something,
you put everything you have into it.
Have you stopped for one second to relax?
Yes. For about five hours every night.
Sleeping doesn't count.
I'm serious, Julian.
I need you to take care of yourself
because I want you to live
for a long, long time.
Well, I will as long as I have you.
Brooke's spa will always be
here to help you recuperate.
Aah!
Alexander did what to Victoria?
Actually, it was Victoria
doing things to Alexander.
Ew.
Totally ew but totally awesome.
And you and Josh made a sex tape.
I don't know which is worse.
I do. But just for the record,
Josh made the tape.
I just suffered through it.
No way.
Yes way.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Skills punched out Melvin.
- It's illegal.
- It's not.
It's absolutely illegal for me to marry
someone just to stay in the country.
Not if there are real feelings involved.
Look, it's late.
Take the night to think about it.
You can say "I do" in the morning.
Someone's up early this morning.
Nervous for your music-video shoot?
Ugh.
You'll do great, Hales. You always do.
Have a good run, dad.
Thanks, buddy.
So, mom, what's for breakfast?
What do you think? It's our new campaign.
I'm calling it "The blunder down under."
I think my hair looks amazing,
but that flag needs to be much bigger.
Mother!
Brooke.
He's half your age.
Lucky me.
I'm serious. What are you thinking?
I'm sorry you're offended that
Alexander and I are lovers now.
No, I'm just offended that you
decided to display that love
in front of all my friends.
Oh, please. Cougars are in now.
Morning, Brooke.
Doughnut?
Have fun with your "cub."
Please.
You've got 30 seconds.
You're used to working
in that timeframe, right?
Last night isn't what you think.
What I think is you're a jerk.
What I saw was you making
out with another guy.
Haven't you ever done something
that you didn't mean to do?
Yes. I had sex with you.
I would appreciate it if you
didn't tell anyone what you saw.
Yeah? Well, I'd appreciate it
if you didn't tape me having sex with you.
Oh, wait. You already did.
I shouldn't have done that.
And I'm sorry.
But I'm asking you,
please... don't tell anyone.
Josh is gay.
Alex, I understand you're upset.
True, but I also caught him sticking
his tongue down to some guy's throat.
are you sure it wasn't
a boyish-looking girl?
It was a guy. Maybe you'll
meet him at the wrap party.
There's not gonna be a wrap party.
No wrap party? Kind of cheap, isn't it?
Not really. Considering
there are two leads
decided to cost the film an extra
million dollars with their sex tape.
Josh made the tape.
I just suffered through it.
You can also suffer through no wrap party.
It's kind of creepy, right?
That this Katie girl looks just like Sara
and she bought the picture of you.
Yeah, it's weird.
But maybe it's just that...
weird but harmless.
How come you never told me about
her whenever you first met her?
I'm sorry. I should have told you.
You know, but with your mom being sick,
it just didn't seem important.
As important.
It's okay.
Mean, like you said,
hopefully she's just harmless, right?
Either that or completely psychotic.
Listen, I'm sure there's
nothing to worry about.
But just in case, I'll make some calls
and see if I can find out more about her.
And, babe, I am sorry for not telling you.
It's okay.
I heard you had a rough night.
Yeah.
You guys look so young.
I wish I would have known
you in high school.
Do you want to talk about it?
It's not like Lauren and I
planned any of this, you know?
It just sort of happened.
But you like her?
I do.
Then you should talk to Skills.
Tell him that.
You guys have been friends a long time.
I should probably be getting to work.
Thanks for stopping by, Millie.
It means a lot.
After all you've done for me,
it's the least I could do.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Do you ever miss me?
Of course.
Thanks.
That means a lot, too.
Look like you didn't
sleep much last night.
That's because I didn't.
Sounds good.
Dance with me.
Grubbs...
Just dance with me.
Practice for the wedding.
I can't marry you.
Why not?
We dance good together.
That's not a reason to get married.
It's a start.
Listen to me.
We need to focus on the
album... your album.
And... and we don't have much time.
The music's good, Michael.
Now you just have to find the words.
Hey, Skills. Can I talk to you?
Where y'all going?
Laundry.
Cooking class?
You're my best friend, Skills.
And I just...
Lauren and I were just
hanging out, you know?
It's not like we planned this.
There's my guy!
- I wanted to check on you. Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm glad you did, though.
I need to ask you a question.
Shoot.
Right after Skills punched me,
were your mom and Alexander...
Yes. Don't remind me. Thanks.
I left the store to avoid them.
Scandalous.
Not as scandalous as two
best friends fighting.
- What?
- Well, it's just funny, hearing that from the girl
who wore a black eye to prom,
courtesy of her bff.
Okay. Well, I remember a certain someone
encouraging me to make up with Peyton...
Something about too much
history to just walk away.
Thank you for that, by the way.
If it weren't for P. Sawyer,
I would have never met Julian.
You're welcome.
So, what now?
I'm very well versed in girl code,
but I thought guy code didn't
extend past a high five.
Usually.
But when a guy really cares about a girl,
guy code is pretty much the same.
I feel horrible.
Well, have you guys talked about it?
I tried. He walked away.
I'm sorry, buddy. That sucks.
Yeah.
"Brooke Davis caught in
sex act with boy toy"?!
That sucks worse.
Skills... round two.
How can you do this to me?
We broke up, Antwon.
Yeah, but only because of geography.
You really think that's all it was?
You left. We barely talked.
And... and that's okay,
but don't put this all on me.
But you stopped calling.
I didn't even know you were coming home
yeah, but with my best friend?
You must feel guilty.
That's why you came over here, right?
I came over here to tell you to
stop being a jerk to your friend.
So, that's it?
You're choosing Mouth over me?
I didn't choose anyone,
but this version of you isn't helping.
You're not helping.
You're not even listening.
Haley!
Grubbs proposed to me.
Do you believe that?
I... I mean, maybe I do like him.
But like isn't love.
And... and like isn't marriage.
Anyway, enough about me.
We should be focusing on your music video.
They're expecting you in wardrobe.
After that, hair and makeup.
The live portion will be at Tric...
"Oh, thanks, Miranda."
Five minutes, Haley.
Alex.
I just want to apologize
about the sex tape.
I know you and Julia put
a lot into this film.
The sex tape was yesterday's problem.
You put a lot into this film, too.
You did great work. Maybe your best work.
But that won't matter if
nobody shows up to see it.
You need to keep Josh's...
personal life under wraps.
Our film is a love story
between a guy and a girl,
not a guy and a guy.
I think that's why they call it acting.
How many openly gay
leading men can you name?
Doesn't make it right.
Doesn't make it okay.
It's just the way it is.
I just don't think it matters.
I hope it doesn't.
But we can't afford to take that risk.
Julian can't afford it.
You have until tonight to
give Paul his money back.
What's that supposed to mean?
How could you do this to us?
And to the movie? And to Alex,
for that matter?
Hey, I'm an actor, okay?
I travel a lot. The road gets lonely.
You know what? Save it. Alex told me.
You didn't think we would
put two and two together
with the extortion?
I'd have you arrested,
if it wasn't for the film.
I wasn't behind the extortion.
I wanted the tape to get out.
My ex-boyfriend is threatening to out me.
That's not my problem.
One bad Indie film isn't
gonna kill my career,
but a scandal like this could.
A scandal like this
could kill us right now.
Oh, stop being so dramatic.
U think that's dramatic?
Wait till I have you fire Alexander.
You wouldn't. I might.
How could you do something
like that in public?!
And better question...
What imbecile would mistake
me for my mother?!
Maybe it's not that bad.
"Clothes over blows"?!
It's the second biggest
scandal of the week!
Well, what's the first?
Oh, God.
Grubbs, you seen Haley?
Uh, I think she's with Miranda.
Can I get you something
to drink while you wait?
Yeah, sure.
What'll it be?
You've never asked me that before.
I'm a little off my game today.
Just Miranda.
Ah. That sounds like
when I first met Haley.
I'll have a whiskey and water.
Actually, you know what?
It's still daylight outside.
Hold the whiskey.
I mean, at least Haley liked you.
Miranda just keeps shooting me down.
Haley hated me in the beginning.
How did you change things?
What did you do?
Nothing. There was nothing I could do.
One day, she just decided let me in.
You can only do what you do, man.
Nathan, have you seen Haley?
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
No, I didn't know that.
Can you tell me why Katie was...
Yeah, any information would be helpful.
And could you have Tanesha give me a call?
Great. Thank you.
What can I get you boys?
Can I get a grilled cheese
with chicken fingers,
extra fries, and a chocolate milkshake?
What? I had leftover Chinese
for breakfast. I'm starving.
Okay.
And a vanilla shake for me.
So... how much did you miss your Uncle Skills?
Oh, come on, man.
It better be more than that.
That's what I'm talking about.
Can I tell you a secret?
Let's hear it.
I know someone who missed
you even more miss Lauren.
She was pretty sad that you left.
I bet she's happy now that you're back.
I don't know, Dawg.
Things are different now. She moved on.
What's moved on?
Mouth stole her from me.
You believe that? My friend.
Or at least my ex-friend.
So you're not gonna be
friends wit Mouth anymore
because he stole miss Lauren from you?
Yeah, well, friends just
don't do that, Jamie.
Well, you stole miss
Lauren away from me first,
and we're still friends.
You want the bad news
or the really bad news?
How about the bad news?
Well, your girlfriend
is the second biggest
Internet scandal of the day.
"Brooke Davis caught in
sex act with boy toy!"
I cannot believe they
confused me with my mother!
Well, in their defense,
she was being blocked by
Alexander's naked body.
Which brings me to the really bad news.
"Alex Dupre and Josh
Avery in steamy sex tape.
Click here to watch."
They released the sex tape.
I know. I sold it.
I'm sorry. You did what?
I did what was best for the film.
We had to cover our investment.
Don't take it personally.
Don't take it personally?
You mean that my father
didn't consult me about this?
That's kind of personal, dad.
And on top of that what about Alex?
How could you do that to her?
It was Alex's idea.
Hey, Skills.
Hey, Millie.
I need to ask you something.
Is it about Marvin and Lauren?
Yeah.
You know about that?
And you're not upset about it?
Of course I'm upset,
but I want Marvin to be happy.
So, why'd you come back?
I just missed my life here.
It's hard starting over in a new place.
It's hard starting over, period.
Lauren was my girl.
And Marvin was my guy,
but we took them for granted.
I guess we made our beds,
and now we have to sleep in them.
* after all
hello?
Haley! Thank God! Where are you?
Um, I'm at home.
Home. Well, what happened?
We're waiting for you.
What are you waiting for?
Um, your video shoot.
What is going on with you?
Nothing. I just...
It's just music.
Just music?
Haley, we're spending 50,
000 dollars a day on this video,
and I am not shooting sock puppets
in front of a white sheet!
So get your ass back here now!
I got to go.
Haley, I'm serious.
Please tell me there's an emergency
or... or give me some reason
I can sell to the label
as an excuse for why you're
not onstage right now.
I'm making soup. Haley...
Haley!
They were in Katie's room.
That's how I knew who you
were when you called.
I just told her that I
wouldn't represent her...
It's not you.
I also found her lithium in the garbage.
Her behavior gets a little...
Unpredictable without it.
How unpredictable?
Let's just say you should be careful.
Mom, I finished my puzzle.
You want to come see?
Um, in a minute.
Oh, are you making grandma's special soup?
Oh, cool! Don't touch! Jamie!
I didn't mean to... look...
look what you did! Go to your room!
But, mom! Just go to your room!
Haley...
What happened?
They've been calling all day.
You just... You just walked off the set?
It's a big deal, babe.
All right. Hey, hey. It's okay.
Just... I'll call them.
You go upstairs and relax.
Let me clean this up.
You know, I'm okay.
I don't need any help.
I just want to be alone.
It's gonna be okay, Haley...
I want to be alone.
No comment.
Look, the thing is,
we didn't want any of this to happen.
We...
Well, I wanted that to happen, obviously,
but not so publicly.
I don't understand why
you just didn't tell me.
Should have.
I feel like an idiot, mother.
I yelled at Paul
because I thought he
stood you up for dinner.
Why keep it a secret?
Unless, of course, you're ashamed of it.
Well, I've never been ashamed of it.
We're not ashamed of it.
Oh, my God.
Fine.
If he makes you happy,
will be happy for you...
So long as I do not have
to hear or see any more...
Details.
Deal.
And you... no more... You know, outwork.
All work and no play
promise.
You're really okay with this coming out?
Yeah, cool by me.
Let the world know.
Clothes over bros.
Yes.
Hello, TMZ.
Uh-huh. That was actually my mother,
Victoria Davis.
Yes.
V-i-c-t-o-r-i-a.
Vocal track, take 1.
Hey, I have something of yours.
Thanks for letting it be
a part of my wardrobe.
Every time I stepped onto set,
it reminded me
that someone believed in me.
And now that the film's wrapped,
well... thank you.
Well, you've come a long way
since I gave you this watch.
Which is why I don't understand
how you would allow Paul
to release the sex tape.
Hope you're not doing this for Josh.
I didn't do it for Josh.
I did it for you and the movie.
You saved my life... Literally.
It was the least I could do.
I needed to let you know
that I believe in you, too.
Hey, what happened, man?
You were almost finish with this thing.
That's not work.
Thank you.
Is mom still mad at me?
It's not you, buddy.
Your mother really loves you.
She always will. Promise.
Let's put this thing back together, huh?
Um...
It's just missing one thing.
I'll be right with you.
Watch the glass, please.
Have an accident?
Can I help you?
I'm here for Clay.
I mean, my photo of Clay.
I know I said you could send it to me,
but I decided that I want him now.
Well, that's unfortunate
because that print's
already been shipped,
per your instructions.
Could take weeks.
So I guess you're gonna have to
get used to being without him.
Excuse me.
Clay, she's here.
Katie?
All right, Quinn, listen to me.
I talked to her roommate,
Katie's unstable.
Yeah, you're damn right. She's unstable.
She's standing in my gallery
telling me that she wants you.
She's about to see how unstable I can be.
Quinn, I'm being serious.
Just be careful and get the
hell out of there, okay? Please.
Okay.
Promise me.
Yeah, I promise.
Um, I'll just tell her I'm
gonna close up and head home.
Okay.
And just call me as soon
as you get out of there.
And, Quinn... I love you.
I love you, too.
I feel sorry for you.
Can't you see how sad he is?
Stop pretending like you
know him and leave us alone.
That's cute. You said "us."
But it was obvious he never
even told you about me.
You need to go now.
I see the way he looks at you.
But you don't know the way he looked at me
the first time he saw me.
He'll never look at you like that.
You'll never be Sara.
Neither will you.
We'll see about that.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
It's part of the game, bro.
You know what I mean.
You there?
Could we just play for a while?
Sure.
I miss her.
I know.
Maybe you should focus
on your music, Haley.
It will see you through.
What if it doesn't?
I'll be here.
What's the difference between
a whore and Alex Dupre?
The one is payed for sex and the
another do it for free.
And another is a turns out
was it for Davis
vacationing down under...
It was her mom.
I guess cougars do live
in Australia.
Okay, here's the deal.
I'm tired of the entire
world thinking I'm a slut.
Thinking?
So at this moment,
you and I are officially together.
What are you talking about? The sex tape.
I don't look as bad as if I
made it with my boyfriend...
Who loves me
you're welcome.
Wow. You look nice.
Well, I was gonna get
dressed for a wrap party,
but now I don't have to.
To my boyfriend, Julian Baker
who survived a day of sex,
lies, and videotapes.
Nice.
Mm.
I almost forgot.
That came in the mail for you.
"You and a guest have
been cordially invited
"to attend the official unwrap party
for 'seven dreams 'til Tuesday.'"
Brooke Davis caught in a
sex act with her boy-toy.
When I'm upset, I bake.
And I was really upset.
Thanks.
Look, I'm sorry.
I never meant to come between you guys.
I don't know how to handle
all of this, Lauren.
I don't, either.
I just know I wanted to see you.
I did, too.
But...
I can't do this to my friend.
I'm sorry.
Ancient architecture... *
she's not gonna go away.
And even what I said thing
this is just the beginning.
Priest on TV: And do you,
Sara take this man, Clay Evans,
to be your lawfully wedded husband,
from this day forward,
for better or for worse,
to have and to hold,
to love and to cherish
until death do you part?
I do. I do.
Haley!
Move!
Are you okay?
Haley!
What happened?
I'm gonna go call my mum.
Sync by fant0m - corrected by chamallow
www.Addic7ed.Com