*****
******
I'm having money problems. dad.
serious I need your help.
You're not an investment
I'm interested in.
I'm not screwing lucas.
I gave lucas to you,And i can
take him back.whatever i want.
Tonight's about us,Right?
Why haven't you told him How you feel?
Doesn't matter now,Does it?
I will tutor you.
You have to remember
That i can't stand you.
There's no reason You should be here.
State championship.
I'm not gonna lose that game.
Tomorrow night's game Is
the last one i'll ever coach.
I really want This championship.
Say goodbye To basketball.
No!
Lose that game.
I'm in trouble. How
could you be so stupid?
How much is it gonna
take To make this go away?
Be an awful shame if the
ground Next to your brother
Started getting crowded.
don't u think?
Bet against the
ravens Tomorrow night.
Make yourself some money.
What are we gonna do,Dad?
You're gonna lose
The state championship.
It's over between me And brooke.
I love you,lucas.
One Tree Hill
Season 4 Episode 9
and there is no joy
in tree hill tonight
because the ravens have
lost the state championship.
whitey durham is the
picture of a broken man,
and you have to wonder
if this opportunity will
ever come around again
for the tree hill ravens.
there are tears,and
there are questions,
starting with what
got into scott?
i mean,he's got a
lot of explaining to do.
no doubt about it
hearts are breaking
in tree hill tonight.
I love you,lucas.
I love you,too,peyton.
We've been through
So much together.
You don't -- You
don't understand.
I've been holding this
in For a really long time.
And i need you to know...
I love you.
I'm in love with you.
You look like crap.
Yeah,just been dealing
With some stuff,you know?
Besides,I'm way too wired to sleep.
Do you realize,In less than 24 hours,
We're gonna be State champs?
I don't think so.
What? Come on,man.
With you,me,skills --
No way pontiac beats us,You know?
We can't win it,luke.
We're not going to.
I needed the money,okay?
You said it was over
That it was just one game.
It was just one game. They
said It was just one game,okay?
But...
Now we have to lose.ok?
God,nathan,What are
you talking about?
This is whitey's Last game ever.
He's been chasing this
dream For 35 years.
What about whitey?
Or mouth?
Or skills,with college?
What about me,nate?
This is the last game I'll ever play.
I'm sorry.
You know...
The night before
I joined the team,
We battled each
other On this court.
I guess we'll be doing
The same thing tomorrow.
Lucas,you only play 15 minutes a game.
You can't change this.
I can try.
And i hated you
That night we played.
I thought you changed,But...
Guess i was wrong.
Good evening,Ladies
and gentlemen.
And welcome to what
may be The biggest day
In the history Of tree
hill ravens basketball.
10,000 fans will pack
The rbc center tonight
To see the ravens battle
Top-ranked pontiac academy
For the state championship.
For coach whitey durham,
Only 32 minutes remain
In a long and storied career.
A little early,Aren't you?
I know,coach, But.
i've been waiting For
this day my whole life.
Me too,son.
Me too.
You said,"oh"? Hold on.
Peyton say,"i'm in love With you,"
and you say,"oh."
Nice work,player.
She caught me by surprise.
What was i supposed to say?
Not "oh."
Okay,What else did you say?
I mumbled something about us
Being friends,and then i left.
And you believe that
That you and p.
Sawyer Are just friends?
Look,you know what,
Skills? For a long time,
i thought We'd be something more.
It just never seemed To work out.
At a certain point,
You got to face the fact
That it's not meant to be.
Even if she wants more?
She's just confused
She's had a hard year,
And i happened to be there
To rescue her a few times.
Maybe you're the one Who confused...
'Cause you didn't just happen
To rescue her a few times.
You didn't just happen to
run Back into school that day
Or save her From psycho derek.
Peyton happened to be there,
But you chose to be there.
So maybe you ought to
think About that.
No,when the boy buys The balloon,
It's a total volume Of one cubic foot.
If he blows up the balloon
At .1 cubic feet per minute,
How fast is the radius
Of the balloon increasing
When he only blows it up Halfway?
I don't know about the
balloon,But this blows.
When am i gonna ever
need To know this?
When you're failing calculus
And want to graduate.
Wait,That's right now.
Okay,let's take a look At
mr. Miller's last test.
Why don't we take a look
At mr. Miller's next test?
That's where they keep them,Right?
How do you know that?
I hear things.
So,how come If you're a student,
You have access To all the tests?
It's no wonder You have a 4.0 gpa.
are you kidding me? It's
called An honor system,
And it's not like i can
access Tests to my own classes.
You need a few extra bucks.
I need a few answers.
How about you sell me the
test? Name your price.
Do you know the meaning
Of the word "honor"?
Of course you don't. It's you.
You know,i really -- i just
Can't deal with this right now.
Let's just pick this up At the game.
The game? The state championship?
You really do hate me,Don't you?
Yep. See you later.
We missed you At the banquet.
Your son was named The team's mvp.
Karen...
Take a shower,Get dressed,
And see if you can find
What's left of your dignity.
Nathan is playing His last
high-school Basketball game ever,
And you're going to it
Whether you like it or not.
So,i got scouts From
three different schools
Coming to watch us play Tonight.
Man,we win this thing, I'm gonna
have my pick Of scholarships.
You gonna tell him he's not
Going to college or should i?
It's one game.
It's one High-school
basketball game.
You think it really
matters If we don't win?
I don't know.
How about you ask them?
I can't believe whitey
Wouldn't let us ride the bus.
And thanks to haley,
We're gonna miss the game
Because you had to stop
and pee Every other mile.
This sucks.
I'm pregnant,And i'm
not feeling very well.
I don't mean it sucks
Because we're gonna be late.
It sucks Because peyton's here.
You guys seriously need
To work things out.
I mean,when i was
In fat-girl therapy...
Look,maybe role-playing.
It's when everyone speaks
As someone else. It might help.
It could make things horrible.
That could be fun,too.
***********
My name's rachel,and i'm a
Dumbass who's failing calculus,
And i really like to
hit On married guys.
See? Fun.
Kind of like When i
slept with nathan.
Damn,that was good.
Okay. Peyton here.
I like to steal boys,
but i'm Afraid to tell
them how i feel.
Speaking of stealing...
Hi,i'm brooke,and i stole
My friend peyton's artwork
So i could put it On
my clothing line,
And i never even said Thank you.
Ok, Peyton here again.
Have i mentioned
That if you love me,
You're probably Gonna die soon?
See mothers one and two.
Brooke.
My name's rachel,And i have red hair.
Oh,i am gonna Kick your ass.
Hey,hey,stop it. Stop it!
I never congratulated
you On your pregnancy.
Although you have to
admit It's pretty strange.
Strange? How?
How keith was there
For dan's child
And now dan wants to
be there For keith's.
You really gonna do that To nathan?
It's one night,deb.
It's one night For your son.
You know,the pacing's Not
gonna make me any smarter.
Besides,the stress can't
be Good for the baby.
I'm not pacing for you.
I'm pacing for nathan.
He's worked most of
his life For this.
I just want it to
be perfect For him.
Just so you know,I
wouldn't have slt with him,
Even if he wanted to.
But we definitely Would have made out.
Can you just finish The exam?
I have to go To the bathroom again.
You were wrong.
You said i was afraid to
tell Lucas that i loved him,
But i did. I told him last night.
He doesn't want to be With me.
You can smile now.
You believe this,man?
Me and my boy representing
For the river court.
Hey,how these pills
work,Anyway? I mean,
How they keep you alive?
They slow down my heart rate
So i can't go full-speed.
That's why whitey only
lets me Play part time.
Maybe he only play you part
time 'Cause he got me full time.
Listen,I got to talk to you.
Nathan's gonna throw
The game tonight.
Remember when we saw him
talking To that daunte guy?
He's going to.
- We got to tell whitey,man.
- We can't.
That'll break his heart
More than losing this game.
What about my heart?
What about your heart?
What about the other
nine guys On the team?
I know.
And that's why We
got to win this game
You and me.
How?
We freeze out nathan...
And play The game of our lives.
Haley?
Come on,you've been in
there Forever. We got to go.
Haley...
Oh,my god.
Let's go,ravens,let's go!
Let's go.
- How you doing,haley?
- Not so good.
I'm sure You'll be next.
Maybe we should try to
get In touch with nathan.
No,i don't want him to know,
Not during the game.
Sara lestage?
Okay,this is a bunch of crap. Come on.
Look,our friend has
been Waiting a long time.
So?
So? She's pregnant,And
she's in a lot of pain.
I know cheerleaders
expect Special treatment,
But guess what -- i never liked
The cheerleaders in my school.
It's probably Because
you looked like that.
Guess who's gonna
wait A little longer now.
Like hell she is. Come on,haley.
Excuse me!
I'll call security.
Yeah,call security. Why
don't you call the police?
Tell them you're discriminating
Against cheerleaders.
Can we get a doctor,Please?
listen to me, I don't care how special
you are In your little high school.
You can't just barge in here.
- What's going on?
- What's going on is
Our friend is pregnant
And she's in a lot of pain
And this bitch is about
To get her ass kicked.
Okay,just calm down.
I'll take a look at her.
You can all wait in the
lobby And cheer for something.
Thanks,you guys.
You're gonna be okay,Haley.
- Slut.bitch.whore.
- Thank you.
Great day For basketball.
Better day For making some money.
Nathan's gonna carry The shame
of this for The rest of his life.
Maybe you should have helped
him Out when he needed it.
Oh,we are almost there,Deb.
Deb?
You're gonna be fine.
Ligament pain brought
on By stress is common.
Your test results don't
reveal Anything abnormal.
Here's your term of your
Pregnancy,your baby's sex.
T-cell count is normal.
My baby's sex.
Um...i'm sorry.
Did you not want to know?
No,it's okay.
Okay,folks,this is the One
we've all been waiting for.
It's the tree hill ravens
And pontiac high school
For the north carolina State
basketball championship,
Brought to you by chili's.
I want my baby-back,
Baby-back,baby-back...
Barbecue sauce.
Gigi silveri,Ladies and gentlemen.
1,2,3...ravens!
Where's haley at?
She's probably putting
money Down on pontiac.
Pontiac's jarvis will jump it up
Against tree hill's Nathan scott.
And the ravens win the tip.
Ball!
Dude,Give me the ball!
Lucas scott with The
first basket of the night.
He looked a lot like The
old lucas on that shot.
Another turnover By nathan scott,
And jarvis slams it home.
Pontiac leads by 9.
Ball!
Skills,Give me the ball,man!
Skills takes it to
the hoop And scores.
The ravens still trail by 10.
Jarvis beats scott again
For another slam dunk.
Lucas scott With another shot in.
He sure picked the right night To
have his best game Of the season.
Still,the ravens are digging A deep
hole Against this great Pontiac team.
So,what exactly did he say To you
Lucas,When you told him.
- What?
- He said,"oh."
Boys can be so dumb.
Yeah,well,i probably Shouldn't
have been surprised.
I asked him once Who he wanted
next to him When his dreams came true.
He said you.
Why would you Tell me that?
I would have given anything
To hear him say me.
Scott tries to double-team,*******
**********
Hey,how about you get Off the floor?
Why don't you Get off my ass?
How about i beat your ass Instead?
Come on,i dare you.
Just before halftime,
And a fight has broken out
Between the tree hill ravens
And the tree hill ravens.
Well,that's how we
started This season.
I guess that's how we'll end it.
At the half end, Pontiac's
leading tree hill,
36 to 21.
i have to say it's
incredibly unfortunate
how the ravens have come
apart at the seams.
after hanging together
through thick and thin,
through good times and bad,
for these ravens to fall
this far is stunning.
and the worst thing
about it all is this --
i mean,after a stellar career,
perhaps the best ever to
wear a ravens uniform,
you find yourself questioning
scott's character.
to walk away from the game
on these terms is shameful.
it's a disgrace,really.
whitey durham is the
picture of a broken man,
and you have to wonder
if this opportunity
will ever come around again
for the tree hill ravens.
That was 18 years ago.
Most of you Weren't even born yet.
Back then,i didn't know
That there'd only be one
chance To erase those words
This chance.
The rest of your
life Is a long time.
If you lose,you lose.
But don't lose this way
Playing selfish,
Bickering with each
other On the court.
I promise you...
It'll stay with you.
Six turnovers
that's not The nathan scott i know.
I got worried When
i didn't see you.
It's okay. Everything's fine.
Everything's fine.
I need to ask you A question.
If i don't go to duke,
If i don't play
College basketball...
I mean,if today is the
best It ever gets for me...
Will that be enough?
Of course.
Nathan,as long As
you're a good husband
And a good father...
To your son.
What?
It's a boy,nathan.
You're gonna have a son.
Although,I have to tell you,
Someday he's gonna
tease His father
For playing like crap In
the state championship.
You might want To change that.
And nathan scott has come Out
on fire in the second half,
Taking the ball to the hole On
the ravens' first Three possessions.
Pontiac's lead cut to 9.
What do you think You're doing?
Trying to win. You gonna help me?
No.
But you can help me.
A steal by lucas scott,And
the ravens are heating up.
Oh,they're already hot,Mouth.
Another dunk by jarvis,and the
Pontiac team goes back to 11.
Taylor knocks the ball away.
Lucas scott... Heaves a
long pass To nathan scott,
Who slams it with authority.
Ravens back within 9.
Pass skills to scott,
Who lays it in.
What teamwork.
The lead now only 5 With time
running out In the third period.
With just under six
minutes left In the game
Skills,scott,To scott,and yes!
Another slamma-jamma!
Ravens strike back
At pontiac once again.
we're early in the fourth quarter,
and we got ourselves a ball game.
It's okay,mrs. Scott.
Welcome back.
Back to where?
You're in a chemical-dependency
Treatment facility.
If it helps... Your
son is playing great.
nathan scott has really turned
it on here in the second half,
leading his team's comeback.
well,if you stuck around,
you've been rewarded
as nathan scott is leading
the ravens on what just might be
the greatest turnaround
in state championship history.
Let's go,ravens,let's go!
They won't win. The kid's
just making it close.
Bear,i sincerely hope You're right.
Pontiac trying to seal The victory.
Jarvis' shot. Blocked by lucas scott!
Out of bounds,But still pontiac's ball.
Skills,Go back in for lucas.
Looks like coach durham's
Putting skills back in the game.
We're almost All the way back.
I know i'm only supposed to play
15 minutes, But this is my last game.
Feeling good?
I feel great.
Good. Let's keep it
that way. Have a seat.
Let's zone up The inbounds!
Skills lands a 3! Wow!
Ravens within a bucket With
only 1:45 left in the game.
Pontiacs with the ball.
Clock winding down.
Jarvis to the hoop!
Rejected by scott!
Controlled by the ravens.
Oh,my,ravens with the ball!
Birds trail by 2,23 seconds left!
You have made a hell Of a comeback.
You played as team.
Even if we lose this thing,
It's still a damn
fine Moral victory.
Now,maybe that's okay with you.
Maybe you want to look back
And tell your grandkids
About the state championship
You almost won.
No way. We're winning
this game,Right,luke?
You tell me.
We're winning this game.
All right.
Lucas,by my count,you've
Played about 14 1/2 minutes.
You got 23 seconds left In you?
Yes,sir.
All right.
Listen up. Nathan...
*********Just breathe.
Can't have you popping out
Another cheerleader right now.
It's a boy.
- What?
- i have a boy .
Haley!
You know,say what you will About the
ravages of sports In this corporate age
Where overpaid athletes
expect Prima donna treatment,
But there is still
something So unifying
About sport In its purest form --
When athletes rise Above themselves
And touch greatness And,in doing so,
Remind us all that we also
have Greatness inside of us.
You're sexy When you talk like that.
1,2,3...ravens!
Let's go,ravens,let's go!
Hey...it doesn't mean anything
If you can't hit the shot.
Sounds familiar.
Let's do this,Little brother.
Okay,this is it.
10,000 people now stand In unison
As the ravens need a basket
To tie and force overtime
Or a 3-pointer to win it.
Nathan scott has the ball Out top.
20 seconds left.
What's it gonna be?
Okay,kid. What's it gonna be?
10 seconds left On the clock now.
Nathan kicks it out to
skills. Now 5 seconds!
ball ! ball !
Skills passes back to
nathan. Nathan has it!
Scott loses jarvis,And
he drives for the hoop!
He passes to lucas
for a 3 And the win!
It's good! I don't believe it!
Lucas scott drains A
3-pointer at the buzzer,
And the tree hill ravens
Are champions at last!
Gigi,can you
We win! We win!
Who the man,baby?
You're the man,baby.
Haley!
You did it!
we did it.
Luke!
Oh,my god!
Oh,this is amazing!
Yeah! This is a dream come true.
So who do you want Standing next to you?
Go.
It's okay. Go.
Hey! Nice shot.
Nice legs
A little chickeny.
Well,I'll be seeing you.
I'll be seeing you.
Hey,peyton!
- It's you.
- What?
When all my dreams come true,
The one i want next to me
It's you.
It's you,peyton.
Look,i want to make a deal With you,
Try to make things right.
You don't have that
kind Of money or power.
I'm not an idiot. I know
You have people to answer to.
But you built your plan On the
shoulders Of a kid with a dream.
Can't blame him for going
A little weak in the knees.
weak. You think he looked weak?
'Cause he looked pretty damn Strong to me.
I'll be in touch.
You know,I didn't pick nathan
Because he was the star Of the team.
I picked him 'Cause
he was dan scott's son.
Turns out the
kid Actually has a soul.
Never would have bet on that.
You and peyton Together now?
I saw the kiss.
Maybe.
It's about time,man.
Hey. You played Like a champ tonight.
I played like half a champ.
If you wouldn't have made That shot,
I would have never forgiven
Myself,so thank you.
So what are you
gonna do About daunte?
I don't know.
Deal with it,i guess.
Whatever he does to me,I can take it.
Besides,if this was The
last game i ever played,
At least it was A good one,right?
Hey,we're gonna take off.
I'm getting kind of tired.
Thanks for taking care Of me.
- Yeah.
- No big deal.
If you died,Who would tutor me?
I graded your quiz.
You got a 94.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
Oh,hey. Don't forget your purse.
There it is. Thank you.
94. Nice job,fondle-me elmo.
Maybe you're not Such
a dum-dum after all.
Got a present for you.
It's the transcript
i got In the mail.
Okay.
Hey,you're getting A "b" in gym.
Look at the name.
What?
I could pass calculus
In my sleep.
You're the one
flunking out,Penelope.
Then why are you getting Tutored?
So i could get you this.
And this,my dumb friend,
Is the key to the cabinet
With the answers
That we're gonna steal.
Unless,of course,You
don't want to graduate.
So how is My little nephew?
Fine. How's his uncle's heart?
Ah,it's fine.
How you feeling,haley?
Hales. You know my
girlfriend,Peyton,right?
- Oh,god.
- What?
You -- since when?
Since now,i hope.
Well,i'll let you know.
Hey,peyton,can i talk
to you For a second?
Yeah.
Okay,i'm liking
This conversation.
Would you like To
have it exclusively?
Sure.
With who?
By the way,i forgot how much
Of a good kisser you are.
Well,maybe you should Come by later,
And i'll remind
you For a few hours.
I'd like that.
This is good,isn't it?
Us.
It's perfect.
stop it. You can't be doing this.
Uh,i've been doing
this For 17 years,dan.
Then it's time To
take a night off.
Seriously,you're pregnant.
It's been a big day.
Let lucas and me lock up.
It'll get you off your feet
And give me a chance to
spend Some time with our son.
Okay.
Hey,dad.
Haley and i are about to leave,
But i just wanted to say...
I'm sorry. I couldn't do it.
Don't be sorry. You be
proud of that victory.
I'll deal with daunte.
So,lucas,how does it feel
To win the state championship?
Always wanted a second
chance At that...
And at this.
Feels surprisingly good.
Which one,being the state
champ Or talking to your old man?
Both.
Just wish keith Were here,too.
So the doctor said you're
fine,You and the baby?
Yeah. We're fine.
We are all gonna be fine.
Listen...
There's a reason that i
played So bad tonight at first.
What do you mean?
Nathan,look out!
Haley!
Haley! Baby!
Haley! Oh,god!
Nathan,what happened?!
They just hit her,man!
I'll call 911!
Lucas,stay with her.
Son of a bitch!
What did you do?!
Nathan!
He's dead.
You killed him,son.
- Go on.
- Dad.
Haley needs you,Nathan.
Your child needs you.
Go!
She's been hit by a car. You got to help her.
What's her name?
Uh... Uh,haley.
How long Has she been pregnant?
I don't know. A few...
Passed out. I got him.
Hold on.
Heart's not beating.
I got a full cardiac
arrest. Requesting backup.
time is running out now,
and i tell you,you got
to feel for nathan scott.
i mean,sure,he has
made some mistakes,
but you get the sense
that if this is how it ends,
he's never gonna forgive himself.
and lucas scott is being swarmed!
i wouldn't doubt it if they didn't
carry the kid out of here tonight
and never bring him back.
i have never seen some
of these kids so happy.
and can you blame them?
they've been waiting a long
time for this moment.
Lucas and haley are
In the hospital.
It's bad,peyton. It's really bad.
and there at the center
of it all is whitey durham
standing alone,taking it all in.
ladies and gentlemen,
the tree hill ravens
are champions at last.
and there's not a
dry eye in the house.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-–°“∞»ÀÕı
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-