Previously on "one tree hill"...
Where to ?
Your place.
Clay, quinn is haley's sister.
She has a lot going on right now.
Stay away from her.
You were a huge hit last night.
They think you're amazing.
You don't think i look like
"a frumpy whore on bingo night ?"
No !
If i did, would i ask you
to model full time ?
Honey, i'm home.
Let's do this.
I told you it was realistic.
Hey, honey.
Alex and i worked everything out.
Isn't that great ?
Dan : "nathan scott :
A basketball star's love child."
Like father, like son, huh ?
She's just so certain.
You don't remember
meeting her at all or... ?
You're actually starting
to believe her, aren't you ?
I heard about your problem.
I was wondering if i could...
you could what, help ?
You save your help
for people who don't know you
And stay away from me and my family.
You've reached renee.
Leave a message.
I trust you had a nice flight.
I have a proposition for you.
Okay, folks.
That's a wrap !
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Um, we, uh we haven't
even shot anything yet.
You might want to call
your agent, son.
You're serious ?
Hey ! Whoa.
What a pity.
I just found my motivation.
This hot body of yours
has just inspired me
To do something
that i've never done before.
Oh, yeah ?
Yeah.
And it's gonna take
a lot of hard work,
a long, long time.
And i'm gonna need you to start
by taking your pants off.
Oh, that sounds amazing.
But alex is coming over to work.
You two were up half the night.
It's all business, brooke.
I don't know. She seems to have
really come around.
I don't buy it.
Once a ho bag, always a ho bag.
Now, as i recall, you...
You might want to consider
what you are about to say
Very carefully.
Now come kiss me
till ho bag shows up.
You're up early.
My shot at peace and quiet...
The west coast wakes up
in three hours,
And my phone starts ringing. Nice.
Did you come down for a swim ?
Yeah, i tried but, uh, couldn't.
I've been afraid of the ocean
since i was a little girl.
Mm. Sharks.
Immensity.
You know, i thought
if i just threw myself in and...
Well...
it didn't quite work out.
You should start smaller,
like a toe.
Work up to an ankle,
maybe even a shin. Who knows ?
Yeah, i'm more of a "yank
the band-aid" kind of girl.
Wait.
Go. It's fine.
Hey, man.
Oh, just relax, all right ?
I...
Okay, i'll get into it.
Yeah, fine.
I'll meet you at your place.
Time to find a phone booth
And change into
that super-agent costume.
Yeah, if only it were that easy.
Um, i hate to run, but...
Go.
Save the day.
Okay. See ya.
Oh, no.
Oh... no.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
I never called marvin !
Keep it down, giselle.
I'm trtrying to write.
Besides, i thought
you were mad at him.
I was "ignore him
for a couple of hours" mad,
Not "disappear for the second
night in a row" mad.
Well, you can thank me later,
but you were way drunk,
So i texted him from your phone
And let him know you were safe.
"Melvin...
"got my drink on with alex.
"If you're done being a tool,
You should come rock out
with your co..."
Oh, my god.
Nope, just little old me.
But i do work in mysterious ways.
So you want me to go on your show
And tell the world my story ?
Dan : that's right.
And you're gonna be on my side ?
Why would you do that ?
Nathan's your son.
It could ruin him.
But you're the one
telling the truth.
Haley :
you're not telling the truth.
About what ?
Renee.
You said you didn't know her
and you didn't remember her.
I don't.
Haley, we've been through this.
Why can't you just believe me ?
Her number is all over
your old cellphone bill.
Nathan !
Excuse me...
Why aren't you explaining yourself ?
Because i shouldn't have to.
But if you insist...
I'm a professional
basketball player.
Girls get ahold of my e-mail,
my telephone number.
They try to contact me.
And when they do, i reply
to them and tell them to stop
Because i'm happily married to
a woman who loves and trusts me.
So i guess i did lie, haley...
But only when i told them
that my wife trusts me.
Marvin.
Don't you mean "melvin" ?
Please don't be mad even though
you have every right to be.
Alex called me
after she left julian's,
And i was kind of already drinking
Because i thought you didn't think
i was pretty enough to be a model.
When did i say
you weren't pretty enough ?
Of course you're pretty enough.
Then maybe we could skip
the whole fight
And you could just be
really excited for me,
Because... it's official...
You're looking at the newest
face of clothes over bros !
Oh, well, not this face.
But once it's cleaned up
with a little makeup...
Congratulations, millie.
I just wish i was the one
you wanted to celebrate with.
Anyway, you'll understand if i
can't stay and rock out with my...
Marvin !
That was alex.
Of course it was.
Well, at least she texted me.
I got to go.
Clay : this situation's
like a war, nate.
We're gonna lose a few battles.
Just stop with the metaphors
And tell me what the hell
happened this morning.
Simile.
What ? Similes use "like"
or "as"... "like a war."
Guys.
We lost the rainstorm
body spray campaign,
And it looks like
the shoe deal's going away.
What ?
Temporarily.
This is unbelievable.
I know it feels like
the sky is falling,
But when something
like this goes down,
Marketing executives
distance themselves
To protect their brands.
All right, almost always,
They come back
as soon as the air clears.
"Almost always" ?
Look, we knew there was a risk
When we decided not to deal
with renee,
But it has become a bit
of an issue with the bobcats.
They don't want me back ?
No, you are far too talented
for that,
But they're using it
to their advantage,
And negotiations have slowed.
Again, like i said,
we expected this.
More importantly, nate,
The whole agency's
on this, all right ?
Everybody respects your decision
to fight this,
And we've got your back.
You just got to have
some faith in us...
And in each other.
Clay.
He's gonna have a career
when this is over, right ?
Haley, i'm not gonna let
anything happen to him.
Because you didn't see
how dark he got the first time.
Look, this is a staring contest.
Our best chance
at having her blink first
Is if the press gets tired of this
And nobody makes this story
any bigger than it already is.
Dan : i'm gonna make
this story huge.
But you don't trust me.
I'd have to hate my son
to tell your story, right ?
You're smart.
I like that.
That means
my grandchild will be smart.
Well, i was
in nathan's situation once.
I refused to recognize
a child that i'd fathered,
And it was the second-worst
mistake i ever made,
But i made it in part
because nobody forced me
To look at the consequences
of my actions.
By coming out in support of you
And allowing you to tell your story,
I'll be forcing nathan
to take responsibility...
If not emotionally,
then at least financially.
He'll never forgive you.
I've made my peace with that.
There she is.
I know... i'm late again,
And we still haven't finished
- - calliope : the inventory.
I also found that shipment
that went missing in new mexico,
Balanced the register
from yesterday,
And took the liberty of ordering
some bellissimo fabrics from milan.
You're gonna love them.
I can't wait.
Isn't she amazing ?
Um, i guess, but that's my job.
Not anymore, miss thing.
The fashion blogs
are still buzzing about you.
You are officially a model.
Your only job now
is to worry about being pretty.
You... you might want to worry
just a smidge more.
I know.
I was out late.
And, brooke, i am excellent
at multitasking,
And i'd be happy to keep my
administrative responsibilities.
Nonsense.
I am not gonna have the new face
of my company doing dirty work.
Now off you go.
Do whatever models do
in their spare time.
Just be back this afternoon
for a swimsuit fitting.
Swimsuits ?
Mm.
Wow.
Okay.
I mean... great !
Oh...
Welcome to clothes over bros.
Hey, man, how you doing ?
I'm doing better than nathan scott.
I mean, that dude
can't catch a break.
What do you mean ?
You haven't checked the board.
Oh, god, mouth...
He's losing his endorsements.
Sports is breaking the story
tonight at 6 : 00.
If charlie asks for me,
tell him i'm...
I'll be back later.
Clay !
Hey.
What, did you run
into some kryptonite ?
You need a friend ?
You have no idea.
Come on.
Seriously,
you've been reading forever.
Look, some of it's
supposed to be funny.
You're not laughing.
You're not even smiling.
Maybe i'm laughing on the inside.
Are you ?
You're not.
You're like,
"wow, does she suck," on the inside.
You're like, "she..."
This is good.
Like "i hate it,
But there's a story
in there somewhere" good ?
No. These scenes
are genuinely good...
Sweet, subtle, funny.
Where did this come from ?
Well, i woke up,
And i was watching millicent sleep.
And she was, like, totally busted.
So i asked myself
what it would be like
if i was that tragic,
with, like, no self-confidence.
And then i just added a boy.
Who are you ?
Stick around.
Maybe you'll find out.
Unfortunately, i can't stick around,
Because you are three hours late,
And i have to meet brooke for lunch.
Oh ! Come on.
Tell her we're on a roll.
Um, no.
She's already a little jealous
of our working relationship,
But maybe we can
meet back up tonight.
It's a date.
No.
Date-ish ?
Work.
Work... date.
We can still pay her.
For what ?
The story's already out there.
For a retraction.
The money she wants
is a drop in the bucket
Compared to the rest of your career.
It's too late for that.
Nathan, you're being stubborn,
And i know
i was against it at first,
But if she were to get out there
And say that this whole thing
has been a lie...
We're not paying her, haley !
We're not giving this woman
a dime of our money.
Quinn : you're really worried
about this.
There's just so much riding on it.
Quinn, i'm not in tree hill
for a vacation.
A while back,
i went off the rails a bit...
Emotionally, and...
Luckily i had earned
enough capital with the agency
That they didn't fire me.
They just scaled back
my client roster
And suggested
i spend the summer here...
Pull myself together.
And then nathan's scandal happened.
So the calm, cool exterior...
Is kind of a lie.
Just when i was beginning to wonder
If we had anything in common.
Quinn, i shouldn't be here.
Nathan doesn't want us hanging out,
And i, uh, i have to respect that.
No, look, clay...
I'm sorry.
Uh, thank you for this.
I mean that.
You're really great.
Chase...
What brings you in ?
Hey. Uh, just doing
a little shopping for mia.
You guys have been together
a long time.
Mm-hmm.
What about you ?
I heard julian moved here.
That must be... awesome.
Uh-huh.
Or not so awesome ?
No.
It's amazing.
I'm just a little annoyed
Because at first
i had him all to myself,
And lately he has been working
with one of my models.
Mm.
Well, i wouldn't worry.
I'm sure it's harmless.
I mean, guys, you know,
don't even really...
Like... models.
What are you doing today ?
That depends
On why you're looking at me
like a piece of steak.
I would have offered to spot you,
But i max out at like 180... ish.
You know, i don't believe
in killing the messenger, mouth,
But every time i've seen you
lately, it's been bad news.
They're running a story at 6 : 00
That says you're losing
your endorsements.
Is it true ?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, nate.
Yeah, me too.
I heard about your demotion.
How long are they gonna keep you
locked up in the basement ?
The truth ?
Till i do a story on you.
Then do the story, mouth.
Nate... i'm serious, mouth.
You've already done
far more than i could ever ask.
Take care of your career.
And then he finally looks up,
and he's like,
"after reading this,
I think we should be
in a relationship."
He said that... "relationship" ?
Well, i mean, he put "working"
in front of it,
But a relationship
is a relationship.
Except in a working relationship,
You never, under any circumstances,
No matter how tempted you are,
have sex with the other person.
You're aware of that, right ?
I think that's sort of a gray area.
It's actually black-and-white,
Crystal-clear, written in stone.
Fine, crabby.
Whatever !
Sorry.
It's just brooke's my friend,
Even if she did give my job
to calliope.
Tell me you are not regretting
your decision.
This modeling stuff is awesome.
I mean, it's hard work,
but it's "pretty people" work.
I don't know.
I was good at my job.
Administrative work
is for fatties, millicent,
And you are not a fatty.
You...
Are a plus-size model.
I take it you looked
at nathan's phone bill.
If i pay you, what do i get ?
I go away.
No, i'm sorry.
That's not good enough.
I want a retraction.
I want a public letter
That says this whole thing
has been a lie.
Fine, if that's what
will help you sleep at night,
But it won't be the truth.
And the price has gone up...
$250,000.
That's crazy.
Actually, that's the estimated price
Of raising your husband's child
until the age of 18.
Do we have a deal ?
I'll tell you what.
You can have until 8 : 00 tonight
to decide.
After that, i have other options.
Brooke !
Hello !
One sec.
Got it.
Can i borrow you ?
Mm.
Want to tell me why you were
mounting your ex-boyfriend
In the back room ?
Because you weren't available.
Very funny.
I'm serious.
This morning i looked over
at this big, sexy body,
And i thought to myself,
"why aren't you making
men's clothes, brooke davis ?"
Mm-hmm.
Clothes for bros ?
Ka-ching !
But in order to make men's clothes,
You need a fit model
for measurements.
You were my first choice,
but, alas...
I was busy with alex.
I get it.
Well, i'm here now,
And i'm all about
taking my clothes off for you
In the back room,
So you can send
your little boy toy packing.
You're very sweet,
But i think
i'm gonna stick with chase.
I'm already halfway through
his measurements.
But don't worry, baby.
We're all business.
Hey, chase, break's over !
Drop your pants.
I want back on the air.
I obviously have an opinion,
But at the end of the day,
i work for you.
You are aware of what's
on the board for tonight ?
Yeah, nathan scott's
losing his endorsements.
I took the liberty
of getting a quote from him.
Nice work.
Glad to hear you've come around.
Don't.
It's the press.
They've been calling all day.
Beat it, nerds.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
And as a favor, it would be great
If you wouldn't give clay
such a hard time
About hanging out with me.
I'm not a child anymore, nathan.
Are you sure about that ?
What's that supposed to mean ?
I don't know.
Running away from your problems
just doesn't seem very adult.
Says the guy who's afraid
to answer the telephone.
Look... if you want to sleep around,
I'm sure there's plenty
of guys in tree hill
Who aren't responsible for my career
That could probably
help you out with that.
You ever hear the one about
people who live in glass houses ?
Yeah, i have.
And if you don't like
living in mine,
You'll welcome to move back in
with your husband.
Nice, nathan.
You know, speaking of running
away from your problems,
Maybe you should try answering
one of those, coward.
I know you love to say
zero is not a size,
but technically zero is my size,
and those are granny panties.
These are a zero.
Really ?
My diet pills must be working.
Your vitamins ?
What ?
Oh, right.
Vitamins.
Okay.
Whatever.
I'll...
see if i can take these in.
Great.
Oh, and speaking of my perfect ass,
I understand from julian
You might be a little concerned
about our relationship.
Working relationship.
You have nothing to worry about...
Seriously.
I mean, i stripped naked,
And that boy didn't even flinch.
He is clearly so in love with you.
Well, you're not chase.
If only.
I asked the waitress
if there was a tall, dark,
And handsome boy
waiting for his date.
She pointed me here.
Sorry to disappoint, but your
"tall, dark, and handsome"
Is getting naked with
my "short, hot, and bossy."
Huh ?
He's doing some fit modeling
for brooke
At clothes over bros.
It's harmless.
I hope.
Hey, can i ask you something ?
Lose the shirt.
I'll go get a tape measure.
No, actually, it's about
being a songwriter.
Do you ever meet people on tour
That surprise you
with their talent ?
I mean, uh...
You know, somebody
who seems simple or goofy
Or even ditzy, and then... bam...
All of a sudden, they write
this amazing song ?
Hi. I'm mia.
No, you're not like that at all.
Maybe not,
but i used to be really shy.
And i think sometimes
all somebody needs
Is someone to look
a little deeper...
Unlock their potential,
like haley did with me.
Was that answer worth lunch
?'cause i'm kind of starving.
On me.
Baby, you are a genius.
The interest in the interview
with renee is off the charts.
You're not having
second thoughts, are you ?
Dan, nathan had a chance
To take responsibility
for this child,
And he chose not to.
Giving this girl a voice
is the right thing to do.
Well, we don't have a show
unless renee agrees,
And i haven't heard from her
since this morning.
You just leave that up to me.
It doesn't matter where i go,
you always seem to find me.
I just follow all the other girls.
They lead me right to you.
It hasn't been easy lately.
Then i guess
it's a good thing i'm here.
How'd you like
to stay the night tonight ?
Like old times.
Well...
That's up to you, isn't it ?
I called renee.
What ?
She said for $250,000,
she would sign a retraction.
Amazing...
The economy's crumbling,
And the truth keeps getting
more expensive.
Well, she's willing to say
this whole thing was a lie,
So...
You willing to believe it ?
I didn't come out here to ask
for your permission, nathan.
I came here to tell you
that i'm paying her.
Are you okay ?
No, i'm not okay !
Ho bag got naked in
front of julian !
"Ho bag" ?
Alex "my butt is the size
of a kumquat" dupr ? Oh.
She is so manipulative
And materialistic and self-serving
And naked and... brooke-ish ?
What did you say ?
Nothing.
Funny, i could have sworn
that i heard you speak.
I meant she just seems
A little bit like you were
in high school.
He always wanted high-school brooke.
Can i put my pants back on now ?
I'll take that as a yes.
You blame yourself
for nathan's troubles.
I wasn't a great influence...
The girls, the parties.
Do you think he did it ?
No.
Then stop blaming yourself
and fix it.
Stay the night.
I miss this.
Is that what you want ?
That's what i need.
Nathan scott is tree hill local
Who overcame injury and adversity
To achieve a dream he had
since childhood...
A dream to play
professional basketball.
But lately nathan's career
has taken a backseat
To allegations of an affair
That led to the pregnancy of a fan.
In my opinion, continuing
to report on these allegations
Without any further evidence
of their validity
Is a reckless attempt
on the part of this network
To boost ratings.
Now, i'm not saying
athletes are above the law.
I'm saying it's up to science
To determine
the validity of these claims,
Not the evening news.
To date, there has been
no new evidence
To suggest that nathan scott
is guilty of these allegations,
And yet he looks guiltier
the more that we report on him.
Sorry.
I think i left my camera
in your bathroom.
For my part, i got into sports news
Because i think
reporting on athletes
Inspires people to be exceptional.
And while i've never been
an exceptional athlete,
I can strive to be exceptional
in my own way...
By refusing to bow to pressure,
By refusing to stoop to a level
that's beneath me,
Just like nathan scott
has refused to.
Found it !
Marvin : i believe in nathan scott.
But i also believe in my viewers.
I believe you don't want any part
In dragging him through the mud.
So if you want sports news
and not gossip,
Turn the channel.
Let my boss know that news
isn't just about ratings.
It's about people and integrity,
But mostly it's about truth,
And that still means something.
I am marvin mcfadden,
and this is sports.
Or at least... it used to be.
Her retraction at this point
won't change anyone's opinion.
It might.
They'll all just assume
we paid her off,
And we will have,
Which will just make us look
even more guilty.
But you know this, haley, which...
Makes me think the only reason
you have left to pay her off
Is that you're starting to believe
She might be telling the truth.
Haley, if i'm guilty of this...
Not only am i the kind of guy
that would cheat on you,
I'm the kind of guy
that would father a child
And then turn his back.
I'm dan scott.
If you think i'm capable of that,
You do what you have to do,
But i guarantee you,
if you've lost faith in me,
All the money in the world
isn't gonna fix it.
Yeah ?
You all right ?
No.
But it's okay.
If i was,
i'd be a pretty lousy person.
I'm sorry about earlier.
It's just been...
I know.
I'm sorry that woman's
lying about you.
I know you'd never hurt haley
like that.
And you're not a coward.
If anyone's a coward, it's me.
I'm not running away
from my problems, nathan.
I'm walking away from
something that's broken.
And that doesn't mean
that i'm not scared.
I just don't know how to let him go.
I guess you do it
a little bit at a time.
You're welcome to stay here
under our roof
For as long as it takes, though.
Thank you.
A candlelit pool-table-top
picnic dinner.
What's the occasion ?
I figured my man was gonna be hungry
After spending the day modeling
for his ex-girlfriend.
She get all your measurements ?
All but one.
Oh, yeah ?
What'd she miss ?
How much i love my girlfriend.
She forgot the most important
measurement of all ?
She didn't forget.
She just didn't have
a tape measure big enough.
Always with the best answers.
Always with the best lips.
If you ask it who's the fairest
of them all, i'm out.
Whoa, hey.
That was a joke.
Millie, i'm not mad anymore, okay ?
Last night was my fault.
I shouldn't have been so...
i think i made a mistake, marvin.
I don't know if i want this.
Then why'd you say yes ?
Because it made me feel special.
I mean, i felt competent
at my old job.
I felt smart and capable
and reliable,
But i never felt special.
I think...
You're the most special girl
i've ever met.
Thank you, marvin.
But that night, it was like
The whole world
believed i was special.
But who am i kidding ?
I'm not a model.
I'm just millicent.
Come here.
What are you doing ?
Funny...
You are definitely the same girl
Who rocked the fashion
industry's world the other night,
And she was a model.
Have you been through
any drastic changes
In the last 48 hours ?
No.
Then, uh...
Unless i'm mistaken,
you're still a model.
And if modeling
makes you feel special,
Then you should do it,
'cause you deserve to feel that way.
You deserve to feel special
every second of every day.
All right, i'll explain this
in a minute.
Take your time.
I am happy to watch.
You work.
I am happy to watch you work.
It's very interesting d work-ish.
I'm gonna get that.
Brooke.
Come in.
Thanks.
This'll just take a second.
You're fired.
I have a contract.
I'll pay you out.
It's worth the loss.
This is so unnecessary.
Julian and i have
a working relationship.
That means no "doing it."
Maybe.
But it's recently been brought
to my attention
That the way you behave is a lot
like high-school me used to,
And i would be insane
To let high-school me
anywhere near the man i love.
The man i love,
Who shouldn't even think
About sleeping anywhere
but the couch tonight.
I'm sorry.
What did i do ?
What you didn't do is tell me
that ho bag got naked for you.
Oh, that.
Yeah, that.
You... couch.
You... fired.
Ciao, bitches.
You can sleep here if you want.
Thanks for meeting me.
Have a seat.
I know it must be hard to believe
That dan's gonna put you on the air
And let you speak freely
About how awful
his son has been to you.
You could say that.
There's something
i think you should know.
When dan heard about you,
he reached out to nathan,
And nathan shut him down,
just like he always does.
So ?
So dan isn't doing this
to help nathan see the light.
He's doing this to bury nathan.
And the deeper nathan is buried,
The more money he'll have to
pay you to dig himself out.
So...
will you do the show ?
Okay.
I'm in.
I didn't do it.
I couldn't.
That's what sets you apart from her.
It's one of a thousand reasons
why i could never,
Under any circumstances,
cheat on you.
I don't want to see you
lose your... your dream.
Lose her ?
She's right here.
And i'm never letting go of her.