.eimaj tuoba klat ot ereh ton m'I
I just always wondered
if he knows who I am.
He found a picture of you once.
What'd you tell him?
I told him you were dead.
It's mia.
She's the magic, Peyton, and I'm telling you, her
spark is getting squashed by this ass of a singer.
Oh, this is for you.
It's supposed to bring good luck.
I know we just met, but I just
wanted you to know that I'm here.
Good to know.
Any student who walks out
that door fails this quarter.
Say goodbye to
extracurricular activities.
Say goodbye to sports, like basketball.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
One Tree
Hill Season05 Episode06
Well, well. Hello, jamie.
How would you like to
come live with grandpa?
Mama! Daddy!Mama!
Hey, baby. What's the matter?
You did have a bad dream, buddy?
He tried to get me.
Who did?
Grandpa dan. He escaped.
From heaven?
Prison.
Did you tell jamie my dad's in prison?
- Maybe.
- Why?
Because he's in prison.
Why, what'd you tell him?
We told him he was dead.
Man, how am I supposed to know that?
I mean, he be asking me stuff.
Well, you have to lie to him, man.
He's having nightmares now.
Look, you know, he be tricking me.
He get all, like, cute.
Yeah, I know. He does
have that going for him.
Well, all right, you
said he asked you stuff.
What else did you tell him?
Not much. Just the truth.
Like?
Like "the man" killed tupac and biggie,
never date girls named
bevin, and santa claus is black.
You say anything about the easter bunny?
A bunny that lay eggs?
You know how many questions
he would ask me about that?
All right, just stay clear
of the whole dan thing
until we figure out how
we're gonna handle this, okay?
Fine by me.
I won't say a word.
can I help you?
Is that your room?
It used to be mine.
Want to see it?
You sure?
I mean, I could be a psycho.
You don't know.It happens.
You're not a psycho.
You're Peyton.
Come on.
It's different.
- molly.
- Molly.Yeah.God!
You know, when I lived
here, the walls were red.
A red bedroom? That's crazy.
Oh, no. It was everything
I wanted it to be.
But I mean, this is nice, too.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
So, you really loved him, huh?
Lucas?
What, are you some kind of psychic?
Was it really true love always?
One would think that since they charge
by the hour for this little venture,
you might be more punctual.
Um, you're brooke's mom, right?
Victoria.
Also known as the money
behind this, whatever this is.
And you're the producer?
Yeah, I'm Haley. I'm sorry.
It's nice to meet you. I'm
a good friend of brooke'S.
Ah, brooke has so many good
friends since her success.
Having said that...
I'd like to have a
listen to our investment.
Okay, I'll just give Peyton a call.
No, I really don't have time for that.
And god knows what gutter
Peyton sawyer is lying in.
So, if you don't mind...
you know what? I'm gonna wait in there.
Yeah, that's fine.
Um, that person creeps me out.
Listen, you're gonna
do great. You're fine.
We just want you to play her a few bars of
"no good, " and we'll make her happy, okay?
Right, like that old
thing could ever be happy.
So, obviously this is the acoustic
version, but Mia really is great,
and I think you're just gonna love her.
So, if you want to come
into the booth with me...
I'm comfortable here.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Okay, Mia! Whenever you're ready!
The song is called "no good."
She's really nervous.
Can you blame her? It's like she's
playing a private concert for satan's wife.
okay. Thank you.Thank you.Thank you.
No, no, no, no, no!
The song's called "no good"?
Appropriate.
Okay, so, this is a huge waste of money.
I would say it was a waste of time, but
you all failed so quickly, it really wasn'T.
So when you locate
Peyton in that gutter,
you let her know I'd like to speak with her
before this catastrophe goes any further.
Okay, so, tell me again, what happened?
She walked in...
we walked in and bitch-toria
was there waiting.
Next thing I know, she scares Mia
half to death, then Mia's gone.
- Gone where?
- I don't know.
She just packed up her stuff, said she
sucked a bunch of times, and then took off.
Can you blame her? She
must have been humiliated.
That was ugly.
Can you just give us a few minutes?
What is Lindsey doing here?
She came with me.
We're gonna have lunch.
I don't want her here. You know
how temperamental artists are, Haley.
So, apparently, are label owners.
I don't want anyone in the studio.
Anyone or Lindsey?
Anyone including Lindsey.
Look, I know everyone loves
her. That's great.Fine.
But right now Mia's gone, and she's in here
running her mouth about how ugly everything is.
She didn't mean anything by it, Peyton.
Don't get mad at Lindsey
just because Mia's gone.
I'm not mad at her.
- You sound mad at her.
- I'm not.
I -- maybe I just
don't like her.
Well, you don't have to...
I'm gonna go, Haley.
Yeah, I'll see you.
Hey, Mouth.
You guys scared me.
What's -- what's going on?
- We're hiding from Alice.
- Why?
Have you met Alice?
Carlton.
E wocausrking on the weekends
sucks, and we've all had it.
That's why...
you got to talk to her.
Me? Why me?
You're the only one that's
ever stood up to her, Mouth.
Listen, guys, I don't know.
Look, Mouth, either you talk
to her, or we go with plan "B."
What's plan "b"?
We pool all our money together, we
hire a hit man, and take her out.
I say plan "B."
Come on, guys. She's not that bad.
Come on, Mouth. Admit it.
You hate her, too.
And do you know why?
Because Alice is a bitch.
Peyton is a bitch!
Your mom's a bitch.
What happened?
She went to the recording studio
and freaked out Mia, who is M.I.A.
Imagine that. And now
I don't have an artist.
I'm sorry, Peyton. I'll talk to her.
Well, it's either that or my fist talks to her
face, and that's gonna be a longer conversation.
I will. I'm sorry.
Thank you. I'm gonna see you at home.
I got to find Mia.
My mother.
- Oh, no.
- What?
- It's him!
- Who?
The hot guy I met at the opening!
Hey, honey.
- Step aside.Hot guy coming through.
- What?
So, listen, I need to buy a
gift for my boss's birthday.
Something nice.
Just please don't spend
my entire paycheck.
I will come up with something.
Okay, cool.
I'll come back by later.
Got to quell a mutiny at work. Bye.
Bye!
Excuse me?
He's cute, huh?
But he was buying a gift for someone.
Oh, please, like Mouth's dating his boss.
You, um...
you like the crew, right?
Crew?
Yeah, you know, the guys at work.
If by "like" you mean "loathe."
I think you'd really like
them if you got to know them.
And I know they'd like you.
Right. Like that's what I'm gonna
do -- go have beers with harry.
It's jerry.
Exactly.
See you at the office.
I'm coming in, daddy!
You need your water
wings, fish face. All right.
Got it? Okay.
Style points for a big splash.
Let's see what you got, jimmy-jam.
Perfect 10. Perfect 10, buddy.
- Come on, nanny carrie!
- Hold on.
Perfect 10, huh, dad?
Throw me, daddy.
Jamie, your dad has to do his rehab.
That's okay. Come here, you
little monkey.You ready?
You splashed me!
- So?
Not so fun now, huh?
Splashing a little kid, huh?
You got a problem with
that? Let's see what you got.
- Get her, daddy!
- Yeah, get me, daddy.
**********
Mama!
Mama! Mama!
Jamie! Honey, I'm here!
It's okay. Mama's here.
No! I want my other mama!
Nathan, did you hear
what jamiejust said to --
******
Good morning!
Not really.
Can I fix yousome breakfast?
Uh, no, thanks.
I'm thinking I might dropa few pounds.
Oh, come on. You look great.
Yeah.
Where's Jamie?
With skills.
And Nathan'sat physical therapy.
So you'll just have to deal with
all this nicepeace and quiet.
Thought I might gofor a quick swim.
Um, carrie...
I don't want to sound
weirdabout this, but, um...
could you not wear a bikiniin the pool?
Oh, my gosh. Of course.
I'm so sorry.
It just seemskind of
inappropriate, you know, around Jamie.
You know, you're absolutely right.
It was poor judgmenton my part.
That's okay. And, you
know, everything else is great.
You're really doinga wonderful job.
Thanks, Haley. I appreciate that.
And I am so sorry.
It won't happen again.
I'm serious, mother.
Peyton was really upset.
And anyway, this is my money.
So just stop.
I don't understandwhy you act like this.
"Why?"
Well, let's see.
I'm staying in a motel.
We have modelsthat are a size
four that should be a size zero.
My daughter is hell-benton
destroying her company.
First of all, I'm not
destroying anything.
And second, zero is not a size!
Our models are... tall!
Tall and fat!
Well, maybe you should
go backto new york...
I mean, if you're this unhappy here.
You have my word, all right?
I won't meddle in
Peyton'sso-called record label.
Thank you.
What I will not do, however, is hold my
tongue when I thinkyou're making a mistake.
Now eat your breakfast.
Oh, I don't knowif I should.
I am a size four, after all.
But you're not a model.
You're my daughter.
You're far too talentedto
waste your life as a model.
So eat.
Nice work, kid.
You're halfway to sleepingin
a van and checking in to rehab.
Daddy's in rehab.
Different kind of rehab.
What other kind is there?
Um, you want to goto the river court?
Did you knowmy grandpa dan?
Yeah, I think we'll goto the river court.
Uncle skills, how comethey
sent my grandpa away?
It's clean. I promise.
Nathan: You told Jamie my dadwent to
prison because he didn't cleanhis room?
Look, man, I was stuck.
I mean, he come up to you with
thosebaby-seal eyes like...
I mean, he just gets youall confused, man.
Well, you're supposedto play
dumb, not scare the hellout of him.
Look, I panicked, all right?
Anyway, man, I don't like lying to him.
Nate, you got to talk to him.
We need to talk.
Did you tell Lindseythat
you don't like her?
Kind of.
What the hell, Peyton?
She's been nice to you.
Okay, in caseyou haven't noticed, I have a
few other problemsto deal with right now.
Do you see this office, this big, empty
office for a labelwith no artists?
You mean the label Lindsey
recommendedI help you with.
Okay, I can't do thisright now.
You have to apologizeto her.
Luke, Mia is missing, okay?
Brooke's mom is killing me.
I quit my job, I moved back
home, and I can't do thisright now.
- Can I help you?
- No.
No, you cannot help me.
That is the last thingthat I want.
Go home to your girlfriend, luke, please.
Okay.
What's so important coach got
to see me onthe weekend for, man?
Well, well.
Mrs. James-scott.
Have a seat, Q.
All right.
So, mrs. Scott here says that
you recently left her class despite the threats
of receiving a failing gradefor the quarter.
Yeah, that was justa
little misunderstanding.
But it's all good now, right, mrs. J-s?
Uh, no, quentin, I warned you about
that, and I'm gonna stand by it.
But I do know how
importantbasketball is to you,
so I figured out a way for
youe to makup your grade.
This book is called"les misÈrables."
Do you know it?
Good. I'm glad.
Now you can read itover
the course of the year,
turn in biweekly book
reportsfor extra credit,
and as long as you meetyour
deadlines, you'll remain eligibleto play.
And if I don't?
I'm not gonna givepreferential
treatment to any studentin my class.
What do you say, Q.
Do we have a deal?
I'll think about it.
That's a great move.
Shame no one's gonna see itthis
year unless you read the book.
Gosh, man! What is this, bad cop/dumb cop?
I said I'd think about it.
What's it to you, anyway?
Well, it matters to
Haley, so it matters to me.
She tends not to give upon
people as easily as I do.
Or maybe wifey'sjust a little afraid I'm
about to break her man'sscoring record, huh?
So she assigned mesome crap book
'cause she knowI won't do it.
Here's the problemwith
that theory --
you're not good enoughto beat my record.
Right, you don't think so?
No.
Okay.
There's one thingthat
every great player has,
and that's the willto do
whatever it takes to be the best.
I don't see thatin you, Q.
And at this point, you don't even have a
team, so, um, maybe you should thinkabout that.
And what team you got, washout, huh?
You so great, right?
Where your team at?
I have a team.
Every day, I wake upand
I put on the uniform --
mistakes, regret, what could have been.
And if I could go backand change all that just
by reading a book, trust me, I'd read the book.
And if not...
well, lcome to the team, Q.
Yeah, that's good.
And I could do a whole lineof t-shirts
with slogans like, "zero's not a size"...
and "my mom hatesall my friends."
Hey, she's not horribleall the time.
You haven't been aroundfor
the last couple years.
She cares about me.
Brooke penelope davis!
I'll be in the back.
Did you schedule a
conferencecall with macy's?
- Yeah, 'cause I was
thinking - - well, don't!
In case you have to hear
it, you have zero business sense!
Mom.
Let me finish.
For the last three years, I've been calling
the shots, and look how this companyhas grown.
You're a talented designer, brooke, but
you don't spin the strawinto gold. I do.
Truth be told, you are
not smart enoughto do it.
Ice queen!
Stop being such a bitchto your daughter!
And did my daughter pay youto say that?
No, I came up with that onefor free.
Well, I advise you keep yourlittle
underachieving mouth shut
because my relationshipwith my
daughter is none of your business.
No, it is when you tear her
downand call her stupid.
See, the truth is, you're
actually worriedshe's smart.
And that's a threat to you because when she figures outhow
to do the business side of this company, goodbye, victoria.
You're one to talk.
Once I convince brookethat you're just
another leech sucking off the money teat,
you will be broke and worthless.
I meant what I said.
Stop tearing down your daughter.
She might have to biteher tongue with you
because you're her mother, but you are not mine.
No, I am not.
As a matter of fact, it's quite
clearyou never had a mother.
Yeah?
Oh, my gosh.Lucas, I
didn't --
it's okay.
Lindsey...
will you marry me?
Say no.
It's what I didwhen he asked me.
Did you fall asleep?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, you better get ready.
We're having dinner with
Nathanand Haley, remember?
Oh, yeah. All right.
Did you talk to her?
I-I tried.
Well, I mean, yeah, I think
she knows my position.
So... we all heard.
You're in linefor the
on-air reporter job.
It's because you stood
upto her. That's why.
She must respect that.
I don't know. I...
what's with the powwow?
Want to get back to work?
You get back to work.
You hag.
Whoever you are, you're fired.
Security!
Where the hell is my cane? Haley!
Hey, have you seen my --
oh, um, where's --where's Haley?
I think she ran out for
somelast-minute dinner stuff.
I told her I'd do it, but she wanted to.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
Okay.
So, are we not supposedto
wear pants tonight?
Funny.
I think I overdidmy rehab, and
so I'm havinga little trouble.
This might not be the
mostappropriate job for you.
Stop it.
Nannies are like doctors.
You let your doctor see
youlike this, don't you?
That depends on wherehe
takes me to dinner.
You know, Haley asked me notto
wear a bikini in the pool.
She said it was
inappropriatearound Jamie.
- There you go.You good?
- Yeah.
Listen, carrie, I'm sure that
Haley didn't meananything by it.
I mean, I know she likes you.
Yeah.
It's just kind of ironic, you know?
I mean, if she's worried about someone
getting turned onout at the pool,
she probably shouldn't
let yougo shirtless.
So, what's going onwith your
writing, luke? How's it coming?
Good, actually.
I'm kind of on a roll lately.
You got to to beloving that, linds.
Yeah, the editor sideof me is.
The girlfriend sidemisses her boyfriend.
So, how'sphysical therapy, nate?
Pretty good, man.
I'm sore a lot these days.
I spend a lot of timein the pool.
Yeah, he's been
lookingreally good in there.
- His rehab's going great.
- Yeah.
Where's your head, hales?
Um, quentin.
I gave him a second chanceto
kind of turn things around,
and I'm not sureif he's gonna take it.
He willif he wants to play.
Lindsey: Well, sometimes
youjust don't know about people.
I mean, I gave Peytona second
chance, and she didn't take it.
I have to tell you, I felt so horrible
about that, and I know Peyton did, too.
Victoria has literallybeen
driving Peyton crazy.
Thanks, but there's more to itthan that.
Peyton feels like she hassome sort of
jurisdiction over lucasbecause of their history.
I was really hoping it wouldn'tbe
an issue, but clearly it is.
Lindsey...
Peyton's got a big heart.
Yeah, to go alongwith her big mouth.
I know I wentto an ivy league school, but if
she keeps it up, she's gonna get her ass kicked.
Okay! Easy.
Sorry. I didn't mean that.
I know she's a friendof yours.
I just wanted her to like me.
Yeah, it sounds like it.
What's so funny?
Uh, I'll tell
youwhat's not funny --
the factthat you're down here instead of
upstairs sleepinglike you're supposed to be.
I'm not tired.
- I'll get him.
- No, I got it.
Jamie, bed, now.
Daddy, can you take me?
Jamie, you're gonna
listento your mother, okay?
Now, go on upstairs.
We'll be up in a
coupleseconds to tuck you in.
He is so cute.
He uses it. Trust me.
And now he's scared to deathto
go to bed because of dan.
But can you blame him? Hell, I had
nightmares about dantill I was, what, 19?
- Think we should go talkto him?
- Yeah.
Excuse us.
Hey, and you are not
allowedto clean at all, okay?
You just make lucas do it.
All right. All right.
Cheers, ladies.
So, carrie, how's everything going?
Really good.
By the way, I completely agreewith
what you said about Peyton.
Just because someone has historywith a person
doesn't mean that's whothey should be with.
Buddy, I've been lookingfor that.
It keeps me safefrom grandpa.
Haley: Um, baby, listen, we, uh...
we try to protect youfrom
things because we love you,
and that's why we didn't tellyou
the truth about grandpa dan.
The truth is, um...
he did some bad things, and
he needed to go away.
Is he ever gonna come back?
Maybe. Someday.
But no matter what, you're
always gonna be safewith us.
Mommy and daddy are never gonna
let anythinghappen to you, okay?
Okay.
But just in case, can you maybe
checkin the closet and under the bed?
Yeah, I think so.
It's pretty nice, P. Sawyer.
Fully stocked barsteps from your
office, complete with a hot bartender, might I add?
Sorry to bother you.
Can I get an autograph?
Yeah.
- It's amy.
- Okay.
Well, okay!
So, aside from noticinghot
bartenders, how has yourlove life been?
No comment.
She sleeps around a lot, but
there's no one special.
You can be fired. You know that.
Um, yeah, but then she'd justcome work
for me, and you'd still bepaying her.
Okay.
I'm not calling myselffamous or anything, but the celebrity
makes ita little hard to meet somebodyyou can trust.
Oh, I'll get it!
All right.
Everything all right, guys?
Oh, poor thing.
We all have stuffwe're afraid of.
You know I'm deathly afraidof clowns?
No, I swear to god. It's really sad.
Hey, sorry to interrupt.
I just wanted to sayI've
been thinking about it, and, uh,
I'll do whateverit
takes to remain eligible.
I'm really gladto hear that.
All right, 6:00 A.M. Practice, Q.
Yes, sir.
I guess I'll leave y'allto it.
I got a bookI got to start reading.
Nathan:I'll see you out.
Way to go, coach.
All right.
You madethe right decision.
I'm comingfor that scoring title, and
when I'm done, I'm gonna erase you.
Yeah, that's whatI would have said.
Oh, that looks good!
Thank you.
Brooke:You're welcome.
- So, you guys ready to go?
- Yeah.
Hot bartender guycoming this way.
I told youhe couldn't resist.
Brooke davis?
Could you maybe sign thisfor me?
Who should imake it out to?
You can make it out to trickfor $37.
It's your bar tab.
I thought you were
askingfor my autograph.
Not really an autographkind of guy, especially
when I have no ideawho the person is.
Brooke davis. I have a line
calledclothes over bro's --
clothing.
More ofa
t-shirt-and-jeans guy.
Maybe if your namewas levi strauss.
Uh, my name is Peyton.
I actually have an officeright in there.
This is millicent.
And you know...
- brooke, right?
- Yeah.
- She makes clothes apparently.
- Yes.
Well, I'm owen.
Let me know if you want my autograph.
Nice work, B. Davis.
Shut up. Let's go.
You know what? I'm
gonna meet you at home.
So hot!
I'm sorry I disappeared.
I just needed timeto think
about everything, and, honestly,
I don't think I'm the
one todo all this with --
start your label with.
Why, 'cause you're scared?
Because I don't thinkI'm ready, and
I know how importantit is to you.
Okay, Mia.
Why do you write songs?
What do you mean?
When you think about
yourcareer, what do you want?
What's gonna be enough?
I don't know.
All right, maybe you're
right. Maybe you're not ready.
I want to help someone.
I want to reach that girlor that boy who wakes up
one day and feelslike it's not worth it anymore.
Why, 'cause you've beenthat person?
Maybe. It's like...
I don't needto be famous, and I
don't need all the moneyin the world.
It's not about that.
It's about that girlwho's having a
horrible day, and she hears your song,
and for five minutes, there's
hope, you know?
It's like, for five minutes, the world's
not such a scaryplace for her anymore.
You askedwhat's gonna be
enough -- that'll be enough.
That'll be more than enough.
Okay.
I take it back.
Maybe you are ready.
you're working late.
Someone has to, right?
mom, I know this has all
beenreally hard on you,
but I just need youto trust me, okay?
And no matter what happens, I
just wantedto tell you that...
I love you... and thatI appreciate you.
And... maybe I don't saythat enough.
Of course I trust you, honey.
More than that, I love you.
And I'm so proud of you.
I wouldn't miss thisfor the world.
Come here.
you're working late.
Someone has to, right?
Mom, I know this has all
beenreally hard on you,
but I just need youto trust me, okay?
And no matter what happens, I
just wantedto tell you that...
I love you, and thatI appreciate you.
And... maybe I don't saythat enough.
Whatever. You can lock up.
Lucas:I saw your light on.
Which isn't that surprising.
I know how hard you work.
You know...
you haven't been yourselflately, Peyton.
I mean, not the Peyton I remember.
Well, I haven't been that
Peytonfor three years.
What's going on?
Okay.
I went by my old house.
There's a teenage girlliving there now.
And she showed memy closet door.
And you knowwhat that said?
"Lucas and Peyton. True love always."
"Always, "
lucas --
that's what we were supposed to have
until you showed up in L.A.Three
years ago and ambushed me.
If by ambushedyou mean proposed to you?
Oh, yeah. Out of the blue.
A proposal that was drivenby some insecurity
that I have never been ableto understand.
Insecurity? Right.
Let me tell you how
you get"always, " Peyton.
When a man asks youto
marry him, you say yes.
You don't say noand call him insecure.
I never said no!
I said that I loved you and that
i did wantto marry you someday.
And -- oh, god, luke!
I wanted to so bad...
but you gave up on us.
- I gave up on us?
- Yes!
By proposing, i gave up on us?
No, by not waiting, you gave up on
us, and you knowthat's the truth.
That's great, Peyton!
You want to talk
truth, let's tell the truth.
Okay.
You gave up on me.
That's why you didn'tsay yes!
You didn't thinkI could do it.
You didn't think I could
getmy novel published.
Maybe you just didn't care, because
it wasn't about youor what you wanted.
Well, if that's the truth, if I never cared, then
how come every timeI see this stupid book,
I buy it --every
stupid damn time, luke?
You said I was great!
You said I could be great!
You said we were destinedto be together!
You said it to the
world, you said it to me,
and I wish you never had because
you did not meanany of it!
Oh, god.
I'm gonna go.
Okay, you know what? I want to pay rent.
I don't know how, but
I'llfigure it out.I just --
whatever this is, I don't
feel right about it.
It's called me being niceto you.
- Well, it needs to stop.
- Maybe you're right.
Tough day.
Sucks about carlton, huh?
Well, you're lucky.
Guess Alicekind of likes you.
God help youif that ever goes south.
Night, buddy.
I'm gonna head home.
By "home, "I hope you mean my place.
Actually, I'm not feeling very well.
Well, maybe you're noton-air
material after all.
I mean, if you're gonna
startgetting "sick" on me.
I'm -- I'm
sureit's nothing.
I'll get a good night's
restand be back to normal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I hope so.
millicent,  I want you to
reschedule the meeting with macy'S.
Your mom's notgonna like that.
It's my company.
And please do
me a favor --
call her victoria.
Don't call her my mom.
Okey
little man's out cold.
You need me to check for clowns?
- I kind of do.
- All right.
Good over there.
All right. You're good.
Uh, I think you forgotthe balcony.
Okay.
Thanks, husband.
Nice to know there aren'tany
monsters in the house.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
One Tree
Hill Season05 Episode06