So, what are you so afraid of?
I'm not afraid.
I'm not. I'm just not sure.
- Not sure of what?
- Josh.
- He wants to have the talk with Piper.
- What talk?
Three dates, no sex. There could only
be one talk he's talking about. The talk.
Safe sex, prior partners.
- Standard dating protocol.
- And sex equals relationship.
And you're not sure
you wanna be a couple.
Well, it's not that I don't like him.
Then what's wrong with
being a couple?
Well, I thought Leo and I were a couple.
And then we coupled, and he took off.
Well, men seem to have a different
definition of coupling than women do.
I do not think that's why Leo left.
- Hey, Prue.
- Hey, Dee. How are you?
- Hey, how's the party going?
- Great.
We're playing Squish the Squash,
and nobody's been able to catch me.
- Is the cake ready?
- Yeah, give us about five minutes.
Awesome. Hey, guys,
five minutes until the cake.
Thanks for doing all this, Piper.
I never would've
been able to afford...
Oh, hey, what are friends for?
Besides, it's worth it
- just to see the look on David's face.
- He's such a great kid.
Yeah, I know.
So much for my Saturday off.
That was Claire.
Something at the auction house needs
to be appraised, so I gotta go. Sorry.
- Bye.
Bye.
- There's no cheating.
- Be quiet.
You cheated. That's not fair.
I'll get it.
Help!
Let go of me.
- Help!
- David, no.
No! Help!
Leave me alone.
Help.
Let go of me.
Help me.
Help. Let go.
Help!
Let go of me.
- What did you tell him?
- I saw a creature
- with whirling eyes take David.
- And what did he say?
What do you think he said?
He thought I was nuts.
Yeah, well, it turns out David's
not the first one to be taken.
An inspector told me that
another boy disappeared yesterday
in the exact same spot.
A demon who steals kids.
Does it get any worse?
Yeah. Apparently it also happened
20 years ago. Same park, two kids.
- Did they ever find the kids?
- I don't know.
- You know, I could've saved him.
- Prue, don't go there.
No, I was just so surprised,
and I looked down at my hand and...
It was the first time you channelled
it through your hands.
Give yourself a break.
- Your power's growing.
- Yeah, I just hope no one saw me.
Okay, look on the bright side.
You won't have to squint
your eyes anymore.
You were starting to get
those little lines.
- So how's Dee doing?
- Not good.
It's frustrating not being able to tell her
who we are and how we can help.
Yeah, well, the sooner we get
to the Book of Shadows,
the sooner we can get
David back home.
An albino demon with whirling eyes.
Sounds like a whole chapter to me.
I forgot about the appraisal.
It's okay, just go. Phoebe
and I can look in the book,
- and we'll call if we find anything.
- You sure?
Don't you just hate cell phones?
Always out of range.
Call me.
Let go of me.
Help!
Leave me alone.
Help me.
Let go of me!
I can't see.
Why can't I see?
Mom?
Mom!
Nothing.
- Did you look under "whirling eyes"?
- About an hour ago.
I found demons with no eyes,
demons with four eyes,
eyes that grow legs,
but no whirling eyes.
Did you find anything?
I found some news clippings
about the kidnappings 20 years ago.
Both boys were taken
in the same place as David.
And one of them
was never seen again.
- Oh, great.
- But the other one was found.
It's right here.
His name was Brent Miller.
Look, honey, I know you're upset,
but that's not gonna help you.
It's not for me, it's for Dee.
I'm taking her a care package.
- Keep reading.
- "Brent Miller was discovered
two days after he was taken,
roaming the streets.
He was fine except...
...he'd gone blind."
- Blind?
- Yeah.
He claimed that some storm-drain
monsters stole his eyesight. Of course,
the authorities believed
he had just caught a parasite.
We can't tell Dee
that her son might be blinded.
Well, maybe if I could find
this Brent Miller guy on the Web,
he might know something
that could help us.
- I hope you're right.
- Piper, we're gonna find David.
- Prue Halliwell?
- Yes?
Hi, Eric Lohman,
Bay Weekly. Alternative press.
- Maybe you heard of us?
- Sorry.
No? Well, you will.
I was hoping you could help me
with a story I'm working on.
- On the auction business?
- No, actually on magic.
- Magic? Why would you come to me?
- I don't know.
Maybe because I saw you
levitate two people in the park
with just a wave of your hand.
I take that as a "no comment."
So, what are you, anyway?
Some kind of a David Copperfield,
Lance Burton?
- A freak of nature?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Look, Prue. Your friends
call you Prue, right?
I would like for you to leave.
Well, tough. Get over it.
I had my police sources
check you out.
It's interesting how your name
keeps popping up
in all these unsolved
murder cases, don't you think?
- What's that have to do with anything?
- Maybe nothing.
But if I wrote an article on it,
it might look like something.
- Your boss subscribe to my paper?
- Don't threaten me.
What are you gonna do? Are you
gonna make me fly into a wall?
Come on.
How clumsy of me.
Bet that took a lot of self-control, huh?
Not to use your powers.
You're a real credit
to your profession.
You know, that kid saw
what I saw too.
Cops get him, he's all
the corroborating evidence I need.
- Security.
- Prue, be smart. Work with me.
I'm gonna break this story one way
or the other. And when I do,
I can either make you
sound like Wonder Woman
or the devil incarnate. Okay?
Think about it.
Mr Miller will be in shortly.
Wow, what a great view.
- You can smell the ocean.
- And hear the traffic.
- Brent Miller?
- That's what they tell me.
- Hi, I'm Phoebe Halliwell.
- Phoebe,
allow me to introduce you
to Helmeth.
He's beautiful. So is this place.
Well, didn't think a blind guy
could live so well, huh?
Oh, no. No, that's not
what I meant at all.
I know you didn't. No, I design
software for the visually impaired.
Life has been good to me.
So how can I help you, Phoebe?
Actually, I wanted
to talk to you about...
...when you were kidnapped
as a child.
I'm sorry. I'm not...
I'm not very comfortable
talking about that.
I understand.
But I read a lot about it...
I said, I'm not interested
in talking about it.
- Okay, but this just isn't for me...
- I said, no!
Is everything all right, Mr Miller?
Yes. Lucy, please just show
this lady to the front door.
Miss.
No, you know what? I'm not leaving.
It's happening again.
In the last 24 hours,
two little boys were kidnapped
from the same park that you were.
Maybe by the same
monsters that took you.
It's all right, Lucy.
You believe my story
about the monsters?
- Yes, I do.
- Why,
- when everyone has always laughed?
- Maybe it's because
I've seen my share of monsters,
and I haven't told anybody about them
because I didn't want them
to laugh at me either.
Mr Miller, I know that you wouldn't
want what happened to you
to happen to these two little boys.
Please.
There were two of them.
I mean, terrifying creatures, really.
They...
...dragged me into a storm drain,
to a junction of some kind.
They held me down. I remember
blue sparks hitting my face.
My eyes felt like they were on fire.
And that was
the last thing I ever saw.
Why do you think
they took your eyesight?
I don't know.
But I remember them saying
something about auras.
Thanks again for the tickets.
Auras, auras. I know
I saw something in here.
Here it is, auras. Grimlocks.
"Underground demons
who roam from city to city,
killing powerful forces of good
by seeing the unique auras
that surround them."
"Which they're able to do by stealing
the sight of innocent children."
So they're like hit men
for the dark side.
"The stolen eyesight will last 24 hours,
but only if the children are alive."
Which means we have less
than 14 hours. "To destroy a Grimlock,
- gather Schisandra root..."
- Piper? Phoebe?
- I know that look.
- What's wrong?
A reporter saw me
use my powers at the park
and is threatening to write
an article about it.
- What?
- Does he have any proof?
- Just what he saw.
- So it's your word against his.
The difference is, his word is delivered
to a half million homes each week.
Everything happens for a reason.
Maybe it's time to let the world know.
Piper, being outed would only
make our lives worse.
We don't know that. At least
I could tell Dee what we're doing
- and give her some hope.
- No, Prue's right.
If we're exposed, we're gonna have
every crazy hounding us day and night.
Not to mention the media circus
on our front lawn.
- Remember E. T.?
- We can't worry about that.
We have to find those boys.
I'm gonna go and see Josh
and see if he has a map
or something of the storm drains.
- Storm drains?
- It's where these demons live.
Well, there's gotta be at least
100 miles of storm drains in the city.
I'll talk to Brent and see if he can
remember where they took him.
Brent?
Prue, the Book of Shadows said
the only way to kill a Grimlock
is to blind it with a potion
made from Schisandra root.
- Can you find some?
- Yeah, I'll try,
as long as that reporter
isn't following me.
Okay, be back soon.
Hey, what if Josh
wants to have the talk?
I'll tell him I have a headache.
All right.
Anything on the night sheet?
Medical examiner.
Thank you. Sent this over.
It's Jerry Cartwright.
A saint.
Donated millions to the
city's anti-drug program.
- M.E.'s saying he was murdered?
- Unless we tell him otherwise.
He's listing the c.o.d.
As a strangulation.
Problem is, the man died
in the middle of a crowd of people
and nobody saw anyone
lay a hand on him.
Inspector Trudeau?
Eric Lohman, Bay Weekly.
He's all yours.
I know who you are.
What do you want?
Cup of coffee would be great.
Okay. What do you say I pick
your brain about Prue Halliwell?
Name ring a bell?
It should.
Her name keeps popping up
in a lot of your murder cases.
A lot of the unsolved ones.
- Is that a fact?
- Yeah, I got my sources.
Cops love to talk, especially
if you pay them enough.
Get the hell out of here.
So I assume you know all about
Prue's unusual powers, right?
Boy, that stopped you cold.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Yeah, right. That's what she said too.
You two rehearse
your stories or what?
I saw her in action
in the park, Trudeau.
She waved her hands and magically
suspended the David Hatcher kid
and his kidnapper in midair.
It was...
It was very cool.
I just wish I had my camera.
Care to comment?
No.
Okay, I'll just change my story
to a police cover-up instead.
- I'm not covering up anything.
- Really?
Great, then I guess you've got
nothing to worry about.
Just remember, I gave you
a chance to work with me.
That's right.
- What was that about?
- Nothing.
You're gonna have to handle
the M.E. case on your own.
Why? Where are you going?
I'm assigning myself
to the kidnappings.
Why exactly do you need this?
A client at Quake is thinking
of throwing an underground rave
- and we might cater it.
- A party in a storm drain?
Yeah, he runs a
Roto-Rooter-type company.
It's kind of a theme thing.
Yeah. Well, sounds dank.
Yeah. Look, anyway, as long
as you're here, can we talk?
- Maybe later. I have to go.
- No, Piper. It cannot wait.
Somebody's a little anxious, huh?
This is important. It could
affect the rest of my life.
Well, not if we take precautions.
- What?
- I'm not saying I'm ready for that.
Because, in fact,
I'm not ready for that.
But when I am ready for that,
I'm just saying
I will be taking precautions.
Piper, what are you talking about?
Having sex.
You're not talking
about that, are you?
What are you talking about?
- My leaving.
- Leaving?
Yeah, I got offered a job
down in Beverly Hills.
I mean, it's not exactly my dream job,
but it's a good opportunity.
Look, my point is,
if I thought we had a future...
Josh, this is all just happening
a little too fast.
Yeah. I know, I know,
and I'm sorry. But like it or not,
you are the swing vote.
Now, if you don't
want me to go, I won't.
Okay, we need to talk about this.
If I ask you to stay,
then we're a couple.
And I'm not sure
if I'm ready to be a couple.
But if I tell you to leave,
and we could've been
a good couple,
then I'll never know if we...
I need more time.
I need lots and lots of time.
Hold that thought. Okay?
Yeah, hello.
I remember their faces.
It's like a nightmare
that never ends.
They took me into this big area.
And there were a lot of pipes.
I'm sorry. I mean,
that's really all I remember.
- That's okay, Brent.
- You're disappointed.
No, no. Not at all.
No. Someone that could
see your face might believe you,
but your voice tells another story.
Gave me away, huh?
You have a beautiful smile, Phoebe.
- How can you tell?
- I can hear it in your voice.
I can see it in my mind.
- What's the matter, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Brent, when they took you,
were you wearing a sweatshirt
with jeans and black high-tops?
Yeah. Yeah,
I think I was. How did you...?
And when you escaped,
were you running through water?
Yes. I remember that,
in the tunnel.
Okay, Brent,
I need you to think really hard.
Do you remember anything?
Anything at all about that location?
Did you hear anything
or feel anything?
All I remember is this...
...sound of this enormous
generator and...
- Maybe some cable cars.
- Cable cars?
- Yeah.
- Hey, do you have a map?
- Oh. Oh! That... That was so stupid.
- No.
I actually do have a map
of that area. It's over here.
What are we looking for exactly?
I don't know, a cable car
turnaround, maybe.
Or the generator that you heard
could've been a power plant.
Right, okay.
Here. Now.
See, on this map...
Okay, there are two
turnarounds on this page.
And there's a...
Right, here it is.
There's a power plant
right here on Varick.
How can you tell?
Well, give me your hand.
Okay, you feel these
three horizontal bumps
followed by the two vertical.
On this... On this map,
that's the symbol for power plant.
I better go.
Phoebe, how did you know what I was
wearing and where I was running?
I mean, are you like some
kind of psychic or something?
Like...
...only different.
- Right.
That's how you've seen all these other
monsters that you mentioned, isn't it?
Phoebe, you're a good person.
And that probably means
you have a strong aura.
Please be careful
with these monsters.
Don't worry, I will.
Don't worry, Billy.
My mom's got a friend
who's got supernatural powers.
She'll get us out of here.
Shut up.
Did you hear on the radio
about that philanthropist
who got mysteriously strangled?
It's gotta be the Grimlocks,
that's how they kill.
We're running out of time.
We've had, like, less than three hours.
- Did you get the Schisandra root?
- No, but I'm leaving now to pick it.
Look, did Phoebe get anything
out of Brent Miller that might help us?
- Who's Brent Miller?
- I'm not sure.
Prue?
I gotta go.
Andy, hi.
What are you doing here?
Working on the kidnappings.
I thought we should talk.
Yeah, well, I already told the police
everything that I know about that.
Not according to Eric Lohman,
you didn't. He stopped by the station.
We had an interesting chat.
Yeah, well, he's a reporter trying
to make a name for himself.
- You can't believe anything he says.
- Normally, I don't. This time, I do.
We've been down this road
too many times, Prue.
I know you're hiding something.
I have my suspicions about what it is,
but I've had to accept the fact
that you can't tell me,
or you don't wanna tell me.
Either way,
it's not just me anymore.
Lohman's onto you,
or at least he thinks he is.
And he's not gonna let go.
Prue, if you don't level with me,
I can't help you control this.
Andy, I'm just never sure if it's better
for you to know or not to know.
I remember a time when we could
tell each other anything.
There's nothing Lohman
won't do to get this story.
Watch your back.
Andy.
Thanks.
Bingo.
- Did you get it?
- Yep, I got it.
What's wrong?
Andy stopped by my office
after Lohman stopped by his.
I think he told Andy
about my powers.
- What did you do?
- Same as I always do,
I danced around the truth.
It just doesn't feel right anymore.
Oh, my God.
Where is the mother?
Oh, thank God.
Wait a second. Since when did
the Johnsons get a baby?
That damn reporter. Look.
- Okay, confused.
- That's Lohman. This is a setup.
We need to get back to where we were
before everything unfreezes. Go.
Don't forget to put
your hands up. Okay.
Don't look, just go inside.
Inside. Go, go.
Purse on right shoulder,
purse on left shoulder.
Purse on right shoulder.
Purse on left shoulder.
What do you know.
She has another power.
Gotcha.
- Is he still out there?
- Unfortunately.
Hey, you guys, I think I found
the entrance to the storm drain.
- What's going on?
- Didn't you see that guy
- parked out front in his car?
- Yes.
Yeah, well, that's the reporter
I told you about.
- He's staking us out.
- What?
He tricked us into using our powers
and nearly caught us.
But fortunately, we figured out
what he was doing
- before he could get any proof.
- Oh, thank God.
The only problem is,
how are we gonna be out looking
when he's camped outside?
We have less than two hours.
Hey, how's it going?
Mind if I use your bathroom?
Don't bother using
your magical powers on me.
I already hid the videotape.
- What videotape?
- Yeah.
You know, best I can guess
is somehow one of you stopped time
or rewound it, I don't know.
But, what I do know
is I've got the whole thing on tape.
- You're bluffing.
- Am I?
How do you explain your
sister's purse magically jumping
from her right shoulder
to her left shoulder instantaneously?
You screwed up, and I got the proof.
Okay, now, here's the deal.
I already got my story ready to print.
But what I really want now from you
is a tell-all exclusive.
All right? I'll write the book,
we can share in the movie rights,
- foreign sales, distribution...
- Get out.
It'd be a good thing.
All right. Okay. I'll just wait
out front until you're ready to talk.
- What are we gonna do?
- All right, look,
I will stay here and finish the potions.
You guys go try and find the boys.
Buy us some time.
Keep on freezing those Grimlocks
- until I get there.
- What about Lohman?
Don't worry about him.
I'll stop him from following you.
Lohman,
I've been thinking
about what you said
and maybe we can work
something out.
Yeah? Why don't I believe you?
Oh, I don't know. Maybe it's just
your reporter instincts.
- Busted.
- Nice try.
You did that, didn't you?
I know you did that.
Really? Prove it.
I'm not wearing
the right shoes for this.
Okay, talk about all roads
leading to hell.
Which way?
- Light, light.
- All right.
Brent said he remembered
a big area with pipes.
Oh, wait. There's a pipe juncture...
...that way. Okay.
So I guess this isn't a good time to ask
how it went with Josh and the talk.
- You're right, it's not.
- Okay.
Inspector Trudeau?
- Yes, Mr Miller.
- You wanted to talk to me.
- Is it about the kidnappings?
- Maybe.
Has a Prue Halliwell come
to talk to you by any chance?
No.
But I have spoken
to a Phoebe Halliwell.
Really?
I think I know where she went
if that will help you.
Who knew anything
could smell so bad.
- Now there's a good sign.
- Meaning?
I saw it in a vision
that I had of Brent.
Piper! Piper!
Piper, are you okay?
Oh, my God. Oh, God.
Piper, I'll get help.
I feel like I should be cackling.
- Hello.
- Prue.
Piper's hurt. And I can't get to her.
- Okay, where are you?
- At the end of Varick street.
Hurry, okay?
And don't forget the potion.
I'm on my way.
Didn't want you to leave me behind
like your sisters did.
- Fix it now.
- Or what?
You gonna hurt me? Go ahead.
Just let me get you in focus.
- Okay.
- I don't have time for this, all right.
Piper is hurt, and
two boys' lives are at stake.
- Do you know where they are?
- Yes.
- All right, you win.
- I win? What's my prize?
I'm a witch with magical powers.
A witch? A witch? This is great.
Great. Terrific, let's go.
- What is he doing here?
- Making my career.
I didn't have a choice.
Where's Piper?
- She's in through this way. Come on.
- Stay here. It's too dangerous.
- No, no, no, I'm coming with you.
- No.
There are too many lives at stake,
including my sister's.
I will not have you risking them.
Stay. You'll get your story.
Okay, all right. I'll just wait out here.
Phoebe, is that you?
Phoebe.
Prue!
Nice.
This is Eric Lohman, reporting live.
I'm in a storm drain underground,
following three sisters,
all of them witches,
as they look for children
who may have been abducted
by a strange kind of...
Okay.
- We've got to get you out of here.
- No, no.
Look, Piper,
just up to the street, okay?
Phoebe and I will
come right back for the boys.
Come on, lean on me, honey.
Don't move.
Andy!
- You okay?
- Yeah, thanks.
So, what Lohman
saw you do is true.
- Andy, what are you doing here?
- Confirming my suspicions.
He knows.
A Grimlock tried to kill him.
- What the hell is a Grimlock?
- It's a demon.
- A demon.
- Yeah.
Look, Andy, I need you to get
Piper up on the street, okay?
- No, I wanna stay. I need to help.
- You're too weak to use your powers.
Her too?
- Will you please get her out of here?
- Prue, I'm not leaving
- the two of you alone.
- Do I have to use my power on you?
I'll meet you up on the street.
You'll be okay.
Okay, we should be coming up
on a feeder drain right about now.
Great, just what we need,
more toxic waste in our sewers.
- That worked well.
- Yeah.
David?
- David?
- Please help me.
David.
Oh, God. Prue, I found them!
- You okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, where's David?
- Over there.
I can see!
I can see you!
I knew you had magic powers.
Come on, get your friend.
Let's get out of here, okay?
Exactly how did you know
the kids were down there again?
- Anonymous tip.
- What about the kidnappers?
Kidnappers?
There weren't any kidnappers.
Kids followed a kitten
into the storm drain.
- Got lost.
- Really?
How do you explain finding Lohman
down there with a broken neck?
Must have slipped when he went
down there after them.
Anything for a story. It's too bad.
Yeah, it's a real shame.
You don't really expect me
to believe all this, do you?
For now.
Have they said anything?
No, just got back
from the hospital.
But who knows what they'll say
once the police question them.
So much for our secret.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, I was just thinking.
When I was in the storm drain
I was kind of out of it
and I kept thinking about Leo.
That's weird.
- Maybe you miss him.
- Maybe.
What are you gonna do
about Josh?
I'm gonna call him and tell him
I think he should take that job.
Sweetie, you can't hold out for Leo.
Who knows if he's gonna come back.
I know, he may not.
But if I'm thinking about Leo,
then I'm definitely
not thinking about Josh.
That's too bad,
he had really nice glutes.
Hey, there's Brent. Hey, Brent!
Over here.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Where's your dog?
He's retired.
You can see? But how did that...?
I don't know. I mean, you tell me.
Someone must've
slayed those monsters.
- Do you know anything about it?
- Oh, I...
It's all right. I mean,
if anyone understands the danger
of telling amazing stories, I sure do.
I was right. You do have
a beautiful smile.
- Are those the boys?
- Yeah.
- Maybe I should have a talk with them.
- That would be so great. Thank you.
No, thank you.
So now you know.
Yeah, although it's still sinking in.
Where do we go from here?
That's a good question.
Inspector Trudeau, is this related
to the one 20 years ago?
Inspector,
what's your official position?
Inspector. Inspector, please.
We need to know...