Come to me, Kali.
I conjure thee, Kali.
I'm here, Aviva.
- It's been over a week.
- I know. Be patient, Aviva.
But I've done everything
that you've asked.
I've followed the Halliwell sisters.
I know their every move.
Which will all become valuable
in good time.
You must trust me.
You must make them want you
as badly as you want them.
- I talked to my mom today.
- How is she?
I don't know.
She's better, I think.
I miss her.
- She's going to be so proud of you.
- Yeah?
I hope so.
Are you ready
to receive your power?
- You know I am.
- Remember, it's a sacred power.
If I give it to you,
you must use it only as I say.
I will. I promise.
Very well.
Reach for the mirror,
put out your hands,
feel the power.
You know what to do.
Go to Phoebe, Piper and Prue.
Well, I think I see... Yeah,
there's definitely something here.
Definitely.
My, Santa, you've changed.
- He's looking for Kit.
- The cat. Right.
Four legs, fur. I remember.
Sorry. You know,
have you tried the shelter?
- Yeah, nothing.
- Well, she had her collar on, right?
With your number on it?
- A very distinctive collar, actually.
- Anyway, thanks for looking.
I'm sure you must be hungry
after all that work.
All what work?
Oh, that's just Piper.
She's gotta be everyone's mom.
Think of her as your mom.
I know I do.
Isn't she a scream?
Well, thanks.
Let me go put these fliers up first,
and I'll be right back, okay?
- Oh, careful. You all right? Careful.
- Yeah, I'll just...
- Antique.
- Thanks.
Grandma's, yeah.
Quite possibly the finest glutes
in the city.
- In the state.
- In all the land.
I saw him first.
Here you go, Leo.
Non-fat milk, right?
- Thanks.
- Just don't call me "Mom."
Trust me, one hot night is all
you guys need to get back on track.
- Yeah, I hope you're right.
- Andy's a cop, you're a witch.
Expect complications.
- Hey, Leo. How's it going?
- Good.
This wall only needs two coats, then
I gotta do the moulding, and I'm done.
Are you sure
it doesn't need three coats?
Nice outfit for 9:00 in the morning
with no place to go.
I'm glad you like it.
Leo, come here.
Got milk?
Phoebe, come here.
Phoebe!
I think that Piper likes Leo.
What's not to like?
He's a great guy.
- I mean, really likes him.
- Your point being?
- Never mind. Classic Phoebe.
- Wait, define that.
I think you know.
Okay, look, Prue, I think we need to
put some major closure on this,
or we're gonna be in rocking chairs,
slurping oatmeal out of rubber spoons,
and I'm still gonna hear
about Roger.
Piper, am I a boyfriend thief?
Totally.
Besides Roger, whom again, Prue,
I never touched.
My boyfriend, Billy Wilson.
- Billy Wil... Eighth grade Billy Wilson?
- You kissed him at homecoming.
No, I did not kiss him at homecoming.
I was helping him find a contact lens.
Oh, please. You were all over him,
with your breasts all... Whatever.
- I didn't even have breasts back then.
- Phoebe, you've always had breasts.
So I think I'll just let you two
work this out on your own,
but just remember, I get the house
tonight. Just Andy and me.
No warlocks, no innocents to protect
and especially no sisters.
So you know...
...it's not like either one of us
has a problem finding guys.
Please.
So if one of us got Leo,
it'd be okay with the other one.
Absolutely.
So we can just consider this
a friendly competition.
- Sibling rivalry.
- War.
Exactly.
Dear Diary...
Aviva, open the door.
...life sucks here.
I'm gonna be late for work.
So that part about this being my room,
that was a lie?
It's my apartment, Aviva.
So you keep reminding me,
Aunt Jackie.
Why don't you get light
and air in here?
Because I like it dark and stale.
Why are you so antagonistic to me?
How come you haven't called
my mom yet?
- What?
- To see how she's doing.
Or just to say hello.
It would help her, you know.
I mean, it's not like
she's got a lot of family.
She has to take responsibility
for her own actions.
She's not in jail.
She's in rehab.
She didn't do anything wrong
to take responsibility for.
She's sick, and that's it.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Whatever.
Have you seen
Lethal Weapon 3?
Not very romantic.
Right.
Hey, how about Double Indemnity?
It's black and white.
- Right.
- Video paralysis.
Excuse me?
You're probably two minutes away
from leaving without a rental.
You mind if I help?
After all, I am a pro.
Sure.
Doesn't really matter
what we pick anyway.
Probably never get around
to watching it.
Oh, yeah?
Pretty cocky.
Actually, what I meant was
something always seems to come up,
- get in our way.
- That's not true.
Okay, well, maybe
sometimes it's true,
but there's always
a perfectly good reason.
Prue, there's never
As a matter of fact, there's never
usually a reason at all.
Good, bad or otherwise.
All right.
You, me, alone tonight.
Nothing, and I mean nothing,
will get in our way. Guaranteed.
I'll hold you to that.
Okay.
I got it.
Body Heat.
We'll take it.
I conjure thee, Kali.
I'm here, Aviva.
I'm going crazy here, Kali.
I can't wait any longer.
The Halliwells don't understand
our way.
They don't yet know the full uses
and joys of their powers.
- I'll show them.
- You must gain their trust first.
You must let them welcome you
into their coven.
I won't disappoint you.
I swear.
Then it's time.
Take the cat
back to the Halliwells.
About done for the day?
Just about.
Well, Prue has a date tonight,
so we kind of gotta clear out.
I was thinking about catching
a movie. Wanna go?
I can't do it.
- Okay.
- You know...
...these are original to the house.
I mean, they really should be sanded
down, finished off with steel wool
and restained, not covered in paint.
Oh, right.
Kind of like making risotto
with Minute Rice.
It's a cooking analogy.
Yeah.
Anyway...
...I have stain samples at home
if you're interested.
I could bring them by tomorrow and
show them to you and your sisters.
Better yet, why don't you just
bring them by the restaurant?
Say about lunchtime? Prue's so busy,
and Phoebe doesn't really care.
She's more into stucco.
- Okay.
So, what time is that movie?
I got it.
Kit! Oh, my God! Where did you
find her? We were worried sick.
I was just walking by,
and I saw one of your fliers,
and poof, there she was.
Like magic.
I can't even believe
she let you hold her.
Welcome home, kitty.
- You must be starving.
- I fed her.
I thought you said
you just found her.
I did. Well, a couple of hours ago,
I mean.
And she didn't try to scratch you?
You know, I'll take
the fliers down tomorrow.
- Let me clean up before the movie.
- Movie? What movie?
- A war movie.
- I love war movies.
- Mind if I tag along?
- Sure.
Why not? I'll be right back.
You guys aren't going out, are you?
You just got your cat back.
Oh, she'll be fine.
Let me get my purse.
- What's your name?
- Oh, no, no, I don't want your money.
- Hey, Andy.
Hey.
Hey, I thought we all
had plans tonight.
- This girl just found our cat for us.
- Aviva.
Well, that's great.
Is 50 bucks enough?
I don't want a reward.
We need to talk.
- About what?
- About Wicca.
Andy Trudeau, this is Leo Wyatt.
You guys chat. We'll be right back.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Thanks again.
- Yeah, I'm sorry you can't stay.
I'm not leaving.
Don't you understand?
I'm one of you.
No!
Very cool.
She didn't... She didn't...
You didn't freeze.
- It's because I'm a witch too.
- A what?
Look, I just wanna be friends.
Guys, we have about 20 seconds
until they unfreeze.
How did you find out about us?
I'm gonna need
more than 20 seconds for that.
We need to move things
along here, Prue.
Okay, you need
to get out of here now.
What? Why?
We don't know who
you really are, so just leave.
- Okay, go, go, go.
- No, I'm not leaving.
- I just saved your cat.
- Leave now or else.
Or else what?
What the hell?
Hey, where did that girl go?
She just...
Left.
Why wouldn't they accept me?
You said if I brought them back
their cat...
Was it the oldest?
Was it Prue who sent you away?
- Yes.
- Avoid her.
She's the strongest.
You must separate them.
Together they're charmed,
impenetrable.
- But what if they don't want me?
- Phoebe will.
In her own way, she's searching
for someone to relate to.
Someone to share
her witchcraft with.
What's the problem?
I... I don't know.
You're the one who came to me,
remember?
You're the one who wanted sisters.
I know I want a family.
I don't have anybody.
What do you get out of it? I mean,
you know, you never really said...
Halliwell magic is old and powerful,
and I want it.
And since they're new to the craft,
if I'm ever going to get it,
it has to be now.
Through you.
Just do as I say, Aviva.
Make Phoebe covet your power,
then we'll both get what we want.
It's not what you think, Andy.
It's hard to explain. It just...
Another one of those things
you can't explain.
It's a broken record, Prue.
Look, I wanted you to stay.
You have to believe me.
What happened? Why'd you
want me to leave?
I told you, something came up.
Sister stuff.
I can't really go into detail
without betraying someone's secret.
- Prue...
- Look, Andy, I'm unpredictable, okay?
That is just part of who I am,
and you have to accept that,
because I can't change it.
I don't want you to change, Prue.
I just...
I just wanna have a normal date,
that's all. Is that too much to ask for?
All right, let's just try again tonight.
Same time, same place?
Same movie?
Yeah.
Okay. So, what, 8:00?
I'll be there. Bye.
All right, bye.
If I ever see that little arsonist again...
Just got done dodging Leo's questions
about her. That was close.
Too close.
The question is, who is she?
- And what does she want?
- Let us not forget Aviva found Kit.
Yeah, she's probably the one
who stole the cat in the first place.
Hello, paranoia chick.
Phoebe, for all we know,
she's a warlock.
- She can't be. She didn't freeze.
- Besides, she said she was a witch.
- Okay, a bad witch maybe.
- A bad witch with a really cool power.
- Better than mine, that's for sure.
- Why are you so quick to defend her?
Why are you so quick
to condemn her?
If she is a witch, a good witch,
then it might be kind of cool,
considering she's the first
we've run across.
- Exactly.
- Guys,
we don't know about her.
How she got her powers,
how she found out about us.
She tried to tell us,
but you kicked her out.
Yeah, she would've exposed us
if I hadn't.
Prue, she's just a kid.
Besides, if she's a witch, she probably
feels just as alone as we do.
Maybe she just needs some friends.
Or maybe she's out to destroy us.
It wouldn't be the first time.
- Okay.
- All right,
until we know who she really is,
let's just steer clear, okay?
I'm late for work.
Me too.
Hello.
Aviva?
I'm so glad that you came.
I'm glad that you called, actually.
- Bet you got a few questions, huh?
- A few.
- What time does school let out?
- Now.
Whoa! Whoa!
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh, the same thing I'm sure you did
a thousand times.
- Am I right?
- Well...
I am right.
You didn't tell your bitch sister
about this, did you?
Hey, watch your mouth.
Prue had every right to be upset
with what you did.
It's funny how you knew that I was
talking about Prue and not Piper.
Hey, come on, let's go for a ride.
I'll tell you everything
that you want to know.
Table for one, sir?
- You own this place?
- No, I just run it.
Actually, I used to be the chef here.
I'm impressed.
Good. I mean,
good that you came here.
As opposed to the house
and Phoebe.
How about those stain samples?
I only brought the ones authentic to
the era in which the manor was built.
Great.
Hungry?
Oh, it's on the house.
You're big on food, aren't you?
You know, and that's good. You know,
actually, in the Mayan culture,
the cook was second in the hierarchy
only to the medicine man.
Mayans? You know about Mayans.
Well, you certainly are a handyman,
aren't you?
So does Phoebe work here too?
Phoebe, work? No, no, no.
She's probably at her gay and lesbian
group right about now.
So, what will it be?
This is the dining room.
This is the parlour.
That's the conservatory,
which is really just a fancy name
for family room.
This is so totally cool.
Oh, I love it here.
And welcome to planet Leo.
- You are lucky Miss Leo?
- Maybe.
Doesn't he like you? I mean, how
could he not? You are so gorgeous.
Well, you see, Piper and I sort of have
this little competition going over him.
So just use your powers.
Cast a spell on him or something.
- You do have powers, don't you?
- What makes you think I do?
Please. You're a witch.
Yeah, which brings us back
to how do you know that?
You promised.
I have this teacher.
She's great. She's like my mom.
She told me.
- Who is she?
- Another witch.
Like a high priestess or something.
She said you were the coolest,
that I would like you the best.
- She was right.
- Well, I'd like to meet her sometime.
Yeah?
Is your room up there?
Come on, I wanna share something
with you.
You're gonna love it.
I promise.
Come on.
I like mirrors.
They never lie to you.
They always tell the truth
whether you like it or not.
It's basic black.
The colour of my soul.
- Do you wanna try it?
- Your soul's not black.
You know the feeling that I mean.
You're different.
You know, you'll never want
what they want.
You belong on the edge.
We aren't pink people, Phoebe.
You wanna see something incredible?
Better yet, do you wanna try it?
Try what?
I'll show you my power
if you show me yours.
Anybody home?
Better not be.
Don't be afraid.
- Okay, now what?
- Watch.
- She's giving it to you too.
- Who is?
- Giving me what?
- The power.
Here.
Touch this.
It's the power of heat.
Your hand is like the sun.
Whoa.
That's pretty cool, huh?
Phoebe, are you...?
- Prue.
- What are you doing?
- Get out. This is her room.
- Aviva...
No. She treats you worse
than my aunt treats me.
- It's not right.
- It's okay. Relax.
Chianti, Body Heat.
What do you think?
- Prue, I can explain. Oh, no.
- Oh, no.
Let me guess, rain check?
- Andy...
- Prue, this is...
- It's getting ridiculous.
- I know.
Believe me, you have every right
to be upset,
and I can't talk about it right now,
but I will. I promise.
Tomorrow, Quake, 1:00, please?
Okay. Tomorrow, 1:00.
I am so sorry. I totally forgot.
What is she doing here?
What's the matter with you?
This is her house too, okay?
She can do whatever she wants.
Aviva.
- She's not what you think she is.
- She doesn't understand, Phoebe.
She'll never understand.
If there were no Prue,
Phoebe would be with us now.
I hate her,
and I wish that she were dead.
Aviva, what's going on?
Who's in there with you?
You skipped school today,
and I wanna know why.
Get out of my room!
How dare you speak to me
in that tone!
What's going on in here?
I said, get out of my room!
Leave me alone, or I'll...
Aunt Jackie!
Oh, my God!
What did you tell the police?
That the candle caught her dress
on fire, and she fell down the stairs.
Oh, my God. What have I done?
I didn't mean to hurt her.
Your powers are growing.
I know, but as soon as
Aunt Jackie wakes up,
she'll tell them
what really happened.
- I gotta get out of here.
- No!
Why not?
You must go back to the Halliwells.
You must complete what you started.
- But how?
- Piper won't stop you,
and Phoebe's already an ally.
Only Prue stands in our way.
You must use your powers.
You must take Prue's place
in the power of three.
Don't disappoint me, Aviva.
You said you wanted a family.
And now you'll have one.
Thanks.
- You poor thing, you're shivering.
- I'm okay.
I know that you don't like me,
and I know the last thing
you wanna do is help me,
but I don't know where else to turn.
I don't have anybody else.
She's telling the truth.
Her aunt was admitted to the hospital.
How is she? Is she okay?
She has a broken arm
and a concussion.
- How did she fall again?
- I don't know. I...
I heard her scream,
and then I found her on the floor,
and I called 911.
I promise, if you just let me spend
the night and get some sleep,
I'll tell you everything you wanna know
about me tomorrow.
- She can't stay alone.
- She can sleep in my room.
- No magic.
- I swear.
Now is the time.
What are you doing?
- I was just looking for the bathroom.
- Down the hall, to the right.
Great. Thanks. Good night.
I'm going to the hospital to see
her aunt. In an hour, I'll be back, okay?
- Sorry, didn't know you were there.
- That's okay.
I'm gonna see your aunt
and let her know where you are.
- We'll talk when I get back?
- Yeah. Sure.
- Tell her I love her.
- Okay.
Come on, let's get something to eat.
I don't understand.
Why is Aviva staying with you?
I don't even know who you are.
Well, actually,
we just met your niece.
We lost our cat,
and she found it for us.
- Oh, that's what she was hiding.
- Hiding?
In the closet. She wouldn't let me
go anywhere near it.
You're lucky she didn't sacrifice
the poor thing.
I'm sorry?
She's a strange kid.
Very troubled.
Into all sorts of weird stuff.
Black magic, voodoo,
God knows what else.
No wonder she doesn't have
any friends.
What makes you think
she's into black magic?
You should see her room.
It seems like every time I walk past,
she's in there chanting or something.
Sometimes, I swear,
I even hear other voices.
I know she's not happy there.
I'm only taking care of her
until her mom gets out of rehab.
Do you mind if I stop by your place
and pick up some things for Aviva?
No.
Great. Thanks.
Feel better.
Andy, I can't seem
to get ahold of Prue.
I know she was going to the hospital.
That's all right, Piper.
Thanks for trying.
- I'm sure there's a perfectly good...
- Explanation.
Wanna bet?
"Kali says we're close to taking over
the Halliwell coven.
I hate lying to them."
- Hello.
- Phoebe, it's me.
Prue, where are you?
Piper called, said you were
supposed to meet Andy at Quake.
Listen, we have a bigger problem
to deal with.
Call her back and tell her
to come home right away.
I'll explain it to you guys later.
And Phoebe, whatever you do,
don't let Aviva out of your sight, okay?
- Yeah, sure.
- All right. Bye.
Prue's on her way home.
We can have our little chat
when she gets here.
Yeah, okay.
Do you mind if I go upstairs
and lie down? I'm not feeling real well.
- Sure, go ahead.
- Okay.
This last coat of stain's gotta dry.
I'm headed over to Fillmore
in a few minutes to do an estimate.
Wait, you're finished already?
Yeah, I'll be back tomorrow to make
sure everybody's happy with my work.
What?
Just out of curiosity...
...are you and Aviva...?
- I mean, Piper said that...
- Piper said what?
Nothing. I think I need some water.
Wait. Leo, what did Piper
say to you?
It doesn't matter really.
Forget it.
Well, whatever she said, you should
probably take it with a grain of salt.
Sometimes her medication
makes her say the strangest things.
But not to worry,
her shrinks are on it.
Shrinks?
Oh, my God, Aviva.
Prue's home.
Oh, no.
Aviva? Aviva?!
What the hell are you doing?
Phoebe, I'm sorry.
Maybe we should take you
to the hospital.
No, it's not that bad.
Well, how did it happen anyway?
Candles. Aviva had some candles lit,
and I guess the sweater got too close.
- And then she ran out of the house.
- Sure caught fire fast.
Leo, we got this. We wouldn't
want you to be late for that estimate.
Are you sure? I don't mind.
No, Prue's right. I'm fine.
You go ahead.
Okay. I'll stop by later
to see how you're doing.
- Great.
Okay, so how did this happen?
I had a premonition
that Aviva was going to hurt you,
so I tried to stop her.
I should've listened to you, Prue.
You were right about Aviva.
She's evil.
No, actually, she's not,
but she is being used by an evil spirit.
And I think I know which one,
so come on.
- Where are you going, Aviva?
- Go away!
I don't want anything to do with you.
I don't wanna be a witch anymore.
But you haven't finished
what we started.
But I'm hurting people!
Don't you understand?
First Aunt Jackie, now Phoebe.
I have to leave.
Aren't you going
to say goodbye first?
Touch the mirror, Aviva.
It's okay. I'm not upset.
Touch the mirror,
and I'll go away too.
Hello, Aviva.
Kali, Kali, Kali...
There, there.
"An evil sorceress cursed
into her own dimension,
she appears in reflections and has
the power to possess..."
"Innocents and uses them as pawns
to steal a witch's power."
Wait, I don't understand.
So she was using Aviva
to try and turn us into bad witches?
Does it say anything
about how to get rid of her?
Yeah, to get rid of her,
shatter her reflection.
However the hell we do that. Here.
- Aviva.
- Hello, Phoebe.
- How's the arm?
- You're not Aviva.
You're not kidding.
- Phoebe, help me!
- Never mind.
My powers are greater
than yours, Prue.
It's only a matter of time.
- Time. Piper, that's it. Freeze her.
- Aviva doesn't freeze.
Yeah, but Kali will.
No!
Prue, the mirror.
Get her to the mirror.
No, no!
Thanks for the dress.
No problem. It's Prue's.
- All set?
- Yeah, I'm all set.
You okay?
I don't think looking into a mirror
is ever gonna be the same.
Yeah, well, the demon's gone,
Aviva. Forever.
Yeah, well, unfortunately
all the other ones remain.
- It's so hard.
- Oh, I know.
It was hard for me too
when I was your age.
- Yeah?
- Are you kidding?
These are the hardest years
of your life.
The one thing I learned
is you just gotta be yourself.
It's easy for you to say.
What if yourself sucks?
Well, you don't have
to worry about that.
No, Aviva, I'm serious.
You are a great kid.
I could totally see us hanging out
together in school.
A couple of troublemakers.
I'm really gonna miss being a witch
and having powers
- and having sisters.
- Yeah, well, you've got your mom.
And your aunt will be home
from the hospital tomorrow.
Okay, now remember,
do not tell anyone
about us Halliwell sisters, all right?
It's just our little secret.
- I promise.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Can we talk?
- Is there really anything to talk about?
Andy.
- I'm sorry.
- So am I.
What do you mean by that?
Oh, come on, who are we
kidding? I mean, let's face it.
One of us is more interested
in this relationship than the other.
- That's not true.
- Isn't it?
How come I'm always the one
left standing there like a jerk?
- I can explain.
- No, you can't.
Or you won't.
Damn it, Prue, I still love you.
I'm not saying you have to explain it all
to me, Prue. That's your prerogative.
All I'm saying is...
...it hurts that you don't
trust me enough.
I do trust you, Andy.
It has nothing to do with you.
It's just...
It's just something that I don't know
if I can ever share with anybody.
Well, I hope that's not true
for your sake.
All I know is there's nothing more
I can say or do to reassure you
that I'm there for you.
Andy.
Are you saying that you don't
wanna see me anymore?
I don't know what I want anymore.