I don't know. The Betsey Johnson
dress might be a bit too much for work.
That's what a new wardrobe's
all about, pushing the limits.
Yeah, and stretching the budget.
Maybe I should just check with Piper.
Oh, my God, Prue...
I'm so embarrassed.
Of course, she might have
other things on her mind,
like having her way
with the handyman.
- I thought you guys were shopping.
- Obviously.
Oh, look, front-clasp bra.
She means business.
- Serious business.
- Do you mind?
No, are you kidding? I think it's great,
as long as he's not still on the clock.
You guys have to get out of here
before he unfreezes.
I never know how long this thing lasts.
- How much did you guys spend?
- Lots.
Prue's new look is perfect
for an SHW.
- SHW?
- Single hot witch.
Prue, are you sure this isn't depression
buying? You know, post-breakup?
Does this look like something
a depressed woman would wear?
- Maybe you should borrow it.
- Okay, time's up.
You two gotta go. Go on.
Go in there and be quiet.
We will if you will.
Kit, what is it?
You forgot to unpack your briefcase
when you got home from work.
And you want to do it right now.
What you're about to pick up
is a tiara,
but you really believe
it's your date book.
Now put it in the desk,
just like you always do.
Excellent.
Now you want to continue
getting ready for bed.
Well?
Prue did exactly as I told her to.
You know, I rather like
this new power.
- And are you sure she didn't see you?
- No, no, she couldn't see me.
- No, I was invisible.
- But then, how did you get there?
I've explained this to you, Hannah.
It's called astral projection. With it,
I can transport myself psychically
and implant a subliminal thought
into Prue's brain.
Just like I did when I tricked her into
leaving the vault today with the tiara.
See, I planted the thought that made
her think she came out empty-handed.
I still don't understand how it works.
Watch.
You want to disrobe for him.
Desperately.
Understand now, Hannah?
If you ran an employment agency,
wouldn't you want me?
Maybe, but I'd definitely
want my suit back.
No, this is part of your old wardrobe.
I'm just recycling.
- Well, the environment thanks you...
- But take it off. Yeah, I know, I know.
Hi. Bye.
Piper, didn't you have to go in
early this morning?
Right, that was the plan.
I'm running a little late.
It just took a little longer to get
out of bed this morning than I planned.
Okay, bye.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
You, Leo, last night. Dish.
Well, it was nice. It was...
Well, it was wonderful.
We just had a few problems.
- Problems?
- What problems?
Well, it's been a while
since, you know, I...
And I was a little nervous,
and I kind of kept freezing him.
- Piper, you didn't.
- I didn't mean to the first time.
Okay, so at what point in the process
exactly did you freeze him?
- Hello.
- I gotta go.
- No, no, Piper, we're only teasing you.
- Yeah, truth is we're just jealous.
Yeah, we're just happy to see you
with a great guy finally.
I mean, between you and Leo,
and Prue, the new, hot Wicca woman,
and me, soon to be employed,
things are looking up.
Don't say that. The moment
somebody says that,
- everything always goes south.
- Unless you freeze him.
I couldn't help it. It was so good.
Okay, okay, okay, come on.
If you're gonna borrow the car, let's go.
- Good morning.
- Yeah, we heard.
- Bye.
- Yeah, have a magical day.
- What does she mean by that?
- Who knows.
I'm late for work. Bye.
- Bye.
Jaime, hey, what's going on?
What happened?
- We got robbed last night, Prue.
- You're kidding. What was stolen?
- The Romanov tiara.
- Oh, my God, not the tiara.
- Prue.
- Rex, hi. Jaime just told me.
- Yeah. Hello, nice to see you again.
- Hi, Rex.
- I'm sorry about what happened.
- Yeah, me too.
I mean, a loss of this magnitude
could severely damage our reputation.
Who is gonna consign anything
with us...?
No, no, no, we just have to get
the tiara back before word gets out.
I agree. Will you take point on this
then? You know, help the police?
You're really the only one
that I can trust.
Sure, but what about you?
Yeah, unfortunately, I've got
another commitment tonight
that I can't get out of.
It's some good friends
who are giving a concert,
and, well, I promised
I wouldn't miss it.
- Oh, yeah? Who?
- The Verve.
- Get out! Are you serious?
- You know them?
Know them? I worship them.
"Bittersweet Symphony"
- is, like, the best song ever.
- Really?
I have an idea.
Why not join me tonight.
Yeah, I'm sure I can rustle up
another ticket.
Well, you wouldn't mind,
would you, Prue?
- Of course not. Why would I mind?
- Then it's a date.
Well, figuratively speaking, of course.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
- Pick you up at 7, all right?
- Yeah, that sounds great. Thanks.
Oh, look at the time.
I gotta get going.
Hey, I promise I'll have
the car back by noon.
Thanks for pitching in, Prue.
- Prue.
- Andy.
- Are you on this case?
- Yep.
I guess fate keeps
throwing us together.
- You two know each other. I forgot.
- No, you didn't.
Well, I suggested that the inspector
speak with you
since you were the last one
to actually see the tiara.
If you need anything else,
please don't hesitate to call.
We'd like to see the security tapes
as soon as possible.
Oh, yeah, I'm sure Prue
can arrange that.
Excuse me.
- How are you?
- Okay.
It'd be better if you stopped by the
station so we could talk about all this.
- One o'clock?
- Sure.
I can't believe you're taking
that little witch to the concert.
Rex, that was my ticket.
Hannah, kitten.
You know I'm only doing it
to upset Prue.
All the better to frame her and force
the sisters to relinquish their powers.
How do you know they even can?
There is a special spell
in The Book of Shadows.
When the time comes, they'll use it.
Trust me.
You put the tiara in the vault before
you left. Was anybody else there?
The security guard, Jaime.
Did he lock up the vault?
No, I did.
Okay, did you happen to take anything
out of the vault when you left?
No. Is this an interview
or an interrogation?
I'm sorry, I'm just trying
to get all the facts, that's all.
There were no signs of forced entry
into the auction house or the vault.
So do you think that one of
the employees might have stolen it?
- Strong possibility.
- Someone like me?
No, don't be ridiculous.
Still, we have to check out everyone's
story. Grand larceny's bigtime.
Could cost a person
15, 20 years easily.
We've got enough for now. We have
any questions, we'll give you a call.
Well, you know where to reach me.
I think I still remember.
- What was all that about?
- You tell me.
Last time you were ready to bust her.
Now you think she's Miss Innocent?
That was a whole different situation,
completely unrelated.
Look, I'm not saying
she did it, all right?
But you have to admit a lot of the
arrows are pointing in her direction.
It's also this. The security tapes
that Prue brought over?
One's missing.
The one from the vault.
You're glowing.
Your face, total afterglow.
It is not. It's just warm in here.
So how much
was that tiara worth anyway?
Well, I didn't get a chance to have it
appraised. We just got it in yesterday.
But I would say well over
a million dollars.
- Did they have any idea who stole it?
- Yeah, me.
So, what's on the dessert menu?
- Hey, how was the concert?
- The best. It was amazing.
Still recycling, I see.
Thanks for taking care of things
tonight, Prue. I really appreciate it.
Don't you just love that accent?
By the way,
how'd it go with the police?
Oh, well, they think
it's an inside job, actually.
Do they? How disturbing.
Okay, shoptalk later.
We're gonna grab a table, okay?
Take that one by the window.
I'll send Cindy over.
- You're welcome to join us, Prue.
- No, thanks, I think I'll pass.
- She's a big girl, Prue.
- Meaning?
He's rich, he's stable, he's handsome.
We should be happy for her.
- I'm thrilled.
- Are you jealous?
No. No.
More like territorial.
Okay, I would just like
to keep my work world
separate from my home world.
Is that okay?
Good luck.
Good morning.
- Wow, roses. Who are they for?
- Guess.
Leo, I need to call you back.
Something's about to come up.
I'll see you later, okay? Bye.
"Phoebe, thank you for a lovely
evening. The job is on its way. Rex."
Oh, what a sweetheart.
Wait, who opened the box?
I can't get over how beautiful
these are. Can you, Prue?
So it must have been quite a night,
you know, after the concert.
I'll put these in some water.
All I did was tell Rex that I was
going to the employment agency.
He said he'd make a few calls
and help me out.
So, what's the big problem?
Phoebe, really,
it's none of my business.
It's just... Watch what you say
to him, okay?
Because there are certain things I
don't want my boss to know about me.
Andy, what are you doing here?
We're here to search your house
for the tiara, Prue.
We've got a search warrant.
Wait, how can you guys even think
that Prue stole the tiara?
We don't, Phoebe. Not necessarily.
Then what are you doing here,
spring cleaning?
Any idea where the vault
security camera tape is?
- I gave you the tapes.
- Not that one.
It wasn't there, Prue.
Why did you do that?
That's why.
No, no, no, wait. That is not possible.
How did it get there?
I don't know. You better come up
with an answer before they unfreeze.
- Someone must've planted it.
- Somebody's been in our house?
It doesn't matter. Just let them find it.
I have nothing to hide. I'm innocent.
That doesn't look very innocent.
Piper, hide it.
You think you should check
under the pillows.
Morris, check under the pillows.
How did he know to look there?
Put it in the dresser.
He's already looked there.
You want to look
in the dresser again.
- This is getting ridiculous.
No, eerie is more like it.
I will be right back.
Don't worry, I'll just keep freezing
them until they give up.
You're a miserable witch.
- What's the matter?
- I don't know.
I feel like calling a shrink
for some reason.
Okay, I put it in the...
Attic, attic.
Nothing.
I think that's good enough
for now, Morris.
I'm sorry about all this, Prue.
I really am.
- Yeah, I know.
- Come on, Trudeau. Let's go.
Witches.
- Well, did the police find the tiara?
- No.
Piper kept freezing them,
then moving it.
Well, how can we frame her if they
can't even find the evidence?
We're gonna have to up the stakes.
Somebody is obviously trying
to set me up,
and they're using magic to do it.
- But who? And how?
- Pick a warlock, any warlock.
Hey, what were the police
doing here?
Oh, nothing much really.
Is it all right if I go up and fix
the bathroom sink?
Oh, knock yourself out, Leo.
Did anyone ever think
that maybe he's a warlock?
Why is it always someone I'm dating
that gets accused of being that?
Don't answer that.
Answer that, it's safer.
Hello.
Oh, yeah. Hi, Rex.
Look, I'm on my way in. It's...
Of course. Hold on.
It's for you.
Hello. Yes, I got the flowers,
and they're beautiful.
That was so sweet of you.
They made quite an impression
over here too.
A dinner party?
Yes, I would love to.
Hold on, let me grab a pen.
- So, what are you gonna do?
- What can I do?
My sister's dating my boss.
I don't really have a...
I meant about who's setting you up.
Do you have any idea who it could be?
It's gotta be somebody
at the auction house.
If I had to guess,
I'd start with the person
who said that they were
out to destroy me.
Hannah?
Smart girl.
Leo, what are you doing? I thought
you were going to fix the sink.
Yeah, I was. I mean, I am. I just...
I need to fix a light downstairs,
and I was hoping there'd be some
old fixtures up here,
you know, that I could cannibalise.
Listen, there's something
I need to tell you.
Something I don't think
you're gonna like.
I might have to leave here soon.
I might have to go back home.
- Is home far away?
- Yeah, it's pretty far.
I mean, I don't know for sure yet,
but, you know,
I wanted you to know just in case.
Thanks.
Well, I better get to work.
You will see
a spectacular apartment.
Phoebe, I am so glad
that you could make it. Please.
- Wow, this is...
- Spectacular?
That is exactly the word
I was gonna use.
We must be on
the same wavelength.
- Champagne?
- No, thank you.
No, I insist.
- Am I early?
- No, you're right on time.
But I thought you said
you were having a dinner party.
Yes, I am.
With a very exclusive guest list.
Just you and me.
A toast.
- To your interview.
- Interview?
Yeah, at Zeitgeist magazine.
They want to meet with you,
you know, perhaps hire you
for the fashion section.
- Interested?
- Very.
- But what's the catch?
- You have to sleep with me.
Phoebe, what sort of man
do you think I am?
I hope you like sushi.
Imported fresh from Kyöto.
Please, just make yourself
comfortable.
You're having a premonition
of Prue at work.
She's in danger.
You fear a warlock's after her.
You must save her.
Prue.
I gotta go. I'm really sorry,
and I can't explain,
but I'll call you, okay?
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
911?
I'm calling from
Buckland's Auction House.
I think someone's trying to kill me.
Please hurry.
Working late?
Sorry. Didn't mean to scare you.
It's okay.
I guess I'm just a little jumpy lately.
Can't blame you,
with everything that's been going on.
Yeah.
Listen, Jaime, I was wondering,
when the tiara was stolen,
was anyone else still here,
like Hannah or Rex maybe?
No, you were the last one out.
Just like tonight.
Hardest-working woman
I've ever met.
For what it's worth, Prue,
I know you didn't take it.
I mean, of all people...
There's no way.
Thanks.
Hannah's computer.
Someone's after you. Behind you.
You fear it's a warlock
with powers greater than yours.
You hear a scream. An innocent
to protect in the warehouse.
- Jaime.
- Grab the artefact just inside the door.
Jaime.
Prue!
- Phoebe.
- Thank God you're all right.
He's dead.
The tape found by the body?
Security. Showing Prue
exiting the vault,
putting the missing tiara
in her briefcase.
- What? That can't be.
- Just saw it for myself.
Somebody must've manipulated me
into taking it.
The same way someone
manipulated me
into being a witness
against my own sister.
- Any idea what they're talking about?
- Not a clue.
You were with Rex tonight,
weren't you?
Yeah, Prue, but I don't think this
is the time or place to get into that.
No, I just meant that don't you
find it a little coincidental
that right when you guys start
dating, all this is going on?
No. And besides, I thought you thought
that Hannah was behind all of this.
- I do.
- Excuse us. Ladies.
Do you mind if we ask
a few questions?
I already told you
what happened, okay?
I was working late, I heard a noise,
I came down here and found Jaime.
- You didn't know he had the tape?
- No, of course not.
And why exactly did you pick up
the murder weapon again?
- You think she killed him, is that it?
- Phoebe.
No, I wanna know how far
he's gonna go with this.
None of this has anything to do with
the fact that she dumped you, does it?
- Stop it.
- Look, we got Prue
standing over the body of the security
guard who last saw her with the tiara.
With the missing security tape
showing her taking it.
And holding the murder weapon,
which you were there to witness.
- What are we supposed to think?
- That I'm guilty as hell.
You know she didn't do this.
Then who did? Did you see anybody
run past you on the way in here?
No.
- I'm sorry, Prue. Brian.
- Yeah?
You're under arrest
for suspicion of murder.
- We should hire a lawyer.
- With what money?
I don't know, but we can't
let her sit in jail all night.
That's why we're here,
to get Rex's help.
What are you doing?
This is so weird.
Are you sure this is the right place?
This is my lipstick. I'm positive.
He couldn't have moved out so fast.
It must've been an illusion.
All of it.
- Even my premonition.
- How is that possible?
Mind control, astral projection,
throwing charms. Who knows?
Prue was right about Rex,
which means I'm dating a warlock.
Been there, done that.
Hey.
- You wanna talk?
- I'm just running background checks
on all the other employees
at the auction house.
- That's not what I meant, Andy.
- Andy?
Did you call me by my first name?
Wasn't even sure you knew it.
I heard Prue say it.
She didn't do it, Morris.
- You keep saying that.
- It's too pat, it's too easy.
The evidence just keeps
falling in our laps.
Maybe her sister was right.
Maybe your personal feelings
are getting in the way.
- We've had that conversation, okay?
- Okay.
But you stopped seeing Prue
for a reason.
You thought she was hiding
something from you.
How do you know she wasn't
hiding something like this?
A secret life of crime?
- I don't think so.
- You got a better explanation?
You wanna book her
into county jail?
No, let's just keep her here
for as long as we can.
At least until the arraignment.
- What are you doing?
- Getting rid of the evidence.
They can't bust Prue for murder
if they don't have a motive.
- Mouth, Leo's in the kitchen.
- Oh, he is? Really?
Focus. And think.
The last thing we have to worry about
is the legal system.
We're up against a warlock now.
Two, if Prue's right about Hannah.
Exactly. Which means we have
to figure out what they want.
It can't just be to frame Prue.
Unless in doing so they think
they can get our powers,
which is what warlocks want.
Which means
they're trying to divide us
so that we don't have
the power of three to stop them.
What are we gonna do?
We have no choice.
- Let's go.
- Go? Go where?
- Phoebe.
- Piper, it's gonna be all right.
This is crazy.
We have to get Prue out
before Rex makes his move on us.
- But we can't break her out.
- Yes, we can. We're witches.
All you have to do is freeze the guards
and then unlock Prue's cell.
Me? What about you?
Somebody's gotta stay out here
in case something goes wrong.
- Ready? On three.
- No, Phoebe.
Three.
Totally cool power. I hate you.
What are you doing?
- Are you out of your mind?
- Just so we're clear,
- this was Phoebe's idea.
- What?
We think Rex is a warlock,
and he's after our powers.
Phoebe's waiting outside for you
to rub her nose in it.
Well, come on, Prue,
before they unfreeze.
- Piper, this isn't right.
- Well, neither is the gas chamber.
If we're lucky, we'll vanquish them and
get you back here by morning rounds.
- That's pretty lame.
- You got a better idea?
- No.
- Let's go.
Don't touch them. Don't touch them.
Don't!
Come on!
Come on.
Quite photogenic.
Now, I should think the police will find
this very interesting, to say the least.
- Rex.
- Wait, how did you know that we...?
What, that you'd be here?
Well, let's just say that
I've been watching your every move.
Without your knowing it, of course.
You bastard.
Don't get too angry, Prue.
You really wouldn't want to injure me
with your power.
I'm the only chance you have.
Whilst you were conducting
your little prison break,
Hannah was retrieving
the tiara from your home.
You should've gotten rid of it
whilst you had the chance.
Personally, I actually thought
that was an excellent idea.
- Astral projection.
- What do you want?
Your powers, of course. That's why
I hired you in the first place.
You know, to see if you really were
the Charmed Ones.
Then I waited, to test your strength,
to see how best to make my move.
- And here we are.
- But why all the drama?
Why didn't you just kill us
and take our powers?
Don't give him any ideas.
No, no, no. I have seen exactly
what you can do
when you've been confronted directly.
That is why I opted for blackmail.
See, there is a special spell
in The Book of Shadows
that strips you of your powers forever.
And this device
will capture those powers.
- And you'll bring them to me.
- Go to hell.
Yeah, I'd love to, darling.
I miss it terribly.
But this will help me return
with honours.
In return, I'll give you the photo and tell
the police I simply misplaced the tiara.
No theft, no motive for murder,
no prison.
You really don't have much time.
Just until the prison guards
realize you've escaped.
Well?
It's a relinquishment spell. If we read it
aloud, it takes away all of our powers.
- Is there any way to reverse it?
- I don't know, it doesn't say.
Well, then I say
we flip to another page
and find a spell
that kicks Rex's warlock ass.
- We can't.
- Why can't we?
Because for all we know,
he's here right now watching us.
And if we don't do exactly as he says,
he'll tell the police I've escaped.
We can't give up our powers
without a fight.
It's like giving up who we are,
who we've become.
- Who we've come from.
- Exactly.
These powers are gifts.
Gifts that were given to us to protect
and, ultimately, to pass on
to the next generation.
Don't you think that I know that?
I mean, how do you think I feel?
I'm the one who got us
into this situation.
- Prue, it's not your fault.
- It's not.
Yeah, but I'm the one
that Rex tricked.
I'm the reason why
we're having this conversation.
There has gotta be a way
out of this.
Like what, become fugitives?
Something tells me that's not
the best way to protect the innocent.
Yeah, well, we can't protect
the innocent without our powers.
And even worse, if we give them up,
we'd be giving them up to evil.
No, we can't let that happen.
Well, we can't let you die
in jail either.
Besides, with you behind bars,
we'll be divided. Rex wins either way.
- I don't wanna have to do this.
- Neither do I,
but we don't have a choice.
All we can do
is take the leap of faith
and hope that somehow
it all works out.
"From whence they came
Return them now
Vanish the words
Vanish our powers"
"From whence they came
Return them now
Vanish the words
Vanish our powers"
Come on, Phoebe.
Okay. "From whence they came
Return them now
Vanish the words
Vanish our powers"
Look.
- Well, it was fun while it lasted.
- Yep.
Let's get this over with.
They're coming.
Good.
Love you too, darling.
Why, Hannah, you've changed.
Dead 08/20/98.
He died 8/20/98.
Mr Morris. Trudeau.
Get your butt over here,
I think I figured out who framed Prue.
Okay, I say as soon as we get
the photo and the tiara back,
we knock the lantern out of Rex's
hands and stomp on it.
- What will that do?
- I don't know, free our powers?
- It's better than doing nothing.
- How do we know this isn't a trap?
You don't, actually. Nevertheless,
here you are. Powerless, I presume.
- Where's Hannah?
- Lurking. It's what she does best.
The lantern, if you please.
It all feels a little anticlimactic,
don't you think? Too easy almost.
Feels as if we need
a more satisfying ending.
No.
Hannah, now. Quickly!
- Wait, we have our powers back?
- How?
Doesn't matter.
Get out of here fast.
Rex.
No.
What have you done?
But it wasn't my fault.
I didn't fail, he did!
No! Please, no!
What the hell was that?
I think you just answered
your own question.
Okay, well, you gotta get me
back to jail now. Let's go.
We're here to see Prue Halliwell.
- Thanks, Eric.
- Thanks a lot.
Prue?
Andy, what is it? What's going on?
Thought you'd like to know
you're off the hook.
Turns out you were right.
Rex and Hannah were setting you up.
- Or whoever they were.
- I don't understand.
Well, we think they killed
two people,
assumed their identities,
then took over the auction house.
Then they bilked it dry and tried
to cap it off with stealing the tiara.
Which we found hidden in his office.
Wow, did you catch them?
Not yet.
I don't suppose you have any idea
what this was doing
in his office, do you?
- Quite photogenic.
- Isn't it?
Spells, incantations, demon stuff.
It's all here.
Everything. Just like before.
- Thank God.
- But how?
- I mean, we didn't reverse the spell.
- Well, maybe we screwed it up.
What? It's not like it would be
the first time.
No, we didn't screw it up. Something
or someone must have done it.
- It couldn't have happened on its own.
- Why not? It's magic.
- Knock, knock.
- Leo.
I... The front door was open.
I hope it's all right. I left my tool box.
That's funny, I don't remember
that being there last night.
Yeah, well, you know what Freud
always said about leaving things.
That you secretly
wanted to come back for it.
- Guilty.
- Don't use that word.
It's a long story. Never mind.
- You're leaving, aren't you?
- Yeah, I'm afraid so.
- Do you really have to go?
- Well, I've fixed everything
I came here to fix.
But I'll be back. Promise.
Nothing could keep me
away from you too long.
Well, at least he wasn't a warlock.
Hey, you don't suppose Leo
was the...? What are you doing?
Getting rid
of the relinquishment spell.
However we got our powers back,
I don't wanna risk losing them again.
- I second that.
- Third.
So witches forever?
And damn proud of it.