- Tempus, I never...
- Expected to see me?
Of course not.
You were not worthy before now.
What is the name
you are using here?
- Rodriguez.
- Ah, yes.
I've been sent to you, Rodriguez,
as a gift.
- Sent? By who?
- I think you know who.
And why.
I can defeat the Charmed Ones
on my own.
I don't need any help.
Really?
What makes you think you've actually
found the Charmed Ones?
You kidding?
After so many of my colleagues
had mysteriously vanished
in San Francisco this year?
There could only be one reason why.
I posed as a cop because
I believed one was covering for them.
And I was right, he was.
That's how I found them.
But, of course, you already know
all that, don't you?
It's what makes me
so worthy now, right?
Watch your tongue, Rodriguez,
lest I split it for you.
It's one thing to have found
the Charmed Ones,
it's quite another to defeat them,
as those who have gone before you
have already discovered.
Tomorrow is Wednesday.
I want you to get all three witches
together in one place by midnight,
and give it your best shot.
- But if you fail...
- I will not fail.
Well, if you do,
I'll be there to help you
learn by your failures.
Trust me.
Now, how do you expect
to get them together?
Trudeau.
Good morning, San Francisco.
It looks like it's going to be
a beautiful Wednesday...
Piper, what are you doing at Quake?
It's 8:00 in the morning.
- Morning.
All right. Yes, I'll be there
in an hour. Bye.
You'll be where in an hour?
Quake. Piper's doing that thing
for the Food Network,
and she needs me to bring her
another dress
because she spilled marinara sauce
all over the one she's wearing.
- Just stay out of my closet.
- Oh, don't worry,
don't think she'd want to ruin
another of yours.
- I don't believe this.
- I'm kidding. Don't have an aneurysm.
No, I'm talking about the paper.
Did you see the front page?
Where did you park my car
last night?
In the driveway, I think.
- Mrs Henderson's car.
- Oh, thank God.
I mean, that your car is in the driveway,
and I'm not in the doghouse.
- Is she okay?
- Yeah, just a little fender-bender.
No big deal.
- Phoebe, Andy's in trouble.
- What? Why?
They think that he killed
that Internal Affairs cop? No way!
Maybe it's a setup trying to
force him to reveal our secret.
Let me see that.
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
I saw Andy, Prue.
He was dead.
You said that you didn't see a demon
or a warlock in your premonition, right?
No, but the way he was hurled across
the room, there had to have been one.
- This room, here?
- Right here, yeah.
Okay, and you're positive
it was Andy?
- Prue...
- I just wanna be sure, all right.
This isn't just anybody
that we're talking about, you know.
- I know. And I care about him too.
- I know you do. I'm sorry.
All right, why don't you fill in Piper,
and I'm gonna go warn Andy.
How? He said it was too risky
for you to be seen with him.
Well, I don't care. Let Internal Affairs
find out that we're witches.
- Andy's life is a lot more important.
- Okay, just please be careful.
We don't know what kind of demon
we're up against here.
You ask me, I wouldn't be surprised
if Rodriguez whacked his own partner.
IA already cleared him.
- IA clearing IA. Go figure.
- Yeah.
- What are you doing here, Morris?
- Backing my partner, Rodriguez.
Something you wouldn't know
anything about.
This is just between him and me.
It's okay, Darryl.
Just for the record,
I'm not saying anything
without my lawyer present.
You don't need a lawyer.
Not if you're willing to help me.
You want me to help you?
What, you can't frame me
yourself, Rodriguez?
- Look, Andy...
- Oh, it's Andy now?
I don't think you had anything to do
with my partner's murder. That's right.
But what I do think
is completely off the record.
And I think you'll understand why.
It's my partner,
or at least what's left of him.
No human could've
done that to him.
I think he was killed
by something supernatural.
And I think you can help me
figure out who or what it is.
- Really? What makes you think that?
- Come on.
I know all about those
unsolved cases of yours.
And I know who's behind them too,
who you've been covering for.
It's very noble.
You must care about her very much
to give up your career for her.
Prue Halliwell is a witch.
A witch, huh?
You wait here.
I'll go warn the Wizard of Oz.
I don't have time
to screw around, Trudeau.
I want you to arrange a meeting
between her and me.
It has to be tonight.
If she can help me find
who killed my partner,
I'll drop all charges against you,
and I won't tell anybody about her.
You think about it,
but not too long.
- You all right?
- I'm not sure.
I gotta go see Prue.
That's funny. She called and said
she had to see you too.
Well?
I'm sure I made Trudeau
suspicious of me.
He'll go to Prue, she'll have no choice
but to meet with me.
But you have to get
all three of them together.
Trudeau cares about her.
He won't let her risk meeting me alone.
He'll insist she have
the power of three there with her.
For protection.
And you think you have the power
to defeat them all?
You don't think I do, do you?
- You think I'll fail.
- Time will tell.
Phoebe, over here.
Thank God. The segment producer's
gonna be here any minute,
and I'm a complete and total wreck.
I thought I was gonna
have to pull a Céline Dion
- and wear my dress backwards.
- Piper, you've gotta listen to me.
I had a premonition of Andy dying.
- What? When?
- This morning.
Don't you check your voice mail?
I called and said it was important.
- Oh, no. Where's Prue?
- She's warning him.
In the meantime, we have to
figure out who the demon is.
Piper?
Piper Halliwell?
I would recognise you anywhere.
You have not changed one bit.
You don't recognise me, do you?
It's Joanne.
Joanne Hertz.
Baker High, class of '92.
Oh, sure. Of course. Joanne.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm the segment producer.
You're the segment producer?
She's the segment producer.
I heard.
Wow, what a small world.
I thought you moved to New York.
I did, and that's where I met
my fabulous husband,
who had this crazy idea
about starting this little cable show,
and putting me in charge
of everything.
And here we are, the Food Network's
most popular show.
Talk about dreams coming true.
Anyway, enough about me,
what have you been doing?
- Why'd you do that?
- What am I supposed to say?
That I'm a cash-strapped,
single restaurant manager
who still lives in the same house
I grew up in with my sisters?
- And the cat. Don't forget our cat.
- Phoebe, this isn't funny.
Look, I don't know why you're getting
so upset. She is a freak.
I'm sorry, but no one is
that successful at age 26.
Besides, you are successful.
You're talented, you're creative,
and the Food Network
is here to see you.
Not me, not her, you.
- Feel better now?
- Very little.
Good. Unfreeze that bitch in heels.
You've got a segment to shoot,
and we've got a demon to find.
Has Phoebe ever been wrong
about her premonitions before?
No. But the good news is,
every other time,
we've been able
to affect the outcome.
- Stop the demon or warlock before...
- Before I get killed.
Can I get that in writing?
Andy, you just have to be
extra careful
until we figure out who this demon is
and why he's after you, okay?
Andy?
I was just thinking,
what if the demon is Rodriguez?
Why would you say that?
He pulled me into the station house
this morning.
I thought he was gonna arrest me,
but what he really wanted
was a meeting with you.
Meet with me? Why?
He thinks his partner was killed
by a supernatural being
and somehow, I don't know how, Prue,
he knows you're a witch.
- How would he know that, unless...?
- Unless he's the demon.
All right, tell Rodriguez to meet me
at the manor at 6:00.
- It's too dangerous, Prue.
- I don't have a choice.
If I don't meet with him,
he'll frame you and try and expose me.
But if he is a demon,
and it turns out to be a trap?
I'll have Piper and Phoebe there
to back me up. The power of three.
- Plus one. Me.
- No, you can't be there, Andy.
That's where you were
in Phoebe's premonition when...
Just promise me you'll stay away.
- I can't do that, Prue.
- I mean it.
Don't make me use my magic on you.
I don't want anything
to happen to you, Andy.
You know how much
I still care for you.
Okay. I promise.
All right, let's go over
the plan again.
Yeah, let's, because I wanna know
why I'm the one answering the door.
Because you're the one
who knows martial arts, all right.
If Rodriguez shows up
and tries something right off the bat,
you can knock him down.
Then I can come in from
the living room and freeze him.
And I can come down the stairs
and send him flying.
Still feel like cannon fodder.
- What time is it?
- Just before 6.
That's a little too anxious.
That's not a good sign.
Which means if he doesn't wanna
kill Prue, he wants to date her.
All right, come on,
let's get this day over with.
Okay.
All right already.
Inspector Rodriguez.
I'm here to see Prue Halliwell.
Yeah, no kidding.
Prue, Piper, company.
Phoebe!
Phoebe.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, God, Phoebe.
- Prue, is she okay?
She's dead.
What?
Phoebe!
Hurts to die, doesn't it?
Especially at the hands of a witch.
Wait. What happened?
Where am I?
Exactly where you were
when you first met me.
Time has been reset.
Or, rather, I have reset time.
But they killed me.
That was Wednesday night, this is
Wednesday morning all over again.
This is why I have been sent to you:
To keep resetting time
until you learn from your failures.
Only you will carry with you the
memory of what has happened before.
And each time you fail,
you will learn more
until, ultimately,
you will kill all of them.
Good morning, San Francisco.
It looks like it's going to be
a beautiful Wednesday...
Piper, what are you doing at Quake?
It's 8:00 in the morning.
- Morning.
Wait a minute.
I am freaking out.
Okay, I'll be there in an hour.
Be where in an hour?
- Okay, pinch me.
- What?
No, I mean it, pinch me.
I wanna make sure I'm awake.
Because if I am,
I am having one killer déjà vu.
So it's just a déjà vu.
Everybody gets them.
Not like this, they don't. Look, Prue,
something weird is going on here.
- I don't believe this.
- No, trust me, okay.
This has happened before.
Everything!
I'm talking about the paper.
Did you see the front page?
See? Like that, right there.
You said that before, I know it.
Okay, and that has happened
before too.
Where did you park my car
last night?
In the driveway. And I told you that
already the last time you asked me.
I think I'm having an aneurysm.
Mrs Henderson's car.
Just a little fender-bender.
No big deal.
Prue, I am not nuts.
Okay, maybe just a little,
but that's irrelevant here.
- Phoebe, Andy's in trouble.
- What?
Let me see that.
Now, that was a premonition
which I've had before.
- Of what?
- Of Andy, here...
...being killed by a demon.
- What are you doing here?
- Backing my partner.
- You got a problem with that?
- Get out. Now!
It's okay, Darryl. I got it.
Just for the record,
I'm not saying anything
without my lawyer present.
Forget your lawyer.
I'm not screwing around this time.
This time?
What are you talking about?
Bottom line, I know my partner
was killed by a supernatural being,
and I think Prue Halliwell
can help me figure out who did it.
Really?
I'll just get the commissioner
to signal Batman
and then I'll get right on it.
You think I'm joking?
I know everything, Trudeau.
Including the fact that
Prue Halliwell is a witch.
You're gonna arrange a meeting
with her tonight, understand?
Or else I'm gonna bust your ass
and expose hers.
- What was that about?
- I'm not sure.
- Well?
- Trudeau will set to meet,
but what I need to know is how to avoid
the pain of getting vanquished again.
Depends on whether you've learned
enough to vanquish them first.
What do you remember?
Last time, I killed the youngest one,
Phoebe, without a fight.
But then when I turned to kill Piper...
I think she's the one
who has the power to freeze.
Adjust.
Simply anticipate where
she's coming from earlier,
before she has the chance
to freeze you.
Then kill Prue.
Andy dies?
Are you sure that's what you saw?
Even worse, I know that I've had
the same premonition before.
I mean, before I had it earlier today.
- You mean, like yesterday?
- Yes. I mean, no.
It's not just the premonition
I've seen before, it's everything.
And don't tell me that it's just déjà vu,
because I know that it's not.
- Okay, all right, then what is it?
- Piper?
Piper Halliwell?
I would recognise you anywhere.
You have not changed one bit.
You don't recognise me, do you?
- It's...
- Joanne.
Joanne Hertz, right?
- I'm right, aren't I?
- I'm sorry, have we met?
Yes. I mean, sort of. Before.
Baker High, class of '92.
Although, I wasn't in that class.
Oh, sure. Of course. Joanne.
- Phoebe, how did you...?
- That's what I've been trying to tell you.
I think we're in some
funky time loop here.
- Phoebe.
- Freeze her. I'll show you.
Okay, Joanne here is
the Food Network segment producer.
She's about to brag how she's
happily married to some rich guy,
how she's following her dreams,
how she's had a really bad nose job.
Okay, I added the last part.
But this is all gonna make
you feel like
you're wasting your life away
in comparison.
Unfreeze her.
Go ahead, see for yourself.
- Are you the segment producer?
- Why, yes, I am.
Following your dreams, are you?
Happily married? Stinking rich?
- Well, I don't mean to brag, but...
- Oh, God.
All right, Phoebe, spill it.
Okay, the best I can figure is
some demon has cast a spell,
and I'm the only one
who can sort of see it
because my power lets me see things
that have happened in different times.
- Do you have a better explanation?
- No.
All right, so if you're right,
you think this has something to do
with Andy being killed?
I don't know, but we'll never find who
the demon is unless we get to...
Book of Shadows.
I'm right behind you.
What if he is a demon,
and it turns out to be a trap?
I'll have Piper and Phoebe there
to back me up. The power of three.
Plus one. Me.
What is it?
This seems a little familiar to me,
that's all. Kind of like déjà vu.
Never mind.
Andy, you can't be at the meeting.
In Phoebe's premonition,
that's where you were when...
Just promise me
that you'll stay away.
- Prue, I can't do that.
- I mean it.
Don't make me use my magic on you.
Andy, I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
You know how much I still love you.
No...
...I didn't.
Anything in there about time loops?
A spell to accelerate time,
that's about it.
I'm telling you,
this is all part of his evil plan.
I just haven't had enough time
to figure it out yet.
- What time is it?
- Just before 6.
I'll get it.
All right already.
Phoebe!
Oh, my God, no!
Piper!
Son of a bitch!
- Failed again, I see.
- Yeah, but I learned.
This time I got two of them.
Third time is the charm.
Good morning, San Francisco.
It looks like it's going to be a beautiful
Wednesday in the Bay Area...
Don't tell me, I already know.
You spilled marinara sauce
on your dress, right? Am I right?
Think, Piper, think. Doesn't all of this
seem awfully familiar to you?
- Morning.
- Freeze.
No, not you, Piper.
Kit knocks over pepper, meows.
Hold that thought.
Okay, Piper, you need to get home
as soon as you can.
Okay, we've got major
demon hunting to do.
Oh, and if you run into someone
named Joanne from high school,
just tell her to go stick it.
I will explain later, just hurry.
- Okay, what's going on?
- Quick, follow me.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Car honks, skids, crashes.
Mrs Henderson's car,
a little fender-bender.
Good thing I parked your car
in the driveway last night.
How did you know that?
Because this has all happened
once before, Prue.
Maybe even more than once.
The day keeps repeating itself.
I know it.
And every time it happens, I think
I figure it out just a little bit faster.
It must be my power of premonition.
Premonition.
I'm supposed to be having
a premonition right about now.
Supposed to? What do you mean?
The paper. Look at the front page.
- Andy...
- Is in trouble.
More than you know, Prue.
If I touch that paper,
I will have a premonition.
The same one that I've had before,
where Andy gets killed, here,
by a demon.
You have got to believe me.
No, I believe you. The question is,
what do we do about it?
Well, you've gotta go warn Andy.
Keep him away from our house
at all costs.
Meanwhile, I've gotta dig through
the Book of Shadows,
find a way to vanquish this time demon
before he can kill Andy.
You really shouldn't have done that.
You shouldn't do anything differently
if you expect to succeed tonight.
I will succeed tonight, old man.
There will be no more time loops.
This time I'll kill Prue first
and then the other two.
And when they die,
they're gonna feel every ounce of pain
they've given me and then some.
Joanne, I'm so sorry,
but I can't do this segment right now.
Something's happened.
Something bad. I have to go.
What? Run out of marinara sauce?
Kidding.
Look, I know I don't have
the flashy job or the flashy ring
or the flashy designer suit,
but that doesn't make me
less than you or anybody else.
And just because I may not
have realised my dreams yet
like you think you have, doesn't mean
I won't find a way to do exactly that.
And when I do, you can be damn sure
I'll be doing it with my own nose
and not the one
some discount doctor gave me.
A time loop? You mean demons can
actually do that sort of thing?
None that I've ever seen before.
But if it is a demon,
it's the most powerful one
that we've ever come up against.
And he's going through all this
just to kill me?
No way, Prue.
If he's as powerful as you say,
then he's gotta be after you.
Please let us handle this.
Whatever you do, promise me
that you'll stay away from the manor.
I can't promise you that.
If you're right and Rodriguez
is the demon, then it's a trap.
I'll have Piper and Phoebe there
to back me up. The power of three.
What if he wants all three
of you together?
If that's the reason he
set the time loop?
- We'll have to take our chances.
- You could get killed, Prue.
I mean it. This is not your fight.
Don't make me use my magic on you.
Andy, I would die
if anything happened to you.
I love you.
I love you too, Prue.
Oh, my God! Prue!
The devil's sorcerer, Tempus, he can
manipulate time any way he chooses.
Does it say how to vanquish him?
Take him out of the time that he's in,
whatever that means.
No!
Andy!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Is Prue okay?
Yeah. She's out cold.
Oh, my God.
He's dead.
The only reason you're still alive
is because I haven't figured out
how to kill you yet.
Go ahead, kill me, witch.
I don't care.
- Phoebe, what are you doing?
- I'm trying to save Andy.
Andy? Andy's dead.
You can't save him, Phoebe.
No? We're in a time loop, aren't we?
All we have to do is start
this day over, and Andy lives.
And I'm willing to bet that his death
somehow triggers the time loop.
I'm impressed.
I was told you wouldn't know that.
Really?
By who?
Tempus? Yeah,
we know about him too,
and we also know
that you're not him.
Otherwise, you would've restarted
the day by now.
- So where do we find him?
- In your nightmares.
Kill me.
I dare you.
Why is he so willing
to let us kill him?
Who cares? He dies, Andy lives.
End of story.
What if that's exactly his plan?
To reset the day
and he can kill us all next?
Doesn't matter. The day's gonna
reset itself anyway,
and there's not a damn thing
you can do to stop it.
Shut up. Come on,
we have to wake up Prue.
Prue.
Prue, come on,
we need your help.
- Prue.
- Prue. Prue.
Come to me, Prue.
Andy, what's going on?
Where are we?
I'm not quite sure, really.
I hoped I'd end up here,
but not so soon.
One thing I do know, though,
is that I'm staying.
You're not.
I don't understand.
I broke my promise, Prue.
I came to your house tonight.
Turns out Phoebe's premonition
was one you couldn't stop after all.
Weren't supposed to stop.
- Wait a minute, Andy, no.
- It's okay, Prue, really.
Trust me.
This is my destiny, I know that now.
Yours is to continue on.
Everything happens for a reason,
remember? You taught me that.
- This isn't fair.
- You need to go back.
You need to keep the time loop
from being reset again,
or you and your sisters
will be killed,
and I will have died in vain.
- I'll kill Rodriguez for this.
- No, you won't.
You're not a murderer, Prue.
You're a good person
who does good things.
- I don't wanna lose you.
- Don't worry, you won't.
I'll always be there for you, Prue.
Prue.
Prue, come on, wake up, sweetie.
Come on.
Come on, we need your help.
Easy, easy, easy.
- Okay.
- Where's Andy?
Prue, something terrible
has happened.
Oh, my God.
It all happened so fast, Prue.
He ran in the door
when Rodriguez attacked.
He was trying to save us.
And he'll succeed.
- Where's the Book of Shadows?
- It's right here.
Why?
Where's the spell that you saw
to accelerate time?
- What are you doing?
- There.
What's going on?
We don't wanna accelerate time,
we wanna reverse it.
No, we don't, trust me.
The only chance that we have
to get rid of Tempus is to do this
by breaking the time loop, okay?
But if we break the time loop,
we won't be able to save Andy.
- I know.
- Prue, are you sure?
No, I'm not.
"Winds of time, gather round
Give me wings to speed my way"
Wait a minute.
"Rush me on my journey forward
Let tomorrow be today"
What's happening?
No!
Prue?
You know what, just untie him.
Get him out of here.
What? He'll kill us!
No, he won't.
He doesn't have the power to kill us.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
needed Tempus.
I will not untie him, Prue.
Get out of here
before I change my mind.
You stupid witch.
We may not be murderers,
but we're no angels either.
Good morning, San Francisco.
Well, it looks like it's going to be
a gorgeous Monday morning
here in the Bay Area...
She really needs another shtick,
that one's getting boring.
Maybe she should hire Joanne Hertz,
boost her ratings.
Speaking of the she-devil herself,
did you ever call
to reschedule your segment?
No, I'm not going to.
- Why?
- I've decided to quit my job.
What?
And, actually, I owe it all to Joanne.
She made me realise
that somehow I'd forgotten
what my dreams were.
Still are.
I always wanted to be a chef
and have my own restaurant,
not manage one.
It's a good job and the pay's okay,
but it's not my dream job.
I think that's great. I really do.
And don't worry, if you need any help
trolling the classifieds, I am an expert.
Prue? Are you all right?
Yeah, actually, I am.
Andy's been exonerated.
They're now looking for Rodriguez.
Good luck.
Hey, are you sure you're all right?
Yeah.
I was just thinking about
all that we've been through
since we became witches.
- Give you a headache?
- No, actually.
It gave me a good feeling.
I mean, look, it's a hassle
and can sometimes screw up
our personal lives...
- Amen to that.
- And we do good things together.
It helps offset the bad things.
I'm gonna really miss Andy.
It's gonna be very sad without him.
Something tells me
that he'll always be with us.
We better get ready for work.
I'll tell her later.
- Tell me what?
- Nothing. It's not important.
- Nothing.