Don't go in the cellar!
Don't go in the cellar! No!
The name in the movies:
"Don't go in the cellar"
And there goes your head.
Stupid teenagers.
He's inside my house?
Oh, my gosh.
Louise, why are you practicing so late?
I'm sorry, dad.
I forgot this was your Tv time.
All right. Look, you know,
I got the premium package, I told you.
If I don't watch 5 hours of tv a day,
i'm throwing money out the window.
I have to practice. Grandma and grandpa
are coming for my recital tomorrow.
- You remember my recital, right?
- Remember?
Are you kidding me?
I'm your Roadie, man.
Sound check is at 11:00 sharp.
And sober, all right?
How come you didn't practice
this earlier, you know?
Well, I had choir practice after school,
then volleyball.
Then I had to study for my geography
test, and then I had my math tutor.
That's too much stuff, Louise. When
are you gonna take time to be a kid?
In my late 30s, like you.
I'd ground you for that, but then
I wouldn't have anybody to play with.
I'm gonna go watch baseball.
Play me out.
Charge!
- = 116 =-
" Gary Uses His Veto "
Sub VO :   ¤Aka¤
Subs-Addicts"
[Sub-way.fr]
- I can't take this.
- Look, it's almost over.
Louise is gonna be playing.
Dear god. She's freaking last!
- I'm making a break for it.
- What?
Act natural. Be cool. Be cool.
Take a break.
Go back. Go back.
This concludes our concert.
I think all of your children were
simply marvelous, and I look forward
to seeing all of you at the next recital
at the mcmartins'house next week.
What?!
Should I bring? Ham?
Jello salad?
I'll start working on both.
Oh, my gosh. I don't mind listening
to my own daughter, but
3 hours of listening to other kids?
I was willing my appendix to burst.
I'll tell you one good thing
that came out of that recital.
I don't fear death anymore.
You've got a real prodigy
on your hands, Allison.
Please don't squander her
talents the way you did yours.
OK, look, mom, I was never going
to become an Olympic gymnast.
I have bad depth perception.
Fine. So gymnastics wasn't your thing.
But you were an excellent swimmer.
I was.
With your tiny breasts
and your huge feet,
you could glide through
that water like a little seal.
OK, look, mom, no one is
squandering Louise's talents, OK?
We both encourage her to
explore all of her interests.
Did I tell you she's starting
Mandarin lessons tomorrow?
What? You didn't tell me.
My granddaughter,
the concert cellist who speaks Chinese.
I can't wait to whip that one
out when my neighbor brags
about her blind daughter
who climbed everest.
Time out. Wait a second here.
Why does Louise have to take Chinese?
When the Chinese take over the world,
they're gonna teach it to us
all for free in the reeducation camps.
Louise is an exceptional child.
She needs to stay stimulated.
Yeah, but she's too stimulated.
You know, she's got volleyball
and cello and now Chinese?
I mean, she's pretty.
She doesn't have to be smart.
She's taking Mandarin.
- Maybe she's not.
- Maybe she is.
Maybe I'll pull out
the big gun on this one.
Please. What,
you're gonna pull out your veto here?
- Try me.
- What are you two talking about?
When we were in marriage counseling,
they gave us a tool to get
through deadlocks the veto.
You get one a year, it's ironclad,
and the other one has to honor it.
Hey, maybe we should.
Gary, think about this.
I mean, all the career opportunities
this could open up for Louise.
- A translator.
- Veto.
- Ambassador.
- International trade lawyer?
- Wait a second. What was that last one?
- International.
- Veto.
- The veto is finito.
- All right, fine,
- but that is your veto for the year.
- Great. Fine with me.
I would do it again if I had to.
Sayonara, Chinese.
- That's Japanese.
- I guess we'll never know, will we?
Hey, mom,
when is the recital gonna start?
It's over, Tommy.
You slept through the whole thing.
But I was here, so it counts, right?
Yes, you were here. You were here
and accounted for. That counts.
All right. I'm gonna go tell Louise
she was great. She was, wasn't she?
You know,
rather than focusing on Louise,
you might want to
spend some time on Tom.
Now, that's a boy that needs
to be interested in something.
Tommy's good at a lot of things.
He's got hobbies, you know?
He, he can fall asleep anywhere.
You know?
Hey, what about golf?
I was gonna play 18 holes
at rancho tomorrow, and I was
may I please play
18 holes at rancho tomorrow?
Hey, you know,
that's a great idea, Charlie.
Let's get Tommy interested in golf.
Can we play?
All right.
But no beer, no cigars,
and it wouldn't kill you
to walk the course.
If it would, i'd walk it.
Well, Tom, welcome to heaven on earth.
What makes you think
I'm gonna like golf so much?
Because every guy loves golf.
Hey, you're walking around
in the great outdoors.
- You're drinking beer. You're cussing.
- Yeah. I like the hell out of that.
- How about no cussing today?
- Can I have a beer?
So basically we're just
in the great outdoors?
Yeah. Have fun.
I'm just gonna sit over here
and study for my history test.
OK, Tom. I want you to bend your knees.
Keep your head down.
All right, eyes on the ball
and make sure you follow through.
Are you OK, dad?
No, I'm not OK!
The ball hit me on my neck!
Tom, you can't learn golf that quickly.
You got to keep trying.
Here we go. Try it again.
Here we go.
Sorry.
In 35 years of golf,
I have never seen anyone lose a shoe.
I guess I'm trying too hard?
Yeah, well,
that's the spin we'll put on it.
Now, from now on, what I want
you to do is to really concentrate
on keeping your feet planted.
Yes! I hit it further than Tom.
Nice shot, Louise.
I'd like to see you ricochet one off
the wall and then hit dad in the neck.
So, Louise,
why don't you try hitting another one?
- I lost it.
- It's not coming down.
I hit that sign. Sorry.
That's OK. That's just
put out there so people know
how far away 200 yards is.
So how long has
your daughter been playing?
Including today? One minute.
Don't beat yourself up over it, Tom, OK?
I know, but that guy seemed
really mad about his windshield.
Right. Look,
forget about it. He'll get over it.
Bentley, very common car.
Nobody learns golf and is good
at it on the first try. Nobody...
- Hey, look, Tom. Check it out.
- Stop showing off, Louise.
I'm still gonna get
my license before you.
You realize you have to
take a test for that, right?
A test?
I did it, Charlie.
I'm a golf dad.
You know, Tiger Woods bought his
paren a mansion and cars and trips.
I know I'm just the grandfather,
but, Louise knows I love her, right?
Listen, I've got to run this by Allison.
We got to get her into lessons.
Yeah, right. Allison. You know,
I don't think she's gonna
be quite as thrilled as we are.
Wait. Why not?
When Allie was younger, I tried to
get her interested in golf
by sort of, shoving it down her throat.
- She never told me that.
- Yeah, it ended kind of ugly.
I think it really peaked when she ran
away from golf camp down in Florida.
She was never the same
sweet little 9-year-old
after they pulled her out
of the everglades.
- No wonder she hates golf.
- And leeches.
God. She's got to go along
with this golf thing. I just...
I wish I didn't veto
chinese the way that I did.
Yeah, well,
you did lay it on pretty thick.
I love to torture Allison.
If only there was a way I could get
her to use her veto on something else.
- Wait a minute. What did you just say?
- I love to torture Allison.
No, after that.
I should get her to use
her veto on something else.
- That is a great idea.
- That's what I should do, right?
Good grief. What is that horrible noise?
Sounds like some nut on a motorcycle.
And it seems to be getting louder,
doesn't it?
- Was that Gary?
- Come on. He's in the garage.
Gary! What the hell are you doing?
I bought Tom a dirt bike.
OK, wait a minute.
So you bought our son a motorcycle.
You said get him interested in
something. He'll be interested in this.
Are you a complete idiot?
Dirt bikes are dangerous.
This is the single most irresponsible
act of parenting I have ever seen.
Boy, if I could,
I would veto the hell out of this.
Don't say that. Don't say that, Charlie.
Come on. Stay out of it.
This is about my son becoming a man, OK?
- No. Dad's right.
- Allison, please,
- don't use your veto on the motorcycle.
- Sorry. You know what? I have to.
- Hold on, dear.
- What?
Now, I can't put my finger on it, but
there's something weird going on here,
Gary and Charlie is doing
that bad acting thing
he does every time he wants
to get away with something.
What? Are you saying my concern
the well-being
of my grandson is just an act?
Well, how dare you!
All right, what's going on?
Why are you trying so hard
to get me to use my veto?
What? No, I don't want you to
use your veto on a dirt bike.
OK. All right. Fine.
- What are you doing?
- What?
You think Tommy should ride
a dirt bike, then that's what he'll do.
Good. Then you call him.
Get him down here.
- What's going on?
- Look what your dad got you.
- You bought me a dirt bike?
- You betcha.
- Mom, you're OK with this?
- Yeah.
If your dad thinks it's a good
idea, then it must be a good idea.
- Is it, dad?
- It's a real good idea, Tommy.
- Mom?
- Come on, Tommy.
Get up there. I mean,
what's the worst that can happen?
Having to learn how to type
with a pencil taped to my nose?
- Come on, Tommy. Jump inside.
- Yeah. Get on the bike, Tom.
All right. Look at you?
Look how great he looks up there, Gary.
Right?
- Why don't you start it up, sweetie?
- Yeah, Tom. Start your new dirt bike.
Be a man.
- Turn it off! Turn it off!
- What? What? What?
What? Come on. Come on.
Don't be afraid. Get back up there.
You know, I heard something weird
with the axle rows connector.
You can't ride this
until I get it checked out, Tom.
Thank god.
I don't know what's going on here,
but I don't like it.
Nothing, nothing is going on here,
Allison, OK?
The only problem with that motorcycle
it's not big enough.
I've got to buy him a bigger
motorcycle and a knife.
Am I the only one left sane around here?
Fore!
Nice.
- Louise, nice shot.
- Thanks, mom.
- That's my third one in a row.
- That's great, honey.
3 in a row. That is great.
- Veto!
- What?
- Are you vetoing paper cups?
- No. Gary, i'm vetoing golf.
That's what this was all about?
You want Louise to play golf?
I'm telling you. My daughter
is not playing that awful sport.
You've got to see how good she is. She's
phenom. She's amazing. Don't veto golf.
You know what? She would have
been really good at Chinese, too.
Come on. A billion people speak Chinese.
Why do you need one more?
Veto!
Please! Finally it's an activity
that I can enjoy with my daughter,
- something I'm interested in.
- All right. So
if it really means
that much to you, maybe I can veto it!
Allie, why don't you do it for me?
Let's not kid each other here.
I'm not getting any younger,
and I would love to see
my little Louise play golf
before the big guy signs my scorecard.
Please.
You'll die when i'm done with you.
That's it, Charlie.
It's the death of a dream.
I saw it all.
I saw little Louise playing
in the dinah shore classic.
On the 18th hole, she sinks a 30-footer.
The place goes crazy, and she looks
right into the camera and goes,
"that was for my dad."
And then
she tosses me the keys
to a brand-new saturn she won.
Look at me, Gary.
What do you see?
A guy with a mustache that's...
mostly nose hair.
Gary, it's you in 20 years
if you don't do something to change it.
Ghost of Gary future,
it's you I fear most of all.
Come on. Charlie, I'm sorry
I disappointed you, but it's the veto.
- It's the one thing we have to respect.
- Knot up, betty.
This is bigger than any
stupid little agreement.
We're talking about Louisa's
future. Look.
I bet you can't name
me one famous cellist.
- Yo-yo ma.
- You see? You see?
You see? Because there aren't any.
But you can rattle on, like,
famous golfers all day long.
And maybe one of those
names could be Lulu Brooks.
- Lulu?
- Lulu. See, it chants a lot better.
- Lulu.
- Hey, it's up to you, Gary.
I leave it up to you.
But when you're my age, do you want
to be looking back at sundays
spent in some stuffy old concert hall
or walking the links
of pebble beach half in the bag?
- Nice shot, dad.
- Thanks, sweetheart.
I still feel weird about
skipping cello practice.
Well, we all do things we feel
weird about that might be wrong.
After a while, that feeling goes away.
And if the feeling goes away,
was it every really wrong?
Great. Louise, why don't you go practice
some chip shots out of the sand trap?
And remember.
I know. Hit two inches behind
the ball and follow through.
Don't tell the boy,
but she's my favorite now.
- It's Connie.
- Don't answer it.
Don't worry. I got it covered.
Connie had me record Louise's
recital the other day.
Something about memories.
Hey, buttercup.
Just calling to see how Louise's
cello practice is going.
It's wonderful.
I'm so proud of our little Angel.
You should see her.
She's playing like a pro.
I am so happy you wanted
to go to Louise's cello practice.
It's not like you.
Well, it's the new me, buttercup.
You know, I think i'm gonna
be going to a lot of
Louise's practices from now on.
Put your hat back on.
You're not supposed to get sun.
All right. Thanks, dear.
We're dead.
What? Why?
Great.
It's the two horsemen of the apocalypse.
It was Gary's idea.
He told me if I didn't play along,
i'd lose my social security.
How did you guys find us?
Louise's cello teacher
called asking where she was.
Cello? Oh cello.
When you said take her to cello,
I thought you said take her to golf.
Mom said you guys would be out here
playing golf, and I said, "of course not
"because Gary would
never do that because I vetoed golf,"
and veto is the one thing
that we both respect, Gary.
How am I supposed to
ever trust you again?
What? I don't know what
you're saying. I'm sorry.
He thinks you're playing his ball.
I'm not playing his ball.
I'm playing my ball. Look. That's my...
I forgive you, Gary.
Come on, honey, let's go.
Time out.
I'm curious as to how my daughter is
fluent in a language that I vetoed.
I don't know. Kids.
What, did you pick it up off the street?
- They're like little sponges, you know.
- Yeah, time out.
Back it up.
Whatever happened to "Gary, the veto
is the only thing we have to respect"?
OK. I ignored your veto, OK?
But you ignored mine.
But you ignored my veto first.
My veto was finito.
- You didn't know that, so technically.
- Enough!
Who cares who did what first?
The point is, you should be celebrating
the fact that you both had a hand
in creating this incredibly
wonderfully talented child.
Well, you're right, Connie.
Thanks, mom.
That's a sweet thing to say.
I would have killed to have had
a child with a fraction of this talent.
- Get the clubs.
- Yes, dear.
Gary, I'm taking Louise to cello now.
You can pick her up at 1:30,
take her to volleyball practice.
And tomorrow she has debate before
school, so you have to take her early.
And then saturday i'm taking her to
golf from 7:00 in the morning to noon.
But be sure to pop in a Chinese
tape on the way to the course
so she'll be ready for her
wednesday night lesson.
Is it too late to veto
having a second child?
I'm kidding. What? She's enriched
our lives in so many wonderful ways.
Come on, mommy. Grandma's in the car.
She says if we don't hurry up,
she's gonna go ahead and smoke.
Coming.
Well, Gary, it looks like
you may get to walk the links
of pebble beach after all,
there, golf dad.
Thank you. You know what?
Thanks for giving me the courage
to break that veto agreement, you know?
If only there was something we could
find for Tommy that he's good at.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, son.
There's got to be
something he's good at.
Team Subs-Addicts"