Oh, my gosh.
That was incredible.
Hey, sorry about the buttons
on your blouse.
I just got a little
frustrated and ripped
them off.
That's all right.
Don't worry about it.
It was only...Prada.
But the one thing
that was confusing
Was what was that list of guys'
names you kept repeating?
That was the lineup for 1988
dodgers. It--it helps me.
So, did it live up
to all your expectations?
You kidding me? It lived up
to expectations I didn't
know that I had.
Holy smokes.
It was thrilling.
It was super hot.
At one point
it was really scary.
Sorry.
I was a trained gymnast.
If I could just get some
chalk on my hands I could
[knuckles crack]
really show you something.
Oh, my gosh. Wow.
So, what happens now?
I mean, I've never dated
anyone from work before.
Do we drive in together
tomorrow?
I don't think so.
I think we should probably
keep work work,
And this this.
Like, keep it separate.
Ok. So, when we're at work,
we don't tell anyone.
And I'm your boss.
And you're my employee.
When you say that
it sounds really hot.
Maybe we should do it again,
I don't have any chalk
But I could probably find
some baby powder.
Sync by deGroote.
www.addic7ed.com
Curtis: Lunch is here.
Kfc?
Mm-hmm.
New fiery grill wings, yo!
Be careful, man.
These things are hot.
I had one in the car,
felt like I was sucking
on a blowtorch.
Whoo!
Let me try one of these
bad boys right here.
Can't be that hot.
Yeah. That's not that hot.
Oh, my god!
Aah! That's hot coffee!
Aah!
What the hell is that?!
It's a bloody mary.
What?! It's 5:00 someplace!
Hey, curtis.
Hello, gary.
Brooks. Nice to see
you in the workplace.
Hello, sasha. Nice to see you.
You look very nice.
Why, thank you.
Oh, not at all.
You guys are doing it.
What?!
What gives you that idea?
Because you guys
are talking like you're
in victorian England.
[british accent]
uh, sasha, nice to see you.
I find myself captivated
by your charms.
I pray you don't
get cholera.
All right!
Just don't tell anybody, ok?
Just keep it a secret.
We don't want everyone
to start gossiping.
Especially hannah in ad sales.
You know, gossip--
That's like heroin
to that lady.
Actually, I think
that heroin is like
heroin to hannah.
Ok. I'm gonna get
some plates.
Oh, plates. No. Sweetheart,
these are fiery wings.
These are meant
to be eaten out of a bucket,
like a real man.
All the same, I think I would
like to take it into my office
And eat it like a lady.
Eat it like a lady? What?
With knife and fork.
No, like shoving it
into my face
Until I feel like I've
punished my mom enough!
Well, somebody picked
the right time to start
sleeping with the boss.
Oh, what are you talking about?
You didn't hear?
The latest ratings book
just came in,
And she's talking about
changing things--
Extending shows,
cutting shows.
But you're going to be safe.
Look. Sasha's the boss.
I'm just an employee.
She controls what happens
in the workplace.
She's going to add shows
that she wants.
She's going to cut shows
that she doesn't want to do.
She's the boss.
She's going to do whatever
she wants. It's her choice.
And it has nothing to do
with the fact
That she's scored
a 10 on my pommel horse
last night.
So, tom, how are things
going at my little boy's
very first job?
Huh? You like working
at hogie moe's?
No. I wanna quit.
What?!
That's told me I'd be in charge
of urinal cakes and lettuce.
Ok. Please tell me
they have a "lava las manos"
sign in the bathroom?
I don't know. But there's
this really sad poem
in one of stalls
About a guy who's brokenhearted.
See he came there--
No! I know it.
I know the poem, tom.
Look, I know it may not be
the most fulfilling job
in the world,
But I think it's important
we learned to stick
with things.
It's easy for you to get
excited. You're starting
a job you've always wanted.
That's true. Working
for the dean of psychology
at ucla--
You know, it didn't just
fall into my lap.
They had my resume there
for over a year and a half
before they called.
And you know what?
Before that I had to work
a lot degrading jobs.
I waited tables.
I bartended.
I was married to your
father for 15 years.
Yeah. That wasn't a paying job.
It is now.
[car horn]
Oh, there's your dad.
Go get your books, ok?
Hello, allison. How are you?
Ok. What's with you?
What do you mean,
"what's with me?"
You're in a good mood.
Your cheeks are all flushed.
So, they're either remaking
"porky's" or--
Ooh, you had sex.
Well, it is true.
Sasha and I did make love.
But what? Are they really
remaking "porky's?"
No. No.
No, gary. No.
Really? You're not
at all afraid
About how sex is going
to affect you two
working together?
Oh, no.
Sasha and I, we both agreed
to keep it professional.
Plus, I read a very interesting
article in "the new yorker"
That said office romances are
actually common these days.
Ok. A) no, you didn't.
And um, b) my guess is
you fell asleep during
a laker game
And woke up during
a dr. Phil re-run.
Gary, sex changes everything.
I mean, it makes everything
personal.
Think about the first time
we did it.
Uh, us having sex
changed nothing.
I went from thinking
you were slutty
to knowing you were slutty.
Everybody knew that.
When you're slutty,
word tends to get around.
Sasha: Ok. Next thing.
Since our kppq family
is growing,
We're running a little
short on parking spaces.
So, are there any volunteers
to park in the lot
across the street?
I'm fine with parking across
the street.
There's no reason why I should
have a special spot.
Thank you, gary,
for being a good
team member.
Hey, you know what?
I'm doing what any other
team member would do.
And last order of business--
this is a little tough.
We will be extending sue
the cat lady's show
"dramatic paws"
To 2 hours
instead of just one.
Based on some
very and somewhat
inexplicable ratings.
What's the matter?
An hour wasn't enough time
For her to do all
her stupid cat puns?!
Have a mice day!
Hope you're feline-ing great!
And since extending her show
will cut into the show
that comes before,
We will be cutting
"the score" with gary brooks
down to an hour.
Wait? What?!
Gary, I'm sorry.
It's purely a ratings thing.
But my show gets
really good ratings.
Yes, it does. But it's new.
And you're still building
an audience.
How am I supposed to build
an audience if you cut
my show in half?
Gary, it's nothing personal.
What do you mean
it's not personal?!
I'm your boyfriend.
We're sleeping together.
Gary!
Come on! Who here doesn't know
that these 2 are doing it?
My bad.
Yes, professor drakely.
It's just that when
I started this job,
I thought I'd be using more
of my psychology expertise
As opposed to running errands
for you.
See, I graduated
top of my class at uc irvine.
Uh huh.
Uh, yeah ok. So fong's cleaners
on santa monica?
Ok. Ready at 3.
Uh, you know what?
Yeah.
I am crushing up your
cialis pills right now.
Yeah. Ok. Bye.
Hi, mom.
Hey, honey.
How was your day
at hogie moe's?
You still thinking
about quitting?
I mean, you were right.
I just stuck with it.
And I'm having
a great time.
Hey, this kid threw out
his retainer when he dumped
his tray into the trash.
And guess who dug it out?
Me. And then my boss told me
I was a hero.
And I made a joke about
a hero sandwich,
And like 4 people laughed.
It was awesome.
Honey, that is so great.
You know it must be nice
to feel so productive.
Yeah. You know,
I'm loving being part
of the hogie family.
That's what we call it.
So, how's your job?
Actually I worked
with a particularly
interesting case today--
Borderline narcissist
who feels the need
to dominate women.
Probably due to his
repressed homosexuality.
Really? Did you help him?
Yeah. Yeah. But if my help
lasts for more than 4 hours,
He's supposed to consult
a physician.
Sasha: What are you doing?
Well, just dotting down notes
for my show.
Wow. Want to not do that
and do something else?
No, I don't think so.
I'm really not in the mood. Ok?
What do you mean you're
not in the mood?
You're always in the mood.
The other day you started
making out with me
When we were watching
"intervention."
And I never found out
if janine the ice skater
got off meth.
Uh, she didn't.
She relapsed and then her dad
killed himself.
I was in the mood then,
I'm just not in the mood now.
I'm not feeling it. Sorry.
Is this about today?
What--of course not.
No, come on.
I have work to do.
Since my show is only an hour,
I have to cut some stuff out
for time, you know.
Ha ha--that would have been
hilarious.
It's gone now.
Ha ha!
That's a classic
that no one will ever hear.
Gary, I'm sorry.
It was a business decision.
Look, your girlfriend
hates that it happened,
But your boss had to do it.
Hey, you know what?
You could have shortened
anyone's show,
And you chose to shorten mine.
I don't get it.
Why not shorten the show
with that old man that talks
about pots and pans?
Antique bob?
Do you know how much
revenue he brings in
With those adult diaper ads?
Our station depends on him.
Gary, I don't understand.
You are the one who said
we should keep work
and dating separate.
This does not seem separate.
Of course
it doesn't seem separate.
I'm so mad at my boss right now,
That I don't even want to play
with my girlfriend's boobs.
So, what? Are you saying
I should give you
special treatment
Because we're dating?
Yeah. That's awesome.
I can't do that.
Well, then I don't know
what to do.
You know, I'm afraid that what
we have is going to get ruined
Because we work together.
So, I'm going to have to choose
what's more important to me.
So, you know what?
Fine I'll choose.
Gary, that is very romantic.
But I don't think you should
quit your job over this.
What are you talking about?
What--you're choosing me,
right?
If by me you mean my job, yes.
You know what?
I think I'm going
to head home.
Ah, sasha, come on.
What am I supposed to do?
It's my dream job!
Oh, I don't expect you
to do anything.
I just hope you don't end up
regretting your decision.
What are you going to do?
Fire me?
No. No. No. That would be
letting my personal feelings
Dictate my business
decisions.
And I am a professional.
So, I will see you
at work tomorrow.
Don't forget
it's casual Friday.
Glad you could join me.
We're back from break
in like a minute.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, man.
Sasha arranged
for a chiropractor
to come in a work on us.
I got an adjustment called
a cox flexion distraction.
And at first it sounded like
something I definitely
did not want.
But now I want as much
cox flexion as I can get.
Ooh.
Can we please get to work?!
Ok. Someone's
a little uptight today, huh?
Sorry. I'm very uptight.
Sasha and I had a huge fight.
I basically had to choose
between her and work.
And you picked the job?!
Yes, I did.
Are you crazy?!
You always pick the girl!
Remember that movie
where richard gere went
back into the factory
And he picked up debra
winger and all those homely
left-behinds were clapping.
What if he hadn't?
If he hadn't,
it wouldn't be
"an officer
and a gentleman."
It would be
"an officer and
a selfish bastard."
You're on.
Hey, welcome back
to "the score"
with gary brooks.
You know there's a lot
of talk about football
dynasties, all right.
Patriots, steelers,
you know what I want to do.
I want to take it
in another direction today.
Let's talk about
the dynasties of failure.
I mean the real losers.
The detroit lions,
they gotta be at the top
of that list right away.
You also have your cleveland
browns. These poor guys,
they can't win on the road.
They can't win
when they go back to cleavage.
Cleveland.
What are you doing in here?
Oh, sorry.
I just left some paperwork.
Yeah. Even your newest
franchises in the nfl,
they win more.
You got your jacksonville
jaguars, your tennessee titans.
They're big, firm--
Ok, you know what.
Let's pause 10 seconds
for station identification.
We'll be right back
with "the score"
with gary brooks.
What the heck are you doing
in here, sasha?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
You're walking around
all sexy, that why
I mean what I mean.
Gary, since we're
in the workplace,
I would appreciate you not
referring to me as sexy.
Oops. Dropped my pen.
Curtis: Gary!
Gary! We are back
from station id.
Well, roll another one!
We're picking up pens
in here!
So, do you want you turn
with the chiropractor?
No. I want you to get out.
I'm trying to do a show here
professionally.
All right. Well, it's
my turn with rhonda anyway.
Ok. Where were we?
Ok. Welcome back
to "the score" everybody.
My name is gary brooks.
How about we take a call.
We have glenn in chula vista.
Glenn, what can
I do for ya, pal?
Yeah, hey gary, listen,
I was wondering,
What do you think
the raiders have to do
To put together a better
team for next year?
Well, I'll tell you, glenn,
if your fans are tougher
than your team,
You have a big turn on.
I'm sorry.
Did you say, turn on?
Yeah, turn on. You gotta
turn on the power, kiddo.
Oh, my god I've never seen
bodies move that way.
Are you talking about
darren mcfadden?
Yes, I am. I'm talking
about darren mcfadden and
his perfect, supple bottom.
Thank you!
Allison!
Alli, I need your help!
Gary, shh.
What?
What's going on?
Why are you in the pantry?
I thought you were tom.
Oh, no. Is it a surprise party?
Did I miss his birthday?
I didn't get him anything.
He likes olives, right?
No, look. I quit my job and
I don't want him to know.
So, when he comes home.
He's going to go upstairs.
And I'm going to come out
and pretend I just got home
from work.
Yeah. But you're in here
for no reason. He doesn't get
home for another hour.
So, you're safe. Let's go.
All right.
Car.
Oh!
There's a car.
All right.
Why'd you quit your job?
Gary, I couldn't stand it.
It was like I was
his personal assistant.
He made me do all his
grocery shopping for him,
pick up his dry cleaning.
I mean, it was like being
married to you
Except I didn't have
to watch one steven
gutenberg film.
Steven gutenberg
is an american treasure.
Ok.
Gary, listen to me.
I took off all of this time
to raise my kids
And now I have to pay
my dues all over again?
But I want to teach
tom a lesson,
So I'm hiding in the pantry
like a coward.
Tom totally respects you.
Tell him you quit your job.
He will completely understand.
Both: Aah!
Oh, jeez.
Hi, honey.
Hey, mom.
Hey, dad.
'sup.
Can I have the triskets?
Oh, yeah.
Here you go.
Thanks. You guys should come
listen to this cat lady show.
It's so interesting.
Did you know that cats
have no sense of hot and cold
in their feet?
Really? That's kind of
fascinating, actually.
I gotta go.
Antique bob comes
on in 10 minutes.
All right, come on.
Let's get out of here.
This is ridiculous.
All right.
So, hey, gary.
What did you want?
Sasha's trying to get me
to regret my incredibly
stupid decision.
But it was her stupid decision
to shorten my show
That made me make
my stupid decision.
Car!
No, it's the neighbor's,
allison!
All right.
What am I supposed
to do about sasha?
Ok. Just do
the same thing to her.
Make her regret her decision
to shorten your show.
I mean, who could fill
someone with regret
more than you?
I mean, remember me?
White dress,
flowers in hand,
Priest asking me if I would
take you as my husband.
You did not regret that.
Yeah, but you know what?
When the priest changed
the vows to
"are you double,
triple, super-duper sure
you'd want to do this?"
I should have taken it
as a sign, gary!
The only reason we were
standing there is curtis double
dog dared me to marry you!
Welcome back to
"dramatic...Paws."
I'm sue the cat lady.
Ok. We have carla
from monrovia on the line.
She's the mom of 2 sweet
little 6-month-old calicoes.
Go ahead, carla.
Um, my question is.
When I bring ginger
home from the vet,
Why does mr. Roboto
hiss at her like he's
never seen her before?
She's still at lunch?
Yeah. Yeah.
What are you doing?
Blowing up
the cat lady.
The answer to your question is
mr. Roboto hasn't
seen ginger before.
Cat's can't actually recognize
one another by sight,
Only by smell.
Isn't that interesting?
Yes, it is.
That's really interesting.
Thanks for you call.
I've got germaine from santa
monica on the air.
Germaine,
who's daddy are you?
Yeah, I don't have a cat.
But I do have a question
about the lakers.
Do you think they're better
off with ron artest
Or should they have stuck it
out with trevor ariza?
I'm sorry. I think you may be
calling into the wrong show.
This isn't [in radio voice]
"the score"
with gary brooks?
I thought that show
went 2 hours.
What is that?
Some kind of weird cat show?
I don't want
to talk about cats.
I want to talk about sports.
No. It's recently
been shortened.
That's a terrible idea
to shorten a sports show
for a cat show.
Well, I could take a stab
at answering your question.
Sure, artest struggled early,
but he's good for 16 points
and 5 boards a game.
And come playoffs time,
you're gonna want his strong
presence in the paint
To bang with bateer,
nowitzski, carmelo,
And likely king james
if they make the finals.
You just aren't going to get
that with a slasher like ariza,
Who, to bring it back
to the subject,
Plays the post
like a pussy cat. Pussy cat.
Gary, what are you doing?
I don't know.
Why don't we go
to my office?
Uh, thanks.
I love your show, sue.
Sasha, look. I'm sorry.
You shortened my show.
I freaked out. I took it out
on sue the cat lady,
Who apparently knows more about
the lakers than phil jackson.
Gary, you never had
to make a choice.
Look, I know working
together makes
dating complicated,
But I was willing
to give it a try.
So, was I. I really wanted
And then I just spazzed out.
I'm sorry.
Uh, it wasn't just you.
I wanted to show you
how wrong you were,
So I dressed sexy
And nearly crippled myself
with that split I did.
Look, could we maybe
try this again. You know what?
Let me rephrase that.
I would really like
to try this again.
So, would I.
Ok. Great.
But if we do this, we have
to sit down and hammer out
an ironclad set of rules
That we stick to
no matter what.
Ok. I agree.
Good. But first...
Let's pick up some pens.
Hey, mom.
Hi, honey.
How was work today?
Uh, great. They promoted me.
When someone orders
a special hogey de la dia--
That's what we call it--
Someone rings a bell. Ok.
You're looking at
the guy who tells the guy
to ring the bell.
So, how was work for you?
Actually, I've got something
to tell you.
I quit my job.
I just--
It wasn't what
I hoped it would be.
And I couldn't make it work.
I hope I didn't let you down.
Thank god.
Huh?
They fired me.
What?!
Oh, gosh! Why, honey?
Well, someone ordered
the special hogey de la dia.
Yeah.
And they asked if they could
have ketchup on it. Ok.
You don't put ketchup on it.
It completely offsets
the flavor,
and everyone knows that!
Yeah.
I refused to give the order
to ring the bell.
Oh, gosh, tommy. I'm sorry.
Yeah. Well, I had to hand in
my hairnet, my key to the
condiment closet--
That's why we call--
That's what they call it.
Ok.
Tommy, it's going to be ok.
The point is that we tried.
We're just going to move on
to bigger and better things.
You know, we're just gonna find
something that's better suited
to us. You know?
Yeah. Well, how about just
living off dad like we've
been doing this whole time?
Hey, if it ain't broke--
Ohh!