- zero one, wait on my scorpio.
- Zero one, copy.
Get those hands up.
your hands up. Keep your hands up!
Hang on. Here he comes.
I got the solution.
- Get down!Get down!
- No!
Don't! don't do it! Stop!
- No! Please!
- Please don't kill us! No!
2 hours earlier
Why not?
What have I got to lose?
You sound very upset.
You're damn straight I am.
Look, I hear what you're saying, okay?
Stay in control. This
is your negotiation.
What do we need to do so
that we can all go home?
You can give me what I want.
I'd like to try.
You know what I'd really like?
I'd like some coke.
How about that, huh?
You give me an ounce, this is over.
- Hello!
- I'm gonna do it. Hello!
- A little help here.
- Hello!
You hear me, but you're
not doing nothing about it.
He's a lying pig.
- I'm not a liar.
- Don't argue. Just get him back.
Okay, look, you're obviously very upset.
Yes. Yes. You know what that means?
You know I really wish a cop
would negotiate us to safety.
Come on, sam, just talk to them.
Dude, you know what I want!
- I'm not giving you cocaine, jackass.
- Bang. Bang.
Jackass? Did he say jackass?
Okay, sam, let's talk this through.
Just give me a minute, sarge.
Can't you just give me
some more time, okay?
What about A...? Just give me a week.
Okay, a couple of days
then. Just a couple...
no, fine.
Maybe I'll get it tonight.
long way from kandahar, huh?
I was doing everything right, wasn't I?
Mirroring, emotional labeling, eye messaging,
everything in the book, but I just...
need to listen.
Look, you can kick ass like nobody's
business, and you look great in the cool pants,
but as long as you're out there, and
you're trying to talk to somebody,
you've got to be able to listen,
you've got to be able to connect.
I know, okay. It's just...
how do I connect to bad guys when
I spent four years shooting 'em?
I just need to finish this review.
No, you need time.
Field training, a little patience, okay?
Remember, you got the cool pants down.
12 months ago, this bank was city central's
lowest-performing branch in the downtown quarter.
Since then, thanks to all
of you, we're at number two.
Now, before we start the new week, I'd like to
highlight the current figures... from our sales team.
Top seller, third week running...
- I'm sorry, miss geller...
- please, join your group.
Top sales figure for
rsps and mutual funds...
goes to wendy trailor.
Great work, wendy.
Let's have an excellent
week, everyone. Thank you.
paul? Paul, a word?
Miss geller, I'm really
sorry. My wife has just D...
paul, please.
You don't have to apologize for what's
happening in your personal life ever.
Thank you.
- It's been a hard week.
- But...
you can't expect your team
to pull your weight, either.
It's a question of priorities.
Figure out yours, please.
- Yes, absolutely.
- That's all.
Oh, and could someone ask
security to call the alarm company?
There was an error code
with the door this morning.
Do you know who I am?
I said, do you know who I am?
- Yes.
- Good.
Then you know what to
do. I want $500,000.
You're going to bring it back up
here, let me check it, and then I go.
- Okay.
- What did I say?
$500,000, I bring it back;
you check it, and then you go.
No dye packs.
You check it. You go. No one gets hurt.
No one gets hurt. That's right.
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
Go on.
Miss geller, is it okay if I grab the
foreign exchange file from your desk?
Uh, no.
No. Okay, well, I can ask somebody
else if you don't want me in there.
Do not go upstairs. Danger.
Robbery. Manager's office.
Robbery!
nobody move! Nobody move!
Hold it! You idiot! what did you do?
you're the big boss. You're the
big manager. Tell them to calm down.
Just calm down.
Everybody, calm down. Calm down.
- Tell 'em again!
- Calm down.
Or somebody's gonna
get hurt, you got it?
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Flashpoint
Season01 Episode05
Team one, gear up. Loud call.
Armed robbery in
progress, young and queen.
Possible hostages,
single suspect, armed.
you got anything else? Okay. Thank you.
You got a video of him yet?
No. Alarm company says someone comes
in early morning with an override code.
I'm gonna assume it's our guy.
Video and audio are all cut.
So nobody could id him when he got away.
Still, would have been kind of
hard, what with the ski mask.
- Great.
- Not great?
MO matches the monday morning
bandit. You heard of him?
Like, five jobs this
year already. That guy?
Six. We got ourselves
a big fish. Guy's a pro.
He knows managers are trained not to pull
the alarm, but just hand over the cash.
Somebody didn't get that memo.
Last one, a couple of tellers gave him some
lip, and he shot them both without blinking.
What about back ways, loading doors?
Any entrance besides the main door?
No, it's just the front doors.
The fire exit's around
the other side, but it'S...
it's all out in the open.
So, there's no way we can get
in there without him seeing us?
Okay. Okay, you figure out how to
get into the impossible building,
and I'll go talk to the
killer with nothing to lose.
If you put it that way.
Sam, you're with ed.
Jules, you're my second.
Let me be second, sarge.
Easy, cowboy. You know you can't blow
or shoot anything up in the truck, right?
I could use the field training.
So long as you're not scared
of blowing anything up.
- No.
- All right, follow me.
- yeah?
- Hello.
This is sergeant gregory parker with
the police strategic response unit.
Am I talking with the person in charge?
This is the guy you're gonna get a half
million in unmarked 50s for, and by noon.
First contact with
subject made 9:27 A.M.
Well, I hear you, but you're
the one in the bank, sir.
Look, I don't know who you
think you're dealing with.
I'm not some junkie that's
looking for his day's fix, okay?
You and I both know that once that alarm
went off, that vault went into hard lock,
and the only way you get it open now
is manual override, you know that, so...
you are gonna get me my money.
You're gonna get me my money.
You're gonna get me a car.
An open car, which you will park at
the northeast corner of young and queen,
and then sit back as me and my hostage
drive right off. Is all that clear?
You're gonna do this by noon, and if
you don't, here's what's gonna happen.
Here, tell him.
this is ruth geller.
I'm the manager of the bank.
Please do exactly as this man
says, or he'll kill us all.
That's very good. Nice job.
have we got an action plan yet?
What about the getaway car he wants?
Couldn't we just fit it with a tracker?
Yeah, we could, but he wants it at one of the
busiest intersections in this city at lunch hour.
My bet, he takes a hostage as a shield, gets within
ten feet of that car, shoots the hostage, runs.
When there's a crowd in the subway,
he'll lose us in two minutes.
This guy is smart. We got
to get to him before that.
Subway.
- You ever hear of joe sampson?
- Underground crew joe sampson?
He always used to say, the best banks
to hit were the ones by the subways.
Underground access, breakable walls.
Nobody sees a thing.
How the hell do you know joe sampson?
It takes a village.
Yeah, we've got just over two hours.
What do we do when he demands his money?
Refer to a high authority, get
concessions, try to keep him on the line.
Good. So, how do we make
a connection with this guy?
Can talk anybody out of anything
if he thinks you don't understand.
So what do you understand?
I don't know. Guy's a thief.
You take pride in your job;
so does he. Connection. Right?
But remember what the point is,
sam. It's not you. It's not him.
It's those hostages. It's
ruth skellar. She's the point.
okay, you got my money?
Okay. Now, passed on your
requests to my superiors,
but one thing that'll help us is
a sign of good faith on your part.
Yeah, this is where I'm supposed to
start turning over my hostages, I guess.
That's not going to happen.
It's nice dealing with a professional.
Six banks, six getaways. That's
something. That's planning.
Is that why you've always worked
alone? That's easier to plan.
Easier to plan, that's right, yeah.
And you're alone now, too,
right? Part of the plan.
It's like I tell my guys, you fail
the plan, you plan to fail, am I right?
Something like that.
And I respect that, but how
long can you keep doing this?
I'm just saying you know
how this usually ends, right?
Don't we all want to go home?
How the hell am I supposed to do that?
What does that even mean?
How am I supposed to do that?
Is it the last job you're worried about?
Shooting the tellers,
what was it 14, 15 times?
That says to me that
something went very wrong.
Something that you
didn't want to do, right?
Yeah, that's right.
That's nothing I wanted.
Yeah, doesn't sound like you.
But it is me. All right.
That's me and I don't get what I want.
And I advise you to remember that.
Just remember it.
- Catch the remorse about the shooting?
- Yeah.
Yep. Not the typical antisocial profile.
Check this with the holdup squad.
Hey, eddie, how are we doing
with our delivered action plan?
Heading underground now, boss.
Excuse me.
What do you want?
People need to go to the bathroom.
So?
So...
so I assume you don't want these
people dirtying themselves on the floor.
And why would I care?
Because it's just going to make
them more afraid, and on edge.
I'm just trying to make
this easier for everybody...
you want to make things easier,
sit down and shut up. Sit down.
We're in the tunnel under the subway.
Jules, distraction on my go.
Jules, where are we?
Good to go. Team?
Checking wall thickness.
okay, I told you noon.
We're still working on everything.
I just wanted to warn
you about something.
The manual alarm, when it was
tripped, it automatically reset,
so in about a minute
it's going to go off again
and I just need you to stay
calm when that happens.Okay?
That's all I wanted to say.
Get back.
- Ready, jules?
- Ready when you are.
Five, four, three, two...
calm down!
We're in. Basement's ours.
Thanks. Will do.
Nice catch.
Littler fish.
Team, listen up.
Subject is not who we thought.
Monday morning bandits' murders
were execution-style, two bullets.
But the story the press got was a
bloodbath-- multiple shots fired.
The subject does not
contradict the press version.
That's all he knew. So, we
have no idea who this guy is.
We're moving up.
- Excuse me...
- What?
This woman has asthma.
She needs her medication.
So what?
I'm doing my part to keep these
people calm. Can't you do yours?
Want to tell me how to do my
job? Is that what you want to do?
No, I... yeah, go ahead.
- Oh, my god.
- Tell me.
You sit down! Sit down,
sit down now! Sit down you!
boss, subject's gone active.
We're moving in. We're east...
police! Police!
Everybody out! Move to the front!
Police! Get these people out of here.
Move! Move! Out of the way.
Right there. Right there.
Set the gun down. Set the gun down.
Put your gun down!
Set the gun down. We're
not going anywhere.
I'm telling you, get out of the bank!
Sir, put the gun down now!
Get out or I kill
her! I tell you I will.
- We're not leaving.
- Well, then she dies. Three...
- please.
- And in two...
and in one...
team one, we're coming out.
- Subject still has a hostage.
- Go!
Lock the door.
Hurry up! Come on, come on.
oh, god!
George!
****connect the video,
but there's no audio.
Here we go.
And freeze it there.
Get the security guy.
Can we get the security
guard in here, please?
Look at them. They're just... she's just
looking at him like they know each other.
Yeah.
Hey, buddy. This guy ring any bells?
- That's george.
- Who's george?
George orston. Head of security
here at the bank. He was my boss.
Was until when?
Uh, till about two months
ago. When she fired him.
10:58, subject's employee record,
delivered by constable lewis young.
Been at the bank since '81.
Head of security for the past ten years.
He's no career criminal.
We need a new strategy.
Initiate stockholm?
Hey, doc, thanks for coming. We've got
a disgruntled employee. Any thoughts?
I had four of those
cases in the last month.
Okay, you need to look for inadequate
personalities, substance abuse.
Appeal to shared experience,
validate his emotional reality.
I hear you. Losing your
job, I'd be pissed, too.
Let him know we've id'd him,
we lose tactical advantage.
Yeah, but I gain
intimacy. I gain a name.
Yeah, but it's going to be hard to calm him
down when he knows there's a camera on hiM.
Going to need a cover story.
Right, noted.
Hey, guys. What do we
have on his hostage?
Miss trailor, you want to tell sergeant
parker here what you just told us.
Look, what george is doing--
I'm not saying it's right--
but ruth skellar came
in around a year ago.
Corporate clean-up.
We were in trouble, and
she turned us around.
But a lot of people lost their jobs.
And those of us that stayed, half
of us are losing our families.
My wife had a baby a week ago.
I barely see either of them, but it's
not like skellar cares. Woman's a robot.
I'm just saying if I was her, I wouldn't want
to be alone with a former employee who was armed.
Please, george.
Shut up! I don't want to hear one
word out of you, you understand?
Not a peep.
Subject's still got a clear view
of the bank from that hallway.
I don't see us pulling
the entry trick again.
I still think you should
try initiating stockholm.
According to the manual, a subject with
a hostage is an object of anger or scorn.
His negotiator should attempt to...
humanize the hostage to the hostage
taker. I know the manual, okay?
Once this guy knows he lost his cover,
he'll be thinking his life is over.
And he's holed up with the
woman that made it happen.
So my goal is getting him to
think about anything but her, okay?
- boss,
- I just...
boss, when you talk this guy out, you're
going to have the white covered already.
I want to put snipers
on red just in case.
We need a side solution. Why don't
braddock and I take zero one and two?
Okay, do it.
- yeah?
- Is this george orston?
I'll take that as a yes.
A colleague identified
your voice, george, so...
can we talk straight?
First of all, this is a big relief.
We thought you were a pretty bad guy.
But now that I've seen your file,
I think you're a guy who got kicked to
the curb and now wants a little payback.
I don't think you want to hurt anybody.
Don't tell me what I want.
You know exactly what I want.
It's exactly the mey fore.
And now, I know I can't trust you.
I want you to trust me, george.
Yeah, well, then, you shouldn't have sent
in the cavalry, then, should you have?
You know what?
I was going to give you just
less than an hour from here,
but now, after what you've done,
that's going to be a half an hour.
You don't give me what
I want in one-half hour,
I'm going to shoot her right here.
Get his focus off her, onto you.
George, listen to me,
I'll do everything I can,
but a half hour is not a lot of
time to get you that kind of cash.
Cash? What am I going to do with cash?
Oh, this is... this is what you're
going to do. Okay, you're going to...
you're going to transfer
that money right in this bank.
I got an account number for you.
Mark it down. I won't
say it again. 0-6...
uh, what is it?
9-8-1-0-9.
Okay?
And then, I'll get the boss lady
here to take me over to a computer,
and she's going to verify for me whether that
money is received within the next half hour.
And if it isn't, I'm going
to put a bullet in her head.
Okay, and don't make the mistake of
thinking that won't be easy for me to do.
It'll be very easy after
what she's done to me.
- Hey, boss, arriving in position.
- Copy.
Hey, spike, I need an id
on a bank account: 0698109.
Copy.
Okay, joe, just forget about her.
Let's talk about you
and why you're here.
Why I'm here is because
of what she's done to me!
That's why we're here.
- It wasn't personal.
- What'd you say?
- Hey, george, just stay with me.
- Shut up.
Come on, george. She can't help you.
I'm the guy who can
give you what you want.
No, I want her... i want her to tell me.
Pretty please?
I want her to tell me how 20 years of a
man's life ended up worth practically nothing.
You tell me how a man works, doesn't
put a foot wrong his whole life,
and then at the end,
you hand him a check,
and it's worth like one week's
salary for every year worked.
What am I suppose to do with
all that money, buy myself a car?
Is that what I'm supposed to do?
Would you mind explaining to me
how you come with that figure?
How did you come up with that number?
It's a standard
termination package, george.
It wasn't personal.
Oh, you're missing all the comedy. It
wasn't personal. That's what she says.
It wasn't personal?
Come on, george, come on. You gotta
know this is hard for her, same as you.
I doubt that very much.
Ruth has done everything right her whole
life, lived for her job, just like you.
You loved your job, too, am I right?
I gotta go.
You know what, this is
looking kind of bad for you...
boss lady.
Are you buddies ?
Georges I don't know if I'd say buddies.
Pretty private guy,
george, but a good boss.
Always made sure I was doing okay.
He's a regular guy, good guy.
What about family? Ever met them?
Other than mary?
Who's mary?
His wife.
See, that's why I don't get this.
The day he got canned, all he said was,
"well, now I can spend more time with mary."
No kids, as far as I know. He
just pretty much lived for her.
Did you ever meet her?
Sure, yeah, she was always
by for lunches and stuff.
Uh, well, not now, but...
what, since he was fired?
No, I mean the last year or so, actually,
but before then, yeah, all the time.
- All right, thanks.
- Thank you.
How'd you get in just like that?
Technical genius.
Bank gave me the pass codes.
Okay, last step, the password.
"Hotstuff": One word, no space.
What?
What kind of account is this?
Looks like a straight payment account.
You put money in, the holder withdraws.
This one's for... there.
Saint ignatius homes, limited.
Whatever that is.
So you planned all this just
from watching security tapes?
George: Yeah, that's right.
All the banks showed them.
They wanted us all to see the guy's mo.
You know what I used to do? Make notes.
- That's pretty good notes.
- Thank you.
Hey, george, is there anybody you want
us to get a message to, anybody at all?
Look, I know what
you're doing, all right?
We're wasting enough time right here.
You got, like, less than 20
minutes left. Give me my money.
I know, we're still working on it.
We just need you to stay calm, okay?
That's easy for you to stay.
You've got a life to go back to at
the end of this-- what have I got?
Well, to tell you the truth, it's not
like you've told me a lot about yourself.
Well, what's there to tell?
And who cares anyway?
You think this one sitting
beside me thinks she cares?
The account's for a
retirement home downtown.
I can go right now and get
the answers faster in person.
Okay, drive fast.
You want someone like her
thinks of someone like me?
Whoa, george, where'd you go?
Don't go back down that road.
Come on, buddy, you were going
to tell me about yourself.
I'm a line item on a
budget, and that's about it.
I'm george orston, $47,000
a year, plus benefits.
Hey, wait, the way I figure
it, you get some kid in here,
pay him half that, and no
benefits 'cause he's part-time.
Hey, where do I sign?
I can't get there fast enough.
You think I like firing people?
- You think I enjoy it?
- Yeah.
George, she's having a hard time.
She can't help you. You stay with me.
I'm the guy who can get
you out of this, okay?
Yeah, right, yeah, 'cause I'm A...
I'm the boss bitch.
I'm the ice queen.
Oh, you think I didn't know the
nicknames, hear the whispers?
I am the first one in every day
and the last one out, so I know.
Good for you.
But a year ago, they were going
to close this branch, george,
and 62 people were
going to lose their jobs.
Sixty-two.
I came in, and I worked
everyone hard, yes.
And I worked harder than i
ever have in my entire life.
And in the end...
it still wasn't enough. It just wasn'T.
Seven people had to go.
Those were the numbers.
Not 62. Seven.
And I am sorry that you
were one of the seven.
I really am, george.
George, george, can you hear me?
We can talk about all of this.
Talking's through--
no more talking.
No more talking.
Where are you going,
george? Where are you going?
What are you doing, george?
put your hands out.
Put your palms together.
Don't do that, george.
Team one, stand by for immediate action.
What's going on, boss?
Just stay ready.
Lean forward.
He's gagging his hostage.
He's dehumanizing her, so when
the me comes, he can kill her.
You don't want to kill her, george.
You don't want to kill her. Stand by.
- Wind's at 1:00.
- More like 3:00 now.
Flag down the street
in front of the park.
Nice.
Thank you, sir.
Is there a problem, braddock?
I was right, you know,
about the proper procedure.
Well, that's the lead
negotiator's call to make.
But I was right. Manual's clear.
You know the boss wrote the manual?
It's tough not being the
best at something, huh?
I'm trying.
It's not something you
can get out of a textbook.
You've got to learn how to make the...
I know, I know. I gotta connect.
Sarge says it every time.
Then, how come you don't hear it?
parker.
It's luria.
You at the retirement home?
George's wife has alzheimer'S.
Oh, that's great.
Diagnosis was six months ago.
Early onset usually means
rapid decompensation.
She's in pretty bad shape.
But now, there's another problem.
They're going to kick her out.
She doesn't have the money.
Thanks, doc.
so, what's going on? Where's my money?
What I got is two names.
First name is george orston.
Ha-working guy, has done everything right
his whole life, married 25 years to...
here's the second name: Mary orston.
A hairdresser, or she used to be.
Right now, she's not doing so well.
In a few years, she might not
be able to do anything at all.
And the kind of place that she
needs to be in doesn't come cheap.
That sound right, george?
You tell me, parker, does
that sound all right to you?
- No.
No, it doesn't sound right.
Doesn't sound right that you lose your job and your
insurance a month after you find a home for her.
You work hard your whole life, and
something like alzheimer's comes along,
and suddenly, the most important person to you
can't even remember your name; that's not right.
No.
Neither is what you're doing,
george, and you know that.
I know.
Look, I tried, parker. I've tried. I've tried
to look for another job, look for anything.
It ain't happening, okay?
I've looked to try and get a loan.
But what am I supposed to do at my age?
It's not exactly easy
out there to find a job.
And then, let's be realistic about it.
How am I supposed to pay
anybody back? It's stupid.
Okay, so that's it. I'm
at my wit's end right here.
This is my last chance.
I know you're feeling really
alone right now, george, but...
being alone, that's not
what's scaring me here.
I'll tell you what's scaring me is
my wife gets kicked out of that home,
and I'm not in a position where
I c-can take care of her anymore.
That's what's scaring me, okay?
This woman here, my wife has
always taken good care of me always.
That's the least I can do.
I got to take care of her.
I'M... I'm just trying
to do what's right.
There isn't anybody in the world
who wouldn't understand that.
I'll bet you ruth's family
would understand that.
okay.
Parker, look, I'll tell you what.
Let me talk, let me talk
to my wife and I'll just...
I'll end this, okay? It'll be over.
What do you mean "over," george?
What I mean is if you
let me talk to my wife,
I'll come out and I'll bring
miss skellar with me, okay?
Just let me talk to my wife.
All right, george, i'll
get her. You hold on.
luria.
So he's ready to come out
once he talks to his wife.
Now, if I let him do it,
he'll probably kill himself.
If I don't, he'll go off,
and I risk losing the hostage.
Hard call.
- Put her on the phone.
- Okay.
Here, mary.
go ahead.
Mary?
Hello?
It's me. It's george.
H-how are you, how are
you feeling, pretty girl?
Where are you?
Oh, I'm just around the
corner. I'm really close by.
So tell me how you're doing.
Tell me how was your day.
All right, I think.
- George.
- Yeah?
Did I do something wrong?
You what? What are you talking about?
It's just... you're not here.
Did I do something to make you go away?
Is that why I'm alone?
Mary orston, I just want
you to know one thing, okay?
That anything that ever went right
in my life is directly due to you.
Now, do you understand me?
Hey, mary.
Just want to tell you something.
I'm real, real sorry.
What for?
I got to go now, mary.
- Okay.
I love you, george.
me, too, pretty girl.
okay, give me your hands.
Careful.
okay, so go. You hear me? Get
going. Get out of here. GO.
What are you gonna do?
Just go. What do you care?
I'm not leaving here
without you, george.
What are you talking about? Why?
- Because I didn't help you before.
- What?
And I can now.
I know if we sit down together, we
can figure something out for your wife.
Figure something out. What are you
talking about, figure something out?
There's nothing to figure out; I've tried
everything. There's nothing to figure out.
There's always something we can look at.
We'll look at early pension
payout options, insurance.
We'll see what the bank can do.
That's pretty nice of you.
- You mean it?
- Yeah.
Okay. Thanks.
Why are you doing that?
Why am I doing this?
I don't want mary to see me coming out.
- Keep your hands up when you're in front of the bank, okay?
- Okay.
Team one, sierra one.
I think he's coming out. Get ready.
That's great. Congratulations.
Negative. Not good.
He said good-bye to his wife
and put his mask back on.
He's coming out armed,
ed. Do you understand?
Loss of a loved one-- that
depersonalizes him and us.
He's looking for direct
confrontation. He wants us to kill him.
Suicide by cop. Hold fire!
Suicide by cop.
Sierra one, wait on my scorpio.
Sierra one, copy.
Shouldn't he give a scorpio now,
in case this guy comes out shooting?
It's his call. He's got one
more chance to talk the guy down.
And if he can't?
We do our job.
Get those hands up.
Hands up! Keep your hands up!
Hang on. Here he comes.
Okay, now see, you're gonna go
down and you're gonna stay down,
'cause they're gonna
shoot me, eh, so get down.
- Get down.
- No.
- Get down!
Don't! Stop! George.
Hold fire. Hold fire.
- I got the solution.
- Wait.
George, this isn't right.
You're trying to make us do
something we don't want to do.
hold fire. He's no killer. Hold fire.
Not gonna do it, george.
Not gonna give you what you want.
Put the gun down.
please, george.
- Take him.
- No.
mary, I-I didn'T...
I didn't know george maybe
as well as I could have.
But I do know how much he loved you.
And he made sure that you'll be
taken care of for as long as you need.
That was very important to him.
Why are you so sad?
It's a, it's a beautiful day.
Yeah, it is.
how you doing?
I don't know.
I've never been questioned
like that before.
Well, it's procedure.
Luria told you what it was about, right?
Yeah, guy's insurance
wouldn't cover suicide,
but it paid out if he was
killed by a third party.
Lucky me, right?
Guys seen parker?
Don't know where he is.
Look, we're gonna get changed.
Let's grab a drink. You earned it.
Hey, sarge.
- You okay?
- Yeah. You?
- Sure.
- Yeah?
- Review?
- Yeah.
Just trying to figure out
where I lost the connection.
Didn't think you did.
Well, guy's dead.
Kept ruth skellar alive, though.
Do you want another
pair of eyes on this?
No, no, I'M... I'm fine. Thanks.
But, you know, if you want...
first contact with
subject made 9:27 A.M.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚