If you want to get out of here alive,
then you're going to tell
me what happened in New York.
Spike,what's going on? I need
eyes in.Get up there with Jules.
What do you want me to say?
I will know the truth when I hear it.
Alpha One and Two,requesting
permission to enter,sir.
We go through the skylight, we'll
spook her. She might use the knife.
What have I done?What have I done?
Boss,I can see this. You're not
seeing it. Sam's not seeing it.
I can see it. We can be in
there within three seconds.
We'll disarm her. The knife is
down. Repeat: the knife is down.
We got to go in,boss. We got to risk it.
- *******
- Go,go,go,go!
3 hours earlier
Do******************
Just********
**********
*******
She*********
Just***********
I'm*****
No********
Maybe************
We**********
Must*************
Maybe**********
***************
I'm************
Look********************
- It's************
- No.No.
- So**********
- No.*************
We**************
Sara*********
9************
*********
But**************
Yeah******************
Last month, we sat
here in this same spot,
and I told you that your
chances were very,very slim,
and that I did not think that you
should go forward with another treatment.
I'm sorry to be so blunt,
but in good conscience,
I can't recommend that
you spend another $15,000.
Okay,all clear.
Not that I don't appreciate a little
excitement, but come on,I think we're safe.
You mind if I don't gamble
my career on what you think?
Unless one of your neighbors works
for the SRU, it's not much of a gamble.
Now,headquarters, that's another story.
I trust you have an entry plan.
Affirmative. I'm gonna drop
you off a few blocks away,
park my vehicle at HQ,
enter through the front.
You're gonna wait a few minutes,
stealth through the rear.
- I was kidding.
- Yeah,I'm not.
Sarah,when you get home, can you see
if I left my phone on the counter?
We're not giving up,right? We're not...
Oh,for God's sake,Sarah,we...
- we're not doing it again.
- Why?
We're not doing it again. I'm sorry.
I-I can't get back on
this roller coaster.
I can't keep feeling like every month is
some sort of test that we have to pass...
You know that's not true.
What else do you want to throw away,hmm?
I mean,what else gets thrown out the window
just in case maybe this time we're lucky.
What are you talking about,Josh?
Everything that we save, sweetheart.
Everything,everything that we hoped for.
You're the one giving up on our hope.
You threw away your work...
which you were damn good at.
And we agreed. We made
that decision together.
- Okay.
- We agreed that that was the right thing to do.
Because you wanted to relax.
You wanted to relax and read catalogs and dream
of babies in a house that we can't pay for anymore.
I never said I wanted that
house. I don't need a big house.
We'll move. We'll get a smaller house.
All our friends who have babies
you don't want to see anymore.
That's not true.
You can't go outside because you're scared
you're gonna see another frickin' stroller.
I went outside yesterday.
- Y-You went outside
yesterday? - Yes.
I've held your hand...
I've stayed up with you at
night. I've dreamed with you.
I've given up a lot that I care about.
I mean,I've done... everything
that I can do, but I-I...
I-I can't do this anymore.
You can't do what?
You know what? I-I should... I'm
gonna go to work. I have to go to work.
- What are you saying?
- I have to go.
- Josh!
- Sarah.
Josh! G... Josh.
What are you saying?
********She keeps putting
my pants in the dryer.
Hold up. Hold up. Your mom
still does your laundry?
Hey,she's Italian,okay?
Try and stop her.
Gentlemen.
Missed you at choir
practice last night,man.
That's another round you owe
the boys. Don't let that add up.
You know what? I lay down for 20 minutes,
I opened my eyes, suddenly it was 6:00 a.m.
I hate when that happens.
Samtastic sleeping alone.
What's this world coming to?
Ed,we patrolling today?
All right,listen up. The El
Colera gang has three strongholds.
We are gonna split up and cover 'em all.
Boss wants us out in
five, so let's go,ladies.
Oh,he's not home! He's not home!
AM********
Oh,no. No.
WHAT**********
ME******
YESTERDAY********
AM*******
So,you want to cook tonight?
Try your new barbecue?
Relax. We're off.
- How did it go with the guys this morning?
- Fine. Don't worry.
Anyway,who cares whate do?
Uh,the sarge,the chief,
the commander. The rules.
- All right,but the thing is...
- Yeah,yeah,yeah.
It's nobody's business.
We're professionals.
Absolutely. You are
utterly professional.
Me,I'm just here for
the sexy sniper chicks.
You doing okay?
Yeah. Yeah,I'm good. I'm good.
'Cause,uh,the other
day at the station...
Oh,come on. Here we go.
- What?
- Look,I'm just saying.
You look through the scope, and
you see things that aren't there.
Maybe you need a break from the action.
When was the last
time you had a day off?
I don't need a day off.
Hey,we could all use a day off,Ed.
All right, thanks,Oprah. I forgot
what a joy it was to ride with you.
Hello.
- Mrs. Scott?
- You must be Hannah.
I'm,um... I write for... Wired
Magazine. I'm here to see Joshua?
Of course. Come in.
- If this is a-a bad time,I
could... - No. No,it's a good time.
Please,come in. Sit down.
You have a lovely home.
Thank you.
Would you,uh... Would you like some tea?
Sure. Thank you.
He's,um... He's at work a-actually.
I'm sorry. I thought he was here.
I-I wanted to talk to you.
I'm s... Youtexted me?
I want to know about you and-and him.
How do you mean?
I think you know what I mean.
Do you know what? I'm gonna go. I'm
sorry that I... that I bothered you.
- Please don't.
- Excuse me.
- I-I have
to... - Don't go.
- You let me go!
- Not until you tell me the truth.
Look,I just... I just
want... I just want the truth.
Okay.
So you stay until we talk. Okay?
All right. Okay,we can talk.
- I'm calling the police!
- Don't. No,don't!
Put it down! Just stay...
Just stay away from me.
No. No,don't do that.
- Oh,my God. Help me.
- Put that down!
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Flashpoint
Season02 Episode02
Team One,gear up. Hot call.
Possible home invasion,
16 Lakerock Crescent.
We're real close. Boss?
Kira,what did 54 Division give us?
911 came in ten minutes
ago. Dispatch flagged it.
There's been a wave of violent
home invasions in the neighborhood.
Underground Boys?
Same grid. Copy that.
Four in the last two weeks, and all
four came through the basement windows.
Last week,they found some woman at
home,tied her up and robbed the place.
Kira,play the 911,would ya?
Here it comes.
Oh,my God! Help me,please!
Help me,please! Help!
Put that down!
How far are you guys?
Three minutes.
Okay,don't approach without
cover. They could be expecting us.
Get some intel. Hold off on
entry until we go in as a team.
Got it.
No signs of forced entry
on black or white wall.
Okay. No broken basement windows?
That's a negative.
Maybe the Underground
Boys are trying a new MO.
Could be something else. Who knows?
Sarah and Josh Scott. She's an
illustrator. Works from home.
He runs a software design company.
Neighbor saw them leave together early this
morning, but she returned home alone around 9:15.
That doesn't sound
like a domestic,does it?
Unless the guy came back and walked in on the
wife doing something she didn't want him to see.
Or she opened the door
to the intruders herself.
Sam,let's move forward on this.
Make contact,but go careful.
Yes,sir.
Jules,I'm dialing in.
Kira,can you patch me through
to the source of the 911?
Come on.
This is Sam Braddock from the
Police Strategic Response Unit.
We're here to resolve the situation, but
we can't help unless you pick up the phone.
We got movement on white Alpha Two.
Throw phone?
Okay,team, it's not a domestic.
The husband was at work,
and he's on his way.
Boss,we're thinking about a throw phone.
If they pick it up, it
will limit their movements.
If they don't,we'll have
the open mike on our side.
All right,copy that.
Here's something weird. I just
talked to the alarm company.
The alarm hasn't been triggered today,
and it was armed a few minutes ago.
So,what,the intruders come in
and then she sets the alarm?
How does that work?
If someone's pointing a gun at you and they
tell you to punch in the code,you'd do it.
How far are we?
Two minutes out.
Please step away from your window.
We are throwing a phone into the house.
The window's going to break.
What the hell was that?
Please,please answer!
- Please talk to them!
- Shut up!
Shut up! You don't get
to tell me what to do!
Don't tell me what to do!
This is Sam Braddock from the
Police Strategic Response Unit.
Get away from my house!
This is Sarah?
Get down and stay down! Stay down!
- Don't... don't move!
- Okay!
I just... I-I just want the truth!
- Sarah!
- Don't!
Sarah!
Just tell me the truth!
Sarge,we lost the ear. She threw
the phone out. It's escalating.
Okay,we have a hostage
situation with an unknown weapon.
Talk is number one.
But be ready with an immediate
action if the hostage is threatened.
Spike,you're less lethal.
Jules,you're Sierra One.
Let's set up the LADD. Number
one on white, number two on black.
At least we can keep listening.
Copy that.
Sam,I want you to say on the loudhailer.
Be persistent with no pressure.
You're not taking over?
- Negative.
- Copy that.
Sarah,I'd really like to know...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I need to make sure
everyone's okay in there,Sarah.
Ed,I'm gonna run tactics.
You and Lou run Command Post.
Wha... Command Post?
Oprah says.
Yes,sir.
Let's get a list of all the
license plates parked nearby.
- What?
- You... in the truck.
What can I tell you?
It's backwards day.
- Let me through. Get out of my way.
- Sir...
Get out of my way. My wife's
in there. Let me through.
Sarah! Let go of me!
Joshua Scott. Mr. Scott.
Thank you,Constable.
What are you doing?
We can't let you come any closer.
My wife is in there. She's
in danger. What are you doing?
Sir,we're not sure it was your
wife that placed the 911 call.
What do you mean?
We believe your wife is holding
someone in there against their will.
Sarah?
No,Sarah would never do that.
Sir,are there any firearms in the house?
No,there's no firearms in the house.
Stand back,sir,please.
Team,husband claims there
are no guns in the house.
We might be looking at a
knife, scissors, razor blade.
Look,she would just never do that.
- Sir,I can't have you do that. You need to step back.
- Okay,okay.
Now I need you to help me.
I need you to help me
with some answers,okay?
What can you tell me about
her state of mind this morning?
She was upset. We had
a fight,an argument.
Your wife isn there with an
unknown weapon and a hostage,
and we don't want to
make her more upset,okay?
I don't think it's a good idea if she
sees you through the window right now.
- Okay.
- You got to trust me on this. This is what we do.
Okay.
Okay,I want you to come into the truck over
here. Talk to my guys, tell 'em what you know.
******Unknown weapon.
*******Sarah Scott.
Unidentified hostage.
Sergeant Parker to direct tactical plan.
How you doing? I'm Ed Lane. Louis Young.
Have a seat, please,Josh.
You texted him twice this morning.
It's professional. I told you.
You're lying.
What about "Yesterday was amazing"?
Any movement?
No,but I definitely scared
them away from the windows.
A little aggressive,huh?
You're doing good.
Okay.
Move as soon as we
got a position on 'em.
Copy.
Gordy,we got ears yet?
Getting an audio signal.
- Please!
- Tell me the truth!
If we could just go outside,please?
You can just talk to your husband.
Please,let me talk to my wife.
Josh,we can't right now. We can't.
Spike's on Less Lethal.
Boss gonna need you with the gas.
What do you mean,"lethal"?
Josh,Plan A is less lethal.
Less lethal?
Rubber bullets.
How can you be less dead?
We dislodge the weapon,
restrain the subject.
This is insane.
You have all this hardware for
an upset woman with maybe a knife.
Knife's as bad as a gun.
It never sticks,never jams, never runs out of ammo
and you don't need traing to know how to use it.
So just sit down and calm yourself.
Please,please, I'm so scared! Please?
I've got eyes. Female hostage.
Knife confirmed. Threat imminent.
- Spike,stand by.
- Copy.
On my go.
Please don't hurt me! I'm pregnant!
She's pregnant. Hostage is pregnant.
Stand down! Stand down. Stand
down. We got a pregnant hostage.
You...
you're having his baby?
No.
You're having his baby.
Your having his...
I knew it. I knew that there
was a reason that,that...
why he'd given up. It was you.
Please,you're not making sense.
You're coming with me.
- Please,you need to talk to someone.
- Get up!
Okay,team,new rules: No Taser,no
CS gas and no rubber bullets.
Not a lot of tools in the toolkit.
Gordy,we hear anything yet?
Yeah,it's not clear.
Please! Please!
Go up the stairs.
- They're wrestling.
- Spike?
I've lost them. I've lost visual.
Boss,let me send in
some gas, clear them out.
Negative. She's pregnant.
We got to go in,boss. We got to risk it.
No!
Enough!
Please watch out for the baby!
Enough,enough. Enough. Enough.
Please,please don't hurt the baby.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Come on. Let's go. Upstairs.
I need to show you something.
So you have no idea who this woman is?
No.
Your wife thinks you're
having an affair with her,Josh.
I am,I am not having an affair.
You understand the risk
you're taking if you lie to me?
I love my wife.
We had a tough time, but I love my wife.
I understand that, but what I don't
understand is who she has in that room with her
and why she has a knife to her throat.
Mr. Scott, we need you to draw
a floor plan of your house.
Both floors,Josh.
Every door-- which way
it opens and every window.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Eddie,Eddie,what's he saying?
That he's not involved with anyone.
- You believe him?
- No.
Okay,she says she wants
the truth,and so do I.
He was saying they were having a fight
this morning, talking about having a baby.
Let's see how that escalated before
this knife starts swinging again.
Lou,I want you to patch
me in on this conversation.
I want Sam and I to hear it.
Copy that.
Sarah,it's Sam.
I'm trying to phone
again. Please pick up.
Did he tell you about this?
What?
About the eight years?
I don't know. I don't
know what you're saying.
Shut up! Over there. Get over there.
Sit down!
I interviewed him for the conference
in New York forWiredmagazine.
We had tea.
That's what I meant by
"yesterday was amazing."
- You're lying.
- The interview... The interview was amazing.
Sarah,I need you to come to the phone
so we can talk about your safety.
- What did you just do?
- Nothing.
We've been trying to have
a baby for eight years.
Eight years of hormone
shots, IVF treatments.
We took out loans. We
drained the accounts.
It looks like we can afford it,right?
But we couldn't.
A year ago we get pregnant, finally.
But we didn't want to tell anyone
because we wanted to be sure.
So we waited-- one
month,two months,three...
At four months,we made this...
we made this room for the baby.
We let ourselves believe.
We told everyone.
And we lost it.
How'd she handle it?
She fought back. She's a fighter.
I didn't want to give up.
For him.
He should be a father.
Is she delusional? Mentally unstable?
No. No,I mean she...
she was depressed for a
while, but she's not deluded.
Then tell me why she thinks you're having
an affair with a total stranger,Josh?
Boss,we're picking up
some kind of audio signal.
What kind of audio signal?
From the house, intercom maybe.
Patch it in.
- Josh,you guys have an intercom at your house?
- No.
Walkie-talkies, anything?
We're picking up voices here.
I mean,we have a baby
monitor, but it wouldn't be on.
Where?
- In the nursery.
- What floor?
It's on the second
floor, front of the house.
Can you get it any clearer,Lou?
I'm working on it.
Okay,team, we know we're not welcome
here, so let's go stealth, low and slow.
Spike and Wordy, I want
you on entry with me. Jules.
My cousin has a baby monitor.
It's a two-way, so the kid can
hear the parents. It's worth a try.
Okay,try to tap into that frequency.
Sam,she's not going
to answer that phone.
We'll try this way in.
Jules,I want you to find a
scorpio position on the roof.
I think I saw a skylight
up there. That'll be Plan B.
And bring a camera pole.
I just need to get through this without
you trying something again. Okay?
Okay,we got ears, and we're
good to talk anytime you say,Sam.
Channel 4.
Good work,Lou. I'm gonna need you on
entry with me, and get the husband's keys.
If you want to get out of here alive,
then you're going to tell
me what happened in New York.
You're going to tell me
why you were there with him.
What happened after tea?
Nothing.
What was so amazing then,hmm?
What do you want me to say?
Huh,what do you want?
I lose either way,right?
What kind of answer do you expect when
you wave a knife in someone's face?
I will know the truth when I hear it.
You're not going to like the truth.
Go,Kira.
License plates coming at you.
All right, let's see what we got.
Josh,you recognize any of these?
Hannah Murray.
Oh,my God.
She rented a car that's parked
down the street. You know her?
She's a reporter from New York.
How do you know her?
Why would she... I
haven't seen her since...
Since when, Josh,since when?
Are you telling me that you
had a thing with this woman?
We got to know,buddy, 'cause if
you did, that changes everything.
I did.
I've known Josh for 18 years.
Before Sarah, we were
friends,really close,
but never more than friends.
From the first moment we met, we
had a connection, you know,like...
a really strong connection like...
the ones you can't really explain.
And we lost touch, and then one
day, I'm in New York in a conference,
and we bump into each other and sh...
she asked me if she could interview me.
Then I'm talking to him face
to face after all these years,
and it's like no time has passed.
Sarah and I were in
this really bad place.
I mean,I don't want blame it
on fertility treatments,but...
He said somewhere in there it was like you two
stopped having anything to say to each other.
Every conversation was about:
when's the next doctor's appointment,
what are the odds, how,how are we going
to afford to pay for the next treatment?
And,you know,I-I don't want to
sound like I'm making excuses.
I-I don't want to make ex... oh,my God.
Josh was still Josh, but he'd changed.
I could see that.
He was sadder, like the life
had gone out of him. like...
like he'd forgotten how to laugh.
And you,you laughed.
Afterwards, I'm lying next to her,
and all I can think about is Sarah,
and I'm thinking to
myself, "What have I done?"
Spike,what's going on? I need eyes in.
Barricaded?
Sarah saw my father through
three rounds of chemo.
You know, she was there in the
hospital with me when my father died.
Oh,my God.
That one night was the
biggest mistake of my life.
It was the night that was always
meant to be. It was just 15 years late.
That night...
Oh,my God, he came alive again.
All right,I'm in position.
No joy yet-- I'm going
to try the camera pole.
Spike, get up there with Jules.
Sam,Sam, this is our last chance.
Unless you got something to go on, I got
to send Jules in on an explosive entry.
No,hold on the entry. Patch me into
the room. Let me give it a shot.
I couldn't tell Sarah,
I just... I couldn't.
You know,and when I got back, when I got
back,every time I looked at her, I just...
I loved her more, and I was so
scared that I was going to lose her,
you know,and that just,
that just changed everything.
It changed everything.
What have I done? What have I done?
Josh,you told us the truth.
You did the right thing.
***********
Yeah.
It's on channel 4.
- The baby...
- Yeah.
Is Josh the father?
Sarah? It's Sam,Sarah.
We were able to open a frequency
on that monitor in your room.
They're talking about
sending a team in there.
I don't want to send anyone in.
I want you to come out,Sarah.
Oh,God...
It's you.
That's why he gave up so easily.
'Cause...
he wants to be with you.
And the baby.
Sarah,please,I need you to listen to me.
You know what he promised me?
He promised me...
no matter what, through thick
and thin, we'd be together.
Is that what she's saying?
That's what she's saying?
And I don't think any
of that's changed,Sarah.
No,no,no.
No,because when he got back
from New York, he was changed.
He was different.
Like he was trying too hard.
when the doctor told us to stop
trying, I couldn't stop crying.
He didn't cry. Not once.
Tell her I did. I...
I just... it was just...
just never in front of her, 'cause I
wanted to be strong for her,I wanted...
I wanted to be strong for...
Look,just t-tell her I'm here.
Tell her that I... that I love her.
T-Tell her about the Bridge of Sighs.
Tell her about the Bridge of Sighs.
Boss,you get that entry option
lined up, you've got to go for it.
No,Ed,hold it.
Give the husband a headset.
Mr. Scott?
This is Sam Braddock; I'm
the guy talking to your wife.
Tell me about the Bridge of Sighs.
I got eyes.
Tell me.
Knife is pointed down.
What's the subject's state?
She's crying,distracted. Boss,threat
is low. I can do this. I can see access.
Alpha One and Two,requesting
permission to enter,sir.
We go through the
skylight, we'll spook her.
She might use the knife.
Sir,she does not want to use that knife.
Do you know that?
This isn't aggression
anymore. This is grief.
She's almost done. She
just wants the truth.
Boss,I can see this. You're not seeing
it. Sam's not seeing it. I can see it.
We can be in there within
three seconds. We'll disarm her.
The knife is down.
Repeat: the knife is down.
The truth is the only
thing she's been asking for,
her one demand, and
she's not getting it.
Okay. Okay,the knife
is still in her hand.
Constable Braddock will
continue with negotiation.
Sarah?
Do you know what?
I'm really not that
great with words,but...
but I've been talking to a guy who is.
And he's been telling
me a lot about you.
About how he made a big mistake,
about how much he loves you...
That's not true!
And he wanted me to tell you...
about the Bridge of Sighs.
When my father died...
And when his father died
and he'd lost his job,
you bought two tickets to Venice,
and you said you'd walk over
the Bridge of Sighs together.
Yeah. To gain perspective.
When you've been through so many...
losses together...
you're connected, you
belong to each other.
Always.
Sarah,Josh loves you.
It's taking about six of us to stop
him from rushing in there,Sarah.
You want the truth?
This is it: he loves you.
Subject is down. Hostage has weapon.
Go,go,go,go!
Move away from the door!
Down! Stay down! Put your
hands where I can see them!
- Stay down!
- Stay on the ground. Stay on the ground.
Keep your hands where I can see them.
Eddie,paramedics,right away.
Hey,buddy, what's her status?
Unstable. Knife hit a major
vessel. Massive blood loss.
Sarah... Oh,my God.
Is she gonna be all right?
We'll take care of her.
There. We'll get you in an
ambulance. They'll take a look at you.
Okaycome on.
Sarah,Sarah...
the hospital where the doc
will take a look at you.
This didn't have to happen.
This did not have to happen.
There are always variables
that we can't anticipate.
But,Sarge, we could've saved them both.
There's no way we could know.
"11:06 a.m.Callaghan: Boss,threat
is low. "I can do this. I see access.
"Braddock: She wants the truth.
She's responding. Give me a shot."
It was a risk either way.
Blah,blah,blah, blah,blah,blah.
"11:09 a.m. "Alpha One and Two, "explosive
entry through Black Charlie Three."
I had a connection. She did
not need to be subdued by force.
"Subject was lying prone on the
floor, a knife wound to the chest."
We know,Jules. We were there.
"11:17. Subject in critical
condition. Taken to hospital."
We were there.
I had eyes in. There was time
to get in. The knife was down.
And then the hostage escalated.
Which she wouldn't have
if we'd already gone in.
Sam,you were the negotiator.
It's your right to
call it how you see it.
We can't second-guess whether an earlier tactical
response might have had a different outcome.
Due respect,sir,but it came
down to talk or tactics,
and you're the one that called talk.
That's right.
Because maybe that's the
call a negotiator would make.
Look,I'm just saying, all right?
I want to know what Ed would have done.
It was the sarge's call!
I want to know,too.
Sometimes you do everything right.
Things still go wrong.
That's the job.
Situation was gray.
The boss made a
black-and-white call.
We saved the hostage. Period.
Uh,sorry. The hospital
just called. Sarah Scott.
Doctors got her stabilized.
She's gonna be all right.
- That's great,Kira. Thanks for letting us know.
- Okay.
Okay,then. That's good. Right?
- Need to talk.
- Take a number.
All right. I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey,Eddie.
I'm sorry.
Today should have gone better.
You need to be back where you belong.
Team needs you back.
I'm thinking,I'm-I'm gonna
get Soph,I'm gonna get Clark.
We're gonna go up and get a
cottage,you know? Regroup,like you...
Like you said.
That's great. That's great.
You know,unless,uh, you feel
useless or something without me.
Decent.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
jumped on you like that.
No,it's okay. I get it.
We all wanted them out safe.
What?
I don't know if we should do this.
Sneaking around on the team.
We put our lives in
each other's hands,and...
Yeah,and you're thinking
we should take a break.
I don't know. I don't
know what I'm thinking.
Me,neither.
Okay,so,take a break tonight?
Give us time to think?
Or we could think while
priming my drywall.
That's not fair.
You know how much I
love priming drywall.
Yeah,almost as much as you love my
protein-mango breakfast smoothies.
Don't do this to me.
I'm just saying.
It's all clear.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚