***
Do you know why we're all here?
It's about helping
you, do you understand?
Help.
But first you have to put the gun down.
You have to put the gun down.
give me, uh, give me "gun down."
Ostavi Pistolj.
give me,uh,"we want to help."
ostavi pistolj.
Put the gun down.
Just put the gun down.
gimme "calm down."
Smiri se.
smiri se.
Just keep it calm.
Sierra,switch channels.
Switching channels.
Sierra one,copy.
come on,come on,come on.
Just keep it calm!
keep it calm!
sierra one.
Sierra one.
Sierra one,go ahead.
Scorpio.
eddie!
Hey,I saw that!
I gotta go.
I gotta go,that's my ride.
I don't understand,you knew about this.
Tell your folks I wish
I could. I really do.
I just don't have a choice.
It's the...
it's the thing for
barney,it's his retirement.
Jakub and dorota are flying in.
Dad wanted to show you off a little.
Clark's quartet's gonna play.
Anniversaries happen every year.
That's what they're for.
This is a retirement.
It happens once.
It'S...
it's not something I can miss.
What are they gonna do?
Demote you to rubber bullets?
I gotta go.
Ed,the world is not gonna end if you
and your buddies skip a few pushups.
Clark,pack it up,it's seven.
It's okay,I'll take the bus.
I'll be right there.
Right.
Soph,everybody's gonna be there.
Everybody.
Even some of the old-timers.
I can'T... this is like...
family.
Good one.
later,kiddo.
Or not.
So,what do you want me to tell my
parents,you missing their fortieth and all?
I...
officer wordsworth,what do I...
what do I tell her parents?
Ah,tell 'em...
tell 'em to remember
their gilbert and sullivan.
* When constabulary duties
to be done to be done *
* A policeman's job is
not a happy one happy one *
okay.
- That's good.
- We got it.
papa?
Next station is st. Catherine.
St. Catherine station.
So,what'd you think?
I told them not to waste my time.
Bremler didn't live up to specs.
Really?
Rolie.
Hey,hey,hey.
Brass let him test-drive
the new bremler.
Oh,yeah?
What did you think of
that double trigger?
Pssh. She's jam away.
better pray for a fat target.
I mean,it's a
sweet-looking piece but...
it's all sass,no class!
Well,that's a good match for you.
All brawn,no brain.
hey.
Hey!
So you know the world of pain I face every
time the walls need to be cleaned,right?
Sorry,sarge.
what,did you get stuck up there? Huh?
Double or nothing?
No. No?
Who won?
Who do you think?
So what's the daily special?
Bread and butter.
Drug squad's got a bust up in jamestown.
Yeah,whose score?
Naismith'S.
He said it was big.
Come on. Naismith?
His last big bust is what,two
kids and a couple of joints?
I know,if every day was christmas it
wouldn't be christmas,now,would it?
Babycakes,how are you?
Frickin' shag carpet.
Been picking it out of
her treads all morning.
Price of love,spike.
Yeah,she didn't even make me breakfast.
Say goodbye to your girlfriend.
Briefing room,five minutes.
yeah
Spikie,retirement party tonight?
Yeah,yeah,yeah,yeah.
I thought you were
doing the family thing?
what am I supposed to do?
Well,maybe what you do is
you get the big picture.
What do you mean,big picture?
It's your in-law's 40th anniversary.
- C'mon.
- I'm just saying.
What,did she pay you to say that?
Hey,you know what?
There's a "cop retires" every
week and one day it's gonna be you.
So who ya gonna come home
to when the day comes?
Marta.
what r y doing here?
martha,please,i just want to talk to you
you're supposed to stay away from me
i'm sorry about everything.
i just want to talk
i'll have to call the police again
i'm sorry.i'm sorry. i
just want to talk to you
come with me
i can't,i have to get back to work
Short of any incoming,we've got a
narc warrant for detective naismith.
the exhilarating,electrifying details
of which we will learn en route.
Ninja teams,ed.
Alpha: Wordy 1,spike 2,lou 3.
Wordy,you man the ram.
Rolie,you head up bravo?
You got it,boss.
Five,six.
Dds,flashbangs.
Lew,less lethal.
What?
Again?
And I shall negotiate
should the need arise.
Snipers: Ed,you're sierra
two; jules,you're sierra one.
Mr. Lane?
Absolutely.
Spread the wealth.
Is it "jules' day"?
Every day is "jules' day".
i love you
i can't go with you
martha
leave me alone,let go of my hand
leave me alone
let go of my hand
don't talk to me that way
leave me alone,please. please
shut up! people will hear you
let go of me,don't touch me!
i only want to talk
let go of me
shut up
help me! Please,someone!
Is everything okay?
go away
sorry,sorry.
where are you going?
martha.came back here!
martha,you don't know what you're doing
i won't
martha,come back here.
do as i'm telling you!
i won't
Martha. i'm telling you,come
back here! martha! martha
i warned you
-=bbs.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:÷• øµ∞∏‚ ﬂ«»‚»‚
Flashpoint
Season01 Episode01
Suspect is flagged alpha.
Seen fleeing
vicinity,exiting first york.
Male,white,40s,blue jacket,heavy-set.
Ten-sixty-four.
Repeat,ten-sixty-four.
Drop your weapon!
I said,drop your weapon!
do you understand me?
Drop your weapon now!
Don't move!
code one hundred.
First york plaza,north of the square.
Immediate backup.
Extreme caution.
Bystanders.
Hostage.
Rangefinders?
Check.
Bipods?
so how'd it go last night?
Great.
Hunh. Really?
Battery packs loaded?
Yup.
And?
And it was great.
And what?
What happened?
You wanted to snuggle up
in front of the tv,right?
It's just I'm sitting there and all I can
think about is I wanna finish my drywall.
team one,let's saddle up.
We got a call.
Let's suit up.
Change of plans.
Game on.
Showtime,baby.
First york plaza,copy.
What's the guy carrying?
A luger.
Oh,a luger?
First victim's critical.
Now he's got a hostage,female.
Got it onscreen. Where's he at?
North square.
Heavy on civilians,so
let's go careful out there.
Over.
Morning.
Good mornin'!
Let's break it down.
8:30 in the morning,rush
hour,business district.
Place is gonna be packed.
Which means we gotta
go high. You take...
north building. You counter...
west.
Too high.
East.
East gives us...
Maximum coverage.
Don't want the guy runnin'
and both of us losing him.
Right. What else?
What do you mean what else?
This gonna be crazy.
Damn right it's gonna be crazy; every unit
in the city's gonna want a piece of this.
And I'm sierra one.
Oh yeah,I'm sierra one.
chill.
I'm just sayin'.
There's nowhere to go.
this is going nowhere.
here comes the cavalry.
Dispatch,be advised,sru is on the scene.
You're good.
Let's keep the peace.
K9 and half the marine unit here.
Copy,10-4.
Lewis,I need you in the
truck,you're my secondary.
You got it.
Rolie?
Southwest needs containment.
Make sure the outer perimeter's
clear,I'll take the inner myself.
Good.
Spike,wordy,you cover parker.
Sierras?
North building.
Jules?
East.
All right,good. Keep a close eye.
This guy doesn't look too happy.
Inspector.
It's all yours,sergeant.
Guy got a name?
No. He doesn't speak english.
What's he speak?
Mid-eastern european or
something,I don't know.
Well,how long have you been here?
I think it's yugoslavian. Croatian.
Do you speak it?
No.
Where's the translator?
Back there.
What's he speak?
Russian.
We need a croatian
translator,anyone you can got;
and let me know when
doctor luria's en route.
10-4.
All right,now back your guys off.
I'm trying to de-escalate here and I don't want my
boys getting shot in the back by sympathetic fire.
Let's move it out.
My name is greg.
It's just a radio. I'm
going to put it down.
let's talk,okay? Just talk.
8:46 A.M.,Sergeant gregory
parker begins negotiation.
- You mind the radio?
- No.
I don't know the identity of the gunman
or his hostage at first york plaza.
He's right outside the building
in a stand-off with police,
- who are characterizing this as a very dangerous...
- can you turn that up?
With one victim critically injured.
- Police are advising people to stay away...
- you know where that is?
Don't worry,we're not
going anywhere near there.
Then let's take a detour.
Sierras,switch on transponders
and go to channel one.
Copy.
Sierra two,north building: Eleven floors,elevator
to the tenth,two lefts,one right,staircase up.
Roger that.
Sierra one,east
building: Fifteen floors.
Look for a fire escape.
ten,please.
thank you.
Elevator?
- Immobilized. We're in lockdown.
- Key?
Steve,where's security contact
for the howswell building?
Thanks anyway.
Easy,easy,this is all
about finding a way home.
We all want to go home.
But first,you have to put the gun down.
Sierra one,what's your status?
Elevator's locked,I'm on the stairs.
Weather report?
Wind's 11 knots north-northwest,but
the plaza's sheltered.
Could be looking at some updraft.
Sierra two,in position.
Updraft is confirmed.
Lovely. What's my elevation?
Yeah. Thanks. Keep us posted.
Elevation... 185 feet.
- Hey,lewis.
- Morning,doc.
8:52 A.M.,Forensic
psychologist on scene.
Nothing on our guy yet.
The woman he shot,looks like
she probably won't make it.
I'll tell the boss.
Can I see the transcript?
Unclear,unclear,unclear.
We can work this out together,one
step at a time,do you understand me?
Dispatch,what's going
on with my translator?
Sierra one,take a left
out of the stairwell.
Go straight ahead.
right turn and you're there.
What?
- Lew,how old are those plans?
- What's wrong?
Renovations.
Is luria on scene yet?
- Good morning.
- Hey,doc,what're ya thinking?
First impression: Not substance issues.
He's in full-on tunnel vision.
I'm thinking multiple stressors.
Might help if we knew
what he was saying.
Dispatch,what's going
on with my translator?
We got someone en route. Ten minutes.
That's not good enough. Patch
him on the phone right now.
Sierra one,I have a
new location for you.
Okay,take me there.
It's a higher angle,full-value
crosswind richochet risk.
Ed,what's your vantage?
I can make it work.
It's all yours.
- You copy that,lewis?
- Copy.
Sierra one,in position.
Sarge,sierra one's
position was compromised.
Sierra two is now sierra one.
Sierra one,talk to me.
He's holding her close.
How's the view?
Cold zero.
I've got the solution.
Put the gun down.
I'm on the scene right now at
first york plaza,in north square,
and as you can see the
hostage situation is...
sierra two,in position.
Good vantage.
Big civilian presence,north wall.
Sierra one looks good.
Easy,mister happy.
Do you know why we're all here?
It's about helping you.
Do you understand? Help.
But first,you have to put the gun down.
put the gun down!
sierra one,you got a solution?
I got the solution.
Dispatch: Copy that.
give me "put the gun down." "Gun down."
Ostavi pistolj.
Ostavi pistolj!
give me... give me "we want to help."
Easy,mister happy.
C'mon,stop bobbin'.
That's it. That's
better. You want to dance?
We'll dance... together.
Hocemo vam pomoci. Hocemo vam pomoci.
ostavi pistolj. Put the gun down.
gimme "calm down."
Smiri se.
Smiri se. Smiri se.
Sierras,switch channels.
Switching channels.
Sierra one,copy.
What's he saying?
"I'll shoot her. Don't
make me shoot her."
Keep it calm! Just keep it calm!
sierra one. Sierra one.
Sierra one,go ahead.
- Scorpio.
- Copy.
come on,my friend,let
me have... this... dance.
Sarge,we got a runner! Rolie,red wall!
Parker: Hold fire,sierra
one. Hold fire,hold fire.
Copy,holding fire.
Tata! Tata!
Tata!
Don't move! Stop right
there! Stop,stop,stop!
Tata!
Easy,easy.
Tata! Tata!
Easy,easy!
One step at a time,now. Tell us
what's "tata"? That's your dad?
Is that your father?
'kay,what do you got?
Male youth,breached the perimeter.
look at me. He's going to be fine,okay?
But we need to talk to him.
- Rolie,what's going on?
- It's the son. I got his son here.
scorpio still a go?
That's affirmative,if he re-escalates.
We may have a tpi here,so let's
see if we can work this out.
If he re-escalates,copy.
Still got the solution.
you know what? We need your
help. We need your help,okay?
No one's going to get hurt here,no one's
going to hurt him,but we need to talk to him.
Can you tell him,no one's gonna hurt
him? 'Kay,no one's gonna hurt him.
what's he saying? What's he saying?
Hey,son,you've gotta
tell me what he's saying.
- Scorpio.
Runner!
jules: Ed! The boy!
Police,don't move!
Police,don't move! Don't move!
Police,don't move! Police,don't move!
what did you do?
Why did you do that?!
tape it up. It's now a crime scene.
Nobody speaks to the subject officer.
Constable,I need your
rifle and your kit.
Now you're under investigation;
you know the drill.
Whenever you're ready.
Now,you know you're
sequestered,there's no talking,okay?
We needed to barricade the doors so
people couldn't come in and out,all right?
Greg. That went down fast.
Lewis has the transcripts in the truck.
- I want another staging area for that media; move it.
- Yes sir.
- It was by the book,norm.
- Yeah?
That'll be for special
investigations to decide.
Well,thank you,stainton.
Ed? This was you?
You know better than to talk
to subject officers,commander.
Thank you,inspector.
Good job,constable.
Parker,let's go,siu's waiting.
- How ya doin',eddie?
- Parker.
You mind just plugging your earholes for a second
while I talk to my buddy here and ask how he's doing?
- How ya doin'?
- I'm fine. Fine.
hey,ed,it was a good job.
Saw the whole thing.
I'm sam. Sam braddock.
Good for you.
Don't see lady snipers too
often. That's kinda sexy.
What's that,a remmy 700?
Classic. Hard to top 1 moa.
I carry a vintage colt myself.
- Pearl grips,you want to see?
- Put your hands where I can see them! put your hands in the air!
Lower your weapons!
Easy! That's my dad. Pearl grips.
Braddock,your instructions
were to report to the station.
Sorry,sir,I heard it on the
radio,I didn't want to miss it.
Good work,team one. Team
three will relieve you.
Siu needs witness statements
then see dr. Luria for a debrief.
Braddock,come with me.
Nice post-incident reflexes,guys.
In the hostage taking that shook the downtown
core,police confirm the hostage is unharmed,
but is obviously shaken.
According to reports,the gunman...
blair kowalski,special
investigations unit. How you doin'?
Okay,let's start with the
vest. I need your vest.
Vest.
Shirt.
Boots.
pants.
You didn't wait.
Just bagging the clothes.
They say debriefing and
you take it literally?
Did you say anything?
You don't have to say anything to him.
That's your right,okay?
Frank mcandrew,I'm
your lawyer,all right?
I'm gonna take care of all this. You
have nothing to worry about,all right?
Saw it on tv,that was great work.
Kowalski,this is a no-brainer.
No pun intended.
Do you wanna talk to him now or what?
Okay.
What exactly do you
mean,"he called scorpio"?
He means he got the order.
When you say you "got the order"...
you gonna get that?
It's okay,it's my wife.
You can get that. If you
want to get it,you can get it.
It's your right to talk to your wife.
Hey,soph.
Nah,I can't talk.
Okay,I just wanted to know if that
was that your team this morning?
Yeah.
That was you?
Well,ah,we'll go home
and wait for you there.
No,no,no,just... you know
what? Just go to the thing,okay?
Okay,eddie. Bye.
- So,picking up,when you say you
"got- - You saw it,didn't you?
Just give him the use of
force wheel. This is textbook.
Just,uh,just show him. Give it to him.
When all reasonable efforts to
de-escalate the situation fail
and the suspect is threatening
a member of the force,
clearly progressing from "assaultive"
to "grievous bodily harm",
okay,there we have it! Okay?
- Are we done here,mr. Kowalski?
- Just about.
Were you aware that the
suspect's son was at the scene?
My observer said there
was a,uh,male youth.
And do you believe that every effort was made to involve
the son in the negotiation as a third party intermediary?
Yes I do.
And are you confident that all options were
exhausted before the use of lethal force?
What,the option of watching
him shoot my teammate?
I'll put that as a yes.
So you know,this is the process:
We investigate alongside
the coroner's inquest
and our director will
deliver his statement as to
whether or not there are
reasonable grounds to believe
that you or the other subject
officer used excessive force.
He knows the process.
Until that time,you're
under investigation.
We recommend you take a break,spend
some quality time with the family.
- Thank you,blair.
- Good.
I'll see you at the inquest.
Hold on,ed.
There's somebody else
that you gotta talk to.
hey,mom.
- Look...
- I know,you're fine.
You did a great job out there,but
you need somebody to talk to.
It's strictly confidential.
doc,if you want a date,just ask.
oh,you know what? Screw it.
I forgot who I was
talking to,for a minute.
you're not that guy.
You're not gonna wonder
if you did the right thing.
You're not going to have any sleepless
nights,flashbacks,memory loss,time distortions.
You're not gonna...
feel alone,feel guilty.
Feel guilty about not feeling guilty.
that's what happens to
other people,you'll be fine.
You know where to find me.
Not that you'll need to.
ed,it's time.
Code of silence been lifted?
- Yeah.
- So how'd it go?
- The way they do.
- Are you good?
- Yup.
- Yeah?
Piece of gum? Minty fresh.
Listen,I saw you up there.
It was a clean shot.
Yeah,it was.
That guy knew what he was
in for. You saved lives.
What I'd tell ya?
- Making the world safe so that others may eat pie.
- Eat pie.
That's right.
Let's hope the stockholm
syndrome kicks finast.
Mr. Lane.
You better have an outstanding
reason for being late.
Good job,son.
And I am done.
As you were.
So we're gonna try this again.
Uh,team one,this is sam braddock.
Sam's gonna be joining you.
Sam took his babysteps at 51st division.
Went army and joins
us straight from jtf 2.
This is greg parker,he's
the team sergeant.
We've got rolie,lewis,wordy,spike,jules
and ed lane as our team leader.
- Nice shot.
- Thanks.
- Team's full,isn't it?
- Actually,it's not.
Rolie,your application's been approved.
You are fast-tracked for sergeant.
- On me.
- Thanks,man.
You guys earned it.
Thank you,sir.
- Well,it's about time.
- it's about time.
- Congrats,man.
- Cheers.
how you think eddie's
gonna live without you,huh?
- Aw,he'll be a lost man,I reckon.
- Yeah.
- So,jules,that short for julia?
- No.
Elite special ops counter-terrorist guy leaves
it all behind for the glamour of urban policing.
What's up with that?
So,sam,how many al-qaeda
guys you take out?
What,you mean like to dinner?
You gotta be wasted to take
seven tases like that,right?
- I could take seven.
- Seven,what?
- I could take seven tasers.
- you couldn't take seven tasers.
You and parker island,right?
What happened in there?
I probably got tased seven times.
You know,everybody's on the same page.
what? What does that mean?
I'm fine.
you may want to do the math,one
day,on all the "I'm fines".
* and I will watch you disappear *
* from my fortress over here *
* and I will never understand *
* every hearts a foreign land *
* and I'm so afraid to... *
* so afraid to... *
* love you *
* and I will turn my eyes away *
* from the harsh light of your day *
* and I have slept
through pouring rain *
What did you do.9:08 AM LETHAL
FORCE DEPLOYED HOBTAGE RELEASED
* it was all that kept me sane *
* and I'm so afraid to... *
* so afraid to... *
* love you *
* and I have drawn lines in the sand *
* to remind us where we stand *
* and I'll build castles
while you thirst *
* they'll fall down
but you'll fall first *
* and I'm so afraid to...*
* so afraid to...*
* love you *
-=bbs.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:÷• øµ∞∏‚ ﬂ«»‚»‚