Team 1,hot call at the Michelangelo
Foodsat Brimley and Matheson.
Armed robbery,multiple hostages.
There's some misunderstanding.
He's only 17.
You have got to get him out of there.
- Wordy,how you doing?
- I'm heading to the drops. Steer me in.
With haste,gentlemen,with haste.
Where do I start?
He's had the year from hell.
- Get out of my face.
- It's over.
Sierra 1 in position.
Hold fire till my command.
- I thought I could trust you.
- Put the gun down.
- Standing by for explosive entry.
- Copy that.
- Think I won't do it?
- I know you won't do it.
- Sierra 1...
- I've got the solution.
- Donnie,give it to me. It's over!
- No!
Scorpio.
So that's it? That's
the plan: Lethbridge?
5 hours eailier
Jack said he can get me a job.
What about the restaurant?
Your dream,our dream.
It'll pick up again,David.
By $30,000?
Just give it time.
See this letter,Liz?
Do you see where it says
"Notice of eviction"?
Don't talk to me like I'm a child.
Well,stop acting like one.
Face facts!
The restaurant's a failure.
So... whose fault is that?
Don't you dare lay this at my feet.
Well,I'm not the one dragging our
family halfway across the country.
Hey,Jules.
Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- That's a nice way to say hi.
I'm sorry. I didn't expect to see you.
Glad you came by.
Actually,I came to talk to the boss.
Which... I should go.
Hey,Jules,what's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
You've been avoiding me all week.
I have not been avoiding you all week.
Yeah,you have,Jules.
Sam,okay,I'm not going to do this here.
Do what?
Hey,do what?
- When I return to the SRU...
- Jules,we talked about this.
We did? Me bringing it up
and you changing the subject.
That's not talking about it,Sam.
Well,what's the point?
The point is,when I return to the SRU,
we have to talk about
what happens then,okay?
Now you're on shift,so
let's talk tonight.
Okay,I'll meet you at your place.
Okay. We'll get a coffee or something.
Okay,coffee.
I can't stand being in
this house anymore,man.
I got to get out.
Want to catch a movie?
Nah,I'm not into it.
Go to the mall. Sit
outside Bikini Cabin.
Come on,Donnie. What are you,like 12?
Man,like you weren't into it
when Tessa Price was there with
the new belly button piercing?
Oh,my God.
- Meet me at the shop in ten.
- All right.
Hey,bud,Mom is out,so I
thought that we'd have a talk.
About moving 3,400 clicks away?
I checked.
I'm sorry you found out
the way that you did.
Well,what about school?
And my friends?
Aren't we just talking about Donnie?
Why are you always ragging on him?
Because it seems like your whole
world revolves around this kid.
I-I... I really don't
think it's healthy.
How about you just try expanding
your horizons a little bit?
Hey,where are you going?
My horizons need expanding.
So had to think fast,right?
Like one of those times when you
got to do what you got to do,right?
So the subject comes
running up screaming.
I kick the door down,right?
Spike didn't kick the door in.
I did.
And the subject wasn't screaming.
Guys,you mind? I'm
telling a story here,okay?
So the subject comes out
with this blade,Donna.
And it's like this big.
Wow,a sword.
Okay,okay,maybe more like that.
- A machete.
- Yeah,sure,it was a machete.
Donna... it was this big.
Wh are you talking about this big?
- I'm just saying it was...
- What is that supposed to be?
That's not even a letter opener.
It doesn't matter about the size,Spike.
What are you doing that? You know
you shouldn't do that to a guy ever.
Sam,you're late for workout.
Sorry,sir.
- No.
- What do you mean no?
I mean,no,you can't go.
Like I have a choice?
Look,my parents are broke or something.
They're behind on rent.
They're kicking us out.
Then all we've got to
do is find the money.
Yeah,and how are we going to do that?
I don't know.
My dad's got some old vinyl.
Maybe we could sell
it online or something.
Donnie,it's like 30 grand.
There's no way.
Dude,you can't go.
You're the only non-jerk I know.
Please,I'm already pissed off.
Don't make it worse.
You should be.
We grew up here.
This is our store. That's our mall.
This is our life.
They're going to throw it all away?
Let's go. I need to chill.
How you doing?
I asked you a
question,Sam. How you doing?
Fine. I'm fine.
- You look like crap.
- Thanks.
- But you're fine?
- That's what I said.
That's what you said.
Oh,you're mirroring me,Ed?
'Cause I'm your
teammate,not your subject.
I know that,but if something's wrong,
it's going to affect your
performance; I need to know.
I'm fine. Really.
Hold up.
Bro,what are you doing?
Why are we stopping here?
I want some cookies.
You serious? They have them
at the convenience store.
Yeah,well,I like the
ones they have here.
Do you know how much they
charge? They're like ten bucks.
Yeah,dude,I know.
I used to work here. That's
how I got hooked on 'em.
Why'd they fire you anyway?
'Cause they're jerks.
I was totally awesome at that
job,man,totally dedicated.
The cookies are that way.
No,no,they're up there now.
What?
I got so much work in the office.
I'm never going home.
That the guy that fired you?
No. He's Ashton,the night manager.
You know,after my dedicated
service to this establishment,
I think I deserve a parting gift.
Can you not do this right now?
Nylons?
For my mom.
Donnie... Let's hit the head.
There's one in the
back-- employees only.
Just drop the stuff so we can go.
Bathroom first. Come on.
What?!
We're not supposed to be here.
Oh,easy,Grandma.
It's almost closing time.
No one's gonna be back here.
In five minutes,the head teller's
gonna give the deposit bags to Ashton.
No.
No,I do not want to hear this.
Just listen.
Ashton's going to bring
the deposit bags down
to the safe to be picked up
later tonight by security.
What are you saying?
I'm saying we stop him.
Jump out,grab the money.
We run out that service door. It's easy.
****missing***
Your dad needs money,right?
For rent?
Dude,come on!
Look,man.
We're brothers,okay?
And brothers are always
there for each other.
Five minutes and everything
gets taken care of.
Five minutes and you
get everything you need.
Some dude did the exact
same thing a year ago.
He made off with like 70K.
Okay,whatever.
It's still wrong.
The store's insured. They don't care.
D,stop.
Stop and think a second.
I have.
And you can either step up and help,
or you can turn your back
and let me go out there alone.
Dude,you know I'm not going
to let you do that by yourself.
So you're with me?
You're with me.
Give me the money!
Come on!  Come on!
Lose the stocking. Lose the stocking!
Drop the bag. Drop it. Drop it!
Come on! Come on!
Help me!
Donnie!
Get him off!
What the... what the hell?!
What the hell did you do?!
You wanted me to help you.
Go. We're headed out the front door.
We're just two customers
walking out the front door.
Nearly there.
Like I said,there was two of them.
A big guy in a black jacket.
The other guy had a red coat.
They were armed... That's them.
We're done,man.
It's over.
It ain't over,bro.
Not even close.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:YTET-¿¨»Ò
Flashpoint
Season 02 Episode 08
Team 1,hot call at the Michelangelo
Foods at Brimley and Matheson.
Armed robbery,multiple htages.
Sam and Donna,recon the
building,all ways in and out.
Copy that.
Okay,here's what we know.
Old-school stickup,two masked
guys come in before closing,
hold up the manager with a knife.
And moved away from the window. No shot.
Spike,let's make sure
everyone's healthy in there.
I can get into the security
system,patch it into the truck.
- Eyes in ten minutes.
- You got five.
- Lew,you're my second.
- Copy that.
Sarge,subjects bumped into
armed security as they fled.
One of the guards
chased 'em back inside.
After that,we don't know
what happened to them.
Okay,well,let's hope they didn't
get their hands on his gun.
See if we can ID him,Wordy.
Copy.
Eddy,tac options?
We got high exposed
ceilings,lots of vantage.
I say we stealth in,set up a
sniper perch,watch and wait.
All right,well,you know
what you need to do.
Copy that.
Look... this is really
making me nervous.
Will you put it away?
Kinda using it right now.
Dude,robbery is one thing,but
now there's a gun,okay?
- There are hostages.
- I know.
It's cool,huh?
Cool?
He used to work here.
No,I didn't.
Yeah,you did.
You're the guy they caught
napping in the storeroom.
- What's your name again? Richie?
- No,it wasn't me.
Yeah,whatever.
- Don't "whatever" me.
- Yeah,man,whatever.
I'm not scared of you.
You're not gonna use that gun.
He's not gonna use the gun.
I'd prefer to give him
the benefit of the doubt.
This is Sergeant Gregory Parker with
the Police Strategic Response Unit.
I will be calling the store phone,
so please pick it up so
we can talk this over.
Okay,dude,when he
calls,we'll say we're sorry.
Let's forget about it and go home.
He sounded nice.
Maybe,maybe he could help.
Maybe,maybe he'll lessen the charges.
It's not like we did anything that bad.
'Cept for armed robbery.
Not like that's a felony.
Is this what it's gonna
take for you to shut up?
- Okay.
- What happened there,tough guy?
What happened? Something scare you?
- Not so chatty now,are you?
- D,stop!
Dude,this is messed up.
Let's just walk away.
Oh,yeah,yeah,walk right into jail.
And you know what
happens in jail,don't you?
To guys like you and me,hmm?
Think about it.
Tape their wrists.
Is there anything you can give
that'll help ID these guys?
Height,weight,tattoos,scars,anything?
Oh,man,it was all a big blur.
One was black; one was white.
One of 'em was wearing one of
those glow-in-the-dark ankle bands.
- Like cyclists wear?
- Yeah.
9:48 p.m.: SRU on scene.
Armed robbery,Michelangelo's.
Establishing command post.
Spike,eyes.
Moments away,boss. Moments away.
That's the cops.
Take over.
Hey,this is Sergeant Greg Parker.
Who am I speaking to?
This is... this is D-Roc.
D-Roc,is that a nickname,last name?
I had a buddy back home.
We used to call him
"D." His name was Daryl.
Your name Daryl?
Look,I know how you guys operate,okay?
Don't try to be my buddy.
Don't play me.
I'm not here to play games,D-Roc.
I'm here to help you.
That went well.
Spike,eyes?
Let there be light.
Got a customer in scrubs. Maybe a nurse?
Those two look like
employees. Possibly a manager.
- That's D-Roc.
Subject one. - Yeah?
Hey,D-Roc,I need to know who
else is in there with you.
Can you tell me?
We got three hostages.
Not including the security guard?
Yeah. Not including him.
- And he's unharmed?
- He's fine.
He's not hurt?
I told you he's fine. He's in the back.
Don't worry about him.
Okay,D-Roc,your partner.
Mind if I ask what his name is?
Backslash.
All right,I told you
what you wanted to know.
Now it's my turn.
- Let's talk demands.
- All right.
- We need to get out of here.
- Okay. Where?
- Where we wanna go?
- Home.
Come on. Gimme something!
Tell you where we're going later.
Right now,you just get us
something to take us there.
Okay,where?
He doesn't know what he wants.
He's covering insecurity
with arrogance right now.
- He's scared.
- But determined.
Not a happy combo.
Those aliases come up in the database?
D-Roc and Backslash come back clean.
Maybe it's a gang initiation.
Nah,Backslash,that's not
street. That's a computer thing.
Okay,could be a handle.
Guys,Facebook,MySpace,online forums.
Copy.
I got a couple of bikes here.
Wordy,check the undersides
for serial numbers.
Uh,there's nothing on the first one.
Wait,I got one.
487 623
Okay,Wiiesubject's bike
has a serial number: 487623.
Accessing Metro Police database.
Got it. Adam Jackson.
32 Fern Crescent,Markham.
- Age?
- He's 17.
Wonderful Winnie.
Have uniforms dispatch to
that address immediately.
You got it.
This is Winnie Camden with the SRU.
I need uniforms at
3230 Fern Crescent ASAP.
- Kids.
- Perfect.
- Guys,no one wants a kid in their crosshairs.
- Copy that.
Guys,I got a way in.
The subjects are barricaded in here
which gives them good sightlines
on the front and side entrances.
- So we come in from the rear?
- Yeah.
We check out the loading dock.
If we can't go through, there's
a trapdoor in the storage rm
that will get us to the machine room.
So we shimmy up,pry open the
trapdoor to the machine room.
Then we're on the roof.
- Exactly.
- Nice.
There's a skylight right
here,which give us good vantage.
Cut a hole,set up a perch.
I line up the Sierra shot.
No,I got it.
Is there any reason why you
don't want me to take it?
Do I need one? It's my team,my call.
Donna,contain the front. Let's go.
Okay,guys,it looks like
the hostages are in the back
right corner of the
store in the deli section.
We're gonna need options if
we're gonna avoid a Sierra shot.
Boss,Adam's mom's here.
Mrs. Jackson,I'm Sergeant Parker.
How's Adam? Is he all right?
He's unharmed,ma'am,but
he's in a lot of trouble.
He's in there with the other
kid. They robbed the store.
It went south. And they took hostages.
No,no,no,that's crazy.
There is some misunderstanding.
He is only 17.
You have got to get him out of there.
- Can I ask you something?
- Yes.
Does the name D-Roc
mean anything to you?
Donnie,Donnie Lakeman.
That's his best friend.
Do you have an address?
Somewhere on,on,Kuniff Crescent.
- Thank you. Lewis,you copy?
- Got it.
Okay. Do you know if
Donnie's been diagnosed
with any disorders or conditions?
I don't know. It wouldn't surprise me.
That's one good thing about us
moving: getting Adam away from Donnie.
I have to call my husband.
You're moving?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Please don't do this.
Just be quiet.
You should... you should get the phone.
Don't tell me. I know.
I'm trying to figure this out.
Look down.
Please?
- You're pregnant?
- 20 weeks.
It's a boy.
I didn't know. I didn't know.
It's okay,but... but now you do,right?
So you can let me go.
Look,you didn't sign up for this.
Please help me.
- Bro,I've been thinking.
- Me,too.
- All right,you see that lady over there?
- We need to get a chopper.
We get a chopper,we can get out of here.
Donnie... Think it through!
If we get a chopper,they can't chase us!
You're not thinking straight.
I'm the one who's trying
to get us out of here.
- You're not thinking straight.
- The last thing we need is...
Look out behind you! He's got a knife!
Subject has shot the
guard. The guard is down!
Shot fired! Shot fired!
What did you do?!
10:05 p.m. Shot fired. Guard hit.
Why did you shoot him?
He was going to kill you.
You saw the way he came at you.
It was him or you.
I just wanted to help my dad.
This is bad,Donnie. D-Roc!
D-Roc.
D-Roc!
Use the aliases.
There's a man bleeding
here that you shot!
We're going to jail!
We've got a man down. Medics
stand by. Gunshot wound.
Eddie,we got to step this up.
Copy. Entering loading dock.
Stupid,stupid,stupid.
D,stop.
Stupid,stupid,stupid,stupid!
Stop. Chill,man. Come on.
All right. Chill? How about this?
Or how about this?
Pick up the phone. Pick up
the phone. Pick up the phone.
I'm so sorry.
He didn't mean... He
didn't mean to shoot.
He didn't mean to shoot...
He didn't mean to shoot!
Give me the phone!
They'll hear us if we blast that.
All right,Wordy,there
it is. Right there.
- All right,you stay here and contain.
- All right.
Give it to me!
Okay,okay.
- Listen to me.
- I'm listening.
You can see in here,right?
I know you can see.
You saw what happened.
He came at my friend with a knife.
What would you do,huh?
Someone came at your
best friend with a knife?
No,you were trying to protect
your friend. I hear you,D-Roc.
That's right. You got that right.
That's what you do.
And that's why I'm
here,trying to talk to you.
Trying to keep you and Adam safe. Okay?
Now,how's that guard doing?
I need you to help the guard.
What? No. No,no,no,no,no. I can't.
Please. Because we can't
go in for murder. All right?
Robbery is one thing,but
if the guy dies...
What am I supposed to do?
- You're a nurse.
- I'm a dental hygienist.
Just do what you can,okay?
Just do what you can,please.
He reay needs your help.
I don't care if it's
complicated,smart g...
Give me some washcloths.Plastic
wrap,whatever.
Okay.
Hey,where are you going?
I don't have time to explain,okay?
She's helping the
guard and we need stuff.
He knows your name.
He knows your name,dude.
That's okay. It's okay.
Just be ready to leave,okay?
I told him we wanted a chopper.
What is wrong with you?
The only way we're getting out of here
is with our hands in the air or
with our backs on a stretcher.
- You don't know that.
- Yes,I do.  We're not getting out.
Well,we have to.
It's over.
It's not. It's not over.
Look,I'm helping those people.
- What about the plan?
- There's no plan,Donnie!
We're finished.
Wait!
Come on.
Let go of me.
Adam?
- Hey,boss? Donnie's mom just got here.
- Okay.
I'm Sergeant Greg Parker. I'm
in charge of the negotiation.
Christine Lakeman.
On the way over here,
an officer was telling me
what's going on inside with Donnie.
That Donnie shot someone. Is that true?
I'm afraid so,Christine.
The man's alive,but needs
immediate medical attention.
I know this is hard for you,
but can you tell me about your son?
Where do I start?
It's just... he's had
the year from hell.
Yeah.
Go on,please.
Well,he's never been
the same kid since...
since Travis passed away.
I'm sorry to hear that. Now,Travis...?
His brother. His big brother.
Donnie worshipped him.
Yeah. Could see that
must be tough on him.
Donnie's
father--
my
ex--
he-he left sometime after
and then Donnie just slid
from As to Cs to Ds and then...
He just got into all
sorts of trouble at school
and... All sorts of trouble.
Sergeant,please.
I have already lost one son,
and Donnie is all I have left,
and I can't... I c't lose my boy,please.
Christine,that's the
last thing I want to do.
I want to do everything I can to
g Donnie out of there safely,okay?
- All right?
- Thank you.
Here.
Where's my chopper?
We're still working on that,Donnie.
How do you know my name?
I spoke to your mom.
I spoke to both your moms.
and they're-they're
worried about you guys.
I know you're worried about Adam,too.
I hear he's moving away,huh?
Oh,he's not moving away.
He's not going anywhere.
Where's the chopper?
Is that what Adam wants,too?
I want the chopper!
Maybe I'm not making myself very clear.
So I'll make it very clear.
I want a chopper now!
Let's get Adam's cell phone number.
- Let's try to go through him.
- Copy that.
Freeze it.
Got it.
Text him,"This is rgeant
Parker. I want to help.
" Who's that?
My mom. Wants to know if I'm all right.
I'll get rid of her.
(Donnie's not a bad guy)
Okay.
"I understand,but we need
your help talking him down.
(He's lost it. I'm scared.)
" Don't be. I'll be with you.
What are you doing?
What were you doing with the phone?
What I said.
Texting my mom.
What,you don't believe me?
Come on,Donnie.
We got to get out of here.
What do you think
I've been trying to do?
- I mean,we got to walk out,hands in the air.
- No!
It will just be me and you.
Like it's always been.
Yeah. You and me.
Go.
Your girlfriend needs you.
Okay,guys,we got Adam cooperating here.
We're on a three-point plan.
Wordy's on a covert earbud delivery.
Ed and Sam,secure positions on the roof.
Spike and Donna,explosive entrs
through the front on my command.
I'll get a window charge ready.
Wordy,you locate the
entry to the vent yet?
Affirmative. You sure you want to let
a 17-year-old kid talk down an EUP?
We got a man down losing a lot of blood.
We got to move fast,and Adam's our
best option to end this right now.
That kid says the wrong thing,
it's going to get way out of hand.
Things always get way out of hand.
Hey,I'm in no hurry to pull the trigger
on someone barely old
enough to drive,all right?
Okay. This is good to go.
Ed,Sam,update!
We're on the move.
With haste,gentlemen. With haste!
Got to get these folks out of there.
I'm heading to the drop. Steer me in.
Yep,I got you on my screen,Wordy.
Taking the heating duct highway.
- Cozy,huh?
- Yeah,real cozy.
Is he okay?
He's shot.
Are you okay?
- How bad is he? Can I...
- Don't
-Don't touch it.Don't move it.
- I just want to see if you...
There's clotting in the blood
at the site of the wound.
If we move it now,we destroy all
the healing that's been happening.
I knew you could help him.
I help pull wisdom teeth.
I'm not a doctor.
Okay. That's it,Wordy. Keep going.
You're approaching a drop right now.
Okay,I see it coming.
Hey,Lew,how much weight are these
things ready to hold up,anyway?
I don't know,man. I guess
we're going to find out.
Great.
Thirsty.
I'm sorry. You can't have anything.
But they're going to have
us out of here at any minute,
and you'll be in surgery
before you know it.
Are you a doctor?
No. I'm...
I'm a medical professional.
Seconds away,boss.
One,two,three.
Wordy,how you doing?
Dropped the earbud.
Next time,remind me to bring a towel.
Copy.
Lew,text Adam.
Earpiece is waing,household
cleaners aisle.
- Good.
- Yep.
This is your last chance.
Yeah,we're still working on it,Donnie.
That's what you said last time.
I know,and you're being really patient.
I want to thank you for that.
You're a smart guy.
What'd I tell you about playing me?
- Paper towels.
- I got to tell you,I'm running out of patience.
Sierra 1 in position.
Hey,Adam,look up.
Sierra 1 standing by.
Sierra 1,you have a solution?
I've got the solution.
Copy.
Entry team.
- Standing by for explosive entry.
- Copy.
Okay,Adam.
Now,don't let Donnie
get too close to you.
He'll see that earbud,all
right? Remember that.
Now,just talk to Donnie about
what he's been through this year.
Acknowledge how ha it must have been.
D... I know this year has
been the worst... ever.
Travis died and your dad bailed.
It's been brutal.
That's great. That's great.
You've always been there for him.
But you know I've always
been there for you,man.
I know.
And,Donnie,I-I'll
always be,no matter what.
No,you won't.
I shot a guy.
I'm going to prison,and
you're going to jail,too.
- No,that's not true.
- It is!
Now,Adam,it's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Just... you're his friend.
Remember that. Just be his friend.
Okay,look... I'm not gonna lie to you.
All right,this situation sucks.
But... thing is...
You can get through it together.
But what?
Adam? What are you doing?
Adam,don't touch your ear.
Nothing.
What's that?
What the hell is that?!
Nothing! It's for my phone!
No,it's not. Who gave that to you?
No one. It's mine.
The cops?
How could you?
- Eddie,you got good eyes on this kid?
- Yeah.
- And what do you see?
- He's scared.
And what else?
Boss,barricaded subjects
usually stay elevated.
This kid's ping-ponging.
Okay,as long as he stays
deescalated,we stand down.
Sierra 1 standing by.
The cops?
You've been talking to the cops?
D,no. I...
It's all right,Adam. It's all right.
Just slow him down,ay?
Just slow him down.
They tell you to say all that?
- No,it was me.
- I thought that was you talking.
I thought that was my friend.
- I'm sorry. I was just
trying to get us out of this.
- I thought I could trust you.
- Donnie.
- Boss?
- Adam,we're done. Walk away.
- Stop listening to them!
- Put the gun down.
Get away. You think I won't do it?
I know you won't do it!
Donnie,please.
Sierra 1.
I've got the solution.
Donnie,give it to me. I'll do it.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
- Donnie,give it to me. It's over!
- No!
Scorpio.
Get out of my face.
No solution. No solution.
- You liar!
- Donnie!
Subject's on the move.
Sam,we're going down.
Where are you going?
Entry Team,go!
- In pursuit.
- Copy.
Hands on your head! Hands
on your head right now!
Stay down!
He's lost a lot of blood.
- I trusted you.
- Donnie,listen.
- Adam,get back. Get out of there.
- Oh,don't hu him!
- You sold me out.
- Put the gun down.
I was trying to get us out of this.
Drop the gun! Put the gun down.
Drop it! Put the gun down.
Donnie,I need you to put
the gun down. Do it now.
No. Let me talk to him.
Put it down,son. Put it down.
- Put it down!
- No.
Please! He'll listen to me.
He won't... He won't hurt me.
He hasn't got anybody else.
Get out of here. I got
nothing to say to you. Go!
I'm not going anywhere.
Donnie,it's gonna be okay.
Oh,it's gonna be okay
Look at... Look at me. It's not.
Boss?
Team,Donnie's at a breaking point here,
and he's dangerous to everyone in there.
Now,we got one shot at this.
Eddie,we got to save this
kid from himself here.
So,it's your call, but I ink we
got to let Adam talk to him again.
- Hey,Sam,that gun goes up,it's over.
- Copy.
Donnie?
What am I going to do?
Son,don't do it.
Don't do it,son.
Son?
Look,Donnie,it's me. Just me.
Listen,I don't
care where we are--
in Lethbridge,in jail.
Doesn't make a difference.
But you do this,it's all over.
Remember? We're brothers.
And brothers... need to
be there for each other.
Always?
Always.
Put the gun down.
That's it. That's it.
Yes. That's good work.
That is good work.
Look,I,uh... I just...I
wanted to say sorry
for riding you so hard.
I just had to know that your...
that your head's in the game,that's all.
No problem.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Sam?
My girlfriend is gonna
break up with me tonight.
I didn't know you were seeing anybody.
Yeah,well. Anyway.
- You want to grab a beer first?
- No,I can't.
- Come on. I'm buying.
- Rain check.
All right,tomorrow night.
- Actually...
- Tomorrow.
Okay. That'd be good.
Maybe they weren't meant to be.
You know what? They never really
looked like a couple to me.
How'd you know there was something up?
I figured it out.
How'd you do that?
Because I'm special that way.
Yes,you are. Yes,you are.
Let me buy you a soda.
It's not if,it's when I'm going
to go back on the team,Sam.
Okay,so,the boss knows.
Right,which is exactly
why we can't be together
if I'm gonna go back. You know that.
I love you,Sam,but I've worked my
whole life for this j and the team,
and I'm not gonna let getting shot
stand in the way of me going back.
You mean I'm not going
to stand in your way?
Jules,that's the first time
you told me you loved me.
I didn't think it would be like this.
- Sam...
- Look,I get it.
I get it. I do.
Well,there's always the other
choice if we want to stay together.
Only one of us has to leave the team.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:YTET-¿¨»Ò
Flashpoint Season 02 Episode 08
www.tvsubtitles.net