Look at me!
You sold me out.
Sean, I didn'T. I didn'T.
Sean, sean, listen to me. Listen
to me, just put the gun down, okay?
That's not gonna...
that's not gonna help.
trouble. Geddes's moved.
He's in the line of fire.
Hold. Hold. We need
keenan's phone number.
Your guys are at the door, get him out.
Okay, team, I'm gonna start
talking. Jules, you're my secondary.
Sean, you don't want
to do this, man. Okay?
I invest in you.
Look, let's think it through, okay?
And you spit on all that
to make yourself a deal?
It couldn't be jacks, okay?
Just leave the kid alone.
- You had a future.
- Don't do it.
One more word.
Sean, please.
I trusted you.
It wasn't me.
3 hours earlier
Milk-delivery guy show?
Uh, yeah, half an hour ago.
Awesome. It's so great how the
shipments arrive in time for my shift.
Yeah, well, it's done. Uh,
soy milk, whole, fat-free.
Sugar packs are refilled and sticks.
My hero.
You got a date?
Uh, yeah.
Really.
You didn't go with flowers.
No, they don't play so well
with the four-year-olds.
so, see you tomorrow.
Julia, what're you doing after?
I dunno.
Um, maybe I'll swing by later.
Okay.
Okay. Um, I'll see ya.
Hey, ed?
- Got you a new mugshot.
- Thank you, sally.
- Warrant?
- Not yet. New mugshot.
We're sure he's gonna be alone, right?
We don't proceed unless he is.
And when we do, it's a no-knock deal.
It's all about the first
three seconds of engagement.
We lose the element of
surprise; whole new rulebook.
Wordsworth: Who's their inside man?
Naismith's isn't saying, but they've had a
narcotics cop deep undercover for 8 months.
And today is christmas.
And it's a record-breaking score.
A brief little window of opportunity
before it disappears onto the street.
Eight months of prep.
And they get to watch us
fly in for the grand finale.
You ain't got the guts...
that's why we get the cool pants.
That's what I'm saying.
Practice area reset.
We're a go for round five.
All right, guys, one more time.
Practice makes perfect.
- Ready, sam?
- I've cleared bad guys before.
It's serving a warrant for the
search of the gentlemen's premises
for the highly corroborated
presence of narcotics.
Speed, surprise, and aggressive action.
Hey, so what about tonight?
Not gonna happen.
It's gonna be a long day,
you're gonna get hungry.
- Dinner's a very important meal.
- Sam.
A burrito and couple of
beers, what's the big deal?
All right, I'm not trying to flatter myself, I know
you're just being nice, I don't want to read into this.
I've just worked way too hard to be
here, to screw it up by getting personal.
It's not worth it. There's like 500
cops waiting to get into the sru.
500 guys waiting for me to
do something that I shouldn'T.
So, I'm sorry, but the team comes first.
Jules, it was just a burrito.
See you at practice.
Jackson.
- You can't just-
- I know.I, uh...
should have called, I'm sorry.
Hey, ella. Hey, how are you?
Sweetie, just go inside
for one sec, okay?
Corrie...
you're gonna show up here with a
toy and everything's gonna be okay?
- She's my niece.
- Not today.
Then when, all right?
It's eight months, four
days and I am clean.
I got a job, I'm doing the
steps and I miss my family.
I'm sorry, the money you stole...
- I'll pay it back.
- $680 dollars?
I'll pay it back.
That money was ella's for music lessons I promised
her, because $680 dollars takes a long time to save.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, you were sorry before.
Look, I promise...
it's always promises with you.
If you want me to trust
you, you gotta show it.
Okay. I'll get you the money.
Okay, you get the money
and then we'll talk.
- I will.
- Okay.
Today, I'll get you the
money. I'll pay you back.
Let's make this drill perfect, team.
Only one shot in real life.
Okay, team, aggressive
entry, our guy's firing.
Sam: Shoot on the
move, limit his angles.
Okay. Our guy's got a flamethrower.
Every eventuality, let's go.
Bravo team sends in a
dd, then rappels back up.
Lewis: Alpha comes in hard other side.
Okay, team, final rehearsal.
Keep sharp and stay in formation.
On my count: Three, two, one, go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!Down!
police! Down! Down! stay down!
Get down! Get down! Stay down!
Your breath is killing me, man.
sorry, shelly made cabbage rolls.
You want to file a less
lethal report on those.
Whoa, watch it.
Let's see his hands.
Get him up!
Subject secured. Again.
Nice work, guys.
Say it.
- Again!
Let's reload the window.
We're out of glass.
Thank you, corporal,
that was very convincing.
Good work, sam, you'll
stand our lead entry.
I'm sure our special ops guest will
agree that we covered every eventuality,
backwards and forwards
and in high heels.
Yeah, well, if your subject can fight these
guys off, tell him we could use him in kandahar.
Good.
All right, let's recap in the briefing room
while we wait for the warrant. Good job.
I was wondering if you could lend
me, I don't know, maybe, like, uh...
like $700 dollars or $600 dollars?
hey, uh, yeah, it's jackson.
I was just thinking maybe I could work for
a week or a couple of weeks, if that's okay.
no. Yeah. Okay.
Um, okay. Well, thank
you. Thank you very much.
uh, like uh... $600, $700
dollars. All right, no problem.
Thank you, though.
I could give you, like, forty dollars.
That's all I got right now,
but you can totally have it.
You know what, it's uh... it's
okay, don't worry about it.
It's not a problem.
Are you still gonna stop by? Jackson?
So, you're gonna join us or what?
My work here is done.
"Deeds not words," my friend.
- Isn't that right, braddock?
- That's right.
What do you mean, "deeds not words"?
Sarmypecial ops motto.
Used to be his motto.
Right, right. So how you been?
Sun always shines on kandahar.
Sally, is that warrant in?
Still waiting.
Yeah. Jackson.
Where you been, little man?
No phone call, no postcard.
All this time and that's the first
thing you ask, you ask me for money?
No, you know what? No problem.
Why don't you come over
and we can talk about it.
Okay, I'm on my way.
What's the deal on the
guy you're taking down?
Name's sean keenan, got a boatload of priors,
squeaked his way out of a couple homicide charges.
He's looking at his third strike today.
Oh, so he's got nothing to lose.
Aw, man, it's the worst kind.
But still, days like today...
- yeah, they make you feel alive. I know.
- That's right.
- Look, you know sam braddock was in our unit, right?
- Yeah.
What, something I should know?
It's not my place to say.
I don't do innuendo.
You got something to say about
a member of my team, say it.
I'm saying that...
watch your team's back.
- Good luck today.
- Yeah.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Flashpoint
Season01 Episode03
Warrants in. Team one,
you're up. You're up.
greetings.
Nothing if not punctual, huh?
What, only two sentries?
That's interesting, a day like today.
You want a
no-tip-off guarantee?
How 'bout we round up
the whole neighborhood.
How's it look?
It's good. Just waiting
on word from geddes.
Seconds away. Here's
the elevator service key.
Geddes' your undercover?
- Harlan geddes?
- Yeah, you know him?
Yeah, we partnered at 21 together.
Had a barbecue a couple of weeks ago.
What's his in?
He's worked his way up through the
ranks over the past eight months from,
uh, low-life to
mid-level runner.
Trust factor's pretty high, so ass-hat's givin'
geddes a slice to sell to the neighborhood kids.
Anything else we need to know?
Yeah, you know about the
double homicide, right?
Yeah-yeah, how'd he beat the rap?
Joys of the justice system.
Look, if this guy feels
cornered, he's gonna bite, okay?
Speed and surprise, we get it.
Yeah, you do this right,
geddes gets a shower and shave.
Takes miriam out someplace
nice for a change.
I thought "junkie chic" got you
into all the good restaurants?
Good to go?
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
Did he say "ass-hat"?
He said "ass-hat".
Hey, nice shoes.
Hey, what's up, man?
You don't look at people
when they're talking to you?
My boy said he likes your shoes.
Yeah, thanks.
yo, I ain't hear no respect, B.
Yo, you better show some
respect before ya get slapped up.
Hey, yo, do I know you?
- Guys, look...
- nah!
Do I know you?
'Cause I don't know you and
you wanna walk my street?
Yo, you gotta drop some paper, B.
Hey, jackson?
Hey, man.
Jackson, what's up, man?
Yo, you wanna be careful, man.
- You ain't been around in a while.
- Yeah.
You need some help? You
need me to hook you up?
Nah, I'm just here to see sean.
All right, man, don't
wanna hold you back.
Thanks.
- Hey, it's geddes.
- We're a go.
All right, planets are in alignment.
The shipment's in, target's alone.
This is it. Let's do this!
Alpha team,we're switching up: Sam, you're
gonna be three, I'm gonna take lead entry.
- We're changing the tac plan?
- Tac plan's a thing of beauty. Let's go.
- Jules, spike, drop us off, roofside.
- Why?
Because when you're democratically elected team
leader, you get to make autocratic decisions. Let's go.
Be careful, children.
And I've got you on screen.
Alpha bravo, proceed.
2:03 pm, elevated risk:
Narcotics warrant...
underway. Subject sean keenan.
Just like we drilled,
team. Secure, enter, arrest.
Floor 4.
Ladies blouses, perfumes and fragrances.
Okay, ed, our guys
are almost at the roof.
You know, I'm good here.
You want to check if your boy's
got the outer perimeter secure?
Oh, it's secure.
I wanna make sure your guys
get my 15 keys out in one piece.
how come we can never get along?
Bravo team?
- Bravo team?
- Gearing up.
Hey, a waste of time, man,
store's closed. Come on.
I'm not shopping.
Little man! Look at you, eh?
look at you.
Where you been all my life?
Hey, we're done.
You get that product on the
street. You're still on probation.
Yeah, I ran into jackson on the stairs.
We should hit it, man.
You two know each other?
Yeah, jackson and me go back.
Interesting.
Jacks, man, we should shake it.
- I got you covered.
- No, I got a better idea.
This is good.
Get in here.
Bravo team seconds away.
clear.
Looks good.
Alpha team holding.
- Bravo team, prepare to rappel.
- Copy.
Where's geddes?
He should be here by now.
Call him.
Alpha, bravo, action on my go.
Three...
two...
yo, I'm still busy with my friend, okay?
- Geddes is back inside.
- One.
Three...
two...
Yo, I'm still busy with my friend, okay?
- Geddes is back inside.
- One.
Hold, hold. Alpha, bravo, hold.
- Holding.
- Geddes's inside. What's he doing?
- I don't know.
Still holding.
- Plan's changed.
- Boss?
Fall back, fall back.
Okay.
you done?
Yeah. Sorry, client.
Jackson... see something you like?
You're not going in?
Give me the tenant profiles.
You know the street value
of the drugs in there?
Do you want your guy
caught in the crossfire?
We're falling back. Tenant profiles.
Alpha team, let's get eyes in.
All right, neighbours to the right.
There's trouble left. Trouble...
stairs?
- It's under renovation.
- That's good.
- Ed, sixth floor.
- Copy that.
Bravo team, fall back
to the sixth floor.
- Game's changed.
- Copy.
So much for speed and surprise.
So, jackson, you gotta meet
up with your probie today?
- no.
- No?
Were you on the breakfast tv this
morning, win the free makeover?
Yeah, guy looks sharph?
think I could clean up as good
as you? Shave and a haircut?
So, like, I was sayin',
we should get moving.
I'll take care of you.
Uh, yeah. Yeah, okay.
What about your money?
- Oh, I'll come get it later.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- No.
Sit.
We need to ask you to evacuate while we take
care of a police investigation in the building.
Please exit as quickly as
you can down the stairs.
- so, jackson...
- Shut up.
So how long were you in for?
- Uh, thirty days.
- Thirty days?
Must be the choirboy face.
So, thirty days, but I haven't seen
you in - what? - Six, eight months?
Yeah, I've been busy doing some stuff.
Fix you something?
no, man. Thanks, I'm good.
Thirty days go by, you're out
and about, you don't call...
I feel kinda hurt.
Yeah, sorry.
How do you guys know each other again?
- I used to see him at the grouse.
- Right.
See, smart guys like you don't come round too often
- case in point.
And we had a good thing
going, hm? Give me your bag.
Come on, man, I got customers waiting.
You're going into partnership.
You remember what I promised you?
Big things.
I keep my promises, little man.
This is me saying, "I want you back."
Show of faith. It's on me.
How much did you say you needed, huh?
You take this to the street,
you're back in the game.
Maybe even got a little
extra left over for yourself?
nah, man, I'm good. I'm just...
you sure you're good? 'Cause
you don't look so good to me.
- And I'm not so sure who it is I'm talking to, who you turned into!
- What are youtalking about?
Sean, come on, man, chill.
It's jacks. It's all good.
I'm talking.
Can I trust you, little man?
Look me in the eyes, 'cause I think
you just failed your first test.
- Yo, we been lookin' for you, man.
- What's up?
- Cops on the roof,yo.
- Yo, it's swat.
Let's get that ball
camera outside the window.
Boss is right, we don't proceed
unless the subject's alone.
The undercover knows we're coming.
You don't wanna have to send
this guy out unexpected company.
Where are my eyes?
Coming up, boss.
Sean, come on, man, I just
came here for a loan, I swear.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay.
- you getting this?
- Yeah, I'm getting it.
Okay, that's geddes.
'Kay, geddes confirmed. That's keenan.
Well, we got somebody else here.
There's three individuals.
- Who's this?
- No idea.
Sally, I'm sending you a snap.
We've got a new subject in our friend's
loft, let's see if we can get some id on him.
Copy that, standing by.
I knew it!
- I could smell it on you!
- Sean! Sean!
Keep it cool, man. What's going on?
- You got your cop buddies outside?
- Cops?
Thirty days?I'm gonna kill
you, you lying piece of-
No-no, no-no, sean, I didn't
call the cops, I swear.
Come here.
You getting this, boss?
The gun's on the unknown, not geddes.
What the hell is going on?
- I said, come here.
- Sean, I would never do that to you.
I took you under my wing, I
gave you financial independence.
Sean, sean, think about this,
man, it's not gonna help us. Okay?
all right, we got a
clean line, let's go.
- Geddes' not armed?
- No.
Team, I need options?
Aggressive entry, beta plan.
Jules, spike, five and six.
Spike, double up on
flashbangs. Let's go.
I'm only doing this because
I promised my sister.
Look at me!
You sold me out.
Sean, I didn'T. I didn'T.
Sean, sean, listen to me. Listen
to me. Just put the gun down, okay?
That's not gonna...
that's not gonna help.
Trouble. Geddes moved,
he's in the line of fire.
Hold, hold.
Give me keenan's phone number. come on.
Sean, you don't want
to do this, man. Okay?
I invest in you. I put my trust in you.
Look, let's think this through, okay?
And you spit on all that
to make yourself a deal?
It couldn't be jacks, okay?
Just leave the kid alone.
- You had a future.
- Don't do it.
One more word...
sean, please.
I trusted you.
It wasn't me.
Officer down!
Sally. E.M.T. 725 parliament.
- No siren, no siren.
- Get him out. Get him out.
No, keenan's still armed;
two people in the crossfire.
Just gimme his phone number.
Your guys are at the door, get him out!
'Kay, team, I'm gonna start
talking: Jules, you're secondary.
- Copy.
- Wordy, lewis, on sentry.
- Ed...
- I'm on it. Got it. Copy.
You still alive, douche?
- You want some more?
- No, no, no, no, no! Don't kill him. He's a cop!
He's not a cop, he's a lousy...
he's a cop, okay? He's a cop.
Don't kill him. Don't make it worse.
You see that hit he took?
Shotgun blast out of a revolver.
That's no saturday night special.
We need a new entry plan.
There's no time. We
should be in there already.
Jules, stay on that monitor, let
me know if the geography changes.
Sally, I need you.
You know he's a cop
and you don't tell me?
I didn't know, okay? I just
recognized him just now.
He's one of the guys that arrested me.
jacks...
hey, you will not negotiate this
while my guy bleeds to death.
You want a free-for-all, go in
yourself and take your chances
or you let me do what I'm here to
do and maybe people come out alive.
damn it.
Sally, isolate the
phone line: 555-0166.
A cop. A frickin' cop.
Hey, we're you going?
- He's gonna to bleed to death.
- Let him.
You want to go down for murder, too?
They ask you, you tell them...
- it was an accident.
- okay.
- He jumped me.
- Okay.
You saw it.
He jumped me, there was a
struggle, the gun went off.
There was a struggle,
it was an accident,
- He jumped me
- The gun went off, It was an accident.
It was an accident.
I can trust you on this?
- Yeah, you can, you can trust me, man.
- Okay...
you're not going anywhere.
You and me, little man.
let's do this.
Bolt the door.
yeah.
This is sergeant greg parker with
the police strategic response unit.
Am I speaking with sean keenan?
Yes you are.
How can I help you, greg?
You want to tell me
what's going on here today?
Why, greg? What's on your mind, hmm?
Option a: We let the boss talk him out.
Option b: We try to isolate keenan,
maybe we got a shot at a clean rescue.
What about immediate entry?
Wordy, hold off.
Well, sean, a firearm was
discharged in your vicinity -
in your area, in your neighbourhood
- and we were just wondering if everyone in there was all right.
We're great.
Thank you very much for asking.
And how 'bout you, greg? How you doin'?
hurry up!
You know what, sean, let's cut the
pleasantries and get to the point, okay?
We both know why my team
and i are here, right?
Yeah? Well, why don't
you tell me all about it.
Thanks, sally.
- Weapon keenan's carrying is called a "jury".
- A jury?
It's a street name. It's new.
It takes five rounds
- shotgun and single bore.
- Explains the size of the wound.
- Yeah.
- Hey, man, hang on
- Easy, easy, easy.
You're gonna be okay, all right.
- You gotta- you should get out.
- You know how I remember you?
At the green grouse, it
was you who arrested me.
- sorry. - No-no-no,
man, don't be sorry.
Turned my life around.
Kid... go on, get out.
We got a guy dying in there.
He's in the line of fire.
And we also have an unknown
who's in the line of fire.
What are we saving cops
or we saving drug dealers?
Don't let it get personal, wordy.
I'm just saying.
He had the gun pointed at the kid.
- Lover's quarrel.
- Body language.
Haircut, nice clothes,
it just doesn't add up.
We do an explosive entry, flashbangs...
Keenan still has time
to fire his weapon.
He's right. We got
more than one life here.
I'm not putting this kid at risk.
I don't give a flying king-sized
crap what you do for a living.
I've got a friend in there and
I want to get him out alive.
You're a smart guy, I expect you're
fully familiar with how to use a toilet.
Hey, you've done this before.
I got nothing but the best
and brightest for you, sean.
Very important to us, so...
if we can both handle
this professionally,
the boys and I won't have to come
in there and trouble you at all.
So you do what you gotta do.
go on, get out.
No, man, we're both gettin' outta here.
Can't do it.
'Cause there's only a couple
of ways this can go, right?
We're not looking for
more people to get hurt.
This guy's on his third strike.
It's gonna be all about
the blaze of glory.
How's geddes doing?
He's hanging in there.
- I don't know how much longer.
- Options.
We're not coming up with any other
choices, boss. We go through the window?
And he'll use you as
target practice. No.
All right. Thanks, sal. Okay.
Our unknown is jackson barcliffe,
21, a former client of keenan'S.
He was arrested 8 months
ago for possession.
His parole officer says that
he's been on the wagon ever since.
On the wagon until today, I guess.
Sean, we can resolve this, peacefully,
right now, if you make the right choice.
Place your weapon on the floor
and you come out your door...
okay, greg, I hear ya.
I just need to think
over my options over here.
well, you do. You think
about those options,
but you think about them very carefully because
you're already apprehended, right? That's a given.
- What about the kid?
- Come on, he's made his choice.
- How's he doing?
- He's still breathing.
If you want to make things
better for your future,
you should think about showing us
that you can make the right choice.
Running out of time, ed.
yeah?
It's the kid in the room.
Jackson.
My name's ed, I'm a police
officer with the sru.
I want to help.
Okay, okay, let's talk.
Jackson, you did the
right thing calling.
The man who's shot, how's he doing?
Uh, there's A... there's lot of
blood, he's bleeding pretty bad.
Okay, is he breathing?
Yeah-yeah-yeah,
he's breathing.
Okay, his name's harlan. Now I
need you to do me a favour, jackson.
I need you to move your finger
back and forth in front of his eyes.
No, no, he's conscious, he's fine.
Okay, that's good. That's good.
Look, um, I can't talk
long, if sean comes in...
if he comes back, jackson,
just put the phone down.
Okay, just put the phone down,
but leave it on, all right?
That way we can hear you.
You make the smart choice and
that sends a positive message.
this is all my fault.
This shouldn't have
happened, I just... I just...
take it easy, jackson-
I, I need the money.I swear to
god I was clean. I'm clean now.
Jackson, that's amazing.
Are you doing the steps?
Yeah, yeah. Eight months.
That's incredible. That's incredible.
That shows me that you got a lot
of strength; that you can do this.
All right, you wanna help? I need you to
wrap that towel tight against his stomach.
Okay, he's still bleeding,
you gotta slow that down.
Okay, we gotta get in there.
We gotta get in there and do our job.
I don't wanna see you get
hurt, so I need you to get out.
No-no-no, I'm not
leaving. This is my fault.
Nope, we've got an ambulance on the way.
It's my fault. I'm not leaving.
Okay. Take a look at the door. Do you
see anything unusual? Any boobytraps?
Any wires around the frame,
around the door handle, any...
No, no, it's two locks and a bolt.
Good. Okay, that's good news.
Okay, here's the thing, if we come in now, jackson,
you and geddes are right in the line of fire.
Okay, so what I'm gonna ask you to
do is move him to the other room.
Oh, god, I can try.
Jackson? Jackson?
Well, you know, greg, I, uh... I
appreciate the approach you're taking here.
You sound like A... reasonable man.
Well, greg, you know, uh...
I respect your point of view.
I do. Yeah.
'kay, man, I'm gonna
try and move you, okay?
All right, ready? Come on.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You know, I'd like to
deal with someone...
- my name is harlan.
- What?
My name is harlan geddes.
Please... tell my wife...
I, I love her.
we're losing him.
The kid's putting
himself on the line here.
No, we got an officer on the line here.
Careful.
Tell my boys... that I'm proud of them.
And I love 'em, okay?
Eddie...
you're gonna be fine, okay, man?
It's all right. I just...
I just gotta move you, okay?
I'm sorry, it's gonna hurt.
Okay.
Bravo team, gear up for rappel descent.
Stay out of the window
and prepare for flashbangs.
There's no time!
Sam, we lost surprise. A window
distraction buys us a couple of seconds.
- Keenan's onto him.
- End of the road, ed.
Immediate action! Beta plan!
Sam, damn it!
Keenan, listen to me, this
is really important now.
Are you listening to me?
greg, what's the story?
Damn it, sam, hold
formation! Hold formation!
- Damn it!
- Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
- police, get down!
- Hold your fire, officers! Unarmed subject!
Get down on the floor! Get down on the
ground! Get down! Stay down! Get his hands!
Constable, likes it rough.
Clear!
Wordy, how's geddes?
Emt! Get me an emt!
How's he doin'?
Jackson. I got you, buddy. I got you.
The paramedics are just
around the corner. I got you.
You're gonna be okay.
He's still breathing.
Move your hands. Move your hands for me.
You did it. You did
it, buddy. You did it.
You did those 12 steps,
you can do anything.
You gotta just keep talking. That's it.
You're gonna be fine, just keep talkin'.
You're fine. You're gonna just hang
on. Just keep talkin' to me, all right?
Okay, you're gonna be
okay. You're gonna be okay.
- You're all right, you're okay.
- Ella.
Who's ella? Who's ella, jackson?
She's such a goof.
no, she... she makes me laugh.
Jackson, I bet she's proud
of you. Stay with me, jackson.
Jackson, who's ella? Jackson,
who's ella? Stay with me... jackson?
Jackson?
Easy.
These guys said you're
gonna be fine, okay.
I'm gonna call miriam myself.
You don't you worry about a thing.
'Kay, I gotta go debrief.
I'm gonna check in on
you as soon as we're done.
kevin, where you going?
I don't know.
- That was messed up.
- I know.
you okay?
Looks like geddes is gonna make it.
Too bad about the kid.
How else was it gonna end?
I don't know.
I don't know, but that is not your call!
And maybe I was wrong, sam. Maybe.
But I need to know that
my team is on my side.
- Then treat me like I'm on your team.
- What?
You wanna know what happened in
afghanistan? Is that what this is about?
I was taking out targets in a
stronghold, 1500 metres away.
The reccy was done,
I was cleared to fire.
We went down to do the id's,
one of them was my buddy matt.
I was sniping with a . 50 cal.
He shouldn't have been
there, I was cleared to fire.
You just had to ask.
You go in on my command.
You keep entry formation and
you don't go in without a shield.
- Are we clear?
- Sir.
2:36PM OFFICER RELEASED BYSTA.........
"Psalm" by Hey Rosetta
* but often it happens you know *
* that the things you donít
trust are the ones you need most *
* so it's cautiously into the dark *
* but you see before long
that your eyes will adjust *
* and under the night you can hear *
* the full moon rise
like a psalm in the air *
* and the air goes into your lungs *
* and around in your heart
and on through your blood *
* goes cautiously into the dark *
* and you see before long
that we all have a part *
* and the air goes into your lungs *
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚