* i'm crazy *
* crazy about you *
* make sure that you have
the best in life *
I think i saw a cop.
* cause i'm crazy *
(low buzz of chatter)
We gotta hold 'em back.
Wordsworth:
mister, out.
Nobody move!
(shot fires,
guests scream)
come here.
stop!
Don't move.
Mmm...
God, this is so good.
It is like...
dissolving right now;
It's like melting
onto my tongue.
(chuckles)
Here.
No, it's all yours.
Let me get this
out of your way.
Oh, actually,
I think she's still
working on it.
Are you?
are you still working on it?
Well, yes, um...
Yes, i am still
working on it.
You remember?
Yeah.
You know much...
trouble i got in
Letting you sit there everyday
for three hours
With that one cup
of coffee?
I was still working on it.
Besides,
with a view like you,
Who wants to move?
I get to look at you
all night.
All night.
(sighs)
are you okay?
(groans) i'm good.
I'm good,
just, uh... just tingly.
You know,
it's... it's weird.
(glass shatters)
Can i help you?
I'm gonna go
to the ladies.
(pained exhale)
If i'm not back
in ten...
I'll send in the hounds.
(patrons whisper disapprovingly)
(classical music plays quietly)
(gasps) god.
This place is so beautiful.
I bet even the...
bathroom's are beautiful.
Enjoy your meals.
I'm sorry about that.
I'll get your bill.
Mm...
No dessert menu?
Hey, hey, um...
Team five is still on
that motel standoff;
You guys mind sticking around
until they get back?
Yeah, no problem.
Guys, you copy that?
Team:
copy. copy that.
Shelly,
i'm gonna be late tonight.
Let me say goonighght
to the girls?
Soph, yeah,
gotta little bit of ot.
Yeah.
All right, save me some.
Hey.
I'm good, thanks.
Yeah,
we have to postpone tonight.
(tight inhale,
chuckles)
I'm sorry.
(cell phone rings)
Lewis:
hello?
spike:
hey, lou.
sorry, bud.
I might be a little held up
at work.
Oh, it's okay.
at least you called.
Woman:
(confused) i have to...
Yeah, i have to...
Go this way.
this is the door.
restaurant patron:
miss? are you okay, miss?
Don't tell me...
mom, i have to go.
I have to go,
i-i wanna go home.
waiter:
your friend needs help
in the bathroom.
after that,
you pay and leave.
Woman:
don't tell mom.
I have to go... this way.
(stammers)
i have to get out of here.
Laura?
I have to go...
laura.
(exhales)
(disbelieving laugh)
It's okay, baby,
come here.
I'm sorry.
(half laughs)
It's okay.
Hey.
Do you still need to use
the bathroom
Or are you done?
no, um...
I'm good.
'kay.
You know what?
let's just go.
What,
without paying?
What? you mean,
after they were so nice to us?
Laura:
(half laughs)
This "bad boy" side of you?
I kind of like it.
Well, the night's
still young.
You ain't seen
nothing yet.
Next?
next.
Let's go.
(exhales)
(gasps)
laura:
what's left on the credit card?
Not that much.
The guy's gone
and doubled the price.
Maybe we could look
at another one?
No.
Are you kidding?
no, that's not the point.
(exhales)
i don't know...
Lo, listen.
I made you a promise
and i'm keeping it.
Well, i guess he shouldn't
have boosted the price.
No, he shouldn't have
boosted the price.
Especially today.
Why don't you go
talk to him?
Hi.
Excuse me?
I'm looking to buy
a watch.
Um...
can you show me
what you have with the...
i'm sorry,
i forgot what they call them.
The uh...roman numerals.
ro-roman numerals.
Um, something...
not too flas..
uh, maybe...
uh, can i see this one?
What is that, what is that?
is that mother of pearl?
What's your price range?
well, we're in the, uh...
Hey!
stop!
Don't move!
don't move.
Call 911.
man:
sir?
Sir, please put down that gun.
male clerk:
no, not this time.
not this time.
This is the fourth time
this month
And i am not taking it!
woman clerk: (on phone)
we're being robbed.
(shot fires,
glass shatters)
(terrified screams)
Help!
Put it down.
i said, put the gun down!
Do what he says.
Let her go.
female clerk:
(crying)
Don't make me do this.
Let her go.
I don't wanna hurt your wife.
They want money,
just give it to them
Hey,
we're short on time here.
Just put the gun down
and let us go.
(sobbing)
(gun clunks on display case)
Okay, son,
I put it down,
Let her go.
Lo, get the gun.
get the gun.
Male clerk:
let her go, son.
please, son, let her go.
please.
Female clerk:
(frighteneyelp)
You know,
You're short on time, too.
What are you gonna do
with what you've got left?
Flashpoint 2x12
Last Dance
Sync by honeybunny @addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
winnie:
team one, hot call.
gear up, guys,
shots fired.
robbery at 2110 church.
One male, one female.
subjects believed to be
high-risk
and under the influence.
Winnie, let's see if there are
any other reports in the area.
winnie:
copy, boss.
(traffic rumbles loudly)
Okay, next.
(excited laughter)
(sighs)
Lo, you still with me?
laura?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
(siren wails)
(vehicle screeches to a halt)
parker:
inspector.
What do you got?
Stainton:
suspects fled in a gold sedan,
they got a .357 magnum,
And we just put out
an apb.
Gun's theirs?
no, it's the shopkeeper's.
A .357?
people these days.
Well, they said they were robbed
3 times the last month.
Ed:
okay.
Okay, guys?
Subjects have fled the scene
and they are armed.
We need you to stay
on the road.
We got an apb on a gold sedan.
Repeat, apb on a gold sedan.
Copy that.
ed:
they're close.
We might be looking
at a moving takedown.
You got an id?
No. there's no camera
in the shop.
Eddie, see what you can get out
of mr. and mrs. .357, will you?
(cell phone rings)
Parker.
Winnie:
boss, no other calls
in the area.
Just a dine and dash,
But it matches the description.
i got a waiter on the line,
if you wanna talk to him.
Okay.
thanks, winnie.
Putting him through.
Hey, i'm sergeant greg parker,
I'm with the police
strategic response unit.
What can you tell me
about these people?
They're in their late 20's,
i guess.
parker:
do you remember
what were they wearing?
Yeah, she was in a...
purple dress,
He was in a blue suit.
Maybe, um... "5'9, "5'10.
You ask me,
they were high.
Can you describe
their state of mind?
Um, like iaid,
crack thieves,
They come in here
all the time.
Yeah?
how were they behaving?
They were making the other
customers uncomfortable.
ed:
can you be more specific?
Intense.
Really out of it.
Glassy-eyed,
knocking things over.
Off-balance.
Her speech was a bit slurry.
And the woman apparently
had a fit in the bathroom.
female clerk:
just before they left,
He was going on about
being short on time.
male clerk:
yeah, um...
"what are you gonna do
with what you've got left"?
What'd they take?
Art deco ring,
five diamonds.
ed:
they didn't grab anything else
on the way out?
No, they knew you guys
were coming.
Okay, thanks for your help.
What's your take,
eddie?
Looking like
substance abuse.
Looking like, huh?
Well, they could've cleaned out
the whole place,
But they didn't.
Stainton:
we got a foot cop saying
he just saw a gold sedan
Going north on yonge
above charles.
Okay.
ed:
wordy, what's your twenty?
Parker:
we'll send you a postcard,
inspector.
stainton:
all right.
Maybe we should stop now
And get home?
Do you see any cops?
(exhales) not yet.
Okay,
then we're okay.
Unless there were cameras
at that place.
So, you really don't think
they can track us down?
I don't want to risk
being at home if they do.
But if we can't get home
then...
Then the plan changes.
But we don't,
we don't have...
Yeah, so, we improvise.
Okay?
Laura?
Laura!
laura!
hey.
lo, you're back.
Breathe.
Laura:
(heavy breaths)
Breathe.
I'm, i'm okay.
You're okay.
i'm okay.
You're fine.
i am...
Oh!
(tires screech)
(loud crunch)
man:
are you okay?
Are you okay?
yeah?
Laura:
i'm okay.
Man:
we gotta get out of here.
Female bystander:
are you okay?
male crash victim:
hey! look at this!
Are you all right?
Crash vicitim:
yeah, i'm all right.
but look what you did to my car!
Come on,
come on.
i mean, look at this.
You're okay?
Hey!
(tires screech,
horn blasts)
Driver:
hey, what do you think
you're doing?!
parker:
so what substances
are you guys thinking?
Could be cocaine.
or meth.
With hallucinations?
jules:
goes with a high dose.
Parker:
you dress up,
you go out to dinner,
And then you try to rob
a pawn shop.
A fun friday night.
parker:
i don't know.
(low hum of chatter)
Taxi!
(cars honk)
(tires squeal)
winnie:
team one, we got something.
Hit and run
involving a gold sedan,
Bloor and parliament.
Subjects abandoned
their vehicle,
And flagged an oakwood taxi,
going west on bloor.
Winnie, alert all units
in the area:
Eyes open for
flashing emergency lights
On an oakwood taxi.
parker:
and no sirens.
sru intervention only.
We're considering this
a mobile hostage situation
With possible drug users.
We do not want to provoke
the subjects.
You got it, no sirens,
sru only.
And, winnie,
Let's track the gold sedan's
licence plates,
See who we're looking for.
Or we put a call
into the oakwood dispatch,
See if we can tap into
the fleet's gps.
Track 'em down that way?
Ooh, these kids
and their toys.
(traffic hums)
I don't feel...
I don't feel well;
my head is spinning.
Ramesh,
we need to go faster.
I can't legally go faster
than this, sir.
What, what are we gonna do?
Hey, no one's following us.
we're okay.
Nothing changes, lo.
Okay.
winnie:
we got a name.
we got a name on the owner
of the sedan.
Evan hewson, 28.
No criminal record.
address: 1382 emilia street.
with common-law partner
laura scheinmann, 29.
her record's clean also.
Boss, that's five minutes
away from here.
Want some help
on the profile?
Yeah, that'd be good.
i'll drop her off
and catch up with you.
parker:
copy.
You don't wanna come with?
When we do a rolling stop,
we'll need the extra vehicle.
Okay.
just as well.
Wouldn't wanna get you
in trouble
With the little lady.
Remind me,
who dumped who, again?
Here, pull over here.
What are we doing?
we can't go home.
Yeah.
but we can get
some here.
(vehicle door opens)
laura:
ev.
It'll be okay.
I'll be right back.
(door shuts)
(vehicles rumble past)
Is everything all right?
A... headache.
I-i just... have a headache.
ramesh:
your friend has gone
to get you something.
Yeah.
(machine beeps)
No, don't touch that!
Look, i know you're just trying
to do the right thing,
But there is something
that i need to tell you.
Can please...
please listen?
When i'm done,
You can do whatever it is
you need to do.
Just... please.
dispatch:
car t6211, call in.
Please listen.
dispatch:
t6211, ramesh, call in.
spike:
i've got oakwood taxi's
gps tracking patched in.
you are looking at the entire
active downtown fleet.
No unusual activity reported,
No crisis signals activated.
(car door shuts)
(vehicle speeds forward)
spike:
i don't like it.
If i got my taxi hijacked,
The first thing i'd do is send
the alarm code to dispatch.
Unless you've been
forced out of the car.
Well, then i'd have
phoned it in by now.
Maybe you're driving
under threat.
Or worse.
Thanks, ramesh.
I believe this is yours?
dispatch:
t6211, call in.
repeat. car t6211,
ramesh, calln.
Lo-lo, i love you.
Woman:
i've known them about 9 years,
since they moved in upstairs.
What kind of tenants
are they?
Quiet.
not a lot of company.
They don't play
any loud music.
Jules:
any trouble with the rent?
Woman:
uh, they missed this month.
Is that the first time?
Woman:
no, usually they call first.
um...
I don't know what's
going on with them.
Any recent changes
in their work situation?
As far as i know
He's still working
at the hospital.
He's an intern.
Uh, laura tutors english,
but that comes and goes.
Lots of dots.
They won't get far.
(phone rings)
Stainton.
What's up, inspector?
stainton:
looks like our friends
just robbed a drugstore.
Not what i was hoping to hear.
Are you aware of any
drug problems?
No, they're...
regular people.
All right, stop me
if anything rings a bell:
mood swings,
either direction,
Volatility, depression,
Confusion, secretiveness.
Yeah, secretive.
Well,
they scoot by the door
Like they don't want me
to see them.
Last time i saw them,
they looked tired.
Depressed.
You know, dark circles
under the eyes.
From st. simon's.
Is that where evan works?
Hey, sarge.
Hey, jules,
we just got word
That bonnie and clyde have
stolen syringes and morphine
From a drugstore.
Well, i just found
their home supply.
One syringe and two vials.
So, morphine.
'kay.
as addictive as heroin
And tolerance develops
real fast.
jules:
yeah, withdral's are nasty.
Irrational and violent
until they get what they need.
so, we know the substance.
Now we gotta know
the people underneath.
Okay, keep me posted.
jules:
got it.
Spike:
boss, i think i got 'em.
Car t6211.
Going west on bloor,
st passed jane street.
Dispatch says
he's not responding to radio.
Car t6211,
subject acquired.
Moving takedown,
maximum caution.
Let's move it, guys.
no sirens,
residential area.
we don't want to trigger
a high speed pursuit.
Lewis: copy.
sam: copy that.
You remember that night
at... the old mill?
(half laughs)
Your mom made you
ask me to dance.
I'm glad she did.
It's all gone by
pretty fast.
Yeah.
There it is.
(exhales)
like it was yesterday.
You see that?
Yeah.
We could come at 'em
from both sides.
wordy approach the driveway
from the west,
We'll take east with sam.
sam: copy.
we got 'em.
ed:
he's coming towards us,
let's block it off.
(vehicles speed up,
tires squeal)
Parker:
get out of the car!
do it now!
Ed:
hands up!
do it now.
move towards me.
do it now!
Wordsworth:
move forward, sir.
do it now!
parker:
hands on the hood!
do it now!
Thank you!
Nah, they're not here.
ed:
you had two passengers
in your car:
A male and female,
late 20's?
Ramesh:
yes.
Wordsworth:
well, where are they?
Ramesh:
they've gone in there.
Spike,
work the truck.
Spike:
copy.
(guests chatter loudly)
Female receptionist:
can i help you with something?
Oh, no.
Are you with
the wedding party?
Oh, we were just
looking around.
To book something
in the future or...
Uh, yeah,
to book something.
Female receptionist:
okay, well, it's little late,
But i can schedule you
a consultation.
Let's see what we have here.
Are you looking to book
a summer wedding or...?
ed:
let's go, guys.
Let's move it, let's move it,
let's move it.
What is this place?
A popular wedding spot
A target rich environment.
I got onboard security snapshots
from the taxi
coming at you.
parker:
thank you, spike.
Ed:
how're you doing?
Officer wordsworth?
wordsworth:
(quietly) yeah.
Hi.
We have a security threat
in your building.
We want you and your staff
to lock down all the exits,
But we don't wanna trigger panic
among your guests.
All right.
parker:
okay, we're looking for
a young couple
in their late twenties,
Formally dressed,
possibly under the influence.
That's most of our guests.
parker:
that help?
They were just here
a second ago.
How many rooms
in the facility?
There's six reception rooms,
they're all in use.
excuse me.
* you can trust in me
and believe in me *
* i'll see u
all the way through *
* because i'm crazy,
crazy about you *
* i used to be lonely *
* nothing special at all *
(room buzzes with chatter)
* ...now that i *
* let's have a quick review *
Female receptionist:
there's one room
just to the left
And there's another room
straight ahead.
parker:
thank you, ma'am.
Now just stay right up
against the wall,
Right here.
Guests:
(confused murmurs)
Sam:
it's all clear
back there.
There's another room
over here.
There any other entrances?
Yeah, just around
the west corner over there.
Sam, wordy.
boss?
parker:
let's go.
(big band music continues)
* i'm crazy... *
I think i saw a cop.
* crazy about you *
Evan:
okay.
Keep dancing.
follow me.
Lo.
It's up to you.
Same plan,
just faster.
Get out now!
let's move.
We gotta hold 'em back.
Mister, out.
Nobody move!
(shot fires,
guests scream and holler)
evan:
stop! don't move!
(panicked screams)
All of you, over here!
Over here! over here!
now!
Parker:
it's all right,
just do as he says!
evan:
all right, link arms.
Link arms. stay together
and don't look back.
parker:
evan hewson,
laura scheinmann,
this is greg parker.
I'm with the police
strategic response unit.
spike:
8:44 pm,
Armed hostage taking.
sergeant parker begins
negotiation
with subjects evan hewson
and laura scheinmann.
parker:
and we're gonna talk
and we're gonna...
figure a way out of this.
how does that sound?
(music continues to play)
* crazy for you *
parker:
evan, i'm gonna turn
the music off,
So i can hear
what you have to say.
okay?
mr. d.j.?!
turn the music off
and get outta here!
(music shuts off abruptly)
parker:
thank you.
Okay, evan and laura?
you wanna take about
what brought us here today?
Get it ready.
What do you mean?
Parker: evan?
evan: keep your distance!
Sierra one, in position.
(light switch clicks)
Landlord:
whoa.
Oh my god, that's me.
Boss, there's more to this.
What do you have?
jules:
laura's office.
Battlefield. reminders.
sticky notes everywhere
like she's fighting
to remember stuff,
Like she's, uh...
like she's losing it.
Okay, go through it,
jules.
see if we can find out what
she's trying not to forget.
Got it.
Spe,
bring in the cabbie.
And see if you can
track down any family.
Copy.
I-i don't recognize
these people.
do you know who they are?
evan:
it's just you and me, lo.
What are you doing
with a gun?
Evan:
no, no.
Parker:
is everything okay, evan?
laura:
i wanna go home.
I wanna go home.
(crying)
I wanna go...
(breaks down into tears)
'cause it looks like laura
could use some help.
I hear you two stopped off
at a pharmacy,
you picked up some things.
you wanna talk about that?
sam:
sierra one, no shot.
obstruction.
jules:
hey, sarge,
i got an appointment
four days ago
At st simon's hospital.
(reading)
"personal."
With a phone number
for a dr. fylin.
Give me the number,
jules.
You know, i really want to get
your friend some help, evan.
Evan:
we don't need your help!
We just need to be
left alone!
Okay, why's that?
Just...
10 minutes.
We just need 10 minutes,
that's it.
10 minutes alone...
Then idoesn't matter.
Tell me what that means,
evan.
ed:
so you weren't driving
under duress?
They didn't threaten you?
No, sir.
Were they using drugs?
no.
You see a lot of people
go through your cab, right?
What's your take
on theses two?
I know what people
who are high look like.
How they smell,
how they talk.
These two...
Right, go on.
She said
they were short on time.
it was their last night.
They wanted to dance together.
They wanted to dance
and that's it?
The rest is not for me
to say.
Okay.
guys, the cab driver's
saying the same thing
That the couple
in the pawn shop said;
That they are "short on time."
spike:
boss, she's not on morphine,
it's not about getting high.
That doctor's appointment?
it was with a neurology clinic.
It took a bit of twisting,
But i got dr fylin
to release the diagnosis.
Laura has cjd.
creuzfeld-jakob disease.
Slurred speech, dizziness,
hallucinations.
A brain disorder.
Spike,
i need to know more.
I'm on it.
(keyboard keys clack)
Jules, how much morphine
is in those vials?
120 milligrams.
That's a lethal dose.
spike:
she has spontaneous cjd.
it's very rare.
It's like one in a million.
Your brain starts
literally disintegrating.
there's no treatment,
there's no known cure.
You can go from diagnosis
to death
In the space of two weeks.
It gets worse by the day.
laura's losing her memory,
her balance,
Her motor skills,
all her major brain functions.
Ed:
cab driver said
all they wanted to do was dance.
And then they were gonna
go home for the morphine
And that's how the night
was supposedo enen
Yeah.
but they couldn't go home,
So he robbed a pharmacy.
parker:
and now he's asking
for 10 minutes.
10 minutes for the dose
to take effect.
sam, keep your eyes on him.
both of 'em.
sam:
copy.
(exhales forcefully)
Laura,
can you hear me?
i'm getting a better
understanding of...
At you went through today.
we know you're sick.
Are you back?
yeah.
Parker:
i can't imagine
what that must be like.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna keep him talking.
Can you get it ready,
can you do that, lo?
Yeah.
Parker:
that you and evan
are very strong
And you're very brave.
You're not gonna take us
apart.
Boss, she's opening her bag.
What do you see?
sam:
she's doing something
inside it.
It's the morphine.
they're cutting to the chase.
Ed, what's your take?
Sam, you got the shot?
sam:
multiple hostages,
it's high-risk.
Less lethal,
n you do it?
Do we wanna do it?
There's a risk
we hit the hostages.
We go less lethal,
we're looking at an injury.
We let her do
what she wants to do
And we are looking
at a death.
we can't let her kill herself.
Yeah, copy.
Morphine's painless.
What are you saying,
spike?
Isn't this her life,
what's left of it?
I'm just saying maybe we should
be looking the other way?
Maybe it's better we let her
have what she wants.
Can't do it.
We interfere,
subject could start shooting.
So we put lives at risk
To save somebody
who's already dying?
ed:
our job's to save lives.
We're cops,
we're not judges.
Boss?
Eddie's right.
we put it in play.
jules.
Yeah, boss?
parker:
get frank mcandrew
on the phone.
Tell him this:
I'd like to solicit
his legal opinion here
On these two
staying together,
based on
compassionate grounds.
if she has two weeks to live,
then...
They're not gonna spend it
apart.
Got it.
parker:
and when i say opinion,
I mean he calls
his favourite judge
And he works his famous
powers of persuasion.
You hear me?
ed:
we take the shot,
he will accelerate,
He's still armed.
We can use the distraction
to clear the hostages.
Copy that.
She's filling the syringe.
Sam, take the shot
if you see it.
You ready, lo?
I'm ready.
(shot fires)
Laura:
no, no, no
ed:
keep the weapon lowered, evan.
just keep it down.
Laura: no!
ed: that's it.
Evan:
what did you do?
Parker:
i'm sorry we had to do that,
evan.
You won't let them take us!
Stay back!
Laura:
what're we gonna do?
Evan?
It's okay.
lo-lo, it's okay.
It's okay,
we'll figure a way out.
Just put the gun
on the floor, evan.
Don't tell me
what to do!
We're gonna talk
through this,
But you gotta look at me.
you gotta look at me, evan.
No!
Evan.
Do it.
(gun hammer clicks)
(sobs) do it.
Evan!
Please!
Laura...
Please?
Just give 'em space.
Sam, switch to lethal.
Copy.
This is crazy.
my son is not a drug user.
(stammers)
he does not rob stores.
I know that, mrs. hewson,
i need you to say calm
Because i need you
to help me help evan.
evan and laura have known
each other for a long time?
13 years.
13 years?
this is where they met.
The best thing that
ever happened to him.
Okay, i'm really sorry,
But i have tell you some
sad news about laura.
I got the solution.
evan, please.
do it.
Please...
parker:
evan, don't do that!
Please!
(whimpering)
please...
Thank you, evan,
that's the right choice.
If that gun goes up
again...
I hear you.
Evan, please!
Evan, i'm sorry for what's
going on in your life
and i really want to help you,
but i gotta tell you,
That we can't let you
hurt laura.
laura:
no.
I don't get to make
many choices anymore,
But this choice is mine.
we... we've talked about it
for 4 days, 4 nights.
We, we made a video,
it's at home,
So that when i'm gone,
evan won't be blamed.
Oh god.
This is why.
Mrs. hewson...
Last week...
he came to see me.
Just dropped in,
wanted to go for a walk.
(chokes up)
He held my hand.
He never does that
any more.
He told me he loved me
like it was goodbye.
Why would he do that?!
Jules, how much morphine
did you find at their place?
How many doses?
Oh god. oh god.
Evan:
i'm not gonna break
my promise.
She gets everything
she wants today.
spike:
2 vials,
120 milligrams each.
Copy, spike.
boss?
Yeah, i heard it.
You guys have known each other
for a long time, right?
About 13 years.
So, since you were, what?
Fifteen.
parker:
fifteen; that's a long time.
That's a lifetime.
that's...
That's a lot of memories.
Laura, i know...
I know something about memories,
And i know a little something
about what happens
When someone shoots
someone else.
It's not like you
think it is,
It's horrible.
it's messy as hell.
and when...
you see something like that,
That image stays
in your head.
Don't listen to him,
lo.
parker:
and what you're asking evan
to do,
It's gonna be the last memory
he has of you,
It's gonna be the last thing
he sees every night
Before he goes to sleep.
Don't believe him.
there's lots i'm gonna see
When i close my eyes
at night, okay?
But i gotta be honest with you,
laura,
It's not gonna get that far.
You see, my team...
is gonna shoot evan
before he shoots you.
(whimpers)
It's the law.
It's our job...
To not let him do that.
I'm take my chances.
ed:
did laura know about the last
part of your plan here, evan?
The part where you intended
to use
That second dose of morphine
on yourself?
Did she know that?
120 milligrams is a lethal dose.
Now you knew that,
right?
You knew that that's
what it would take,
Did you tell her
that you had a second vial?
did you tell her
you were gonna kill yourself?
that you were gonna go
with her,
Did you tell her that?
Ev?
But why?
ed: (quietly)
hold off, guys.
let's give 'em some space.
I can't.
I don't want to.
I don't want to live
without you, lo.
You have to, okay?
You have to.
Please.
I can't,
i can't.
You have so much time
still.
Your mom,
she needs you and...
And your family needs you.
You are gonna love
someone else some day.
No, that's not gonna happen.
Yes it is.
Ev, how am i gonna live on
if you don't live?
jules:
sarge.
i just heard back
from mcandrew,
He thinks they can swing it.
Copy that.
good work, eddie.
Evan?
No matter how much time
you have left,
Two days or two weeks,
We're gonna make sure
the two of you stay together.
We're not gonna
split you up.
Laura:
are you with me?
(breathes a sigh of relief)
So that's the story.
I'm sorry, mom, dad,
All you guys,
for not giving any...
Advance warning.
* i will be here
by your side *
laura:
i guess i didn't really
get much warning myself.
* no need to be afraid *
laura:
i just don't want a fuss.
you know, you get that,
right?
* close your eyes,
close your eyes *
I don't want pity or...
Two weeks of goodbyes.
* and when you do *
* i look at you and wonder *
* i wonder *
* can you truly be mine? *
* be mine *
Sync by honeybunny @addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com