don't tell me what to do.
Want to take out your phone?
Take a little video?
You could show all of your friends.Wouldn't that just be hilarious?
No,I don't,billy.
Billy...
third door,north end,west side.
You know my name?
See,that's funny to me.
-Copy that. -What do you usually call me?
Tell me.
Sam,jules.
What do you call me?
He's upstairs.We're headed up.
****
Can I see?
yeah,sure.
It's amazing.
Kind of looks like a map or something.
It kind of is,I guess.
Like,you know when you see those guys on tv with those big screens behind them,
and they have,like,that map with a big snowflake on it?
See,what I think it would be really cool is if we saw the people-- l
ike,drawings of,like,little people,of course,but...
and they're,like,walking around being like,"where are my gloves?
" Or like,"where's my scarf?
" Or like,"where's my jacket?
" well,what's your map about?
I don't know.
My life,or something.
It sounds really stupid when I say it out loud though.
Is that you?
Seriously,billy,it's really good.
That's the thing about art class,you know.
Like,when I'm there,I just...I feel happy.
It's the only time I really feel like that.
I'll see you later,okay?
Hey,what's going on?
-Nothing. -Nothing?
Sorry about the detour.
Sleeping beauty there couldn't get up in time to take the bus this morning.
No worries.
Teenagers and mornings-- not a good fit.
Well,teenagers and anything-- not a good fit.
how's school going,clark?
Clark?
What?
Ed: Mr.Parker's talking to you.
Clark: I'm listening to music.
Ed: Can't you just tell him how school's going.
Parker: It's okay.
School's fine.
That's good.
-See ya,mr.Parker.
-Good to see you,clark.
"Thanks for the ride,dad.
" that takes some patience,huh?
Yeah,you have no idea.
Yeah.
Yeah,I'm lucky I guess.
Yo,k-way.
-Girl: Hey,billy.
-Oh,come on,buddy,don't be rude.
Scott,leave him alone.
Where you headed?
Uh,the corner store.
Nutritious lunch?Cookies and chips?
-stop it.
-Scott: Stop what?
You're looking after k-way here?Your little artist buddy?
Come on.I was going to give him some lunch money.
-God,scott!
-What's your problem?
-I don't have a problem. -Hey,let her go.
-Excuse me?
-I said let her go.
I heard what you said.
-Then let her go.
-Guys,come on.
Or else?
-There's no "or else.
-" Really?
Boy: Scott...
'cause I kind of believe in "or else.
-Girl: Scott!
-Don't talk to me or else.
Or like,uh,stay out of my business or else.
-Boy: Get him!
-Nice one.
I didn't think gay boys could fight.
I'm not gay!
Why are you hitting yourself,huh?
-Why are you hitting yourself?
-Girl: Scott!
Oh,ouch.It's got to hurt.
-Tony?
-It's priceless.
Come on,smile,gay boy.
-Girl: Tony,stop it!
-Smile.
Just say it.We all know the truth-- you're a little piece of garbage.
-That's why you're eating
-girl: Scott!
Little piece of garbage.
You're doing great,k-way.
You're doing great.
-Stop it!
-Scott: He'll say it,he's gay.
-I'm not gay!
-Say it!
: I'M...I'm gay.
And "I'm a piece of garbage.
" And I-I'm a piece of garbage.
What a loser.
Scott!
give me that.
It's funny.
to-- full friends list.
Subject-- "k-way eats garbage.
Sending.
Done.
Later,k-way.
Ella.
trace?
Oh,it's you.
shouldn't you be at school?
get me a beer.
What the hell are you doing?Get me a beer.
decent?
Yeah.
So?
First day back.You nervous?
Nah.
So I heard,uh,I heard you took some time off.
Beaches and margaritas?
Yeah,a little r & R.
But I also went back to the base.
Really?
Wow,I thought,uh,I thought you and your dad...
when the general summons,you don't say no.
what was that about?
Well,he pulled some strings and he wants me back in the military where I can really make a difference.
Nice.
What did you say?
I said I can make a difference here.
Good for you.
He thought he heard me wrong,'cause it didn't sound like "yes,sir.
" Anyways,dealing with my dad,that was...
that was the easy part.
What was the hard part?
When my mom asked when she gets to meet you.
Each fall the weather changes...
obviously.
Cool winds are being pushed south,but the atlantic ocean is still warm from the summer.
This makes for...can I help you?
If you're not in this class,you'll have to wait till the bell rings.
will you please leave my classroom...
don't touch me,okay?
I have no intention of touching you.
But you,sir,are disrupting my class.
Hey,buddy...
don't touch me.I'm just trying to find somebody,okay?
-What's your problem? -I don't have a problem!
You're not even in this class,you loser.So get out of here.
Don't call me that!
teacher: Get down!Get down!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-ещещ╥и
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
flashpiont
Season 02 Episode 11
Bee-utiful parker: Okay,last,but certainly not least,tomorrow a big drill with team five.
And I for one am firmly anticipating a team one victory.
-You got that right. -That's right.
Which is why we're going to spend the rest of this afternoon training in gear with weapons in the sixth story building
we're going to use for tomorrow's training.
Training for a training exercise?
We play to win,mr.Scarlatti.We play to win.
team one,hot call.We have an active shooter at a high school.
Two injured.First responders on their way.
Jules,you ready for this?
48 days in phyiso,four hours a day at the gym,double time at the range.
Yeah,I think I'm ready.
Let's go make a difference.
parker: Okay,guys,three exits.
North,west,cafeteria to the left.
Lewis: We got cops at all three doors.
Princil's inside,first room othe le.
Okay,where are my first responders?
Following protocol apparently.
Lock down,intelligence.
Subjects-- how many?Where they at?
We've got one gunman,looks like a student.
Two injuries.That's all we know for now.
No further shots fired-- that's a good thin?
Right ed: Depends.
-I'm principal chivali.
-Hello,ma'am.
I got the alert from room 312.
We used a teacher's intercom-- predetermined code word.
-Which is? -"Code red.
-Sounds a little obvious,I know.
-What happens with a code red?
It means we follow the drill.But the teachers know it's the real deal because it hasn't been prearranged.
Lock the doors.Make sure any glass is covered.Close the blinds.
Get the desks in a barricade in the corner.Students behind the desks.
As far as most of the students know,this is still just a drill.
We do them every few months.
But all these kids have cell phones.
They're going to be calling and texting each other.
Who knows what they're saying,what they know.
That's why we're going to do this quickly,keep it calm.
-You heard from tony? -No,I can't get through.
Clear them out.
Out of the way,guys.Out of the way.Back it up.
Police.Let them in.
Spike: Sru on the scene,1:37 P.M.Two shots fired at approximately 1:21 P.M.
Ma'am.
Ma'am,where did the first responders go?
The,uh,first officers on the scene.
I don't know.They just went in.
We got one on each door,two heading up to the third floor.
Okay,eddie.
Sru only.We got to control this,okay?
Ma'am,you got any further idea who we're dealing with here?
I mean,with all the cell phones,somebody must have seen something.
Yeah,male,caucasian,15 to 17,hoodie,medium height.
Definitely a wellesley student.Possibly a sophomore,but that wasn't confirmed.
Okay,so,uh,white kid in a hoodie.
Yeah,no,I know.It sounds like half the kids in my school.
This is sergeant greg parker with the sru.
-All first responders within the school.
-Everybody in.
Subject is caucasian,15 to 17,medium height,wearing a hoodie.
Do not engage.
Come back to the principal's office,which is considered command post,asap.
-Officer: Price,we got to move.
-Come on,everybody in.Golet's
.Price,come on.They want us at command post.
Price: Okay,lock that door.
15 minutes,no further shots fired.
Parker: Good.
Okay,let's lock down the exterior.Uniform on every door.
All the kids that are already outside,let's contain them in the parking lot.
Sam and jules are bravo team.Let's get a lay of the land.
Lou,you're with cops and first responders.
Spike,you're with me.
Let's monitor all cell phone chatter.
Let's stay on the intercom.Let's keep the classrooms calm.
No one in or out unless they're being escorted by the police.
Copy.
All right,eddie.
Injured first-- let's get them safe and any information we can on the subject,anything at all.
All right.Let's go.
just go to class.
Answer your stupid phone; I don't care.
It's geography.It's mrs.Hilton.
She's,like,a hundred years old; she won't even notice.
If you have something to say.
I don't want to do this anymore.
One month,that's what it's been.
One month going out with you,and I don't even feel like myself anymore.
Okay.
You beat the crap out of my friend.
No,I was sending him a message,all right?
That guy was trying to get between us.
-He was helping me!
-You don't need help from a guy like that.
Guy like what?
-That guy is...
-what?
Weird?A big loser?
Yeah,well,so was I.
Until a month ago,when you decided that I was worth the time of day.
God,at least,at least he's interesting.
-He's smart.
-Okay,yeah,see,there you go.
Thank you very much.
He's smart and I'm what?
Just some jarhead football player?
So sorry I don't do arts and crafts.
Let's just go.
Mrs.Hilton,it's the police.
My name's ed lane.I'm with the strategic response unit.
We need you to open the door.
Ma'am,please open the door.We understand you've got some kids in trouble in there.
We're here to get them out.
Thanks,ma'am.
They're over here.
Marcus paley and rachel heintzman.She's not moving.
Marcus,you okay?
Wordy: How's rachel doing?
Um,she passed out about five minutes ago.
Look,I-I'm fine,I swear.
Please,just get her out of here.
That's exactly what we're gonna do.
You okay if we come back for you?
Okay,we need you to stay calm,stay warm,conserve your energy.
Keep this tight.Watch your hands.
It's my fault.
I called him "loser," and he went nuts.
I don't even know who he is.
I'm sorry.
-It's okay. -So sorry.
It's okay,marcus.It's not your fault.
Guys,guys,we know this is a dangerous situation.
And we're gonna be back for you just as soon as we can,okay?
but right now,the safest place for you to be is right here with the lights out and doors locked.
You're doing everything right.
You have any idea who this kid was?
Jen thinks he mightbe in tenth grade,but we just couldn't see.
Okay,anybody-anybody have A...
have a yearbook?
-Here. -Good.
All right,while we're gone,I want you guys to look through that book,
see if you can identify this kid,okay?
We're gonna be right back for you.
Meantime,we're gonna get rachel to a hospital.You guys are doing great.
Wordy.
We got to get her out to the paramedics.They can't come in under lockdown.
Mrs.Hilton.
Keep this door locked,okay?
Keep the door locked.
Guys,the news is spreading.Kids are texting each other.
The phones are jamming with 911 calls.
-Shooter hasn't been active in...
-18 minutes.
Good.Spike,stay on the chatter.
Hey,there's a kid up there with a gun.We got to get up there as soon as possible.
Every second counts.
Parker: Which is why we're slowing down movement until we get further intelligence.
See,right now,the subject is inactive.
And by "the subject," you mean the gunman.
Zero fatalities,two injuries.Sounds like they were unplanned.
Which affects our subject profile,which affects our response.
Okay,and what about the injured?
We're on it!Sir.
Boss,I'm not liking this cafeteria.
It's too open.
Sitting ducks.
Parker: Yeah,agreed.Let's evacuate the lunchroom.
And,uh,any stray kids you find in the hallway,get them into classrooms,
safe and out of the way.
spike,we need to know who this kid is and what he wants.
I'm on it,boss.
Parker: Alpha team?
-Ed: Almost back.
-Copy.
Boss,we're headed to the lchroom.
Police!Don't move!
-I said don't move!
-Jules.Show me your hands.
Step outside.Stand up and turn around.
Put your hands on the counter.
Okay,pal.You're gonna be okay.
We're gonna take you to a place where someone's gonna ask you a few questions.
what are you doing?There's a guy in the school,and he's got a gun!
-Let us in!
-They can't!
Remember the drills?The doors stay locked.
-Once they're locked...
-lunchroom.We go to the cafeteria.
No,we'd have to cross the school.
Make a run for the front doors.
we're getting reports of a possible gunshot near the gym.
We're getting a ton of cell phone chatter.
This is no longer a drill.The kids inside know what's happening.
Okay,boss,wee at the west door.
How's she doing?
Not good.Let's go.
Teacher confirmed an id of the subject from the yearbook,eddie.
Billy dresden,16 years old,tenth grade.
We're trying to reach his parents now.
Any idea what he wants?
-Spike?
-Nothing firm beyond the id.
"Huge loser,loner,total freak.
"Eats alone,never talks to anyone,always wears the same clothes.
" I found a picture.
Let's start at the gym.If he's gone active...
you go in hard.
Parker: Bravo team,what's your 20?
Cafeteria's clear.
-Maybe not.
-Okay,go careful.
We think the subject's on the first floor.
All right,guys.We've got you.We're going to move slow and calm.
You're going to follow us.
Boss,we've got about six in here.We can't contain it.
We're going to take them out.
-Copy.
-Lou,we got six kids coming out the west door.
Everyone's out.Cafeteria's clear.
Alpha team's headed to the gym.Bravo team stays east.Copy that.
You guys are back in.
Ella,where the hell are you going?
I don't know where else to go.
Okay,we just have to hide until it's over.
Okay.
Behind here.
Billy.
Well,this kid hasn't killed anyone yet.
He's had ample opportunity.
Nothing on the internet.No creepy photos.
No "look at me and my gun" stuff.
Classic domestic scenario.Regent park,projects,poverty...
mom's unemployed,dad's got a criminal record.
Drugs,couple of destic assaults on the mother.
Probably where he got the gun.
Yeah,well,a kid like this,no money,horrible home life,stuck in a fancy-pants high school?
It's a perfect storm.
It's still no excuse.
-This is gina maxton.
-Gina,hi.
-This is greg parker.
-Hi,gina.
I understand you know billy dresden.
From art class.
So,what happened?
Some guys near the field,football guys mostly,they were shoving him around.
They were...putting garbage in his face and stuff.
Do you know who was doing it?
It's okay.
Gina.This is really important.
Tony sent this to everyone.
-Billy: Please!
-Scott: He's gay.He'll sayt.
-No.
-Scott: Say it!
I'm gay.
Scott: And you're a little piece of garbage.
Billy: And I-I'M...
I'm a piece of garbage.
-Tony who?
-Tony price.
Gina: But it was scott mink,mostly.
Alex rosati.
Okay.
Thank you,gina,for coming forward.
All right.Let's get the locations for all three subjects.
If this is target-specific...
could be good news.
Eddie,this may be target-specific.
Stand by for locations.
-Good news how-?
-It means he might be looking for specific individuals.
Better if it's not random.It's easier to contain.
I'm pulling up the schedules on all three names.
Buddy,you got to leave this scene.
You're in big trouble if they find out tony's your son.
Get out of here.
Now.
Got 'em!
Okay,eddie.You ready?
Gym's clear.We're ready.
Tony!
I-I-I just need to talk to you,okay?
I know you're in there!
please.We were just getting a projector,but they locked the door.
Tony,come out,okay?
Come out.
please.
-Please don't hurt me.
-don't tell me what to do.
You've been doing that for two years now.
All of you.
But you don't get to do that anymore.
Tony,where the hell are you?
I...look,it's dad.I don't t re whayou did.
Just please answer the phone.
Uhjusti'm going up to the command post.
Want to take out your phone?
Take a little video?Some photos?
You can show all of your friends.Wouldn't that just be hilarious?
No,I don't,billy.
Billy?
You know my name?
See,that's funny to me.
Because what do you usually call me?Tell me.
What do you call me?What do you call me?
It's not me that calls you that,billy.
Please.
-Please.
-Don't move!
Keep your hands up and go down the hallway.
Go.
And give me your phone.
-Sam,jules.
-Outside the cafeteria.
First floor looks clean.
See you on two.
busy.
How can 911 be busy?
Scott.No one knows we are here,okay?
-It's fine.
-I know,I know.It's just...
who would do this?
Yeah,I know.Who would be so vicious?
I'll keep trying.
Guys,we're on the second floor.
Right there.Right there.
He took tony down the hall.
-Which way did he go?
-That way.
-I'm afraid he's going to hurt him
-calm down.Calm down.
We need you to stay right here.We're going to send somebody back for you.Right there.
Spike,student on second floor needs retrieval.We are in pursuit of subject.
say it,tony.
Say it.
: I'm sorry.
I don't believe you.
I am.I'm sorry.
Smile,tony.
I'm so sorry.
You're on camera.
Please.Don't hurt me.
: Team one,the situation has just escalated.
We have an active shooter.It's a new deal.
Spike: Alpha team,respond.Are you in the vicinity of the gunfire?
Where are you guys?
North stairwell.
One shot fired.
Subject may be above us.
Kids are saying he may have a hostage,tony price,one of the targets.
If you need to,you take him down.
Boss,we're heading upstairs.We're on the move.
Boss?911's patched in a relevant caller.
Ella brandt,tenth grade.Claims she knows the subject.
: Ella?
Ella,hi,this is sergeant parker.I'm with the police.Where are you?
Um,we're hiding.
We're okay.I just...
it's billy,isn't it?
How do you know billy,ella?
He's my friend.
I mean,he probably won't be after today.
Parker: Because of what's happening?
No.Because of what happened to him.
tony : I'm sorry.
-Billy : I don't believe you.
-Tony: I am!
: I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.Please.
-Are you scared?
-Please!
Are you sad right now?Because that'S...
okay,ella.You just tell me where you are.We'll come get you.We can talk about this in person.
He is a good person.
He wouldn't hurt anyone.
At least,he wouldn't have.
I just...I just wish...
I should have done something.I could have changed this.
No.This isn't your fault,honey.
When he was getting the crap kicked out of him,I didn't have to just stand there like some idiot
while the biggest jerk in school was going after him.
He was standing up for me.
He was defending me.
Tony!
Tony?
Ella,you said "we" before.
Who are you with?How many people?
I'm going to make sure that one of my team gets to you as soon as we can.
Just tell me where you are.
: Oh,my god.
What's happening?
-He's here.
-Parker: Who?
Ella: Billy.
El,where are you?
Ella : I'm in the art department.
Paart dertment.You stay put.
We're sending somebody right now.
Guys,we got a 20 on our subject.Fourth floor,room 409.
Art department.On the south side.
Alerting first responders.
We got a 20 on billy dresden.No interference,okay?
Keep it tight.We're going to close off the fourth floor.
I'm going to go talk to him.
What?
Ella,no.You stay right where you are.
You stay right where you are.
He is my friend.
I need you to believe me.
He's a good person.
Ella.
: Can you hear me?
: Stay here.
-Billy?
-Ella?
What-what are you doing?
Ella: I don't know.
What are you doing?
I just...
I just wanted to see what I'd done.
You know,it's funny,sometimes you think something's gonna work out.
Even if it's not beautiful,you at least think that it's gonna work.
And then...
a few hours later,you come back and you see that it...
it's nothing.
It just doesn't work.
Ella: I think I know what you mean.
Billy: You do?
Ella: Sure.
I feel like that all the time.
Okay,guys,she's talking to him; he seems responsive.
Alpha team,what's your 20?
We're outside 409.
Window's covered-- we don't have eyes.
We can be in there in a split second.
Copy.Waiting on bravo.
Bravo team,what's your 20?
We're on our way.
How many doors in the room?
Two-- main door and a rear door.
Sam and jules,head for the rear.
Third door,north end,west side.
Copy that.
So,what's bugging you?
What's bugging me?
About the painting.
You came up here to see the painting,right?
It doesn't go anywhere,it's just...
there's no point to it,there's no place for it to go.
It's just...
I-it's just scared.
But you're not scared of me.
I just wanted somebody to care!
Some-somebody to apologize.
It's so stupid,and...
I just made it so much worse.
I sent...
a video out to all of tony's friends.
I don't even know what I'm doing!
Billy...
everyone is scared.
You know what happened after lunch hour?
What?
I told scott that I...
couldn't go out with him anymore.
I think you scare him.
I think you freak him out because you're smart and you're interesting.
And because I like you.
He feels stupid,and he acts like a jerk,but it's not your fault.
It's his.
Billy...
it is not your fault.
This whole day,it shouldn't have happened.
I wish I could take it back,I really do.
Yeah.Me,too.
I-I'm sorry.
No,it's okay.
Hey.
I'm right here with you.
Hey,you and me,together.
Parker: Okay,he's showing remorse.He's de-escalating.
We got to let them play it out.
Okay,why don't we just go talk to them.
Okay?
But you got to put that down.
Just put it down on the table,and then we'll go and talk to them together.
Yeah?
-Okay.
-Boss.
Sam,jules.
Almost there.
Are you good?
Okay,'cause I'm right here.
Every step I am right here.
Promise?
I promise.
Just put it down.
Put it down on the table,and then we'll go.
Okay?
It's gonna be okay.
She's walking him out.
We're getting him out.
who's there?Who's there?
Scott?What?You lied to me!
-No,no,she didn't!
-Okay,we've got a third party in there.
Go in!Now!
Billy.Billy,don't worry about him.
That's not who you need to be worrying about right now.
Where's tony?
I-I don't know.
Look at me we heard gunfire,billy.
Ella: Billy...
please.Please.
I just wanted you to be okay.
I just wanted us both to be ay.
drop your weapon!
Put the gun down!Now!
Do it now!Put the gun down!
Get down!Get down now!
I repeat: Subject's contained,he has been shot.
Guys,let's get this kid out of here.He's still breathing.Jules?
Ella,it's okay,sweetheart.
It's okay,you're safe.Juith les.That's it.
Ella?
Ella: Get away from me!
Down on your knees,hands behind your back.
Why?What did i do?
Just do it,please,sir.
My son tony was one of the targets.
He killed my boy.
Come on,let's go.
Yeah,put him on.
Somebody wants to talk to you.
-Dad?
-Tony?
I'm okay.
: Tony,you're okay...
he just wanted me to say I'm sorry.
Tony...
price: Oh,my god.Oh,my god.
I've got a son; he's in high school,too.So I get it,all right?
I...I get it.
but this is our job,and you got to let us do it.
I'm sorry.
Yeah,me,too,buddy.
Me,too.
son of a bitch.
* a million tears a million codes one-fifteen *
* no where to go you point your finger to the moon *
* it looks like rain coming soon *
* I figured all my worst fears believe in childlike heroes *
* but I don't want to go that way *
* surrender hope again *
* I don't want to go that way surrender hope *
* and faith again *
boss,this is ella.
Ella,hey.
I'm greg.I was on the phone with you.
You did great.
You did everything right.
* Your blood,your fire your kiss good night*.
billy's on his way to st Mike'S.
He's gonna make it.
Because you were there to help him.
'Cause you were there.
I think that's your mom.I think she's waiting for you.
You want to turn around and tell me if that's your mom?
Is that your mom?
Yeah.
You go,go on.
* The fire linger and fade away *
* the shadows run from yesterday like everyone *
welcome back.
* your blood,your fire your kiss *
* good night your words and touch *
* they might be mine *
* I feel this love could cross the sand *
* I want to feel that way oh,*
* don't want to feel that way oh,*
* don't make me feel that way oh,*
* d't want to feel that way *
* I'm breaking through these walls of steel pushing that *
* wall for something real I'm falling far and faster still wake up,*
* wake up wake up,wake...*
you can't keep doing this to yourself.
I miss my boy.
I know.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents