We're not a threat, We're salvation,
The world will have to deal with us.
Previously on The 4400:
I see you've been spending
a lot of time With ShaWn,
People see her, they see a woman.
A beautiful woman.
And they might forget that inside
she's just a little girl.
I'm glad she has you around
to be a friend,
You killed people.
That's not what we discussed
when you approached me.
We are in a war.
It's gonna cost money.
You sold us out.
I'm very disappointed in you, Shawn,
and I'm afraid I can't forgive you.
Diana Skouris,
your adoption of Maia Rutledge
is hereby complete,
legal, and binding,
Ms. Skouris, my name is Sarah.
I'm Maia's sister.
Do you see the future more clearly
since you stopped taking the inhibitor?
- Who are you?
- I'm Lindsey.
I'm a part of her collection.
We all are.
Tyler! Duncan!
You've been here
ever since you Walked
through the front door of my house,
You're in the future.
We had to bring you here, Maia,
you and your friends.
Before we put you back
in your new time,
we'll make you forget your mother.
Please, don't!
They'll forget you too,
Hey.
Marco, they're beautiful.
How did you know I like anemones?
You remember
that bad ltalian restaurant?
I asked you what your favorite
flower was, and you said:
Anemones.
Most guys don't even listen
to table talk.
You not only heard me,
you remembered.
Do you know how lucky
you're gonna get tonight?
Then my plan is working.
I thought it was just gonna be
the two of us.
It is.
Then who is the other plate for?
Di?
I don't know what I was thinking.
- Are you having fun?
- Of course, I'm having fun.
You sure you don't want
a turn at the wheel?
It's your fantasy.
Okay, honey. Hold on.
Look out!
- You all right?
- I think so.
- You saw her too, right?
- Of course, I did.
Why would a girl
be in the middle of the road?
- I have no idea.
- A joy ride in the country.
That's what we agreed on, right?
A great car, a deserted road.
Hitting some kid at 80 miles plus?
Where the hell does that come in?
What happened to her?!
Thomas.
Hey!
Hey. Hey.
Hey, what...? You...?
You okay?
Who was she?
I have no idea.
How many times
have we done this?
Gone away in one
of these fantasy worlds you create?
- A dozen times? Two dozen?
- At least.
And these worlds,
they always feel real.
Except this time, a girl without a face
appears out of nowhere.
It felt more like a nightmare.
But something like that was bound
to happen sooner or later.
I build these worlds
out of our memories.
I guess this time I dredged up
something incomplete.
A fragment of something.
A sort of mental hiccup.
Okay, but this girl?
Is she part of my memory or yours?
Yours, mine, both.
There's no way to know, is there?
One of us might have
seen her picture in a book,
or seen her in the street.
Yeah, we just
don't remember her face.
It might have just been a glimpse.
Yeah, well,
that glimpse pretty much
ruined our night.
Well, tomorrow night will be better.
I promise.
Anywhere you wanna go,
anywhere we wanna go,
- and anything we wanna do.
- You know, for his 1 2th birthday
I took Kyle fishing
up at the Dosewallips River.
I thought maybe the three
of us could go there.
That sounds great.
And maybe this time we could
actually catch some fish.
Okay.
I don't know what's wrong
with my bedroom.
Or yours for that matter.
We've already done it there
a bunch of times.
Experts say you should do
adventurous things
to keep relationships
more interesting.
They say that, huh?
What could be more adventurous
than a quickie in the staircase?
Did you switch
from Encyclopaedia Britannica
to Cosmo magazine or something?
What--?
Well, I read lots of stuff.
- I'll take the elevator.
- Devon.
How embarrassing for her.
Isabelle, just stop! Just...
What's the matter, Shawn?
What's wrong?
She's not gonna tell my father.
- She'd be too afraid of me.
- lsabelle.
She's gonna tell someone,
and then they'll tell someone else.
And then, everybody's gonna know.
Where's your partner?
Late.
A 4400, Christopher Dubov, was
attacked outside his home last night.
I wanna know if we're looking
at a hate crime.
It says he's a lawyer
at Teller and Dutch.
That's a major mergers
and acquisitions firm.
They've been all over
the financial pages this year.
Yeah, which makes him
a high profile 4400.
A target for somebody
looking to make a point.
No, it makes him a corporate raider
who's put a lot of people
in the unemployment line.
His 4400 status isn't the only motive
someone might have to attack him.
Just talk to him.
See if he can write you up a list.
- Oh, alarm clock need new batteries?
- No, it's a crappy morning.
Are you opening up a newsstand?
No. Just a project
that I'm working on.
So, what do we got?
Yeah, you could call it a hate crime.
My son, Michael, certainly hates me.
Your son did this to you, Mr. Dubov?
His mom and I split up.
He blames me.
I'm the one who introduced her to Bob,
her new husband.
I knew they belonged together.
I could smell it.
- I'm not sure I follow.
- It's my ability.
It showed up once I stopped taking
the promicin inhibitor.
I can smell pheromones.
You mean the stuff people put out
to attract other people?
- Weird, huh?
- Things between my wife and l
haven't been too good for a while.
Then I met Bob.
He's my new dentist.
Right away, there was
something familiar about him.
Then I realized what it was.
He smelled just like Caroline.
So I made her an appointment.
I had to know whether
or not they belonged together.
Let me guess, love at first sight.
Sight, smell, whatever.
You and your son
look very happy together.
Those were taken
when Michael was 1 0.
Ten.
That's a... That's a great age.
Mr. Dubov, do you want us
to talk to Michael?
Explain to him that assault
is a serious crime?
No, forget it.
I'm sorry my secretary called you.
Besides, I think I know a way
to get him to forgive me.
There's a new bar
around the corner.
One of the waitresses,
she smells just like my kid.
Let's hope she's not married.
Amen to that.
You know, I bet if that guy quit his job
and opened up a dating service,
he'd make a fortune.
I'm not sure how turning
a corporate lawyer into cupid
is gonna help save the future.
Wha--? Hey.
Honey, what's going on?
- Are you all right?
- Dubov was gone for five years, right?
I...
I bet his son really missed him.
Probably.
I mean, every 4400
left someone behind.
Are you sure
it's not something else?
No. It's fine, really.
It'll pass.
Okay.
Physical.
You and lsabelle?
You wanna explain that?
I asked you a question! What is going
on between you and my daughter?!
We never planned
on going behind your back.
In fact, we never planned it at all.
It just kind of happened.
Friendship! Remember?
We talked about that.
That's as far as it
was supposed to go!
I don't know what to say. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I'm sorry I ever trusted you.
- lsabelle is just a child!
- No, Richard, she isn't.
She's emotionally immature
and you took advantage of that!
That's what you think?
You know me better. That's not fair.
I know your judgment stinks,
that's what I know.
You're gonna stay away
from my daughter.
I'm not gonna make
that promise to you.
I am not giving you a choice here,
you understand me?
This thing between the two of you,
it is over.
I don't recall saying "come in."
I thought perhaps a referee
might be in order.
May I advise you gentlemen
to go to your neutral corners?
This is a private conversation,
Matthew!
It may have started out that way, but
I assure you, it's becoming very public.
I could hear you out in the hallway.
And for the record,
I happen to agree with Richard.
This relationship with lsabelle
is ill-advised at best.
I thought referees didn't take sides?
If I were you, Shawn, I'd take this
opportunity to make a graceful exit.
Think about what I said, Shawn.
I'm expecting you to do
the right thing.
What's for lunch?
Prosciutto with figs.
Rosemary chicken,
couscous, and raspberries.
Wow. You know,
when Kyle and I used to go fishing,
we'd take a half a dozen
peanut-butter-and-jelly sandwiches
- and think we were living like kings.
- I like to think the reality I create
is a little bit tastier than that.
Good.
Hey, we gotta get going. Hey, Kyle!
Come on, buddy!
Come on, Kyle. Let's go.
Come on--
It's you.
The girl on the road.
That's right. You remember.
Maia.
Have we met before?
Don't be silly.
No, I'm sorry, l...
I don't remember you.
Sure you do.
Think harder.
Is that why you keep showing up?
Because you want me
to remember?
I'm here because
you brought me here.
There has to be a reason
why this girl keeps showing up.
There was nothing familiar about her?
Nothing at all?
No.
But she kept acting
like we knew each other.
And if she's right,
if I did bring here there,
then I must know her
from somewhere.
Tom.
Shouldn't you be at work?
- Jarvis said you called in sick.
- Well, I'm allowed.
Thanks for checking in on me.
Diana, talk to me, will you?
What the hell's all this?
Just a project I'm working on.
I mentioned it to you.
- Who's this supposed to be?
- I wish I knew.
I know this might sound creepy,
but I was up all night last night
cutting up pictures of little girls. None
of them seemed to be the right one.
I mean, I think I'm going crazy.
Then we both are.
You know those little dream vacations
I take with Alana?
This little girl keeps showing up
in them. This little blond girl.
Says her name is Maia.
Maia?
- Oh, Tom.
- What?
You have to come with me.
I have to show you something.
Who is she, Tom?
Who is Maia?
I don't know.
I've already checked. There's no
mention of Maia in any of our case files.
Okay, well, maybe we met her
together someplace else?
Maybe at one
of Garrity's barbecues?
No, that does not feel right.
I didn't just meet this girl once
at a barbecue.
I know her better than that.
All right, just calm down.
Well, there's a reason this girl
is haunting us, Tom, okay?
She's out there somewhere,
and she wants us to find her.
Right now the only place
I know she exists
is in one of these dream worlds
Alana and I create.
Well then, I need for Alana
to take me there.
I need to meet this girl, talk to her.
No, but you wouldn't really
be talking to her, Diana.
You'd just be talking to whatever
your subconscious remembers of her.
Well, maybe that would be enough
for me figure out who she is.
How do I sound?
Like you've been playing for years.
I haven't. It's my first time.
I kind of figured that.
Isabelle, do you have a minute?
Have a seat.
Isabelle, you know I'm proud
of you, don't you?
This is about Shawn
and I having sex, isn't it?
That's part of it, yeah.
Yeah, but only a part of it.
Right now everything's new to you.
You're learning so much so fast.
How to be a daughter.
- A friend.
- A lover.
That part you might be learning
too fast.
You don't want me
to get my feelings hurt.
I would just like if you and Shawn
slow down.
- Stop sleeping together?
- For the time being.
There's no reason to stop.
Shawn cares about me.
I care about Shawn.
The sex is wonderful.
It makes us both very happy.
It should make you happy too.
Maybe it should, but it doesn't.
I suppose that's normal.
But everything is gonna be okay.
Shawn would never
do anything to hurt me.
He's way too smart for that.
So you see?
You have nothing to worry about.
I wonder if anyone at the Center
has a cello.
So, what do I have to do?
Well, the main thing is to relax.
Well, I usually close my eyes
and count backwards from ten.
Before I reach zero,
we're somewhere else.
Have any idea where you want
Alana to take you?
We usually have
a destination picked out.
Well, wherever Maia is.
You can do that, can't you?
You can take me to her?
She seems to show up
anyplace we go.
So it's really up to you.
Well, let's just keep it simple.
How about my apartment?
All right.
Now, let's begin.
Alana,
this is not my apartment.
I know. I'm not quite sure
what just happened.
You done talking to your friend?
- You're Maia.
- Stop fooling around.
Come on. He's waiting for us.
There you are, Ms. Skouris.
The documents are all ready.
If you'll just have a seat,
and sign where indicated,
we can finish up.
You still wanna do this, don't you?
Diana Skouris,
your adoption of Maia Rutledge
is hereby complete,
legal, and binding.
So witnessed by me,
Henry Biederman,
of the 1 0th Circuit Family Court
of Seattle.
You know, some of us
have to look far and wide
to find the people we'll call family.
You two had to look
clear across time.
Diana, let me introduce you
to your daughter, Maia.
Maia, say hello to Mommy.
Oh, my God, Maia.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- Diana, what happened?
She was kidnapped, Tom.
She was taken by a woman
pretending to be her sister.
She took Maia,
Tyler Downing, Lindsey Hammond,
and a whole bunch of 4400 kids.
Do you remember any of this?
No. No, I don't.
So this woman took these children
and somehow made everyone forget
they ever existed.
Yes, but they existed.
Maia Rutledge disappeared
from Crescent City, California,
March 3rd, 1 946.
So wait, you're saying
she was abducted,
then returned with the other 4400s,
then taken again.
And none of us remember this
but you.
- It's like they've wiped our memories.
- But why?
Because they didn't want us
looking for them.
The 4400 were taken and returned
to change the future in some way.
Maybe Maia and the others were taken
so that they could change it again.
I don't know and I don't care. All I know
is four days ago she was here with me.
And I need you to believe
that I have a daughter named Maia
and that she's been taken from me.
I don't remember Maia,
or the kidnapping, or any of it.
The idea that my memory's been
messed with scares the hell out of me.
But after everything
we've been through with the 4400,
yes, Diana, I believe you.
- Hello?
- Richard Tyler?
- Yes, who's this?
- My name is Daniel Armand,
- You knoW Who I am?
- With the NOVA Group?
I think it's time you and I met,
Richard.
We have a lot to discuss,
I have a lot to say to you too,
but I don't think you'll wanna hear it.
Well, now you see,
that's the problem right there.
We should be allies,
not adversaries,
My group and your organization
have the same goals,
We're advocating
for the rights of the 4400.
Except that you advocate
through assassination and intimidation.
We lack the strength in numbers,
Richard,
so we use the tools at our disposal.
Is that what you called me for?
To have a debate?
I called to arrange a truce,
And to talk about Shawn Farrell.
- You'll make more threats against him?
- No, we need to discuss his future.
Because unless you and I can come
to some kind of agreement,
I'm not sure he's gonna have one.
I should meet him on the corner
of Pike and Gorch Thursday at 4:00.
And then?
A car will be there to pick me up
and take me someplace
for a face to face with Armand.
Sounds to me like the NOVA Group's
been reading too much John le Carré.
- What did you say?
- I told him I'd think about it.
What is there to think about?
You're not going.
Let's not rush to judgment.
I've dealt with this guy before,
remember?
He wants one thing.
You know what it is: Money.
And probably the names
and addresses of every 4400
in our computer.
If they have an ability that he can use,
he will exploit it and people will die.
People have already died.
Maybe I can stop him.
Are you gonna make him
see the light?
No, but I can stop him
from killing you.
How? How?
By putting this place and everything
that we've worked for in jeopardy?
- I won't let you do that.
- Noble words, but may I remind you?
If the NOVA Group wants to strike
at you, I don't think we can prevent it.
Thank you for the pep talk, Matthew.
I'm just being realistic.
So am l. If I don't show,
it's like a declaration of war,
and we all know
who the first casualty will be.
You and Jordan Collier built this place.
You're its heart and soul.
Then listen to me, Richard.
I tried to deal
with these people before.
It was a disaster.
I'm warning you. I'm asking you:
Please do not make
the same mistake.
Please.
Skouris, I have a list right here
of ever 4400 who returned that night
to Highland Beach.
There's no Maia Rutledge.
There's no Tyler Downing.
There's no Lindsey Hammond.
I've explained that:
They've been erased.
From the records,
from our memories.
Someone has tried to wipe out
every trace of them.
We talked to the families.
In the last week,
all of them have been haunted
by phantom memories of children
they supposedly lost years ago.
Okay, let's say I am buying
any of this, and I'm not.
But if I did, we don't even know
where they were taken.
The future?
- That's kind of out of our jurisdiction.
- I've seen Maia.
I've spoken to her.
We both have.
Look, you're asking me
to commit manpower
and resources to find a little girl
that only exists
in some shared fantasyland
you guys play around in.
Look, I'm sorry, but I can't do it.
You guys through?
Because I think I found your kids.
Here we go. Watch this.
That's him. That's Tyler.
It's dated September 1 9th, 1 893.
They sent him back
further into the past. Why?
Well, that I can't tell you.
But Tyler Downing
did graduate first in his class
from Yale University in Engineering.
I knew I'd heard the name before.
In 1 91 5, he helped develop
synthetic petroleum.
You drove to work this morning
because of this guy.
This is from the estate
of Robert Goddard.
You know, the rocket guy.
He adopted an orphan
named Lindsey Hammond.
She lived with the family,
eventually worked in his lab.
And she invented
all the composite materials
used in the first lunar colonies.
Okay, so, what about Maia?
Did you find any photos of her?
No, she was a little harder
to track down.
But I finally found something.
That's Maia's handwriting.
It's a diary from Maia Rutledge
dated April 1 9th
through September 2nd, 1 847.
It was written while
she was part of a wagon train
making its way
along the Oregon Trail.
I'm sorry. She crossed the Rockies
in a covered wagon?
No.
She died of smallpox
in October of '47.
She was 25.
No. I'm sorry, Shawn.
It's not my father's decision.
- It's mine. I'm not breaking up with you.
- It's got nothing to do with your dad.
Not really.
You and I made some decisions,
we did some things.
We did what we wanted to do.
And there's no reason
we can't keep doing that.
We'll be more careful.
My father won't know it.
That's not gonna work.
Not anymore.
Lying to him, going behind his back?
We've done enough of that.
The truth is, lsabelle,
I kind of took advantage of you.
And I'm really sorry.
You are so sweet
the way you worry about me.
I don't want this relationship to end.
So it's not going to.
I need to see her.
Please, can you take me
to see my daughter?
Diana, you know it's not really Maia
you'd be seeing.
Oh, I don't care.
Today I found out that my daughter,
who I loved,
was sent back into the past
and died 1 50 years ago.
I'm sorry, but that's gonna take me
a while to come to terms with.
I just...
Please let me do this.
I need to say goodbye.
Give me your coat.
I'll put some coffee on.
Ready?
Mommy?
Mommy, I'm starving.
Can we have pancakes?
I'll help make them.
Okay.
Well, I'll need the eggs
from the fridge.
And bring me the big, plastic bowl.
Oh, my God. Alana! Alana! Alana!
Honey, my God, you're bleeding.
You okay?
I think so.
Diana. Diana, can you hear me?
Diana, look at me.
What the hell happened?!
I thought I was bringing us out.
Well, why isn't she awake?
I couldn't hold onto her.
It's as if she pulled away.
Thomas, I think she's still
inside the dream world.
Wait, how can she be in there
without you?
I'm not sure.
When you and I separate,
we let go of the illusion.
But she's not letting go.
Wha--? She's not coming out?
I think she's happy there
with her daughter,
and she has no intention
of ever leaving.
Oh, come on.
At first, I thought she'd suffered some
kind of intracerebral hemorrhage.
But the MRl didn't show
any bleeding in the brain.
So she hasn't suffered
any damage?
Not yet, but the EEG
was very troubling.
Her brain activity is far above normal
and continues to accelerate.
The same is true for her heart rate,
her breathing, her blood pressure.
They're all redlining, if you will.
Any idea what's causing it?
I really can't say at the moment.
Her metabolic rate can't stay
at this level for very long.
Eventually her organs will fail.
What, she could die?
Unless we can slow down her rates,
we're looking at a very poor outcome.
Does she have any family?
- Yeah.
- You should call them.
I need to talk to her, Alana.
Can you do that?
Take me to see Diana?
- Push me a little, Mommy.
- Okay, I'm pushing you.
Then make it higher.
Look, not too high.
But that's the whole fun.
She has a point.
I thought I'd be seeing you two.
I didn't hurt you, did l?
It felt a little jarring when you left.
- No, I'm fine.
- You, on the other hand, are not.
Well, that's where you're wrong,
because I feel great.
You're in an lCU, Diana.
I thought I might end up there.
What's my heart rate?
Is it 1 70? 1 75?
- Higher.
- That still probably gives me
what, anywhere from three weeks
to two months?
That could be forever in here.
You're talking about suicide.
I appreciate your concern,
Tom, I do.
But really, I'd like you to leave now.
Both of you.
Listen, Diana, believe--
Don't walk away.
The first time I came to these places,
I never wanted to leave.
But I came to realize,
this is not the world.
None of this is real.
Including Maia.
Mommy, push me a little harder.
She's real enough for me.
Oh, she's not coming back, is she?
She's going to die in there.
That seems to be her plan.
I can't help but think this is my fault.
I took her there.
No, don't do that to yourself.
You didn't take Maia away.
The people who did that,
they're to blame.
Maybe.
But these people in the future?
They don't seem to care
who they hurt, do they?
No, they don't.
Four o'clock is fast approaching.
Have you come to a decision?
Do I want to get in bed with a terrorist,
or go to war with one?
That does appear to be the question.
Whatever you decide,
you can count on my support.
Isabelle?
My relationship with Shawn
has nothing to do with you.
That's not true. I just care
about what happens to you.
You can care about me all you want,
just stay out of my business.
I'm not gonna do that.
Yes, you are.
Isabelle...?
Daddy?
I'm sorry.
Okay, move on.
It's all right, baby.
I don't know if you can hear me,
but I've been thinking.
Ever since the 4400 came back,
it's been one sacrifice after another.
You and your daughter.
My son.
It has to stop.
So I have a plan.
I'm not sure it's gonna work.
It might be the stupidest thing
I've ever done.
I kind of wish you were here
to stop me.
But you're not,
and I have to try something.
Maybe this is goodbye,
maybe it isn't.
The job wouldn't have been
any fun without you.
Okay, okay. Okay.
This is gonna work, right? Okay.
It worked, right?
I'm not dead.
Not this time, no.
Next time,
you might not be so fortunate.
The children you took,
Maia and the others.
I want them back.
You were never meant
to remember them.
We went to great lengths
to erase them from your memory
to spare you any pain.
It didn't work.
It appears we underestimated
the bonds they had forged.
It's called "family."
Are you familiar with the concept?
You had no right to take them,
treat people like that.
Maia was only 25 when she died.
Now, either return the children,
or put that rope back around my neck,
because I'm done.
In that case,
I need to show you something.
They're alive.
You forced us to go back,
extract them from the timeline.
But returning them to you
would be a mistake.
For our time, and for yours.
The 4400 were an experiment
we always knew might fail.
There were so many variables.
It was impossible to predict them all.
So you're telling me everything
you've done--
Taking the 4400, sending them back.
--it hasn't changed anything?
The catastrophe's still coming?
Our enemies are more resourceful
than we imagined.
Enemies?
There are those among us who would
prefer history to remain unchanged.
That the 4400 fail in their mission.
You mean they want
humanity to die out?
They are convinced
that they will survive.
Not only survive,
but benefit from the chaos.
If you think we are heartless,
I assure you, that the other side
is unimaginably more brutal.
And they've let loose
a terrible evil into your time.
Sending these children further back
into the timeline
was an attempt to combat that evil.
If we return them to you,
all the good that they have done
in the past will be negated.
The 4400 and everything
that they were meant to achieve
will be in jeopardy.
This evil, there has to be
some other way to deal with it.
There is.
You. You are the other way.
It's a burden that we had hoped
not to place on you.
If you return Maia and the others,
I'll do whatever you want.
What we want,
you may not be willing to give.
Do we have a deal or not?
We do. But it's a deal I'm afraid
you'll come to regret.
Hello?
Is there anyone here?
Maia?
- Tom!
- Maia! Maia!
It's okay. He works with my Mom.
- We were kidnapped!
- Where's Sarah?
- Did you catch her?
- Can we go home now?
Yes. Yes, you guys.
- Where's my Mom?
- You're all going home.
It's over. You're all safe now.
Is my Mom here?
She's not here,
but I'll take you to her, okay?
Hello.
Has he arrived yet?
Then he's made my choice for me.
Where are you hiding? Come on!
I know you're watching me.
I know you're listening.
Where are you?
I found you. I found your bug.
I found your stupid little bug.
Okay, sweetie, lights out.
But it's still early.
It's 9:30, and it's time for bed.
Okay, but first I need you
to do something for me.
- Maia, no stalling.
- Mommy, please. It won't take long.
All you have to do is shut your eyes.
All right. Okay.
Well, they're shut. Now what?
Maia?
I'm here, Mommy.
You can open your eyes now.
Mommy?
Wake up.
It's okay.
I'm back.
Everything's fine.
But you have to wake up.
Mommy, please.
Wake up. Please.
Maia? Maia?