over the last 60 years
4400 people have been abducted
all at once they were returned
with no memory of
where they've been
they haven't aged a day
and some have returned
with new abilities
all are trying to reconnect...
...with a life interrupted
We're not a threat.
We're salvation.
The world
will have to deal with us.
Previously on the 4400...
okay, we're clear, right?
It's over
between the two of us.
You once told me
that good and evil was a choice,
and i'm afraid if i lose you
i'm going to make the wrong one.
Welcome to haspelcorp.
How may i help you?
Hi.
I have an appointment
with dennis ryland.
Learning anything new?
Yeah.
She's incredible.
In a week,
we've made discoveries
we thought
it would take years
to get to.
Isabelle, i don't love you.
Shawn, you and i are
the two most powerful people
on the planet.
We have to get married.
[Richard]:
I knew she was different.
Dangerous.
[Gasps]
You can't kill me, shawn.
Richard, if i believed
that staying with isabelle
would save all those lives,
i would marry her tomorrow,
but what happens
if she gets tired of me,
or i make her angry?
There are things
i was sent here to do.
Brutal things.
[Shawn]: I don't know
how you can know that,
but it doesn't
have to happen that way.
We need to be together,
because i think
you're the only one
who can stop me.
www.1000fr.com Present
Capture:xxy
Sync:FRM@°¢À­²¼²¼
Looking for a date?
Not you.
Him.
[Sighs]
Tim.
You've got a customer.
[Engine turns over]
So it's 40 bucks,
if you want
to get started.
I just want
to look at you
for a second.
Do you have any idea
how special you are?
You don't, do you?
Look, we can talk
if you want to,
but it's still 40 bucks.
Timothy winters mccarren.
You're going to
change the world.
How'd you know my name?
It's true.
You're going to
change everything...
unless i stop you.
That's it. I'm out of here.
[Rattles door handle]
Come on, man. Let me out.
I'm serious.
[Screams]
[Screaming]
[Man]:
I rolled that myself.
It's my way
of saying thank you
for inviting me
to your wedding.
Well, thank you,
but you didn't have to.
Isabelle and i
invited every 4400.
I wouldn't have missed it.
I'm quite excited.
You must be, too.
The ceremony's so close.
Uh-huh.
Four days.
I have to offer you
a word of caution.
The cigar...
when you smoke it,
you might be surprised
by its effects.
Oh, i'm not going to
get arrested
for having this,
am i?
[Chuckling]:
Of course not.
About a year
after we returned,
i learned i have an ability.
When i come in contact
with a person,
they sometimes see a vision
of their future.
I see nothing,
understand...
only those i touch...
but i'm told
it can be quite accurate.
That's a nice talent.
Thank you.
I grew this tobacco
myself.
It's been in contact
with my hands,
and so it contains my ability.
Wait, so,
what you're saying is
if i smoke this cigar,
i'm going to
see the future?
Your future.
A possible one,
anyway.
As i said,
use with caution.
You might not like
what you see,
but it seems
an appropriate gift
for a man
on his wedding day.
Well, it is better
than a toaster oven.
Thank you, claudio.
My congratulations
to you.
The centerpieces
are amazing.
You should take a look.
Uh, yeah, sure,
after we're done
with these meet-and-greets,
though, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, you taking up smoking?
[Door opens]
This is edwin garrett
and his wife, denise.
They came all the way
from edinburgh
to be here.
Thank you so much
for coming.
The guy's name
was tim mccarren.
He was a hustler.
Worked an area of the park
not far from here.
I found his body
just after sunrise.
Now, i've already
interviewed
his colleagues,
and they say he got
into a pickup truck
with a man in his 20s
at about 1:30 last night.
One of the other
working boys
got a real decent look
at the driver.
So you could probably
sit him down
with a sketch artist.
Probably could,
but you do realize
we're not homicide cops,
right?
We're from ntac.
So why'd you call us?
That's why.
[***]
* so long ago, another life *
* i can feel your heart beat *
* it's not a dream
remember us *
* i can see it in your eyes *
* we'll find our place in time *
* our place in time
beyond the sun *
* we'll find our place in time *
* our place in time
to call our own *
[***]
My best guess?
His body
was completely oxidized.
It's a chemical reaction.
Cells change
at the molecular level.
Oxidizing?
That's what happens
when metal rusts.
Exactly.
Well, almost exactly.
Rusting is
a slow process.
There's nothing gradual
about what happened
to tim mccarren.
One minute he was alive,
the next...
have you ever seen
anything like this before?
No.
There's no
documented disease
that affects
the human body this way.
Meaning a 4400 ability did this.
That's for you to figure out.
All i can tell you
is there's no...
earthly explanation
about what happened
to this guy.
Thanks.
So nothing
even close?
Okay.
Thanks, brian.
That was the lab.
They ran
the composite sketch
of the driver
against our database
of 4400s.
No matches.
Anything
from forensics?
No.
They pulled a couple
of partial prints
off the safety pin
that held the note
to the kid's jacket,
but nothing we can
make an i.d. From.
Okay, what about the note?
It's a deliberate message
to whoever found the body.
That's typical
of a serial killer
pathology.
Yeah,
but it says "27."
There can't be
26 other corpses
like tim mccarren's
out there.
Even one would make it
onto our radar.
So we'll talk
to mccarren's friends,
families...
maybe he's got
a connection to a 4400.
Diana...
there is
one other thing
i want to
talk to you about.
You got plans on sunday?
Y-you want me to go
to shawn's wedding...
with you?
It's not a date, okay?
I figured you might be
interested.
Almost a thousand 4400s
are coming.
Oh, so it's
a professional courtesy.
Yeah, that's one way to put it.
Look, to be honest,
i'd rather not be the only one
sitting at the ntac table.
You'd have a hard time
finding a dance partner.
Look, you know,
maia begged me to go,
and i told her no.
All those 4400s in one place...
we have no idea
what could happen.
Diana, it's shawn and isabelle.
Nobody's going to cause
any trouble.
I mean, would you want to be
on the bride's bad side?
I can't imagine you're eager
to welcome that girl
into the family.
I'm not...
this all happened
a little too quickly
for my liking...
but shawn won't talk to me
about it.
I must have left him
20 messages.
I was thinking
about going to see him
after we finish work today.
Just make sure
bridezilla is out of earshot.
I have to.
"Have to"?
You're about to
get married, shawn.
You should want to.
What's going on?
is she...
is she pregnant?
No, no,
nothing like that.
Is she forcing you?
Look, shawn,
if you're
feeling trapped,
if you're looking
for a way out of this,
just tell me.
I can help.
"Help"?
I'm not in front
of a firing squad.
I'm getting married.
People do it all the time.
Come on, shawn.
You're marrying isabelle.
She's a very dangerous girl.
I happen to know that.
Okay, i know all about her, too,
so don't think
you're going to surprise me.
I appreciate
you coming down here,
i know you mean well,
but this marriage,
it is the right thing.
The right thing for who?
For everybody.
They just cannot
keep anything working
around here.
This always happens
when i work late.
You know,
i don't even know
where the stairs are
in this place.
Right down here.
Come on. I'll show you.
So, do you always
work past 8:00?
Most nights, yeah.
Trying to get ahead,
you know?
Dedication.
I like that.
You could accomplish
great things.
Her name
was paula nakata.
She was a lawyer
at a firm in the building.
My god.
The poor woman.
That's two bodies
in less than 24 hours.
It doesn't
make any sense.
Most spree killers,
they have a type,
but tim mccarren
and paula nakata
could hardly be more different.
A prostitute
and a corporate attorney.
Why would someone
target these two?
And why is she labeled "11"?
The numbers on the bodies
are working backwards.
It looks like we might have
a partial print
on the wedding band.
It's probably from the victim,
but you never know.
Let's hope
whoever did this
slipped up,
because i don't think
he's anywhere close
to finished yet.
We were so close.
We were going to
save everything.
Isabelle changed you.
You don't even...
know who you are anymore.
She didn't change me.
She showed me who i am.
I know myself
better than ever,
and i know exactly
what has to happen here.
Don't do this.
[Gasps]
[Rasping]: Shawn...
[coughs]
Marco?
Did you go home
last night?
Uh... no.
Uh, i was working
on your case.
It got late.
Cold.
We had a message
you wanted
to talk to us.
Uh, yeah.
The print that they pulled
from paula nakata's
wedding band
wasn't hers.
Does it match the one
we found on tim mccarren's body?
It does indeed.
The print belongs
to a man named
darren piersahl.
Piersahl?
I never heard of him.
I'm not surprised.
See...
he is not a 4400.
Well, then he's not
the murderer.
Marco, you saw both bodies.
A 4400 killed these people.
It certainly looks that way,
but the fingerprint match
wasn't from
our database.
It was from
u.s. Military records.
Piersahl was
an army ranger
for seven years.
"Was"?
What's he doing now?
Not much.
According
to army records,
darren piersahl is dead.
He was killed in action
in iraq in 2005.
I'm wondering...
how could
an army sergeant
who's supposedly
been dead for a year
be using a 4400 ability
darren always wanted to be
a ranger.
It was his dream,
ever since he was old enough
to read.
I encouraged it.
I spent 20 years
in the service myself,
so when darren signed up,
it was like carrying on
the family legacy.
Why is ntac
so interested
in my son's death,
anyway?
It's part of an ongoing
investigation, mr. Piersahl.
Please,
anything you could tell us
would help.
Not long before he died,
i got a letter from darren.
He was excited.
Said he'd been accepted
into this elite training unit.
He couldn't tell me
much about it,
just that it meant
he was being transferred
off the front lines
and out of harm's way.
And he was
killed in action
soon after that?
Two weeks later.
The army told me
he'd been flying
a recon mission
in an oh-58 helicopter.
It got hit with an rpg.
They never did
find his remains.
I'm so sorry,
mr. Piersahl...
but you said
the army "told you"
he was flying a recon mission.
Did you have any reason
to doubt that?
Well, i thought the timing
was peculiar.
I mean,
i just got this letter from him
saying he was done fighting,
so i did some checking.
There were six soldiers
reported dead
in the crash that killed my son.
And why is that unusual?
Because an oh-58 flies
with a crew of four.
It can't hold six people.
A secret training program?
A death under suspicious
circumstances?
There's something off here.
Even the kid's dad
knows it.
It's weird...
i'm not denying it...
but let's just take
our time with this, okay?
There are explanations
that don't involve
a cover-up.
Someone could have planted
darren piersahl's
fingerprints
at the crime scene.
Who knows?
It could be a 4400.
Someone who can mimic
other people's
fingerprints.
Maybe...
[cell phone ringing]
But if you were
trying to frame someone,
why would you pick a dead man?
Baldwin.
Where?
We'll be right in.
They just found another body.
[Clinking]
I'll let you all in
on a little family secret.
My brother and i haven't always
seen eye to eye,
so we didn't talk
for a while.
I went to college,
he became
the most famous person
in the world...
but it's all good,
because he's a great guy,
and i'm really proud of him.
I think we all are.
So...
congratulations, man.
I couldn't be happier
to see you walk the plank.
[Group]: Congratulations.
Cheers.
Is there anything
you'd like to say, daddy?
[Glass clinking]
Toast.
The father of the bride
wants to speak.
Uh...
shawn...
isabelle...
i have to say,
i had my doubts...
but my daughter
has managed
to overcome them.
She was determined
to make this marriage
happen,
and here we all are.
Shawn, she couldn't have picked
a better partner.
I'm proud to call you my son.
Cheers.
So...
where you going
on your honeymoon?
Well, we haven't really
figured that out yet.
If you'll all please
excuse me...
stay.
You keep charming your in-laws.
I'll see what's up.
Isabelle...
oh.
You saw me die?
You're sure?
I killed you,
and richard,
i swear to god,
it looked like
i was enjoying it.
The whole reason
that i'm marrying isabelle
is to keep her attached,
normal...
that's not what happens.
I don't make her
more human.
She makes me less human.
Listen, i have to try something.
I have to go.
I have to see
if it changes anything.
You're going to walk out
on the wedding?
Maybe. I don't know.
I'm... i'm getting out of here,
and then i'm going to see
what happens.
If you leave now,
it's not going to make isabelle
very happy.
It might not be that easy
to come back.
I know that,
but i have to do it.
Just...
tell them i'm sick
or something.
I'm sorry.
Just tell them
something, okay?
Her name was holly martins.
She was a housewife
in madison park.
The pool man found her body.
Was there a note?
"92"?
How many people
is this guy targeting?
[Knock on door]
Guys, i figured out
what all these corpses
have in common.
All the victims
had the same mutation?
We did a genetic workup
on all three corpses.
Every one of them
has a slight alteration
of the 11th chromosome.
It's called
the starzl mutation.
That could be a coincidence.
Not likely.
The starzl mutation
is extremely rare.
The only documented cases
are in the seattle area.
See, there's two kinds
of mutations.
Some occur naturally.
You know, something goes wrong
when the body
is building itself.
Others are induced.
The genes are changed
by external factors.
The starzl mutation is induced.
That's right.
Starting in 1969,
seattle presbyterian hospital
used a flawed radiation machine
to treat their cancer patients.
The microswitches
that controlled
the thing
weren't working,
so the dosages were all off.
How long
did this go on?
Just under five years.
Once the hospital
figured out
what they were doing,
they tested everyone
who had ever been
exposed to it.
In some cases,
the radiation induced
a small mutation.
The starzl mutation.
Yeah, they named it
after the company
that made the bad machine.
And the mutation's replicable.
People who got it
passed it on
to their kids,
which includes...
our three victims.
But they were all living
normal lives.
They were healthy.
Just like most mutations,
you can have it
and not even know.
After everything
went public,
the lawyers
came out to play.
There was
a class-action lawsuit.
Seattle presbyterian paid
a huge settlement
to everyone who was
affected by the machine.
They almost went bankrupt.
So darren piersahl,
who's supposed to be dead,
is targeting carriers
of the starzl mutation,
which only occurs
around seattle,
and has absolutely no effect
on its carriers.
Okay, but why?
Excellent question.
When you find out,
make sure you tell me.
If there was a lawsuit,
there's a paper trail.
I bet you that hospital
keeps a master list
of everyone they paid.
[Shawn grunting with effort]
[Gasping]
You okay?
Shawn...
you have to stop healing me.
No, you're going to make it,
uncle tommy.
No, shawn, i'm not.
This is all my fault.
I should never
have talked you
out of marrying
isabelle.
No, that was my decision,
not yours.
I can't help thinking
that it didn't
have to end this way.
Everyone we love is dead.
I'm sorry.
The catastrophe is here.
Hey...
no, no, no.
Hold on, hold on,
hold on...
[choking]
No! Let me go.
Let me go!
Save as many as you can, shawn.
You're lucky.
Until six weeks ago,
i hadn't pulled that file
in years.
If you'd asked me then,
it would have taken me hours
to find it.
What happened
six weeks ago?
Some guy in a suit
showed up.
He had a document with him
saying that the military
needed the file
for, uh, research
in the war on terror.
Yeah, there we go.
There it is.
That's the master list
of everyone we paid
in the starzl case.
This man,
can you tell me his name?
Yeah...
miles enright.
Why? You know him?
Not yet.
There's 123 people here.
123 people we know have
the starzl mutation.
And the numbers
we've been finding
on the dead bodies
correspond to where
they appear on the list.
Number 27, timothy mccarren.
Number 11, paula nakata.
And holly martins, 92.
So darren piersahl,
if he's the killer,
is working from the same list
we're holding.
But the order seems so random.
I mean, is he just killing them
as the opportunity arises,
or is there some method?
I'll try
and find a pattern.
Hey, um...
how's maia been?
She's okay.
She asks about you a lot.
Yeah?
I just checked out
miles enright.
He's a vice president
of research and development
at haspelcorp.
Dennis.
You've been
ignoring our calls.
I'm busy, tom.
Why don't you go
through my assistant?
Maybe we can talk
next week or so.
It's important,
ryland.
It's about darren piersahl,
and your company's program
to create a division
of the u.s. Military
with 4400 abilities.
I don't know, tom.
I've been working here
less than three months.
I still don't know where
the supply closets are,
and now you've got me
heading up a covert program
where i'm injecting promicin
into united states soldiers?
Six weeks ago,
the vice president
of research and development
acquired a list of everyone
with the starzl mutation.
Miles enright.
Maybe you know him?
Sorry. It's a big building.
I haven't met everybody yet.
Three people are dead.
Now, you need to tell us
everything you know
about darren piersahl
so we can bring him in
before he kills anyone else.
I've never heard of him,
and i've certainly
never heard of this...
what do you call it?
"Starzl mutation"?
This is your last chance
to cooperate
before we find piersahl.
If you help us now,
we'll make it look better
for your company later, dennis.
Well, how can i help you
when i have no idea
what you're talking about?
Now, if this program
existed...
and please understand,
i'm not saying it does...
you seem to think
that people would be shocked
to know that
it's out there.
Me, i think
they'd be grateful.
I think any good citizen
would be thankful
that his government
was working on this,
because you can be damn sure
our enemies are.
If everyone would be so happy,
why not just tell us about it?
As usual,
you have no idea
of what the stakes are.
Whoever controls
promicin
has a strategic
advantage
over the rest
of the world.
This is
another manhattan project, tom,
and they didn't close it down
because a couple of technicians
got radiation poisoning.
They kept on working,
and they were right
to do that.
It's made the world
a better place.
Not that you're admitting
that the program exists, right?
What program?
So if i go through
with it,
if i marry isabelle,
you and i
become enemies.
I kill you.
If i don't do it...
richard,
things are even worse.
People are dead.
A lot of people.
In the second vision,
your uncle said
that the catastrophe was here,
right?
The place looked
like a war zone.
What the hell
am i supposed to do?
Look, you can only deal
with the information you have.
In one future, i die.
In another,
it sounds like
thousands of people,
maybe millions,
are at risk.
That's no choice at all.
We're talking about your life.
The guy said each vision
was one possible future.
If you do marry
isabelle...
at least
we're going into it
with our eyes open.
Now that we know
what could happen,
we can change things.
Nothing's inevitable, right?
Let's hope not...
because believe me...
i don't want to die.
Meet staff sergeant
john shaffner.
Okay, so why are we meeting him?
He was one
of six fatalities
in the helicopter crash
that "killed" darren piersahl.
A helicopter
that seated only four.
Right.
Turns out john shaffner's family
never received his remains
either.
You know, there was really
a helicopter crash
that day in iraq,
but four families
got their kids' bodies back,
and two didn't,
so here's what i'm thinking...
you think piersahl
and shaffner
were recruited into
haspelcorp's training program
at the same time.
So they used the crash
to fake two deaths,
so that piersahl
and shaffner
could disappear
into the program
with impunity.
So we have a second member
of haspelcorp's program,
which is great,
but it doesn't get us
any closer
to darren piersahl.
Good point.
It doesn't, really.
Not until...
you look
at shaffner's dog tags.
This is shaffner's
military serial number.
Look familiar?
Should it?
27.
That's what the note we found
on tim mccarren said.
That's also where
we found his name
on the list of people
with the starzl mutation.
11.
That was paula nakata's number.
And holly martins
was 92 on the list.
There is a pattern.
He's picking the order
based on his buddy's
serial number.
Okay, but why?
Maybe it's a message,
maybe they're
doing it together,
but if he's consistent,
the next victim
will be number 38
on the starzl list.
Alex messina.
I already
checked him out.
He manages a bike store
in madrona.
Yeah, i recognize him.
He was in here
earlier today.
Did he say
anything to you?
It was kind of weird, actually.
He asked me if my name
was alex messina,
and he said it
like that.
You know,
the full name?
He wanted to know
if i could come out
and take a look at his bike.
He needed
to replace a part.
I told him
just to bring it in.
He said he'd come back
when we were less busy.
Send a tactical team over
right away.
Thanks.
If piersahl makes a move,
we'll be ready.
Tom.
It must be from piersahl.
Hey.
Do you like this color?
This place needs to be
a little more girly
if i'm going to be
living here.
Yeah, it looks great.
I think so, too.
I'm glad you're back.
If piersahl knows
we're on to him,
he'll change
his pattern of attack.
There's about
a dozen people
we can't find.
Let's hope we get to them
before piersahl does.
[Man]: Tom baldwin?
Yeah, who's asking?
My name is john.
John shaffner.
I was a volunteer
in the same program
darren piersahl was in.
The one
that drove him crazy.
Yeah, we know
who you are.
And we know about the program.
Good.
We were volunteers.
All of us.
I still remember
the sales pitch.
We'd be the elite,
a new type of soldier.
We had to give up
our lives,
forfeit our identities...
they said it was the only way.
The program had to operate
in complete secrecy.
When did you start
getting the injections?
Right away.
It started slow,
but about three weeks ago,
they started upping our dosages.
That's when guys started
to lose it.
Where did they
get their promicin?
I don't know,
but they seemed to have
plenty of it, though.
Darren was the first one
who could do stuff.
An ability.
He killed one of the instructors
by mistake.
It freaked him out.
You two escaped together?
Once we got out,
we pretty much went
our separate ways.
I had no idea
he was going do this.
So he's awol?
These murders aren't sanctioned
by anyone?
No, darren's
freelancing.
That's why they want him back
so bad.
He's compromising the program.
Our c.o. S, they told us
about the starzl mutation,
they told us
it could be a threat,
but they never told us
to kill anybody.
Then what is it?
Why does darren
want them dead so badly?
It's got something to do with...
babies.
So far,
any time a 4400
has a kid
with a member
of the regular population,
their babies are normal.
They don't make promicin.
They don't have abilities.
We know.
We've been tracking the births.
The starzl mutation
changes all that.
If a 4400 has a kid with someone
who has the mutation...
the baby would be
promicin-positive.
They'd have abilities.
How would the military
even know that?
Have they tried it?
I don't know,
but they seem pretty
goddamn sure it's true.
I know
this is going to sound crazy,
but darren
is a victim here, too.
They gave us so many stimulants.
They amped us up to kill,
and he snapped.
I don't know if he thinks
he's on a mission or something,
but i know
he needs to be stopped.
I'll do whatever i can
to help you find him.
[Ryland]: so, what
do you think you know?
Everything,
including the starzl mutation,
and i have to
give you credit...
if what you say is right,
it would explain
why the 4400
were sent back in 2004,
why they were all brought
to seattle...
this is the only place
the 4400 can reproduce
and have kids with abilities.
Any of this sound familiar?
I think i read the same theory
in a supermarket tabloid once.
We know about your enhanced
soldier program, dennis.
We have one of your people.
John shaffner
been showing up
for many roll calls
lately?
Well, as soon as
we have piersahl,
we're going public
with this,
and there's nothing
you can do to stop that.
All you can do
is make yourself
and this company
look slightly better
by cooperating with our efforts
to bring him in.
We want piersahl's
personnel file.
Everything you have.
If it's not in my hands
in 90 seconds,
john shaffner will be standing
in front of a bank of cameras
before lunch.
This could be something.
Maybe.
It reads like some kind
of personal statement.
An essay by piersahl.
Yeah, we had to do those
to get in the program.
They wanted us to write
about some goal
we achieved,
something
we were proud of.
This is all about
a volunteer program
that he did.
There was a patch of forest
that got cleared by a fire.
Piersahl volunteered to renew it
so that he could become a...
darren piersahl
was an eagle scout?
Yeah, he used to talk
about those woods
all the time.
When we were
in the middle of the program,
whenever things got really bad,
he used to tell me
that's where he'd go
in his head.
He'd imagine himself there.
It calmed him down.
This patch of forest,
any chance you know where it is?
[Camera clicking]
Maybe you could put
your arm around her, mr. Tyler.
That's great.
The magazine wants to get
a shot of the bride and groom.
Has anyone seen the groom?
Who gave you the key?
Your own bodyguard.
[Keys clatter]
You started a war,
richard.
You turned the 4400
into an army,
and you launched an attack
for no reason!
We didn't have a choice.
It had to be
a preemptive strike.
No choice?
Look at what
you're doing!
Look at it!
It has to stop.
Isabelle changed you.
You don't even know
who you are anymore.
She didn't change me.
She showed me who i am.
I know myself
better than ever,
and i know exactly
what has to happen here.
Don't do this.
[Gasps]
[Rasping]: Shawn...
[knock on door]
Shawn.
Sorry to barge in on you.
It's just...
they need you
down in the garden.
Pictures.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm just...
a little overwhelmed.
Darren?
Darren, you out here?
What are you
doing here?
Darren, relax, man.
It's me, shaffner.
John.
We're friends,
remember?
Shaff.
You came.
That's good.
I need your help.
I'm never going to make it
all the way through this list
on my own.
Darren, you don't have to
finish the list.
It's someone else's agenda.
You've got it all mixed up
in your head.
Come on with me.
There's some people
i want you to talk to.
They can help us.
"They"? Who are "they"?
It's got to stop, man.
Please.
Come with me.
No.
Wait!
We've got people
covering the access road.
We'll pin him down.
Fan out!
[Bellows]
Oh, jesus.
Tom!
I can't see anything!
Tom...
tom!
Tom?
[Sputtering]
We lost shaffner.
Piersahl's dead.
He was on his way out
before we even
started fighting.
Piersahl had a stab wound
in his stomach.
I guess shaffner
didn't go down without a fight.
Yeah, well,
they're both gone,
and there's no one left
to talk about the program.
We still have evidence.
We can go after haspelcorp.
Expose everything.
Yeah, but it
would've been nice
to have a face
to put out there.
I mean, now all we have
are accusations
and a paper trail.
And five dead bodies.
Hey, you guys got to see this.
We are proud to announce
the existence
of this
enhanced soldier program
to all the world,
but it should not
in any way be seen
as an offensive
maneuver.
We have evidence
suggesting
that other countries
have similar programs.
This is merely a response.
The young men
i'm about to
introduce to you
have been working
in secret,
and we've made
numerous advances.
In time,
they'll become
the first non-4400s
to develop
extra-human abilities,
and they'll use them
in the defense
of the united states.
Now i'd like to introduce
eight heroic young men,
all of whom have given
so much of themselves
to make this breakthrough
possible.
Ryland's preempting us.
Trotting them
out there on stage
like they're
the first astronauts.
Major jeremy elwood...
first lieutenant
raymond garcia,
first lieutenant jeff rice,
first lieutenant brian dawson,
second lieutenant
james knowlon,
dirk danoff...
the press conference was
a clever move, dennis.
I have to give credit
where it's due.
But this company
has five bodies
on its hands,
and i'm going to
make sure
everyone knows it.
Knows what?
We're not denying
anything.
It's unfortunate
that one of my men went awol,
but he was
clearly deranged.
I've got a whole team of doctors
standing by
to testify to that effect.
You created an assassin.
It's a tragedy,
and it's news, i'll admit that,
but tomorrow morning,
the piersahl case
will be below the fold
on every newspaper,
and all the headlines will be
about our program.
That's the way i see it, anyway.
Who's feeding you
your information?
You knew about
the starzl mutation
before we did.
You have a source
of promicin
for your program.
Who is it?
You give me
too much credit, tom.
That stuff happens
way above my security clearance.
The soldiers you're creating...
are you really going to use them
to defend the country?
Or are you just going to
send them after the 4400?
Is there a difference?
Enjoy your
nephew's wedding.
You sure you're
ready for this?
You look ready.
Let's do this.
[Cheering and applause]
Hello there.
Thank you for coming.
Thanks, kids.
Thank you for coming,
so much.
Thank you
for being here.
Thank you so much
Thank you.
Thank you for coming so far.
Appreciate you coming
all this way.
Thank you so much.
Shawn!
Shawn farrell?
Do you know who i am?
Welcome to www.1000fr.com