Over the last 60 years 4400
people have been abducted
All at once they were returned
With no memory of where they've been
They haven't aged a day
And some have returned with new abilities
All are trying to reconnect...
...with a life interrupted
(缺一句)
Previously on the 4400...
lily,are you all right?
- Where's my wife?
- What are you talking about?
Mr. Tyler,when your wife fainted this morning,
she was a young woman.
When she woke up less than a minute later,
she was 50 years older.
Are you my mother?
(缺一句)
I understand there was an incident this morning.
You attempted to harm yourself.
You had no right to do that!
Don't you understand who you are?
What you're here to do?
I'm injecting myself with a modified
version of the promicin serum.
I will have taught my body
how to produce promicin,
and then I will be the first non-returnee
to develop 4400 abilities.
That was T.J. Kim running from the courthouse.
When she hit this place,T.J. Drove every man
in the building into a homicidal rage.
Ever since we took them off the inhibitor,
they're either developing new abilities or
they're refining the ones that they've got.
(缺一句)1
(缺一句)2
You sold us out.
I don't guess we'll be seeing
her in court any time soon.
This is a message from the nova group.
We are the defensive wing of the 4400.
Today,the world has seen what happens to
those who try to harm us.A new era dawns.
Hi.
Need your auxiliary rounds as well,
agent baldwin.
Oh,yeah.
Of course.I forgot,ian.Thanks.
- You can go in.
- Great.
Hi,T.J.
What do you want?
Dr. Burkhoff?
I have your prescriptions.
Hello?
Say something if you're here.
Don'T.
Please.
I've been having migraines.
How severe?
Bad enough.
Don't worry.They're just headaches.
I've been getting them for years.
7:45.
You're just in time for my wake-up call.
(前面还有)How many a day are you up to now?
Six.
You've doubled your dosage?
I thought you weren't going to do that
we're talking now.
Look,I'm training my body to
produce a new neurotransmitter.
And I guarantee you i'm not the only one trying.
The moment the first 4400 manifested an ability,
an arms race began.
Someone is going to produce a promicin serum
that will cause non-4400s to develop
extraordinary abilities.It will happen.
The only questions are who's going
to do it and who's going to control it?
Hopefully someone with a highly
developed sense of responsibility...
and some judgment.
Let me ask you--
in your day-to-day affairs?
Do a lot of them hold
high-ranking government posts
or sit on the board of
giant pharmaceutical companies?
Dr. Burkhoff...
I knew that you had some...
personality quirks,
but I never pegged you for a cynic.
I can't afford to have a charitable view
of human nature.There's too much at stake here.
If these experiments cost me
some headaches...some sores...
I'd say that's a price worth paying.
Wouldn't you?
I'm here,right?
Holy mother--
why are we doing this?
Everything I'm telling you,
it's all in my file.You know it already.
Relax,T.J.
I just think it's important we review
everything you've told the government so far.
Have we?
Yes.
(前面还有)That's everything I know.
Okay.
Thanks for your cooperation.
We're just trying to consolidate information.
You'd be amazed how hard that can be in a bureaucracy.
Yeah,well...
I hope you don't expect me to say "you're welcome."
What are you doing?
What,this?
It's nothing.(后面还有)
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-wk120 gagegao
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
Season 03 Episode 03
Get geared up.We're leaving in two minutes.
What for?What's going on?
Your partner registered to
see T.J. Kim this morning.
When tom left the interview room,
T.J. Was dead.
- What?
- Two gunshot wounds to the head.
Apparently,tom snuck a small firearm
into the interrogation room.
By the time the guard went into the room and
found T.J.'S body,tom had already left the building.
- We're going to pick him up right now.
- Wait,wait.
This is tom we're talking about here.
There's got to be some explanation.
Maybe T.J. Used her ability on him.
No,she had concentrated promicin
inhibitor pumping through her veins.
We've tried to contact tom,
but he hasn't been picking up his phone.
We need to get him in here
just let me talk to him first.
He trusts me.
Now,this is tom.
Come on.We owe him that much.
Yeah,okay.
I wasn't trying to drown myself.
I don't even know if I could.
Okay.
Isabelle,I just thought that after
everything that happened with lily--
shawn...
this has nothing to do with my mother.
I was teaching myself to swim.
In your clothes?
Well,I never wore a bathing suit before.
I didn't know what to get.
And I'm too old to ask for help.
It's embarrassing not knowing how to swim.
Everybody's got to learn sometime,isabelle.
I learned when I was a kid.
But I never was a kid.
That's why I never learned how to swim,
or how to drive,or ever went out on a date.
I keep reading about all these...
rites of passage.
Like stuff everyone goes
through before they grow up?
Yeah.Yeah,but I am grown up...
and I missed out on all of it.
It's not fair.
I've got to catch up,
so I made a list.
(缺一句)
Well,isabelle,
there's a pool at the center.
I could probably teach you the basics.
Really?
Thanks,shawn.
Dad?
How old were you when you learned how to swim?
(缺一句)
You want me to teach you?
Shawn said he'd do it.
(缺一句)
Well,just make sure he doesn't
throw you in the deep end right away.
That's what my grandmother did to me.
Look,isabelle...
I'm going to be gone overnight.
If you need anything,see shawn.
Where are you going?
I'm going to take your mother home.
I'm putting her to rest.
Well,can I come with you?
I don't think so.
I'm flying,and...
I don't think you're ready to
be away from the center yet.
You want to be alone with her
when you say goodbye,don't you?
Yeah,I guess I do.
- Tom.
- God!
You scared the hell out of me,diana.
What are you doing here?
Why is your gun out?
What the hell is going on?
Jarvis is on her way over.
She's got everyone with her.You need to come in.
What are you talking about?
You shot T.J. Kim this morning.
- What?
- You don't remember?
Don't remember?I didn't shoot anybody.
I've been here all morning.
Can someone confirm that?
No.No.I was supposed to have a
conference call they canceled,though.
Look,I took a half a personal day,
diana.I went jogging.I wasn't at work.
You got to stop saying that,
because two dozen people saw you there.
Now,I don't know what's going on.
Maybe you're blacking out,like kyle did.
Maybe it's something else.
Maybe it's like some 4400 ability.
I mean,I don't know,but...
(缺一句)1
and what happens if I do?
I get arrested for murder?
You know,we'll figure it out,okay?
Everyone wants to help you.
You just--you just have to come in.
You mind if I get dressed first?
Sure.
Are you sure you remember
everything you did this morning?
There's no time gaps or anything?
You didn't take a nap?
Tom?
Tom??
Damn it.
Yeah,hi. It's me.He got away.
I-I don't know how.
They only sent one agent after him.
Look,sorry.He got away.
What?
No way. He's an ntac agent.
They'll be expecting that.
Okay.
You're right.This has to happen.I'll do it.
I was letting him get dressed.
I didn't think he would jump
from a second story window.
Well,obviously,you underestimated
your partner's resolve.
Does he still seem blameless to you?
I don't know.Look,
it was a really bad call,
and I take full responsibility.
I've alerted local law enforcement,the fbi.
I've told them that tom is wanted for
questioning in connection with a murder.
He's a fugitive now.
Oh,don't give me that look,diana.
I had no choice.
Sorry.
- It's tom.
- Yeah.
Tom?
I'm sorry I ran out on you.
Where are you?
- (缺一句)
I believe you.But you have to come in,
and we can figure out what's going on.
No,I'm not going to jail.
No one's going to put you in prison.
They did it to my son,diana.
Was it really him that pulled the
trigger the day jordan collier died?
He's incarcerated.(缺一句)
You're a fugitive,tom.
Every police department in
washington is looking for you.
Some local cop wants to be a hero,spots you,
you know how these things can end.
(缺一句)
Look,dig around,diana.There's got
to be some evidence that will clear me.
Just...help me find it.
Did he give you a location?
Marco,help me out here.
If you were trying to prove that your partner didn't
commit a crime that the whole world thinks he did...
where would you start?
Well,I guess I'd start by pretending
that my partner wasn't involved.
Okay,just think of it like any other case.
What's the first thing you do when you start?
Well,look at the evidence.
I mean,there's a dead body,
there's the gun that tom left behind,
and there's a bunch of
people that saw him here.
Well,they've got security cameras
down in the detention ward,right?
You're serious?You're really
asking me for all that footage?
Of course I'm serious.
Is that a problem?
Well,it's just...
I gave all the tapes to him,
like an hour ago.
what are you talking about?
I haven't been up here all day.
What is this,a joke?
Marco,come on.
You were just here.You signed for
all the footage from the detention ward.
This isn't so hard.
That's because i haven't let go yet.
All right...I'm going to move my hands.
Are you ready?
No,not yet.I'm kind of comfortable.
You're kind of comfortable?
I'm freezing.
I don't know what's going on.
This pool's supposed to be heated.
- Want me to make it warmer?
- You can do that?
I think so. Hold on.
How did you do that?
I don't know.How do you heal?
It's not the same,isabelle.
Healing's one thing.
That's what we can all do--one thing.
Not me.I guess I'm different.
Shawn.
Sorry to barge in.
We're scheduled to brief the board of directors.
- That's starting now?
- Five minutes ago.
They're on hold.
Psst.
Alana.
What are you doing here?
I'm in trouble.
My bosses at ntac,
they think i did something.
I need you to come with me.
- What are you talking--
- I don't have time to explain.
Thomas!
- Hello?
- Alana,I'm right down the street.
I need you to come meet me.
Honey,I'm in trouble.
Everyone thinks I killed somebody.
Who is this?I know it's not thomas.
What are you talking about?
I'm looking at thomas right now.
Honey,listen,that's not me.
The man you're looking at,
he can impersonate me somehow.
I don't believe you.
He walked into ntac and
he shot someone this morning.
Alana,he's dangerous.Get away from him.
Alana,listen to me.
Your mother's middle name is madeleine.
You wanted a dog when you were a kid,
but your parents gave you a bird instead,
a parakeet named charlie.
Listen,we made love last night.
There were two candles burning.
Just hold on.I'll be right there.
Did I have a dog when I was a girl?
I don't have time for this.
- What are you doing?
- What's going on,tom?
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
- Where is he?
- He just ran through the back.
Hey!
Did you see a guy come down this alley?
He looked exactly like me.
- I didn't see anybody.
- (缺一句)
He's gone.
What do you mean?
He just ran out a few seconds ago.
There was no one here.Just some kid.
It was him.
It had to be.I had him.
Had who?What kid are you talking about?
The one who's impersonating me.
The guy who's framing me for murder.
He looked like you.He sounded like you.
He was standing as close as you are right now,
and he had me completely fooled.
(缺一句)
At least we know what's going on now.
He's a 4400,isn't he?
Somehow he can pass himself off as you.
Yeah. I'm not sure how.
I mean,maybe he's got some
kind of optical camouflage.
He can convince your brain you're
talking to whoever he wants you to see.
He's a boy.Why would he want to kill anyone?
Not just anybody.
T.J. Kim,I mean,think about it.
You get rid of the one member of
your cell who could testify against you,
you compromise a government agent,and ntac,
the one agency that's trying to hunt you down,
is wasting their time chasing one of their own.
Alana.
You might want to get in here.
There's all kinds of people
flashing badges everywhere.
They said they're ntac agents.
Look,stall them.I want you to go home.
I want you to lock the doors,
and don't open it until this is all cleared up.
If I need to get ahold of you...
I'll use a password.
How about "death in venice"?
Your favorite book.That's a good choice.
Listen,shawn,thanks for letting me come in here.
I just didn't know where else to go.
Look,you guys must have
a database of 4400s here,right?
I need to get a look at it,here.
I can pull it up on my laptop for you.
This might take a while.
You mind if I let myself out?
There you go.
You know,uncle tommy,
you can stay here if you want.
I might take you up on it.
All right...
but hey,you get the couch.
Okay...
kidneys,huh?
That explains the blood in the urine.
Kevin,we had a deal.
I was going to help you through this as
long as it wasn't compromising your health.
Well,guess what--
I'm calling the hospital.
But they won't let me take my shots.
Oh,no.
You're done with your shots.
I know we had an agreement,
and I'll honor it.
Just let me show you something before you call.
What happened to your fingernails?
Uh,they fell off.
Dissolved,I guess you'd say.
If you're trying to change my mind,
you're not doing a very good--
Kevin...what the hell did you just do?
Kevin,you've developed a 4400 ability.
It's getting there.
Doesn't always work?
I was nervous about that.
It's fun to drive fast.
Yeah.
All that information
about compression rates
and gear ratios just
seems completely irrelevant.
Well,you're not driving home.
Get out of there.
You're lucky you didn't
wrap my car around a pole.
Is there anything on this list
of yours that involves,you know,
a little less risk of bodily harm?
We could have sex.
Come on.You have a big bed.
Whoa,isabelle,hey...
uh,no.
Why? It's on my list.
It's an important rite of passage into adulthood.
It'll be fun.I was good at driving.
(缺一句)
I don't know.
For one thing,your dad would kill me.
Why?I'm an adult.
Well,you are and you aren'T.
Let's just say he has a right to
have an opinion on the matter.
I don't know,isabelle.I feel like
I'd be taking advantage of you.
But I want to.
Well,I'm flattered.I really am.
But I just don't think you're ready to
make that decision.We barely know each other.
I know you better than I
know anyone else in the world.
That may be true.
It's still not going to happen.
Lessons with isabelle going well?
They're not lessons,
and it's completely innocent.
Do me a favor and don't ask about them again.
- This is skouris.
- His name's boyd gelder,diana.
He's a 4400.I know where he lives.
Where who lives?Who's boyd gelder?
The kid who's doing this.
And not just imitate.
He can be me.
At least make you think he's me.
He lives with his mom.
I'm in schenley park.It's right by his house.
Well,can you wait for me?
I'll be 15 minutes.
I'll wait...but diana,just you.
Just me.
We just got here.Where you going?
Schenley park.
I think we caught a break on tom's case.
Tom!
(缺一句)
Just marco.
At least,I thought it was marco.
I looked across the park.
You were standing there.
But it wasn'T.
Tell me about it.You weren't the one
actually chasing yourself across the park.
I mean,I don't really run like that,do I?
It's an amazing ability.Marco's
going to have a field day over this.
Good.Get him working on it.
We're going to need
a way to handle this guy
wait,wait,wait.No,
you don't need to skulk around anymore.
You can come in with me now.
I'm still on the hook for murder,diana.
No,you're not.
Boyd posed as you.He shot T.J.
Kim.You're not responsible.
Listen,I just saw his abilities
that's proof of something right there.
I will back you up on everything you say.
Which means exactly nothing.
I mean,thank you,diana,
but you're my partner.
Everyone expects you to stand up for me.
There's only one way to
prove I didn't kill T.J. Kim.
- I have to get boyd gelder.
- Okay,let's go.
You sure you want to come?
I'm your partner.
Everyone expects that I'll stand up for you.
I should be back by tonight.
I've...
been taking my time,stopping off at
all the places your mother liked.
Everything okay?You been going
to your doctors' appointments?
Most of them.
We need to keep monitoring you.
I'm fine.
Shawn's taking good care of me,just like
you asked.He's doing a really good job.
- Oh,yeah?
- Yeah.
He taught me the backstroke,
he let me drive his car...
and then I asked him to
have sex with me,but he said no.
He said you'd be angry.Is that true?
Isabelle...
you're too young to be thinking about...
- that.
- (缺一句)
But I thought I was almost 20.
How old were you when
you lost your virginity?
It was...
things were a bit different in my day.
It's not the same.
It's not?
Why?
You know what,isabelle?
I'm not having this conversation
with you over the phone.
So shawn was right.You are mad.
I don't understand.
What does ntac want to
talk to my son for,anyway?
He's in some trouble.We can't discuss it.
We just need to talk to him.
Well,he's not here.
He went away on a ski trip with some friends,
and he won't be back till tomorrow.
Ma'am...
your son is not on a ski trip,and this
is serious.Is there any way you can contact him?
First tell me what's going on.I mean,
what is it you think my son did?
Mrs. Gelder,there are a lot of agents...
people get hurt.The sooner we
get to your son,the safer he'll be.
So why don't you call him and
convince him you need to see him.
(缺一句)1
(缺一句)2
Nice mom,nice house...makes you wonder...
if the nova group can turn this kid,
who else have they gotten to?
Everyone keeps telling the 4400
they're here to save the world.
- Whatever that means.
- Exactly.
Say what you like about nova.
They do seem to have a game plan.
Well,I'm just guessing,
but I don't think that's boyd.
How the hell did ntac get here?
Maybe boyd figured out it
was a trap and tipped them off.
- (缺一句)
- Alana,open up.
There are ntac agents watching the house.
They just drove away.They must
be changing shifts.Come on,let me in.
Death in venice,okay?Open up.
I don't want anyone to see me come on.
What did you do with your key?
I lost it.I must have lost
it while I was running around.
Come on.It's me,tom,alana.
I gave you the password.
Please don't make me.
I don't have anything against you.
Tom...says it's your house.
Alana?
I just wrote a letter on your computer.(缺一句)
- Boyd?
- It's a confession.
(缺一句)
You shot T.J.,And now you can't live with it,
so you've decided to kill yourself.
Where's alana?What did you do?
It's my "get out of jail free" card.
See,you're the only
one who could identify me.
Everyone else,they've just been
seeing double.They'll sound crazy.
I'm not signing a suicide note,
boyd.Put alana on the phone.
Oh,you'll sign,'cause either I shoot you...
or I shoot her.
It's a trade.
Your life for hers.
You know what?
I don't think i can let you do this,tom.
We need to call jarvis.We need to block off
the street.We need to surround your house.
- He has alana.
- Tom,
he wants to kill you.The least thing we can
do is make it a little bit difficult for him.
If it was maia in there...would you call jarvis?
Do you like it?
Why did you bring this to me?
You're a young woman.(缺一句)
It's going to look good on you.
See for yourself.
Thank you.
I see you've been spending
a lot of time with shawn.
So?
(缺一句)
Shawn's a very isolated young man.
He doesn't get to spend much
time around people his own age.
I think...you should get
as close to him as you can.
Matthew?
Shawn's nice.
What I'm doing with him is not for you,
and it's not because i'm trying to use him.
Of course not...
but eventually,isabelle,
you and shawn are going to be on opposite
sides of a very large ideological divide,
so...enjoy your friendship...
but don't let your emotions run too deep.
It'll make things more difficult later.
What things?
You'll know.
It doesn't match your eyes.(缺一句)
You were a beautiful woman.
Both of you.
You looked exactly alike.
I never could figure out why.
One way or the other,I've had a
lily in my life for over 50 years.
That's all gone now...
and I don't know what I'm going to do...
but,uh...
it makes me feel better knowing
the two of you are together...
forever.
This is it for you,you know.
I don't know what kind of fairy
tale the nova group sold you,
but it doesn't matter
what happens to me,or tom.
Your life is over.
They sent you on a suicide mission.
I volunteered,and I don't think you're
in any spot to be giving me advice.
You're a 4400.
You're special.
You're supposed to be changing things.
Live with an ntac agent.
And what are you going to change,boyd?
You killed a girl.
How does that make the world better?
T.J. Kim was a soldier.
She would rather have me put a
bullet in her head than betray us.
Everyone talks about saving the world.
(缺一句)
Everything's been turning bad,
one disaster after another...
but we're going to show the world a new way.
We're going to take them down a new path...
by force if we have to.
Why can't you see the real
catastrophe is to sit back and do nothing?
Did you hear that?
Stop it!
Stop it,both of you!Stop,or I'll shoot.
Nice work,alana.We got him.Shut up!
Alana,death in venice.
Yeah,that's the password.
Come on,alana.Give me the gun.
We'll call ntac.It's over.
(缺一句)Ask me a question. Anything.
Don't fall for it.
He's probably read my file.He knows
everything about us.Don't listen to him.
Ask me something about us.
Something only I would know.
Anything about us.
(缺一句)
Baby...
I am so proud of you.
(缺一句)
You know about billy?
Yeah.That was your son.
He died in a car accident.
Alana,he did research.
Anyone could find that out.
Give me the gun.Just give me--
give me the gun.
Alana,give me the gun.
No.Alana...
give me the gun.
Get down on the ground.
What?
No,you've got the wrong one.
Think about this.
I said get down.
Don't move.
You're just a boy.
I'm a soldier.
And there are more of us every day.
Let's go,soldier.
Welcome back.
Yeah,thanks.Everything go okay?
Yeah,thank you,and thank you
for keeping an eye on isabelle.
Oh,well,it's not a problem.
Didn't really do much.
Yeah,well,thank you anyway.
I worry about her.
You don't really need to.
She seems to be getting along really well.
I'm her father. It's my job.
And it's harder with isabelle.
People see her,they see a woman,
a beautiful woman...
and they might forget that
inside she's just a little girl.
Still...
I'm glad she has you around...
to be a friend.
(缺一句)
How did you get in here?
I can do stuff,remember?
Yeah.
So,what's up?What do you need?
Just one thing.
It's on my list.
First kiss.
This isn't smart,isabelle.
Okay.
" 4400  Season 03 Episode 03 "
-=END=-
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
Proudly Presents