We're not a threat, We're salvation,
The world will have to deal with us.
Previously on The 4400:
I've been offered a job
working with the children
at the school.
I blew the surprise, didn't l?
I just wanna make one thing clear.
Me breaking up with Danny
has nothing to do with you.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I'm the guy who killed you.
Is this list complete, huh?
Because I'm just wondering
how many 4400s you did kill.
What's up? Who are these guys?
They've been brought in
to help expedite the interrogation.
I know you find this hard to believe,
Tom, but we are on the same side.
One of our members
has been compromised.
I have to assume
he's gonna give up my name.
If you know where Armand is,
we'll tell NTAC. They'll take care of it.
Daniel Armand's inside. He's all yours.
This is it.
The last member of the Nova Group.
It's the last one
we know about, anyway.
If this tip is good
and we bring in Gary Navarro,
this could pretty much
be the end for the Nova Group.
The tip is good.
All right, here they are. Let's go.
Move. Move.
Gary! It's over!
- Go. Go.
- Downstairs.
- Room searched.
- You two, that way.
- Got it.
- Clear.
Check over here.
Clear, sir.
There's nobody here.
Looks like he just left.
In the middle of making lunch?
He must have known we're coming.
Someone must have tipped him off.
Isabelle.
You're not hearing me.
Sure, I did.
You said you don't wanna
be with me anymore.
I just don't see why.
The Nova Group's gone.
My dad knows about us now.
There's nothing to stop us
from being together.
Yes, there is.
Me.
This is because of what happened
to Matthew, right?
You think I killed him.
And the people
from the Nova Group too.
I wasn't in my right mind, lsabelle,
so I don't know what happened.
Well, then I'll tell you.
Matthew had a stroke,
some terrorists died
and you got better.
What's to question?
I just think that you and l
got a little too intense, too fast.
See, I thought that was the best part.
Sorry for the interruption.
Shawn, there's someone here
to see you.
She's a friend of yours.
She says it's important.
Nikki. Oh, my God.
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
It's been a long time, Shawn.
Yeah.
- Hi.
- I should have called first.
- No.
No, it's fine.
You look great. How have you been?
Good. Good. School's kind of fun.
It's just...
My father.
He's been sick.
Oh, your dad? I'm sorry to hear that.
It's cancer.
It's in his pancreas.
There's nothing they can do.
Shawn?
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
I just need to deal with this thing now.
So we'll talk later, okay?
Okay.
So, Amy, you used to call
your grandmother Mimi?
Yes. I'd go stay with her
for two weeks every year.
But when I came back
with all the other 4400s,
my mom told me she was gone.
Alana Mareva?
We're from
the National Security Agency.
You need to come with us.
What is this about?
The Pentagon has commissioned
a study on the membership
and the origins of the Nova Group.
We've been authorized
to interview all persons of interest.
And why would I be
a person of interest?
Ma'am, we have a list.
Your name is on it.
Let's not make a scene
in front of the child.
How did my name get on the list?
What am I being accused of?
We have evidence that suggests
you're a member of the Nova Group.
I wrote a check.
My friend, Ryan, at the Center,
came up to me one day
about six weeks ago.
He said he couldn't pay his power bill.
They were gonna shut it off
if he didn't come up with the money.
It was a small loan, $1 65.
- No big deal, right?
- Ryan Freel?
We picked him up three days ago.
He's one of the names
Daniel Armand gave us.
So they were right. He was in Nova.
They say they can hold me
for providing financial support
to terrorists.
It was just a loan, Thomas.
How long are they
gonna keep me here?
They can hold you for questioning,
without any charge, for 36 hours.
But it's not gonna come to that.
This is harassment.
It's not gonna continue.
I'm gonna talk to Ryan Freel.
I'll get him to admit
that this is just a casual thing.
That it had nothing to do with Nova.
Alana, I promise this is all
gonna be over soon, just--
Just sit tight, okay?
I love you.
I know it's frustrating,
but there's nothing we can do.
Nina, it's harassment, pure and simple.
Yeah, I know it is.
And I don't like it either.
But the Nova Group
made a lot of people nervous.
Now that it's broken, the military wanna
make sure that it's dead and gone.
Yeah, we all do.
It's still no excuse to hold an innocent
woman based on absolutely nothing.
Well, I agree.
But the Pentagon
went around us on this one.
They went private.
They hired the Haspel Corporation
to conduct the study.
Haspel Corp? They do a lot
of defense contracting, don't they?
Yeah, right now, they're focusing
on this Nova report.
NSA even loaned them agents
to do field work.
Now some conglomerate has
the right to arrest and detain people?
Where is the oversight?
There isn't a lot.
Look, this whole thing
runs on the discretion
of the executive in charge of the study.
So who's this executive?
I appreciate your frustration, Tom.
It's unfortunate that your girlfriend
got involved in this mess.
But my people are just being thorough.
Your people?
Alana's being held
by the National Security Agency.
The way I remember it,
your life in public service ended
with a perp walk through NTAC.
Yeah, there were
some unpleasant moments.
But that's the past.
I was censured for my part in the
inhibitor scandal, I guess you'd call it.
"Scandal"? Why don't you try
"murderous plot."
Your opinions
are already a matter of record.
Not that the majority of people
agree with you.
Anyway, after the government saw fit
to terminate my employment,
I weighed my offers
and wound up here. Haspel Corp.
And Alana just happened to wind up
in your crosshairs, right?
Tom, do you think
I would use your girlfriend
to prosecute some kind
of personal vendetta?
Actually, Dennis, yeah, I do.
So that's his punishment
for causing the deaths of 28 4400s?
A six-figure consulting gig
and a corner office.
Don't act so surprised, Tom.
We always knew Ryland
had a lot of support for what he did.
Learning anything new?
Yeah. She's incredible.
In a week, we've made discoveries
we thought it would take years to get to.
Where'd you find this girl?
He didn't find me.
I found him.
Shawn.
It's all right, Jimmy.
Hey.
That was amazing.
It looks like my father could walk
out of here this afternoon.
Good.
And I know my whole family
just thanked you again and again
but I wanted to say it too.
- So thanks.
- It's all right, Nikki.
You look so different.
Last time I saw you, I don't think
you even owned a belt.
You used to wear the same
flannel shirt every day for a week.
A lot's changed, I guess.
And now you're doing so great.
Kind of makes me wonder
why you never call
just to say hi, you know?
I was just trying to put everything
behind me, I guess.
But I thought about you a lot.
- I've gotta go, I guess.
- Yeah.
Tell your dad not to hurry back
to the office, okay?
He always was a workaholic.
We just got the phone records
in from Gary's safe house.
A call came in at 1 1 :1 4 a.m.
Eleven-fourteen?
That's right before we got there.
It's a tip-off call. It had to be.
It came from inside the 4400 Center.
Look, I really don't know what to say.
I can't tell you why that call
came from my office,
but I didn't make it.
Heather, we've got phone records
that say it came from your extension.
You said the call
was made around 1 1 :1 0, right?
Then there's no way
it could have been me.
I was teaching a class
from 1 1 to noon.
I was standing in front
of 1 2 students for the entire hour.
I never left the room.
Anyone else have access
to your office?
Just the janitor. But you'd have
to ask Maintenance about that.
We will. We'll need to talk
to your students as well.
Look, Heather,
NTAC isn't the only organization
investigating the Nova Group.
There's gonna be a lot of people
looking at those phone records.
They're all gonna be less friendly
than we are.
Sorry, guys.
It's like I said. I was in class.
That's all I know.
I got a little worried about you
this afternoon.
You were gone all day again.
I was out walking.
I like to do that now.
Dad, I need you to talk to Shawn.
Tell him he can't break up with me.
It would be a mistake.
I can't do that.
For one thing, I don't think it is.
I know how much it must hurt
right now, but you'll get over it.
Don't talk to me like I'm a teenager.
There are things I have to do.
They're going to be really hard.
Dangerous.
And if Shawn's not with me,
it's gonna make things worse.
Worse for who? You?
No. Everyone else.
And what if he says no?
Be more convincing.
Heather. What's up?
I need to talk to you.
Listen, I've been thinking
all day about this.
I didn't tell you everything
this afternoon.
There was someone
who had the key to my office.
Okay, this person,
I need to know who it was.
Tom, it was Alana.
I didn't wanna say anything
in front of your partner.
I'm sure you understand why.
Tom, did Alana know
that you found out
where this guy Gary was living?
Yeah. Yeah, she did.
I was on the phone with her
when the tip came in. I told her.
She knew we'd been
chasing Gary for a long time.
Heather, come on, it wasn't Alana.
There has to be
some other explanation.
I hope so.
And I hope you find it.
But what do I do while you're looking?
You said it yourself, you're not the only
one with access to those records.
You're not the only one
who's gonna come asking questions.
You tell anyone who asks the
same thing you told me this afternoon.
Your alibi checks out.
Unless you say differently,
no one is gonna be able to prove you
lent that key to Alana or anyone else.
Heather, Alana didn't make that call.
If you just stick to your story for one
more day, this whole thing will be over.
What if I say no?
She comes after me? You?
I don't know.
I know she's determined
to get you back.
It's like she sees you
as her one connection to the world,
to people, to a normal life.
So, what you're saying
is it's like my job,
to keep her, I don't know, human?
It sounds that way, doesn't it?
Look, Shawn...
...I'm not trying to tell you what to do.
But I do know this.
Isabelle's not giving up.
Not without a fight.
And we've both seen what happens
when my daughter decides to fight.
Is everything all right, Thomas?
Don't think about it as informing.
You're helping us catch a criminal.
Now, I need you to tell me, who
did you lend Heather's office key to?
Sweetie, please. This is important.
Somebody compromised
our investigation.
I didn't give the key to anyone.
It was me, Thomas.
I called Gary Navarro.
I don't understand.
Are you a member of the Nova Group?
- No, of course not.
- Then why?
I trusted you.
I told you what we were doing
and you used it to betray me.
I wasn't betraying you. I did it for you.
How many times have I heard you say
that you felt responsible
for what happened to Gary Navarro?
He came to you for help
and instead the government used him
and turned him against his own kind.
I don't like what happened to Gary.
But he chose to become a terrorist.
He joined Nova of his own free will.
Gary wasn't with the Nova Group
anymore.
What?
How would you even know that?
A lot of people at the Center know it.
After the Nova Group
had T.J. Kim murdered,
he turned his back on them.
How can you even believe that?
Gary personally tried to murder
Dennis Ryland.
Ryland is responsible
for the death of 28 4400s.
Twenty-eight people that might
have changed the world for the better,
were they allowed to live.
He declared war on us.
I almost died, Thomas.
All Gary did was fight back.
You should have told me
what you were gonna do.
I wanted to.
But I couldn't.
You were bound by your job.
You couldn't give Gary
another chance.
So I did it for you.
And now you're gonna stand trial
right alongside of him.
You made that phone call
from the Center.
It's right there
on Gary's phone records.
They'll figure it out it was you, Alana.
So, what?
Am I supposed to lie for you now?
Am I supposed to become
Gary's accomplice too now?
I'm not asking you to do anything,
Thomas.
If you want to turn me in, fine.
But I believe I did the right thing.
And I hope the man I love
would believe it too.
Nikki, if I did pay off
your dad's hospital bill--
And I'm not admitting to anything.
--let's just say
that it's not that big of a deal, okay?
I'm glad to do something
with my money.
Giving up my social life to work
seven days a week at this place
has to have its perks, right?
I have a hard time believing
that you don't have a social life.
Running this place is a big job.
You know,
it kind of cuts you off from the world.
Well, I don't have $60,000.
But if you're feeling isolated,
you know, maybe I can
pay you back in another way.
There's a new sushi place
that opened in Belltown.
It's supposed to be pretty cool.
You like sushi now?
You're not the only one
who can change.
Just give me a second, okay?
Hey, Shawn.
Have you seen my copy
of The Republic in here?
No, you know what? I haven't seen it.
Hello again. I'm lsabelle.
Nikki. Nice to meet you.
I've heard of you.
Well, let me know if you find my book.
I'm right in the middle of it.
So tomorrow night?
You wanna check out
this new sushi place?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Tom, I'm so sorry.
Anything I can do to help?
I don't know.
I don't know what I can do.
I can't just turn Alana in.
If we do catch Gary,
eventually he's gonna give her up.
So, either way, her life is ruined.
Well, Tom, there's no way
you can try
and shake this agency off
Gary's scent.
You'll wind up a felon yourself.
I have to do something, Diana.
We're talking about Alana.
And one way or another, we've been
together for more than a decade.
I have to protect her.
Once I know she's safe,
then I can figure out how we move on.
If we move on.
You need to keep yourself safe too.
I think that the best thing
that we can do,
the only thing we can do...
...is to take ourselves off this case.
And do what?
Cross our fingers.
Hope Gary buys himself
a one-way ticket to Costa Rica.
What did you expect to happen?
I don't know.
But it's only for 36 hours, right?
- That's all they can hold her for.
- Honestly, I'm not sure.
They can hold her for as long
as it takes to investigate her alibi.
We're talking about
Dennis Ryland here.
You told me a dozen times,
he'll do whatever it takes
to get information.
He's going to interrogate her
and I don't know how far it's gonna go.
Alana, I'll call his office
in the morning.
I checked out
Heather's alibi myself.
I'll give them my notes.
It'll all go on the record.
Right now it's all I can do.
You know, I'm always happy
to talk to one of the 4400.
But I have to say,
I was surprised to find you
waiting outside my office this morning.
You can release Heather Tobey.
That phone call to Gary Navarro,
I was the one who made it.
Dennis, thanks for seeing me
on such short notice.
What were you thinking, Tom,
to get romantically involved
with a 4400?
What Alana did was misguided.
It was wrong.
But Gary wasn't part
of the Nova Group anymore.
Are you actually gonna stand here
and defend Gary Navarro to me?
The Nova Group isn't a bridge club.
You don't just leave.
Even if Gary tried to,
that doesn't absolve his other crimes,
which include attempted murder.
If the doctors had gotten to me
30 seconds later,
I would have been dead.
I know how badly
you want him, Dennis.
If it was up to me, Gary Navarro
would never even make it to trial.
Okay, forget about Gary.
Can we just concentrate on Alana?
Well, I'm afraid it's not possible
to make that distinction.
They're kind of intertwined,
aren't they, Tom?
Alana will be prosecuted like
any other member of the Nova Group.
She's not a member
of the Nova Group.
Dennis.
We've known each other
for 25 years.
You have to help me.
Like you helped me
when my back was to the wall?
Okay, I'm not a petty man, Tom.
I'll honor our relationship.
Thank you.
I appreciate anything you can do.
I'll tell NSA
you had nothing to do with this.
You may be a dupe,
but you're not a traitor.
And as for Alana,
the best chance of seeing mercy
is to cooperate fully
and help us find Gary Navarro.
Now you wanna catch
Gary Navarro?
Tom, we've already passed
the case off to Roth and Tierney.
We've got to get him before they do.
We've got to get him before
Ryland does. Before anyone.
Look, Ryland wants Gary.
It's a personal thing.
If we get can get Gary first,
we can deal with Ryland directly.
A straight-up trade. Gary for Alana.
So Ryland gets his hands on Gary
and it happens with no official record.
No arrest.
None of that sticky due process.
You really think
that Ryland's gonna agree to that?
If we dangle Gary in front of him?
In a heartbeat.
Look, Tom, l...
You saved my daughter's life.
I owe you everything for that
and I'll do what you want here.
But this is dangerous.
And it's a lot of trouble to go to for...
...a woman
who just betrayed you.
I owe her that much. More than that.
My son is incarcerated, Diana.
Alana's been right there with me
all the way through it.
And she doesn't deserve to rot in some
secret prison for the rest of her life.
Well,
any idea where we'd start?
Yeah.
Hey, Shawn.
Isabelle.
What are you doing in here?
I came by to talk.
I know you're still thinking about us,
but we're still friends, right?
I can still drop by.
Well, lsabelle, usually friends knock.
What's up?
I came to talk to you about Nikki.
I know you pretty well.
I don't think
she's the right girl for you.
Well, I don't know
why you think she's my girl.
You're entitled to your opinion,
though, I guess.
I'm just trying to protect you.
I just have this feeling
that if you guys get together...
...it's going to end badly.
Isabelle, what does that mean?
- Are you threatening Nikki now?
- Of course not.
Why would I threaten Nikki?
It's just, I have this feeling
that if you two hook up,
it's not going to end well.
Not for you.
Especially not for her.
It's always harder on the girl,
you know?
Hey.
Are you doing okay?
Yeah, more or less.
I want to help you, Alana.
I want to get you out of here.
- I don't think you can.
- I do.
I think there's a way,
but I need you to trust me.
I think you should cooperate
with Dennis Ryland.
Tell him whatever he wants to know.
I can't do that, Thomas.
That would be a betrayal.
Learn to live with it.
Listen to me, if you don't cooperate,
I don't think you're ever
gonna get out of here.
I can't.
Then I can't help you.
Thomas.
I was supposed to take the students
on a field trip to the aquarium
this afternoon.
I need you to go there
and leave them a note.
There's a bulletin board
outside the aquarium.
You should put it there
and it should say "field trip canceled."
Some of the kids will show up
with their parents.
When you see them,
give them my apologies.
I'll make sure they understand.
It was a code. At least I think it was.
She was telling me
how to get ahold of Gary.
Well, I don't know, Tom.
It's already been two hours.
Let's give it another 1 5 minutes.
Diana.
Gary, stop!
- Oh, my God.
- Get down, get down.
- Move along.
-Get down, get down, get down.
- Look out.
- Get out of the way.
Look out, look out.
Get out of the way.
- Hey.
- Go get the gun.
Come on.
Get the kids, get the kids.
Look out, get back.
- Go, move.
- Watch out, watch out.
Don't move, Gary. Don't move.
It's over, Gary.
Come on, get up.
So you're gonna turn me over
to Ryland.
You know
what he's gonna do to me, right?
Ryland is gonna interrogate me.
Yeah, you know all about that.
You've seen that firsthand.
And then he's going to
disappear me.
No trial. No record.
I'm not a mind reader, Gary.
Not like you.
I have no idea
what Ryland's gonna do with you.
That's how you get through this
hand-off with your conscience intact?
All right, you wanna know?
I'm trading you for Alana.
She helped you, now it's your chance
to help her. You owe her that much.
You made your own bed, Gary.
Nobody forced you to join Nova.
Nobody forced you to kill people.
I was a baseball player.
I was worried
about making the major leagues.
That's it.
If I hadn't met you two,
I'd be shagging grounders right now.
Okay, you should go.
If you still want to, that is.
But if you make this deal with Ryland,
it's forever.
I mean, we live with this.
I'll call you after the meet.
You're gonna have to
move him right away.
Seven-thirty, on the nose.
I gotta say, I'm impressed.
A big mogul like you,
figured that you'd keep a girl waiting.
- Hey.
You ready to go?
Nikki,
Iisten, we can't do this.
Do what? Dinner?
Shawn, it's not a big deal.
That's what people do at night.
You know this is about
more than just dinner.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to stand you up.
I just can't do this right now.
Shawn, I don't get it.
What happened?
Did some adviser tell you
that I don't fit in with your PR strategy?
No, nothing like that.
It's gonna sound like
a stupid guy thing.
Me leaving here right now
is the best thing I can do for you.
All right, then.
Go.
Bye.
So, Tom, I'm guessing
that if I don't agree
to this trade you're proposing,
you're not gonna drop Navarro off
at the nearest police station, are you?
You say no
and you can forget about
getting your hands on Gary Navarro.
I'll get him a passport,
a plane ticket.
He'll be in a Third World country
by this time tomorrow.
And if I decide to play along?
You want to know whether I'll be
asking questions about Gary Navarro
after you drive away with him?
No,
I won't be.
It's gonna be tricky to make
the charges against Alana go away.
You can do it, Dennis.
I have faith in you.
Let's go.
Listen, take this key ring.
The blue key
opens a safe-deposit box.
There are eight letters inside,
and I'd appreciate it if you'd mail them.
These letters,
who are they addressed to?
Eight families. All over the world.
Your NSA work.
Those are the families of the 4400s
that you helped target.
Right. I figure...
...it's time to let them know
what happened.
Give them a sense of closure.
Seems like the least I can do.
Seems like the only thing I can do,
actually.
You okay?
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I know it wasn't your idea.
Nice working with you again, Tom.
Well, that went well.
Tell me, why do I have
such a weird feeling in my stomach?
It's not easy
to sentence a man to death.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Quiet back there.
It's all right. Let him pray.
Forgive us our trespasses as we...
Look out. Pull over.
Get out of the car. Get out.
Keep your hands
where I can see them. Up.
where I can see them.
- Are you okay?
- Okay.
Tom, you need to think about this.
Tom, you're letting a terrorist
walk free.
No, I was a soldier.
You created me.
All I did was switch sides.
Well, guess what?
Now I'm done fighting.
- I'm walking away from the war.
- There is no walking away.
You've got numerous federal charges
hanging over your head,
including attempted murder.
Murderers walk free
all the time, Dennis.
Some of them even get cushy jobs
at Fortune 500 companies.
Very cute, Tom.
Have you thought about
what this means for your girlfriend?
Making her a fugitive is kind of
a funny way of showing your love.
I'd rather be on the run
than be responsible
for handing over a 4400 to you.
Skouris, you're supposed to be
the level-headed one.
Are you really gonna
throw your career away
because your partner
is on some personal crusade?
Oh, I don't see it that way, Dennis.
And if you want to hold on to your job,
you won't say anything about this.
A 4400 you personally signed out
of a military detention facility?
A secret trade in a remote location?
It's all kind of messy.
I'm guessing this one
stays off the books.
Let's go.
Nice working with you again, Dennis.
There's two lDs in there, and there's
enough cash to last you for a while.
The Canadian border's
about 30 miles away.
I'd-- I'd cross as soon as you can.
Ryland will be looking.
Yeah.
You know, it's been almost two years
since I've met you two.
And I remember that you said
that you would help me.
Well, it's been a long time coming,
but I guess you finally came through.
Thank you.
I didn't want us to end, Thomas.
Ever.
And especially not here, like this.
It doesn't have to end.
I can come with you.
You can't.
You need to be here.
You're one of the only good men
left in this fight.
I'll find a way to bring you back.
I promise.