Over the last 60 years
4400 people have been abducted
All at once they were returned
With no memory of
where they've been
They haven't aged a day
And some have returned
with new abilities
All are trying to reconnect...
...with a life interrupted
We're not a threat.
We're salvation.
The world will have to deal with us.
Previously on the 4400...
the canadian border's
about 30 miles away.
I'd cross as soon as you can.
Ryland will be looking.
I didn't want us to end, thomas.
Ever.
I'll find a way
to bring you back, i promise.
April!
Surprised?
How's it going,
sibling?
Jordan, you just told me
there's a little girl out there
who can see the future, and she saw you dead.
Do i stay away from the center?
I cut myself off?
Even if you confess, kyle,
he is still going to jail.
You try to bury stuff like this,
it changes you.
We have to get married.
It's the only way we can be sure we'll
never lose each other.
Shawn!
Shawn farrell!
Do you know who i am?
Get out of the way!
Jordan!
Let us through!
- Jordan!
Jordan!
Did you see jordan collier
come through here?
No, sir.
- Long hair, beard.
Anyone?
You saw him, right?
Yeah.
Look, i want
this place secure.
No one gets in or out
until i say different.
Come on.
All right, guys,
let's look around.
Guys, we've been
all over the grounds,
and we can't find anybody.
Are you sure it was collier?
It was him.
He looked right at me.
He talked to me.
It did look like him,
but i only saw him
for a second.
Well, if he's on foot,
he can't have got far.
I think we should call ntac, get them
to sweep the neighborhood.
Shawn ?
What's going on?
The ceremony was supposed to start
20 minutes ago.
Richard,
i just saw jordan.
He's alive. He's here.
What?
Where?
Look, shawn, me and diana
have to get moving, okay?
Hey, no, no, no, no.
I'm coming with you.
- What?
I'm going to help you
find him.
Jordan looks different now.
I'm the one who got
the best view of him.
Shawn, you're in the middle
of your wedding.
We've got
a thousand guests here...
The media...
Isabelle ?
You're going to have to do
some damage control.
Tell isabelle that the wedding's
not off...
It's just postponed...
And I... And I'll come see her
as soon as i can.
I'm sorry.
Are we ready to go?
Daddy, what is it?
I thought we agreed.
I don't want to see you.
This couldn't wait, kyle.
He's alive.
Jordan collier is alive.
I'm going to
find him, kyle,
and i'm going to get you
out of here.
It's okay, sweetie.
It's going to be okay.
I just feel so bad for you.
I'll be fine.
You don't need
to worry about me.
Shawn. Thank god.
What happened?
All the guests are gone.
Everybody thinks
you walked out.
That's...
it's okay. I just...
i need to talk to isabelle
for a second...
If you don't mind.
So, your "daddy" came home, huh?
Your dad told you
about jordan?
He did.
I was really curious as to
why i wasn't getting married.
I'm sorry, isabelle.
I am.
Jordan's out there somewhere.
I need to find him.
And then what?
If he's alive, what does
that mean for you and me?
I'm not sure.
Jordan was dead,
and now he's not...
shawn, is the wedding off...
or isn't it?
It's still going to happen.
Just not today, and not until
i figure out
what's going on with jordan.
I know
collier means a lot to you.
To everyone here.
Find him.
Di...
April, my god,
what are you doing here?
I came to see my sister.
Tell me, do you have some kind of allergy
that keeps you
from calling ahead?
I wasn't sure
that was a good idea.
If i called,
you might have refused
to see me.
So, are you going to hug
your only sister,
or are you going to
shut the door in my face?
I'm sorry. I just...
you surprised me, that's all.
I mean, i didn't even know
you were in seattle.
I'm moving here.
Why?
Are you in trouble?
No! I'm in love.
I know what
you're thinking...
"same difference"...
but not this time.
This guy's the keeper.
Oh, that's... that's great.
I'm really happy for you.
Well, wait till you meet him.
Which should be any minute now.
He's parking the car.
April, i'm in the middle
of something for work.
It won't take long.
Just a couple of minutes.
Please?
It'd mean a lot.
I bet you
maia would be happy, too.
Aunt april!
Someone's getting tall.
Look at you.
You're like a supermodel.
I bet the boys
think so, too.
Maia, this is
my friend ben.
I heard a lot about you, young lady.
Your aunt says you're a very special girl.
Maybe a little.
Sorry, i'm in a bit
of a rush.
I actually told april
we should have
called ahead.
See? Polite.
And if you did
a body search,
you wouldn't find a piercing
anywhere.
April mentioned
that you're
a photographer.
Uh, yeah.
April and i just
got back from india.
I was doing a piece
on the caste system there.
It's all for a show
he's putting on
at the museum
of contemporary art.
Really?
Wow.
Well...
- Yeah..
I spent some time
in india
when i was
a graduate student.
We were doing
an epidemiology study
in the nilgiri range.
We were there.
Well, you are
so lucky.
It was so beautiful.
I used to wake up early
so i could watch
the sun come up
over the foothills.
Yeah, i've got some shots
of the sunrises,
just for my own
personal collection.
If i'd known
you were interested,
i'd have brought them by.
- I'd like to see them.
I'll bring them by.
I look forward to it,
but right now,
i really got to rush.
Bye.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
Bye.
- Bye.
You're right.
He is a keeper.
This is a nice place.
Collier sure had an eye
for real estate.
I mean, what,
this is the sixth place
we've looked at today?
Must be nice to have
that kind of money.
Diana...
look at this.
Someone's been staying here.
Guys.
It's from a soup kitchen
downtown.
What does
the notebook say?
The whole thing's full.
"The city is
a thousand miles wide.
"The last city.
"The walls
are a hundred feet high.
"Nothing grows
on the outside anymore,
"so the people
beg to be let in,
but nobody listens."
It's all like this.
Is that collier's handwriting?
This is just preliminary,
but i ran the handwriting
from the notebook
against the sample
from collier's
that you gave me.
Now, they don't
look alike at all.
I mean, the handwriting
from the notebook
is shaky,
almost like
whoever did it is sick,
but the software says
that they're a probable match.
So jordan wrote this stuff?
I can't say for sure,
but there's a lab
in d.c.
That'll be able to give us
a positive identification.
But it's probable, right?
Jordan's alive.
Well, we don't know that yet.
I'll tell you
one thing...
if he did write this,
he has seen
some interesting stuff
while he's been gone.
The whole thing
goes on and on
about a walled city.
You know,
a privileged elite
lives on the inside.
Everything else
is just a wasteland.
Oh, and then the last few pages
are just one phrase
repeated
over and over again.
"The war for the future
will be fought in the past."
Mommy?
Oh.
You scared me.
Sorry.
I couldn't sleep.
Oh, well...
why don't you come on in.
I'll make you
a bowl of ice cream.
Our family's
going to get bigger now.
Oh, sweetie...
don't get too attached
to the idea
of your aunt april
living in seattle.
You know how she can be.
That's not it.
You're going to get married.
I saw it.
Not too long
from now.
You look the same
when it happens.
I'm getting married?
Isn't it great?
You're going to be
so happy.
Okay, well, um...
did you happen to see
who the lucky guy was?
Yeah.
It was the man we just met.
Ben.
Maia...
you saw me getting married
to my sister's boyfriend?
Mm-hmm.
But ben is with aunt april.
I guess
they don't stay together,
'cause you two are going to
get married.
You're going to
have a husband.
I'm going to have a dad.
Isn't that the best?
Hello?
Oh, hey, tom.
No...
we're up.
Have you seen this man?
Sure.
I volunteer at
st. Alban's kitchen.
These guys brought
the sketch by
when we were
closing up tonight.
We bring food down here
twice a week.
I've seen him.
You sure about that?
Positive.
I remember him
because everyone else
always lets him go
to the front of the line.
They get
out of his way.
I've never seen that before.
But you haven't seen him today.
Not for
a couple of weeks,
but i always see him
eating with will.
Will's kind of
the elder statesman around here.
He knows just about everyone.
Yeah, i know him. We all do.
The preacher.
"The preacher"?
He never said his real name
was jordan collier.
I thought collier was dead.
Who are you guys, anyway?
We're from ntac.
We need to
find this man.
When's the last time
you saw him?
Just now.
He's here?
He's always here.
It's pretty empty.
You're sure
he's back here?
He never goes anywhere.
Okay...
say hello...
to the preacher.
You made
a painting of him?
Not me personally,
but the preacher's
a popular guy.
He's got some amazing stories.
The guy claims
to have seen the future.
People around here...
we believe him.
You lied to me, isabelle.
I don't remember much
about being a baby.
You and mom, mostly.
Vague stuff.
I remember collier.
I remember
how he made you guys feel,
and i remember how i felt
when he touched mom that time.
You gave him something
to remember that day.
Collier was recovering
for months.
That's not the only thing
i did to him.
Right before he died,
he came to talk to me.
I know it sounds weird...
i was just a baby...
but he wanted me to tell him
whether it was safe
to go ahead with the party
he was planning.
I remember.
That's when he asked to take you for a walk
through the gardens.
He wanted... power.
He wanted acclaim.
A name that would live on
after he died,
so that's what i showed him.
So, what,
you gave him a vision?
He had the party.
He got shot.
I didn't pull the trigger,
but daddy,
i made that happen.
If collier's back,
he knows what i did.
What does he want? Revenge?
We don't even know
whether or not he is alive.
What if he tells shawn
what i did?
You sound like you're
scared of collier.
Isabelle...
Collier's a very powerful man...
but he is just a man.
He was just a man.
We don't know what he is now.
Guys, i've got something
you need to check out.
You know that graffiti mural,
the one that might be collier?
Well, there's a national
graffiti database.
I ran the portrait
against it.
And?
This preacher guy?
He gets around.
That one's
from st. Louis.
That's el paso.
Tempe, arizona,
reno...
these are from
all over the country.
If this is collier, he's been a very busy man.
He might need a shave and a haircut,
but he's still got charisma.
He's got followers everywhere.
So, what, he's traveling around,
preaching the gospel of the future?
Are you almost done?
I was going to
make you a snack.
Five more minutes.
- Okay.
Did you see ben today?
You mean
your aunt april's boyfriend?
No, i didn't see him,
and i'm not going to see him.
Your antenna is not working right
on this one, sweetie.
Okay.
Hi.
Hum...
look, i'm not the type of guy who drops
by unannouncedall the time, i promise...
Okay...
But i was just in
the neighborhood.
I didn't have your phone number.
The pictures we talked about?
Oh.
Thanks.
Um, come in.
Hi, maia.
Hi, ben.
I'm going to go to my room
to study.
You two talk.
Um, so,
you going to open it?
Does it look
familiar?
That's
the nilgiri hills.
Yeah.
Listen...
this is not going to happen.
Excuse me?
Married?
Are you sure
she meant me?
Uh-huh.
Well, that can't happen.
I'm glad you agree.
April told me about maia
and what she can do,
but she's wrong here, right?
Oh, she's going to be.
Okay, um...
i'm going to go...
And no more visits
to bring you pictures.
No more visits, period.
Okay, well...
it was nice
meeting you...
and then resolving
never to see you again.
Yeah, nice to meet you, too.
Did you kill me?
That's him.
That's him!
That's jordan collier!
Tell them i didn't kill you!
Tell them
you're jordan collier!
Tell them!
Tell them you're
jordan collier!
Tell them!
is that who i am?
When you went
to see kyle,
you signed in
as jeffrey paulson.
Why?
I found a library card
in the pocket of my coat,
and that's what it said.
I thought...
i thought
maybe that was my name.
Your name
is jordan collier.
You don't
remember that?
You're one of the 4400.
Am i?
You were shot.
You died.
Ah...
Yes, i saw that in the papers.
I thought i looked
like that man.
You disappeared.
Do you have any idea
where you've been?
Everywhere.
I have been everywhere.
I've been alive for hundreds of years,
maybe thousands.
I couldn't speak to anyone.
I just...
i wandered.
No food, no sleep...
And i watched it all.
I watched the world...
change...
and it just kept
getting worse...
and the skies
filled with smoke...
and all the machines
stopped working,
and the streets,
and the rivers...
were filled
with bodies.
The dead...
were everywhere.
The earth...
cried out...
and it...
it never stopped.
The things you're talking about,
they haven't happened.
Not yet, anyway.
It's 2006.
It's been less than a year
since you were shot.
How could it be?
I've been wandering
for so long.
That's the preliminary
dna report.
That man we're holding
is jordan collier.
Well, at least
somebody's sure of it.
I need collier to remember who he is
so he can stand
in front of a judge
and ask for my son to be freed.
But tom, this is
already a win for kyle.
Collier's alive.
So he serves a term
for attempted murder
instead of murder?
No, no, no, diana.
That's not good enough.
Look, collier knows who he is.
It's buried in there somewhere.
He showed up at the wedding.
He found his way
to one of his safe houses.
We just need to find a way
to help bring it all
to the surface.
Tom, i just got off the phone
with the national security
advisor.
He wants to schedule
a conference call
with him, me,
and the joint chiefs of staff
to discuss the fact
that jordan collier
is somehow
back from the dead,
and you want me
to look the other way
while alana mareva, a fugitive, walks into ntac
and uses her ability on collier?
She can access his memories.
Show him his life.
These people in d.c.,
they need collier to remember
who he is, too, right?
They need answers.
This might be the only way
to get them.
Nina, please...
Come on.
We're talking about my son.
You have a way
to get in touch with alana?
Make the call.
I got it, maia.
You just couldn't stand
to see me happy, could you?
April,
what are you talking about?
What did you say to ben? Huh?
What did you say, diana?
Nothing. Why?
He broke up with me!
You weren't supposed
to break up with her.
That's not why
i told you what maia said.
I realize that,
but you have to understand,
a precog just told me
that i was
with the wrong person,
and if you know
you're with the wrong person...
why stay with her?
I don't know.
Maybe because you love her.
I do love april.
At least,
i thought i did.
You know, i can't believe how casual
you can be with all this.
Maybe it's because
you live with a 4400.
But someone just told me
that i met the person,
the woman,
that i'm supposed to be with.
I can't ignore it.
You know, i want you
to tell me the truth.
When you look at me,
do you feel anything at all?
An attraction?
An inkling of an attraction?
Yes.
I do.
You asked
for the truth,
so, yes, i do.
and if i met you
under different circumstances,
yes, i'd...
i'd want to see you again.
Yeah.
Me too.
But it doesn't matter.
We can't do it.
Yeah, i know.
I'm going to take my sister's
stuff and go.
But wouldn't it be something
if we were giving up
our shot at happiness?
Hello, thomas.
You cut your hair.
I can't believe
you're here.
Thank you
for doing this.
For kyle, i'd do anything.
You know that.
Besides, i missed you.
You ready?
You don't have to
do anything.
Just shut your eyes
and relax.
You won't feel anything.
I promise.
My name's jordan collier.
If i could stay here
for a while...
you're one of the 4400.
That baby could be the key
to the future.
Peter has all the time
in the world.
Hi, peter.
My name is jordan collier.
Hello, richard.
Welcome
to the revolution.
Collier, are you all right?
My name is jordan collier.
I know why they sent us back.
I saw the catastrophe,
and i know what we have to do to stop it.
You say you have
all these answers.
Tell us what they are,
and then we can talk,
about letting you out of here.
You'll learn what i know
when everyone else does.
When will that be?
As soon as i am free,
you and the world
will know what i know.
And what if we hold you
indefinitely?
I've grown accustomed
to waiting.
Yeah, well, i can't.
My son is in prison.
You're the only one
who can get him out.
Then you want me released
as badly as i do.
Your son kyle
is innocent.
He is a pawn,
and i will say that
to whomever you want...
the moment i am a free man.
I can't believe this, nina.
My son could be one court
appearance away from freedom,
and you're refusing to let
collier testify on his behalf?
I'm not refusing.
The pentagon is.
Their official position is,
collier's not even back.
Come on, nina.
They can't honestly believe
that they can squash this.
Well, they're
going to try.
Look, collier's return
changes everything.
We're not just talking about
galvanizing the 4400.
There are
religious groups
all over the world
who would consider him
the messiah.
No matter what he says,
no matter
how crazy it is,
people are going to listen.
So maybe we should find out
what's on his mind
before we stick him in front
of a bank of microphones.
And what if we don't like
what he has to say?
We stick him in the basement,
pretend this never happened?
I don't think
that's going to be our decision.
I'd be surprised
if collier's
not transferred out of here
by this time tomorrow.
They should be here by now.
You sure you're okay?
L-i will be.
When i touched collier,
those things i saw...
they weren't only
from his past.
There were other images, too.
Terrible ones.
It was like a nightmare.
I don't know
how collier
lived through it
and stayed sane.
I don't want to leave you,
thomas.
I don't want
to go on the run again.
You know, maybe
you don't have to.
What you did today,
it helped ntac.
If i tell them
they can have access
to your ability,
maybe they'll drop the charges
against you.
I'd never hurt the 4400...
I know.
Maybe we can work it
so you don't have to.
Okay?
Uncle tommy.
Wait right here.
What the hell's
going on?
I didn't help you find jordan
so you could lock him away.
Shawn, they're scared.
This is how the government reacts
when it's scared.
You know, if we wanted,
we could take him.
If we set our minds
to it,
we can get into ntac,
and there won't be
anything you can do to stop us.
You may be right...
but there might be another way.
Here.
That's a still
from a security camera at ntac.
It was taken
this afternoon.
You show it
to everyone.
You let the world know
that collier's back.
Thank you.
Yeah.
wagon wheel.
You know, i used to
live on those things in college.
Ben...
what are you
doing here?
Well, i eat, too.
So...
what do you think?
Coincidence? Or is this thing going to happen
whether we try to stop it
or not?
Well, normally,
i'd give you a lecture
about free will right now,
but i have to admit,
it might sound a little hollow.
Well, we're both here.
We're both shopping.
Want to join forces?
I loved doing
the final project.
Let me guess...
faces of the elderly.
Red lights.
Every time i stopped
at a red light,
i'd take a picture.
Mm-hmm.
You had to study
these intersections
that you never
really noticed.
Like, the stores,
the people,
the garbage cans...
huh.
Everything.
That's very creative.
I was just
screwing around.
No, i would like
to see them.
Okay, yeah, i think
i've got them somewhere.
No...
wait.
What?
We can't do this.
We just did.
That was a date,
and that was
a pretty good one.
No, it wasn't.
It was nice,
but it wasn't a date.
Then why do i feel
like doing this?
You got to admit,
that was nice, too.
Can i see you again?
Free collier now!
Anyone else feel
like it's bastille day?
Well, it does feel
like the start of something.
We have got to let him go.
It's either that
or bring in troops.
And we won't just be
reading the riot act to 4400s.
There's clergy out there.
Citizens.
Look, we can't just sit on this.
If collier
is some kind of messiah,
he needs to be free.
If he's not,
letting him out
is still the right move.
It would give him enough rope
to hang himself.
I'll call d.c.,
but they're going to
want to know
how those people
got their hands
on a picture of collier.
Any idea what
i should tell them?
Yeah, tell them it's hard
to cover up a resurrection.
Free collier now!
Free collier...
It's you.
Welcome back, jordan.
Thank you
for keeping the center alive
while i was gone.
Richard...
i'm glad to see you
still with us.
You'll have
an important role to play.
I stand here...
and i see the future.
4400s and non-4400s
working hand in hand
toward a common goal.
Saving humanity
is no longer
the exclusive province
of the 4400.
Each and every one of you
will have work to do...
and the work starts now.
We're going to the courthouse.
There is an innocent man
who needs to be freed.
Look, just get those people
away from this building.
You're impeding
the business of my court.
They won't leave
until you listen
to what i have to say.
I hereby withdraw
any and all charges
against kyle baldwin
for my alleged murder.
Well, Mr. Baldwin
still assaulted
two federal agents.
Now, he fired a high-powered weapon
into a crowd of people,
and he admitted it all
in a detailed confession.
My son has been in jail
for months.
He's a first-time offender.
You could release him
with time served.
Those people out there,
they listen to me.
They will be back every day
until this man's son goes free.
Well, these are
highly unusual circumstances.
I'll grant you both that.
Perhaps we can revisit
the murder plea.
Do. Quickly.
Thank you.
I thought
you didn't want to see me.
Oh, i don't.
I want to see your pictures.
Oh.
Well, okay,
so i knew you'd be here.
Well, then why'd you come?
I guess i've been thinking
about the grocery store,
and...
i thought
it was a good date, too.
It just didn't end right.
Okay...
and how should it
have ended?
Hey, mommy.
Hi.
Where you been, di?
Nowhere.
I just...
had to work late.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Don't apologize.
Those things you saw in me...
pride, ambition, vanity...
they were there.
I had to die
to lose them.
I've done bad things...
and i'm supposed to do more.
I know.
And i'm trying not to.
Tell me what to do.
I'll do anything.
Leave.
Leave the 4400 center,
and never come back.
Nothing you can do will change
what you are, Isabelle.
You are the enemy
of the 4400,
the enemy of everything
that is good,
and that part of you that is human...
It is much smaller
than the part of you that's not,
and your struggle to keep it
alive will fail.
No.
I have a choice.
Others might. Not you.
If that's true,
if we're enemies,
then why shouldn't i
just kill you right now?
You're welcome to try,
but it won't work.
I'm ready for you this time.
This place is mine again...
And you're not
welcome here.
Goodbye, Isabelle.
Transcript : www.1000fr.com
Synchro : FRM@mywsz, Benj!.