over the last 60 years
4400 people have been abducted
all at once they were returned
with no memory of
where they've been
they haven't aged a day
and some have returned
with new abilities
all are trying to reconnect...
...with a life interrupted
We're not a threat.
We're salvation.
The world will have to deal with us.
Previously on the 4400...
I need you to talk to shawn.
Tell him he can't break up with me.
It would be a mistake.
Isabelle's not giving up,not without a fight.
I don't want this relationship to end...
so it's not going to.
I know I haven't always been there for you,kyle,
but I thought we had a pretty good relationship.
We do. It's just...
growing up with a dad who works for the fbi,ntac...
it can be pretty intense,you know?
You're supposed to say,"I wanted to."
Don't push your luck.
I told you what we were doing,and you used it to betray me.
Ryland is responsible for the death of 28 4400s,
28 people that might've changed the world for the better were they allowed to live.
Alana will be prosecuted like any other member of the nova group.
You're one of the only good men left in this fight.
I'll find a way to bring you back.I promise.
Hi,erika.
Stay away.
I'm not going to hurt you,erika.
I just want to talk.
That's what you always said.
That's how you used to get me up into your room.
I mean it now.
I swear.
This time I'm for real.
I'm not going to let you touch me!
It's okay.
Uncle patrick's here.
Tom baldwin?
I need your initial by the X.
What is it?
Sorry,man. Not a psychic.
"These are not dinner.Hang in there. Diana."
Baldwin.
Jarvis said this is a suicide.
Any idea why we got called?
Not really.
She said there's a D.E.A. Agent at the scene.
Apparently,he requested an ntac presence.
Hey,by the way,thanks for the cookies.
That was really thoughtful.
Cookies?
Yeah. The basket full of cookies.The ones you sent.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I didn't send you anything,tom.
In fact,I was going to thank you.
Thank me? For what?
I got a basket of cookies,too,maybe an hour ago,from you.
At least,that's what the card said.
I didn't send you anything either.
You two from ntac?
Yes.
Matt ruddy.
I'm with the D.E.A.
Come on in.
I guarantee you'll find this interesting.
Her name's erika lundgren.
She's our third suicide in the past two weeks.
Why is the D.E.A. Investigating suicides?
Because we think they're all connected.
For the past six weeks or so,
we've been hearing about a new recreational drug hitting the streets.
It's called "blink."
We got a small sample off a dealer we arrested.
But why call us? It's hardly our area of expertise.
We had the sample analyzed.
One of the components our laboratory guys isolated was like nothing he'd even seen before,
so they did some more checking.
It's similar to what they found in the 4400s.
What do you call it?Promicin?
What,so,this drug "blink,"you think a 4400 is synthesizing it?
That's why I called you guys.
If there's a 4400 involved in this,
I figure you could help track him down.
Absolutely.
It'd help if we knew more about this drug.
We don't know much about it,
except it seems to be a powerful hallucinogen.
Well,how do you know erika lundgren was on blink when she jumped?
Her roommate told us.
Erika took blink this morning.
Pretty soon after that,
she started telling me she was seeing her uncle.
She was really freaked out.
I mean,the guy's in some prison for 12 or more years.
Do you know where she got the drug?
When erika wanted to get high,
she'd go see this guy she went to school with.
I guess he deals now.
I mean,I don't know if that's where she got it from,
but his name's greg.
He usually hangs out in cowen park.
He always wears this old high school varsity jacket.
Erika said he used to be a track star or something.
Tony.
Take care of her.
Thank you.
We should probably head to cowen park,
find out where this guy greg gets his blink.
Hello,tommy.
Dad?
Hey,tommy,you're standing in the middle of the street.
Better be careful.
Tom?
Tom,what are you doing?
Come on.Off the road.
What's going on?
Diana,that D.E.A. Guy,
h-he said blink causes hallucinations,right?
Of course. Why?
Because I think I just saw my father.
He was right over there.
Tom,your father's been dead nine years.
Exactly.
sync:fisherchen
www.YDY.com
Proudly Presents
It was the cookies.It had to be.
Tom,slow down.
Why would anyone want to slip you blink?
I don't know. Maybe it's some bitter 4400,someone who hates ntac.
Yeah,maybe,but I ate a cookie too.
I'm not seeing a dead relative.I feel fine.
Tom,you've been under a lot of stress lately.
All this talk of hallucinations--
your mind just decided to play tricks on you.
Yeah. Maybe.
Still,though,I think I should probably drive.
Well,what do you want to talk about?
Diana,do you see him?
See who?
My father. He's right there.
Tom,I don't see anything.
Nobody else can see me,pal.
I'm just here for you.
Just be quiet.You're not real.
Listen to me,tom.There's no one there.
Real or not real,I'm here,
and you're going to have to deal with me.
What do you want,dad?
It's not what I want.It's what you want.
You're the one who brought me here.
Must be something you want to say to me.
I've got nothing to say to you.
Tom,listen to me.There is no one back there.
You just have to try and calm down.
Yes,there is,diana.He's right--
he's gone.
He was right there,diana.I swear.
Tom,I'm going to take you into ntac medical,all right?
It's going to be fine.
That was nice.
See? It all still works between us.
I'm glad you came back.
Isabelle,not right now,okay?
I've got stuff I should do.
Let it wait.
Isabelle...
this time,if you want,
I could make you think I'm someone else.
Anyone you've ever had a fantasy about?
I can make the earth move for us.
Literally.
Isabelle,you don't need to use your abilities to tempt me.
Believe me,you're just fine on your own.
I've just got to go.
You never used to leave right after.
We've lost something,haven't we?
I mean,we still fit together and everything,
but it's not the same,is it?
No,it's not.
And we keep pretending everything's the same way it used to be.
I still keep pretending.
How's it working for you?
Not well.
I think I know what we need to do.
Good.
I'm glad you realize it too.
We have to get married.
It's the only way we can be sure we'll never lose each other.
Isabelle--
you go do your stuff.
I'll start thinking about a guest list.
Your cat scan came back fine,
but your blood pressure is still a little elevated.
Aside from that,your vitals are holding steady.
What about his labs?Any drugs in his system?
The toxscreen is negative,but that's not surprising,
because we don't know a lot about testing blink.
We've given you a mild sedative,
but that's all we can do for the moment.
So I can go home,right?
I haven't seen my dad in,what,six hours.
Well,typically,it takes about 48 hours for a psychotropic drug to leave your system.
We don't know much about blink.
So it's impossible to say how long the effects will last.
Or how severe they'll be.
Hallucinogens tend to affect everyone differently.
It depends what kind issues you're carrying in your subconscious.
All right,I'll have garrity give you both a ride home.
You two are taking a couple of days off.
I don't need a couple of days.I feel fine.
Yeah,but you ate the cookies,too.
And until we're sure the drugs are out of your system,
you're both on medical leave.
I spoke to your dad about our conversation.
We wanted to talk to you together.
I don't know if you're serious about this whole proposal thing,
but we need to nip it in the bud right now.
You and me getting married is not a good idea.
You're both too young,
and neither of you are ready for that kind of commitment.
I can't allow it.
I'm your father,
and I'm telling you this is not going to happen.
Your father speaks for both of us.
I'm not going along with this.
I get what the both of you are saying.
There are millions of reasons why we shouldn't get married.
There are just more reasons why we should.
Did either of you ever think that maybe this relationship was meant to happen?
That shawn and I were set up to meet,fall in love?
Isabelle,I don't love you.
Shawn,you and i are the two most powerful people on the planet.
We're supposed to be together.Who else is good enough for you?
Isabelle,the man just told you straight up--
he doesn't want to marry you.How much clearer does he have to be?
You have to accept that.
No.
I don'T.
Actually,you two need to change the way you're thinking.
Maybe it would help if you thought about it like an arranged marriage.
The future wants us to be together.
We're going to be together.
I'll make sure of it.
Are you sure you're going to be okay alone?
Because I can stay with you if you'd like.
No,I'm fine.
With any luck,that stuff's worn off already.
Well,call if you need anything.
I will.
Good night.
Okay,garrity,you can take me home now.
Hey,diana.
Josh?
It's good to see you.
You look...different.
You look exactly the same.
What are you doing here?
There's some stuff that we need to talk about.
I don't think so.
I mean,we haven't spoken in,what,11 years?
I don't see any reason to change that.
That's a bit harsh,don't you think?
We've been through a lot together.
No,you put me through a lot.
There's a difference.
You all right?
It looked like you were just talking to yourself.
No. I'm not okay.
I think I got slipped a dose of blink,too.
Really.
Who'd you see?
No one.
Just some guy I used to know.
You were engaged?
Yeah. In grad school.
I had to take a physics course.
Josh sandler was the teaching assistant,
and we dated for three years.
I'm sorry. I know it's a lot to spring on you.
Yeah,well,you never said anything.
Well,it's not something I particularly like to talk T.
Uh,I don't want to sound jealous of a hallucination,
but...you must think about this guy a lot,huh?
Tom's seeing his dad.
You know,that makes sense.
Every kid's father is buried deep in their psyche.
Erika lundgren saw her uncle.
Who knows what kind of history they had.
Look,I can't answer for her,
but I can tell you that josh and i have plenty of our own history,
and most of it bad.
We had a fight about 10 days before the wedding,broke the engagement.
It was ugly.
Do you want to talk about it?
No.
The last thing I want to do is talk about josh sandler.
Listen,I'm exhausted,
and I just want to take a shower and get into bed.
Want some company?
No,not tonight.
I'll call you in the morning.
Okay.
You got the place to yourself now,huh?
A lot of room for one guy.
You know,now that alana's gone,
you ought to think about selling the place,
get some kind of an apartment.
Than for the suggestion,dad.
I like it fine here.
Still holding out for your son to come home,huh?
I've got to tell you,buddy,
I don't think that's going to happen.
Hey,don't get mad.
Trying to have a conversation here,
except you're not saying anything.
I wouldn't even know where to start.
Pick a topic.
Fine.Let's talk about when I was a kid.
I used to hate coming home when I knew you were going to be there.
You were nasty to mom.You drank.
You hated being a beat cop so much that you did everything you could to keep me out of law enforcement.
When I did get into the fbi,you never called.
Never said congratulations.
Too busy being jealous of your own damn kid.
Okay.I'm officially talking to myself now.
Feeling better?
Come on,tommy,you're a grownup.
I never figured you'd still be carrying so much anger toward me.
Being a father,you know how complicated it gets.
Look at you and kyle.The kid's in jail.
He won't even talk to you,let alone see you.
Kyle needs some time,and I'm giving it to him.
That's called respect.
I have always been there for him,good times and bad.
I didn't learn that from you.
I know I wasn't much of a father.
I tried to be there for you and susan.
Look for understanding someplace else.
In fact,why don't you do us both a favor and just go away?
That's not going to happen.
Fine. Then I will.
You can't just walk away,pal.
It ain't going to be that easy to get rid of me.
If you won't go away,I'll make you go away.
I'm going to find the 4400 who's doing this to me,and I'm going to force him to stop it.
You're going back on the case?
I'll come with you.
No,no.
I'm not working an investigation with my dead father.
I don't think you've got much of a choice,tom.
Either I come along for the ride...
or you and me go back inside and talk some more.
Fine.
Just don't show up when I'm in the middle of talking to somebody,okay?
No problem.
It's been a long time since I worked a case.
It's going to be fun.
You still make those late night bowls of ben & jerry's,huh?
Josh,I want you to go away.
Just stop showing up in my life.
You know,it's funny,
but you'd only make yourself ice cream after everybody else had gone to bed.
I used to wonder what that said about you.
You know,you're going to have to talk to me eventually.
No.
You see,you're a hallucination,
so I just have to make a conscious choice to ignore you,
and eventually,you'll be gone.
That's a good plan.
I just don't think it's going to work.
See,there's a reason I'm here,diana.There has to be.
You're random,just a mental hiccup.
Josh sandler isn't even dead.
I googled him tonight.
He teaches astronomy at pomona college.
So?That's the present-day josh sandler.
Your issues are with me,the guy you were engaged to.
I don't have any issues!
Mommy?
Are you okay?
I heard noises.
I'm fine,sweetie.
I'm just...practicing something for work.
Come on.
Let's get you to bed.
You were engaged?
Why does everyone have such a hard time believing that?
Well,it's not a hard time believing it.
Just... well,you never told me.
It was a long time ago.
It didn't work out.
Listen,I'm glad you called.
I don't like the idea of a drug in my system that caused three suicides.
These hallucinations we're having--
so far,it doesn't seem like the same thing erika lundgren went through.
All my dad wants to do is talk.
I know. Josh hasn't threatened me either.
As long as it stays that way,
there's no reason we can't use our "free time" to look into this case.
There's that delivery service.
If we can track down the source of those cookies,
maybe we can find the 4400 who's behind all of this.
And there's cowen park.
That dealer doesn't know anyone's looking for him.
I'll take the park,you take the delivery service.
Sounds good.
Anything but waiting around for my ex to show up...
devon,all of these messages are from this morning?
Yeah,well,everyone wants to congratulate you on your engagement.
Don't you want to start returning?
No,I don't want to talk to anyone.
Not even your mother?I have her on hold.
Yeah. Thank you,devon.
Mom. Hey.
No--
mom--
mom,who told you I got engaged?
No. I'm coming right over.
Mom,where are you?
A little mischievous one,wasn't he?
So cute.
Look at those eyes.
Look at that little butt!
Somebody tell me what's going on here?
If it isn't mr. Secretive.
I'm just showing your fiancee your baby pictures.
Consider it punishment for not making me the first phone call.
Come on,sit.
I'd love to,but isabelle and i have to actually get going.
We have a lot to talk about.
You bet we do.
My oldest boy is getting married,and I'm going to help plan the wedding.
I promise we won't make any decisions without you,
but isabelle,we need to go now.
Shawn,you're being rude.
I don't mean to be,but we really need to go.
Now.
It was really nice seeing you again.
You too.
I love your son very much.
We should probably be heading in the other direction.
Great. You're back.
We're going to covington,right?
You shouldn't backseat drive,josh.
You know,it was always one of your least flattering qualities.
Could you speak up a bit,ma'am?I didn't catch that.
I wasn't talking to you.
I was j--
sorry.
I don't mean to be annoying.
I'm sorry for everything,actually--
the way things worked out with us.
I-- I just had to say that out loud.
Apology not accepted.Do you mind just being quiet?
You know,I have to admit,
this is not how I pictured you at all.
I mean,working for the government,you're carrying a gun...
the whole thing with us,the wedding--
it really must have changed you.
As usual,josh,you're placing yourself at the center of everything.
Maybe I have changed,but it's got nothing to do with you.
In fact,until you showed up yesterday,
I hadn't even thought about you in...five years?
What?
It's just that your left eye still does that little twitching thing when you lie.
Yeah,I remember you.The gift basket.
Right.Well,there were cookies inside,
and we have reason to believe that they were laced with an illegal drug.
Hey,I don't know anything about that.
I just pick stuff up and deliver it.
Well,you delivered it to me.
Where'd you pick it up?
That's supposed to be confidential.
I guess it's okay this one time.
It was an old building downtown.
Here it is.156 liberty avenue.
Look at these people.
They don't even try to hide what they're doing.
I tell you,things have changed since I was walking the beat.
Yeah. I know.
You would have won the war on drugs singlehanded.
You've become a really angry guy,you know that?
I'm not trying to pick a fight here.
I know I'm not perfect.
You're not even alive.
All right,fair enough.
I wasn't perfect.
I blame most of that on the job.
You get burned out dealing with this crap.
Violence,ugliness...
it got inside my head.
I couldn't switch it off when I got home.
That's why I drank.
That's why I got nasty sometimes with you,your mother.
I'm not making excuses for myself.
You seem to need some kind of an explanation for what I did.
That's the best one I can give you.
Okay.
It's not anything I didn't already know,but...okay.
That dealer we're looking for?
Didn't you say he wears some kind of a high school varsity jacket?
Yeah. Why?
I don't know what you're so worked up about.
You won't find anything.
This wouldn't happen to be blink,would it?
So what if it is?
Blink's brand new,man.
Feds haven't even had time to make it illegal yet.
Yeah,we'll find time.
That's what we do when people start dying.
So who's supplying you with this?
You think I'd tell you that?
Baldwin.
Did jarvis say what this is about?
No,just that there'd been some break in the case.
These are the agents that were affected?
This is tom baldwin,diana skouris.
They were compromised yesterday.
I am so sorry about all of this.
You were drugged against your will,
and those young people committing suicide--
it's all so terrible.
Uh,ma'am,who are you?
My name is naomi bonderman.
It's my ability that did this to you.
I caused all of this.
one day about 3 months ago
I woke up with what I thought were sweaty palms.
Then I realized it wasn't sweat.
It was some kind of...
oil,I suppose you'd call it.
And that's when I first saw my sister.
This sister of yours,you hadn't seen her for a while?
Ruth's been dead for 30 years.
And there she was,standing at the foot of my bed.
We were never close.
But once I realized I hadn't gone completely batty,
we had a very nice visit.
Finally,after all these years,
we worked things out between us.
In the morning,she was gone.
And then I touched gordon's hand.
Gordon?Is that your husband?
No,my mailman.
And that night,he was visited by some army buddy of his who was wounded in the first gulf war.
That's when I started wearing my gloves.
Mrs. Bonderman,have you any idea how your ability came to be sold on the streets?
At first,I had no idea,
but now,I think it had something to do with my fried chicken.
I use a lot of herbs in my cooking.
I grow them myself.
That's the only place I don't wear my gloves,
when I'm working in the garden.
And the herbs absorbed the oil from your hands.
My family had come over for sunday dinner,
and that night,they all started having their own encounters.
It was very emotional for everyone,
but it all seemed to work out for the best.
No one died or anything.
Could someone have gotten ahold of these herbs,
used them to make this drug?
Well,that must have been what happened.
The tuesday after the dinner,I went out to water,
and all of my plants were gone.
Pulled out.
Someone stole the herbs from your garden...
someone who knew the effect they could have.
I had hoped one day my ability might be used as a kind of therapy,to help people,
but now it's being sold on the street and people are dying.
It's just horrible.
Mrs. Bonderman,have you any sense of how long these visions usually last?
Sometimes the visitors stay for days,weeks,even.
I know one thing,though.
The more you ignore them,the longer they stay and the more insistent they become.
I know we're officially on medical leave,
but I thought I might check out that address we got from the delivery company,
try and find who sent the cookies.
You want to come along?
Actually,I was going to stop by mrs. Bonderman's house,
go over the guest list from that dinner one more time.
She seemed a little vague about who was there.
You think one of them might've gone into business with grandma's recipe?
It's a place to start.
Isabelle,this has to stop.
You can't force me to marry you.
You've got cold feet.
I've read about this.
No,it's not cold feet.
I want you to understand this not going to happen.
I'm not going to marry you,
and if you can't accept that,
if you want to hurt me for rejecting you,
you go ahead and do it.
I'm right here.
Let's get it over with.
I would never hurt you,shawn.
That's good to hear.
Okay,we're clear,right?
It's over between the two of us?
You told me once that good and evil was a choice,
one you get to make.
Well,right now,I'm at a place where I have to make that choice,
and I'm afraid if I lose you,I'm going to make the wrong one.
Who will you threaten this time? My mom?
Shawn,I'm not threatening anyone.
I'm asking for your help.
My help?
There are things I was sent here to do,brutal things.
Your mother and millions of other people could die because of me.
I don't know how you could know that,
but it doesn't have to happen that way.
You can fight it.
That's what I'm trying to do.
That's why you and me,we need to be together,
because I think you're the only one who can stop me.
Are you sure this is the place?
Yeah. I stood right here.
Guy came out from the back,handed me the cookies,that was it.
The management company said this office has been vacant for eight months.
You said these guys are drug dealers,right?
I mean,maybe they move around a lot.
Maybe they operate out of a whole bunch of different places.
And the man who gave you the cookies,
you don't remember anything about him?
I wasn't really paying attention.If I saw him again,maybe.
Look,since no one's here,can I go?
I've got to get back to work.
Yeah,sure.
Thanks for trying.
Call me if something comes to you.
Sure.
Is that a clue?
I'm trying to work here.
You know what,this isn't fun for me either.
I've got my job,too.
There must be something you want to say to me,talk about old times--
old times?
You cheated on me,two weeks before the wedding.
Who does something like that?
I figured you'd still be still mad about that.
It took me forever to get over what you did.
The hurt,the betrayal--but I did it.
I put you behind me,I moved on,
I'm not interested in a single thing you have to say.
Josh?
Are we done?
Anybody could get over that fence.
Thanks for pointing that out.
Remember when you were a kid,you used to help me mow the lawn?
I remember you yelling at me for missing spots.
I wanted you to do a good job,
take pride in your work,be a man.
Yeah,well,it worked.
No matter what the situation,
I just think about what you would do,and I do the opposite.
Never failed.
That's my tommy.He's got all the answers,huh?
When it comes to you,I do.
All right,then,answer me this.
The last time I went in the hospital,
the time I didn't make it out,
why didn't you come see me?
It's a simple question,tom.
Agent baldwin?
Would you like some iced tea?
Let's see,there were barry,kathleen,and the twins--
oh,they cried all through dinner--
philip and his new girlfriend.
I'm afraid I don't remember her name.
Uh,roger and julie.
I'm sorry,julie was sick that day.
A sinus headache.She gets them all the time.
That's my grandson,randy.
He works for door-to-door delivery?
He's still finding himself.
Does he know about your ability?
Oh,of course he does.
He was here at that dinner.
He had two helpings of chicken.
Neighbor says randy left a few hours ago.
No idea where he went.
We know he's not at work.
I'll check the bedroom,see if I can find an address book.
Don't you guys ever stop for lunch?
I thought I'd gotten rid of you.
No,no,we still have some ground to cover.
You know that thing that you said about how you moved on,
that you put me behind you?
I'm not really sure I'm buying it.
I don't care.
Well,maybe not.
But if you're so over me,
how come you haven't had a single serious relationship since we broke up?
I have had plenty of serious relationships,
ones that were a lot more respectful and successful than the one I had with you.
You want to name one?
What do you call marco?
I'd call him a very sweet guy who would do anything for you.
You could learn something from him.
Still,it's a relationship with no future,and you know it.
That's why you're with him.
I have no idea what kind of future I've got with marco.
We haven't been going out that long.
You'll go out for a couple of months,
and then when he pushes you for a commitment,
you'll finally tell him the truth,
that there isn't any chemistry,
that you're really not right for each other--
all things you already know.
Is that really the way I treat the guys I date?
Di...
you're an amazing woman,and I blew it.
What I did to you was cruel,
but you can't keep protecting yourself forever.
It's not fair to you,and it's not fair to marco.
Offhand,I'd say somebody's been doing some baking.
Yeah,but where did all of the cookies go?
Look,buddy,I know you're busy,but you never answered my question.
Why didn't you come see me when I was dying?
Dad,I really can't talk about this now.
Hey,it's not my favorite memory either.
So let's get it over and done with.
Then I'll leave you alone.
You mean if I tell you,that's it?
We're done,you're gone?
It would be a step in the right direction.
I was in baltimore,working on a case for the bureau.
When I got the call from mom,I booked a flight home.
I was all set to go,but then the case heated up and I missed my plane.
By the time I could get another one,it was too late.
I asked you for the truth,tommy.
You're just giving me excuses.
You want the truth?
I stayed away as a favor to you.
You didn't want me there,dad.
Whatever I'd say,whatever I'd do,
it would only piss you off,like always.
I figured my not being there would make it easier for you.
I let you die in peace.
I wanted to see you one last time.
You're my son,tommy.I love you.
Well,that's nice to hear,but it's a little too late.
I know.
That was my fault.I'm sorry.
But I did want you there,tommy.
You were wrong about me,about how I felt.
Maybe you're wrong about some other things.
I hope you're going to show me a kitchen filled with cookies.
I wish.
I think he took them with him.
Better take a look at that.I found it wedged behind the dresser.
It's like he kept a record of everyone he dosed.
You think it's some kind of enemies list?He's trying to get back at all these people?
Diana...
that's the food fair.It starts today.
Now we know where he took the cookies.
Tom...
stop!
Get up.
Where are the rest of the cookies?
There aren't any more,I swear.
He just opened the box.Looks like we made it just in time.
Nice work,you two.
Ntac medical will be busy for some time.
Yeah,we'll keep them under observation,get them counseling.
I take it you both have been too busy ignoring your medical leave to deal with your own situations.
We figured first things first.
Yeah,if my dad showed up,I'd be spending a lot of time at work,too.
But now,I want you both to go home and deal with this thing.
If you feel you can't,
we'll book you adjoining suites at ntac medical.
Okay?
I just want you to know I never meant to hurt anyone.
Well,tell that to erika lundgren and the others who died.
I'm really sorry about that.
Honestly.
But all I did was give them a chance to deal with their problems,
you know,face to face.
I just wanted to share the enlightenment.
I guess they couldn't handle it.
Well,I don't get the connection.Why send the cookies to us?
What are you talking about?
You guys exposed the promicin scandal.
You saved my grandmother's life.
It was a gift,my way of saying thank you.
"Thank you"?
I guess no good deed ever goes unpunished,huh?
All this stuff isabelle told you,
you sure she wasn't making it up,scaring you,trying to keep you close?
Because I'm telling you,shawn,
this sounds crazy.
I can heal people.You can move things with your mind.
We live in a crazy world.
When she was a baby,
even younger,when she was in her mother's womb,
I knew she was different,dangerous.
Richard,if I believed that staying with isabelle would save all those lives,
I would marry her tomorrow.
But what happens a month from now,or a year?
What happens if she gets tired of me or I make her angry?
I get it. Marrying her is not the answer.
We've got to find another way to stop her.
She's my daughter,shawn.
What would you have me do?
Hey,I was out with some of the guys.
I came right over as soon as I got your voicemail.
You okay?
I picked up some italian on the way here.
Don't be nice to me.
Uh,I don't like the sound of that.
I know this isn't pleasant,but you're doing the right thing.
Does this mean we can say goodbye?
As a matter of fact,it does.
Try not to miss me,di.
I won'T.
Goodbye? You mean you're leaving?
All I've been doing is making you miserable.
I figure I did enough of that when you were a kid growing up.
Yeah,we're done here.
We've made about as much progress as we can make,huh?
You take care.
I'd shake your hand,but it doesn't work that way.
Dad?
You know what I said before about my missing that flight home as a favor to you?
That wasn't true.
I never thought it was.
I did it for me.
It was just the idea of standing around that hospital room,watching you die...
with all of that anger still between us,
knowing that we'd never work it out,
that we'D...
we'd never be as close as I wanted us to be.I couldn't do it.
It's okay,tommy. I...
I didn't deserve to have you there.
I should've been there anyway.I'm sorry.
The clock just ran out on us,huh?
Well,I guess there's no clock now,is there?
I've got all the time in the world,
not that we have to use it.
Why don't you come and sit down?
Tommy,we don't have to do this.
I know.Why don't you,uh...
why don't you just come back in the kitchen and park it,okay?
I never liked eating alone.
Nothing worse.
So...what do you want to talk about?
Happy now?
You tried.
It didn't work.
You can't kill me,shawn.
I guess we're going to get married after all.
sync:fisherchen
www.YDY.com
Proudly Presents