Dr. Marcus.
What was so urgent you
needed me here tonight?
It's Dr. Walden. There's been a complete
normalization of his higher brain functions.
Considering the source of the trauma,
nothing surprises me.
You mean the Kawatche caves?
How does a linguist go into a coma
deciphering a Native American language?
If you had that answer, doctor,
you'd be running the place.
The day is coming.
The day is coming. The day is coming!
Lana.
It's almost midnight.
Yeah, I took a chance
you'd still be up.
You getting a head start
on your term paper?
I've gotta give the toast
at Lex's rehearsal dinner.
Makes European history
seem like a breeze.
- I'm supposed to guess what's in the box?
- No.
You're supposed to close your eyes.
Don't peek.
Okay.
I know. It's not your birthday
for another seven minutes...
...but I wanted to surprise you.
You did.
I get the feeling
it's not in a good way.
It's just, it's not really
my birthday.
It's just some date my parents picked off
the calendar for the adoption papers.
Maybe some of us want to celebrate
the day you came into our lives.
I never thought of it that way.
Make a wish.
I've been wishing for the same
thing ever since I was 5.
And now?
And now I don't have to.
She's standing right here
in front of me.
- Good morning, Mom.
- How was your birthday party?
So you're the one who told Lana.
She knows we're not
big on birthdays...
...but wondered if she
could do something special.
Thanks.
I feel bad. We never had parties
when you were little...
...but we were always nervous.
- It's okay, I understand.
I know...
...but what mother denies her son a
birthday party? It's a part of childhood.
All the mistakes you made with me,
you can correct with the baby.
- Wouldn't want to scar the little one too.
- Thanks a lot.
So, last night?
- Are you prying?
- Okay, never mind.
- Hello. Look what the cat dragged in.
- Lex, have you had breakfast?
Thanks, but I can't stay.
I just wanted to ask you
and Mr. Kent for a favor.
I know we've had our differences,
so this might sound strange...
...but it would mean a lot to me.
It's customary
for the bride and groom to sit...
...with their parents
at the rehearsal dinner...
...so since mine won't be there,
I was wondering...
...would the two of you
consider standing in?
Lex, we would be honored.
Great. That just leaves one
open seat at the table.
Right next to you, Clark.
Any suggestions?
Chloe.
The one name you won't find
on the list...
...for Smallville's biggest event
of the century.
Don't worry,
it's not like I'm holding out...
...for my fairy godmother
to bring glass slippers.
I'm still not convinced Lex
won't have me in a headset...
...running around with ice buckets.
Is this what you were doing until
2:00 in the morning last night?
Yeah.
Well, I can't vouch
for my calligraphy skills...
...but if you need any help,
just let me know.
Hey, you guys.
I'd like a double espresso, please.
Were you burning
the midnight oil last night too?
I was just...
...working on a toast
for Lex's dinner.
Chloe, ready to go?
- Everybody okay?
- Yeah.
- Great.
- Perfect.
Just checking.
Right. Well...
We better get going.
I have ashes to sweep
and wicked stepsisters to undermine.
- You didn't...?
- No.
I had a really good time last night.
I was thinking maybe we could go out
after the rehearsal dinner tonight.
Maybe.
Lana, is everything okay?
If this is about last night,
we can take it slow.
Clark, I think last night
may have been a mistake.
I'm really busy.
I'll call you later?
Here's the revised seating chart
for the rehearsal dinner.
- Who are the people marked in blue?
- Relatives who still talk to each other.
How about the red?
Family feuds and people who haven't
spoken in at least five years.
And the yellow ones
scattered throughout?
Buffer zones.
Relatives who have no
particular allegiance...
...and whose conversation
won't incite a riot.
If this medical career doesn't work out,
you should consider the United Nations.
- I'm not done yet.
- By the way, put the Kents at our table.
I asked them to sit with us at the dinner,
fill in for my parents.
Lex.
I think it's great that you wanna
make them a big part of this, but...
But what?
Don't you think this might be the right
moment to reach out to your father?
Helen.
I'm touched that you
want us to reconcile.
But it's not gonna happen.
Besides...
...the only family I need is you.
I don't believe this.
We should call the police.
Is anything valuable missing?
Gosh, I'm sorry to hear that, Helen.
- They take anything important?
- The vial of blood I drew from Clark.
Tell me why you
would even still have that.
I thought I might need it someday,
in case he got sick again.
It wasn't labeled. There's no way
anyone could connect it to Clark.
Then why would anybody
wanna steal it?
It looks like somebody just broke open the
refrigerator and took whatever was inside.
The police think it may have been
junkies looking for drugs.
Or maybe somebody who wanted
to make it look that way.
Are you saying you think
that I staged this?
We're the only ones who knew
about Clark's blood.
- And you never told anybody else?
- Of course not.
Not even the man
you're about to marry?
Mr. Kent...
Lex is not the man
you think he is.
Considering that you're about to spend
the rest of your life with that man...
...and what you know
about my family...
...you had better be right.
I don't think it's a good idea
that you seat Lana next to me.
What happened?
I wish I knew.
Clark.
None of us really
understands the fairer sex.
It's why we're so
captivated by them.
I went for it last night.
- Don't tell me she shot you down.
- No.
It was the opposite.
It was like this perfect moment,
and then this morning...
She wanted to pretend
it never happened.
You've upped the stakes, Clark,
and she's scared.
She figures if she folds now,
she'll cut her losses.
We're meant to be together.
I've never been so sure about anything.
Yeah, well, don't tell me, Clark.
Tell her.
- Hey.
Come on.
- Lana, last night was a big deal for me.
- Clark.
Look, you don't have to avoid calling me
if you don't feel the same way.
No, it meant a lot to me too.
Everything seemed so clear, but today
it just feels a lot more complicated.
Is this about Chloe?
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't worried about her...
...but there are three friendships at stake
here, and I don't wanna risk losing ours.
The friendship isn't gonna go anywhere.
It'll just become something better.
And what happens down the road
if things don't work out?
- Will our friendship survive that?
- I don't know.
Lana, I've wanted this for so long,
I think it's worth taking the chance.
The day is coming.
Clark?
Are you all right?
The day is coming.
Clark, what is it?
I'm sorry, I have to go.
The day is coming.
- What do you think it means?
- It's probably just delusional rambling.
But your scans say his
brain activity is normal again.
The day is coming.
Does that look normal to you?
The day is coming...
The cataracts, they're gone.
They faded during
the course of a day.
- How do you explain that?
- I can't.
I know you want to see if he says
anything else, but for his own safety...
...I need to sedate him.
- The day is coming! The day is...
The day is coming.
I think it says,
"The day is coming."
- You learned how to read the symbols?
- No, just an educated guess.
It's what Walden kept
saying before he escaped.
I wonder how he wrote it.
Apparently, he's developed the ability to
emit some kind of energy from his hands.
I think maybe it has something to do with
whatever happened to him in the cave.
Why are you telling me all this?
You found him, Clark.
Just wondering if you could shed
any more light on the situation.
I've already told you
everything I know.
These symbols...
...they look like the one on your barn.
Lex, I told you. I don't know
how to read this language.
I believe you, Clark.
Then what am I doing here?
I thought, based on our
mutual interest in the cave...
...we could solve this mystery together.
I'm sorry, Lex.
I'm as mystified as you are.
I know who you are.
Hey, Helen.
Are you planning a rehearsal
dinner or a peace summit?
This whole wedding is starting
to feel just as political.
It's hard to know
what side everybody's on.
You're not having
second thoughts, are you?
Sorry, l...
- It's all gotten very complicated.
- Sounds kind of familiar.
You wouldn't be talking about a tall,
dark, handsome best man, would you?
If you knew that Lex was
keeping secrets from you...
...but he was being truthful
about the important things like...
Like the way he feels about you.
Would that be enough?
I guess you have to decide.
Is the part of themselves that
they're willing to share with you...
...better than not having
them in your life at all?
You don't really think he's
hidden it in here, do you?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- I'm talking about the valuable object...
...Lex stole from your office.
Lex would never steal from me.
If you believe that, what are you doing
rummaging around in here while he's out?
How do I know you didn't
break into my office?
Oh, my. It seems I've antagonized
the lady of the house.
Please, would you tell my son
I dropped by to offer my best wishes?
Oh, no.
That would be difficult,
wouldn't it?
Because we'd have to explain
that we ran into each other...
...when we were in here and
I caught you snooping and...
Oh, that could get really messy.
Especially with your
wedding day almost upon us.
Get out.
Can I ask you a question, Helen?
Why are you marrying Lex?
Because I love him.
Dr. Walden?
It's me, Clark Kent.
Dr. Walden.
Are you down here?
Interesting, isn't it?
- Mr. Luthor.
- That...
...octagonal recess
in the wall, I mean.
I once had what you might call
a keepsake that matched this.
Exactly.
Just disappeared from my office.
It was that same day you rescued
your mother and me.
What are you doing down here?
I have taken over
conservatorship of the caves.
- Didn't Lex tell you?
- No, he didn't.
He just doesn't want to admit defeat,
and he's still fighting me on this.
I ran into some of his
security people down here.
They were looking for that doctor.
Dr...?
Dr. Walden?
Dr. Walden was obsessed
with these caves.
Well, I could understand why.
Look at this.
These symbols...
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
They are...
Are they arranged in a different...
...order than they were before?
That's strange.
Don't you think, Clark?
It's all Kawatche to me.
If you see Dr. Walden, be careful.
He could be dangerous.
I don't get it.
First the refined kryptonite,
now the caves.
What does Luthor want?
I don't know, but I think
we have a bigger problem.
Dr. Walden can read Krypton language.
He wrote it on the ceiling at the hospital.
- You think he's figured out your secret?
- Is that why you're so worried now?
I'm not sure, but something's
going on in that cave.
The symbols have changed.
- What does it say now, son?
- "The day is coming...
...when the last son will begin
his quest to rule the third planet."
- Clark.
- Don't you see? I'm the last son.
Why humiliate yourself
like this, Dad?
When are you gonna accept
the fact that you're not invited?
You know, Lex, I'm not here to grovel
for a place at your table.
I wanted to tell you that...
...your restraining order to keep me out of
the Kawatche caves has been rejected.
Flat out.
And you couldn't have had your lawyers
tell my lawyers that over the phone?
It's curious, though...
...your renewed interest seems to come
right on the heels of Dr. Walden's escape.
And Clark Kent seems
to share your opinion.
He was down there too,
looking for your linguist.
Lex!
- I did it, Lex.
- Dr. Walden.
I finally read the wall.
I know what it says.
We'll talk all about it,
but first we need to get you help.
- Let the man tell us.
- Stay out of this.
The wall, doctor,
what does it say?
"The last son will rule the planet."
Don't you see?
It's Clark Kent!
- I think that's a pretty big leap.
- No.
I've never seen
more clearly in my life.
- I know exactly what has to be done.
- What is that, doctor?
We have to kill Clark Kent.
Before he destroys us all.
Dr. Walden, you're confused.
"Dear guests..."
No, it's gotta be something else.
"Friend..."
"Friends and family..."
First line's always the hardest.
- Hey, Chloe, what's up?
- Big news.
Your friend Dr. Walden woke up.
I wouldn't exactly call him
a friend of mine.
I was just wondering if you wanted
to come out of retirement...
...and do the story with me.
Hey, I appreciate the offer,
but now really isn't a good time.
I didn't mean right this second, Clark.
I wish things could be like they were.
Yeah, me too.
I just feel like there's this
huge rift between us...
...and no matter how hard I try,
I can't get back to you.
We'll get there, Chloe.
It's just gonna take a little bit of time.
Well, whatever happens,
let's just...
Let's promise to be
honest with each other.
I mean, you're a big boy, I'm a big girl.
I think we can handle it.
As long as we tell the truth.
Okay, well, I'd better get going.
You have your rehearsal dinner,
and I have the Torch. So...
Break a leg, Clark.
Sorry I'm late.
- Where have you been?
- Business crisis.
Don't worry, I'm all yours now.
I need a moment
with the best man.
Okay.
- Hello, Mrs. Kent.
- Everything is beautiful.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
- Hello, Lex.
- Hey.
- Mind if I have a word with your son?
- No, go right ahead.
- Is everything all right?
- Dr. Walden paid me a visit.
Nobody was hurt.
He's on his way back to the hospital.
- Well, that's good news.
- Clark, he was ranting about you.
- What'd he say?
- That the writing on the cave wall says...
...you're going to rule the world.
I'm gonna rule the world?
- He's obviously nuts.
- Of course he is.
Unfortunately, my father was there.
He heard the whole thing.
He didn't believe him, did he?
He quoted one of his
favorite Elizabethan poets.
Twixt truth and madness lies
But a sliver of a stream
He's not just gonna let this drop.
I thought I'd warn you.
I certainly do admire
your work ethic, Miss Sullivan.
- Late at night, here you are, still at it.
- Yeah.
Well, I wasn't invited
to the rehearsal dinner, so...
Yes, we have a lot in common.
I spoke to the managing editor
of the Daily Planet. It's all set.
A weekly column on current affairs
from the young person's perspective.
I don't know how to thank you.
Nurturing a promising
young talent is a reward in itself.
And I've got your first assignment.
A complete investigative
profile of Clark Kent.
What possible interest could the Daily
Planet have in a farm boy from Smallville?
This isn't for the Daily Planet. They'll
be in touch with you. No, this is for me.
Just combine it with any research
about his family you already have.
I blew off my journalistic skepticism...
...and allowed myself
to actually believe...
...that you were interested
in just helping me.
You're playing in the real world now,
Miss Sullivan.
You have to give to get.
Mr. Luthor. I don't know
what your interest is in Clark...
...but you can take the offer and shove
it down your thousand-dollar pants.
Clark's very lucky
to have a friend like you.
All that integrity.
I wonder, though, if he had to make
a choice, would he sacrifice his dream...
...out of loyalty to you?
Any change?
No, he'll be out for hours.
Can I have everyone's
attention, please?
I think Lex picked me to be
the best man because he knew...
...how comfortable I was
speaking in front of people.
I've been looking through every book
from Socrates to Shakespeare...
...trying to find someone
who can put into words the way...
...Lex and Helen
feel about each other.
But what I realized is,
there are no words for it.
That when you have it,
you trust it.
You believe in it.
Take a chance on it.
You're willing to sacrifice
anything to keep it.
No matter what the cost.
- To Helen and Lex.
Thanks.
- Clark, are you all right?
- Yeah...
...I just gotta get some air.
- Clark.
- Son.
- What's the matter?
- It's the key.
There's something wrong at home.
I have to go.
I came looking for you.
And I found the proof.
You...
...are the one.
Dr. Walden, listen to me.
- You need help.
- No.
You need to die.
Dr. Walden...
Dr. Walden, no!
- Doctor, you're making a mistake.
- No, I'm not. I'm doing this for mankind.
With the exception of Clark's migraine...
...I thought the evening
was mercifully uneventful.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
If we're gonna spend our lives together,
we need to be honest with each other.
You're always saying that.
I found a file on Mrs. Kent
in your bookshelf.
It contained confidential
medical records.
From my office.
I got that from a Disease Control agent
who was investigating Mrs. Kent's case.
You mean you bribed someone for it.
I've told you...
...the Kents are very important to me.
I was concerned about Martha's health.
What were you looking for, anyway?
Something that was stolen
from my office.
Do you think I was involved
in the break-in?
Please tell me you weren't.
If you really believe I'm capable
of that kind of deceit...
...maybe you
shouldn't be marrying me.
Maybe you're right.
I had to pry it from his hand.
It wasn't your fault, Clark.
The man tried to kill you.
He was delusional.
Even the sheriff agreed, son. Walden
was responsible for his own death.
What if he was right?
- What if I am a threat to mankind?
- I'll never believe that.
And neither should you.
What does it mean? The day is coming
when I'll begin my quest to rule?
We don't know, son.
But when and if that day does come...
...your mother and I both know
that you'll do the right thing.
His entire body's been burned
beyond recognition.
But look.
Whatever he was holding here,
it protected the skin it was covering.
I've never seen anything like this.
Send it to me.
Send you what?
The hand.
I never got a chance to tell you
how beautiful you look tonight.
Clark, you scared me.
Surprised me.
Just wanted to see you.
Kind of ran out on dinner.
I thought your toast
was really beautiful.
I had a lot of inspiration.
Sorry I've been so confused about us.
It's just...
I'm scared.
So am I.
You have so many secrets in your life.
I know.
I just don't want my feelings
for you to be one of them.
Neither do I.
Kal-EI, it is time.
www.tvsubtitles.net