- Hey. You sure I can't help?
- Absolutely not.
- All set.
- Oh, Martha, you make this look so easy.
- It's not too much, you think?
- Are you kidding?
This is just perfect.
It's exactly the way
I always dreamt that Easter should be.
- Mommy, look!
- Oh, good for you, Michelle.
What you've done is really fabulous. The
kids are gonna remember this forever.
I hope there are
some things they won't remember.
- What is she doing here?
- Her son is in Michelle's class,
Martha. Be nice.
Jenny, hi.
It's good to see you.
Hey, Ellen. Martha.
She's shaken up, Howard.
It took me two hours
to put her to bed.
All I'm saying is...
No, I didn't see any bird.
But whatever it was, it scared her
and she wants to be with her daddy.
That's all I'm saying.
Well, can't you come home
one day early?
All right, fine.
I love you too.
- Anything?
- No. She'll come.
It's a matter of time.
Well, I hope you realize
there's no evidence whatsoever...
that this mystery woman
of yours has even committed a crime.
Though her wardrobe
comes close.
Ah. Six prostitutes
were seen with her at Dirty Dames,
never to be seen again.
Not only might she be a female
serial killer, rare in and of itself,
but twice police raided
that club to arrest her.
And twice they came up
empty-handed.
She's on tape goin' in, the exits
are covered. She's nowhere to be found.
What happens to her?
She disappeared? Turn invisible?
Well, I hope we catch her
so she can tell us...
before I have to spend
another night here.
You know, Mulder, I don't know
about you, but I find this
all very depressing.
This round-the-clock exposure
to the seamy underbelly.
It's a job, Scully.
Vigilance in the face of privation.
The sheer will that it takes
to sit in this crappy room...
spying on the dregs of society
until our suspect surfaces.
There is something
ennobling in that.
Mulder.
Now?
All right. I gotta go.
Mulder?
- You wanted to see me, sir?
- Yeah, sit down.
Two weeks ago, a woman named
Martha Crittendon...
disappeared from her home
in Bethany, Vermont.
Local police haven't
turned up any sign of her.
I'm hoping you may
be able to.
- I'm already on a case.
- You're on a stakeout.
I'm confident Agent Scully
can continue in your absence.
Why? What did I do?
There may be aspects
to this that...
speak to your strengths
as an investigator.
Specifically?
Ravens.
What do you know
about 'em...
their mythological
or paranormal significance?
Well, the, uh...
the raven is considered
a very powerful symbol...
in certain Norse, Celtic
and Native-American cultures.
Mostly a negative one.
Indians view it as a deceiving spirit.
Christianity mostly
associates it with evil.
And then, of course,
there's Poe's Raven...
and Nevermore
and all that stuff.
Martha Crittendon's
seven-year-old daughter...
claimed she was attacked by a raven
earlier the day her mother disappeared.
Later, she heard one inside
the house before she discovered
her mother was missing.
No, really,
what did I do?
It's the only lead
that hasn't been explored.
I wanna know if it has
any bearing on the case.
I'm also assuming that the fact
that Martha Crittendon's father...
is a federal judge also has
a little bearing on this case?
It's been made clear to me that
locating her is my top priority.
I'm making it yours as well.
- Agent Mulder?
- Yeah.
Phil Adderly. Welcome to Bethany.
I appreciate the help.
Sure. I don't know
how much help I'm gonna be.
I know you had a lot of good
investigators on the case.
- So, uh, you wanna just take
a quick look around?
- Great. Thanks.
So tell me about
Martha Crittendon.
Well, she and my wife Ellen,
they're best friends.
Martha's much admired here.
She's devoted to her family,
active in the community.
I mean, needless to say,
the whole town is very concerned.
- So, what's your theory
on what happened?
- I'm hopin' you'll tell me.
There's no ransom note,
no prints or blood evidence.
- Her husband was out of town
when she disappeared?
- In Miami at a conference.
It checks out.
Howard didn't have
anything to do with this.
What do you know
about a raven?
Yeah, yeah.
Michelle, their...
their little girl
was saying something about that.
Got me.
Poor kid.
- You wanna talk to her?
- Not necessary.
You sure, uh, Martha's
last name isn't Stewart?
Tell me about it. Last year this place
made the cover of New England Home.
How many talons
would you say a raven had?
Never mind.
You know what this is?
Do you know what was hanging here?
It was a mirror.
It was found broken.
- You had no other signs of struggle?
- Not a one.
- Does that mean somethin' to you?
Howard, this is Agent Mulder
with the F.B.I.
Sir.
I hope we can help.
I appreciate your coming.
I'm wondering now... if this isn't
just a waste of your time.
How so?
With all the police
coming and going,
this place is a wreck.
I was straightening up
and I... found something.
Uh, birth control pills.
I think Martha was having
an affair.
After Michelle, we decided
not to have more children.
I had a vasectomy.
They're in Martha's name.
She ordered them off the Internet.
Because I guess
small towns talk.
Of course, then I started
looking all around and I...
found this in the pocket
of her favorite coat.
I don't know what
this goes to...
or what it means,
if anything.
But the pills...
Do you have any idea
who your wife may have been seeing?
Whoever he is,
Martha may be with him.
It explains why
we haven't found her.
She doesn't wanna be found.
Cute kid.
Oh, Jenny, you scared me.
- You do those up yourself?
- Uh, yeah.
I know Martha and you were good friends.
You must be pretty upset.
Of course.
I'm sure we all are.
Maybe you'd like some to put up
on your side of town.
My side of town?
- Yeah, sure.
- Look, I didn't mean that
the way it kind of sounded.
No, it just naturally comes
out that way when you think
you're better than everyone.
You and Martha
are two peas in a pod.
Jenny, I don't think
I'm better than anyone.
You and me got more
in common than you know.
Yeah, right.
Right. Thanks.
Whoever Martha was seeing, the two of
them covered their tracks pretty good.
Phone records don't show anything. You
think this person took her, harmed her?
I wouldn't rule it out, but I doubt it.
According to your Audubon book,
a raven has four talons.
That matches the scratches
we found on Martha Crittendon's mantle.
You're not saying a raven's the reason
Martha's gone missing?
No, no, not a raven itself.
But in folklore, ravens
are companions to evil...
evil spirits, witches,
warlocks, that kind of thing.
Agent Mulder,
I appreciate the different tact
you're taking on this investigation,
but this whole bird thing?
And keep in mind, you're basing this
on the word of a seven-year-old girl.
Well, there was also a broken mirror
in Martha's house.
Mirrors are considered
items of enchantment.
A broken one...
means something.
I'm not exactly sure what it is,
but... it means something.
Oh.
- Hey, sweet girl.
- There's Papa.
Agent Mulder, this is my
daughter Katie and my wife Ellen.
- Nice to meet you.
- We're so glad you're here.
Look, our house is your house.
- We have a spare room set up.
I'm sure you'll be comfortable.
- No, that's...
There's no arguments. We're so grateful
that you're here to find Martha.
It's the least we can do.
Okay.
I should really get the bureau
to reimburse you for room and board.
- Don't be silly. This is just
a typical meal around here.
- Really?
Bill works so much that supper is
usually the only time we see each other.
- And I like to make it special.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Thanks.
- Mulder.
- Mulder, please tell me I can go home.
Hey, Scully.
How's the stakeout?
Well, the furnace broke
and I can just about see my breath.
Ouch.
Sorry to hear that.
That, and I've witnessed
a couple hundred things
I'd like to erase from my brain.
Eeew.
But as of yet, no mystery woman.
Well, she'll come.
You know, it's just a matter of time.
She'll show up.
I'm sure of that.
Not before I die
of malnutrition.
Scully, tough it out. Whatever doesn't
kill you, makes you stronger, right?
- No, no. No capers. Thank you.
- I'm sorry. What?
I said, "What a crazy caper." I'll talk
to you later. And keep warm. Bye.
Did I hear you say something
about stakeout? What's the case?
Sweetie,
this is family time.
- Don't make our guest talk shop
at the dinner table.
- Fair enough.
- Cheers.
What's the matter,
sweetheart?
I thought that
was your favorite.
It tastes different
when Mommy makes it.
Yeah.
I know.
How 'bout we go get hamburgers?
Would you like that instead?
It's back.
- Everything's all right, sweetheart.
I'll be right back.
- Okay.
What do you make
of these claw marks?
Well, one time I saw the victim of
a bear attack look something like that.
Only bears don't plant
their kill in the rose garden.
I was gonna say.
The body's been around here for a while.
Probably since she went missing.
What about your ravens?
Howard said something
about ravens.
Yeah.
Feedin' on her. See?
You okay?
I'm not arrestin' Howard.
I don't care how it looks.
- Body buried in his own yard.
He didn't do this.
- I agree.
The poor guy's suffered enough already.
- What are you doing?
You shouldn't be here.
- What...
Oh, my God.
- Martha, no.
- Ellen, honey, I am so sorry.
It can't be.
It's okay. It's okay.
The thing that did
that to her,
I think I saw it today.
I saw its reflection.
It had a face out of a nightmare.
These long claws, the kind that could...
The window shattered. I don't know how.
And when I turned around, it was gone.
I don't know what I thought it was.
I didn't think it was real.
How could it be?
But then when I saw
Martha's face...
Honey, you've been
through a lot.
You don't believe me.
I do.
You said the car window shattered
after you saw the reflection.
And there's a broken mirror
in Martha's house.
I don't think
that's a coincidence.
- But what could it mean?
- Mirrors are considered doorways.
In the Victorian era, they built
mirrored rooms called "psychomantiums,"
where they thought they could summon
forth spirits from the spirit world.
Denizens from the spirit world
were brought into this world.
"Denizens of the spirit world?"
You asked about the raven.
The raven is a carrion bird...
attracted to death
and decay.
What if... this entity
that you saw...
is somehow a personification
of that?
What if this creature was brought forth
in order to attack Martha?
Then the question becomes
who summoned it forth.
Ellen, do you know if Martha
had any enemies?
Can you think of anyone at all
who would have wished her harm?
I sure as hell didn't
have anything to do with it.
They're just routine questions,
Miss Uphouse. Answer 'em
and we'll be out of here.
We understand there was no love lost
between you and Martha Crittendon.
And where do you
understand that from?
- Mrs. Sheriff, right?
- It's not exactly a town secret.
Right. Like there aren't
enough of those already.
Queen Martha and her perfect
little Easter egg hunts.
She's so above the rest of us.
Except I heard she was
steppin' out on her husband,
knockin'boots
with who knows who.
I'm not happy she's dead and all.
But you need to look into that.
Well, let's stay on the subject of you...
on your police record, for instance.
You don't suffer people
that don't give you respect.
I'm thinking of that hair
salon owner you assaulted.
That was forever ago.
And I paid for that.
And I had nothing
to do with Martha.
Where were you the night
she disappeared?
At home, all night.
I gotta get back to work.
I don't know about you,
but I believe her.
She didn't do it.
I just don't get that vibe.
Fair enough. But why did
she lie about her alibi?
I got that vibe pretty clear.
- Excuse me.
I'll be in the car.
Mulder.
Mulder, when you
find me dead,
my desicated corpse
propped up...
staring lifelessly
through the telescope...
at drunken frat boys peeing
and vomiting into the gutter,
just know that my last thoughts
were of you...
and how I'd like to kill you.
I'm sorry.
Who is this?
It's a freak show, Mulder.
It's a nonstop parade
of every single lowlife imaginable.
The view may not be too different here.
It's dressed up nicer,
but underneath the surface
it's the same seamy underbelly.
It's not the same.
Trust me.
You know, Scully, this case
has turned out to be a little
more interesting than I thought.
- And I could use your help.
- You talking about a reprieve for me?
Well, there's a murder victim I'd like
you to autopsy. What do you think?
Scully, you still there?
Hello?
- That van is back.
- What'd you say?
- Nothing, Mulder.
I'll talk to you later, okay?
Katie...
Get away from her!
- It's okay, hon. Come on.
Be quiet now.
Shh.
Hush. Be quiet.
Oh, God. Ellen?
Ellen, what happened?
Are you feeling
a little better, Ellen?
Can you... just talk to me
a little bit about what happened?
It came back.
It came back?
The... The creature you saw?
It was here, Phil.
It chased me.
It's all right, honey.
Please don't encourage this.
This is not what she needs.
- I believe she saw something.
- And I believe she didn't.
Her best friend just died,
for God's sake.
These imaginings of hers
are brought on by stress.
I have been through the entire house
and I didn't see any indication
anyone else was here.
- What about the two broken mirrors?
- What about them?
You think broken mirrors have
some deeper meaning, but you
still can't tell me what it is.
And in this case,
I'm thinking Ellen broke 'em herself.
What?
It's number six. It's a match
to the one Howard Crittendon
found in his wife's coat pocket.
- What would this be doing here?
- I don't know.
Ellen, do you recognize
this key?
Oh, I was...
sweeping the floor...
and it got caught up
in the sweeper.
I never saw it before today.
You found it before
you were attacked?
Right before.
Right before I saw the raven.
Let me see if my department can run this
down and find out what lock it goes to.
Hey, I can't do this anymore.
- Can't, huh?
- No.
- We gotta stop.
- Well, that's too bad.
- Hey, good morning.
- Good morning, Ellen.
Wow.
- Have you seen my shirt?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- I left it...
- It's over here.
Oh, Ellen, you didn't
have to go to the trouble.
No, it's no trouble.
Actually, it helps me.
Whenever my life's a mess,
I just do some housework.
Gives me the illusion
I'm in control.
- Well, maybe I should try that sometime.
- Have a seat.
Thanks.
Yikes. Wow.
It's just Phil's
breakfast times two.
Well, Phil is living large.
Where is he this morning?
Uh, probably out on a call.
He'll be back.
You... You just dig in.
- Whoa. Ow.
- Sorry.
- Do you need milk?
- Mm-mm. I'm fine.
I get the feeling you're not
used to anyone taking care of you.
Well, that has a...
a vaguely pathetic ring to it.
No, I just meant
I didn't notice a wedding band.
- Oh.
- Do you have a significant other?
Um, not in the widely
understood definition of that term.
Oh. Well, the right woman
will come along and change all that.
Don't miss out
on home and family, Mr. Mulder.
With all the terrible things
you must see in your work...
Well, it could be
a refuge for you.
- Hi, honey.
- Sorry I'm late. Paperwork.
- Good morning, Agent Mulder.
- Good morning.
I'm gonna go
check on Katie.
You sleep well?
I only woke up once,
when you went out.
Well, I'll try to be
quieter next time.
We've got a deputy out.
We're shorthanded.
I had to take some calls.
- All night?
- Yeah. We were busy.
I spoke to the coroner
this morning.
The autopsy shows Martha Crittendon
was four weeks pregnant when she died,
despite her birth control pills.
Probably didn't even know it.
Any idea who the father might be?
I mean, Howard's vasectomy
pretty much puts him out of the running.
Any inkling who it might be?
Just say what's
on your mind, Agent.
You have a piece of evidence
in your possession that I'd like back.
The skeleton key.
Number six.
You wanna tell me
what this unlocks?
Once I find out,
we'll talk again.
I'm gonna hit the shower.
I know, Brett, sweetie,
I'm sorry.
No, I'm gonna be home
real soon.
Mommy had to work
a double shift.
I know. I'm gonna come home
and make you breakfast.
No, no, no, don't eat
a lot of cookies. No.
Only two. I...
Yes, oatmeal cookies
have oatmeal in them.
Okay.
All right, three.
I love you.
Bye.
Sheriff, you know that talk
I said we should have?
I left her sleeping.
So, you were having an affair
with both Jenny and Martha Crittendon?
I gotta hand it to you, Sheriff.
You put the service back
in the "protect and serve."
I cared about both of them.
They knew about
each other?
But I'm assuming
Ellen doesn't?
No.
But even if she did,
she'd find a way to rationalize it.
I'm not defending myself,
but... two years ago
I wanted a divorce.
Ellen won't hear it.
She got pregnant with Katie
and locked me up good.
Well, I figure you got bigger problems
facing you right now.
I didn't do this.
I swear to you.
Anyway, what about
the broken mirrors and the raven?
You said that it was an entity that
did this. Don't you still believe that?
I said it was an entity
summoned by somebody else.
Whether or not they even knew about it,
is that possible?
Can I be the reason
for all this...
and not even
know about it?
Hi. You've reached the Adderly's...
Phil, Ellen and Katie.
- Please leave a message.
Ellen, this is Phil.
I was really hopin' you'd be home.
Look, I'm in a bit
of a situation here...
and there's things
we need to talk about.
But Agent Mulder's on his way
over there to explain it all to you.
So, if you get this message,
you just wait for him, okay? Thanks.
I think this sleepy
little girl needs a nap.
I do.
I love you.
Go to sleep now.
Okay, baby?
Ellen?
Mulder.
- Mulder, I am free.
- You're free?
Mm-hmm. I'm gonna go home,
take a shower for,
I don't know,
eight or nine hours,
burn the clothes that I'm wearing
and then sleep until late spring.
- You solved the X-File.
- Yes.
Except it's not
an X-File, Mulder.
What are you saying? You didn't catch
our blond mystery serial killer?
Oh, no, we caught her.
But, uh, she isn't
a serial killer.
Nor is she a blond.
And she isn't even a she.
What are you talking about?
What I'm talking about is these six
missing prostitutes aren't dead, Mulder.
They are alive and well
in a halfway house...
that was set up
by this mystery blond...
who happens to go by the name
of Mark Scott Eggbert.
And Mr. Eggbert wishes
to acquaint lost souls...
with the teachings of Christ.
And that's his hook, I guess.
He dresses up like
a fellow prostitute...
to make the girls
feel at ease.
But this vanishing act
is no more paranormal...
than a change of wardrobe, Mulder.
He goes into a place like a woman
and comes out as a man.
- Right under...
- Our noses.
Exactly.
A wolf in sheep's clothing.
Or I guess in this case,
a sheep in wolf s clothing.
Well, good work, Scully.
I'll call you back later.
Ellen?
- Ellen, it's Agent Mulder.
- Please go away.
Ellen, Jenny Uphouse is dead.
Your husband is in custody
suspected of murdering her,
only I don't think he did it.
Do you?
Ellen, you went out...
this morning after breakfast.
Where'd you go?
It's not me.
It can't be.
I think it is.
Ellen, I think you have a whole
other side that you're afraid to face.
That would explain
all the broken mirrors.
You don't want to see yourself
for what you really are.
Ellen, you have to
come out of there.
Then what?
My marriage, my life?
Everything I thought I had...
is nothing.
It's all lies.
I wish you'd never come here.
Ellen, you need
to open this door.
You wanna see her?
Does she wanna see me?
The doctors say she's got
some kind of dissociative disorder.
A split personality.
That doesn't explain
what happened, does it?
I think it's about as close
as science can come.
I think the basic idea's right.
There's some multiple
personality disorders...
where an alternate personality displays
traits that the host doesn't have,
like nearsightedness
or high blood pressure or even diabetes.
I think in Ellen's case, the... changes
were just a lot more extreme.
Like... Jekyl and Hyde?
She wanted so much
from her life with you.
A perfect life.
And I think that at some point
she found out you were cheating
with Jenny and Martha.
I don't know when,
but at some point she did.
Like you said, I think
she had to rationalize that.
And she just bottled up
her anger.
Swallowed it, and it
had to come out some way.
I think she did what she did
to protect her family.