Previously on Jake 2.0:
I'm Jake Foley, tech support.
I see you're still at the NSA.
We got a problem.
You see how the nanites have positioned
themselves along his
central nervous system.
This guy can interface with technology.
He's like a universal remote,
and every one of his body
functions is enhanced.
I've just been authorized
to create a special ops team
with you at its core.
- Jake.
- Sarah.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm just researching some case law.
Privacy issues, e-mails, NSA stuff.
Well you're not going
to get anywhere today.
It-it's Sunday. The library's closing.
Oh, man.
I just ran all the way across town.
What are you doing here?
Ugh, soybeans.
The farm bill.
I thought I told you this.
Oh, right, right, right.
Well, uh, I'm free.
You wanna, you want
to go get some coffee?
Sure, yeah.
Great. Okay.
Oh, my god, that was horrible.
I've never seen a human
being that shade of green.
All right, look. In my defense,
it was the first time
I'd ever tried tequila.
You picked a hell of a place to do it.
Lincoln fought a war
to preserve the union,
and you thanked him
by puking on his shoes.
Yeah, he never looked
at me the same after that.
Oh, we were better with beer.
Mmm. Grown up a little bit
since then, huh?
You did. You definitely have.
You think?
Yeah, you seem more confident.
Especially lately.
I don't know,
I can't really put my finger on it,
but you're just different.
Well, I've been
working out a little bit.
Can't tell.
Oh, man.
Oh, come on, you
set me up for that one.
So you can tell.
Um... not really.
I'm just kidding.
What's happening?
Base, come in.
Base, we are under attack.
- They're jamming the signal.
- What do we do?
Nothing. The glass is
completely bulletproof.
The body is a zinc-alloy steel.
They're not getting in here.
Come on.
We got to get out of here.
Do not open that door.
We can't do resist it.
- I'm getting out.
- No!
Give it to me.
That's me. Jake Foley,
I'm in Tech Support.
Security Clearance:
Low. Very low.
Then one day, it all changed.
Now, I can do things
I've never dreamed of.
I've been upgraded.
I have these powers.
Life just got real interesting.
Okay, go left on the next street.
Come on. Yeah, yeah. Here we go.
Okay, Jake, you're pushing
too hard, all right?
No, no, no. I'm about
to make the Eiffel Tower.
No, no, no. I think that
we need to take a break.
No, no, no, no.
I'm almost to the Eiffel Tower.
Jake, the purpose of this exercise
is not winning the game, okay?
Yeah, right.
Come on.
No, okay, I'm going to turn it off.
No, no, no, no. Hold on,
hold on. There it is!
Almost there. Come on.
There it is, there it is. Yeah,
Oh yeah, I won it!
Hhmm... I beat the game.
Oh, yeah, you broke the machine.
Um, see, the purpose
of the whole exercise
is not to win the game, it's to learn
how to control the nanites,
and, you know, just for your info -
not controlling the nanites.
- I'll buy the NSA a new one.
- Oh, well...
somebody's in a good mood today.
Yeah, I had a good weekend.
- Yeah, really?
- I had a date.
Sort of. Uh, I don't know -
it kind of seemed like a date, I think.
A sort of, kind of date. That, uh,
sounds intriguing.
- Yeah.
- Uh, who's the girl?
Sarah. We went to
Georgetown together.
She never really gave me
the time of day,
but yesterday at lunch...
I don't know. It kind of seemed like
things might be changing, you know?
That's good. My advice to you -
don't push too hard.
It was a perfectly orchestrated attack.
What were they after?
John Ramsey, senior engineer for GDLS.
He was transporting
preliminary schematics
for a next generation composite tank.
Plastic and glass fiber.
It's as strong as what we've got,
but 70 percent lighter.
They can be flown in
just about anywhere.
So who are we looking for?
There's been increased
chatter on echelon
indicating possible
Chinese involvement.
How long since you've
had contact with Mei Ling?
Two and a half years.
I can't help you.
Kyle,
she is our most senior double
agent in Chinese intelligence.
If there's anyone who could
confirm their involvement,
let alone help us get this
thing back, it would be her.
There must be someone else
who's been handling her.
No one she's been nearly
as forthcoming with.
The schematics are on
an encrypted laptop.
They have to be physically
removed from the country
in order for their techs to decode it.
It could be smuggled by diplomatic
pouch at any moment, Kyle.
Are you ordering me to do this?
Once you've determined
the meeting place,
we'll get a team in
there and monitor...
No. No.
You want me to talk to her,
I talk to her alone.
No, Kyle, it's protocol.
It's for your safety as well as hers.
This woman reads a room
better than anyone I know.
She can sniff out any agent.
Not necessarily.
They call this art?
You must be in trouble.
And why do you say that?
You called.
I'm sure you know the Chinese have
stolen something very important to us.
We want it back.
A statement was issued.
We've formally denied...
That means nothing.
It's all I know.
So, tell me...
when did you become such a patriot?
Two and a half years ago.
I'll give you the exact date
if you don't remember.
I remember.
I'm prepared to offer you full asylum.
Five years expenses.
Why should I trust you?
Because this is work, Mei Ling.
I've never failed you there.
Full asylum, and two million dollars.
That's a lot of money.
You have a lot to make up for.
I need to get authorization.
I'd suggest you work quickly.
The schematics are
being held in the archives
within the secure corridor
at the embassy.
It's scheduled to be taken out
tonight by diplomatic pouch.
How do we get it?
There's a reception
beginning at 8:00 pm.
You'll be my guest.
You haven't changed.
Neither have you.
So, you and Mei Ling
kind of have this
casablanca thing going on.
Which is none of my business.
It's just... I can sort of relate.
See, I'm having this situation
with someone from my past...
right, you don't care.
So I guess you're going
to that party tonight.
Absolutely not.
Lou, those were her terms.
Kyle, you're no longer a field agent.
Your cover was blown.
Anything you do out there's a risk.
Well, you had no problem
sending me out there this morning.
D.C. is not the field.
That embassy is sovereign territory.
You get caught inside, you're on
your own. There's nothing we can do.
Once those schematics
leave the country...
then there's nothing we can do.
We have other agents who
can perform this operation,
ones who wouldn't be as valuable
to the Chinese if they got caught.
I don't think that's possible. Uh...
I heard everything that they said, and
she only wants Kyle.
To-to do this.
Do you trust her?
I trust her enough.
Well, this is all kind of sudden,
don't you think?
I mean, the nanites
are really sensitive,
and it's not like you mastered control,
you know, that's fine in the
video game, but this,
this is the Chinese embassy, okay?
They have guns and guards
and, and foreign languages.
I mean, anything could go wrong. Jake,
have you really thought about this?
Diane, this is my first mission.
I'm nervous enough,
you're really not helping.
Yeah, sorry.
Mei Ling Wong has arranged
an invitation for me
under the name Felix Garay,
Venezuelan Oil Executive.
At 10:00 pm in the main ballroom,
she'll give me a security card.
It'll allow me access to
the main secure corridor.
Now, at this point, we have
to get Mei Ling out.
If they trace that card
to her, she's dead.
How do we get her out?
Catering truck. Agent
De Grasso will be the driver.
The secure corridor is located
in the basement of the embassy.
Once I'm down there, I'll be
out of range for thermal imaging.
Getting there from the main ballroom,
I'll encounter security cameras here,
here... and here.
Security guards change shifts at 10:30.
That's where Jake comes in. Diane?
Diane?
Yes. Jake, Jake will interface
with the security
recording devices, and,
uh, rewind them thirty minutes,
temporarily disabling
them in the process,
so when Kyle's on the move,
the hallways will appear empty.
The main security office
is located here,
just off the main ballroom.
How close does he have to be?
Uh, well, based on our tests,
I'd say no more than, uh, 30...
- 30 feet.
- Great, great.
So what's my cover?
Uh, I speak a little Spanish, so maybe
I can be another oil executive.
Wait. But... oh no, 'cause we,
we can't be together uh... royalty?
Too obvious? Okay...
billionaire software mogul...
Jake... we create the cover.
Oh, right. Right, sorry, of course.
So, uh, what do you have in mind?
Hors d'oeuvres?
They don't serve themselves.
We've added markers to our
agent's heat signatures.
This way our satellites
can distinguish them
from the other guests at the party.
That's Kyle and Jake in the ballroom,
and De Grasso by the van.
Oh, no...
I got data streaming
in from his nanites.
What the problem?
He's really nervous.
Thank you.
Oh, uh... thank you.
Don't mention it.
Stop and go. Stop and... go...
Thank you.
Jake!
Sarah. Hey...
Okay, this freaking me out.
I keep running into you everywhere.
Yeah, that's... that's crazy.
Must be fate.
So what are you doing here?
Um...
you know, just another invite.
Heard they had good food.
Oh, the wild mushroom tart is fabulous,
you have to try one.
Oh, you know, I've had a whole tray.
Jake. You look great.
Ah, it's a rental.
Well, you certainly fill it out well.
I told, I told you I was working out.
Look, uh, look...
I don't know who,
who he's talking to, but,
his, his blood pressure is rising
and his heart rate is increasing.
His adrenals are activated. Lou...
Lou, is there any way maybe
that we can pull him out of this,
because, I, I don't know,
I, I think this is not good.
Diane. The mission
hasn't even started yet.
Okay, yeah.
Are you nervous?
What? Ah, no. No, no, no,
I'm having a great time, this is,
you know I missed this last year,
and it's, this is good.
You think?
You're not having fun?
Fun?
You know why I'm here, Jake?
Congressman Williams.
The Agriculture Committee?
My fun involves lingering
around the background,
waiting for the right moment
to make small talk,
in the hopes he comes
aboard for the Farm Bill.
Truth be told,
I'd rather be anywhere else.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry... talking your ear off.
One glass of veuve clicquot too many.
- Uh...
- What are you doing?
Uh, nothing. Nothing, it's just so
crowded over there.
Hot, you know, uh,
you, you wanna go dance? Let's dance.
How have you been?
Well, I haven't danced in a while.
I couldn't tell.
Now you're just flattering me.
Is it that obvious?
About as subtle as that
dress you're wearing.
Does it look familiar?
Hong Kong.
Impressive.
And I wasn't even wearing
it for very long.
Look at those two.
I mean, get a room.
Maybe they're just
caught up in the moment.
Yeah...
that happens.
Right now,
if you had to choose,
me or the mission...
At the bar, directly
behind me, is a waiter.
He's an agent.
He'll escort you to the catering truck
and get you out of here.
Mei Ling, you have to go.
Now.
Oh, incoming. There's your mark.
Oh, whoa! Why'd you do that?
Do you know what? It's,
it's nothing that can't wait.
Just for... just for right now,
I want to forget about work
and have some fun.
Okay. What'd you have in mind?
I want to feel like we did in college.
You know, I want to... get a six pack
and go to the Lincoln Memorial,
and not worry about anything at all.
What do you think?
Uh... I think that sounds...
perfect.
Okay. Come on, let's do it.
Uh... I, I can't.
Why?
Excuse me. I need a refill.
You're, you're a waiter.
Yes, he is.
And let's make it a double this time.
Can I get a rye on the rocks?
Make it a double.
- Was that really necessary?
- Yes, it was.
Jake, you can't afford
to get distracted.
Well, I wasn't the only one
who was being distracted.
You still have feelings for her?
- That's irrelevant.
- Is it?
You know what - it's time.
Let's just finish this.
Jake's in place.
Kyle's on his way.
Jake...
What are you doing?
I'm, uh...
I'm not exactly sure
how to explain what I'm doing.
You're moonlighting.
You're making a little
extra money on the side.
Jake, you don't have to
pretend with me.
Sarah...
I'm an undercover agent.
I'm here on a huge mission.
That's hilarious, Jake.
Okay, when are you getting off?
Uh...
l-l-less than an hour.
Right. Lincoln Memorial.
- I'll get the beer.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm quitting.
He's in.
Telephone. Agent Wallace.
Lou Beckett.
What do you mean, she never
made it to the safe house?
Where's the driver?
Oh, no.
Good job.
Unfortunately,
you made the wrong choice.
It will help you be more honest.
I know how difficult
that could be for you.
You could've gotten out.
You could've been free from this life.
I am out.
Delivering you is my final mission.
Don't do this, Mei Ling.
It didn't have to be like this.
Two and a half years ago,
we could've made a life together.
Two and a half years ago...
you would've been dead.
We have a situation
at the Chinese embassy.
Yes.
I understand.
Jake is still on the grounds.
What's happening?
Mei Ling never made
it to the safe house.
I can't reach Agent De Grasso.
Kyle was supposed
to check in ten minutes ago.
His intel on our mainland agents
is far more valuable to the Chinese
than the schematics.
Well, but he's an experienced agent.
I mean, he would never...
say anything.
When they're through with him,
he won't have a choice.
Ms. Beckett.
Agent De Grasso's dead.
Jake, you listen to me.
You need to get out of there now.
I can't. There's guards everywhere.
Your cover hasn't been compromised.
Just act casual.
Walk through the front gate.
We'll have a team
waiting there for you.
Where's Kyle?
We haven't heard from him yet.
What?
I can't just leave him here.
Jake, Kyle's an experienced agent.
If he has any problems,
he can handle it.
Okay. Okay.
Now, you just stay on the phone.
You're just talking to a friend.
I don't believe you.
We intercepted a message.
Chinese intelligence suspected
you were working with us.
They had snipers waiting
outside the Hotel in Seville.
If I had shown up there...
if I'd even shown up in the city...
they would've killed you.
I did what I did...
to save your life.
You're lying.
Mei Ling, listen to me.
Why do you think I'm here?
Why do you think I'm doing this?
To get you out once and for all...
so that we can be together.
I love you.
It's too late.
You're almost there.
Yes... she didn't want the glass.
She wanted the whole bottle. Yeah.
Wait a minute.
We're not getting anything out of him.
- I hear him.
- What?
I hear him. It's Kyle. He...
he's in the basement.
- It was a setup.
- What?
They wanted Kyle all along.
This whole thing was a setup.
Jake, you need to get out
of there right now.
Uh...
hello?
Where are you going? Jake, you-you-you're
not heading towards the gate.
I'm, uh, I'm losing you.
Jake.
All you have to do...
is give me names.
I see.
Oh, my god.
He's gone. Look at this, he's gone.
Seventy-five thousand volts
of electricity.
Are you sure?
You go ahead.
Enough?
You go to hell.
No worries, I've all night
Hey!
Come on.
What are you doing?
I'm getting you out of here.
No... Jake. Jake.
There's no way out.
Sure there is.
I want you to stab me in the throat.
As hard as you can.
- What?
- Jake, listen to me.
They make me talk,
people will die.
This is what being
an agent is all about.
Now, do your job.
My job...
is to get you out of here.
Now, come on.
Jake, there's no way out.
I can't see anything.
You've got to trust me.
Look. Look!
They're alive.
How are we doing this?
Those new Cadillacs,
they're completely computerized, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Go. Go, now.
Come with me.
I can't.
You must go now. Go.
Are you going to open the gates?
Nope.
Thank you. Thank you.
They're out.
That fear thing...
it never goes away.
Bali.
On the beach.
She was wearing a white dress...
no shoes.
Georgetown.
Freshman year.
I have no idea what she was wearing.
I just remember her eyes.
D.C.
She held a gun to my head...
then she kissed me.
I never kissed her.
www.tvsubtitles.net