Previously on FlashForward...
- You want to tell me what this is?
- It's my book. It's all there.
- We need someone on the inside.
- You want me to be a double agent?
This is where you get to prove
your dedication to the cause.
Kill Benford.
- What's up with you?
- I'm pregnant. Mark, I just hope that
- you know you can still count on me.
- I never doubted that.
I could've used you, Stan.
Now I gotta deal
with Vice President Clemente.
In my vision, it was clear
that Jericho had done
some things that threatened
our national security.
You got military clearance.
As soon as you can document
what Tracy knows, I want it uploaded.
As of this moment,
the world thinks you and Simcoe
accidentally caused this blackout.
What happens if they find out
you were awake while it happened?
Simon Campos has disappeared.
He took the damn ring.
Did you overhear anything?
They said he's going to cause
another blackout.
On october 6th,
the planet blacked out
for 2 minutes and 17 seconds,
and the whole world saw the future.
Some of us were alarmed
by what we saw.
Others were elated and rejoiced.
Still others saw nothing at all.
They were left confused, concerned
and otherwise uncertain.
But that uncertainty
will soon be resolved.
Tomorrow is d-day...
The day we catch up
to the flash-forwards.
Our future both as individuals
and as a collective
is upon us.
This building may very well come
under attack tomorrow night.
But we will not back down.
We are the FBI
and we will be open for business.
That said,
the director is instituting
high maximum alert protocols
and procedures.
Agents Benford and Noh
will be coordinating SWAT
and sniper teams to provide
external security and support.
Vreede, Hawk,
will be briefing supervisors
on additional OPS plans.
We are in uncharted waters, people.
But we will get through this...
Together. That's all.
Walk with me. Simon Campos?
His photo's out to all local
and national agencies.
- His cell phone?
- So far, inactive.
What about his sister?
She's back with his family.
Maybe he'll try and contact her.
RCMP is sitting on the house. We also
have a trap and trace on their phones.
He's gone underground
and taken that QED ring with him.
I want him back here immediately.
We're on it.
Gentlemen.
This is turning into
one hell of a day.
- Breaking news out of Los Angeles.
- What is this?
WYKR has just obtained footage
of what appears to be a man who
was awake during the global blackout.
I gave strict orders for this
to be kept under wraps.
- Who released this?
- Wait a minute. This isn't us.
Authorities are still trying
to identify the man, but...
It's a different angle.
He's right.
No one's seen this on our end.
Where did it come from?
The better question is, why now?
With april 29th only one day away,
the stunned world wonders,
who is this man,
and why was he awake?
Hi. My name's David Walker.
Hi. My name's david walker.
My name's Dave Walker.
Is this seat taken?
All yours.
- Have I seen you somewhere before?
- Me?
You have such a cute face, Simon.
Don't hide it.
Who are you?
Lita.
And if you run, they will find you.
- What do you want?
- I'm here with an offer.
An offer?
Like what, take my last remaining
nine fingers and kill my mother?
You'll want to hear us out.
Simon, please.
I'm dying of thirst.
Just pour me one drink.
I suppose a taste wouldn't hurt.
What'll it be?
Not here.
-= Blackout Team =-
Saison 1 - Épisode 20
-= The Negotiation =-
This is Agent Noh of the FBI.
I need to speak to the news director
that took possession of
the suspect zero footage.
See if you can find him.
I'll hold.
- What are you doing here?
- Hi. Is something wrong?
I'm just surprised to see you.
What's going on?
I was in court over on spring.
I need a favor.
What's up?
Take tomorrow off.
Tomorrow? Not a chance.
- You know what tomorrow is.
- Exactly.
I looked into airfare to Hawaii...
Dirt cheap.
Apparently, people are afraid
to fly on flash-forward day, so...
- Baby, listen...
- We can make this happen.
Tomorrow can be
whatever we want it to be.
We're not tied down to anything now.
Let's just go.
Listen, we can't just pretend I'm not
connected to other people, all right?
You know what's supposed to happen
to Mark, and there's Janis,
- and there's Wedeck...
- For once...
Baby, can this just be
about you and me?
I'm gonna be on this plane tomorrow.
I'm hoping you will be, too.
This isn't fair.
Hang on. Hi.
This is Agent Noh from the FBI.
I need to speak
to your news director...
Whoever took possession of the footage.
I need to know how you got it.
I've got McDow in your office.
Olivia is with him.
Why?
They got some kind of connection.
She keeps him calm.
If he knows anything about who's going
to attack this office tomorrow night,
I want to be the first
to hear about it.
That's not right.
That's in the wrong place.
- I don't think you should touch that.
- This... it's not right.
Don't touch it.
- That's not right. Who did this?
- Could you leave those, please?
It's not right. It's not right as rain.
So many things I missed before.
- My name is Mark.
- You're Mark Benford.
She's Olivia Simcoe. I'm gonna meet
Stanford Wedeck and Janis Hawk
- when they walk through that door.
- Wait, wait. Go back.
- Go back to the drawing board.
- No, go back...
It's not right, see? See it?
Right time, wrong place.
See it?
It's not right.
And this one, that's not right.
- Can I take a look at that?
- It's my book. You be careful.
It's my book. It's my book.
How did you draw this?
With a pen.
With a pen. It's with a red pen,
because I like to use
the red pen for the lines...
Gabriel was given
multiple flash-forwards,
- so he may have been here before.
- I was here...
With Dr. Frost.
Dyson Frost?
He told my mother
he'd take care of me.
He didn't say it would be good care.
It wasn't.
Olivia took care of me at the hospital,
and I got some new shoes.
- Do you like my new shoes?
- They're cute.
And I have a huge hippocampus,
FYI.
Thanks for bringing him in.
Glad I could help.
We have to formally
debrief him, though.
I'm gonna go now.
- Should I stay, or should I go now?
- You're staying.
You're staying?
- You're gonna stay.
- Please...
- Can you let go of my arm?
- You're staying.
- Listen...
- You can't touch! You can look,
but you can't touch this.
- You can't touch this.
- Gabriel, it's okay.
- Maybe I should stay.
- I think that's a good idea.
- Everything's okay. It's all okay.
- It's okay now?
See? It's okay.
You want a soda?
Yeah. Can I have a soda?
With a straw?
Good. Here we go.
It's over. I'm done.
Pull me out.
- I've gone as far as I'm willing to go.
- Just take a breath.
They want me to kill Mark.
I tried to stall by going to DC,
but Carline's been calling me
every single hour.
You can't say no.
What am I supposed to do?
He's an FBI agent.
He's my friend.
I'm not gonna do it.
If you say no,
they'll find someone else
to kill him,
and then they'll kill you.
There is no coming in
from the cold here, agent Hawk.
The only way out is to finish
what we started.
Look at me.
We're close.
Fine.
But they're getting antsy.
They're gonna burn me
if I don't give them something big.
Then give them something big.
I tried calling you last night.
- And the night before that.
- I know. I'm sorry.
Things have been really crazy.
I didn't want to talk to you
about this at work, but...
I think we need a plan.
I'm really busy. Do you think
we can talk about this later?
I want to be a part of what's going on
with this baby.
I really appreciate that you were there
for me when I needed you
but you don't have
to do anything now.
She's my responsibility. It's fine.
What if that's not okay with me?
What if I don't want to walk away?
You have a second chance at life.
You and Zoey should make
the best of it.
I put everything in place for the
security detail at the house tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll have 'em lay low
so as not to upset Charlie.
- What's the matter?
- I don't know, Mark. It's just weird.
It's weird to be talking to you
about security details,
and not...
I don't know, garage door openers
and parent/teacher conferences.
Yeah. I wish I had something to say
that would make it easier.
Gotta make it right, yeah.
Gotta make it right.
It's wrong. Right is right.
- That's right.
- Hey, I thought I told you...
What's he doing in here by himself?
Where's Vreede?
He went to get my book.
It's not in the right place.
It's not right.
I can't have you
pulling things apart like this.
All right? There you go.
Make it look right.
- I don't understand.
- You. You make it look right.
Make.
You. You make it look, like,
like this.
Like that.
That's where they're holding Tracy.
Joshua base.
Jericho has these bases all over.
None of them on a map.
Kidnap,
imprison, torture whoever they want.
A shadow army.
That does things
your government wants to do,
but legally can't.
Who are you sending those to?
Someone who shares your belief
that Jericho are criminals.
There.
That's where they conduct
all the interrogations.
Tracy will be in there.
You get these uploaded,
then we'll get my daughter back.
Authorities have identified him
as physicist Simon Campos...
Run away with me.
... along with Dr. Simcoe
took responsibility...
Where would we go?
Well, I would say Paris,
but you messed that up when your people
plastered my face all over the news.
Don't get snippy with me.
I'm just the messenger.
Besides,
Hellinger wants to help you.
Who's Hellinger?
Hellinger's our boss.
I don't have a boss.
Everyone has a boss.
He paid for your school,
got you a job equal to your talents,
protected you along the way.
He's the big guy.
Piss off. I'm done paying my debts.
Hey, we're not the enemy.
We're your only friends.
Well, I have a message
for your friends.
I'm done dealing
with lower level functionaries.
I thought I sent
that message with flosso.
These things need to be
face-to-face.
Believe me, he got that message.
He's anxious to speak with you.
Why are you here?
Trying to keep you in one place.
One thing you should know...
He's a very charming man...
Until he's not.
Mr. Campos.
Let's share a drink, shall we?
Yeah, all of them.
We were...
We were all together at Raven river.
And you're certain about her?
Nhadra, yeah.
Nhadra had a nice smile.
Not in this picture,
but Nhadra had a nice smile.
And this is Kent.
This is a terrible picture of Kent.
Kent's my friend. Although technically
he's dead, he's still my friend.
All of these people were together,
and they're all connected
by the experiment?
We can posit that Raven river
was some kind of research
and development,
and Somalia was an alpha test
for the GBO on October 6th.
Or October 6th was the beta test,
and this is just the beginning.
Do you have any idea
when the next one will be...
The next global blackout?
We need your help with this.
Is there a specific date or time?
Dr. Frost was in charge. He...
He chose the time and the day.
No, I just went on my trips, is all.
I just went on my trips,
and then I wrote down the notes.
Dyson Frost ran the experiments
by himself?
Was there anyone else?
Yeah, the big guy.
He's the boss. Big guy.
You have his picture?
I drew his picture. He's very clean.
Does big guy have a name?
I just... I just told you his name.
His name is big guy.
Where is his picture?
- In my book.
- This one?
Yeah. Page 15.
It's a good picture.
It's in the black pen.
That's big guy.
Big guy.
I need you to tell me
everything you know about this man.
Hey, sorry to interrupt.
Mark, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Hey. What's up?
- It's not safe.
- You're safe here.
I'm fine! I'm fine!
He's not supposed to be here right now!
He died! You died!
Very sad that day, but that's...
That's the way it has to go
if things are gonna work out right.
You died that day.
Can you imagine
what vile, diseased lips
last touched these glasses...
or those sheets?
I'd hate to see them
under a black light.
The life of suspect zero.
You'd be surprised
what you get used to.
So...
We're about a day
away from the 29th.
It's time to come home.
Piss off.
Can we get a little ice in here please,
Lita?
You have every right to be angry.
Oh, I'm way past angry, mate.
Where do you go from here, Simon?
You're a fugitive from the FBI,
the whole world, for that matter.
Your life's work is over.
You have nothing.
You are nothing.
I can give it all back to you.
Come work for us.
You will be protected.
Your work will continue.
And we can even arrange for you
to see your family from time to time.
Your dear Annabelle.
That's the carrot.
What's the stick?
The stick...
Is the stick.
I don't want to consider that.
Because there is no stick.
What are you gonna do?
Kill my family?
Cut me up? Hasn't worked so far.
You need me,
otherwise I wouldn't be here.
At some point...
we will cut our losses.
I'm the only person
that can calibrate the accelerator,
and you know it.
This is your final offer.
I'd say sleep on it,
but we're running out of time.
Yeah.
Well, you'll be receiving
my response soon enough.
Maybe Gabriel's "big guy"
can give us a lead on Simon.
We'll run this through
facial recognition analysis,
get it out worldwide.
We're closing in, Demetri.
You with me?
- I'm sorry. It's all right.
- Did McDow get under your skin?
A little.
And the whole thing with Slingerland
trying to kill people
to course-correct the universe,
and Dyson Frost and his garden
of forking paths. Now this guy.
I know where you're headed
with this.
Don't go there.
You believe any of that stuff?
That the universe
is somehow pushing us
towards one certain outcome?
Then my being alive isn't somehow...
Screwing things up?
I think you're screwing
a lot of things up,
but the universe
has nothing to do with it.
Thank you.
That was really touching.
Happy to help.
After 10:00 tomorrow night,
we're gonna have to go back
to living the way we used to.
Thank you.
Not looking ahead.
Gotta say,
kind of looking forward to it.
Me too.
I can see you're feeling better.
I have a huge hippocampus.
F.Y.I. Yeah, Olivia...
Olivia told me so.
- Olivia said so.
- She would know.
- Yeah.
- How's the debriefing?
- Stressful.
- Very stressful.
- I know. I've been there.
- How's it going without Simon?
Struggling
with the decoherence equation.
Yeah, the equation.
Yeah, the equa...
The equation?
You do the math.
I don't do math. I do art.
You do the math. Do the numbers.
You do the numbers together.
They have to be in the right order,
and then you're part of the equation...
Both of you are part of the equation.
This confirms Clemente's suspicions.
This entire operation
is not supposed to exist.
- You got what you're looking for?
- I do.
- You've done a great job.
- Then it's time to get tracy.
- You're not going in there.
- Yes, I am.
Don't.
Please sit tight,
At least until I can get the military
there to back you up.
Negative.
My daughter is now the priority.
- I've held up my end of the deal.
- I know,
and I appreciate that, Aaron,
but I want to keep you safe.
Stay where you are.
I can't.
Damn it!
They're putting her in the truck.
Let's go.
I'm running out of excuses for you.
You asked me to kill my friend, Carline,
not to bake a cake.
I didn't ask you to do anything.
And when I tell you something
needs to be done,
you need to do it.
I understand that,
but Benford's an F.B.I. agent.
I can't just walk into the office
and shoot him in the head.
I'll take care of it.
When I can do it without getting
myself killed in the process.
It better be before tomorrow night.
- Why?
- Questions get you killed, sweet pea.
Where are we with mosaic?
Don't piddle, Janis.
You are hanging on by a thread.
If I go back empty-handed,
it's over for you.
You have a baby to think about.
Gabriel McDow.
Do you know him?
Yeah, I know Gabe.
He's in the F.B.I. right now,
laying the whole thing out...
Raven river, Dyson Frost, all of it.
And they're buyin' it?
They know he's a gold mine
and that your people want him dead.
He has been a bit of sand
in the petroleum jelly.
Can you deliver him?
He's being moved to a safe house.
I can tell you when and where.
I don't care
what they say about you.
You're worth the money, honey.
News director says
the suspect zero footage
came on a flash drive by messenger.
I've got forensics on the envelope.
Review the surveillance tapes
from the news building.
I want to talk to that messenger.
Marshals have a safe house
available in Sylmar.
- It's our best option for McDow.
- Overused. And Silver Strand Beach?
D.E.A.'s using it.
Sylmar it is.
We're on the move within the hour.
McDow's gonna blow a gasket
if we separate him from Olivia.
I'll let you break the news.
Thanks.
Olivia, could I talk to you
for a minute, please?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna be right outside.
Right there.
We're gonna take you
to your new house.
You'll like it there.
Can you tell me what you see?
Loose ends.
I know the feeling.
Listen, before you go,
I need to ask something.
You called. You said...
"Olivia...
"Olivia... Simcoe."
- Olivia Simcoe, yes.
- That's right.
I need to know,
is that how this all turns out?
It's what I've seen.
I see so many things.
So many things I see come true,
and I've been waiting a long time.
Is she gonna be okay?
Will she be safe?
That's far enough. Let's put her down
and start digging.
Nice shot.
Don't move!
Don't move! Don't move!
Tracy, it's me. It's dad.
- You're safe now. You're safe.
- We've got to move and take cover.
I'll assess her injuries over there.
You're gonna be okay.
I got you.
Daisy?
Yes, it's Stan.
Can you get the President for me?
Put him through.
Big day tomorrow, Stan?
Yes, it is. Listen...
- What's wrong?
- I'm sitting here with something...
That I don't want,
and it has to do with you.
Well, you know all my secrets, Stan.
We've come all this way.
How bad could it be?
Joshua base.
It doesn't ring a bell.
Then I have nothing to worry about
if I turn these photos over to Clemente
- for further investigation.
- Why Clemente?
Have you ever asked your Vice President
what she saw happening...
Tomorrow?
I always knew this call was coming.
I just never figured
it would come from you.
I appreciate the call,
Assistant Director Wedeck.
Assistant Director Stanford Wedeck
for Vice President Clemente.
- Gentlemen, we all squared away?
- Ready to go.
- How you doing, Gabriel?
- I'm bulletproof now.
Feels good, doesn't it?
- Where's Dem?
- Prepping the van. Let's go.
McDow is on the move.
Black van, two agents,
two S.W.A.T., heavily armed.
118 east to Sylmar,
exit Foothill towards Arroyo.
- 20 minutes.
- Copy that. We're on our way.
It's the day
before the flash-forward,
and once again, everyone's asking,
"what did you see?"
So I'll tell you exactly what I saw.
I was, and will be,
enjoying atomic
wings at Wing a Ding Ding
off Tujunga!
Tuesday night is ladies night,
where ladies...
Jackass.
Sounds good to me.
This guy didn't even think
about using his blinker.
Learn the rules, son!
- You all right back there?
- We're good.
Check this out.
Get out of here. Reverse.
Go, Vreede!
Don't shoot!
- Drop your weapon!
- On the ground.
Play along.
Just play along.
We're after the big guy, okay?
Call your boss.
Tell him you have your man.
On the ground!
Are we clear?
My men will interrogate this soldier,
we'll see
what he knows about Tracy.
There must be a military hospital
back near Kandahar.
The roads are too dangerous.
They'll flag us at the checkpoints.
Even if we manage to get there
without getting killed
- I don't think she'll survive the ride.
- Hold on, honey.
- I got you.
- Daddy.
- Aaron, we can't go back now.
- You listen to me, buddy.
We are gonna drive back to Kandahar,
and you're gonna save her life.
I saw her alive.
She's gonna make it.
We all are. Now drive.
Hold on, sweetheart. I got you.
We're gonna be fine.
I got you. Drive.
Mr. Hellinger said right over there.
Gabriel McDow.
Welcome back into the fold.
- It's a trap!
- Don't!
Red! Red!
Burn it all!
Move!
Hellinger, freeze!
Down on the ground!
Face down!
Don't move!
Game over, Hellinger.
Start talking.
Simon Campos...
does he work for you? Is he here?
Tell me where he is!
Damn it, Mark!
You scared me.
Who do you work for?
What?
You're not FBI.
So who the hell signs your paychecks?
CIA.
How long?
Vogel recruited me at Quantico.
Three years.
How did you know?
I got suspicious when you sold out
Marcie as the mole.
Marcie has a brother.
He's dying in Missouri
in a full-care facility.
It's expensive.
The meetings with Vogel,
the fish store...
where I assume you were meeting
your contact.
But it was the Hellinger sting,
confirmed everything.
Your assignment today
goes beyond being
- McDow's decoy.
- How far beyond?
Intel says they're planning to kidnap
McDow en route to the safe house, so...
It's out best chance
to capture someone of value.
Based on what intel, Janis?
- There's a lot of chatter.
- "There's a lot of chatter"?
There is no chatter.
We don't even know where to listen.
- Who's your source?
- My source
is reliable.
You blew your cover
by setting him up.
Why now?
Because they wanted me to kill you,
Mark.
I told them I would.
A lot of people are gonna be wondering
who you really are.
I did what I had to do.
"Sacrifice for the greater good."
I've tried that line. It doesn't work.
Looks good on a plaque, though.
Don't say that to me, Mark.
I've been living
in between two separate lives
in this tiny space
where nothing ever happens.
I can't have any friends.
I can't
fall in love.
Nobody even knows me.
I was doing my job.
That has to count for something.
It does.
Too bad all anyone will ever see
is the deception,
and they will never get past it.
You're on the outside now, Janis.
If you sacrifice everything,
be prepared to walk alone.
You're walking right beside me.
You're about to lose your family.
Is it worth it to you?
I don't ask that question.
How can you not?
Too much at stake.
Please don't tell Demetri
just let me do it.
It's all over.
I'm glad to be out from under
all that lying.
I don't understand how you could.
I thought I could get away clean
and not hurt anybody.
What about the pregnancy?
- How does that not involve me?
- Demetri, I just...
I needed a way out.
I thought it would be
a new beginning.
I'm sorry. You're my friend,
and I should have done better by you.
But this baby is the most important
thing that has ever happened to me.
It didn't just happen to you.
Every little decision you make leads
to something else,
and now we're all connected...
You and me and Zoey.
No, we're not.
Demetri, there's me and my baby,
and then there's you and Zoey.
Don't let this situation
ruin your life.
You don't need to be part
of the mess that I made.
I already am.
Meanwhile, in the ready room
of the American eagle squadron,
Yank, Doodle and Dee watch
while Dan tries to contact
Roger Ramjet.
Roger should have located
the No-Goods' hideout by now.
- Then why can't we reach him...
- Hey, Gabriel.
- Agent Noh.
- Yeah, I know.
Mind if I sit?
Take a seat.
Sure. Take a seat.
- "Roger Ramjet"?
- It's Dr. Evil Kisser.
- I love this show.
- Yeah, me, too.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah, sure.
In all the futures you saw,
was I in any of them?
No, you died.
People...
people were sad.
Very sad.
What do you think happens when...
the future you saw changes?
That's not possible.
It's not possible.
It's like trying to find
a different path.
You wind up in the same place.
Always in the same place...
Like fate. Like Lloyd and Olivia.
Everyone is ending up...
Where they're supposed to be.
Even you.
Makes sense.
- Now what's your plan?
- Find that diabolical machine
- before it's too late.
- Then hurry.
Wait here. Wait here.
My god.
This is it. We're here.
I'll always find you, kiddo.
It's okay.
We made it.
Janis, relax.
Relax.
I need your help.
-= Blackout Team =-