The last time Mark had a problem,
he was away from home
- testifying in one of his cases.
- Why can't you remember everything?
Because I was loaded, okay?
Before he turned around,
the flash-forward ended.
- I don't think he saw me.
- His son's your patient.
My son's condition makes him
a little hard to read. Dylan's autistic.
You're panicked over what might happen.
But we've gotta use these flash-forwards
- to our advantage.
- Mark.
We got our funding.
Mosaic's still alive.
I know what caused
the flash-forwards.
- You don't believe me.
- Of course I do.
The world's greatest mystery's
been solved by a boozer
on a train bound for Los Angeles.
Can you connect to the internet
with that? Real quick.
Do an image search
for "quantum physicist genius."
Go on. I'll wait.
Which popped up first?
Me winning the Robert Wilson award
or the jaunty one of me holding
lab goggles over my genitals?
Hold up. You really...
- I'm obviously wasting my time.
- I'm sorry.
I've just heard
that line a hundred times before.
- You genuinely want to know?
- Of course.
The flash-forwards
were caused by you.
It's simple quantum
mechanics, really.
Whenever a heavenly body carries
such an intense force of attraction,
the universe just goes...
bananas.
- Sounds technical.
- Helps if you have a PhD or two.
If my calculations are correct,
your dark energy could bring
about another catastrophe
at any moment.
Luckily, I've pinpointed
the one location on Earth
that has an irresistible enough force
to counteract you.
Let me guess...
- Your sleeper car.
- Grab your purse.
We've not a moment to lose.
I thought for sure that would work.
A 21-year-old sorority girl, maybe.
But, I've learned
never to go anywhere.
Unless I'm gonna get the real thing.
The actual cause?
I have a theory, but...
the science is a little complicated.
I'm a complicated girl.
I can handle it.
The most basic concept you need
to understand is quantum superpositions.
Are you aware
of the double slit experiment?
- There was that one time in college...
- What about Schrödinger's cat?
No, I'm not that kinky.
Close your eyes.
Give me your hand.
Now... imagine you have a cat...
B.B.L.'s a liter in the field
and only one P.I.V.
We need access here!
A teeny, tiny cat...
- What have we got?
- A gunshot wound to the abdomen.
- We need to set up a peripheral.
- We need access here!
That fits in the palm of your hand.
You also have a poisonous sardine.
Once we close your palm,
there are two possible scenarios.
Bring the code cart.
Come on, let's go.
Clear.
Either the cat eats the sardine and dies
or doesn't eat it the sardine and lives.
- No response.
- Going again.
Quantum physics says.
Until we open your hand
to discover the cat's fate,
both eventualities occur
at the same time.
Clear.
Still no response.
C.P.R.
For us, the cat is
both living and deceased.
- But how can that be?
- The miracle of quantum mechanics.
The observer gets to decide.
The kitty's already
made up its mind.
Alive or dead?
See for yourself.
"Scary Monsters and Super Creeps"
Hemoglobin's holding at 12.
Hallelujah.
Fascia's closed.
"O" silk on a driver to Dr. Varley.
I'm gonna be honest. A few hours ago,
I didn't think we'd get this far.
Close the skin.
Let me know when she wakes up.
This is Mark. Leave it here.
I'll get back to you.
Hi. It's me. Where are you?
I have been calling and calling.
I tried Demetri and Stan.
I just can't get through.
I tried the office,
and they're just stonewalling me.
After this thing with Janis,
I don't know, I'm worried.
Can you just call me?
Please?
I love you.
Again, Daddy, again.
- You're not bored with this one?
- No!
Cards. Make the cards.
Okay. I'll turn around,
and you choose.
So, Dylan,
you know it's almost time
for you to leave the hospital.
We're gonna go to Palo Alto.
Which one?
- Which one?
- Did you pick a card?
Okay, now look at it
and remember.
Now it's just you and me.
I was thinking that the best idea is
you come and live in my house with me.
Cards.
We all lived there
before your mother and I...
I mean, you'll have your own room.
It'll be great.
- Cards!
- Please.
I need you to go along with this.
Is this your card?
It's my house, too.
Hey, buddy.
- Almost time for tric or treating.
- That's today?
Yeah, it's the 31st. It's Halloween.
- The kids go from room...
- I just forgot to get him a costume.
I'll be right back, okay?
Excuse me.
- Playing cards, bud?
- It's my house, too.
- How's Janis?
- Two uniformed cops outside her room.
Only her doctor and FBI badges
are allowed inside.
- Good work.
- No one will be able to get to her.
But what about you guys?
Whoever it was that came
after you last night,
- what's to stop them from trying again?
- Nothing.
Are you okay?
What happened?
It's nothing. It's nothing.
But you have blood on your shirt.
Well, now listen.
There's a room full of
FBI agents that need a doctor
to tell 'em if Janis
is gonna make it.
- Oh. Okay.
- All right.
- Hi.
- Hey.
We had her in surgery
for five hours.
The bullet did some damage, but
there shouldn't be any lasting effects.
And?
And she's in recovery.
She's sedated.
We'll know more when she wakes up.
You saved her life.
Thank you.
All right, everybody, it's been
a long night for all of us.
It'll be a while before
we know anything more.
The hospital doesn't need us
clogging things up.
So I got your numbers.
Get some rest.
I'll call you if I hear anything.
You, too, Demetri.
I'm sorry, boss, no. I'm either
staying here to see her through,
or I'm going out and finding
who did this to us.
There are already
two dozen agents working this
who didn't have a grenade
launched at 'em last night.
Now I'm serious.
Get outta here.
And if it helps,
consider it an order.
Come on.
You tired?
Well, Wedeck told us to go home.
No. He said for us
to get out of the hospital.
- It's a surface wound. Just leave it.
- Are you kidding me?
I want to see what
those D.C. doctors did.
Livy, it's nothing.
You want to tell me what happened?
- You don't...
- I want to know.
We were attacked.
Pretty bad firefight.
Wedeck and Demetri
killed two of them.
The others escaped.
It's gotta be connected to
the guys who came after Janis.
Simultaneous attacks.
Because you're
investigating the blackout?
Why would anyone want
to kill you because of that?
I don't know.
Still trying to figure it all out.
Oh, see? I knew
I shouldn't have told you.
No, it's not that. It's...
When they brought Janis in,
I couldn't get ahold of you.
My imagination just ran wild...
not knowing where you were,
not knowing what was going on.
It was horrible.
But I'm here,
and I'm okay, all right?
I'm all right.
We have just been so...
obsessed with what we saw,
and with the future,
with what might or might not happen.
And it's a distraction.
It's just pulling us out of today,
and today, right now
this moment is all we have, babe.
It's all we have.
I don't want to miss it.
Me neither.
Hey, Dewey.
How is she?
A lot better than these guys.
Attagirl, Janis.
Do you mind?
Got no I.D...
No cell phone, no keys.
No fingerprints, no dental records.
It's like our guys
in the parking garage in D.C.
We got nothing.
Got nothing.
Which means
we're dealing with real pros.
What about,
um, medical history, Dewey?
So far just one removed
appendix here,
one Achilles surgery there.
I'm checking for radial keratotomy scars
as we speak.
What?
You doing okay in here?
Yeah. Why?
You put yourself on Mosaic.
You think there's anybody in the office
who doesn't know by now?
But the point is,
you just got shot at 12 hours ago.
Now you're standing in a morgue...
acting kind of weird.
You've been acting kind of weird for
a couple of weeks yourself, all right?
So...
You want to talk about our feelings,
or you want to get back to work?
Work sounds good.
This guy's right eye is
covered with corneal scarring.
No big surprise there.
What assassin worth his salt
doesn't get LASIK?
Should practically be
a union requirement.
Wait.
You see that?
Looks like a hand stamp from a bar.
No, it's a blue hand.
It's a clue from Mark's board.
Something about Baltimore...
A hand... a blue hand.
This son of a bitch is
gonna be useful after all.
That costume is super fly.
It was the last thing
they had left in his size.
I like it. Really, it's cool.
Although he doesn't seem
to like this very much.
Yeah, it's hard to tell with him.
I think he's mad at
me about the move.
I was wondering
if in the next couple of days
Dr. Benford might come by
so we could, uh...
Yeah, say our good-byes.
Yeah, sure, I'll let her know.
Great, thanks.
- Hey.
I'm glad she's okay.
It's pretty scary stuff
for all of us.
Listen,
it's been a rough week,
and maybe I said some things
that were
out of line. Um...
Let's take a deep breath and...
get back on track here, hmm?
This only takes quarters.
I got it.
- There.
- Thank you.
We're even now.
The guys who came after you,
the guys who shot Janis, all Asian.
Why don't I head over
to Huang's office,
see if blue hand has
some special significance
- in Cantonese or Mandarin?
- Mandarin? Come on, man.
According to the CIA,
China might have caused the blackout.
If they did, trying to blow up
a team of federal agents
- seems a little showy, don't you think?
- Well, in their minds,
it could be as simple
as neutralizing a threat.
Then why come after us?
The CIA agent who testified
at the hearings yesterday
is fine, but Mark talks
about D. Gibbons, Suspect Zero,
the crows, for the first time
outside of this office,
and then 8 hours later, it's...
China is a dead end.
I don't want blue hand
to become one, too.
Do you know where you are?
I am in a hospital?
Very good.
Do you know who I am?
But for some weird reason,
I get the feeling that your husband
is a little bit of a neat freak.
I don't know.
Something about how
he doesn't like his black pens
to touch his blue pens.
Does that sound familiar?
She's back.
You're an amazing doctor.
An overworked one.
- I wish I could be with you tonight.
- We'll take pictures.
Can you make sure
she doesn't eat too much candy?
- Sure.
- Like, couple of pieces
20.
I'll see what I can do.
Bye.
When Mark had you pin
the blue hand card to the board,
he knew it was related
to the word "Baltimore."
That's what I'm saying.
Okay, Baltimore Street
is 5 miles away.
Let's go.
But you were attacked in D.C.
So Baltimore, Maryland,
is the better bet.
But the guy who had the blue hand
stamp on him was in L.A.
Baltimore St is in Silver Lake.
If I'm wrong...
We've wasted an hour.
What?
You believe in these visions?
It's complicated.
No, I get it.
If I hadn't had a flash-forward,
I'd be doing everything I could
to prove those visions weren't true.
If we had anything
to go on at all here,
any real-life lead whatsoever,
believe me, I'd be the first
talking to ballistics or forensics.
But we don't.
I want to find the animals
that are trying to kill us,
and Baltimore St. is the only thing
I can think of.
Come on.
I'll buy you a sandwich
from the Cuban place.
Sold.
One hour.
Trick or treat!
Super shark has Monkey-See and Monkey-Do
in his helmet! He's trying to eat them!
- Daddy, that pulls.
- Happy Halloween! I've almost got it.
I can't believe
you don't have a costume.
- You always have a costume.
- I've been busy, lately.
I can finish
if you want to get in it.
Thanks, Nicole,
but I'm not wearing a costume.
You could go
as Tim-Tim's dad, Jim-Tim.
What does Tim-Tim's dad look like?
Don't say a word, Obi-Wan.
You've got to be kidding me.
Was that a kangaroo?
That is the best costume
I have ever seen.
Got some milk from the nurses.
I'm sorry.
I seem to have lost my son.
- What's he look like?
- He's about this big, wearing...
A pimp's outfit.
- I turned for a second.
- Not seen but there're tons of kids.
- Check the nurses' station.
- Thank you.
Sir, you don't have
to stay here with me.
I'm sure after
that happened last night,
the office is chaotic.
I'm right where I need to be.
I just feel really uncomfortable
in this gown...
I associate those crappy gowns
with my wife delivering our son.
After you've seen
a thing like that...
Was it awful?
Just the opposite.
It's... primal.
You feel like you're at the beginning
of something... miraculous...
A new life.
You'll see.
What's that?
That little monitor up there.
Sorry, we take you back to the O.R.
Bring the type specific.
Blood count's dropping.
Get her on a portable.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
Times Square.
April 29th.
The estimates on the Mosaic
have us at half a million people.
The ball is gonna drop
and everything.
Half a million people
going to their future.
It's a glorified New Year's party.
- Do you have something better to do?
- You could say that.
Who is she?
Come on.
I told you mine.
He...
had a neck like an ox...
smelled like a meat locker.
What were you guys doing?
I had my hands around his neck.
I don't know where I was
or who the man was...
But I felt my thumbs
press down on his trachea...
until something
snapped.
And then I let go...
Looked down at his lifeless body,
quite satisfied.
Aren't you glad you asked?
- I found this on the south exit camera.
- That's him.
- How long ago was this?
- 17 minutes.
Where could he be heading
at this time of night?
I have no idea.
You getting on?
Then get on. We gotta go.
Hey, kid, you gotta pay the fare!
You gotta pay the fare.
Now do you have it or not?
Are you lost?
To our friends,
at 25696 Sawyer Court,
Los Angeles, California, 90024.
He's brain damaged?
I'm gonna put you down like a sick dog
if you don't shut up.
- It's my house, too.
- That's your house?
- You know that address?
- Yeah, and he's gonna need a transfer.
That's $1.55.
Don't worry, kid.
Do you know any magic tricks?
No, mijo, I don't do magic.
You said an hour.
It's been over three.
She's back in surgery.
- She'll pull through.
- Why?
She had a flash-forward,
so she has a future?
450 out,
and she's tachy in the 130s.
What are we waiting for?
We only have one real option here.
5-0 Vicryl.
- With all due respect, Dr. Benford...
- We're gonna do a B-lynch.
Did I tell you about the night before
she and I graduated from Quantico?
We're at some dorm room
getting hammered. I get us a beer.
We finish.
She gets us a couple more...
Then a couple of shots,
and I'm starting to worry
that nerdy little girl's
gonna have to have her stomach pumped.
Maybe not a B-lynch
will contain the bleeding.
It's a far less invasive procedure.
Gives her a fighting chance of
still having a normal, healthy uterus.
Barely.
Next thing I know, it's 4:00 A.M.
I wake up on linoleum,
got a foot in the toilet.
I look over.
Janis is at the kitchen table
playing quarters against herself.
Her insides are stronger
than any bullet.
- I'll tell you that much.
- Be honest.
Would you be making the same decision
if you didn't know this patient?
5-0 Vicryl.
Let me get this straight.
You blacked out after five drinks,
and you keep your badge?
That's...
You know why?
Because I'm always right
about everything.
It's like the hand on Mark's board.
Trick or treat!
Dig in, cowboy, princess.
A very cool costume.
It's my house, too.
You really should see a dentist.
My parents couldn't afford braces.
- Thanks for coming out tonight.
- I love Halloween.
And I was worried about you.
It's good to see you out
doing normal stuff.
I think it's a good idea
- for all of us to start...
- Let's go!
Paying a little bit more...
Watch her.
Stop!
Stay where you are!
Same hand,
only this one's missing some fingers.
And,
the other way.
That was the orientation
on our assailant.
Am I crazy, or does it look
like it's pointing that way?
Stop right there! FBI!
Wasn't my...
It wasn't my idea!
I didn't throw any eggs!
I just threw some toilet paper!
- Where did you get this mask?
- 99 cents store, man.
You're not gonna call my dad?
I'll be right there.
Makes sense.
You run an underground club, you want to
make sure only the right people find it.
If the hand's positioning
is the direction,
why the missing fingers?
The last hand had three fingers?
Right.
We just drove three blocks.
That's it.
Nice.
Sorry, but I tried Olivia first.
- She's in surgery.
- You did the right thing.
He came out of nowhere,
and he had on this hospital bracelet
that I was able to get off
and call his dad. He's on his way over.
I'm Mark.
What's your name?
My name is Dylan.
My favorite book is
"Harry Potter, Prisoners of Azkaban".
My dad does magic.
Does your dad know you're here?
This is my house, too.
No, Dylan, this is my house, and
I'm trying to find out
how you got here from the hospital.
Go ahead.
It's your house, too.
How do you know this address?
"To our friends
"at 25696 Sawyer Court,
"Los Angeles, California,
"90024."
- Hey, Dylan!
- Hi, Charlie.
Nuts to you, Squirrelio!
- Toot, toot!
What was that?
It's from the cartoon.
Do you know Dylan from school?
He's just my friend.
What?
Excuse me.
Hello.
I think my son is here.
He's right here.
Come on in.
- Are you all right?
- Don't worry, he seems fine.
He slipped out of the hospital.
I can't believe he'd wander off.
Thank you for taking
such good care of him, Mr...
Benford.
Mark Benford.
And I didn't catch your name.
Lloyd Simcoe.
This is my son Dylan.
- Wait.
- Benford?
Are you somehow related to Olivia,
Dr. Benford?
I'm her husband.
Of course.
That makes perfect sense.
Your name being Benford,
her name being Benford.
Trick or treat!
Hey, honey.
You're her.
Not yet.
Charlie, why don't we double check
your candy in the kitchen?
Nicole, you want to come?
Good idea.
What's going on?
I thought you might know.
Dylan came here.
- Why?
- This is my house, too.
It's your house, too, Dylan.
He keeps saying that.
Dylan is autistic.
- The repetitive speech...
- I don't need a diagnosis.
- Now I understand.
- What?
Why I made her...
- Why I made you so...
- Uncomfortable?
Okay, clearly,
this is an unusual situation.
- No kidding.
- Don't be like that.
I can make this comfortable
for everybody.
You leave,
you don't come back.
I'm very sorry if we've caused you
any inconvenience.
Thank you...
Both...
for the kindness you've shown Dylan.
Thank you.
It's my house, too.
- Come on.
- Good night, Olivia.
- Come on, Dylan. Let's go.
- Good night, Dylan.
Looks like the party's over.
Definitely over.
These came from a friend
of yours named Maya...
"Worried about you."
You okay?
When I got shot...
the bullet...
bounced around all over the place.
The only thing they said
they could do without...
taking the whole thing out...
Olivia did this thing
called a B-lynch.
But with all the scarring...
They said that it's gonna
be almost impossible...
Why am I crying?
I never even wanted to have a baby.
It's gonna be all right.
I can see why you like him.
He's very charming.
I don't like him. Come on.
Can you stop so we can
actually talk about this?
I don't like him.
- He's the father of one of my patients.
- I know who he is.
I want to know how his son
found his way here.
I have no idea.
Really?
I'm a little confused,
because I thought you said
you had Dylan moved off your rotation.
- I did.
- You did?
Then why are you listed
as the attending on his wristband?
Oh, God.
I had nothing to do with that.
My boss made the decision.
Your boss also tell you
not to say anything about it?
No, I didn't say anything about it
because I thought it would make
a horrendous situation that much worse.
So you thought hiding it
was a better plan.
That's not what was going on, Mark.
Don't turn me into someone I'm not.
Don't you turn this around
and make it about me.
The man you might be sleeping with in
six months' time was in our living room,
and I sure as hell didn't bring him
into our lives. You did!
That's not fair.
Just be honest.
Have you been talking
to him at work?
Come on!
Come on, Mark.
Have you done anything else
I should know about?
- Mark, don't interrogate me.
- Then be honest with me!
I am!
- Are you being honest with me?
- What are you talking about?
All the old patterns are back, Mark.
You're out of the house
all the time.
You're more and more secretive.
So I'm asking you the same thing
that you asked me...
Be honest.
Are you hiding anything from me?
In my flash-forward...
I was drinking.
Here we are again.
- This isn't like before.
- The lying's already started.
What? No, it hasn't.
This isn't the same.
Don't condemn me for
something I haven't done yet.
Did you even hear
what you just said?
You've been punishing me this whole time
for an imaginary relationship.
But when it comes back to you,
you want to be let off the hook.
But our past together, Mark...
All we've been through
with your drinking...
That's real.
That still hurts.
I'm not going through it again.
I promise you...
I'm not gonna drink.
But it's not about the drinking.
You know that.
It's about trust.
It's about trust, and we don't
trust each other anymore.
So...
everything we said
at the hospital today about...
only living in the moment, well...
All that was a lie?
It's not a lie.
It's what I want.
I just don't know
if it's possible anymore...
Not now...
Not with us.
Am I missing something?
On the same night our guy tries
to kill Janis, he's hanging out here?
I don't know,
but they found this
on one of the bodies.
Remember the Rutherford case?
We were talking about a case
that I don't think even exists yet...
The Rutherford case.
It begins tonight.
All right.
It was quite a day.
Is it gonna be Halloween
again tomorrow?
Just today.
Good, 'cause it was kind of scary.
Yes, it was.
I'll see you in the morning.
Thanks for coming to get me, daddy.
Damn it, Simon.
You scared me half to death.
Did you ever take the train
down the coastline?
Breathtaking.
What do you want?
You disappear to Los Angeles.
You don't return my calls.
I'm worried about you.
We all are.
Yeah, well,
I made it perfectly clear.
I don't want to see
any of you right now.
I don't care.
We have to talk.
Our experiment killed
20 million people, Simon.
What more is there to say?
-= Blackout Team =-