Okay, we know
what we're gonna do.
Till the government
indicts, anyway.
Jimmy?
This answers your concerns?
I think
a lot of good ground
was covered.
Okay, i guess that's it.
All right.
You know, you better
get the tickets.
I got'em already. Don't worry.
Fuck, the rangers
are gonna lose anyway.
You're right, it's him.
All of a sudden,
he asks for a meeting...
to discuss shit
we already covered.
He's wearin' a wire.
You got my okay.
Make sure
you send a message
to everybody else.
Done.
See you later.
Who was it that told me
you hated fuckin' russians?
Ah, the two needle pricks
junior brought around
to pound my ass were russian.
For a while i was bitter.
But tony'sgoumada
is russian.
You couldn't ask
for a nicer person.
These two tonight
are friends of hers.
I got enough cologne on?
You smell like paco rabanne
crawled up your ass and died.
Oh, easy for you to say.
I don't get young ones
like before.
Well, you're gonna
be glad i got you
out of bed tonight.
Russian boo- boo's, you go
for some basic foreplay,
they'll detail your car.
How's the hygiene
over there?
I don't know.
This is here.
You didn't even let me
put anything decent on.
Here we are.
Hi, elena, baby.
How are you?
Hey, okay.
Is tatiana here?
I'll go get her.
You are jimmy?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm jimmy.
Oh! My man!
Big tits, little feet.
A hit in any man's league.
Have a seat.
Fuckin' punk- ass
pieces of shit.
- Did you forget i'm a captain?
- Why don't you call for help
in your radio mike?
- You fuckin' rat.
- Mother of god!
- What's the matter?
Not wearin' one tonight?
- Nah.
- He didn't have time
to put on anything decent.
- God!
Come on. Stop.
I want to watch.
- Kiss me.
- Ha- ha, georgia o'keefe.
Was that your back gate?
Hmm, it's
probably nothing.
Come here.
That's what people always
say in these creepy movies.
And the last thing i need
is your parents come home and
your dad sees my dominican ass.
Seti- i- imia!
Jesus fuck!
I just saw my grandmother go by
the window. How'd she get here
from her nursing home?
Settimia!
Cakey! Tell my sister
to open the door.
Grandma, it's me.
Anthony, junior.
Well, you've got
whooping cough.
- Get yourself
under the vaporizer.
- Holy shit.
- Hey, what do you want, lady?
- Go away.
I will never speak...
another word to you
again, settimia.
Grandma, aunt settimia's
dead. It's me, meadow.
Facia bruta!
Grandma, it's meadow,
remember? Come sit down.
Yes. Meadow.
Ohh!
I can't stay in this house,
honeybunch.
Not while thatfacia bruta
is in here.
Come on, grandma.
Let's go see who it is.
- Evening. How are we tonight?
- Make my sister get out
of the house.
It's 1:00 a. M. , dear.
Why were you walking on
mountain avenue at this hour?
Shut up.
We got a complaint
from your neighbors
of a woman wandering.
- She's my grandmother.
- Hi, grandma.
Ahh!
How are you?
- Ow, shit!
-
you know this young man?
Of course. He's--
he's my- my grandson.
And is this
your house, dear?
Where was she trying
to get to?
Schrafft's.
She's being retested...
for alzheimer's.
It's been a long odyssey
with your mother, hasn't it?
Oh, these last 500 years
just seemed to race by.
Listen to me.
- It's okay. -
- let it out.
- They're transferring her
to the nursing unit.
Which is...
the thing that
she dreaded and feared.
Isn't it interesting
how this memory loss
has cropped up...
right after
you failed to be killed
in the carjacking?
- You think
it was a carjacking?
- Course not.
But i got an idea
who was behind it,
and...
'nuff said.
- You don't want to go there.
- Maybe you don't want
to go there.
What are you
talkin' about?
Well, let's track it.
Right around the time
of the shooting, you were
having hallucinations...
of that isabella figure?
The "protective, loving"
mother?
Your subconscious was
shouting something at you.
On the day before the shooting,
you said to me that
she kept going on...
yet again about news stories
of mothers throwing their babies
out of windows.
Why don't we put
our fuckin' cards
on the table here?
Wh- what do you think, my mother
tried to have me whacked'cause
i put her in a nursing home?
In your worst dreams,
a duck flies off
with your penis.
- Castration.
- Hey, my mother never
went after my basket.
No, not literally.
Look, ordinarily
a patient is helped
to make his own breakthroughs.
But your life is in danger,
so okay, i'm willing to put
the cards on the table.
I say what your mother has,
at the very least,
is what we call borderline
personality disorder.
A borderline personality
disorder?
Let me read to you
from the d. S. M. - Iv, okay?
Definitions
of the condition?
"A pattern of
unstable relationships.
Affective instability."
It means intense anxiety,
a joylessness.
These people's internal phobias
are the only things
that exist to them.
The real world,
real people are peripheral.
These people have
no love or compassion.
Borderline personalities are
very good at splitting behavior,
creating bitterness and conflict
between others in their circle.
You twisted fuckin' bitch.
That's my mother we're
talkin' about, not some
fuck up in attica...
stabbed you
in the shower.
Relax.
See, we're through,
you and i.
We're finished.
And you're lucky if i don't
break your fuckin' face
in 50, 000 pieces.
Okay.
I mean, let's face it,
jackie's work is
what killed him.
All thatagita
brought on the disease.
But his reign was peaceful.
This shooting with tony--
suppose my jackie
hadn't died of cancer.
Who knows how his life
would have ended?
Look at angie bompensiero.
A fuckin' shell since
pussy disappeared.
Ladies,
compliments of the house!
Buccetin"matriciana.
Artie, you want
a pair of hippos
to walk outta here?
That's imported pancetta
in there!
You gonna hate me, artie,
if i say i like this place
better than the old vesuvio?
A few bugs to be ironed out.
And the one in your salad,
that was a freak occurrence.
My produce man,
he's the most expensive
in the area.
The insurance
really came through!
- Yes, it did.
- Carm, what do i hear
about tony's mom?
- Chiara was talkin'
to meadow in school.
- Yeah, looks like alzheimer's.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
Aw, i've known
mrs."s" since--
she's always been a--
an individualist,
should we say? Huh?
But she's a real pistol.
What a character!
- Aw, poor tony.
- Yeah, he's beside himself.
He's got a lot
on his plate.
The attempted carjacking--
- hey, well--
- i'll let you eat.
Okay. Enjoy!
Thanks, artie.
Oh, my god,
look who's here!
What?
You hiding back here?
Your best friend's
on table 12.
When are you gonna
bury the hatchet?
Arthur, i love carmela
like a sister.
We just don't want
this place to become
another mob hangout...
like the old vesuvio.
Get it into your head
that a certain amount...
of that kind of patronage
creates "buzz."
Artie, that kind of buzz
we should avoid in droves.
Sh- it!
- Your first time here?
- The dellacroces gave me
a gift certificate.
It's part of artie's
opening promotion.
- You will notbelievethe food.
- That's what i hear.
Although they'd have
to be doing something
pretty special back there...
to trump you two ladies
at the spice rack.
I was over at carmela's
the other night, ro.
We had somezabaglion'that--
well, now, of course,
we did make it together.
But everybody was
just raving about it.
Please, you made it,
basically.
I only wish tony had
taken me up on my offer to talk
to him about the carjacking.
- Well, that makes two of us.
- Yeah.
Well, i better
get seated and order.
No, wait, wait.
Stay here.
Take a load off.
Yeah.
H- how's the watch,
father phil?
Oh, it's fantastic.
I realized this morning
i can set one of the dials
to the millennial countdown.
- Well, i haven't done it yet.
- Is that jackie's watch?
Thanks again, ro.
Mr. Soprano was kind enough
to come with us.
Yeah, when you
threatened to wait
until my kids got home.
I'm sure
agent harris explained...
that there's something
we'd like you to hear.
The springsteen boxed set.
I already got it.
- You know agent grasso,
i believe?
- Yeah, how are you doin'?
Have a seat.
As we both know,
there's been an attempt
on your life.
You have enemies.
I'd say it's a safe assumption
that you may have...
finally run out your string
here in north jersey.
The lovely agent harris and i
have had this conversation.
I'll pass.
You haven't heard
what's on the tape.
Play it, 'cause
i don't give a fuck
what's on it.
I understand you
and agent grasso...
had an interesting colloquy
about our, uh, shared heritage.
- Colla- who?
- You and i are
notcompare, tony.
You on the one hand,
me and agent grasso
on the other,
even though our ancestors
all hailed from the same
sunny peninsula.
What the fuck
is your problem?
But we do share
some cultural ideas.
Religious, culinary,
matriarchal--
maybe we can motivate you
to testify.
Why don't you get
the kumquats out of your mouth
and get to the fuckin' point,
because i don't know
what you're talkin' about.
Boy, anthony must've really
gotten under your collar.
Admit it. You're lookin'
to crack hiscoglionifor
puttin' you in here.
I- i don't know what
you're talkin' about.
Yeah. And i'm playin'
shortstop for the mets.
A psychiatrist. He's been
seein' one for a while now.
God only knows
what he says.
You wired green grove.
You must have
taken me for an idiot.
It was my idea.
Everyone else thought
it was a waste of money.
My cousin cakey,
after he had his lobotomy,
looked exactly like my son.
Livia--
empty, a shell.
Better cakey had died
than go on living like that.
That's what his own mother
always used to say.
What are you talking
about, meetings? Well, who,
for christ's sake, livia?
All of them.
Raymond.
- Larry.
- Three of my capos have
their mothers in this place?
If this is true, livia,
you know what i--
i mean, i'm the boss,
for christ's sake.
If i don't act--
blood or no--
i have to.
Mrs."s."
How are you?
You remember me?
Arthur bucco?
That's right.
- Victoria's boy!
- That's right.
Yeah, you and my johnny
used to play little league
together.
No, johnny was yourhusband.
But you're right
about the little league.
- That was me andtony.
- My son. That's right.
Yeah.
Aw, gee, what's
the matter with me?
- How are you?
- Well, how are you, arthur?
Never been better.
It's a nice room.
Lots of sun!
Yeah.
Oh, sit down.
How's your mother?
- You call her every day?
- Mom passed away.
Really?
When?
About six months ago.
Please,
give her my regards.
Is she still on
that crazy diet?
I, uh,
i brought you something.
Um, from my restaurant.
- I don't know
if you remember vesuvio?
- Oh, of course i do.
That was way back
when your dad had it.
Good for you!
Yeah, i got
a new restaurant.
Here you go.
Gavadel!
With the nice duck ragout.
Homemade. It's northern.
Oh, northern.
Mrs."s,"
what's the matter?
- Is it something i said? -
you're a good boy, arthur,
comin' to visit me.
We go back a ways.
You made a mean p. B. And j.
After what
my son did to you--
oh, how can i look you
in the face?
Tony?
What did he do now?
Y- you don't blame him
for setting the fire?
Well, you're
a bigger man than some.
Well, we should all
be grateful that...
nobody was
incinerated to death.
Altieri's wake is tonight.
I phoned in
a bomb scare.
You know,
that's over the top.
It was junior and mikey
that definitely
took out the hit.
- Start things movin'.
- Not like we didn't know.
- How did you find out for sure?
- No room for interpretation.
Minchia.
"T," i'm sorry.
Your own uncle.
Now, let's do it right.
Act normal.
Plan things out.
- Make no mistakes.
- If i'm your uncle,
i gotta finish
what i started.
He can strike first.
Yeah, and he won't use
boys 2 menthis time.
- He'll go with what he knows.
- Chucky signore.
No, mikey's now
too high up.
So, chucky's gotta
disappear without
settin' off any alarms.
I just passed
my coast guard tests.
"T." anything else?
My ear hurts.
Here.
One of mine.
It'll help you sleep.
What kinda person can i be,
where his own mother
wants him dead?
The problem
is not with you.
That woman is
a peculiar duck.
She always has been.
Yeah, but that's
not the point.
She's gotten worse with age.
You think my mother
didn't warn me about her
on my wedding night?
Please, don't start
with that again.
Your sisters left
new jersey so young
you would have thought...
there were contracts
out on them!
I know.
But you
were different.
You tried
to make it work.
Two pricks
with nine millimeters.
My self- esteem is
nonexistent right now.
Well, i could kill her.
With these two hands.
The next time i see her,
it's gonna be--
you gotta play
"the concerned daughter- in- law."
You gotta stay even- keeled,
for the sake of the business.
Fuck the business!
And let me tell you something,
tony, dollars to donuts this
alzheimer's thing is an act,
so she can't be called
on her shit.
Uncle jun and i,
we had our problems.
With the business.
But i never
should have asked him
about eatin' pussy.
This whole war
could have been averted.
Cunnilingus and psychiatry
brought us to this!
You had to see a shrink
because of the mother
you had.
When i look at the guys now,
all i feel is humiliation.
I'll take care
of my uncle.
And i'll take care
of mikey "p."
And i'll get
some satisfaction.
But inside,
i'll know.
Ton'!
Jesus christ, relax.
- What the fuck
you doin' here?
- Takin' thestugatz.
- Puttin' it in
the marina next door.
- No shit.
Look at this baby i caught
right off the point here.
- Just wait a minute.
Wait. All right, wait.
- Oh, no! No!
- Look, look,
i need to talk to you!
- No!
Come on!
I'm dialing 9- 1- 1.
Because you've given me
no choice.
Come on!
If anything happens to me,
they're gonna hear everything.
Look, you wanna talk,
we'll go down
to the coffee shop.
- Plenty of people around.
- Emergency services.
May i help you?
Hey!
I need to talk to you.
Do i have your word that
i'm in no physical danger?
Yes. I am humbled
that you would take
my word. Yes.
- What?
- Aw, fuck me. Yes!
You've got my word!
Emergency services. State
the nature of your emergency.
Come on!
Hello? Hello?
Oh, god!
I take no pleasure
in the fact that i was
right about your mother.
You have any dreams since
you heard the f. B. I. Tapes?
No.
Some sex dreams.
Involving--
my neighbor.
Jeanne cusamano.
- Go on.
- Well, we're doin' it,
doggie- sty--
- you know jeanne.
- That's okay. Go on.
I'm doin' her
doggie- style.
And i finish, you know,
and her big ass is--
oh, look, we don't
got time for this shit.
It's interesting
that you would say
a big ass,
'cause jeanne
is quite slender.
We got bigger things
to talk about than
jeanne cusamano's ass.
Like feelings of worthlessness,
sparked by your mother's plot
to have you killed?
One of the reasons
that they tried to
have me clipped...
is'cause
i'm seeing a shrink.
- You.
- Oh.
Uh.
You know that
patient- doctor conversation
is privileged,
and i couldn't testify
against anybody.
Well, maybe they know that,
and maybe they don't.
Either way, they're using it
as a fuckin' excuse.
You never mentioned
any of your associates
by name!
All except for that,
uh, one fellow,
uh, booty?
- Pussy. Pussy!
- Pussy, booty--
i don't know his last name!
And look,
anything concerning
your uncle junior--
all right,
shut the fuck up a minute.
You're in danger.
Get outta here!
That's not fair!
Fair? What are you talking
about, fair? They don't
give a shit about fair.
Okay, what am i
supposed to do?
Leave town.
Today. Right now.
I'm gonna get some guys here
to stay with you
until you get on a plane.
I can't just do that!
Lam it!
- I have a life!
I have patients!
- Tell'em august came early.
It doesn't work that way.
I have patients
who are suicidal.
They're not gonna feel
any better about their life
if you get clipped.
- Jesus fucking christ!
- Look, i know.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm gonna work
on this problem with the people
that pose a threat to you,
and i'll take care
of it, and you'll be
able to come back.
My god.
People are gonna get
murdered, aren't they?
Don't worry about distractions.
You keep your eye on the ball.
- I know what you're thinkin'.
- You have no idea
what i'm thinking.
You're thinkin' you're
gonna go to the cops! But you
can't give them anything.
Don't be stupid.
Even in the short term.
Get the fuck out of town.
You been a good doctor
to me. Thank you.
Artie, how's your rash?
- What the fuck are you doin'?
- How could you?
- How the fuck couldyou--
- you took their money?
Good, then do it.
Do it, 'cause i don't
give a fuck anymore.
That restaurant
was like my child.
So they got in your ear.
Three generations...
of buccos sweated over
that same stove.
Even your mother
treasures the memory
of vesuvio.
My mother?
Oh, don't say
she's lying, ton.
Because why would she?
What'd she tell you,
my mother?
Don't make it worse.
Do me the respect
of not treating me...
like a fuckin' idiot
piece of shit.
When you blew up the restaurant,
you made me party
to a criminal conspiracy.
Did you ever stop
to think about that?
I don't know what
she told you, my mother--
of all people--
two arson investigators
gave that fire
a clean bill of health, artie.
- Why the fuck would i
blow up your restaurant?
- To help me!
You fuckin' bent psycho.
You hear your uncle's
gonna hurt my business...
by stagin' a hit
in my place, and
that's your solution?
To burn it down
for the insurance money!
What kind of stupid,
sick, twisted logic?
All right.
Ask yourself a question:
Am i that fuckin' stupid?
Huh?
Really?
My mother,
god bless her,
is goin' senile, artie.
- I mean, you saw.
- I loved my new place so much.
And this ruins everything.
I swear to god...
i didn't touch
your place, artie.
My mother was confused.
Look me in the eye.
Tell me you didn't lay
a finger on my place.
I didn't burn down
your restaurant.
I swear on my mother.
Take it easy!
What the fuck
are you doin'?
Come on. Look out!
You could--
it's good we can
get together, you know,
for our regular sunday dinner.
Or somebody's nose
could get out of joint.
Joint!
You've got to admit it, ma,
it's a nice nursing unit
where they let you be signed
out for family occasions.
I don't have to
admit anything.
- I gotta leave in ten minutes.
- Meadow!
Well, i don't want
dessert, and i have
to study with hunter.
- Is this pork cooked?
-
kids are growin' up.
Gonna be
out of the house soon.
- Even goo- gootz over there.
- If you believe
she's going to study,
- i got a bridge to sell you.
- I read last week
in the paper...
about this family
in "saint luis" obispo.
In california.
That whole family died
of trichinosis.
That's uncooked pork.
That was last year.
That same family.
Listen to him.
He knows everything.
So, uncle jun, what do
you hear from your lawyer
on the big thing?
Hey, on and on it goes.
Ma, don't you agree...
they should not talk business
at the table?
What's goin' on
in your little corner
of the world?
- Such as?
- I don't know.
The state of the union?
So, i hear artie bucco
came to see you.
Who is artie?
- Friend of mine,
from elementary school. -
he owns a restaurant.
They had
a little fire in it.
He came to see me?
Where? Wh- where--
where are we talkin' about?
Here?
I've lost faith in everything.
You moved away from god
quite some time ago, though.
Is it fair to say it's
not just this recent crisis?
Yeah. Back in high school.
Maybe before.
I- i bring the kids
here on holidays,
but my mind wanders.
I just...stare
at the stained glass,
people's hats--
i'm full of rage, father.
Murderous...whatever...
urges.
I don't just hate this man.
I hate all men.
I hate life.
Have you talked
with your wife?
I can't.
Why?
Oh, what
it would do to her.
She's been through
so much.
Charmaine's a strong woman.
Anyway, she's going
to find out in the course
of the investigation.
I, uh-- i didn't go
to the insurance company.
Why not?
Well, legally,
what if i'm wrong?
I could get hit
with a defamation suit.
Arthur, you know what
your heart is telling you.
I think the only reason
you haven't told charmaine...
is because you know
she'll insist you go
to the police immediately.
And this will jeopardize
your restaurant.
Everything.
You must be strong.
All due respect,
father,
you're getting
off the subject.
Sorry i'm fuckin' late.
Okay.
I need to tell you
something.
And i want you should
hear it from me, not from
some asshole in the street.
About four or five
months ago,
i started seein'
a psychiatrist.
You know, i was
passin' out, and uh,
they couldn't find nothin'.
She's been helpin' me
with that.
Okay, come on.
Give it to me!
Give it to my face.
Well, i'm sure you did it
with complete discretion.
And, uh, speakin' for pussy,
if he's still alive,
i'm sure he would agree.
Business was not discussed.
No names were mentioned.
Junior knows.
He's decided
to use it against me.
Ask now.
'Cause we're not
discussing this again.
It's not the worst thing
i ever heard.
I was seein' a therapist
myself about a year ago.
I had some issues.
Enough said.
I learned
some copin' skills.
Look, uh,
this thing of ours,
the way it's goin'--
it'd be better if
we could admit to each other,
uh, these are...
painful, stressful times.
But it'll never
fuckin' happen.
What about you?
You got a problem
with this?
Uh--
what was it like,
marriage counseling?
Yeah, like that.
Sort of, yeah.
The contra commandant was
trying to scare us priests.
That's so dangerous
down there.
Mm! Aw--
oh, the fresh basil
really adds to it.
Mm- hmm. Mm- hmm.
Yeah?
Mm.
Oh, father,
you got a little--
mm, thanks.
...mess here.
You want a little bit?
No, please.
I have so much at home.
And so,
how are the twins, rosalie?
We should start with,
"would you like a cocktail,
or see the wine list?"
Yeah, sure.
I'll do it however you like.
On my other job,
the waiters usually do...
the cocktail solicitation,
but if you want, i'll do it
as i seat them.
Good. Great.
Thanks!
All right.
She catches on fast,
that one.
Very conscientious.
She's workin' two jobs,
to become a music manager.
Whatever that is.
Everything is goin' so good.
The new exterminators?
I got faith.
The owner is portuguese.
They're sticklers.
I feel so wonderful
we're up and running again.
Oh, you said you had
something to tell me.
I like the bar stools.
You're in a good mood
today, dad.
And if chucky calls,
you get me on the cell phone.
Ho!
You hear me?
Yeah, okay. I think that
i heard you, already.
Go take a midol.
Nipps. Nipps!
Jeez.
Bad boy!
- You prick! -
yeow! Motherfucker!
Ow! You son of a bitch!
Oh, come on. Please.
Please. Come on.
Come on!
Oh, come on!
Come on, please!
Please!
Fuckin' poison ivy
all over.
My friend brendan,
you shot him
in his bathtub naked.
- No chance to run.
- No! I swear to god!
- It wasn't me, it was junior.
He hated that kid.
- Yeah, right. It was junior.
- Mister magoo.
- Oh, come on!
Please! Please, please.
I can feel it
itching me already!
Corrado soprano?
F. B. I.
Fuck.
Are you lawrence barese?
Aw, what the fuck.
Go on.
Joseph sasso,
you're under arrest.
Fuck.
Junior soprano, alleged boss of
the new jersey crime family...
that bears his name,
was indicted today on
federal racketeering charges.
F. B. I. And local police--
talk about fuckin' timing.
- He's lucky he's still alive.
- ...along with
lawrence "larry boy" barese,
ailing alleged underboss
joseph "beppy" sasso, and
13 other reputed mob figures.
Oh, my god.
It's uncle junior.
Yeah. Look at the old guy.
Makin' him do the perp walk.
- A legitimate businessman.
- Dad, cut the crap.
Go blow- dry your hair.
These indictments are part of
an ongoing investigation,
stretching back
nearly four years.
They represent
the most crippling blow
to mob activities...
in the new jersey area
since the early 1980s.
Uncle junior got busted.
Cool.
Not seized today, although
named in the indictments,
was alleged soprano enforcer
and loan sharking chief,
michael "grab bag" palmice.
Authorities believe palmice may
have fled the new jersey area,
acting on prior knowledge.
Oh, lucky him!
Earlier today,
palmice's wife
denied any knowledge of
her husband's whereabouts.
Yeah, he was, uh,
he was so happy.
He was going out
to try out these
new running shoes.
You know, he told me
that he loved me,
and that he would
be right back!
- I can't--
all right, go.
Come on. Go eat
somewhere else.
Coming up next,
rain from canada.
Hello. Yeah, counselor,
thanks for gettin' back
to me so quick.
He says it's a broad
indictment that sounds better
for the feds than it really is.
I wasn't named'cause the focus
of the investigation is some
telephone calling card scam...
that junior and larry
had goin',
and this diamante
technical stock thing
that i wasn't into.
Thank god.
That prick altieri
gave them reams of shit.
They got stuff on me,
they got stuff on all of us...
from the surveillance
at the green grove.
They just don't have a case yet.
"An ongoing investigation,"
the d. A. Said.
They always say that
to make it sound good.
But this is
no fuckin' joke.
What i gotta
worry about now...
is the guys that got
pinched today, if they flip.
All right. Good work.
Art! Hello.
How are things?
Good, father.
Busy!
Yeah!
You?
Like the man said,
"rust never sleeps."
Listen, father--
i want to thank you
for taking the time out
to talk to me the other day.
Ahh. Did you bring
your wife into things?
No.
No?
Sitting there in the house
of god, i realized...
you can either be
a "yes" person
or a "no" person.
A positive ion
or a negative ion.
I- i'm not quite sure
i get what you're saying.
It's just that...
this woman's always
been an odd bird,
a sea of negativity.
Even as a kid, we all
learned to take her ravings
with a grain of salt.
But you also said
the son was unstable.
Complicated? Yes, he is.
Little too comfortable
outside the law?
Yes, he is.
But it would only add
to the quotient of sorrow
in the world to doubt him.
When the source,
unfortunately, is a person...
who rarely has
a kind word for anyone.
Hmm.
You seem at peace.
I am, father.
Thank you again, father.
Sure.
Okay, artie.
Do you prefer
"corrado" or "junior"?
I prefer "mr. Soprano."
Your tenure as boss
was a short one.
Actually, it was unusual
in several ways.
Let me put this to you
as simply as i can.
You can avoid sentencing
on these charges if
you will testify that, in fact,
you were not
the boss of north jersey;
that, in fact,
your nephew,
anthony soprano, wasandis.
Thathe, de facto,
controlled your capos...
with the backing of two
of the new york families,
communicating through
their emissary, john sacrimoni.
We want johnny sack.
But more than him,
we want mangano and teresi.
I wanna fuck angie dickinson.
See who gets lucky first.
We want you
to corroborate information
that we obtained...
through informants
and wire tap...
that you were allowed
to profit, more or less,
but you were not
making policy, and you were
not in the new york loop.
You were positioned
to take the hits,
and now you've taken them.
Question is, how long are
you gonna keep eating shit?
You're 70 years old.
How many years you got left?
My nephew running things?
Not thatstrunz.
Not in this life.
Hey! Here,
let me schlepp that.
You got any more
in the car?
Mm- mm.
How did you
get in here?
Liliana.
She said to tell you
that she left early.
So, what they're sayin'
on the tv about the storm
that's headed this way, huh?
Yeah. You want
some coffee?
Only if you're makin' it.
Father, don't start that.
No, really.
I mean, it's practically
the cocktail hour anyway.
- Would you rather have
a glass of wine?
- How about a lillet?
You in the mood?
Just came to check on you guys,
see how you're holding up
with these indictments.
We're hangin' in.
Oh.
So, what we were
talking about,
a few months back--
think any of these
recent developments have
brought tony any closer...
to reexamining his life?
Making some hard choices?
I told her she was
not to use my card again.
No, that's mine.
One true thing,
just out on dvd.
I was over at video one
anyway, i thought maybe...
you might want to take
your mind off these stressors.
You want to stay
for dinner?
- Something wrong, carm?
- Just tell me so i know
how many steaks to defrost.
- Tony's not gonna make it.
- Well, if--
you know, as i was saying,
my real concern for tony--
father, he doesn't give
a flying fuck.
You know it
and i know it-- at least
for the foreseeable future.
Then that's even
a bigger reason to--
he's a sinner, father.
And you come up here
and you eat his steaks,
and you use his
home entertainment center--
carmela,
the dvd is for you.
Really? Even after
just last week i told you...
i'm not a big
renee zellwegger fan.
You did?
I- i don't remember that.
You wanna watch
one true thing, fine.
At least admit it.
I d--
i thought you liked movies.
Mea culpa.
Jesus, you know,
i get exactly the same
"who, me?" shit with tony.
Two i don't need.
"Has tony thought
about changing?"
Father, please.
You do think i'm
a schnorrer, don't you?
A- a- a parasite.
I asked you that before
and you denied it, but clearly
that's what you think.
No. You know
what i think, father?
I think that you like the--
i don't even know
what to call it--
the, uh,"whiff" of sexuality
that never goes anyplace.
I had feelings for you,
carmela. I admitted it.
It's my job to deal
with them so i can...
carry on my pastoral duties.
How does rosalie aprile
fit into your feelings for me?
Oh, so that's it.
I really appreciate
everything that you've done
for me, father phil, truly.
The religious counselling,
the book on buddhism,
the wonderful chats--
i am very fond of you.
More than fond.
But i think you need
to look at yourself.
Call this an intervention.
Because i think
you have this m. O.
Where you manipulate...
spiritually
thirsty women,
and i think a lot of it is
tied up with food, somehow,
as well as
the sexual tension game.
Whoa.
Oh, mr. Soprano?
Your wife found you. Good.
Found me?
What are you talking about?
You haven't spoken?
We left a message
on your home machine.
Your mom's had a stroke.
Stroke?
The news on tv yesterday,
it really upset her.
Not that it's
any of my business.
Anyhow, it just happened.
The e. M. T. 's are
stabilizing her for the ride
to st. Vincent's.
Ma.
I know what you did.
Sir, please--
your only son.
Your middle child.
- She can't answer you. Her
speech center's been affected.
- Yeah, my ass.
Heard the tapes, ma.
The fuckin' f. B. I. Tapes.
Don't tell me you don't know--
hey!
George clooney, don't get in
the fuckin' middle of this.
Mr. Soprano--
alonzo, call security.
Uncle jun's in jail now.
And i got one last detail
i gotta take care of.
Mr. Soprano!
I didn't tell you, i don't
die that fuckin' easy, ma.
I'm gonna live a long,
happy life, which is more
than i can say for you.
That's enough!
Yeah?
Keep her moving. Keep moving.
- I try to do right by you.
You try to get me whacked?
- She doesn't understand you.
She smiled!
Look at the look on her face!
Go look at the look
on her face. She's smiling.
Get off me. Off me.
Look at her face!
She's got a fuckin' smile
on her face!
All right, that's enough.
She go vacation!
Dad, give it up. We're not
gonna make it to aunt patty's.
Dad, hello. We're not gonna
make it to aunt patty's.
Why did i buy a goddamn
off- road vehicle?
To waste petrochemical
resources?
She's right. We can't
keep drivin' in this. I can
hardly see in front of us here.
What street are we on?
I think it's
walnut parkway.
I got an idea.
Come on, come on.
Inside.
It better be open.
Forget the umbrella.
Come on.
Artie, thank christ.
We went to pick up
the kids at school because
of the buses and all.
We can't get to the house.
There's a huge tree
across mountain avenue.
Oh, marrone.
We been driving around
since 7:00.
Nobody's eaten nothing.
Ton, i got no power,
no lights--
i'm closing as soon as
these last few people leave.
Let's go to mickey d. 's,
they'll be open.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
No! Come on!
What do you-- come on!
We'll figure out something.
Come on.
They gave me steroids, too,
but it fucked me up.
Yeah, well, keep away
from me when i ski,
all right?
Hey, look at this.
Hey, what are you doing, ton?
Hey, squirt.
How are you doin', pal?
Adriana, you look beautiful.
How are you doin'?
- How are you? -
chiara, her brother and sister,
are back in the kitchen
if you want to say hello.
More refugees.
The gas is still workin'.
I been cookin' by candlelight.
I can make anything
on the menu except--
- whatever you got is fine.
- Jose! Cabernet, por favor.
- Regaleali, right?
- Yeah. Beautiful.
No cigars, please.
Look at that fuckin'
lovesick pygmy over there.
The skip seein'
a psychiatrist--
how's that sit
with your ass?
I usually do
sit with my ass.
Why don't you sit
with yours?
Hey!
Pat cooper over here.
Wait a minute.
This bothers you?
Yousawa fuckin'
psychiatrist.
Not a woman.
I can't get past that.
It don't compute for me.
You're the one with
the fuckin' issues.
Womanissues.
Ah, i don't even wanna
fuckin' go there.
Well, let's not.
Irregardless,
i said my piece.
What are you
gettin' at, paulie?
Nothin'.
Look, he's gonna be
their new boss now.
In name, in everything.
Wish himbuona fortuna.
You guys have any
peanut butter back here?
You gotta be kidding.
Oh, god, artie, you saved
our friggin' lives here.
It's beautiful, artie.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
- Ah, fuck!
- Hey!
You said "frig."
All right,
wait a minute.
I'd like to propose a toast.
To my family.
Someday soon, you're gonna
have families of your own.
And if you're lucky,
you'll remember
the little moments.
Like this.
That were good.
Cheers.