[Man]
Get going.
Please.
Do your damn job.
[Girl]
You can't think Milli Vanilli is cool.
I will disown you.
[Laughs]
You are unbelievable.
[Chuckles]
Okay, I may puke,
but I have to ask.
Which one do you intend
to marry, Rob or Fab?
[Doorbell Rings]
Janet, get that.
[Mouthing Words]
Hang on.
I'm like the servant
around here.
Yeah?
Triboro Cable.
What do you want?
Your cable's out.
Is it?
I don't think so.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Wait a sec.
Maybe my dad called you.
You better... come in.
TV's in here.
Dad! Cable guy's here!
Can I help you?
There's a problem
with your cable?
I was just watching the game
upstairs.
I think you got
the wrong house, buddy.
Oh.
Is... that your work order?
Who called it in?
[Phone Beeping Off-hook]
[Beeping Grows Louder]
Police! Don't move!
Oh, God Almighty.
Face the wall.
Face the wall!
Johnny, check the other rooms.
They're all dead.
Got you.
Got you, you bastard.
D-O-G-G-E-T-T.
Two Gs and two Ts.
I was the arresting officer.
You're making a huge mistake.
I don't care what it shows!
I appreciate that,
but I don't care what it shows.
It's wrong.
I was there.
We got the right guy.
An X-File?
I'm telling you,
you let this guy go...
more people are going to die.
Was that the DA on the case?
Assistant DA.
Some jag-off who was...
probably in ninth grade
when this happened.
What is it exactly
you want him to do?
Keep the bastard locked up
where he belongs.
Did you read that?
My partner and I
busted this guy Fassl...
when I was a beat cop
13 years ago.
He killed seven people.
Now they want to let him go
so he can kill again.
It says here the DNA evidence
proves he's innocent.
It's wrong.
It's some lab mistake,
simple as that.
My partner Duke and I,
we catch this 9-1-1.
Neighbor's hearing screaming
coming from this house...
on Flatbush Avenue.
We get there.
Teenage girl, mother, father...
all dead.
There's blood.
I can still remember
the sound of the blood...
squishing under my shoes.
This guy Fassl's
just standing there.
So you didn't actually
catch him in the act.
Ten seconds earlier through the door,
and we would have.
[Footsteps Approaching]
Tell me you got good news.
I have combed through every detail
of this ME's report.
I have read and reread it.
And I am sorry, Agent Doggett...
but the DNA fingerprinting
does indeed exonerate this man.
You're telling me there's no way?
There's not even
a million-to-one chance...
that these DNA tests are wrong?
Actually, a hundred million.
I need the reports run again.
I need you to do it yourself.
Agent Doggett, you...
It'll take at least 48 hours.
That's too long.
Where you going?
New York.
I can't just sit here and wait
for this guy to kill again.
John...
Look, I get it.
Enough people tell you
you're drunk...
it's time to lie down.
But I know what I know.
I could really use your help.
[Door Sliding Open]
[Footsteps Approaching]
It's time to go.
Congratulations, Bob.
Best of luck to you.
How does it feel
to be a free man?
Are you going
to sue the police?
What do you think...
you'll do next?
It goes without saying
that my client is happy...
once more to be a free man.
I myself am overjoyed.
I think today is a day
to celebrate.
But tomorrow,
we will be looking...
very closely at the reasons
why Bob was falsely accused...
and incarcerated.
Thirteen years of his life
were stolen from him.
We'll be looking
at the Brooklyn DA's office...
and the New York City
Police Department.
[Voice Fades]
Bob...
Bob, let's get you out of here.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- How do you feel?
That's enough.
- [All Shouting Questions]
- Thank you. Enough.
Wait a minute. On top
of springing loose a murderer...
you're telling me...
the City of New York
is going to pay him off?
Hell, yes,
and count ourselves lucky.
We didn't spring a murderer.
We sprang an innocent man.
Or maybe you didn't glean that
from our previous conversation.
Mr. Kaylor, on the off-chance
that that's not true...
what would be the harm
in letting us look...
through your documents
pertaining to this case?
I mean, who knows,
maybe we can save...
the city some
settlement money.
Or maybe it gets me
in an even bigger jackpot...
when Jana Fain starts crying
police vendetta.
Yelling at the papers
about the disgruntled former cop...
who's out to get her client.
Somebody committed
these murders, right?
And now that you've
sprung Mr. Bob Fassl...
the victims' families are
going to start asking who.
How you going
to answer them?
There's a lot
of material here.
Where should we start?
Right there.
The original arrest report.
"Arresting officer:
John Doggett."
It must've been
a career-maker.
Well, it didn't hurt
when I put in for detective.
The murders had been
front-page news for weeks.
The sense of relief
everybody felt...
when we caught Fassl, it was...
You know, John...
whatever we find here, sometimes...
sometimes even good cops
make mistakes.
Yeah.
And I've made more
than I can count...
but this wasn't one of them.
Whatever you think...
I'm not here trying
to cover my ass.
That's not what I think.
It's not. I just...
I just worry that maybe this
is about you feeling guilty.
I feel guilty.
Like what, subconsciously?
Like I was told I sent
an innocent man to prison...
only I refuse to accept it?
A cop I know,
a man I respect deeply...
he told me one time...
you don't clock out
at the end of your shift...
unless you know you did
everything you could.
That's what this is about...
me not clocking out.
Bob, I just want you
to make yourself at home...
while you're here.
Just relax.
Oh!
Mrs. Dowdy,
this is Bob Fassl.
He'll be staying
with us for a while.
Oh, I have your room
all made up.
I hope you'll be
quite comfortable.
Thank you very much...
Mrs. Dowdy.
You're rich.
Well, my parents were.
I inherited this
when they died.
I've been very fortunate.
That's why I try
and use my family's resources...
to help where I can.
You do good things.
You're a good person.
Well, I guess
it takes one to know one.
I know some businesspeople...
who are sympathetic
to your situation...
and when you're ready...
we'll set up
some job interviews.
[Bed Creaks Slightly]
I can only imagine what
you must be feeling right now.
I'm so sorry for everything
you've been through.
And I'm so happy for you now.
[Muttering Prayer]
[Eerie, Raspy Whirring]
[Horn Honking]
[Siren Wailing In Distance]
[Doggett]
Hey, buddy...
did you steal that car?
[Chuckles]
If it ain't the FBI!
[Laughing]
Duke Tomasick.
Looking good.
Well, hell, yeah.
I was always the pretty one.
[Laughing]
Not that I'd steal you away...
from even one minute
of retirement...
but I got to get another viewpoint
on this case...
from someone who was there
that night.
And, Duke, I'm racking
my brain on this thing...
and I'm coming at it
from every possible angle.
Was there something we missed?
Well, yeah,
we arrested the wrong man.
I'm sorry, John.
I've been torn up about this...
since I read it in the paper...
but unless there's something
that you know that I don't...
I mean, it looks like, uh,
we just got to face facts.
Duke, you were there that night!
Fassl was the only one
in the house!
He killed those people!
John, wise up.
Will you drop this thing?
What did you always tell me
about being a good cop?
You said never to clock out.
Well, I got another lesson
for you, huh?
Keep after this thing...
it's going to bite you
in your ass.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to see
how you were settling in...
and I should have knocked.
I'd read in your file...
that you had once
attended the seminary?
That you studied to be a priest?
I think it's wonderful
that all you've been through...
hasn't diminished your faith.
I pray all the time.
I pray even when it looks like
I'm not praying.
I know someone's listening, Bob.
Good night.
[Raspy Whirring]
No. Don't.
Please don't hurt her.
Plea...
Were you here all night?
There's got to be something here...
the prosecution overlooked...
I overlooked... something...
I can hang this guy with...
DNA or no.
Well, speaking of DNA...
Ah, come on.
The retests of the typing
confirm the original results...
that the hair samples
do indeed belong...
to someone other
than Robert Fassl.
So, what do we do?
We just go home?
This is wrong. This is...
Well, John, there is...
something else.
It's something
that explains why 13 years ago...
the science of the day
identified the hair as Fassl's.
I spoke
to the forensic examiner...
who ran the tests...
and he found a match
in 12 of the 13 key genes.
- What does that mean?
- It means...
that the mitochondrial DNA
in the hair sample...
is genetically similar to Fassl's.
In fact,
it is remarkably similar.
It is so similar that
it must be from a blood relative.
Wait a minute.
Fassl's an only child.
His parents died when he was 13.
He's got nobody.
I know.
You know?
Then you know that what
you're saying's impossible.
And yet somehow it's true.
Would you get dressed
and come on downstairs, please?
Bob, this morning
I noticed something...
that I have
to talk to you about.
The dresser drawers
in my bedroom...
have been opened...
and somebody had been
through my things.
You weren't home last night?
I think you know that I wasn't.
As it happens, I was
called down to county lockup...
on behalf of another client.
If you're going
to stay here...
then you have to respect me,
my privacy, my possessions.
You're a free man now...
and with freedom
comes responsibility.
[Sighs]
I am late for a deposition.
Uh...
help yourself to breakfast.
Mrs. Dowdy seems to be
running late this morning.
[Squishy Chopping, Crunching]
Agent Reyes.
I'm Brian Hutchinson...
the superintendent
of the prison.
I appreciate you seeing me
on such short notice.
Anything I can do to help.
Great. I'm reviewing evidence
pertinent to the Fassl case.
Whatever I can do to ensure...
he gets locked back up again,
by all means.
Tell me what you need.
Well... thank you.
That's an extremely
helpful attitude.
What's your reason for it?
I just don't think the system
should have let him go.
Why, exactly?
The court says he's innocent.
Maybe, but there's another murder
they don't know about.
[Hutchinson]
Bob Fassl's cellmate...
was a biker named Spud Jennings,
a real bad-ass...
or at least he thought he was.
Jennings was murdered?
Oh, yeah.
We found him in a hallway
that Bob Fassl had been mopping.
He was lying ten feet
from Bob Fassl's mop bucket.
Fassl nowhere to be found.
Well, Fassl killed him?
The murderer was caught
on a security camera...
once he turned the corner.
This is a videograph,
a pretty clear one.
You can see the blood
on his hand.
One problem: This isn't Fassl.
This isn't anybody.
This man...
doesn't fit the description
of any inmate...
currently incarcerated here.
We haven't been able
to find him since.
Don't ask me to explain it.
We couldn't charge Fassl
with it, either...
but I sure as hell know
he had something to do with it.
Agent Doggett?
A word, please.
Don't you have something
to tell me, Agent Doggett?
What do you mean?
The DNA retests.
I understand you received
the results this morning.
Mr. Fassl has been exonerated.
Again.
The results aren't that simple.
The DNA is similar to Fassl's...
to a degree we haven't quite
made sense of yet.
Look...
I just spoke to the DA.
He's authorized
a settlement offer...
which I intend to deliver
to Mr. Fassl's counsel...
posthaste.
I'll send the bailiffs down
to retrieve the case files.
Have a nice flight back to D.C.
We need more time
to get to the truth!
This isn't about the truth.
This is about getting a conviction,
Agent Doggett.
And if we can't
get a conviction...
then the truth doesn't matter.
John...
I may have a break in this case.
A suspect.
A suspect?
Not Fassl?
You really need to see this.
[Doggett]
So, who is he?
[Reyes]
I'm wondering...
more along the line
of what is he?
I ran him through
the known offender database...
facial recognition...
came up with nothing.
It's like he has no identity.
Yet somehow...
this person materialized
inside a maximum security prison...
killed an inmate
and then vanished into thin air.
Materialized how,
like Casper, the Friendly Ghost?
When Duke and I...
entered that house back in '89...
we didn't find ZZ Top here.
We found Bob Fassl.
End of story.
Yeah, but what if the two
were somehow connected?
Monica, for God's sake,
this is not an X-File.
Don't try to turn it into one.
In prison, this being,
this person...
whatever you want to call him...
- he acted as if he were
protecting Bob Fassl.
- Protecting him?
How, by getting him locked up
in prison in the first place?
So, either he's
doing Fassl's bidding...
or Fassl's doing his.
However you slice it,
I'm thinking this bearded man...
was the one who
committed the other seven murders.
I think we can prove it.
DNA evidence
in the Sing Sing murder...
was gathered and filed
by the prison authorities.
All we have to do
is compare it to the DNA...
from the 1989 murders.
No.
Unfortunately,
that's not going to work.
The 1989 evidence
has to be thrown out.
What are you talking about?
The hair samples...
Iogged to your crime scene,
Agent Doggett...
were not there on the day
the crimes were committed.
Are you accusing me?
Are you accusing me
of planting evidence?
I am simply stating the facts...
okay?
The DNA evidence that was used...
to convict Bob Fassl...
was planted.
[Knocking]
Mr. Fassl.
I'm Damon Kaylor.
I need to speak
with your attorney.
Is she here?
You were at my hearing.
I'm the Assistant
District Attorney.
Is Jana home?
She's not here.
Mr. Fassl, I came to
make a settlement offer on your case.
It's... There's no reason
to be upset.
This is good news for you.
Tell her to call me.
We'll work it out.
I want to go back.
I'm sorry?
Please, send me back to prison.
Uh, listen, Mr. Fassl, I, uh...
I shouldn't even be
discussing this with you...
without your attorney present.
But it's my fault.
L-I... I can't be hearing this.
It's the truth.
That's not my concern.
[Low Gurgling Sounds]
[Gurgling]
I'm sorry, John.
You framed Fassl.
You saw how it was going down.
We arrested him at the scene...
but he-he left no prints,
no hair, no fiber.
Nothing to actually tie him
to the murders.
How did you do it?
I took a...
part of a hair sample...
that was found
at a-a previous murder...
and put it in
with the evidence...
from our crime scene.
[Sighs]
Johnny...
it was the one and only time
I ever did anything like that.
L-I was scared
Fassl would walk.
L-I couldn't let that happen.
Not when I knew that...
that he was guilty.
Guilty. God Almighty.
You know this is going
to come out.
I mean, no one's going
to hear it from me...
but... but I can't put
Agent Scully on the spot.
I can't ask her to lie.
I don't want you to.
Duke, you son of a bitch,
this is a felony!
I don't know how I can
forgive you for this.
You break my heart.
[Door Opening]
[Scully]
Excuse me.
Agent Doggett?
ADA Kaylor... I assume
you haven't seen him.
No. Why?
Apparently, nobody has.
[Water Rushing]
[Plastic Rustling]
[Reyes] Mr. Fassl, when was
the last time you saw Damon Kaylor?
[Jana]
Two days ago, at his release hearing.
My client had nothing to do
with Mr. Kaylor's disappearance.
No direct involvement.
None.
I think we can...
accept that.
We're also prepared to accept...
that Mr. Fassl
had no direct involvement...
in the seven murders...
he was previously convicted of.
How magnanimous of you.
It's too bad
you're 13 years too late.
Is that it?
No.
Actually,
we believe this person...
committed the murders.
[Reyes]
What do you think?
Do you recognize this man?
You know...
we're here as a courtesy...
which is something the police...
and the prosecution...
never showed Bob once.
Are you a Catholic, Bob?
So am I.
I remember times in my life
when my rosary...
was a great comfort to me.
Comfort in times of tribulation.
And watching you now,
I get the feeling...
that this is a tribulation
for you.
This man.
Is it that he won't
leave you alone, Bob?
Is it that you just want him
to go away?
Tell us about him.
Tell us so we can
help make him go away.
No more mind games.
We're done.
[Door Opens And Closes]
What the hell was that?
I don't know about you...
but that was me
changing my theory.
What, no more ghosts?
Uh, nope.
Just Fassl.
[Reyes]
What if a man of profound faith...
a devout Catholic...
was incapable of contrition?
As in he couldn't
admit his own sins?
Or even that
he had a sinful side to him...
as we all do.
What if he were
so frightened by it...
that he couldn't even admit it
to himself?
Might not someone like that
manifest a second personality?
But it wouldn't
explain the DNA evidence.
It would...
if he physically became
that other personality.
So, what, we've moved on
from Casper, the Friendly Ghost...
to Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde?
There is a precedent...
in the Catholic Canon itself.
Transubstantiation:
The manipulation
of matter and energy.
You mean, water into wine.
Or the communion wafer
into the Body of Christ.
Monica, I've slept through
my share of Sunday schools...
but I never heard the story...
about the guy
becoming another guy.
It's the one explanation
that makes sense.
It explains
what happened 13 years ago...
and it explains
what's happening now.
So what you're saying is...
because this man won't face himself,
won't face his own sins...
then he is forced
to become someone else.
A killer.
So, how does someone go about
catching a killer...
who hides
inside an innocent man?
Do it.
I don't want to hurt her!
[Knocking On Door]
[Jana]
Bob? Are you okay?
Kill her.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
I, uh... l-I fell.
[Gasps]
I'll fix you up.
You'll be okay.
[Gasps]
I'll take the next couple
of hours.
You should get some shuteye.
John, give yourself a break.
You haven't slept in 48 hours.
I'll sleep once we make sure...
this guy Fassl never kills again.
Fassl and his...
Charlie Manson sidekick.
They're one
and the same person.
Monica,
I don't want to hear...
Okay, but I just need to hear
another theory that makes sense.
That theory
doesn't make any sense.
How the hell to you
does that make sense?
Meat-and-potatoes police work...
is what busted this guy
13 years ago.
And it's what's going
to bust him again.
And that's enough.
And the day that's not enough...
then I don't know
what to tell you.
[Sighs]
'Cause I got nothing else.
I'm going to go check it out...
the front door.
Jana Fain... check on her.
Oh, my God. He was here.
He was here...
the man in your photo.
The bearded man?
Where's Bob Fassl?
Oh, he-he was right there...
and then he wasn't... I don't...
I don't know where.
Agent Reyes?
Call the police.
Agent Reyes!
"Cable access."
Fassl worked for Triboro Cable.
[Grunts]
Trail ends here.
Blood.
He could have gone either way.
John!
[Gunshots]
You okay?
Yeah.
Come on.
I'll take this way.
[Water Dripping]
[Water Rushing]
[Metal Clanking]
[Screaming]
John!
Monica!
- [Screams]
- [Pistol Plopping]
Let him go. You hear me?!
Let him go!
Don't waste your breath.
Just shoot the bastard.
Bob Fassl, I'm talking to you.
I know you're in there...
Bob.
There's some small part of you
in there...
that couldn't killJana Fain
when you had the chance.
I'll kill him!
I believe you, Bob,
because you're a murderer.
Shut up!
I'm not him.
You're not just a murderer.
You're a sinner.
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
Monica!
[Gunshot]
[Grunts]
[Sniffles]
My housekeeper...
Mrs. Dowdy... can I see her?
It's better that you don't.
And the district attorney?
There are a lot
of bodies in there.
Oh.
There are many more victims
than anyone ever knew.
[Sighs]
I saw a bearded man.
I know what I saw.
[Sighs]
Ms. Fain, I think
we better get you home.
John...?
I've been 48 hours
without sleep.
I found out my ex-partner's
a liar and a felon.
Don't ask me to explain
how this could be.
So what happened tonight?
All that was just
you seeing things?
I can't accept this.
If you can, God love you...
but it's not the way
my mind works.
You closed this case.
This time around,
that was enough.
What happens next time?
[Child]
I made this.!