Previously on 'The 4400'.
We're not sure what's
happened. There's something out there.
The light has gone and
thousands of people have appeared.
Diana Skouris, Tom Baldwin.
You will be one of the teams
investigating what happened
to the returnees.
- We're letting them go.
- Letting them go?
We don't have a right to hold them.
Why disappear a little girl,
hold her for 60 years
and send her back,
able to predict the future?
- What were they thinking?
- Is there a 'they'?
Whoever sent them planned
for these changes to take place.
You're talking about a ripple effect?
I wasn't pregnant when I was abducted,
but I was when I got back.
You haven't told your counsellor,
have you?
My foundation has an opening
in the security department.
- If you're interested, come and see me.
- I'll be there.
Despite nationwide
protests, Homeland Security refuses
to divulge the names or whereabouts
of the 4400 living in the United States.
You don't do journalism,
You're getting in the way.
What are you going to do?
Disappear me?
- About last night...
- The kiss.
And other things.
We've got a lot to talk about.
I was reviewing Kyle's EEG
read-out and it seems last Thursday
he had a momentary burst
of increased brain activity.
Shawn, did you do something
to him? Talk to me.
- How long have I been in the dark?
- Kyle?
The results are inconclusive
but we must be missing something.
People don't regain consciousness
after a three year coma for no reason.
We don't care why this happened.
Right, Tom?
We're just glad to have Kyle back.
You've been prodding him for a week.
When can we take him home?
- I don't see why not now.
- That's wonderful.
But there is something else.
Patients like Kyle often have difficulty
adjusting to their awakenings.
They do best in environments similar to
those they were in before their comas.
In every detail. Places, the people...
All right, come on.
- Why are we here?
- We thought you'd be happier at home.
- Then, why take me here?
- Kyle, this is your home.
This is your room, Kyle.
It's just the way you left it.
OK.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I got you.
This isn't my room.
And this isn't my house.
- Kyle.
What are looking for, buddy?
What are you looking for?
- We can help.
- Kyle, Kyle, talk to us.
- What is he doing?
- I say we just let him work it out.
But he hasn't recognised his room.
Linda, the doctor told us
he'd be disoriented.
I'm glad you're moving back in.
I'll try to stay out of your way
as much as I can.
Come on, Jordan,
aren't you overreacting?
No, I'm not at all.
Publishing the names and addresses
of the 4400 is a crime, Barbara.
It's a violation of the privacy
of over 4,000 people.
Whoever did it should be prosecuted.
So, warning people
they may be living next to
a public menace is a crime...
- We don't want any.
- Shawn, it's your uncle.
Let me in.
- Uncle Tommy.
- Hey, Shawn.
- Come to take the tour?
- Quite a procession out there.
Yep. They started driving by the house
the day my name showed up on the Net.
They haven't stopped since.
Yey for us!
Well, I know this is hard for you, Shawn.
I just stopped by to say thank you.
We took Kyle home yesterday
and... I'm grateful.
- He's doing good, right?
- Yeah. He's got a lot of work to do but...
...he's awake.
Aunt Linda, does she know?
- About what I did, I mean?
- No, I figured you wouldn't want that.
Truth is, Uncle Tommy...
I don't know what happened.
I put my hands on him. That's it.
He woke up.
- He woke up and I don't know why.
- You see, Shawn.
This thing that you can do.
Whatever it is, we need to learn more.
Well how? How?
I could go into quarantine again.
They could study me some more.
No! I'm done with all that.
With the hypnosis and the dream
journals and the counselling.
I hear you. But I can be an ally.
Maybe I can help you.
I don't think so, Uncle Tommy.
That was some movie.
Biggest screen I ever saw.
And the sound and all those, er...
- Special effects.
- Yes.
- So, did you like it?
- Not really. But it sure did look good.
- Something's wrong.
- Down!
- The genie is out of the bottle.
- Three different bombings in one day.
Each targeting the 4400s
whose addresses were made public.
Wait a second.
- It's a pipe bomb, tripwire trigger.
- It's about as basic as you can get.
Amateur.
Diana, I just found part of the casing.
Mm-hm.
It's beautiful.
Shawn's name is on that list.
I had my sister upgrade
her security system, but...
Yeah, I'm worried about Maia, too.
Did you ever think about
putting her back into quarantine?
Yeah, I've thought about it.
I've even talked it over with her.
She started crying.
She wants to stay with me, Tom.
I'm glad it's working out.
Who would have thought?
How's Kyle adjusting
to being back home?
Still weak, his memory's a mess
but he's out of that damn hospital.
What does his doctor think?
He's stunned, just like us.
It's a miracle. I don't have
any other way of putting it.
What about Shawn?
What about him?
Where was he when Kyle woke up?
I have no idea.
All three bombs so far were
identical in design and composition.
Pipe casings, tripwire triggers.
I did a chemical analysis
of the explosive.
It's homemade plastique,
boiled down from bleach.
The recipe's on the internet.
Just like the list of victims.
I'd like to get my hands on
whoever leaked those names.
Come on, Tom.
Who do you think leaked them?
- Barbara Yates.
- Goddamn right. It's just her style.
Cheap, inflammatory
and dangerously irresponsible.
I'll handle Yates.
You two back-trace hits on websites
that published these bomb recipes.
- We'll have the results soon.
- So will I.
- You own this entire complex?
- 80 homes.
Once we have this place off the ground,
I'm planning developments in Chicago
and Los Angeles.
I intend to provide a safe haven for
any 4400 in this country who needs one.
We're opening sooner than I planned
but the bombings make that necessary.
You do think big, don't you?
I'm a business man.
I've been given a second chance
to do something with my life,
besides make money.
Cos right now, that's just not enough.
Or maybe I'm having a mid-life crisis.
93 Tomberra Lane,
what do you think?
Oh, they're beautiful.
They're all beautiful.
Well, it's yours.
You'll be our first official residents.
Oh, we can't afford a house right now.
Consider it a gift
for the two of you and your new baby.
It's a small world.
You did it, didn't you?
Kyle waking up?
That was you.
You fixed him,
just like you fixed my hand.
- Have you told Danny?
- No, and I don't want you to.
But maybe if he knew
what you did,
he'd stop thinking of you as...
A monster.
I've been doing some thinking.
This thing between Danny and me.
- Maybe it was a mistake.
- I don't want to hear this.
It's not your fault.
I mean that.
Danny's sweet.
I like him, but...
...that's all.
He more than likes you.
I know.
- Dennis Ryland?
- Yeah.
I'm Warren Lyttel. I believe HomeSec
in D.C. Mentioned I was coming.
Oh yeah, they warned me.
Well, they're never happy.
They seem to think you need to be more
aggressive investigating the 4400.
I'm here to nudge things along.
"Authority to review all 4400 case files.
"Access to all meetings
and briefing sessions.
"Permission to ride with field agents
at your discretion."
- That's a pretty broad mandate.
- They're looking at five murders.
Three unsolved bombings.
Barbara Yates
bashing us all over the airwaves.
Seems to them you could use help.
I suppose it could look that way
from a conference room in D.C.
It looks that way from everywhere
except this glass tower of yours.
I have 1,000 returnees
within 75 miles of Seattle.
I've got two dozen agents
to ride herd on all of them.
You wanna help me?
Get me some more personnel.
Get D.C. Off my back.
But you're not really here to help me,
are you?
No.
- We're here to clean up your mess.
- Where did they recruit you from?
- FBI? NSA?
- Doesn't matter where I came from.
How long have you been
in public service? 15, 16 years?
And suddenly you got a shot
at a command of your own.
Well, you come and take it from me.
If you can.
Kyle, what's going on?
- They're lies.
- What do you mean?
These pictures, I don't belong in them.
These people, I don't know them.
No, no, no. Of course, you do.
Look. This is you at the zoo with
Grandma Fran when you were eight.
Remember?
And this is your birthday party
when you turned ten.
You remember George?
- He was my friend.
- That's right. That's right.
And Freddy,
you have to remember Freddy.
He was over here all the time
when you were little. Remember?
- Bugs Bunny.
- That's right.
- Exactly. He was crazy about cartoons.
- Don't touch me!
I'm sorry. I'm, I'm... trying to help.
It's not my memory.
You're my father. I recognise you,
but I don't know who you are.
It's like you're a stranger.
Kyle, Kyle.
Kyle, just look at me.
Just look at me.
- I need help.
- I want to help you.
- Why can't you help me?
- I'm trying.
I'm trying.
The ripple effect. What about it?
Every time we stop by the theory room,
you and Marco always talk about
how every case we work on
has a ripple effect.
Every case but
the Friday Harbor murders.
What if these bombings
are that ripple?
Knox went from killing prostitutes
before his disappearance
to killing random women
once he came back.
- What if they weren't random?
- That's interesting.
We should look into Knox's victims.
See if we can find a connection there.
I can't condone these bombings,
but I understand the fear behind them.
The easiest way to stop the violence
is to put the 4400 out of harm's way.
Someplace safe for them and for us.
Now, I know to some of you that
that may sound harsh, heartless even.
And I assure you, I don't mean it to be.
Just as I assure you that
there are those among the 4400 who...
Truck's ready to go.
I won't be happy till we torch them all.
They can all burn in hell.
- Hey, I was listening to that.
- I'm sick of listening to it.
- She's on our side.
- That woman is a parasite.
She doesn't give a damn about us
or that our sister was murdered
by one of those 4400 bastards. OK?
Why don't you unload the fertiliser, eh?
Leave the air filter on.
Those damn fumes are killing me.
Kyle! Kyle!
Hey!
It's good to see you, man.
What are you doing
sitting out here in the rain?
What are you staring at?
Listen, you're looking pretty good.
The way your folks were talking
I thought you'd be some kind of zombie.
They won't leave me alone.
Asking me questions,
staring at me all the time.
They're just glad to have you back.
My mom did the same thing to me.
My parents had you come here, didn't
they? To try to make me remember.
- No, Kyle. Hey!
- I'm going inside.
- I've got reading to do.
- You've got reading to do!
Kyle!
Come on! I just got here.
Look at you!
I could have bought a car in my day
for the price of this suit.
- How's it going?
- We've got a lot of work to do.
Five families moved in today.
Seven more by the end of the week.
Got half a mile of property line
to shore up. The fences are too short.
- Overhanging trees along the perimeter.
- Along the perimeter?
Well, as long as you're on the job,
I feel safe and so does the baby.
Two happy residents.
That's a start.
It has been a crazy day.
No, my assistant's out.
My phone sheet is a mile long.
I never got to the end of it. Anyway...
Miss Yates, Dennis Ryland
would like to speak with you.
Dennis.
What a pleasant surprise!
Well, this is a bit theatrical,
don't you think?
- Read this.
- What is it?
- It's a story. A good one.
- About the 4400?
No, about a TV talking head that was
involved in a car accident last year.
A hit and run, actually.
It was really ugly.
The pedestrian she hit died instantly.
It was a shame.
He was 40 years old, father of three.
No wonder she spent
so much money covering it up.
So...
Are you blackmailing me, Dennis?
I shut up about the 4400 and this
envelope goes in a vault somewhere?
Not good enough, Barbara.
- What do you want me to do?
- It's too late for you to do anything.
I gave you a chance and you refused.
Steve Smizick from
the D.A.'s office wants to talk to you.
He's going to charge you
with vehicular manslaughter,
among other things.
Look, face it.
Shutting me up is not going to make
the 4400 disappear from the headlines.
And eventually,
they will cost you your job.
We'll see.
Goodbye, Barbara.
Is this wisest move under
the circumstances, Mr Collier?
All these 4400s in the same place
is a target.
There are always dangers.
That's why I hired the security team.
Mr Tyler, I know you're trying to protect
your family, but you must realise
that by staying here,
you could be in serious danger.
Maybe.
But you know I was born in 1922,
in Missouri.
And my skin was as black, then,
as it is now.
So, I've had to worry about fire
bombings and beatings my entire life.
And if there's anything I learned,
it's this.
Eventually a man's got to take a stand.
I'm making mine right here.
...a sprained ankle.
- To the other side.
- Maia, how did you do today?
- Miss Skouris, can we talk?
Well, give us a sec. Can you?
Sorry I'm late again.
Please understand...
I'm afraid you can't bring Maia
back to school anymore.
We have to consider
the safety of the other students.
- Has Maia been a problem?
- Not at all. She's lovely.
But it's the bombings.
With Maia's name on that list we can't
risk having her here at school. I'm sorry.
I understand.
I'm sorry, Maia.
We'll find someplace else, I promise.
- It'll be OK.
- No, it's not OK. It's wrong.
No, I mean, someone's coming
who will make everything better.
We just have to wait a little longer.
Oh, you got too warm.
Come on. Let's look pretty.
Don't you want to look pretty?
That's better.
- Is that a blasting cap?
- It's a commercial detonator.
It'll be easier to trace
than a bottle of bleach.
We'll send it to the lab. It needs serial
numbers. Or a purchaser would be nice.
What do you have on the victim?
Mary Denneville. 27-years-old.
The flower shop was her father's.
She disappeared in 1999 but picked up
her life right where she left off.
Until today.
Are the 4400 that frightening to people?
Are we too close, so we don't see it?
Something like this isn't fear.
This is hate, pure and simple.
Baldwin.
Right now!
- What?
- We have to go in.
Nikki.
Shawn.
- There's something I need to tell you.
- I know.
- I saw you and Danny talking yesterday.
- I just... want to make one thing clear.
Me breaking up with Danny
has nothing to do with you. OK?
OK.
Do you ever feel like you just...
...wanted to get away
from your life for a while?
I did that for three years.
I don't recommend it.
- You know what I mean.
- Yeah.
Find a quiet place where you
can pretend that... things are simple.
That nobody's angry at you,
or hurt or sad.
I know just the spot.
Come on. I'll take you. Yeah?
- Yeah.
- OK.
I've been studying your case files.
You're the first investigative team
I've talked to,
but it seems like
you're the right place to begin.
Where shall we start,
Orson Bailey, Oliver Knox?
How about Maia Rutledge?
Age eight. Disappeared in '46.
What about her?
It says here her foster parents returned
her to quarantine, no reason given.
Then there's all these reports of
her making predictions that come true.
Next thing, she's been removed from
quarantine by one of our field agents.
I believe it goes on to say,
"For further study".
But you haven't filed any other reports
though, have you?
All of this was approved by Ryland.
I don't see what the problem is.
Next case, Shawn Farrell, aged 17.
Disappeared in April of 2001.
It's a little thin. Isn't it, Tom?
Why don't you accuse us of whatever
it is and let us get back to work.
You two are good field agents.
But it was a mistake to let two people
with such obvious conflicts of interest
to remain on the 4400 investigation.
This is not a conflict of interest, it is
a window into these people's lives.
You have a gang task force,
you want people on it who know gangs.
We know the 4400 better than anyone.
That's why we're on this case.
- Nice spin. Is this what Ryland thinks?
- Is that all your after? Ryland?
You know it's ironic. The North-West
Division used to be a backwater.
It was given to Ryland like a pat on
the back for a career of good service.
A quiet place where he could ride out
his last years before retirement.
But his free ride ended the night
the 4400 showed up by that lake.
Now there's going to be a change
around here, whether you like it or not.
You can either be part of it
or you can get swept aside.
- Lily Moore to see you.
- Uh, send her in.
- Lily, what can I do for you?
- Um...
Yeah, Chilean sea bass?
Tenderloin medallions? Lobster sushi?
Jordan, I just asked if I could use the
common area for our support group,
I didn't mean for you to cater it
like a black tie dinner.
People want to eat whether
they're wearing tuxedos or not.
It's going to be
a really emotional night.
These people are like me. Their family
reunions didn't turn out as planned.
It's all paid for.
Anyone ever tell you
you're a control freak?
Once or twice.
Or that throwing money
at people might make them question
what you want in return?
That sounds awfully serious.
If I've made you uncomfortable...
It's just... you go so far out of your way
to make sure I'm taken care of.
You give me for than I've thought about,
or asked for or needed.
You know I'm in love with Richard, right?
Lily Moore, you are a blunt woman
and I find that attractive,
which I know was not your intent.
Look, why would I try
to break up you and Richard?
One, I'm smart enough to know I'd fail.
Two, I just would never do that.
Lily, thanks for coming by and I hope
your support group enjoys the lobster.
The William Wayne Construction
Company bought the blasting caps.
OK. Check their employee list
with the names from the Knox case.
I'm already onto it.
- I'll call you back if I find your ripple.
- Thanks.
- How is he?
- You better see for yourself.
What are you doing, buddy?
I'm looking.
- For what?
- For me.
- This is the spot?
- Yep.
Me and 4,399 of my closest friends
popped out of a ball of light right here.
It's so pretty. I wonder why
they sent you back here?
Why not on the White House lawn?
Or in the middle of Times Square?
I dunno, maybe
they just appreciate a good view.
- You think?
- I have no idea.
- You're such a jerk.
- You're just figuring that out now?
- Hey, let me see this.
- What are you doing?
Doctor's follow-up. Just...
It looks good.
I keep thinking you're still fourteen.
I'm not.
I know.
Tom? I've found something.
What do you got?
Gone.
- We've got fertiliser.
- And tyre tracks.
They've got a truck bomb.
The tyre prints matched
the phone company's service trucks.
So, we pulled their personnel records
and found one Dean Keating.
As in Gail Keating -
Friday Harbor murder victim?
- Dean's her older brother.
- Not only that.
Gail's younger brother, Glenn works
construction and on his last job
the company was short
two dozen blasting caps.
So, a returnee kills their sister
and they get revenge.
And the 4400 go from being a threat
to being sympathetic victims.
Your ripple effect.
All right, put out an APB
on Keating's truck,
and don't let it
get to where it's going.
Come on. Where are you?
Mr Tyler, we're looking for a truck
bomb. Be on high alert.
Understood. Thanks.
We're running out of time.
There! Truck number 85. That vehicle's
assigned to Dean Keating.
And it's heading north on...
Aurora.
Heading into Richmond Highlands.
We need a list of all the 4400s
in Richmond Highlands.
There's only one 4400 in that area.
It's Tom's nephew.
Tom, hold up!
Operations. Patch me through
to that phone number again.
Farrell residence.
We're not in. You know the drill.
Susan, Shawn, Danny. If you
can here this, get out of the house!
Is anyone there?
There it is. Number 85.
Get us down. Now!
Put your hands where I can see them!
Out of the truck. Keep
your hands where we can see them.
- What the hell...
- Shut up! Stay down.
- You're not Keating. Where is he?
- He didn't come in.
No explosives. The truck's clean, Tom.
They switched vans.
It's not Keating. Come on! Let's go.
We got the wrong van.
Re-check all principle targets.
Report anything suspicious.
We've got a 12ft step van
parked near Collier's housing complex.
No plates, new paint job.
That's what the phone company
uses. Patch us through to Collier's.
- Use any line you can find.
- The phones are dead.
Code Red. Main gate.
There they are. Get me over there.
Go!
I've set it. Go!
Hands over your head!
Down! Down! Down! Down!
On your stomach now!
You are being arrested as a terrorist.
You will be treated as
an enemy combatant.
You do not have the right to an attorney.
Whatever you say
will damn sure be used against you!
Doctor MacMillan to...
Doctor Mayhew. I'm Warren Lyttel
from Homeland Security.
I need to ask a
few questions about Kyle Baldwin.
- Tom, you have to come quick!
- What?
Just come!
Kyle!
What are you doing?
I know what's wrong with me.
- I finally understand.
- What is it, Kyle?
Tell me!
There's only one explanation.
Why I remember everything,
but can't feel anything.
Why all the people in my life
seem like strangers.
They're not strangers.
I am.
I'm not Kyle Baldwin.