All right, now,
my next guest is the guy
that people magazine
voted "sexiest man alive."
[ audience catcalls ]
America's sweetheart,
mr. nice guy,
The star of the new smash-hit
romantic comedy "love mate,"
Leading man of my wife's dreams,
liam mcbride!
Liam!
Look out!
Yes, liam mcbride.
Yeah!
Whoo!
All right.
Here we go.
here, come on.
Have a seat.
sit down.
Wow.
Look at that.
Well...
I didn't get to do that
with her.
All right, big fella,
time to get to work here.
[ grunts, laughs ]
So -- so, liam,
how's it going, my friend?
Fantastic, man.
couldn't be better.
yeah, i guess so.
Well, your reputation
precedes you.
Uh, in fact,
it says right here
That tmz has you listed
with 19 women in the last year.
[ audience murmurs ]
yeah, that's wild, man.
Completely wild.
how do you find
the time?
Well, you know what?
i'll tell you, it's not easy.
[ laughter ]
Yeah.
a-any of them serious?
No. no way.
You know,
they only want one thing --
their picture with me
in us magazine,
And they're willing
to [bleep] to get it.
[ audience murmurs ]
[ chuckles ]
all right.
uh, w-what's the new movie
about, then?
Oh, you know, same old crap.
Boy meetgirl,
boy digs girl, girl digs boy,
Girl and boy hump like rabbits.
All right.
all right.
Okay,
uh, this isn't cable.
W-we get the picture.
No, you don't.
See, these girls --
they just use you.
I mean,
everybody uses everybody,
But these no-talent bitches --
They just want to ride
your [bleep] to stardom.
[ audience booing ]
What the [bleep] do you think
you're booing, huh?!
Oh, they're
just getting rowdy.
No, really,
what the [bleep]
liam.
Yeah, you --
the fat cow in the back!
where is he going?
It's all right.
you want to
[bleep] with me?!
No, the show's --
all right, let's do it!
Hey!
[bleep]
Ohh!
Get him out of here!
[bleep] off of me!
[ audience booing ]
you [bleep] dregs of society!
You [bleep] pious sheep!
You self-righteous
[bleep] bastards!
You can't [bleep] think
for yourself!
you know what?!
[bleep]
all right.
[bleep] you, you pious --
oh, you want to...
[ clears throat ] this occurred
approximately two hours ago.
What's he been doing
since then?
studio security grabbed him
As he was about to drive
his ferrari
Right through the guard gate.
It's just unbelievable.
This is liam mcbride,
"america's wet dream."
He has a history
of substance abuse --
Probably on something,
most likely ice.
When's he due in?
Uh, liam and his people,
whoever they are,
Are about to arrive
in about...
15 minutes.
That's about 1600 hours,
general.
The media helicopters
are following a black navigator
With smoked windows.
That vehicle will pull up
tohe curb
Of the e.r. entrance.
God, there must be 100 paparazzi
waiting there already.
That's the decoy.
Liam's manager,
andy something,
Will pull up to the delivery
entrance at the same time.
Liam will be
in the backseat, hiding.
[ siren wailing ]
how do we get him
up on the ward?
I've secured an elevator from
the lobby to the third floor.
It should work.
It'll work.
[ chuckling ]
What is so funny?
We're dealing with
a major celebrity here.
In today's world,
that's a flood.
There's no way
we're not gonna get wet.
Not on my watch.
who's the attending?
This is my area.
What area?
addiction.
He hasn't even been
diagnosed yet.
High card wins.
what?!
Uh...uh...
[ sighs ]
Please.
Uh...
Yes!
King of spades.
All right,
any other concerns?
Once he gets here, we treat him
like any other patient.
No special privileges.
[ indistinct radio chatter ]
[ helicopter blades whirring ]
Hey, uh, who's who?
i'm andy forndale,
liam's manager.
Nora skoff,
hospital administrator.
nora.
I'm jack gallagher,
The director
of psychiatric services.
Help him. help him.
[ indistinct conversations ]
Uh, can we get him
into t war
I gave him a pill.
what kind of pill?
How the hell
should i know?
there was no pill.
It was a blue one.
[ women screaming,
camera shutters clicking ]
[ indistinct shouting ]
Surf's up.
[ ding! ]
[ camera shutters clicking ]
All of your questions
will be answered.
Dr. carl belle?
Yes, that's correct.
Dr. carl belle...
with an "e
Woman: dr. belle,
i have a question.
question over here,
doctor.
Did liam
sleep through the night?
He was given a mild sedative.
he fell asleep around 11:06.
Uh, he awoke sometime before
dawn, used the facilities,
And then went back to sleep
until 8:00 this morning.
Yes.
Have you made
a diagnosis yet, doctor?
That would be premature.
We've yet
to do an in-depth intake.
In order to ascertain
The exact nature of the mental
illness of a patient,
One must be...
...patient.
[ indistinct shouting ]
okay, okay.
[ knock on door ]
they just caught
two reporters
Hanging from
the window ledge on --
Oh, my god!
Can i see?
Wow, it's stunning.
Is it a secret admirer?
Nope.
Anniversary present.
Wedding anniversary?
No.
Anniversary of my divorce!
Oh!
[ chuckles ]
Right!
I really shouldn't have.
If you knew how much
i paid for it...
No. you deserve it.
It took me
10 years of marriage
To realize
i made a mistake
And a bout with cancer
to get me up off my ass.
The hell with it.
I think
we should celebrate this.
Girls' night out?
We could hit the clubs.
[ chuckles ]
oh, i have nothing to wear.
[ both laugh ]
we could do a lunchtime
shopping spree.
Oh, no,
not with cnn hovering,
And i've got barbara walters
waiting on...
No...oh...
What ledge?!
[ imitating gunshots ]
[ lasers blasting ]
I can't believe
this is happening.
How long have you been
his manager?
Forever.
Got him his first big break
And negotiated
his last $20 million fee.
[ blasting continues ]
Has he ever broken down
before?
You got to understand,
liam's an actor's actor --
Real thing --
totally immersed in his roles.
And, yeah, sometimes he mixes
reality and fiction,
And he doesn'tome out of it
until the picture's wrapped.
That's his gift.
[ breathing heavily ]
This is all my fault.
The agency rushed him
into doing his next picture.
He's been prepping for it
night and day.
He's totally exhausted.
i should have put my foot down.
Tell me
about that new movie.
It's a total departure.
it's a serious role.
It's oscar-winning
material.
The producers are calling me
like every three seconds.
I'd like to read
the script.
uh...
[ chuckles ] you got to
understand, doc,
It's pretty hush-hush.
Can't have the general public
knowing.
It will just be me.
Yeah.
Okay.
And now...
Instead of mounting
barbed steeds
To fright the souls
of fearful adversaries,
Me capers nimbly
in a lady's chambers
To the lascivious pleasing
of a lute.
Look...
liam's not just a client.
He's my best friend.
he's like family.
But i, that am not shaped
for sportive tricks...
Whatever you need.
Just get me that script.
...for sportive tricks,
Nor made to court
an amorous looking glass --
I, that am rudely stamped
And want of love's majesty
To strut before a wanton,
ambling nymph...
"richard iii."
Not bad.
[ birds flapping, cawing ]
aah!
They're circling!
The gulls...are...
Circling!
[ screams ]
Hitchcock.
[ chuckles ]
Classic.
Classic symptomatology --
Auditory hallucinations,
desired illusions,
Disorganized speech
and behavior -- classic.
If that'the case, he's chosen
the wrong profession.
I would think the emotional
demands of an actor
Would exacerbate the problem
over time.
He's been in and out
of rehab for years.
Are we not gonna consider
a drug component?
I ordered blood work
to exclude hypothyroidism,
Systemic affection,
h.i.v.
I've also ordered a c.t. scan
and a drug panel.
Jack...
You got anything to add?
Psych 101 --
textbook psychotic break.
Right.
Textbook.
A messenger
brought this for you.
Thank you.
Oh.
the daily news
and people magazine --
They want to send a photographer
to take your picture.
And ellen and, um,
Jules luckman,
president of liam's fan club.
Yeah, i know who he is.
Little twerp
got ahold of my cellphone.
How do celebrities do it
day in and day out?
I mean, your life
is not your own.
Lucky you drew the low card.
[ chuckles ]
That's ellen.
Blood work?
No, no blood.
hey, liam,
it's just a little test.
No blood!
no leeches!
Get them off!
no leeches! get them off!
No leeches!
no leeches!
Get them off me!
get them off me!
No leeches!
no leeches!
Get them off me!
Get them off of me!
Hey, take it easy. liam.
liam, calm down, all right?
Get them off me!
[ beep ]
[ grunts ]
I'm a little teapot,
short and stout.
Here is my handle.
here is my spout!
[ clapping ]
Bravo.
A couple of notes
on performance --
While psychotic behavior
Can include,
uh, disorganized speech,
Auditory
and visual hallucinations,
Rapid mood swings are part of
a different syndrome altogether.
Kind of got
your research mixed up.
Bravo to you, doc.
You got me.
"crazy going slowly am i"?
His new movie.
"cuckoo's nest"
for the new millennium?
[ sighs ]
Ohh.
This was really sick.
[ laughing ]
fooled you.
[ sighs ]
Someone get me a damn latte.
Whew.
[ ding! ]
How could a staff
of trained professionals --
Carl: since
you are clearly not,
I suggest you take
your criticism --
[ laughing ]
come here.
look at this.
you're the [bleep] problem!
I've seen it.
Why not release
a statement?
We knew it was an act
l along.
We were simply helping
mr. mcbride prepare
For a, uh, difficult role
about serious mental illness
In order to increase
public awareness.
Why not?
Because we are not sailors
on the good ship lollipop.
We're living
in the real world.
There.
now i've crossed the line?!
you don't like me now?!
guess what -- you made me!
i'm you!
get him
off the [bleep] stage now.
you self-righteous [bleep]
What's he doing?
Ranting.
perforng.
do you know how many cars
i've bought with your money?!
seven -- seven cars!
you know how many boats?!
three!
Jack:
it's gone to commercial.
Stage lights are off, so who
exactly is he performing for?
Lots of actors perform in front
of mirrors without an audience.
It's their process.
sheep!
They filmed the damn thing
in cambodia.
Land mines
all over the place.
Really?
Hey, doc.
Hey, hey.
Excuse me.
No hard feelings,
i hope.
I-i do have
a tremendous amount of respect
For the medical profession.
Of course not.
no hard feelings.
I could never do what you do
day in and day out,
And i apologize
if i stepped out of line.
no.
No. hell no.
In fact, i've got to
hand it to you.
It was a, uh...
It was a hell of a publicity
stunt for the movie.
I loved the gull thing.
Yeah, that was great,
wasn't it?
I see 'em all the time.
I got a place
on the beach in malibu.
Andy's a genius.
It was andy's idea?
It wasn't, uh --
what do you call him? --
Your agent,
your publicist?
No, no, no. those fools?
I fired their asses.
[ sighs ]
So, what did you think
of the script?
It was good --
a real page-turner.
Yeah, it's fantastic,
isn't it?
Okay, i'm ready.
Drop by anytime.
[ scoffing ] yeah.
You mean that?
yeah.
It's for a good cause.
Yeah, it is.
Glad you see it
that way.
Shame, really.
what?
Oh, that you're leaving.
I'm sure you've observed,
Uh, quite a bit
since you've been here.
And i understand your movie
starts shooting monday?
Eh, it's too bad y can't
stick around till then,
Let it really soak in.
Yeah?
yeah.
I've never granted
that kind of access, of course.
I can swing it
if you're interested.
No way.
You think i should?
For purely selfish reasons.
[ chuckles ]
I'd like to see a, uh,
psychiatric ward and treatment
Portrayed realistically
for a change.
You can't --
you can't make this stuff up.
You've got to live it.
Yeah, no, no,
you're so right.
Otherwise it would become a --
what's the word? -- caricature.
Laughable, even.
[ beep ]
If you're serious...
I'm serious.
I'll offer my services
as your personaluide.
Excellent.
Carl:
have you lost your mind?!
You talked him
into staying,
Even after the embarrassment
he caused this hospital?
And to you personally.
He used a public facility for
his own self-serving research.
He's a callous,
manipulative son of a bitch,
And i want him
off this ward!
What are you up to?
why'd you ask him to stay?
Because
he's mentally ill.
he was putting on a show!
He said so himself!
He was also putting on a show
when he appeared on tv!
so?
When the cameras stopped rolling
and the lights went off,
He was still performin
Actually,
he wasn't performing.
I think he was having
a breakdown --
For real --
And only later came up with
the publicity-stunt cover story.
so you actually think
he is psychotic?
How would you assess
a patient
Exhibiting sexually
provocative behavior,
Melodramatic expressions
of emotion, easy suggestibility,
A desperate need
for excessive admiration,
And a grandiose sense
of self-importance?
Oh, you think
he has a narcissistic
personality disorder.
So do a lot
of creative types, too.
Hmm.
So?!
Discharge him
and find him a therapist!
We just agreed he has
a personality disorder.
What we don't know
is why.
If we discharge him now,
we run the risk
Of another
psychotic break.
He needs to be here!
Absolutely.
[ door opens ]
Hmm.
Andy:
of course i knew...
When i booked the show.
Liam thought it would be
a good opportunity
To promo the picture.
Jack: you telling me
it was his idea?
And mine.
Liam might be a great actor,
but you're not.
When you brought him in,
You were genuinely
concerned about him.
You care about him.
Obviously,
he cares about you.
You survived the massacre,
didn't you?
He fired his agent
and publicist.
Not justhem.
The last few months,
he's been cleaning house.
He also fired
his personal assistant,
His lawyer, his trainer,
and his stylist.
Liam needs
psychiatric help.
[ laughs ]
He's an actor.
De niro put on a hundred pounds
for "raging bull."
He got himself a hack license,
Drive a cab around new york
for "taxi driver."
Hoffman -- he stays up
for three days
So he can get that really
tortured look in "marathon man."
Cage goes on a drinking binge
in "leaving las vegas."
I mean, that's the biz, man.
They're not really insane.
Liam's on the verge
of a major breakdown,
One he might not
recover from.
I'm supposed to have liam
On the set of
"crazy going slowly"
monday morning.
I cannot begin to tell you
how dangerous it's gonna be
For him to play
a mentally ill person
In his present state.
We have a flight out of l.a.x.
in six hours.
He'll be on it.
[ knock on door ]
Liam.
Doc.
[ clears throat ]
I'm really glad you've taken
the time to experience this,
You know,
for your research.
Oh, i wouldn't have
missed it.
Now, you're gonna be playing
the part
Of a dangerously
psychotic patient,
Which probably means
you'd be put in restraints.
Is that okay?
mm-hmm.
[ sighs ]
Radical-exposure therapy is,
Simply put, exposing people
to their biggest fears.
Like the rats in "1984."
Great book.
So, uh, let's say
you're afraid to fly.
Exposure therapy would involve
taking you up in a plane
And forcing you
to face that fear.
Got it.
So what's the patient's fear
we're dealing with?
You tell me.
What, like an improv?
okay, brilliant.
Um, fear, like, um, fear
of the dark or being alone?
Perfect.
let's start with those.
Yeah, sure.
[ clears throat ]
Good, liam.
you're doing great.
And let's overlay
the feeling
Of being
in a deep, dark tunnel,
Trapped,
unable to escape.
Okay!
Okay.
I get it.
lose the restraints, okay?
That's good, liam.
that's -- that's good.
Right about now, the patient
would be feeling agitated
And -- and be sort of begging
to be sefree.
Yeah, i get it.
Let's turn the lights on,
And let's take
the restraints off, okay?
I'm not kidding!
i want out!
Sure you do.
That's so good.
and so does he.
But it's not really
the restraints that
are holding him back.
That's just a mechanism.
What's holding him back
are the thoughts --
The thoughts inside his head
that he can't get rid of.
No, no, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, doc!
Doc, doc, doc! doc!
D-dr. gallagher, sir?!
[ screams ]
Doc, i want out!
this isn't a game!
[ screams ]
Please, dr. gallagher, sir?!
You son of a bitch!
you son of a...
[ grunts ]
this is not a game!
You son of a bitch!
You're doing this
on purpose,
Payback
for the publicity stunt.
Look at him.
I am.
Are you?
Is he really
that good an actor?!
Dr. gallagher,
please, come --
Are you his friend?
Are you his family?!
Or is that just another helping
of hollywood rubbish?
[ crying ]
[ breathing heavily ]
Help him.
Please help him.
I will.
[ ding! ]
[ siren wailing ]
"liam mcbride, who voluntarily
committed himself
"after a breakdown
on an afternoon talk show,
"later admitted it was all
to hype his upcoming film,
"'crazy going slowly am i.'
"however, liam has now decided
to remain in the hospital
"to do further research
And to wage his continuing
battle with prescription drugs."
See, hollywood's fine
with drug addiction.
It's almost
a rite of passage.
But mental illness,
on the other hand...
You should be
really proud of yourself.
He came in here
pretending to be crazy,
And you actually
made him crazy.
Proud? no.
Vindicated.
What about the drug thing?
Pure fiction.
the panel was negative.
So,
what's the treatment plan?
Psychotherapy.
Something's
gumming up the works.
Leaving me
to fend off the media incursion,
The wrath
of hollywood producers,
And liam's new agency.
That's why you get paid
the big bucks.
yeah.
I need to know
about his family,
Where he grew up --
complete and accurate history.
I'll see what i can dig up.
[ gasps ] oops.
What's this?
Liam's official press kit --
Everything you wanted to know
about liam mcbride,
Or everything the studio
wanted you to know.
Why, thank you.
mm-hmm.
How did you, um...
Slowly, painfully, i'm learning
to anticipate your every need.
And ignore most of them?
That's for your own good.
Not in the mood?
I haven't had sex
in two days.
Is that unusual?
[ scoffs ]
unprecedented.
People think my life
is so much better than theirs
That all they have to do
is sleep with me,
And some of it rubs off.
You've never been
married?
He never met the right girl.
He grew up
in lincoln, nebraska.
Yep.
Right down the street
from the movie theater.
What about family?
Only child --
Dad and mom.
Dad was
a plumbing contractor.
Believe it or not, liam can fix
a toilet pretty well.
His mom worked
for the phone company.
How'd he get the bug?
He played baseball
in high school --
Team captain junior year --
Until he broke an ankle
sliding into home.
Rather than sitting around on
the bench collecting splinters,
He ended up in a drama class
and never looked back.
[ echoing ] his bio says
he moved to the west coast
After college,
got a job waiting tables,
Started acting classes,
and met andy...
[ normal voice ]
who discovered him...
And launched his career.
No.
Not andy.
It was somebody else.
Hey.
Yeah, it's really me.
He's worse.
He's talking about liam like
he's a totally different person.
Dissociation.
comes and goes.
And he's not worse.
he's evolving.
What does that make you --
darwin?
I tried to talk to liam
about his past,
And this is what i got.
"dad was
a plumbing contractor.
Believe it or not, liam can fix
a toilet pretty well."
so?
"rather than sitting around on
the bench collecting splinters,
He ended up in a drama class
and never looked back."
Verbatim quotes
from a studio bio.
What's the real story,
andy?
Don't know.
Liam doesn't like to talk
about his past.
Who would know?
[ sighs ] look...
I can't help you.
Even if i could,
i wouldn't,
Because then i'd be history
like the rest of liam's posse.
I'm his only friend.
[ dog barking ]
[ knock on door ]
Door's open.
Norm, of course.
I understand.
But...
Let's be clear.
If you don't have
that check on my desk,
I'm gonna come over,
And i'm gonna burn
your building down.
Love you.
Huh. huh.
I think i have
something for you.
Actually, i'm here
to talk about liam.
Oh, stop right there.
What the hell
is wrong with you people?
I already told the press
That i don't give interviews
about my former clients.
I'm dr. jack gallagher.
i'm his psychiatrist.
He's in trouble, maggie.
I need information,
Anything you can tell me
about his past.
[ sighs ] i had a feeling
that someone like you
Would show up
at my door one day.
Have a seat.
[ crickets chirping ]
[ chuckles ]
I just had a really
interesting phone call.
Nice for you.
yeah, it was
from a daily news reporter.
She was looking for confirmation
for an anonymous tip
That she'd received
from in the hospital.
I've said it before --
Security here
is practically nonexistent.
The place is a sieve.
yeah.
What sort of tip?
Well, that liam mcbride
Wasn't staying on
to continue his research.
In fact, he'd had
a huge breakdown
As a result
of his treatment here.
Whoops.
yeah.
What was
your response?
No comment.
They're going
with the story?
Not without
confirmation.
What surprises me,
particularly seeing
As that you were way out
in front of the press
On this matter,
Is that
they didn't call you.
that is surprising.
Perhaps they have yet
to get to me.
Of course, my response
would be the same as yours.
Do you really think this is the
way you'll get rid of jack --
With petty sniping
and subterfuge,
And in the process, defaming
the good name of this hospital?
Never crossed my mind.
Though as long as we're
soliciting for confessions,
You might as well admit,
at least to yourself,
That you lie in bed
at night
Wishing that gallagher
were far, faaway,
Clearing the path for you
to become director.
What i think about
when i'm lying in bed at night
Is none of your business.
Perhaps not.
Though i do find the topic
fascinating.
[ electricity zaps ]
Ohh!
God!
What the hell?!
not again.
Oh, aren't you
the boy scout.
[ chuckles ]
"be prepared."
Thank you.
Can someone please
check the generator?
[ doorknob rattles ]
Ohh!
Oh!
[ grunting ]
N-no!
[ ding! ]
[ birds chirping ]
Veronica:
he was trying to inject
himself with testosterone?
Why on earth...
Because
he was hing trouble
Living up to his image
as the sexiest man alive.
Where did he get it?
The ever-resourceful andy,
Who forgot to supply
a syringe.
[ chuckles ]
so it was drugs,
st not the kind we thought.
At least now we know
the problem.
No, we don't.
I agree.
Testosterone
over-supplementation
May cause anything
from increased sex drive
To shrinking testicles
and mood swings,
But it doesn't present
As a narcissistic
personality disorder.
If this should leak
to the press,
His career is over.
Discharge him.
Not yet.
i think he is addicted.
His drug of choice is himself --
the image of liam mcbride.
Not his real name,
by the way.
I think he's addicted
to being the person
That everybody sees him as --
handsome, witty, charming.
Sex symbol.
most importantly.
Testosterone was his way
of self-medicating.
Uh-huh.
so?
So i have to find a way...
To get him to open up.
[ knock on door ]
Hey, hey.
[ door closes ]
I assume you're not here
for my autograph.
[ laughs ]
I was, uh, hoping
to try something,
With your permission.
What?
Hypnosis.
I've seen those
in old movies,
But i didn't know
they were still used.
Oh, yeah.
yeah, they work.
I thought hypnosis
was pretty much discredited,
Like vegas voodoo.
What's that?
This?
It's, uh, de-inhibitor
solution --
Spy stuff.
ah, i don't know.
T dangerous.
Liam, you know
you can leave here tomorrow
With those demons
that keep you up at night.
Or you can leave knowing
you tried to face those demons
And, uh, hopefully
get on with your life.
Okay, liam,
i want you to clear your mind
Of all your thoughts.
Just relax.
Now look directly
into the wheel.
Take a breath,
feel the beat of your heart.
Slow it down, down, down.
Let it go.
Now, let's go back.
Let's go back to when you first
arrived in los angeles.
How old are you?
14.
Are you by yourself?
Yeah.
Why did you leave home?
Because my mom left the house
one night with her boyfriend
And didn't come back.
And where
was your father?
I never knew my father.
All right, liam.
How are you supporting
yourself?
There's this guy named rob.
He's got a place,
and a lot of guys stay there.
Um, i'm partying a lot.
There's really good dope
and booze.
There's pretty girls.
I'm running errands
for rob sometimes.
What kind of errands?
It's all right, liam.
We'll go back to that.
Now, you've been in los angeles
for six months.
How are you doing?
I'm broke.
i have nothing to eat.
I stole from a friend.
Rob is gonna kick me out
unless...
I don't want to be
on the street alone.
What is rob
making you do?
Rob says i can make money --
$100 or more a night...
...'cause i'm a pretty boy.
He knows older women that like
to have sex with pretty boys.
I don't want to do it,
but i go with him one night.
But it isn't women.
It's men.
[ echoing ]
liam? liam?
Liam?
What happens then?
I told him i wouldn't,
but i'm just so strung out.
And he offers me $50.
I told him $100.
He pays me.
And i do it.
Rob says it gets easier
after the first time.
But it never did.
Liam...
When i count to five...
And click my fingers..
You will be completely
and totally...awake.
One, two, three,
four, five.
[ fingers snap ]
[ sobs ]
It's all right.
It's out there now.
[ sniffles ]
We can handle it.
Mm.
Well, you know,
at least you're dating again.
Yeah.
but it's just...
I don't know.
Isn't it weird, after being
married for so long,
To have to go shopping
for condoms?
I know.
tell me about it.
It's embarrassing.
Why are you shopping
for condoms?
'cause i'm having
an affair.
What?
Someone from work.
Who?!
Rylan -- dr. rylan moore.
Isn't he like 18?
Nora.
Why?
Are things
with denny so bad?
No.
It's just that --
It's just that
when we met, we --
I was a 20-year-old,
d i just fell for...
A really cute musician
with zero ambition.
And guess what --
surprise, surprise --
We just grew apart.
Oh.
I'm glad you told me.
Yeah.
I'm glad i told you, too.
I-i don't like
holding things from you.
What?
what? nothing.
Well, there's something
i haven't told you.
I met this guy,
And we had this really
beautiful weekend...
...at a ski resort
in vermont.
Ah, i knew it.
i knew it.
There was something more
to that trip.
Us sleeping together
has nothing to do
with why i hired jack.
I mean, actually,
i almost didn't hire him
because of that.
You still attracted to him?
[ laughs ]
Yes.
But nothing's gonna happen.
You're so full of crap.
You hire a guy
you slept with,
You're still attracted
to him,
And you actually think
you can sit there
And decide
that it's not gonna happen?
You marry somebody
that you can dominate,
And then you're having an affair
on him with a younger guy?
And for you.
Why, thank you.
And you.
Mmm.
enjoy.
I feel much better now.
Me too.
[ camera shutters clicking ]
Guess this is the part
Wheri'm supposed to thank you
for saving my psyche, huh?
A little out of character,
though,
'cause, as you know,
it's all about me.
It's not about one of us.
it's about you, okay?
You have
some serious work ahead.
Yeah, i know.
I'm ready.
[ elevator bell dings ]
[ camera shutters clicking ]
[ indistinct shouting ]
What up, guys?
Liam, what was it like
in there?
It was quite humbling.
Stay back.
there are a lot
of very sick people here,
But there are also
dedicated professionals
Trying very hard
to help them.
He's good?
better than good.
I called an old friend of mine
from med school,
Specializes
in personality disorders.
Liam will start therapy
straightaway.
oh.
Do you believe your research
will make for a better film?
Yeah, bet on it.
Pretty smooth.
Eh, he's an actor.
Hypnosis, huh?
Any other tricks
you got up your sleeve?
Unfortunately,
i don't even have that one.
What do you mean?
I faked it.
A little de-inhibitor solution
also helped.
There's no such thing.
Yeah, well,
he didn't know that.
Saline?
Yeah.
All he really needed
was an excuse to let go.
Oh.
Well, you really missed
your calling in life.
An actor?
No way!
[ laughs ]
What i really want to do
is direct.
www.tvsubtitles.net