9 holes friday,
full 18 on saturday,
Unless we're too wasted
after friday night's debauch.
How's the course?
Five star all the way.
Green's as smooth
as a maiden's thighs.
And hopefully
as reachable.
[ Both laugh ]
You're bad.
You bringing the wife?
I thought the idea
was to relax.
Oh. Just so you know,
she's welcome.
Dad and i
consider you and yours
To be part
of the highgard family.
We talking board seat?
Could be.
Hmm.
[ Both laugh ]
[ Beep ]
I will be at the desk.
Hello.
Hi.
Woman on p.A.: Dr. Ryan
to the psychiatric ward.
Dr. Ryan
Admissions, please call
nurse's station two, south.
Dear? Hon?
Hello?
Hi. I need you to print up some
patient data for me a.S.A.P.
Mr. Highgard,
You know that patient files
are access restricted.
Well, i won't tell
if you won't.
I won't have to.
Fine.
I'll put carl on it.
I don't believe we've met.
Jack gallagher.
There he is,
the new man in charge!
Tom highgard,
highgard pharmaceuticals.
Doesn't ring a bell.
We do a ton of business
with you people.
The somnilex drugs?
Uh-Huh.
Drawing a blank.
Our signature
sleep-Disorder drug, somnilex.
[ Laughs ]
Frankly, doc, i'm surprised
you're not more up to speed.
They must be keeping you pretty
busy with the day-To-Day stuff.
[ Laughing ]
oh.
Pushing that pencil.
Sure.
[ Beep ]
No problem!
Carl belle's been
our point person for years.
Gallagher:
oh, good man.
Oh, the best.
Mm-Hmm.
Say, we-- We're having
this little corporate getaway
In laguna next week,
and i can, uh...
I can try to squeeze you in.
You know, meet the guys.
Maybe [chuckles]
break a few commandments, huh?
[ Laughs ]
sounds good.
Great. Great.
Say, tom,
Has carl mentioned our new
aggression-Therapy technique?
No.
Cutting edge.
You must check it out.
Oh. Well,
do i get a hint, or...
Well,
it's confrontational,
Fast-Acting,
a real problem solver.
So?
So...
[ Grunts ]
[ Sighs ]
You guys
seen tom highgard?
You just missed him.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Ding! ]
The most disgraceful,
Unprofessional conduct
that i've ever heard of.
How's highgard?
Furious.
With good reason.
Gallagher should be terminated
immediately.
Short of that.
Reprimanded and put on notice
by the board,
Forced to apologize
to tom highgard on his knees.
Short of that.
Gallagher may not appreciate
the financial gold mine
That highgard and the other
drug companies represent
By running clinical trials
at this hospital,
But i know that you do.
Of course i do,
Not to mention the prestige
and the p.R.
The only reason highgard
isn't talking to his
attorneys right now
Is my assurance
that we would make this right.
Dr. Gallagher
will offer a written apology,
Including unequivocal support
for the ongoing relationship
Between highgard pharmaceuticals
and wharton memorial.
What about this?
I haven't seen that.
Well, it's gallagh's
new policy,
Barring drug company and other
sales reps from patient wards
Without permission
from the director in advance.
I'll get back to you
on that.
Gallagher just got here, and
he's already a runaway train.
You're only delaying
the inevitable.
Aren't we all?
Dr. Stone,
please respond to your page.
[ Telephone rings ]
Darren knuth.
Age 23, no history of treatment
for mental illness.
There is, however,
a history of violent acts
Beginning
in his early teens --
Two convictions,
one as a juvenile.
Police brought him in last night
on a 72-Hour hold.
Veronica:
under what charges?
Assault and battery.
Beat the crap out of two
high-School football players.
What set him off?
They were leaning
against his car.
Why is he here
and not in jail?
Well, after the incident,
He drove his car
into a brick wall...
Four times.
When the police got there,
He was still sitting in it,
sobbing.
You did the intake?
He has issues
with his father --
Tremendous amount of anger,
also abject fear.
I suspect a lifetime
of physical abuse,
So i have a call scheduled
with his father later.
Medication?
Sertraline.
I'd like to sit in
on the patient follow-Up.
Of course.
Gideon graham.
Tms scheduled for today.
His daughter will be here
observing the procedure.
Fashion model.
Transcranial
magnetic stimulation?
Yeah. I hope to god
the damn thing works.
I had to promise the guy
at county my firstborn child
To get him
to lend it to us.
It works. I took it
for a test run last night.
What?
You tried tms on yourself?
Tapping sensation
at the contact points
Is a little bit irritating.
Get past that,
and there's a nice little buzz.
Okay, obviously, i need to
restate the hospital policy
On self-Experimentation.
How crazy are you?
Question is, will tms
have any affect on gideon?
Well, nothing else
we've done has.
Well, i hope we're not ready
to throw in the towel.
We owe him better.
He's an icon --
National treasure.
Are you suggesting,
dr. Gallagher,
That your personal fascination
with gideon
Should influence the amount of
effort we extend on his behalf?
I'm suggesting
that we failed him.
We need the bed, jack.
If it doesn't work today,
we're done.
It looks
like an execution.
Well, the actual amount
of current generated is...
Is about the same
as an mri.
I hope you people know
what you're doing.
[ Monitor beeping ]
Will it hurt?
Some patients experience an
uncomfortable tapping sensation
At the point
where the current's applied.
It's not that bad.
You're gideon's daughter.
Jack gallagher.
Naobi.
Veronica:
we're ready in here.
The generator will produce
short magnetic pulses
Directed towards certain areas
in gideon's brain.
We'll measure and monitor
any resulting activity,
Although there may be
some visible contractions
To muscles
of the scalp and jaw.
Okay?
Breathe.
[ Monitor beeping ]
Come on, gideon.
This is your wake-Up call.
[ Thunder crashes ]
Okay, we're increasing
the intensity.
Is that safe?
They'll keep it
within the guidelines.
[ Grunts ]
What's that?
Involuntary spasm.
[ Thunder crashes ]
Stable.
Hold the coil on
the contact point for longer.
Aah!
Jack.
[ Thunder crashes ]
[ Grunting ]
Okay.
Syringe, now!
It's okay.
It's okay, dr. Graham.
[ Monitor beeping ]
Don't worry.
They've got it under control.
What the hell happened?
He responded...
More than he has
to any stimulus
Or any treatment
since the accident.
It's progress.
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
Pre-Columbian?
Lucky guess.
Anthropology major
at oxford.
And ended up
a real-Life supermodel.
I love my father.
I just want
what's best for him.
I've been doing
some research.
What subject?
Keraunopathy --
The pathology of lightning.
It's fascinating.
This research,
pure coincidence?
I'm a fan, big-Time.
I've read and reread every page
he's ever published.
Are you going to cut
gideon loose?
Is that what you want?
I want you
to keep trying,
Unless you're ready to tell me
right now
That it's never
gonna happen.
How much do you know
about catatonia?
Not enough.
The lightning strike
caused organ failure,
Burns,
neurological trauma,
And your father's body
and mind shut down,
Passed in to a coma.
As his body recovered,
He went from coma
into his present state.
Coma's
a physical condition.
Catatonia
is a neuropsychiatric one.
So you're saying he went from
being damaged to being insane?
I ha-- I hate that word.
I have no idea what it means.
Think of it this way --
Um, your father's
lost inside himself.
Why?
At a guess,
overwhelming grief.
My mother's death.
And here's where your father's
intellect and imagination
Might actually
impede recovery.
He has the capacity to --
To build an incredibly rich,
airtight internal environment
And use that as a wall
against reality.
I would rather
see gideon dead
Than see him as a houseplant
in some institution.
Work with him.
Naobi,
we're a way station.
People don't stay here
indefinitely.
My father's exceptional.
I agree.
So make an exception.
Hey, boss.
Jack:
how's the water?
Jump in.
"Do we seek the womb
in aquatic environments,
Or is it simply the nearest
we humans come to flying?"
That's nice.
Gideon wrote it.
Really?
You wrote that, mr. "G"?
Malcolm, take a breather.
You're a real trip, doc.
Jack:
nice-Looking scar.
Hard to come by, too.
Consider the odds --
1 in 700,000
Of being hit by lightning
in any given year.
Malcolm:
that was weird.
Never happens with you.
Him tensing up like that?
Uh-Huh.
No.
Gideon loves the water.
You want to see something
even weirder?
Always.
All right, let's try
and get some shoes on you.
All right,
let's try the other one.
Happens every time.
All right, mr. "G,"
no shoes for you today.
Interesting.
[ Ding! ]
[ Mid-Tempo piano music plays ]
[ Sniffs ]
This would all be
much simpler
If you'd just tell me
what you're thinking.
[ Telephone rings ]
Been working
on a gideon theory.
Good.
Nora just put his release
paperwork on my desk.
We've been
surrounding gideon
With the fabric
of his own life --
Visitors, favorite music,
keepsakes --
Trying to reconnect him
to the world.
No response.
Drug therapy, same.
Electroshock, same.
We tried tms -- The least
invasive therapy of all.
And the guy freaks.
Why?
You're the man
with the theory.
Do you know
what a flashover is?
Can you get arrested
for it?
In a strike,
lightning impacts the body
At specific entry
and exit points.
In between, the current
flashes over the entire surface
Of the body
causing lichtenberg figures.
The burn patterns
on gideon.
Mm-Hmm.
It's like a wave.
A very fast wave.
Milliseconds.
Like an electromagnetic pulse.
Are you saying
that the tms
Made gideon relive
the lightning strike?
Why didn't the same thing happen
with the e.C.T.?
We administer electroshock
under anesthesia.
Tms is come as you are.
Sounds thin, jack.
Told you,
i'm working on it.
Send gideon's paperwork
over to me.
It can sit on my desk
for a while.
You seem tense today,
darren.
My new meds are crap!
And the relaxation exercises
we worked on?
They make me want to puke!
When we entered your room
just now,
What was the first thing
you thought of?
Bitch-Slapping
your ugly face!
[ Breathing heavily ]
Careful.
What are you
gonna do about it?
It's what i hope
to avoid doing.
What's that?
Talking to your father.
No.
Once was enough.
Instead,
we'll vary your medication
And go back over
those exercises.
Okay?
Okay.
[ Door closes ]
[ Clears throat ]
Sign this.
Am i buying something?
Your apology
to tom highgard.
Oh. I assume
i was suitably contrite?
Profoundly remorseful.
Pressures of the job?
Having had
a really bad day.
Et cetera, et cetera?
Which leaves us
with the unfinished business
Of your apology to me.
You don't make policy.
I make policy.
This hospital needs to remain
financially viable
To prosper and grow.
I fight those battles
so you don't have to.
Nora, these guys peddle drugs.
That's all they do.
They don't give a damn
about patient welfare.
They'd be happy to reduce
our role in treatment
To handing out dime bags
on the ward.
Who makes policy here?
You do.
Write a memo.
Cite specific examples,
things you've observed.
I'll consider it.
Did you know that lightning
is 16 times hotter
Than the surface
of the sun?
Kiss my ass.
I fly out to new york
next week.
I'll be there
for about 10 days.
Will you miss me, daddy?
[ Footsteps approaching ]
Look who's here.
Gideon,
may i borrow your daughter
For a couple of minutes?
Malcolm
will keep you company.
Thank you.
Mom and dad
were hiking in the sierras.
A storm came in.
All the other people,
they went for shelter,
But dad refused.
Dad took mom to the edge
of the cliff to watch the storm.
Lightning hit.
They both got cpr,
but only dad lived.
Do you blame gideon
for your mother's death?
He knew she was afraid
of lightning.
What was gideon working on
before the accident?
A new book --
"Book of judges."
About what?
Oh, i stopped reading
his material a long time ago,
But i can get you
the manuscript.
Gideon ever have a problem
with footwear?
[ Grunting ]
[ Chuckles ]
What if we're wrong?
Do you ever start a conversation
at the beginning?
What if gideon's conscious?
You mean faking?
Hiding.
It would explain
his lack of progress.
Well, so would
severe brain trauma.
What do you say
we test it out?
How?
[ Door closes ]
dr. Belle.
[ Zipper unzips ]
The patient today,
you believed every word he said.
I had no reason
to doubt him.
Patients lie.
My sense is he lied to you
at least once.
That's why you have to probe
deeper, be less accepting.
Find his sore spots.
Okay.
Also [clears throat]
the threat to call his father --
Heavy-Handed.
Could have transferred his fear
onto you and lashed out.
Heavy-Handed. Got it.
Arturo,
you're a fairly good doctor
Who might someday
become a very good doctor.
You're also arrogant.
Dr. Belle,
i'm sorry if --
Too late.
Did you know
[clears throat]
That as chairman
of the residency committee,
My vote secured
your position here?
I'm grateful.
You should be.
We both know part of
your transcript was falsified.
A small part.
It's still fraud.
More than enough to justify
rejecting your application.
Even so...
You voted to support
my residency.
[ Chuckles ]
Despite
his limited tenure here,
You've come to admire
jack gallagher, haven't you?
Dr. Gallagher is innovative,
dynamic, devoted to his work.
I admire him very much.
Good, because i think
that you and dr. Gallagher
Should become friends.
He'd probably like a friend.
Seek him out,
stand in his shadow,
Earn his confidence...
...and report what you learn
back to me.
You want me to spy?
Call it
returning a favor.
Obviously,
you have a choice to make.
[ Lock clicks ]
[ Gasps ]
Don't ask.
[ Elevator bell dings ]
I'm just waiting
for someone.
Lucky guy.
[ Chuckles ]
This is grand theft.
No, it's not.
I signed for everything.
Under what name?
Dr. Carl belle.
[ Laughs ]
nice touch.
Well, tom highgard
would be pleased.
Somnilex does put people
to sleep.
Highgard's been testing
sleep patterns,
So we're gonna see just
how asleep gideon really is.
71 minutes.
Normal r.E.M.
And non-R.E.M. Sleep patterns --
Completely normal.
Jack, he's --
Yeah. The lights are on,
and gideon's home.
[ Ding! ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Morning.
Hey.
Nice bike.
Yeah. It's good exercise.
No carbon footprint.
I know. I've been thinking about
getting one myself.
You know what to look for?
[ Cellphone rings ]
no. Not really.
Becky? Hey.
How are you doing today?
Becky,
you know, if you --
If you ever want to have lunch
with your big brother,
You know
i'm always available.
You remember where --
Wharton memorial.
Why don't you just jump
in a cab,
And i'll -- I'll pay for it
when you get here?
Becky?
[ Click ]
Damn it.
Sister live here?
Uh...why don't you stop
by the office,
And i'll point you in the right
direction on that bike?
I'd really appreciate that.
Woman on p.A.: Wheelchair
to admissions, main lobby.
Wheelchair to admissions,
main lobby.
Thank you.
Walk with me.
Sure.
Don't worry about highgard.
I smoothed things over with him.
Does that mean we're still on
for laguna?
[ Scoffs ]
I don't think
it's your scene.
No?
No, but very much mine.
I can see that.
Thing is...
I'll do more long-Term good
for this hospital in one weekend
Than you'll accomplish
in months.
On the, uh...course?
It's where the money flows,
doctor.
[ Beep ]
Did you sleep?
I went for a bike ride.
You?
An hour's nap, hot shower,
bowl of cereal.
Real exciting life.
I'm surprised you're not in
a better mood.
What have we really
accomplished?
Well, we have a theory,
And with the sleep data, we have
support for that theory.
At least we can make a case
for keeping him here longer.
You said it yourself --
We've already tried everything.
Just keeping him here
isn't enough.
Now who's ready
to throw in the towel?
There's a next step.
I just have to figure out
what it is.
Mm-Hmm.
Uh-Huh.
Mr. Breyer.
Jack gallagher.
Thanks so much for meeting me.
Well, it's a pleasure.
You've been gideon's editor
for quite some time.
27 years.
Wow.
That's remarkable.
It's nice work.
I wouldn't change one day.
Can you tell me
who "v" is?
Where did you hear
that name?
The book is dedicated
to him...
Her...it.
Well, you're holding
his best work, you know?
There's no question.
And "v"?
No. Thank you.
I begged him not to.
He was adamant.
I told him the dedication
would lead to nothing good.
Vivian.
How long
had it been going on?
Not that long, really --
Less than a year.
Nor was vivian the first.
What made her
so different?
In a way,
the dedication itself.
I mean, sansa knew, of course.
Sansa always new.
But the dedication
made the truth public
And, therefore,
intolerable.
Was he deliberately
trying to sabotage his marriage?
No. No. Without sansa,
he was nothing. He knew that.
Then why?
Why? Ask him. I did.
He laughed.
Pure ego, perhaps.
Maybe she knows.
Um, i'm gonna go upstairs
in a minute.
It's been, um, difficult
to see him like this.
Do you think my visits
do any good at all?
Oh, yeah.
I think so.
Conventional wisdom
says so, anyway.
You know what gideon
called conventional wisdom?
Rank stupidity.
Not an easy man
to be friends with.
I miss him.
Where can i find
this vivian?
Someone finally asked
the right question.
If you knew he was here,
why didn't you come before?
I never had
more than half of gideon.
And, by the end,
almost nothing.
I'm not sure
i want to help.
Oh, come on.
Tell me about the book.
Our relationship brought
something into gideon's life
He never
experienced before -- Guilt.
I suppose i was flattered.
When sansa found out
about the dedication,
She threatened to leave him,
and he broke it off immediately,
And, well, that was
less than flattering.
So you're saying that,
through the book,
Gideon was finding a way
of judging himself.
In his mind,
no one else had the right.
Where is gideon's mind,
by the way?
I was hoping
you'd tell me.
Wherever he is,
he is laughing at us.
Why do you think that?
I assume he escaped
the thing he feared most --
What we all fear
if we're sane...
The awareness,
the constant reminder that...
Life is not forever.
A world without death,
without inevitability.
Gideon
never believed in gods,
But i think he would have liked
to have been one.
He seems old.
I never thought about gideon
as being old before this moment.
Has naobi
been to see him?
Naobi's convinced that gideon
ignored the storm's danger
And deliberately led sansa
to the edge of the cliff.
Well,
it's very likely.
For what possible purpose?
Well...he was intolerant
of personal weakness
In himself
as well as in others.
I wish he could see
where it's gotten him.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Is this a social call?
What happens when you get struck
by lightning?
Your hair frizzes.
You literally get blown out
of your shoes.
Gideon's shoe thing?
Uh-Huh. I think he's cognitive
and functioning.
I want to try something --
Two things, actually.
Convince me.
Gideon,
in the old testament,
Appears in the book
of judges,
And that's also the title
of our gideon's latest work.
It's about choices,
responsibility,
And controlling
your own fate.
So?
I think i'm finally getting
into his head.
I think he's exactly
where he wants to be.
At wharton?
Somewhere else.
I'm beginning
to know how he feels.
Can we cut to the chase?
Gideon's judging that world
that took his wife from him,
And he's judging
his role in her death.
The things that you wanted?
Tms again.
Is another seizure
a possibility?
Yes.
Is fatality even remotely
a possibility?
Yes.
What was
the second thing?
Okay.
What are we doing?
We've been making it
too easy for him,
Filling his world full
of memories, associations,
Sounds, smells,
things and people he loves.
Why should you have it
so good?
Huh?
Malcolm:
he lost nearly everything.
Seems to me he deserves
some of his stuff around
To make him happy.
Guys,
we've been enablers.
You want to see gideon
have a chance at recovery,
Help me cut him off.
[ Thunder crashes ]
Help me give him a reason
not to stay where he is.
Emotional withdrawal.
Cold turkey.
Sorry, pal. Strip him.
[ Ding! ]
Legally,
in case anything goes wrong.
It's the only way
i could make it happen.
Seizures, possible brain injury,
possible death?
Unlikely, but possible.
And if i don't sign?
Then we're back
where we were.
You taking all of his pictures
and d d uff off the walls,
Leaving him in his room,
and not letting me visit him
Or read to him
or play music to him?
It's had some effect.
We've seen slightly
increased levels of rigidity
And physical movement.
Over time?
No way to predict.
You know that wall that gideon
was building against reality?
It's getting higher.
It's getting stronger every day.
What if it's
a better place?
I'm not sure.
[ Sighs ]
What's it like where you are,
gideon?
I'll bet magnificent.
Sansa's there, isn't she?
At your side,
where she belongs.
Except sansa's gone.
Gone. Do you remember?
You killed her.
You knew she was afraid
of lightning.
You knew the danger,
but you thought --
You thought, "here's an
opportunity to improve my wife,
To help her face her fears!"
Who are you to judge?!
You can't control everything,
gideon.
You're just one man.
Finite...
Vulnerable...
And, in the end,
i think a coward.
The pain and the guilt of
an unjust world -- That, i get.
What i don't get...
Is you abandoning
your daughter.
Sansa may be alive
in your world,
But she's an illusion.
Naobi is here.
[ Chuckles ]
she's real.
I bet where you are it's safe.
You're the man.
You're in charge.
You push the buttons.
You judge.
You, and you alone,
wield the lightning, huh?
Well, i'm here to tell you
that you're wrong!
Naobi.
Naobi: daddy.
What sentence is passed,
gideon?
He's seizing!
Exiled for life?
Your verdict was wrong.
No!
Who are you to judge?!
Where's your lightning now?
Huh?
It's a history of
institutionalization and arrests
Dating back
to her 20th birthday.
Paranoid schizophrenia.
The arrests
were drug-Related.
Becky's short
for rebecca?
Yeah.
Gallagher's
fraternal twin.
Yeah.
Anything else?
No.
[ Chuckles ]
Worthless information,
but "c" for effort.
Next time, do better.
That door leads
to the outer hallway.
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
Carl: gallagher,
you're your own worst enemy.
Please don't make this
too easy for me.
Woman on p.A.:
X-Ray tech to room six.
Thank you.
Thank you both.
There's a lot
of work ahead.
I'm gonna take him back
to new york with me,
Continue his treatment there.
Maybe he'll travel again
one day,
Write another book.
Maybe it can help.
Maybe.
[ Grunts ]
[ Doorbell buzzing ]
I thought you'd left.
I have
some unfinished business.
[ Ding! ]
www.tvsubtitles.net