Jack: it's been a while
since i've done this.
I had a few sessions in vermont
when things got tough.
Now, um...
Well, thank you for seeing me.
Man: why do you think
you need therapy?
Why does anyone?
A million different reasons.
you know that.
Pick one.
I have a decision
to make.
I need
to talk it through.
What decision?
Whether or not
to quit my job.
Man #2: we're gonna be back
in an hour!
Woman:
all right, then! see you!
I can't do it, dr. skoff!
The cleanup begins
at 6:00 a.m., you see.
By the time they get
her admitted, i'd have
Doctor?
it's critical only.
Well, it's just
for 24 hours.
No.
The day
after tomorrow's fine.
Why don't you try county
for tonight?
They -- they've been
lending a hand.
Okay.
Uh, carl, why is
mr. thompson restrained?
Because he refused
to leave
Without orders
from the commander in chief.
Obama?
Roosevelt, theodore.
[ chuckles ]
What's going on?
Oh, we have to shut down
the entire psych ward
For 24 hours,
as of tonight.
Word came down
this morning.
Where are you transferring
all the patients to?
Just to county.
hey, how was palm springs?
Warm.
shut down? why?
Well, there was a lawsuit filed
against the hospital.
A guy came in
for a knee reconstruction.
He just caught a bug.
It turned out
to be some kind
Of serious respiratory infection
that nearly killed him.
[ telephone ringing ]
Purely precautionary.
The workers arrive
tomorrow
To start disinfecting
the entire complex by sections.
Psych drew the short straw,
so they're up first.
Hey, that's a nice tan.
good.
Arturo:
so, let me understand.
When you say someone
might get hurt,
Are you referring
to a specific person
Or an action
on your part?
I don't know how
this works, so...
Look,
i'm running out of time.
So just take me in.
i need to be locked up.
Unfortunately,
mr. kahane,
We're not accepting any new
patients prior to the shutdown.
If you have your therapist
call me, i promise you --
Moonrise is less than two hours
from now!
Problem?
Can, uh -- can i at least talk
to someone?
Certainly.
Here at wharton memorial,
We don't simply
turn people away.
Why don't you two take
mr...kahane? ellis?
Yes. take mr. kahane
to my office,
And i'll join you
in a moment.
Right this way.
Where's gallagher?
Uh, personal business.
Well, why not?
I mean,
the man works like a slave.
He needs to learn to enjoy
his life, huh?
[ scoffs ]
you're in a rare good mood.
Caroline,
you made a commitment.
i know.
these areveryuncertain times.
[ knock on door ]
Well, uh, all right,
Would you consider
scaling back
To, uh, maybe half
your original pledge?
Caroline: sure, no problem.
i can do that.
Yeah, talk to george.
let me know as soon as you can.
Bye.
thanks.
[ clears throat ]
Out there?oing
Uh, oh, i think we'll clear
the ward in time.
Major donors?
major bailers
is more like it.
Between that
and the lending slowdown,
Our budget
is disappearing.
Well, how serious is it?
Well, if we don't get this
turned around,
We'll be facing...
drastic changes.
wait.
like my clinic?
Everything is
on the table.
Okay, what can i do?
Like i-i told jack,
if there's some way to cut back
Without eliminating
essential services...
Board meeting
is in 40 hours.
So, when and where did
the, uh, animal bite occur?
I told you --
it was a werewolf,
A real, live werewolf!
When and where?
What difference
does it make?!
Mr. kahane.
I was walking home
from -- from work.
I own a print shop.
It was 29 days ago,
just before the last full moon.
I was attacked.
immediately, i knew something
was -- was really wrong.
It's not unusual for dog --
animal bites
To be associated with pain
or swelling due to infection.
I'm sure the doctors at the
clinic explained that to you.
Explain the howling,
hmm?
the -- the scratching
at the bedpost, and my breath.
The "breath from hell."
Literally.
And that was just
during the first full moon,
Before the transformation
had time to take full effect.
[ door opens ]
carl: mr. kahane.
We've seen you
at this hospital before,
Though it's been
some time, no?
You were diagnosed
With a generalized
anxiety disorder in your teens.
And you've been
in some form of therapy
And taking medication
ever since?
This isn't that.
This is the beast
planted inside me.
What if i lose control
And i harm
innocent human beings?
I could forfeit my soul.
We can inoculate
against that.
We can?
I'm gonna write you
a prescription.
You have this filled
as soon as you leave here.
This will counteract
any transformation.
No one will be harmed.
You come back
the day after tomorrow,
Or, as dr. suarez
suggested,
You have your regular therapist
give us a call.
You sure this will work?
I'm a doctor.
[ breathes shakily ]
[ door opens ]
[ door closes ]
[ telephone ringing ]
woman over p.a. system:
lab tech to room 200, stat.
There are documented cases
of lycanthropy.
It's rare.
But extremely dangerous.
You know,
the myth's based on reality.
He can really
hurt someone.
You're forgetting about the
anti-man-to-wolf medication.
One hour to moonrise.
[ howls ]
itisa big deal.
All i ever wanted to be
was a doctor.
Man: and now?
I'm not so sure.
Let's say you've quit
your job,
You're no longer a doc.
First day of the rest
of your life --
What do you do now?
I don't know.
Make it up as i go along,
like i always do.
and that's worked out
so well.
This is the way
it's gonna be?
I pour my heart out,
And all i get from you
is sarcasm?
i'm not here to give you
what you want.
i'm here to give you
what you need.
And time is running out
for you, jack.
[ sighs ]
[ rhythmic knock on door ]
[ chuckling ]
Nora: tom.
[ door closes ]
what brings you here?
I heard you might need
a little help.
Help with what?
Nora, i'm a salesman.
I talk to people all day,
every day.
I know what it's like
out there.
The money's panicking.
andyou?
i have a proposition.
I'm breathless
with anticipation.
[ chuckles ]
I have it
on good authority
That you will fall
somewhere
Between $4
and $4.5 million short
Of your projected contributions
to keep this place afloat.
Your good authority
wouldn't happen to be
Carl and i talk.
it's no secret.
We both care deeply
about this institution.
Oh, well,
that goes without saying.
Here's the deal --
Hygard pharmaceuticals
will make up any shortfall
In your fund-raising,
Up to 100% of your original
projection to the board,
plusa letter
of commitment
To conduct a new series
of clinical trials
Of hygard products
here at wharton.
Speaking of the board,
We have our meeting
to discuss the budget
The day after tomorrow.
Is that a coincidence?
a timely coincidence.
Mm-hmm.
Think about it --
no cutbacks, no layoffs,
No disruption of service
to the community.
We can even talk
about the new children's ward
You want so much.
Your generosity
is astounding.
What could we possibly do
to repay you?
Oh, just one
little thing.
Ask.
Fire jack gallagher.
[ animal howling ]
[ howling continues ]
[ ding! ]
I'm not depressed.
Man: really?
Decreased appetite,
decreased sleep,
Chronic fatigue,
reduced concentration,
Feelings of hopelessness,
disorientation, loss.
Diagnosis, doctor?
I'm going through a rough patch
right now.
Doesn't mean
i'm clinically depressed.
could never happen
toyou.
We're not immune.
no one is.
Depressing, isn't it?
[ man speaking indistinctly ]
You know i can't discuss
everything the board talks about
Behind closed doors.
Georgia, how long have we been fighting
this fight together?
i need to know
where i stand.
You still have friends
in the room, including me.
Friends?
No matter what?
No, of course not,
Especially where economics
are concerned.
How determined are you
to keep your guy on?
Since jack gallagher
got here,
Our department has never been
in better shape.
He's the key
to our future.
Hmm. so, it's your intention
to just walk in there
And tell the board
that you plan to retain
The present
management structure,
To hell
with hygard's offer.
How many solid votes
you think i'll have?
5 of 11?
Um, hanson, levin,
murphy, singer --
We've got those.
Griffin and moore
undecided.
You know, if we can turn
just one of those,
You could win.
How?
Find the money
someplace else.
Gallagher may be the key,
but without adequate funding,
your psychiatric hospital
may not have a future.
Are you saying the board
would consider coming in
And shutting us
down entirely?
[ sighs lightly ]
Hey, hey,
what's in the news today?
Well, i haven't had a chance
to read it yet,
But with this economy,
it can't be good.
How's becky?
ask her doctors.
that's all i get to do.
Sorry.
it's a sore subject.
[ elevator dings ]
we're seeing you at your house
Yeah.
okay.
Hi, nora.
Hey.
hi.
We will find some budget cuts
for you by this evening.
I promise.
How you doing?
Okay.
Did you find
a therapist?
I think
i found someone i like.
Man: how much of this
is really about becky?
[ sighs ]
All of it.
I miss her.
[ breathes deeply ]
I think about her
constantly.
Uh...i'm distracted
When i should be concentrating
on helping people.
Becky's an excuse,
always has been.
Go to hell.
Oh, that's right.
get angry. let it out.
Take it out on me.
An excuse for what?
For always needing
to run away.
I just spoke with one
of the undecideds.
Everything is going our way.
Yes, positive.
we have a clear majority.
Thank you.
glad to hear of it.
Now, concerning the arrangement
we spoke about earlier --
Taken care of.
Should be a lucrative deal
all around.
We'll see you
tomorrow morning.
[ elevator dings ]
Arturo, qu pasa?
Nada mucho, dr. belle.
You haven't spoken
much lately.
Not much to report.
Ah. no worries.
Where jack gallagher
has dinner and who with
Are the last things
on my mind.
Lighten up.
[ elevator dings ]
woman over p.a. system:
pain management,
please call extension 320.
Carl's in a weird mood today,
almost friendly.
I don't get it.
Ooh. i'm starving.
Stop. those are for the meeting
at jack's.
I guess congratulations
are in order.
They offered you the residency
in cardiology, didn't they?
You gonna take it?
I'm not sure yet.
You know,
in my opinion --
[ breathes deeply ]
Jack: cup of tea,
not coffee, right?
Thank you.
I like your place.
it's great.
[ doorbell buzzes ]
I got it.
Hey.
Chloe.
[ exhales deeply ]
Oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is your little home
away from home, huh?
I like it.
That's right.
you haven't seen it before.
Sit down.
have a cup of coffee.
All right, guys,
nora meets the suits tomorrow.
And we need to, uh,
save her some money
And still keep
the ward open.
When are we gonna
get out of here?
Why, carl?
do you have a tee time?
2:30.
[ doorbell buzzes ]
I'll get it.
Well, uh,
i have some proposals.
Unfortunately,
one involves the elimination
Of the resident day clinic.
Chloe: oh, no.
let's hope
it doesn't come tothat.
Mr. kahane.
What are you
doing here?
I went by the hospital.
Mr. kahane,
i don't know how you got here,
But this is completely
inappropriate.
Why don't you call
my office tomorrow?
We'll set something up.
[ gun cocks ]
get back.
Okay.
I know how to use this,
all right? get back!
[ door slams ]
I came by looking
for help yesterday,
And you kicked me
out the door.
Not this time.
The moonrise
is 7:38 tonight.
We're gonna stay here
together until then.
If anyone tries to leave,
I will shoot them!
okay.
Does rise...n
...god help you all.
Carl: mr. kahane --
Ellis -- please be sensible.
hand me the weapon.
[ women scream ]
[ ding! ]
You could have
killed me.
Shut up!
all of you, shut up!
People will be looking
for us.
[ telephone ringing ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ grunts ]
[ clatter, ringing stops ]
I want all your phones.
i needallof your phones.
put them in that bag.
Now! do it!
Put it back
on the couch.
We haven't been
introduced.
Who are you?
Jack gallagher.
i own the place.
Get you a beer?
coffee?
No.
You a patient
of dr. belle's?
[ grunts ]
Here, let me give you a hand
with that.
It's heavy.
No one would listen
to me.
They didn't believe me.
Arturo and i spoke to him
initially.
Dr. belle didn't believe
that he fell under
Which he didn't.
i gave him a prescription.
you gave him the equivalent
of two aspirins
And told him to call you
in the morning.
are you suggesting
this is my fault?
She's not just
suggesting.
You forget yourself,
doctor.
Jack:
why exactly did you --
Did you want to be admitted
last night?
Doesn't matter.
it's too late now.
Mr. kahane told us he was going
to turn into a werewolf
When the full moon rose
last night.
A werewolf?
So you believe you can turn
into a wild animal?
It's already happened.
are -- are you not listening?!
Yes, i am listening, ellis.
you have a gun in your hand.
Mr. kahane has a history
of generalized anxiety disorder
And has repeatedly taken
medication for it. yes?
Medication.
You thought
a couple of pills
Was gonna stop me
from transforming?
Or were you just
lying to me?
I was merely trying
to calm you down.
i am not insane!
Jack: ellis,
you said it was too late.
Too late for what?
What exactly happened?
Ellis: the moon was high
in the sky.
Hey, buddy?
I had just transformed.
You okay?
i smelled him.
You all right, man?
The hair on my arms and my body
was long and rough.
My teeth were pointed.
[ growls ]
[ man screaming ]
[ sighs heavily ]
So you attacked a man
last night
After you left
the hospital?
Yes.
And after that?
I don't remember.
I must have
transformed back.
[ sniffles ]
I went back
to the motel...
Stripped off my clothes,
Scrubbed myself clean.
There was so much blood.
Jack: well, what do you want
from us now?
I told you.
You're gonna see me transform
when the full moon rises.
And -- and after
the transformation?
Well, then you'll know
the truth --
That i'm not crazy.
I really am
this terrible thing.
You okay, ellis?
can i get you something?
No.
Veronica, how about you rustle
up a couple of sandwiches
And maybe a cup
of coffee?
I said "no."
Hey,
you mind if i sit down?
Not too close.
Wouldn't even
think of it.
Man: think about your other
so-called relationships.
What about them?
Every serious relationship
you've ever had,
You've sabotaged.
Why?
You know why.
i'm afraid of commitment.
Come on, jack.
There's much more to it
than that.
You guys, we can't just sit here
and do nothing.
Well,
what do you suggest?
Why don't you, uh, women --
i don't know --
Stage a distraction,
Some kind
of emotional breakdown
Or cry or something?
Look, once he's distracted,
arturo can jump him.
Why me?
Because you're younger
and you're faster.
and what willyou
be doing?
Coming up
with the plan.
Griff, have you spoken
to georgia yet?
Well, why is it moot?
Well -- well, she told me
that you were still undecided.
[ sighs ]
Griff, look, i'm gonna be
really honest with you.
you're my last chance.
ireallyneed your help.
You've always been there for us.
If it weren't for you,
We wouldn't even have
a day clinic.
[ dial tone ]
[ sighs ]
Jack:
we have four hours to talk him
So, we -- we're supposed
to just treat him
Like any other patient?
Stop talking about me!
You're a man with a gun
who thinks he's a werewolf.
We're psychiatrists.
Of course we're talking
about you.
Now, why don't you tell us
what happened?
I've already told them.
Well,
we need some evidence.
When the moon rises,
You'll have all the evidence
you're gonna need.
Arturo: mr. kahane,
It would help everybody
if they knew the full story.
Fine.
29 days ago,
i was attacked by a werewolf.
Arturo:
the clinic in pasadena
Erroneously treated him
for a dog bite.
Ellis, when you were a child,
did you own a dog?
We had a neighbor
who used to have a pit bull.
It would run up to the fence
and show its teeth.
Once in a while,
it would get out,
Run around the neighborhood.
I wouldn't know where it was.
It would scare the crap
out of me.
This clinic in pasadena --
did they give you a shot?
Yeah, a whole bunch of them.
So you were treated
for rabies.
Yeah.
But i-i knew
it wasn't gonna cure me.
What's gonna cure you?
nothing can cure me.
this is who i am now!
All right, ellis.
Do you have a family?
I had a life!
i own a business!
My family -- they --
I have a wife...
Two kids.
Nick --
he just turned 8.
Can throw a football
30 yards.
Danny --
He's 18 months old.
He's already talking.
He's so smart.
Do they --
do they know about...
I told sandra
what happened to me.
She held me,
and we cried together.
She's the one who told me
to go to the hospital.
Are you still living
at home?
I left two weeks ago.
I was afraid
i was gonna hurt them.
For your information...
...i transform body and soul.
It's not me.
I don't know
what i'm capable of.
[ crying ]
What?
Jack.
What's it say?
Let me see it.
let me see!
Take it.
take it.
He's dead.
I didn't dream it.
Dead.
Oh, my god, i really did it.
I killed last night.
[ gunshot ]
Oh!
[ ding! ]
I told you.
i told you what would happen.
This isn't who i am!
No, it isn't, ellis.
you're right.
I can't escape him.
How is he?
he's not good! he's --
Chloe:
he's going into shock.
he needs an e.r.now.
No.
no one's leaving!
Then make us understand why,
ellis.
Tell us everything we need
to know about last night.
Come on!
no. no, no, no.
You think
that i'm crazy,
That i imagined it,
but it was real.
I woke up
covered in blood!
What do you mean,
"woke up"?!
[ dog barking in distance ]
I must have passed out
when i turned back.
I don't know.
i don't remember.
Tell us
what you do remember.
I was tired, achy...
Dizzy -- what difference
does it make?!
I tore a man's
throat out!
Calm down.
sit down.
[ breathing heavily ]
he did not deserve
to die.
Probably had a family.
I don't even know.
Man:
you hate being alone.
I frickin' hate it.
So get off your ass
and find someone.
that's not the point.
what is the point?
I can't let myself
get involved,
Can't get married,
have a family.
Why not?
Say it.
Because something might happen
to me.
[ groans lightly ]
Jack.
[ breathing heavily ]
Dr. belle's
been blackmailing me.
The boy's delirious.
No, i just
don't care anymore.
I falsified
my transcripts
When i applied
for residency here.
Carl found out,
And he's been using it to get me
to spy on you ever since.
He wants jack out.
He's been putting
a list together
Of everything
you've done.
And i helped him.
I'm sorry, jack.
i'm so sorry.
I'm sorry you were put
in that position.
[ grunting lightly ]
This is unacceptable.
I don't need a lecture
from a rank amateur
Who almost single-handedly
brought down the hospital.
I mean, jack...
Your own sister didn't trust you
to treat her.
Maybe she had a point.
Man: what do you think
is gonna happen?
[ exhales ]
I can't talk about it.
You have to.
Same thing that happened
to becky.
Schizophrenia.
One day she's fine,
and the next she's --
She's counting imaginary cracks
in the ceiling.
Why her?
Why not me?
He's losing
consciousness.
We need an e.r. now!
No.
no, everyone stays.
you want him to die, too?!
you want to kill two people?!
No, but the wolf
is inside me.
I can't stop it
from coming out!
Pulse is weak and thready.
do something!
Oh, we can't.
this lunatic has got a gun.
If you had just listened
to me,
None of this
would have happened.
They wouldn't be here.
He wouldn't
have been shot!
Jack:
ellis! take it easy.
Take it easy.
i have a suggestion.
It might just help.
Bite me.
What?!
No. no, i-i can't.
You don't want to face
the moonrise alone.
That's why we're here.
you're all alone.
I don't want
to be alone now.
No. come on.
Two werewolves have got
to be better than one.
Wh-why would you do that
for me?
Fancy a change.
i'm dying to know what happens.
Bite it, right here,
hard.
Wait --
Go on.
Ohh.
[ both breathing heavily ]
Aah.
There you go.
[ crying ]
Okay.
Now we're in this
together.
[ crying ]
[ ding! ]
Am i going to jail?
You're here in custody
on a 72-hour hold,
To be assessed.
Thanks, officer.
You can close the door.
we'll be fine.
All right.
[ door closes ]
When i change --
when we change...
...or not...
Then we'll see.
You don't believe
it's gonna happen, do you?
Here's what i think.
Doctor speak --
Your pathological fear
of dogs,
Combined with the bite,
the fever,
The infection,
the fact that they occurred
During last month's
full moon --
It all adds up
to psychosis.
No. no, no.
No, see,
the man in the park was real.
The blood was real.
It was in the newspapers.
i saw it!
Do you own a gun?
No.
have you ever
owned a gun?
No.
Where did you get the gun
you had today?
I don't know.
I must have picked it up
somewhere.
You got it from the man
who assaulted you.
That man wasn't trying
to help you, ellis.
He knocked you out,
tried to mug you.
The police say
he has a long history
Of violent
armed robberies.
I killed him.
he was a human being,
and i killed him.
It was self-defense.
I shot a doctor,
for god's sake!
He'll be fine.
he's a tough kid.
That doesn't change
what i am.
I infected you.
i ruined your life.
Who knows
what i'm capable of?!
We'll soon find out
what you're capable of,
And we'll do it together.
Now, relax.
Lie down for me.
[ breathes deeply ]
Do you think my family
will ever forgive me?
They already have.
they'll be here tomorrow.
[ sighs ]
[ breathes deeply ]
Look at it this way --
You're either crazy,
or you're a werewolf.
Either way,
we'll deal with it.
[ sniffles ]
One day i'll wake up.
Man:
hear voices?
Hallucinate?
yeah.
Be institutionalized,
No control
over your own destiny.
You know the statistics.
What are the chances
of late-onset schizophrenia
In a man of our age?
[ sighs ]
Practically nil.
An irrational fear.
You asked me
what i was afraid of.
Irrational or not,
it's there.
[ chuckles ]
This is gonna make one hell
of a pickup line.
I can see it now --
"so, there i was,
"face-to-face with a wolf man
and a gun,
But there were lives at stake,
so i went for it."
Yeah,
like a complete idiot.
[ sighs ]
Actually...
I thought you were
pretty freakin' brave.
What are you doing
hanging around here,
When there's a bunch
of reporters outside?
You can go get
your 15 minutes of fame.
Nora's keeping them
at bay.
Besides,
the only person
They're really interested
in talking to is jack.
Of course.
So...
This is goodbye?
I don't know.
I'm having second thoughts
about cardiology.
Really? why?
Held hostage
by a mythical creature,
Forged documents,
elaborate spy plots?
How can a triple bypass
hope to compete?
I'm a little worried
about the forging and spying.
Like jack said,
Carl can't afford
to let any of this surface
Any more than you can.
I think it's a tie.
You know, you're just in time
for my sponge bath.
Oh.
i'll go get malcolm.
[ both laugh ]
[ crying ]
There you go.
Jack: everyone thinks
i'm fearless, a risk taker.
I've been a coward.
So what are you gonna do
about it?
I still don't know.
All you ever wanted to be
was a doctor, remember?
So be a doctor.
Here?
Well, you're here now,
doing a job you love.
And you're not half-bad
at it.
It's that simple, huh?
No, the hard work
is just beginning.
What do you demand
from your patients,
Before anything else?
That they face
their problems.
So face your problems,
jack.
[ chuckles ]
I must be crazy already,
Sitting here
talking to myself.
In that case,
what are you worried about?
Do we try to push the board
meeting back a couple days?
I say we can still
pull this off.
I think i can still spin
this situation our way.
Gallagher allowed
a dangerous lunatic
To take his staff hostage.
One was seriously wounded.
I was nearly killed.
how's that heroic?
Has nora come up
with any alternatives?
No.
She's been striking out
all over town.
Good.
Let's go rub her face in it.
Not tonight.
Dr. gallagher and i
will deliver a statement
To the press
sometime tomorrow.
Well, our main concern
right now
Is getting the hospital up
and running by morning.
Yes, mr. kahane is here,
undergoing treatment.
Man: fine.
well, thanks a lot.
Thank you. okay.
So, you mean to say,
While we were being held hostage
with a gun to our heads,
Hygard was doing
the same thing to you?
You can bet carl's into this
up to his eyeballs.
He almost had me.
So what changed?
Well, the media's
all over it now.
The board can't force me to fire
the hero of the hour.
It's a two-day story,
Stacked against
hygard's millions.
The most it'll do
is buy us a little time.
Well,
i could use that time
To try to find
a little bit more money.
If you could have,
you would have.
It's too much to risk
the entire psychiatric program
Against one man's job.
Take the deal.
[ sighs ]
What kind of place
would this be
If hygard pharmaceuticals
and other big companies
Can just buy us?
As long as you and veronica
are here,
You'll make it right.
Well, so what?
you gonna resign?
No, you can't resign.
so just --
I think i just did.
Well, i'm not accepting
your resignation.
Well, then fire me.
Oh, jack, shut up.
what if it's in
my best interest?
[ door opens ]
Oh, hey.
hey, tom, look --
[ chuckles ]
Sparky and the gang --
they're all here.
How fun.
Your timing's impeccable,
gentlemen.
Tom.
Jack.
Carl.
Oh, god.
Jack!
[ breathing heavily ]
[ chuckles ]
That's a --
that's an unprovoked attack.
Directed towards
another hospital employee.
Ah.
Immediate and irrevocable
grounds for dismissal.
[ sighs ]
You're fired.
Nice.
[ indistinct conversations ]
Where am i going?
Not a clue.
Nearest bar, nepal...
Never-never land.
But i feel optimistic...
And terrified.
[ whistles ]
Where am i going?
You'll be the first to hear.
[ ding! ]
www.tvsubtitles.net