I'm, you know --
You pig!
Friend of yours?
I thought it was going so well.
Actually,she was my date last night.
And that was her roommate.
- Not your day. - Not my year.
Maybe it's your technique,or the fact
that you're a misogynistic pig.
Maybe if you'd ever had
a relationship with a man,
You'd have something to offer here.
This is what i love to see
first thing in the morning --
Two of my favorite colleagues exchanging
important behavioral diagnosis.
What's the subject?
Dating, failed relationships,
suicidal ideations.
- Ah.Comes with the territory.
- What does?
Intimacy issues, research,
on my desk tomorrow morning.
What's the divorce rate
for psychiatrists
As opposed to, say,internists?
I'm assuming a little more?
Almost double.
Research, on my desk,
tomorrow morning.
You know, when i go to a party,
I don't tell anyone that
i'm even remotely attracted to
That i'm a shrink.
Yeah, they just freeze up
and run for the hills.
You're dating an architect.
You pass by a beautiful building.
Suddenly, they start warbling on
About how aesthetically wrong
the whole thing is.
Fascinating, but you suck it up.
You're a shrink.
Do you ever
start talking
About how this person
or that person needs therapy?
- No. - Why not?
Well, it's too invasive.
All comes down to the same line --
"Stop analyzing me."
Stop analyzing me.
Dr. Cutlett, dr. Briar,
Please report to pre-Surgery corridor.
Craig! Hi!
What are you doing down here?
Hello, doctor.
I'm -- I'm gonna have surgery tomorrow.
What kind of surgery?
Uh, brain operation.
Dirty whore!
I-I don't understand.
When you left the resident day clinic,
You were doing so well --
What happened?
I was.I-I-I thought so, too,
but, um...
Things have changed.
I'm -- I'm going downhill.
I'm so sorry to hear that,craig.
Do you -- Do you know why that is?
I -- I have to go now. Uh...
M-Mimi's waiting for me.
I-I need you to focus for a minute.
Do you know what -- What kind
Of brain surgery it is that you're having?
It's called a cingulotomy.
Douchebag!
???
Look,i -- I have to go.
The last thing i need
Is to get in a-Another fight with mimi.
You're having troubles
with mimi? Since when?
Listen...i can't talk about it now.
Bitch!
All right, craig.
The irony is,behavior is our specialty.
We should be better at this than anyone else.
Why can't we sustain a relationship?
Wait a minute.You and --
Yeah,i got a "dear chloe" e-Mail.
Oh, i'm sorry.
What?No "i told you so"?
Hey, i've been there.
I know what it's like.
What happened?
I just think she couldn't handle
How involved i was in my career.
I mean, she has a life, i don't.
We're residents. We work 18 hours a day.
What does she expect?
It's not just the hours.
It's the fact that we're intimately involved
In every detail of our patients' lives --
Their sexual needs, their fantasies, their dysfunctions.
What did you expect?
It's not the hours.
But you're always telling us
to ask more questions, dig deeper.
And the deeper we dig
into our patients' lives,
The more we're burying our own.
- I'm incredibly tuned in. - And humble.
No, i mean with my patients.
I sense what they're feeling,
what they need from me.
Women? I have no freakin' clue.
I always end up saying the wrong thing.
Or end up sleeping with their roommate.
Maybe we're just screwed up.
Is that terminology in the dsm-Iv?
No, i-I mean to begin with.
People who are drawn to this field --
Like you guys --
Usually do so because something
in their own lives
Has led them to believe
that people are, in general,
Including themselves, totally screwed up.
So, basically,
you're saying that none of us
Is destined to have
a successful relationship?
That we're gonna go through life
lonely and miserable?
God, what is wrong with us?
What's wrong with you?
You're psychiatrists.
www.1000fr.Com presents
capture:´ó±¦
sync:nick
Mental s01 ep01
w w w . B i e r d o p j e . C o m
A cingulotomy!
I mean, can you believe this?
Who ordered the surgery?
Some hack shrink
i've never even heard of
His wife, mimi,put him onto.
I mean, the wife calls the shots.
How long have they been married?
10 years, no kids --
They were happy.
Listen, this man was doing
so well in my clinic.
When he first came to me,
his ocd had gotten so bad,
He was presenting with tourette's.
Six months later,i said goodbye to him,
The outbursts, the ticks --
Virtually gone.
He got himself a new job.
His marriage was back on track.
When's the surgery scheduled?
Tomorrow morning,8:00 a.M.
A neurosurgeon here at wharton's performing it,
A dr. Zan avidan.
What kind of name is that,
anyway -- Zan avidan?
I have no idea.
Anyway,i can't find her.
I've been down to the neuro unit.
I've -- I've left voice-Mail
messages -- Nothing.
Anyone would think she's hiding.
"In recent studies,
"32% of patients previously
unresponsive to medication
"And behavioral treatments for ocd
Were at least partly improved
after a cingulotomy."
But that's just it --
He had vastly improved
With behavioral treatments and medication.
Does it mention there the side effects
Of having the brain surgery?
"Deficits of focus and sustained attention,
"As well as mild executive dysfunction,
Loss of speech,loss of memory."
So he undergoes the surgery,
Has parts of his brain tissue burned off,
The success rate's below 50%,
And there's side effects --
Nice.
I'm with you.
The surgery's still
in the experimental phase.
I'm not a fan of cutting anyone open
if an alternative exists.
Now, obviously, he wasdoing well
in your care
With therapy and medication.
Very well.
Right.I think i'll go down
to pre-Op
And have a little chat
with mr. Peters.
Really?I-I'll go with you.
Officially, he's not our patient.
Well, officially, no.
My department,my responsibility.
Let me take the heat.
Okay.
- Craig? - Yes
Dr. Jack gallagher.
Are you the anesthesiologist?
Actually, no.
I'm the director of psychiatric services
here at the hospital.
Dr. Hayden-Jones -- Veronica --
She asked me to drop by.
She was very concerned about you.
Why? Tch!
Douchebag!
How much do you know about
the operation tomorrow, craig?
I was -- I was informed
about the procedure.
I-I was told that i would feel
much better afterwards,
And this surgeon --
Surgeon assured me that
the operating room was sterile.
Oh, yeah, it's sterile.
Did they tell you, though,
right before the operation,
Someone's gonna come down here with
a razor and shave your head?
My whole - My whole head?
But i-I don't have
very much hair to begin with.
And then they're gonna take you
down to the operating room,
Where someone's gonna drill
a hole in your skull.
But, uh... i'll be asleep by then.
Oh, yeah,there'll be no pain involved.
At least not till you wake up.
You see, craig,most surgeons i know,
They're very good at slicing people open,
But they're not so good with helping
With the months of recuperation afterwards.
Months?
Mm-Hmm. Afraid so.
But my, uh --My symptoms --
The ticking,the swearing,
The oc-- Ocd --
It's all gonna improve, right?
Maybe.At least for the ocd anyway.
No guarantees.
Though were also no guarantees
With psychotherapy and medication,
And you did improve tremendously
in veronica's day clinic.
Nobody had to shave your head,
drill a hole in your skull,
Kind of root around inside your brain.
Can i -- Can i still change my mind?
I was hoping you'd ask that.
Thought he was growing on you?
No, he is, like a weed
invading on my territory.
It's not that he's doing a bad job.
It's just that, you know,
craig peters is my patient.
And, you know, he just comes in,
and he takes over.
- No more shop talk.- Sorry.
So, was the penne puttanesca
up to your standard?
Mmm. It was a little al dente. Yeah.
The goat-Cheese capellini
was just shy of perfection.
Okay.
You should come over one night.
I'll cook for you.
Maybe i will.
You won't.
- What? - You won't.
I've asked you a dozen times
to come over to my place,
And every single time,
you've had some excuse...
Not to.
What are you afraid of?
What you might find?
Bachelor-Pad extraordinaire?
Lava lamps, water bed, animal-Print rug?
Moose head?
Not afraid of what i might find.
Just that, you know, well, maybe --
Maybe i'll like it there.
No. And want to stay.
Rylan...
All right. Okay. All right.
How about tonight?
If i can get away early.
Okay.
Four seasons? Motel 6?
There's a park bench.
Your choice.
About going to your place --
That's all right. No, i get it.
Ah, you're missing out.
Steak tomato. Ahh.
Charm the pants off you.
My pants are coming off me anyway.
So are yours.
Mm, mnh-Mnh, mnh-Mnh, mnh-Mnh.
Nothing for him, mario.
He's not staying.
Arturo, what kind of game
are you playing?
Not playing any game.
I gave you an assignment.
You're obviously not taking it seriously.
I need information.
You need to keep your job.
I'm trying.
Have you had dinner with him yet?
I've asked.
Outside of work, he's kind of a loner.
Is he sleeping with anyone?
Anyone at the hospital?
I don't know.
The problem in a nutshell.
What do you want me to tell you?
Dr. Gallagher's a good guy.
Be aggressive. Be inventive.
Tell him you're having a crisis of conscience.
You're wondering whether to continue spying
Or be like mario here, serving lunch for a living.
Given the stakes,
I have every confidence that you'll find a way.
I'm not trained to do this, dr. Belle.
No?
I thought acting ran in your family.
What happened at the poker game?
Nothing.
He's a good card player. He won.
Did you see any drug
paraphernalia in evidence?
Other than alcohol, no.
Was he drinking?
We all were -- Beer.
Do you believe
he has a problem with alcohol?
Not from what i've seen.
I don't know everything about you, arturo.
Mmm. Yeah. Thank you.
But i do know this.
You want, more than anything,
To be sitting right
where i'm sitting right now.
And i can make sure that that happens.
Or i can make sure that that never happens.
Dr. Gallagher. I got a page.
Excuse me. Are you dr. Gallagher?
Hmm. You got me!
Yeah, figures.
- Excuse me?
- Well, they told me you were a bit odd.
Who's "they"?
I'm here about my patient -- Craig peters?
- You must be -- - Dr. Avidan.
Ah.
You literally come down to my pre-Op,
And you kidnap my patient.
He left voluntarily.
Only after you scared
the living crap out of him.
Just had a little chat with him.
Excuse me. Excuse me, sir.
Uh, would you rather spend the next 20 years
In psychotherapy or an hour and a half
in an operating room?
Uh, i don't know --
How do you like it?
Where the hell do you get off
Talking my patient out of surgery?
"A," you have no business
even speaking to him,
And, "b," this operation
is extremely important.
- To whom? - Excuse me?
Cingulotomys are rarely performed.
It's a risky and unproven procedure.
Is your concern for your patient
or your résum?
Listen, doctor --
And i use that term loosely --
You're about to cut a hole
in the head
Of a man you know nothing about.
I-I know that he's unable
to live a normal life.
I know that you geniuses
have had him on the couch
For six months,
and he still can't go to work.
He can't eat at a restaurant.
He can't have sexual relations
with his wife.
Why?
Because of his
obsessive-Compulsive condition.
But why?
Why exactly is he ocd?
What's the root cause?
I don't see how
this has anything to do with --
You're treating symptoms, not the disease.
Leave the medicine to the real doctors,
Will you, gallagher?
Oh. And who are they?
I want peters back in pre-Op
by tomorrow morning,
Or i'm filing disciplinary
charges against you.
It's craig's decision.
Not with you up his ass!
Well, you'll have
to arm-Wrestle me for him.
You'd lose.
Orderly, 319. Orderly, 319.
Wow.
I don't understand.
It was all taken care of.
Craig went to a psychiatrist,
Who referred him to a surgeon --
Dr. Avidan.
Why is he back up in the psych ward?
Mimi, you say you know
what's best for your husband.
- If that's true -- - Of course it's true.
He needs to have  surgery.
Well, unfortunately,
we're not convinced.
"We"?
You're not the ones
who have to live with him.
He twitches,
he screams out "dirty whore,"
He refuses to take me anyplace
Because of all the germs
in public places.
He carries a bottle of disinfectant
With him at all times, even in bed.
He sprays me with it!
Last week, he put a plastic bag
over our cat.
She nearly died.
I'm -- I'm very sorry, mimi.
Look, i'm just trying
to save my marriage.
I love craig. You know that.
I've spent 10 years with him and this ocd.
But now it's...
It's just gotten so bad.
I don't know how --
How anyone can take it.
Mimi, there's no easy solution.
We had a solution -- Surgery.
This is mimi. This is craig's wife.
Uh, drs. Gallagher and suarez.
Thing is, mimi, we can always
reschedule the surgery.
Good. Then we'll reschedule it now.
After we've had a chance to treat him
With medication and therapy,
We can get him right back on track
Without such an invasive step.
No, no, no i'm done with that.
I want him back.
I want the man that i married back.
I can't wait years for...
We're not talking years.
It may just be a matter of months.
No.
Not months, not weeks, not days. I'm done.
He's having the surgery,
or i-I don't know what i'll...
Arturo, would you take mrs. Peters
To the doctors lounge
and get her a glass of water?
Sure.
Have you seen mimi?
She's, uh...
She's still with arturo, i think.
Well, there's something wrong with her.
What? Well, you know, it's like
she's -- She's changed.
She's like a completely different person.
Walk with me.
She dropped him off and picked him up
From the clinic every single day.
She was never late.
She'd hand him his lunch
before she left,
Remind him to take his meds.
You heard her. He's not
the easiest personto live with.
Perhaps she's at the end
of her rope.
I don't buy that.
She was a dedicated caregiver.
Her only concern was --
Was making sure
that craig got better.
Even the way she looked.
What do you mean?
Well, the low-Cut top,
the black stockings --
This woman used to dress
so conservatively.
She would never wear a skirt.
She was mousy, and she was shy.
And this was only a few months ago?
Yeah. The change in her is radical,
And i think it's affecting craig.
So, i'm still waiting
on those disciplinary charges.
- May i? - No.
I'm warning you, gallagher,
If craig isn't rescheduled for surgery
In the next 12 hours,
you're in a world of trouble.
Nothing to do with me.
It's craig's decision.
Mm. Yeah, with you aiding and abetting.
This isn't a conspiracy.
That's exactly what this is.
This is a psychiatric conspiracy.
So, what, are you opposed
to all types of surgery
Or just neurosurgery?
No, you got me all wrong.
I like all forms of modern medicine.
But i also like good,
old-Fashioned ones like, um...
Talking to the patient.
More ways of getting inside a brain
than just sawing it open.
Tell me that the next time
You have a cerebral aneurysm, okay?
I'll pray you're on call when that happens.
So, how long you been at wharton?
Longer than you have.
Please, i'm just making conversation.
Yeah, to what end?
What, you think your charm,
your personality,
Your -- Your -- Your handsomeness
Is gonna win me over
after what you did?
I have charm and personality
and handsomeness?
Excuse me.
Hey, hey.
Hi.
How are you, craig?
Great.
I haven't ticked for at least 20 minutes.
That's good.
What's happened to you, craig?
Since you left the day clinic.
Well, things were going pretty well.
Got a job as a teller
in the bank where mimi works.
Oh, yeah? You still on the job?
No, i got fired.
Money is very unsanitary, as you know.
Yes, it is. Filthy.
You speak to the manager
About maybe wearing some plastic gloves?
I did. She said it wasn't allowed.
Mimi's the manager.
Oh.
How are things with you
and mimi at home?
Not so good.
You know what it's like.
Actually, i don't.
Never been married.
Well...
You've seen mimi,
So you know
what a sexual dynamo she is.
She wants to, you know,
do it every night --
Sometimes two or three times,
and...
I can't.
Because of her germs?
No.
I mean, i spray a lot,
so that's not it.
We used to have
a great sex life, but now...
You know, she's not satisfied... ever.
And it makes the...
Ticking and everything worse.
I -- I don't want to have this surgery.
But...
...i'd do anything for her.
She -- She's put up with me
for all these years.
No one else would have.
She's my whole life.
Mrs. Peters.
Please call me mimi.
Mimi, come on in.
Have you seen craig today?
Yes. I just came from his room.
He seems calmer.
He's on the same medication
we gave him before.
It might be a week or so
Before you see any difference
in the ticks.
Mimi, if i thought this
operation would cure him,
I'd be wheeling him down
to the o.R. Right now --
That i can promise you.
Would you like
to sit down?
Well, yes,
actually, i would.
We don't have to just talk
about craig, you know.
No?
No.
We could talk
about other things.
Like...
...are you seeing anyone special
right now?
Is that important to you?
I'm --
I'm just curious.
I have to get back
to work, so...
I'll see you later?
Sure.
Mm.
- A garter belt?
- Uh-Huh.
What color?
I don't believe it.
She's not the type.
Still waters...
Sounds like she was
coming on to you.
Do you think it's possible she has
some kind of hypersexual disorder?
A nymphomaniac?
Why are women nymphos
and men popular?
I wonder if craig knows.
He could know.
He could even improve.
It's possible.
Arturo, did you notice
anything unusual?
So, what color
was the garter belt?
Black.
Gray, actually.
[ Chuckling ]
sorry.
How did this happen?
I don't know.
I-I mean, i do, but...
It was crazy.
I-I mean, i took her to the doctors
lounge like you asked me to.
And i-I turned around to get her
a cup of coffee.
And she's right there,
And she puts her hands
on my ass...
Unzips my fly.
There was
no stopping her.
I get the picture.
This has never happened
to me --
With a patient,with a patient's
family,in a hospital.
This will never
happen again.
Okay.
Dr. Gallagher,
she's...
Pretty persuasive.
Okay.
Now, i know that i have no
right to ask this of you,but...
I'd appreciate it if we kept
this between ourselves.
If dr. Belle found out...
Why so concerned about carl
in particular?
He's just...
He can be very judgmental.
This will stay
just between us.
Thank you.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
Why am i not surprised?
You do anything normal?
God, i hope not.
[ Car alarm deactivates ]
yours?
Why am i not surprised?
Pretty sweet.
Course,i'm not ruining the
environment with greenhouse gases.
Eat your heart out,
bike boy.
Need a lift?
Infectious diseases?
Parasitic worms?
Mm-Hmm.
They fascinated me.
But then i thought,
A career spent diagnosing
irritable bowel syndrome --
No, thanks.
Fair enough.
You gonna eat
those fries?
So, what was it, exactly,
about these little worm things
That did it for you?
They're nasty
little buggers.
Tough to kill.
So you're saying
you admire them?
Yeah, their --
Their tenacity.
How 'bout that pickle?
Mmm, thank you.
I'm just so hungry.I didn't
have a chance to eat today.
[ Chuckling ]
what, you don't approve?
Actually,
it's refreshing.
I like a woman
who's not allergic to food.
What kind of women
have you been dating?
Well, they, uh...
they know who they are.
They're not
easily intimidated.
They know what they want.
I want...
That burger.
[ Ding! ]
Hey, doc.
Hey.
Hey, uh...
Look, that -- That --
It -- It wasn't, uh...
You know she's married --
To a patient on the ward.
Yes, yes, i do.
I'm -- I'm really sorry, but...
I mean, come on,
she's a...
- Sexual dynamo?
- Yeah.
I heard that.
No more?
- Swear to god.
- Okay.
Mimi?
Can i see you in my office
for a minute?
Of course.
[ Door closes ]
Did you want something,
doctor?
Yes, mimi,
i want to talk to you.
Well, i want to talk
to you, too.
All right,
there are a few --
I know what you really want.
And i really want
to give it to you.
That's better.
I believe you have
a real problem.
You mean you're the one
with the problem.
[ Door closes ]
Carl: all right, mr. Hygard,
watch and learn.
Care to make it
interesting?
How interesting?
Say a grand.
You're on.
[ Laughing ] okay.
Aah!
[ Laughs ]
[ Grunts ]
Didn't quite make it,
did it?
I mention how gorgeous
this club is?
Oh, you can't even buy
a membership here now --
Not for any amount
of money.
Got to be
grandfathered in.
How's our little friend
doing?
Burying himself a little deeper
every day.
How about that resident you own?
Anything we can use?
No. That's just icing
on the cake.
Old gallagher's
a walking time bomb.
Just a matter of time
before he explodes.
Well, hopefully,
not too much time.
11 votes on the board.
If we call for a dismissal
hearing today,
We can count on
no more than five.
By the time i'm through
with him, it'll be unanimous.
You can bet on that.
Speaking of betting...
I'm happy
to take a check.
I assume
you're good for it.
- Tom --
- Cash is great,but i'm happy --
Double or nothing.
You're a greedy bastard.
Oh, you have no idea.
Jack:
craig, what's going on?
Craig:
i'm gonna have the surgery.
- Why?
- I had no choice.
Mimi said she was --
Stop!
Stop that. Stop that.
Look at me.
Why?
Mimi said she was gonna file
for divorce.
Just give me
one more day.
Okay.
[ Door opens ]
I'm not gonna have the surgery
till tomorrow morning anyway.
Jack: whoa.
What,are you stalking me now?
I just came down here
To see what the real doctors
get up to.
- Mm.
- It's fascinating.
Oh, isn't it?
This is an mri.
We use it
to prep brain surgery.
Really?
Sounds complicated.
I assume
you'll infect the lesions
With the electrolytic destruction
of the anterior cingulate gyrus,
As opposed to a bilateral
surgical incision.
As a matter of fact,
i will.
So, one little zap
and out goes the ocd,
The ticks,
and the tourette's.
You got it.
An astounding 1/3
of the time.
Why are you here?
I'm here
because of craig.
I need your help.
Let me
get this straight.
Craig is scheduled to have
surgery tomorrow morning.
You want me talking him
out of it again.
That would be nice.
When was it, exactly,
that you lost your mind?
I want to arrange a sit-Down
Between the psych unit
and neurosurgery.
Just chatting over
our differences
For the sake
of the common good.
Your good
is more like it.
Well, it would be a useful
training exercise for my staff,
And veronica's up my ass
about craig being her patient,
So you'd be doing me
a solid there.
But we both know
this is about craig.
The consequences
could be severe.
What consequences?
Are you really certain
that this surgery is gonna work?
A sit-Down --
That's all --
And then you'll leave me alone
about this?
Promise.
You bring your team,
i'll bring my team.
Don't forget mimi.
We'll all sit down
like adults
And talk through this
peacefully,
Once and for all.
All right,
all right, all right!
All right, let's look at some
of the things we agree on.
Craig has ocd.
It's interfering
with his life,
And we must take steps
To improve the situation.
Immediate steps.
So, we can agree
that we're all here
Because we want
to help craig.
Nan: well, craig has made
his choice, doctor.
Craig hasn't even had a say
in this!
So, what are you
suggesting?
That he's being forced
into this?
Craig wants to have
this surgery.
What craig wants
is to please his wife,
Regardless of the risks.
What risks?
Loss of brain function,
including memory and stroke.
High-- Highly unlikely,
doctor.
Blood clots, blindness,
infection, death.
All this together adds up to less
than 1% of most surgeries.
Jack: all right.
Can i see you outside
for a moment, doctor?
[ Clears throat lightly ]
[ Door opens ]
I think
there's a strong possibility
That mimi's got
kluver-Bucy syndrome.
What hat did you pull
that one out of?
I know, i know, it's rare,
but i've been watching her,
And she's got a cluster
of symptoms --
Hyper-Reality, fearlessness,
hypersexuality.
Are we talking
about the same person here?
Mimi -- Craig's wife?
She's a sex addict.
Ahh.
And you know this because...
Because she slept
with half my staff,
And she tried to do the deed
with me, as well.
I see.
Have you even been watching her
in there?She's already fixated.
She's flirting with that
good-Looking young resident
That sat next to you.
You know, the one
you can't keep your eyes off?
Yeah, you know, he is kind
of good-Looking, isn't he?
And, just so you know,
Not every hypersexual person
Is suffering
from a brain lesion.
It's a long shot.
Humor me.
I'll rule it out.
Mimi:
i'm not changing my mind.
Mimi, this is not
about a cingulotomy.
This is about you.
We're concerned.
We're concerned
About your compulsive
sexual activity.
Well, that's none
of your business.
Uh, it is, mimi.
Craig is our patient,
And we believe that your
behavior is affecting him.
How long has it
been going on?
I mean, you guys have
an open relationship?
No.
It's only been going on
for a couple months.
But what does my behavior
have to do with craig's ocd?
Couple of months,
you say?
All right,
let's look at the timeline.
Craig leaves the clinic,
what, a few months ago?
A couple of months ago,
you start these urges,
And craig
can't fulfill them,
So he gets nervous,
he gets agitated,
His ocd comes back,
And his tourette's comes back
with a vengeance.
So his condition
is my fault?
Not saying that, exactly,
but you may have exacerbated it.
But even that
may not be your fault.
Mimi, look.
We believe
you may be sick.
We think that you may have
a condition
Called kluver-Bucy,
Which is a brain lesion
or tumor...
Most likely not life-Threatening
or cancerous.
What, you're telling me
that i have a tumor
And that this tumor is
what's causing me to want to,
You know,
have sex all the time?
We think so, yes.
But we can't determine it
for sure
Until we do a workup --
Blood work, a physical,
cat scan.
So, i have
all of these tests,
And you find a tumor,
then what?
It should be removed.
And once it's gone,
The hypersexuality,
we think that'll go, too.
And i'll be back
to the way i was before?
And craig will have a very good
chance at improving, also.
[ Piano plays softly ]
Excuse me.
I think
i'm in the wrong house.
Honey.
It's just dinner.
I got home early, so...
Third time this week.
To what do i owe
the pleasure?
Now, i'm making
your favorite --
Caesar salad, new york steak,
and strawberry cheesecake.
How was your session?
Actually, it was great.
They want me to sit in on piano
again tomorrow.
Really? Fantastic.
How was your day?
Oh, you know,
the usual insanity.
Tell me.
Well, um...
We're dealing with a real-Life
nymphomaniac on the ward.
She's the wife of one
of my ocd patients,
And she's putting the moves on
all the males in the hospital.
Really?
What's she look like?
Not like you'd expect.
Not at all.
But her poor husband,
Who's so ocd he can't even
hold down a job,
His wife's everything
to him, and he --
He hasn't got a clue.
Maybe he does.
Maybe he knows.
I mean, a husband
can usually tell when...
When what?
When his wife
is running around on him.
You're having an affair,
aren't you?
Why would you say something
like that?
Because you're happier
than you've been in a long time.
And i know better than
to think it's because of me.
It's very small
and benign.
That's good news.
How long
has it been there?
There's no real way
to tell.
Uh, could have been there
for years.
Or it could have been there
just a couple of months.
Jack: couldn't it?
Yes, it could be
a very recent growth.
So, what now?
Well, i'd like to schedule
a surgery to have it removed.
But you said it wasn't cancerous
or life-Threatening.
Well, it could develop
into something more serious.
But it's not serious now.
I don't want
the surgery.
Mimi...
Look.
We believe that
this hypersexuality
That you're exhibiting
might be caused
By the tumor pressing down
on the brain tissue.
I could do therapy.
I mean, you're the one
who says it's better
To have a non-Invasive course
of action.
Well, this is different, mimi.
This is a tumor.
There's a potential risk
to us not operating.
You know, we can't be sure that
you won't lose vital cognitive
Or even basic
life-Sustaining functions
If you don't let us get
this thing out of your head.
Why don't you discuss this
with craig?
Oh, no, no, no.
Craig can't know
about my...symptoms.
Well, in fairness,the way
you're carrying on,
It's possible
he already knows.
Maybe after
craig's surgery.
Even if the cingulotomy
is successful,
It's not gonna help
craig's ocd
If you...carry on behaving
the way you're behaving.
Arturo: the real reason
she doesn't want the operation
Is because she's happy
with the way things are.
How can you say she's happy?
She's confused.
She doesn't know
what she wants.
- Her marriage is falling apart.
- What does she care anyway?
She's out there
hustling other guys.
- You should know.
- Suggestions, people.
Veronica:
i just think this whole thing
Is completely ironic.
I mean, mimi's insisting
craig have the operation
When there's
a very viable alternative,
And yet she's refusing to have
an operation herself.
She's insisting there is
a viable alternative -- Therapy.
Well, that's one thing
she is right about.
The sexual addiction can be
controlled through therapy.
She's not even interested
in controlling it.
Well, she should be,because
right now,it's controlling her.
Look, it's simple.
She's afraid
of the surgery
Because she doesn't want
to go back to her old life.
Chloe: what mimi's really afraid
of is losing the power --
The power that she now feels
over men.
She did say she was a virgin
when she met craig.
Exactly. She never got
the chance to play the field.
The fact that she can use
this condition
As an excuse to go out
and freely flirt,
Pick up, and seduce any man
on the street
Is self-Medicating.
Well, maybe,
but it's dangerous.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
So, um...
Where are we going?
Well, it's like
i told you earlier.
I thought
you could use a drink.
[ Mid-Tempo music
playing ]
[ Music continues ]
Jack: so...
Here they are.
Who?
Your future
sexual partners.
[ Scoffs ]
If this is some kind of joke,
it's not funny.
No, it's not a joke.
I'm gonna hazard a guess.
I'd say these are, uh,
half the number of men
You've slept with
in the last two months alone.
Who are they?
Who's this guy?
Is he out on bail
for murder?
Look at those guys
down there.
What's the condition
of their health?
That guy have herpes?
What about his mate there?
Does he have aids?
Look at this guy.
Member of the american
nazi party.
Do you really care?
I love the way
this feels.
Look at me.
I was never sexy,
even if i got all dressed up.
No way a man
would take notice.
But now?
Doesn't matter
what i look like.
I feel sexy.
I feel like i can have
any man that i wanted.
And you will always
have that choice.
What about craig?
He loves you.
He thinks you're sexy.
Thinks you're a goddess.
And he's willing to have
his head cut open for you.
Craig: they said they'd call me
when the surgery was over.
Veronica: well,
it should be soon.
Don't worry.
She'll be fine.
Then things will be better
between you and mimi.
They already are.
It's complicated,
isn't it?
What is?
Marriage.
Jack: craig!
She's in recovery.
Come on.
[ Monitors beeping ]
[ Door closes ]
Surgery
went really well.
Uh, tumor's all gone.
She's fine.
Thank you, doctor.
M-Mimi,
i was so worried.
Mm.
I love you.
I made so many mistakes.
- Craig, i didn't mean --
- You were sick.
You're gonna be fine now.
So am i.
- So, end of story.
- Not quite.
Anyone ever tell you how sexy
you look in those scrubs?
So many times,
you don't even know.
I think i look sexier
without them.
Hungry?
Starving.
Well, this could be construed
as our second date.
What do you say
we go and do something
A little bit...
romantic?
Let's go to henry's,
let's get carryout,
And then let's go back
to your place.
[ Ding! ]
www.tvsubtitles.net