She might not be so easy to recognize.
I'll know her.
And none of these are her.
Four years on the street is a long time,
dr. Gallagher.
You want me to stay on it?
Of course.
At the same level?
If you need more people,
it isn't be an issue.
I'm staying.
You might wanna scale back.
Why would I do that?
Rebecca's name and picture
has been out to the police,
The neighbourhood, and any shelter,
aid organization, church
Every clinic in the area for months.
I can't say we're any closer
to finding your sister
Than were the first day you walked
into my office.
I'm trying to be straight with you.
I appreciate it.
Same level.
Ethan!
You have to take your meds.
They make me sleepy.
Even so...
What if he calls?
He'll call back.
What if he doesn't?
Bottoms up.
He promised that he'd call.
Calloway, Ethan.
Obsessive Delusional Disorder.
You know, why don't I stay here
for a little while?
Just in case?
There you are.
It's okay, ethan.
[ beeping ]
[ sniffs ]
[ sighs ]
[ exhales deeply ]
[ doorbell buzzes ]
[ buzzing continues ]
Hey, stranger.
Rebecca?
[ both laugh ]
How did you get here?
I don't know. i --
I-i don't know.
it -- it just happened, jack.
I -- i woke up,
and i was back.
Are you okay?
i-i can't explain it.
Sit down.
sit down.
I don't know if it will last,
but i'm here.
You -- you okay?
[ voice breaking ]
i tried to speak,
But i couldn't.
When i called
and you talked to me...
I know.
I want to get better,
jack.
We're gonna
make that happen.
[ breathing heavily ]
I'm gonna get you
some water.
Okay.
it's okay.
[ chuckles weakly ]
Are you hungry?
what can i get you to eat?
[ chuckles ]
surprise me.
Omelet --
um, spinach, mushrooms.
[ microwave beeping ]
[ sighs ]
My computer is fine, Carl.
Mm, it's obsolete.
it is a doorstop, as is mine.
oh, which is the point
of this conversation.
What's the point?
Oh, carl wants a new,
upgraded company laptop.
He assumes
if i join in the chorus,
you'll be more likely
to lend your support.
Why would carl
assume that?
well, carl thinks
you favor me.
ridiculous.
I think i favor carl.
Ridiculous that this hospital
expects us to do our jobs
Lacking
the requisite tools.
Hard-drive envy.
It's a guy thing.
Ira: carl!
Ira.
how are ya?
Slumming?
You know i enjoy these visits
to loony land.
Uh, dr. gallagher,
ira greenbaum,
Senior staff, neurology.
Zan's dr. gallagher?
What brings you?
Oh, transferring
a patient --
Bauer, william --
new-onset asthma,
Atypical retinal signs,
thermoregulatory dysfunction.
Requiring the services
of a pulmonary specialist,
Endocrinologist,
and ophthalmologist.
Done, done,
and, oh, done.
Also, infectious diseases,
Allergic medicine,
and neurology.
We all drew blanks.
he's not symptomatic?
Well, his symptoms
are real enough.
They're just not
physiologically based.
Could be multisystem
conversion disorder,
Something
in the somatoform family?
My god, sherlock,
you've cracked the case!
Obviously,
i'm in the right place.
Yeah.
I'll, uh,
e-mail his file.
[ indistinct conations ]
Be right back.
There you go.
Tell me about the accident,
billy.
[ exhales ]
It was about four --
four months ago on a site.
You work construction.
Yeah, i'm getting
my contractor's license.
[ sighs ] "was."
What happened?
we were tearing down
this old apartment building.
we were excavating
the basement,
when i thought i was clear
of the pit,
but the ground gave way
underneath me.
it took them about eight hours
to dig me out.
Must have been terrifying,
being swallowed up like that.
yeah.
dark?
pretty much.
cold?
[ exhales sharply ]
real cold.
Must have been a lot of dust
in the air,
What little air
there was.
[ chuckling ] yeah.
i still wake up
every morning choking.
[ coughs ]
You all right?
No.
[ exhales sharply ]
[ sniffs ]
[ groans ]
[ shivering ]
Mr. bauer...
You could have
been killed.
Instead,
you survived an accident
With only minor injuries.
You might consider yourself
fortunate.
Well, i can't drive.
I can't work.
I can't go to school.
I can barely get around.
i feel very fortunate,
thank you.
Carl:
you wanted to see me?
William bauer.
Somatoform disorder,
Possibly heightened
by latent claustrophobia,
Activated
by the accident.
you do know
about the accident.
I read the file.
Well, then, you realize
the correspondence
Between what bauer experienced
while buried
And the symptoms now are
too exact to be coincidental.
He's immobilized,
in fear of his life.
He's cold,
can't see, can't breathe.
Symptoms you accentuated
By feeding the patient images
during intake.
Now,
why would i do that?
To validate
your diagnosis.
Treatment options.
Carl: pharmacotherapy
and psychotherapy.
With an ssri
to elevate mood
And the right sleep medication
and a good talk therapist,
Billy's life should resume
normal patterns
Within a fairly short
period of time.
That's optimistic.
no, it is not.
Bauer's
a healthy young man
With no prior history
of psychological disturbance.
What about the time gap --
Three months
between the accident
And the onset
of physical symptoms?
how does that sit
with conversion?
You think i'm giving the patient
short shrift,
A too-quick diagnosis
leading to a hasty prescription.
what do you think?
I think your bloated ego
Occasionally clouds
your judgment.
Occasionally?
Rylan.
Hola.
You don't smoke.
i don't smoke
around you.
Today's the exception.
Okay,
what the hell happened?
Nora told me you walked out
on a patient in the e.r.?
Well...
Nora, as usual, is...
Very well-informed.
It's true?
With an explanation.
What,
you're joking about this?
That is the essential
rylan moore --
Service with a smile.
Ugh. cut the crap.
[ sighs ]
Paramedics brought in
a prostitute --
Christine.
Apparently, one of christine's
johns demanded a refund
And when she objected,
stuck a knife between her legs.
We managed to stop the bleeding,
but, uh, she's very close.
As we were finishing up
with chrtine,
Police brought in
the john --
He had a gsw
to the right shoulder,
Resisting arrest.
He was very lucky.
it barely clipped him.
Well, you've dealt
with similar situations
Dozens of times.
I probably would have helped
this case, too,
If he hadn't opened
his mouth.
And said?
"let the whore bleed."
You should go home.
I was thinking
the same thing.
Want to come?
I'm in the middle
of my shift.
Right.
I could see you later.
I'm thinking about
driving up the coast,
Maybe spend a couple nights
in santa barbara.
We talked
about doing that.
You know i can't.
Then i'll see you
when i get back.
Yeah, good.
[ sighs ]
How's billy doing?
He's not so good.
Damn.
i really liked that kid --
Always on time, good attitude,
smart, steady, you know?
And then this.
My business manager
keeps telling me
To expect a lawyer letter --
suing my ass for damages.
But i don't think
billy would do that.
Do you think the accident
was your company's fault?
It occurred on my site.
Is that really what started
all this?
It set something
in motion.
The timing's
too coincidental.
I don't know.
What can you tell me
about it?
Come on.
i'll show you -- that way.
It happened down here.
The ground just gave way
without warning.
It's all filled in now.
I didn't see the collapse,
But i came running
when i heard the shouting.
Wewhat did you see?
Must have been
an old air shaft
Predating the building
we were demolishing --
About six feet across.
Billy landed
about 20 feet down.
I suppose these things happen,
just not to me.
You saying it hurt
your business?
No, not really. it made all
the local news channels.
Everyone loves
a happy ending.
Having one of your employees
buried alive?
What? what's this
"buried alive" crap?
Billy wasn't buried?
Hell no!
Like i said, he fell
about 20 feet below the surface,
He could see out,
And the rescue team in
at all times.
He could breathe?
His legs were trapped,
But he could still move his arms
and his head.
He spent most
of the eight hours
Chatting up the cute little
paramedic looking over him --
Annie.
The only reason why
i know her name
Is because afterward,
billy and she dated.
Was it cold that day?
In l.a.?
Ethan.
What if he calls?
Well, if he calls...
What are you expecting him
to say?
He'll advise me.
He'll tell me
what to do.
mm-hmm.
about what exactly?
My life...
Whatever i need.
You never actually met
your grandfather, did you?
He died when i was
So, without knowing
who you are --
At least,
the man who you are today --
Do you think
it's possible
That he could dispense
good advice?
He watches over me.
But he didn't say that,
did he,
The first time that he spoke
to you on -- on -- on the radio?
Not exactly.
No. what?
what exactly?
I told you.
He said, "stay tuned.
Big changes are comin'."
Yeah.
but why not more?
I mean, he had you right there
on the line.
why not say then exactly
what he wanted you to hear?
Well, i don't know.
D-do you think
that there's a problem?
What if the problem
isn't with your grandfather?
what if the problem is actuay
with you?
Oh, god.
what have i done?
No, ethan, it's okay.
What i'm actually
suggesting is that...
Maybe your grandfather
is waiting
For you
to be ready to listen.
Ready how?
Calmer,
more in control of yourself,
Not so tied up in knots.
And i think --
I think that's what
your grandfather
Probably wants to talk to you
about, more or less.
Well...
Am i ready to listen,
dr. jones?
I believe you are.
[ gasps lightly ]
[ coughs ]
[ groaning ]
Malcolm,
i've got a code!
Hurry it up!
Room 102 is coding.
get a crash cart.
[ coughs ]
Come on.
i need ice-cold towels.
Weeed to get
his temp down.
got it.
Hurry it up!
come on!
[ groans ]
here you go, doctor.
[ breathing heavily ]
Nurse:
put it under him.
You need more, doctor?
What the hell is this?
[ beeping ]
On this ward, we don't always
succeed with our patients,
And how we measure success
is debatable.
but we don't typically come
this close to killing them.
Mr. bauer's temperature
is back to normal.
He appears to have suffered
no ill effects.
His temp spiked at 106.
Any higher,
we might have lost him.
Do we have any ideas
at all?
Although i admit
the severity
And range of psycho-symptomatic
response is startling,
The diagnosis stands --
somatoform disorder.
Considering the relatively
benign circumstances
Of the accident,
none of it makes sense.
Are we even sure
that that's what caused it?
The logic is unassailable.
We're not set up
for critical care.
We can't endanger
this manife.
We can't just turf him back
to the main hospital.
That's too dangerous.
Well, what do you ,
jack?
I need more time
with the patient.
mine.
my patient.
I'll take
responsibility.
Tell me what you're seeing,
billy.
Billy: it's the same --
dim, blurry.
I used to be able
to make out shapes,
And now,
unless i'm close
Or something's
right in front of me,
I can't make out any detail
at all.
[ scoffs ]
I'm gonna end up totally blind,
won't i?
I want to build things,
dr. gallagher.
I want to plan them.
i want to create them.
I want
to see them through.
It's the only thing in life
that i've ever been sure of.
You told carl belle...
That, um,
you're having trouble sleeping,
That you'd wake up
choking.
Is there anything else?
I have these dreams.
They startbout a month
after the accident.
The other doctors --
they couldn't care less.
I'm not
the other doctors.
No, i know.
You don't think
i'm faking it.
You think i'm a nut case.
So why don't you tell me
everything?
What difference
would it make?
Probably won
believe you anyway.
What about these dreams?
It's dark.
I'm walking through some kind
of cave or tunnel.
I'm either freezing cold,
or else i'm --
I'm -- i'm --
i'm burnint.
I'm scared.
i've...never been that scared.
Something in the air
leaves a bad taste in my mouth.
It's like metal.
There's a cask
filled with water,
But it's so cold
that the top is frozen.
So i have
to break the ice.
And i see myself
In the reflection,
Only...it's not me --
Older, dirtier.
I have a bandage
over my eye.
How can i dream
that i'm somebody else?
I spoke to tom hearst.
His version of the accident
is way different than yours.
Well, i'm sorry if i gave anyone
the wrong impression.
I wasn't exactly buried,
was i?
No.
With everything,
i get a little confused.
You mentioned annie.
Yeah.
We don't see
each other anymore.
Wh that?
She split.
Look at me.
i can't blame her.
Nora:
have you talked to rylan?
Briefly.
he went out of town.
I'm seeing him
tomorrow night.
The disciplinary committee
is meeting tomorrow afternoon.
What do you think?
It depends
on his reaction
And whether this guy
wants to sue the hospital
For malpractice.
So what should he do?
Come up with an excuse --
any reasonable excuse --
And stick to it.
He's got a good reputation.
people like him.
He's likable.
How you holding up?
I've just never seen him
look so unhappy before.
[ breathing shallowly ]
Annie jester.
Right there.
Annie: [ clears throat ]
i told you. i just got here.
All right. bye.
[ cellphone beeps ]
Annie?
dr. gallagher.
Hi. thanks for coming in.
did i get you out of work?
Oh, it's okay.
billy's here?
yeah.
Since when?
Checked himself
into the main hospital
About two weeks ago.
We've had him,
oh, less than two days.
When was the last time
you saw him, spoke to him?
Since we broke up,
almost two months?
I didn't know
about any of this.
Shortness of breath,
nightmares, sweats, chills?
No, none of it.
How long
were you two together?
[ beep ]
Four weeks.
I know that doesn't sound
like much.
Maybe it had something to do
with how we met,
But we just clicked
right away.
It was intense, you know,
like it was meant to be.
Sure.
That's why it hurt so bad
when he dumped me.
he dumped you?
One day,
out of the blue,
He told me he didn't want
to see me anymore.
It was really hard.
Are you ready for this?
Look, consider this.
It was around about the time
that you two broke up
That billy started having
these physical symptoms --
Nightmares, and, in particular,
his loss of vision.
You're saying he broke up
with me
So i wouldn't have to go
through this with him?
Do you want to help?
[ knock on door ]
Billy?
I brought you
a visitor.
Billy.
It's me.
it's annie.
The paramedic
ex-girlfriend?
How did you know?
Tom hearst.
This...
Might not be
a good idea.
Because i'm breaking
protocol,
Bringing in a surprise visitor
to see a patient?
Nothing you do
surprises me anymore.
If you had come to see me
Before going to see
billy's employer,
I could have saved you
a trip.
Instead,
you went behind my back.
If there's anyone here
who has a tendency
To pursue private agendas,
it's you.
I didn't know
you were keeping score.
Anything else
i should know?
[ inhales sharply ]
You might want
to ask billy
The name
of the apartment building
They were demolishing
when he was trapped.
What's that got to do
with anything?
aah!
annie: dr. gallagher!
What's wrong?
let me help.
no! my legs!
Come on.
lay back.
I'll help you.it's okay.
Dr. Gallagher!
[ groaning ]
Oh, my legs!
Ohh! what the hell
is happening?!
[ groaning ]
Nora:
an allergic reaction.
Some new solvent
that they're using
In the hospital
laundry.
At least that's the theory,
anyhow.
Are you buying this?
it's nonsense.
Well, there haven't been
any other similar reactions
From any other patients
in any section of the hospital.
What's your explanation
of this?
Soing else.
Carl:
mr. bauer exists
In a heightened state
of somatic reactivity.
Had he been started
on the drug regimen i suggested,
Which dr. gallagher
overruled,
This would not
have happened.
Billy's extremely reactive
and...suggestible.
He's living out
his nightmares.
We've got a very sick kid
Who's been prodded and probed
and tested
And passed around
until his headpinning.
He's too hot.
he's too cold.
He's choking.
he, uh -- he's beding.
He can't see,
and nobody knows why.
This is not
somatoform disorder.
And unless we dig deeper...
We've failed him miserably.
[ siren wailing in distance ]
I don't want
to see her again.
Why not?
[ scoffing ]
look at what happened.
You connect that
to annie?
What's the connection,
billy?
She was in the dreams.
Can you be
more specific?
I'm buried.
it's dark.
I-i can't move.
i'm freezing cold.
Man:
we need some oxygen!
I can't breathe.
My -- my legs hurt.
Everything hurts.
I look up, and i see her
leaning over the pit.
It doesn't look like her,
but somehow i know it is.
And she's looking down at me,
and she's smiling.
And there's -- there's other --
other people around me,
But they're dead --
their bodies are cold.
and i just -- i just want
to scream at her.
I want to scream at her
to stop smiling,
But i have [exhales]
i have no air in my lungs.
[ breathes deeply ]
[ sniffs ]
And i look at her,
And i know
that i'll be dead soon, too.
[ coughs ]
I'll get you
some more blankets.
What was the name
of the, uh, building
That you were
demolishing?
[ sniffs ]
rose park apartments.
Jack: tom?
jack gallagher.
Hi.
quick question for you --
What was the name
of the apartment building
That you were tearing down
when billy got hurt?
Uh-huh.
No, that's it. that's great.
i appreciate it.
Thanks, tom.
[ beep ]
Veronica: no one died
or was harmed in any way.
The patient was seen by another
doctor within minutes.
It's not that bad.
I denied an injured man
treatment.
Yeah,
but at the hearing,
You just say
that you felt sick
And you had to leave
the room.
That's a lie.
Well,
under the circumstances...
Look [exhales]
No one gives us the right
to make moral judgments
As to who we help
and who we don't.
Okay. so, no excuses.
you snapped.
In that moment,
You -- you say you're sorry,
it'll never happen again,
And you accept whatever penalty
the committee recommends,
And you get past this.
I'll be under
a microscope.
Yeah, for a while.
I wanted him to die.
Ohh.
Why do we need
this grief?
[ chuckles ]
Either of us.
What a you
talking about?
Maybe it's time
for a change.
I've been thinking
about moving back to austin.
I want you
to come with me.
Well, you know i can't.
i know...
You're unhappy
in your marriage.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be here,
naked in bed with me.
Oh, jesus.
you'd love austin.
There's the university
med center.
And with
your credentials --
There is no shortageof crazi
And you really think
emergency medicine's
Gonna be any different,
There's no ugliness,
no violence there?
[ scoffs ]
come on, rylan.
We'd be together.
[ chuckles lightly ]
I just can't just pack up
and...leave.
You can.
it's so simple.
You pack a bag,
get on a plane.
What are you
really leaving behind?
[ knock on door ]
Professor vilchek?
Dr. gallagher!
Close the door.
maybe we'll start a rumor.
[ chuckles ]
the rose park mine disaster --
why come to me?
Wrote the book,
professor.
a book, one of a dozen or so
on the subject,
And hardly
the most notable.
Well, you're the only one
i found here in l.a.
Fate. [ chuckles ]
i believe in fate. do you?
Actually, no.
Well,
you're still a young man.
consider, then, the fate
Of the 263 coal miners
Who descended
into shaft number 3
Of the rose park mine
on a frozen january 11, 1903,
Never to emerge.
So what went wrong?
Fire.
They used mules down in the pits
in those days
To pull the coal carts.
Mules need hay.
some fool parked a hay cart
under an open torch?
Kerosene and coal dust
are latile mixture,
And they felt that explosion
eight miles away.
It was one of the worst mining
disasters in u.s. history.
Those who managed to survive
the initial fire, explosion,
And tunnel collapse
Were overcome
by the black damp.
Poison air?
but there were survivors.
16.
15 of them had just gotten off
the elevator hoist
And were hauled up
to safety.
the other one
wasn't so lucky --
Trapped
for six grueling days.
The searchers had given up
looking for survivors,
And they were just
bringing up bodies,
And they found him
surrounded
By nine friends
and co-workers.
They barricaded themselves
into a side tunnel.
The black damp had taken
the rest of them.
Far right.
billy: and i see myself
in the reflection,
only...it's not me --
older, dirtier.
i have a bandage over my eye.
for me?
Signed by the author.
[ book claps shut ]
That's what i admire about you,
gallagher --
You go the extra mile.
I-i was content to do
my research online.
And not share what you've
learned with your colleagues?
You step in on my patient
without my permission,
you pay the freight.
And i was curious to see
How long it would take you
to catch on.
Past-life memory?
Not the first thing
that comes to mind --
not my mind, anyway.
So, what explanation will it be
for mr. bauer --
That he's experiencing
symptoms
From an event
he only dreams of?
Reincarnation and
the transmigration of souls,
Jung's collective
unconscious,
Or those millions of tiny units
of information
Mysteriously buried
in our dna
And passed down
through generations?
I can't explain it.
so i won't try.
But billy's got a right to know
what i've uncovered,
Whatever it means.
Maybe you should talk
to somebody
Better versed
in the area.
How do you know her?
[ pen thuds lightly ]
Love the new laptop.
Woman: great class.
[ chuckles ]
Bye!
Louisa: see ya!
Bye-bye.
Woman #2:
hey, guys, wait up.
[ birds chirping ]
Dr. gallagher?
It's very good of you
to see me. thank you.
Just so i'm clear,
uh, this really isn't about you?
A patient.
Mm.
Some people come to me
Pretending to be someone
other than themselves.
They do, huh? why?
Well, past-life regression
is hardly a mainstream belief.
you're a believer.
As were and are many cultures,
both modern and primitive,
Not to mention hundreds
of documented cases,
Some chronicled by people
in your own profession.
I'm familiar
with the studies.
[ chuckles ]
But you don't believe.
These regressions --
how do you perform them?
Well, i don't use drugs
or hocus-pocus,
If that's what you mean.
The subject
must be willing,
And with my help they enter
into a meditative state
And begin the journey
of self.
I act as guide.
And what do they get
from the experience?
Hopefully release.
If you're scared of elephants
and can't imagine why,
It might be helpful
to know
That you were once trampled
by one,
Perhaps as a member
Of hannibal's army
crossing the alps.
You aren't scared of elephants,
are you?
unh-unh.
I need some
general information.
So, you're a friend
of carl belle's.
We work together.
A very old soul,
With a very interesting
lineage.
[ knock on door ]
What happened
at the hearing?
Sit down.
[ clears throat ]
Well, um, it's over.
Oh, my god,
they fired him.
No.
A couple
of hospital lawyers
Went in
to take a statement
From the patient,
But he was so high
when they brought him in
That he didn't remember
anything.
So a decision was made
to let the whole thing die.
[ chuckles ] that's fantastic.
does rylan know?
Yeah, of course.
What?
Well,
he thanked the committee
And tendered
his resignation.
What?
Where are we going?
We're heading
for the basement.
I don't want to.
Let's just go back
to the hospital.
Ask me what's down here.
Ask me.
What's --
what's down here?
Whatever it is
that you're afraid of.
[ plank thuds ]
Four months ago,
An air shaft opened up
right here,
And you fell in.
But something else
happened.
[ indistinct shouting ]
What was the name
of the building
That you were
demolishing?
Rose park apartments.
Wait.
[ indistinct shouting ]
Park view apartments.
Where did you see the words
"rose park"?
[ indistinct shouting ]
What's g--
what's going on here?
Okay. look at this.
Who is he?
[ grunting ]
I don't know.
I-i can't make him out.
You've seen him before --
in your dreams, billy.
[ indistinct voices ]
Then who is he?!
His name is
dwayne jenkins.
Dwayne jenkins was you
in a past life.
[ exhales ] that's --
that's not possible.
Just get me out of here
right now.
There's an explanation.
i don't care
what the explan--
i think you do care,
billy!
I think you're damn tired
of being buried alive.
Now,
what do you remember?
We were working
when it happened.
Bodies were everywhere,
trapped.
And i, uh...
...i was gone.
So, dwayne jenkins died
in a mine collapse,
And 100 years later,
I fall into a hole,
and i remember being him.
Heat from the fire
and explosion,
The cold and darkness
that followed,
Painful wounds to the back
of his leg,
Air choked
with coal dust,
The terror
of imminent death...
...jenkins' life...
Not your own.
I think it's the confusion
of memories past and present
And the fear
that that brings
That's causing
your symptoms.
This past-life regression
will help?
Well, hopefully by examining
them in detail and in context,
We can separate
jenkins' memories from your own
So you can stop living his fears
in your life.
I think
you'll get better.
and i think
you will build things.
I think i'm ready
to go back now.
There's one more thing.
When you were trapped
and down in the hole,
You looked up,
and you saw the face of annie.
When jenkins
was also trapped,
he looked up, likewise,
and saw the face of his annie.
But if jenkins died in the pit,
how could he have --
Dwayne jenkins
was the last survivor
Of the
rose park mine disaster.
[ coughing ]
When they brought him
to the surface six days later,
His wife, ella,
was waiting for him.
They lived together
for 30 years,
And they raised
a family.
now, as you were
dwayne jenkins,
Annie was ella.
Billy.
[ exhales ]
That's a lot to take in.
I know.
you have time.
There's a condition
called nystagmus
That only affects miners.
When they spend
too long underground,
Their eyes lose the ability
to detect light.
And annie?
Well, there's a theory
Among believers
in reincarnation
That, um, some souls can choose
to, uh, travel together
Through the generations.
Romantic.
uh-huh.
And so now
you're a believer.
Hell no.
But you referred him
to this woman, louisa,
For a series
of past-life regressions?
it's not what i believe.
it's what billy believes.
His vision's already started
to clear, by the way.
Well, i tend to believe
in miracles.
[ exhales ]
Yeah. indeed.
Hey, wouldn't it be nice
If all our, uh, shortcomin
and indiscretions
Could be corrected
in another life?
You mean like a do-over?
[ laughs ]
Yeah, that'd be great.
[ scanner beeps ]
Carl.
Jack.
Louisa knox tells me
you're a very old soul.
She would know.
[ chuckles ]
When did you first suspect
billy was mixing up
Past- and present-life
memories?
After i talked
to hearst.
And during the intake,
In describing
the construction accident,
Billy said that he thought
he was clear of the pit.
It's a mining term.
Ah. i should have picked up
on that.
Ah.
you should have.
But you obviously
do believe.
Here's what
i don't get --
You let me stumble
around the truth,
While u were denying it
the whole time.
Only a practitioner
with no regard for his career
Would go on record
for having treated a patient
for past-life trauma.
[ chuckles ]
Kind of thing could come back
and bite you in the ass.
That's good advice.
[ chuckles ]
You should listen
to me more, jack.
You ever again
withhold information
That's relevant to the care
of a patient on this ward,
And either you or i
will be out.
Louisa also mentioned something
about lineage.
Oh ho ho, no!
[ both laugh ]
Ready to go?
Yep.
He called
about an hour ago.
You were right.
I needed to be ready
to listen.
What did he say?
"keep up the good work."
Congratulations.
he did leave a message
for you.
for me?
[ chuckles ]
well, what -- what was it?
"stay tuned.
Big changes are comin'."
You won't reconsider?
Quitting felt too right.
Uh...
Just so you know,
if we'd never met
Or, uh, gotten involved,
I'd be doing
the exact same thing.
It's time to go home.
Well, you knew
what my answer would be.
I was pretty sure.
Hey.
Yocan't feel like you're
the one being rejected here.
You know
where to find me.
[ door opens ]
[ door closes ]
[ doorbell buzzing ]
[ exhales sharply ]
Rebecca?
Mm.
[ moans softly
[ exhales sharply ]
[ moans softly ]
Rebecca?
Mm.
It's gonna be okay.
Sync and part of transcription by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net