-==זזאדנאצפ°חדחי·מן׳==-
±¾׳צה»½צ¹©ס§ן°½»בק£¬סן½ףדףתילעµףדם¾
???
??
hurry!
???
??
i won't ,i won't.
???
??
rebecca, ???
no, i think i ...
???
no,i'd ...
jack
don't talked him.
rebecca?
beccie
jack
rebecca
rebecca?
???
it's ok.
i'm right here.
gallagher, rebecca.
schizophrenia.
???
??
?? like
???
??
lady ??? coffee
yeah, thank you.
???
the ??
how ??? talk about?
how ??? come back
and i thought
even ???
can you tell me what happened this morning exactly?
i heard ???
???
what can you doing?
jefferson, clayton.
post-traumatic stress disorder.
???
??
??? problems.
don't tell ???
what???
rebecca, who's there?
rebecca?
it's okay.
they can wait.
whoever it is,
okay?
is james coming here?
they're flying together.
the whole family.
you don't have to see them
if you don't want to.
how do i look?
you're a mes
but with potential.
amazing potential.
mm-hmm.
everything will be different
this time.
is there any chance
that the shot was accidental?
no, he changed hands.
what do you mean,
he changed hands?
clay's right-handed.
when i came
down the stairs,
he was hding the gun
in his right hand.
then he took the gun
in his left to fire.
he was so calm
about it.
it was no accident.
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
ביע½ µתע»¼¾ µת11¼¯
-=זזאדנ׳צה»׳י=-
ך±¼הצב£÷אןצ×
and clay jefferson --
how's he doing?
very good.
the surgeon said
that he would retain 70% to 80%
of the use of his hand
with therapy and treatment.
has he been told?
yes, and he understood
that i didn't detect
any great relief.
suicidal?
i can't rule it out,
but instinct says no --
the self-mutilation
was just so specific.
does he constitute
a threat to his wife and son?
well, having fired the weapon
four times inside his home,
the answer
would have to be yes.
where did the other
three shots go?
into the diorama.
he built a full-scale model
of the battlefield.
so, who filed the complaint --
the wife?
no, the neighbors.
they called the police
when they heard the gunfire.
i get the sense that everyone
would be very happy
to see this go away.
why is he not at the v.a.?
his choice.
they have
private medical insurance
through his wife, laney,
who teaches at the high school.
so, 72 hours.
jack, i really need your help
with this one.
i tried to do
the intake.
but he can't remember a thing,
and he refuses to try.
he just refuses to see his wife,
even his little boy.
i just find him
completely impenetrable.
we'll have a go.
ah, mr. jefferson,
this is dr. gallagher.
maybe you can tell him
why you're here.
i'm here so that you can
put your "x" in the box
next to post-traumatic stress
and feel like you've done
your good deed for the day.
you have ptsd?
we all do.
didn't you know?
crazy ex-killers,
violent and unpredictable --
uncle sam's
dirty little secrets.
if we had any decency,
we would have died over there
and become
true american heroes,
instead of dragging our problems
back to your doorstep.
it's a nice speech --
think it up while you
were lying there?
clay, have, um --
have you changed your mi
about seeing laney?
keep my family
out of this.
when did you leave
the army?
it's in the file.
i'd rather hear
you tell me.
the spoken word
has got an emotional content.
that way i can get
a real good bearing
on how much
of a nut case you are.
discharged six months ago,
two weeks after i was released
from the hospital
for my injuries.
i don't have ptsd.
it's just easier for you
to think that.
so, it was
a rational decision
to unload a weapon
at your wife and child
and blow a hole
in your hand?
i'm getting real sick
of your bogus questions.
maybe we should
just come back later.
i'm still
kind of curious...
...about what he's got
in the basement.
man:
go, go, go, go!
it's just a hobby.
oh, hi, sweetheart.
oh. oh, jackie.
hi, mum.
where's your luggage?
we left them at the hotel,
but i've --
i've brought some clothes
for becky.
sure.
hello, james.
hello, son.
you're looking well.
i am well.
she's waiting for you.
all right.
how did she find you?
well, she called,
and, you see,
i told her where i lived,
where i worked.
i think it sink in.
she walked over.
has she talked
about the attack?
she hasn't said much.
some people tried to
steal her food.
she's got some cuts,
abrasions,
cracked ribs,
some bruising.
is she still having
conversations with herself?
still crazy, sorry to report --
very disappointing.
it's just a question, darling,
just a question.
who -- who's she?
jack:
that's dr. chloe artis.
she's a resident.
she's -- she's very talented.
ah.
and what was she doing?
establishing
a therapeutic relationship.
very attractive girl.
you're still single,
right?
you offering me
some fatherly advice?
i don't --
i don't understand
why i can't go
in there, jack.
it's easier for becky to focus
on one person at a time.
[ sighs ]
you know what?
i'm -- i'm going in there,
i mean, just to say hello.
hey.
you look
so gorgeous.
[ laughs ]
jack said i was a mess.
he's a doctor.
what do doctors know?
yeah, i'm sorry.
doesn't she
look gorgeous?
she seems safe.
dr. gallagher?
major.
i'm here about clay jefferson --
arlen rawlins.
is thisan official visit
well, i know clay.
i was one of his
commanding officers in iraq.
he's a fine young man --
served his country
with distinction.
how's he doing?
i'm curious
how you know he was here.
our patient files
are confidential.
or at least i thought
they were.
well, it's nothing
cloak-and-dagger.
clay receives
medical disabilities,
and the injury to his hand
prompted an inquiry.
that's all.
from whom?
i thought you might like
to see clay's service record.
i thought
it might be useful,
give you
some additional insight.
thank you
for the personal delivery.
the army takes care
of its own.
even after they've left?
bonds of loyalty
formed between soldiers
serving in wartime
transcends
formalities of status.
there's nothing in here
about ptsd.
when he was
in the hospital,
he was being treated
for his physical injuries.
ptsd was never diagnosed.
now, for the record,
i'm not one of these people
who doesn't believe in
the disease or its seriousness.
in fact, i am very familiar
with the work you've done
with veterans
in your vermont clinic.
it's commendable.
you seem to be familiar
with a lot of things, major.
i try to stay informed.
i know that clay will receive
the care he needs here, doc.
anything i can do to assist,
just ask.
thank you.
woman on p.a.:
orderly to ward two.
what have i done now?
nothing yet.
preemptive strike?
did your parents
get here yet?
parent, stepfather.
oh, god.
spare me the family drama.
what's your plan
with becky?
as soon as she gets
a little stronger,
i'll transfer her
to a long-term-care facility.
narrowed it down to two --
they're both excellent.
great physical eonments,
top staff.
who've already agreed
to let you
puppet-master her recovery
from afar?
you know, just a guess.
what of it?
i'm worried
about your focus,
for your sake
as well as the hospital's.
i'll find the right balance,
nora.
where are
these facilities?
one's north of san diego.
the other's in ojai.
i'll see her
on my days off and vacations.
i'll give you
plenty of notice.
and no time for yourself.
i don't see it
as a burden.
it's actually more
of a gift.
and look
on the bright side.
i finally
get to buy a car.
what's that for?
for a little.
clay: i can walk.
regulations -- i know you know
about regulations.
if i wanted to take off,
how would you stop me?
recent surgery,
major trauma --
you might not be as fast
as you think.
i wouldn't run from you.
i'd run through you.
well, given your youth
and your training,
you'd probably take me
in a fair fight.
???
but that's
not the point.
what is?
you can threaten me,
insult me, ignore me.
you can do
all those things.
but you won't shake me,
so you might as well
stop trying.
why did you decide
on a military career?
i'm third-generation army.
i bleed khaki.
at least i did.
i spent my teens
on naval bases.
where?
south carolina,
new england, d.c. area --
my stepfather.
he was, uh..
he's retired two years ago.
he was a vice admiral.
[ clears throat ]
annapolis man.
i got a little problem
with you, clay.
why's that?
well, if you don't open up,
your whole evaluation
is gonna have to be solely based
on your actions.
i'll take what i deserve.
what you think you deserve.
i might have
a different opinion.
see, mental disease,
disorders, phobias,
whatever you
want to call them
they can be traced back
as far as genetics,
but they can also be
the body's reaction to stress.
there's a reason
you wanted to hurt yourself.
and it's got
to start somewhere.
what do you want to know?
i want you to bookend
your memory loss for me --
the last thing you remember
before you don't
and the first thing
you remember after.
man:
go, go, go, go, go!
my platoon
was taking fire.
rpg! down, down,
down, down, down!
look out!
left two wounded with the medic
back on the road.
we got pinned down.
and that's
when it happened.
sonny!
sonny went ahead.
next thing,
everything exploded --
maybe an i.e.d.
i woke up in the hospital
in the green zone.
sonny didn't make it.
sonny?
first lieutenant
sonny bostock --
my best friend.
a commander of yours
dropped by to see me today.
major arlen rawlins.
who?
mum: i love it.
ah, it lacks soul.
[ laughs ]
no.
what it lacks
is a woman's touch.
oh, don't go there.
[ laughs ]
i'm your mother.
i can go there.
thank you, sweetie.
i guess some things
never change.
cheers
what are her chances,
realistically?
i mean, will she ebe
able to live an ordinary life?
well, leshoot
for extraordinary.
is that optimism
or determination?
[ laughs ]
both.
how's life, mum?
better now.
james has a job.
did you know?
no.
yeah, he's consulting with a --
for a defense contractor.
and -- retirement
didn't suit him.
we're doing very well,
in fact.
that's great.
he's a fine man,
your father.
he was a fine man
who died a long time ago.
oh, jack,
you are so stubborn.
i don't want to have this
conversation with you anymore.
tomorrow, when you
drop by to see becky,
have them come find me.
i'd like to go over
her transfer plans.
of course.
i worry about you.
i want you to be happier.
we found her.
she's safe.
and she'll finally get
the care she needs.
okay.
laney:
why won't he see us?
i was gonna ask you
the same thing.
i don't know.
shame, i guess.
i mean, he loves nathan
every bit as much as i do.
the idea of hurting him
would make him sick.
you know, at first i --
i was convinced
that i didn't want him
around us anymore.
now i --
i just want him home.
yeah.
so, what do you think?
when did he
start building it?
about six weeks ago.
any idea
what set it off?
4vyeah,
he ran into moon
at the hospital
after one of the checkups.
moono's moon?
he was a friend
from his platoon.
he was one of the men wounded
during the initial attack.
so, moon
told him something?
he said that clay came back
to the humvees to check on him.
this was after sonny
had been killed.
so suddenly,
that couple of seconds
that he couldn't remember
turned into a couple of hours.
and the next day,
he started hauling in bags
of sand and cement.
what -- what are you gonna do
with the diorama?
hire someone
to haul it away.
hold off on that
for a while.
i miss you.
you shouldn't be here.
you all right?
uh-huh. perfect.
can you do a favor
for me?
anything.
be nice to james.
mum put you
up to that?
no.
remember when mum first
brought him home for dinner?
he was an ass.
he was frightened.
of what?
us.
will you go back
to sleep?
okay.
you went to my home?
you took pictures of my work?
laney misses you.
so does your son.
i can't go back there
after what's happened.
i think you've punished
yourself enough. come here.
which one of these
little fellows is you?
come here, lieutenant.
this guy?
yeah.
what about sonny?
well, um,
he was supposed to
stay back with the wounded,
seal off the road.
i don't know
where he came from.
all right.
so, this iu.
where were you
leading your team?
there.
the gunshots
came from the roof.
i saw muzzle flashes
and movement.
all right.
there's something else
i don't understand --
this, this, and those.
bullet holes.
real bullet holes?
i'd been working
the model all night.
everything felt wrong.
i got frustrated,
and i lost it.
all right,
so, you fire three times.
you hear a sound.
you turn.
your cover with your loaded
weapon. it's nathan.
he thought
i was playing with him.
but it was sonny
that i saw.
clay!
all right,
so, you lower your weapon.
nathan's fine.
he's safe.
laney's safe.
no harm done.
but you switch the gun to your
other hand, and you fire.
what are you thinking?
it ends here.
hey.
hey
[ clears throat ]
what's all this?
uh, it's a patient --
army lieutenant wounded in iraq.
those are of a model he built
to re-create a situation
in which he was wounded.
he's got
some memory loss.
i'm trying to help him
fill in the blanks.
where's mum?
she's still with becky.
how is she?
she's not too good today.
she's confused.
i don't understand what --
what happened.
well, i told you.
she goes in and out.
she's doing really well, but
she's a long way from stable.
look, james, i'm --
i'm kind of under the pump.
can we make it for later?
we can eat at the loft.
oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
that -- that sounds fine.
so, this is -- this is meant
to replicate a combat situation?
yes. yes, it is.
hmm.
can you take a look at these?
you can take them with you.
yeah.
[ sighs ]
all right.
what's so interesting?
well, you know,
old habi die hard.
when you see something,
i'd like to know.
your patient was
the commander, right?
yeah, it's --
he's here.
yeah, well,
he's a lousy soldier, jack.
well, he's west point.
what?
well, all right,
you tell me
exactly what
i'm looking at here.
all right, so,
clay's leading his men
in -- in this direction
towards this building here
when they start coming
under heavy fire.
right, and this is the target
structure, right?
yeah.
well, why would he
have his men enfilade?
i'm sorry, what?
well, lined up to take enemy
fire along their longest axis.
that's bad?
that's fatal --
the easiway for the enemy
to inflict maximum casualties.
you h...
all right, here.
see?
these are the good guys,
okay?
yeah.
i'm the bad guys.
how can i miss?
i miss the guy in front,
i take down the guy behind him.
and it makes return fire
even harder
because the guys
in the back of the line
have to fire through
their own men at the enemy.
see what i mean?
it's fatal.
you know, i'm gonna wait
for you outside.
it shouldn't be long.
come in,
dr. gallagher.
gallagher,
how's our boy?
our boy hasn't the faintest idea
who you are.
well, it's a big army.
there was
no insurance inquiry.
are you accusing me
of something, doctor?
well...you're keeping
your eye on clay
long after his discharge.
what do you want,
rawlins?
i just want
clay and his family
to have a good life.
he's earned it.
that's all?
this is satellite imagery
of the baghdad neighborhood
where clay and his men
were attacked --
one taken shortly before,
the other just after.
no explanation?
by helping you,
i hope to help clay.
he may have a decision
to make.
regarding what?
jack, meet moon.
nice to meet you, sir.
you, too.
private --
just moon will do.
moon, what do you think
of lieutenant jefferson?
he's very cool
for an oer.
when i was hit,
he was right there.
lieutenant's good people.
lieutenant bostock --
sonny?
good people,
excellent.
now, nobody likes to talk ill
of the dead, of course.
that's right.
you know,
we're both doctors, though,
so whatever you say
is completely confidential.
we're trying to help
lieutenant jefferson.
he's having a hard time.
james: florida.
there's a facility
very near our home,
extremely highly rated,
also near the beach.
and your mom and i
would be 10 minutes away.
when you come to visit,
you stay with us.
there's a guest room.
but best of all,
as becky progresses,
if they let her out on weekends,
she could come home.
before any of this happens,
we'd like you
to check out the facility
and consult with the doctors.
we'd rely on you.
well, this is,
uh...unexpected.
[ sighs ]
she's our daughter, jack.
we -- we've talked about this
for years.
it was a major factor
in buying our home
and locating where we did.
why didn't you tell me
about this?
it's just speculation.
we had no way of knowing
under what circumstances
becky would be found,
or even if.
i don't know.
i -- this is gonna take me
a little bit of time to --
how lore you guys
in town?
jack.
please don't just reject
this suggestion out of hand.
i'm not gonna reject
anything...yet.
look, i realize that
we've sprung this on you,
but it deserves
serious consideration.
and i'll give it
look...guys, really,
i've -- i've got an early start
in the morning,
and it's getting late.
can i call you back?
yeah, okay, thank you.
i need legal advice.
okay, i know a number
of good attorneys.
just listen
for a minute.
okay.
they want to take becky
back to florida and put
her in treatment there.
and i think they have
becky's power of attorney,
authorizing themo make
medical decisions on her behalf.
and you want to fight that?
how do i keep her
in california?
um, get becky to revoke
the power of attorney,
file suit on her behalf.
your medical credentials
should help your case.
she's here now.
it's gonna take some time
for your parents
to get a court to act.
by that time, hopefully,
she'll be settled
into a facility
that you've chosen.
i need those names.
how do you think
the stress of a legal battle
will affect becky?
maybe she doesn't
have to know about that part.
it could get pretty ugly.
it'll be what it is.
why else did you build it, clay,
if not for this?
it ends here.
sonny!
[ explosion ]
man:
man, we got to go!
that's the last thing
i remember.
maybe these will help.
that's right
there was...a home.
i ran through it
a thousand times.
i couldn't figure
how i could let us
get caught out in the open
like that.
????
neither.
the explosion.
i thought it killed sonny.
that was his grenade.
man: move!
get inside now.
what did you see?
bodies.
mostly women and kids.
moon told us
that on a previous mission,
it seems sonny rolled a grenade
into a house
without looking inside
to see who was there.
sonny was firing
into the bodies...
sonny!
what are you doing?!
...making sure
they were dead.
there was a boy, maybe...
maybe 5 or 6.
blood on his face.
sonny put his rifle
to the boy's head.
i tried to stop him.
don't do it, sonny.
i killed my best friend.
you knew what i did
all along?
nope. no one else
was inside the room.
and now that you do...
you can't tell anyone?
patient/doctor thing.
right.
but i can.
we thought laney
should hear this, too.
we filled her in
on some of the background.
so, here's what we got
from moon.
soon after you
entered the house,
reinforcements arrived,
and the enemy fire melted away.
that's when rawlins showed up,
went inside where you were.
and no one else was allowed
inside the house.
i remember.
he -- um,
he ordered me to carry on,
said there'd have to be
an investigation.
sometime after that,
a car showed up.
someone handed rawlins
some gear in a duffel bag,
and he went
back into the house.
when he came out,
the duffel was empty.
i saw the detonator.
that's when you went
running back to the place.
i thought the boy
was still in there.
no. he'd already been
medevacked out.
and the whole place was
vaporized -- no more building.
that was
the second explosion,
the one that caused
your injuries.
and the amnesia?
post-traumatic
stress disorder.
it's all over,
baby, okay?
it's for the army
to decide.
nathan.
these little fellas
are for you.
come here.
here you go.
there you go.
attaboy.
but if it
were nathan?
what?
what if it were
an unnamed soldier...
aiming the gun
at nathan's head?
would you really condemn the man
that saved your son?
come here.
no crimicharges filed.
he'll receive
outpatient therapy.
he has decided,
for the good of his family,
to let the past
stay in the past.
case closed.
you knew the story
all along.
we both got to the same place
by different roads.
someday, god willing,
we'll make it
so that good men
like clay jefferson
will never again be placed
in impossible situations.
until then, i'll look
for small victories.
come here.
that's it.
i've got you.
זזאדנ׳צה»׳י
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
»¶ף­¼ףטכ
www.tvsubtitles.net