www.flamby70.com
Synchro :
Flamby70
His handiwork, i assume.
mahatma gallagher.
He mentioned something
about shintoism.
celebration of
nature's spirits and ancestors.
Nice touch.
So, what's his story, anyway ?
What do you mean?
Divorced, attached,
fugitive from the law, c.i.a. mole ?
He's currently uttached,
severe commitment disorder,
exercise junkie,
peter pan syndrome.
Not that i've paid much attention.
He has a seriously smokinbody.
Not that i've noticed.
Hey, guys.
beautiful day,
isn't it?
So...
Are you ready for some
patient-doctor bonding ?
Well, 're waiting for rounds.
we just need to get in six north.
- Great, then...
- And the director
usually accompanies us
on the rounds.
Gotcha.
- Doctor, i need a little help.
- Talk to me, gorgeous.
Ranier, Melissa.
Third trimester.
Here visiting relatives.
She was alone shopping at the grove
when she jusstarted having
contractions and faied.
just took her b.p.
she's slightly hypertensive.
okay. thank you.
You busy later ?
But i'm pretty sure you're not.
I'm dr. moore. How are you doing?
I started getting contractions,
and...then i got
so light-headed.
i'm only seven months.
i'm so scared.
Is my baby okay ?
well,
let's take a look.
where are the patients?
What's going on ?
relay races?
is this supposed to take
the place of morning rounds?
Of course not. rounds are good.
Actually, veronica,
instigating a morning fitness
regime is not a bad idea.
exercise has been shown
to elevate
brain-derived
neurotrophic factors.
right, but this more
than encouraging the patients
to work out.
this is a trust exercise.
trusting
other patients?
no.
trusting their doctors.
the three-legged race
is up next.
wait. hey... we're...
you mean we're supposed to...?
you can't be serious !
actually,
it looks like fun.
unfortunately, my back.
i'm in heels.
guys, whether these patients
are here on a 72-hour hold
or they've committed
themselves voluntarily,
they've all put their well-being
in our hands.
if they don't believe
that you're willing to get
down and dirty with them,
how can you expect them
to confide in you?
and, people,
this is not a suggestion.
this is gonna be a little cold,
and i'm sorry.
it's okay.
i've done this a million times.
i'm gonna get you something
to stop those contractions, ok ?
back in a flash.
Ready !
on your mark!
Set !
races ?
it's cool.
i just called you. i need you down
at the e.r. for a psych consult.
really?
yeah.
absolutely.
let's go.
so, what's up?
we, this patient informed us
she was seven months along.
she fainted
when contractions started.
she has hormone levels
that are raised
and cervical softening.
well, then why -- why are you
asking for a psych consult?
call an ob-gyn.
take a look
at the ultrasound.
what's wrong
with this picture?
i don't get it.
i can't even see a baby.
there is no baby.
Pseudocyesis
Is she still pregnacy ?
is she still in the e.r.?
- I ordere some blood work.
- Why ?
just to buy some time.
i read about this
in med school,
but i never thought i would
actually see it firsthand.
and she actually looks
pregnant?
Not just looks.
she has all
the classic mptoms
right down to hormonal levels,
water retention.
the mind speaks.
the body answers.
But for seven months ?
is there a husband?
she's wearing a ring.
So, what should  do with her?
well, i told her there was
no room in maternity.
i just -- i wasn't sure
how far to push at the intake.
we should go easy on her.
something tells me we shouldn't
burst her bubble just yet.
Let's get her to the psych ward.
is there any other business ?
want to grab some breakfast?
i'm buying.
thanks. I have a budget meeting.
try not to, piss anybody
important off today.
- really go...
- he baby cakes.
Denny.
what's going on?
it's thursday.
i have a standing engagement
at the hospital, remember?
yeah, i blew it off.
you know, i'd much rather play
for the kids here.
what's the matter?
what about those producers
you said were really hot?
those guys
are all the same.
they're all part
of the same corporate machine.
they make
a ton of promises,
and they never deliver.
so, what?
you want me to go?
no.
i just -- i just question
your priorities.
that's all.
hey, if you think i'm being
irresponsible, jt say so.
hey, we'll set you up
outside.
i'll call down to pediatrics,
let them know you're here.
great. thanks, malcolm.
i got to go.
you gonna come by later
and hear me play?
yeah, if i can.
so, i understand
you're from out of town.
yes.
florence, arizona.
and we're here visiting
my husband's family.
how long
have you been married?
it'll be two years
this spring.
is this
your first pregnancy?
yes.
and... have you...
have you picked out a name ?
- Sean.
- Oh, that's nice.
tell me, melissa,
have you experienced
any other discomfort
during your pregnancy --
morning sickness,
spotting?
no.
actually, everything's been
pretty easy up until this trip.
were you working
when you got pregnant?
yes. i was waitressing
when i met richard.
we started dating.
we went on this whirlwind trip
around europe.
we got married
at the hotel cipriani.
- That's in venice.
- Yes.
it's a beautiful hotel.
isn't it?
And...
well, a month later...
we both wanted
a big family.
i come from one.
richard's an only child.
- Is richard on his way here?
- Yes.
they called him from the e.r.
and left him a message.
he'll be here soon.
can you hold on a minute?
the --
excuse me.
- sure.
- i'll be back very soon.
becky,
hold on a minute.
the reception
is no good inside.
do you have any children?
oh, well, i'm -- i'm --
my husnd and i have talked
about it, of course,
and, uh, even though
the clock is ticking --
and it's ticking --
there just never seemed to be
the perfect time.
is he a doctor, too?
no. he's a...
musician.
oh, wow!
how wonderful!
what does he play?
the piano, jazz piano,
and he composes, too.
must be amazing
to have talent like that.
i wish i did.
we've been playing beethoven
and bach sonatas for the baby.
oh, that's nice.
so, melissa...
do you have the name
of your ob-gyn at home
so we can get in contact
with him or her?
actually, it's richard,
my husband.
okay.
he's got the whole world in his hands
he's got the whole wide world in his hands
he's got the whole world...
Thanks for not hanging up.
i'm outside in the garden area.
it's really nice.
there's jasmine here, beck,
loads of it.
it's a bit like the isle
of wight. do you remember?
you said you loved the smell
and you never wanted to leave.
rebecca, you know,
i was thinking...
it would be really nice
if you could stop by. We could...
he's got the whole world in his hands
he's got you and me brother, in his hands
he's got you and me, brother, in his hands
he's got the whe world
in his hands
he's got the whole world
in his ha-a-nds
All right !
it's the perfect alibi.
what is?
well, having your husband
as your ob-gyn.
that's assuming
her husband actually exists.
it could be
just another delusion.
well,
we'll know soon enough.
dr. delusion
is on his way over here.
it's just so sad,
i mean, believing you're about
to give birth when you're not.
it's also incredible.
cessation
of the menstrual cycle,
abdominal enlargement,
breast enlargement,
quickening galactorrhea,
cervical softening,
uterine enlargement.
yeah,
but how is it possible
that the abdominal enlargement
is so massive?
excess bowel gas,
uterine distensi,
bladder retention.
could be aot of things.
but she's not gonna be able to
keep this up much longer.
Help !
My water just broke !
Hey Melissa, feeling better ?
yes. thank you.
I told you already !
i'm looking for my wife !
oh, Richard !
oh, thank god you're here !
i'm so sorry.
are you okay?
yes.
She's fine now, mr. Ranier.
I'm dr. Hayden-Jones.
it's dr. ranier.
who's in charge here?
you're the idiot who put my wife
in the psych ward?
what the hell is wrong
with you people?
i want her transferred.
i need an sma 20,
cbcc, beta-hch,
and an abdominal
ultrasound stat!
why are you
just standing there?
my wife is seven months pregnant !
this baby could be in distress !
have you all lost your minds ?
i need to speak
to the hospital administrator.
now!
Good idea. I'll call her.
stay with them.
are you okay?
yes.
- Yes ? You feel all right ?
- I'm so glad you're here.
you look so beautiful.
no way.
this guy's legit.
Dr. Richard Ranier licensed physician
with an impeccable reputation.
i suppose it's possible
he never examined his own wife.
she told me she'd been
under his care exclusively.
she's allegedly had
regular checkups.
i mean,
she'even had amnio.
and we're absolutely sure
that she's not pregnant?
yes, carl, we're sure.
how could he have lied to her
for seven months?
probably kept her
pretty isolated.
so, now what?
well,
i'll tell you one thing,
he's not gonna let us
hold his wife without a fight.
so, don't fight it.
in a couple of months,
they'll figure out
the wholthing for themselves
without our interference.
it's not interference, carl.
it's called treatment.
just let them go!
Nice, carl, let her give birth,
raise the kid,
send it off to college,
and sit back and wait
for the imaginary grandkids.
oh. he's screaming his head off
and asking for you again.
Well, might as well
face the music.
pure folly
to keep this farce alive.
you're a gens, carl.
pure folly.
that's exactly what it is.
followy lead.
i'll follow you anywhere.
because
that very important person
you weren't supposed to
piss off today...
that would be me.
i am so sorry for
all the confusion, dr. ranier.
i'm nora skoff,
departmental administrator.
we, of course,
welcome all visiting physicians
to whartonemorial,
and i promise
you will receive
the full measure
of our professional courtesy.
the maternity ward,
unfortunately, remains full.
are those her tests?
the, fetus does not appear
to be in distress,
and... i can assure you
that the birth is not imminent.
there's been no dilation.
well, the blood work
can't be right.
melissa said that you did
an ultrasound?
yeah. thank you.
whoever did this ultrasound
is a moron.
the image is so blurred,
it's useless.
i-i personally did an ultrasound
on melissa just days ago.
I have it. Here it is.
okay.
there you go.
sweetheart, i am so sorry that
i couldn't get here earlie
it's okay. i'm fine.
the baby's fine.
i just --
i lost control
of my bladder,
and i thought
that my water had broken.
it happens.
sweetheart, there's no reason
to be ashamed.
come here.
it's a good thing
that your water didn't break.
it's too soon.
the baby is protected.
and there's no chance
for infection.
sean is healthy and happy.
what you need now is rest.
i'll make the arrangements
to take you home.
i'll be right back.
well, my wife
has had quite a scare,
but i know her very well,
and she's ready to travel now.
so, if you'll just give me
the release forms...
actually, we'd like
to keep her overnight
- Just as a precaution.
- No.
no, i've already put up with
what i consider to be
gross incompetence
on behalf of this hospital.
that ultrasound was shoddy.
You're absolutely right.
let's schedule another one
tomorrow morning.
and there are
liability issues.
i'm sure you can understand,
doctor.
fine.
fine. i'll do the ultrasound
myself...
Today.
excuse me.
may i?
i'd rather you didn't.
i'm expecting a call any minute.
no. i don't mind.
hey, honey.
i'm just taking
a quick lunch break.
how did the opening go?
that's great.
i miss you, too.
is it snowing there?
perfect. t weather's
always perfect here.
but it's not new york.
i know. i can't wait.
i got to go, too.
i'll call you later.
love you.
long-distance romance...
doomed to failure.
unless...
unless what?
you have a lot
of meaningless but hot sex
with skilled but
emotnally detached partners.
i'm available.
arturo, seriously,
what do you think
is gonna happen here?
seriously,
i think that you're gonna come
to your senses and realize...
do you honestly believe
that you're the personal panacea
to my lesbianism,
that i'm suddenly gonna realize
i'm straight
and want to jump
on top of you?
Yeah.
One night.
that's all it'll take.
maybe two.
i can work with you
on that.
stand up.
drop your pants.
i want to see it.
show me what i'm missing.
rock my world.
not that i'm shy, honey,
and god knows i had
no reason to be, but...
That would be
highly unprofessional.
Exactly. Unprofessional.
like you coming on to me
at every opportunity.
there.
there's the head.
it's beautiful.
melissa, look! look!
there's a hand.
healthy heartbeat.
healthy fetus.
okay.
get dressed.
we're leaving.
i'm sorry, doctor,
but i can't allow your wife
to leave just yet.
you don't have
that authority.
i absolutely do.
- We're leaving.
- No, you're not.
Melissa's my wife,
Ok ?
you don't tell me
at to do!
melissa is your wife,
but this is my ward.
i say when
a patient's discharged.
security !
will he live ?
probably, but he's never gonna
play the trumpet again.
glad you guys
are enjoying this.
you did say he wouldn't leave
without a fight.
you're fine.
later, slugger.
doctor, that thing
you asked me about earlier.
the thing...
oh, no.
i'll... i'll find you.
security is holding him.
he's claiming self-defense.
yeah, right.
and just so
as we're clear,
if he hadn't sucker punched me,
i could ha taken him easy.
Jack, you can press charges.
no... no. come on.
the guy's got
enough problems.
you're right.
Folie à deux.
translation from the french,
"folly for two"...
"a rare
shared psychotic disorder
"when an otherwise
healthy person,
- The secondary partner..."
- Melissa.
"...begins believing
the delusions
"of someone with whom they have
a close relationship,
- The primary partner..."
- Richard.
"...who is already suffering
from a psychotic disorder
with prominent delusions."
So, melissa believed
she was pregnant,
and he came to believe it,
as well?
other way around.
richard's the primary.
he convinced her she was
pregnant. he was her doctor.
so she had no reason
to question him. took the bait.
She's got a bun in the oven.
if richard's
the dominant partner,
then melissa's delusion's
more fragile.
easier to convince
that the baby's not there.
and with richard,
it's gonna be a lot more tricky.
but why?
what put this in motion?
melissa couldn't get pregnant,
so he just invented it?
that is exactly
the right question.
why don't you grab chloe
and do some digging?
i can't keep doing this.
i can't keep being here
and going home to denny.
you know that.
if you say so.
i really mean it
this time.
it's over.
you don't believe me,
do you?
no.
Dr. ranier quit hipractice
in phoenix seven months ago,
presumably when he found out
his wife was pregnant.
he told everyone
that he wanted to spend
every moment with melissa
until she gave birth
to ensure the health
of their child.
according
to phoenix general,
the ultrasound richard gave you
is not two days old
but almost two years old.
so, this ultrasound...
It's not hers.
melissa told me and veronica
this was her first child.
but she also said
she got pregnant
about a month
after her honeymoon,
which was
almost two years ago.
looks like whave
some more digging to do.
goody-goody.
hey, wendy.
how are you doing?
do you think
you might be able to
put your head underwater
today?
Aquaphobic. Selachophobic.
oh, i-i don't think so.
well, that's okay.
that's okay.
you can always try again
tomorrow.
ultrasound taken
two years ago,
definitely hers.
she has a child?
it was never carried to term.
it was a molar twin.
oh, god.
when did you give melissa
the neuroleptic?
about an hour ago.
it should be working by now.
good.
well, when you're done here,
let's go have a chat with her.
Heard about
the folie à deux.
interesting, huh?
very.
spoke to nora about possibly
writing up a journal article.
it's good advertising
for the hospital.
Taking one for the team ?
Actually,
if i were the attending,
i might proceed
a little differently.
you see, the first thing i'd do
is i'd separate them.
the husband and the wife,
they're just finding
off of each other,
merging in their... mania.
under some circumstances,
you might be right,
but not this time.
well, you are in charge.
Yeah.
I'am.
Hi, melissa.
How are you feeling ?
sleepy.
And...
I'm a little warm.
that's the medication
we gave you.
it's supposed to relax you
a little bit.
do you remember
when we asked you
if this was
your first pregnancy ?
yes.
actually...
...there was another,
but i'd rather not
talk about it.
we know what happened,
melissa.
richard was so happy.
i got pregnant
right after we got married.
this isn't
his first marriage.
he tried with his ex-wife...
but she couldn't conceive.
you should have seen his face...
when the tests came back.
all his life,
he delivered babies.
Now...
He's finally gonna have
one of his own.
i lost this baby, too,
didn't i?
this time...
there was no baby.
it's okay, melissa.
Molar pregnancy.
It's pretty horrific.
two sperm fertilize
the same egg,
producing one healthy fetus
and one mass of cells
without the genetic material
to form one.
and that mass of cells
growing quickly
can overwhelm the healthy fetus,
literally devouring it.
that would shake
anybody's world.
it unhinged richard.
that's for sure.
i'd say that's what
set all this in motion.
if his delusion is so deep-seated,
how are you gonna break it ?
i'll think of something.
why does that not give me
a warm and fuzzy feeling?
can you hang on
a minute?
rebecca, i'm inside.
i can't hear you.
damn it.
she's still calling.
you'll find her.
is my husband still being held
in security?
yes, he is.
you know,
maybe you should press charges.
maybe he belongs in jail.
look what he d to me.
he wasn't
just my husband.
he was my doctor!
i mean, he knew i would believe
what he told me.
i'm so stupid.
i guesthat's what
he was depending on.
he's incapable
of depending on anything...
even his own mind.
he wants a baby
very badly.
and that's not
such a bad thing to want.
he divorced his first wife
because she couldn't give him
what he wanted.
he married me...
A younger woman,
A breeder,
'cause he was sure
i could do better.
he doesn't love me.
of course he does.
all this is just a product
of his disease.
to him, this all seems very,
very real.
no.
he doesn't love me.
he loves the baby more.
that's not true.
let me prove it to you.
i regret... no time for that now,
richard.
thank you.
it's okay.
melissa's
having contractions again,
and she's hypertensive.
the baby's in distress
and needs to come out now.
where is she?
she's in the o.r. being prepped
for an emergency c-section.
we have an anesthesiologist
and a surgeon on standby.
i presume you want to be present
at the delivery?
Yes. yeah, ye... of course.
I-i'll scrub in.
you okay?
i'm gonna be a father.
why so happy, arturo?
dr. gallagher has invited us
to be present
at the delivery
of the ranier baby.
the imaginary
ranier baby?
yeah.
that's the one.
Well better i get going later.
are you aware
of what's abouto happen?
vaguely.
and you intend
to let him proceed?
for now.
have you anticipated what
the board's reaction will be to this
Ill-conceived charade ?
i dn't planned
on discussing it with the board.
are you suggesting
that i should?
undoubtedly,
someone will.
i'm trying to protect you,
nora.
ani appreciate that, carl.
thank you for your support.
you put more than your reputation
on the line when you hired him.
- Whatever do you mean ?
- You know what i mean.
i seriously doubt you can handle
that kind of financial hit.
how did you find that out?
do you honestly believe
thers anything
going on in this hospital
that i don't know about?
i suppose not.
is that all?
no.
are we ready?
yes, doctor.
is the fetal
heart monitor on?
yes, doctor.
stabilized, 2 mics per kilo.
perhaps you'd like to make
the first incision.
You're going to feel sleepy now.
just wait.
we can't wait.
richard, the baby's in distress.
it needs to come out now.
Check the heart monitor
and the fetal monitor.
something's not --
it's not right here.
this is what you wanted.
make the incision.
no.
no, no, no, no.
please stop. just stop.
it's not right.
please.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's over now.
i would never
let anyone hurt you.
Never.
I love you.
Delusional. Shared Psychotic Disorder.
"Folie à Deux".
I love you, too.
Dr. ranier
voluntarily committed himself?
He knows he's sick.
Worst part's over.
You aren't gonna
say anything ?
About what ?
About the fact that you
booked a working o.r.
at the cost
of thousands of dollars
and were about to perform
an unauthorized c-section?
That you had real
surgical instruments in the room
and tried to put
a deadly weapon
in the hands
of a mentally ill person?
No.
I'm sorry i'm late.
I got something
i want you to listen to.
Is that new ?
Wrote it for you.
We talk about
social imperfections...
Is... is everything okay, baby ?
God, denny.
I-i...i don't know what to say. I...
I was so mad
when you came by today, and i...
and then i just saw you
with the kids, and...
they're great kids.
you know, maybe --
I don't know, maybe we should
start having some of our own.
You'd make a great mom.
and it's me
that wants it all to be now
to be somehow
cause it's me that wants it all
Wharton memorial. Dr. gallagher.
here.
- Yes.
- Thanks, mal.
She... she has been admitted.
Look, i assure you...
- Who left this ?
- A lady.
She asked if you
were here and dropped it off.
- When ?
- A couple of minutes ago.
What was she wearing ?
Damn it, malcolm. this is important.
what was she wearing ?
I'm sorry. I was so bus
i didn't even notice.
S-sorry. I'm so sorry.
www.flamby70.com
www.tvsubtitles.net