-What's wrong?
- Keeler.
He's bringing your ex-husband into this
debate, the investigation into his company.
Then face Keeler's lie with the truth and
trust that the people can tell the difference.
- What's going on? Where's Tony?
- He's been shot.
- How bad?
- He was hit in the neck. He's alive.
They're getting him to the hospital.
You're in command.
(distorted) Deliver Ram Ãn Salazar
to the Van Nuys Dam.
Whoever sent this message is
controlling Singer's movements.
We have two hours to find him
before they release the virus.
- What are you into, Kyle?
- These cops came to my apartment,
saying something about using me
to bring some disease into the country.
A disease?
Go! Run!
(screaming)
No!
- You going to see Salazar?
- Yeah.
- Dad said questioning him is a waste of time.
- Sitting around here is a waste of time.
I need you to generate
a prisoner transfer document.
- What's this about?
- I need to move Ram Ãn Salazar.
This has priority clearance.
No one at CTU's supposed to know.
Either I hand over Ram Ãn Salazar,
or his brother will release the virus.
I understand that this is an impossible
choice. I have another option for you.
Ram Ãn Salazar would be broken out
and delivered to him.
Sounds like quite a plan, Jack.
Who'll break Salazar out?
I will, sir.
This would be my last assignment.
If you play this cool
you're walking out of here now.
(alarm)
Open the cell blocks now.
Move!
Good evening to those on the East
Coast and good afternoon in the west.
Welcome to the first of three debates
between President Palmer
and Senator John Keeler.
We'll begin tonight with a two-minute
opening statement,
followed by the first question,
which will go to President Palmer,
this decided by a coin-flip
backstage just moments ago.
How you feeling?
Is that a medical question or a personal one?
- Both.
- I'm fine.
It'll be conducted
within the rules agreed to
by each member of the debate
and by the two campaigns.
Now we'll bring to the stage the candidates.
Ladies and gentlemen, Senator John Keeler.
(applause)
I'm sorry you have to deal with
my ex-husband's lies.
It's all right.
We have the truth on our side.
Ladies and gentlemen,
President David Palmer.
Senator Keeler, good evening.
I'm looking forward to discussing
some of the critical issues...
(yelling)
OK... when I tell you to,
you start fighting with me over the gun.
I gotta pull two guards off the main corridor.
OK, come on.
Help! Help! Help!
(Ram Ãn) Now!
That's enough! Enough!
Put on his uniform now.
I want a team at every security post.
Jack and Salazar are in east block.
- You partner's not my only problem.
- Warden, today he is.
He and Salazar need to be
contained and kept alive.
Want me to redeploy my men? I need
to know how real this terrorist threat is.
Salazar's brother will spread a virus into
the population unless we release him.
If we don't, the death toll will be
in the hundreds of thousands.
(low dispatch voice)
This is Mitchell. Tactical unit five, you are
now under the command of Agent Edmunds.
Thank you.
- Yeah?
- What the hell is going on over there?
- Jack's breaking Salazar out of prison.
- What?
He thinks he'll deliver him to Hector
and stop the virus from being released.
He's gonna get himself and Salazar killed.
I know, I know. I'm trying to protect him.
What about Kyle Singer?
- We're close to locating him.
- As soon as you do, call me.
If Jack knows we got the carrier
of the virus, he'll return Salazar.
Everyone is working on it.
- We'll find him.
- OK.
Negro?
I'm sorry, Linda.
Linda...
Am I gonna die?
It depends...
if they find us in time.
What do you mean?
The guy from the government.
He told my dad that I had
a couple more hours before l...
before I become contagious.
Maybe they'll find us by then.
You'll be OK.
Yeah... maybe.
- What are you doing?
- There must be some wires in here.
- What do you need wire for?
- Get you out of this.
Adam, look at this.
Got it from a Caltrans server.
Traffic camera right near the mall.
It's a blue shirt. Isn't that
what Kyle Singer was wearing?
Yeah. There's enough to enhance.
Release it to my screen.
Got it.
- Kim.
- Yes?
I need you a second.
- You got this?
- Yeah.
All right.
Something wrong?
Have you heard what's going on
at the prison?
No. Adam and I have been working
on finding Singer. Why? What is it?
- Your dad's trying to break out Salazar.
- What?
He's acting on his own authority.
He's trying to remove Salazar by force.
What you mean by "force"?
He started a prison riot to cover the escape.
- Why's he doing this?
- We're trying to figure that out.
- When did you last hear from him?
- About a half hour ago.
He asked me to issue a transfer order
for Ram Ãn Salazar,
and he gave me a password.
And you did it?
Yeah, he said Salazar needed
to be moved. This isn't true?
No, Kim, I'm sorry. Your dad lied to you.
Why would he do that?
He knew if he asked anybody else, they
would know he was violating protocol.
- What's gonna happen to him?
- We're gonna try to find him.
The best way out of this
is to find Kyle Singer.
Then your dad will give up Salazar.
So go back to work. Help Adam.
Yeah, sure.
We're clear!
They'll funnel their forces
through one entrance.
There must be another way, Jack.
The prisoners have taken control.
We have to fight our way through.
(gunfire)
Get ready.
(inmate) Pick him up! Come on!
Come on, get 'em on their feet!
- Come on, let's go, let's go!
- Move, move!
Hold your fire!
We got hostages, so back off!
Come on, man.
Move! Let's go!
Move!
Move it, move it!
..and in order to do this,
our reserves must be kept
and our fossil fuels must be conserved.
- Did you send me that Kalman filter?
- What?
- I need it to clean up that image.
- Shoot, I forgot. It's in my outbox.
How can you forget?
It's all you're working on.
I'm sorry. Look, I'm sending it
to you right now. Done.
We need to find Kyle Singer
before he's contagious.
I'm doing the best I can.
"The best I can" isn't what we do.
It's done or it's not.
So why are you lecturing me?
It's in your system.
(phone ringing)
- Kaufman.
- Is there a problem?
I need to make sure
things are running smoothly.
I haven't had a chance to brief you, but
Jack's created a situation over at the prison.
- What situation?
- He started a riot to free Salazar.
They're caught up in the middle of it.
Whoa.
He used Kim to create a transfer order
that started it, so cut her a little slack.
Um... yeah, OK, I understand.
We're all under a lot of pressure, so
let's find Kyle Singer before it's too late.
Yeah, OK. Thanks, Michelle.
Kyle, what are you doing?
There's no way out of here!
You don't deserve what happened.
I do.
If I die, the virus is dyin' with me.
- Kyle!
- (choking)
Kyle!
Put your feet on here!
Kyle, hold on.
(coughing)
Oh, Kyle.
A welcome-home party?
- You shouldn't be doing this.
- What are you talking about?
You've been running things.
Show Ram Ãn you're going to be his partner.
Not his caterer.
Why do you care? You don't want
to be involved in my business.
No, Papi. I care about you.
And I want you to get what you've earned.
(cellphone rings)
- Yes?
- It's me. Riot's still going on.
- But we know Ram Ãn's alive.
- Yeah.
But Bauer's gotta get him out soon.
CTU's getting close to finding Singer.
If they do, they'll never let Ram Ãn go.
- Then make sure they don't.
- I'm working on it.
Get it done.
That's him. That's Singer.
Is that a gun?
Yeah. Someone's got him.
We won't be able to get
the licence plate from the shot.
I'll get access to the traffic cameras.
See if we can find them again.
Michelle, we found Singer being driven
from the mall 47 minutes ago.
- Are you working up a vehicle lD?
- As soon as we get another visual.
- This camera's still functional.
- The hostages are on the right.
- Try and pan the camera over.
- They may see the camera move.
We have no choice. Do it.
There they are.
We gotta get in before they kill everyone.
Come on, faster! Faster!
Let's start wasting the guards
unless they let us walk.
First step outside - bam!
Headshot from a sniper.
You don't know that.
I know cos that's what went down in Chino!
They'll let the guards get wasted.
All they care about is keeping us in.
What the hell are we doing here, then?
Give me your gun.
Bring 'em over here.
We're gonna have a little fun with 'em.
Put 'em on their knees.
Who wants to live?
(gunshot)
- OK.
- Do 'em all, dude. Do 'em all.
Let's try it again.
- Who wants to live?
- Me! I do.
Him. Over here.
Who else?
I've never seen you before.
I'm new here.
Him, over here.
One in six chance.
You're first.
Please... don't make me do this.
There's nothing to it.
Just put the gun to your head...
I can't. I can't.
You're gonna do it. You hear me?
Please... please...
It's easy. See?
All you gotta do is smile.
And pull the trigger.
- (gun clicks)
- (laughter)
Now it's one in five.
Let's go!
No! No!
(sobbing) I can't. I can't.
- This is a waste of my time. Shoot him!
- No, wait! Wait!
Come on, man. Just do it.
This way at least you got a chance, OK? Do it.
Come on.
You're gonna do it... or we will.
(gunshot)
(inmates) Yeah! Yeah!
We have a winner!
- Let's hear it for the new guy.
- (cheers/applause)
We're now seeing concrete results.
This is a road we will continue to travel.
I got a shot from a camera
at the next intersection. The same truck.
Can you read the licence plate?
We won't be able to read anything
until it finishes downloading.
I just saw the lAD inquiry
come in over the system
about what your father's doing at the prison.
They're questioning the transfer order
you generated for him.
I heard.
If you want me to say you didn't know
he'd use it to break out Salazar, I will.
Thanks. I'll be OK.
Hold on. It stopped downloading.
I'm getting an error message.
Error 402. That means trouble
with an internal router.
Gael. What are you doing?
There's a problem with one
of the routers. I'm trying to fix it.
- Why don't you call a tech?
- No, it's OK.
I think I found the problem.
Protection circuit kicked in.
Must've been a line surge.
Should be up and running now.
- Let me know if you have more problems.
- I will.
(Adam) It's back up. What was it?
I'm not sure. Is it possible a surge
could've knocked out a router?
Not from my side.
You could ask Chloe.
- Got it.
- (dialling)
- (phone rings)
- Hold on.
I've got a plate on the pickup.
Where do you have it?
In the north quadrant
of Santa Fe Springs, driving west.
Put this out to mobile units.
I want everyone looking for this vehicle.
OK, right.
Ryan, I'm back.
So, do you have any idea if Bauer is
trying to break out Salazar on his own
or if he's working with someone?
- I'll get back to you when I find out.
- You do that.
- Chloe.
- Yeah, Michelle?
- Know what's going on at the prison?
- What's happening?
We don't have the details, but Jack's
behind it. Check his phone logs, email.
See what case files he's accessed recently.
What am I looking for?
Anything to help us know
why he's doing this.
Are you sure?
You really want me snooping in his office?
- Yes.
- You got it.
(dialling)
- Surgery.
- This is Tony Almeida's wife, Michelle.
- How's he doing?
- I'll check. One moment, please.
- Mrs Almeida?
- Yeah?
He's still in surgery. You'll be contacted
as soon as he's rolled into Recovery.
- What room is he in?
- Operating room four.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Network op seven.
- It's Michelle.
Do we get OR feeds from Good Samaritan?
Let me check.
Yeah, they do. What do you need?
- See if they're video-docking OR four.
- Yeah, they are. Where do you want it?
- Send it to my desktop.
- All right. It'll take a second.
- There you go. Anything else?
- No.
Sure.
- Four by four.
- More pressure.
- Can you hold that down?
- I've got it.
Got another clamp?
Clamp.
I'll lD the location for the explosives
once we get to the laundry room.
Your weapon, sir.
Sir, we're ready for you.
It's on. Monitor's up.
Should be seeing it on your eyepiece.
- It's working.
- OK.
Radio silence while we're in.
If they hear us, they might kill everyone.
Let's go.
All right! Round two!
(inmates) Yeah!
- And you.
- I'm a prisoner, not a guard!
Ram Ãn Salazar.
I'm sure you've heard of me.
Pick someone else.
He's telling the truth.
He transferred to this block less than
a week ago. I'm a federal agent.
I was escorting him out of the prison.
That's why you've never seen us before.
Good. Federal agent.
- What's your name?
- Jack Bauer.
All right! It's gonna be Agent Jack...
against Ram Ãn Salazar!
- A battle to the finish!
- (inmates) Yeah!
Come on, Jack.
Show this foreigner how it's done.
- (clicks)
- (inmates cheer)
If I die, my brother will find you.
Shut up and do it.
(chanting) Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it!
Do it! Do it! Do it!
(continue chanting)
(chanting) Die! Die! Die! Die!
- (clicks)
- (cheers/applause)
All right, you're up.
Looks like you might lose the title, Jack.
(chanting) Do it! Do it! Do it!
(continue chanting)
(gunshot)
Ram Ãn, stay down!
(gunfire)
Ram Ãn, come on.
All clear. Hold your fire.
Jack!
(Palmer) Senator Keeler would have
you believe that I have no triumphs
and only defeats.
God.
(dialling)
- Lab.
- This is Chloe O'Brian.
I'm in Jack's office. Could you send
someone up with a drug kit, please?
On his way.
The differences on the issues are clear.
But I believe you don't elect a platform;
you elect the man.
I am troubled by some
of the personal choices
that this president has made
and continues to make.
We're all aware of the allegations and
indictments surrounding his former wife.
Most of us have operated
under the assumption
that he would not repeat his history
of associating with persons
of questionable moral character.
However, my office has just learned
that the woman with whom the president
is currently involved, Dr Anne Packard,
is being accused of helping to fabricate
the results of a clinical drug trial,
a drug which later led to the deaths
of three innocent people.
This is outrageous. This debate is not
a court of law, nor is it a tabloid paper.
This is neither the time nor the place
to personally attack a private citizen.
Mr President, the senator still has
30 more seconds, sir. Please.
This is the right time.
I believe the choices your leaders make
in their own lives
reflect the choices that
they will make on your behalf.
And so the question remains:
Did the president know of these accusations
and choose to ignore them?
Or is he repeating past mistakes once again?
Mr President, your rebuttal.
I can tell you with complete confidence
that the senator's accusation is false
and that I believe it is the senator's way
of avoiding the issues at hand.
I came here to discuss
the real issues pressing our country.
Oh, God.
- I assume that the senator...
- Now do you get it?
(Keeler) This is not something to be
swept under the rug and forgotten.
It's positive.
I'll go tell Michelle.
What are you doing in my dad's office?
Michelle wanted me to go through his stuff.
Why?
To find anything that could help us
understand what he's doing.
Can a line surge shut down a router
on your side of the lTS room?
No, my circuit protectors are upstairs,
not in lTS. Why?
It's probably nothing. Hm.
- Did you find anything?
- I can't talk about this.
- Why not? Maybe I can help.
- You can't help, so just go, OK?
- What's in the box?
- Stuff I'm taking to Michelle.
This is really inappropriate behaviour, Kim.
Why are you doing this?
I'm just trying to help you.
I don't have to have this conversation.
Field Op mandate regulation 40 or 41
says that I have jurisdictional prerogative.
- So could you just leave?
- Not until you tell me what's in the box.
I think your dad's been using drugs.
- What?
- That's right.
Rubber tourniquet... syringe.
We just had the vials tested for opiates.
It was positive.
And he's been acting really weird. OK?
It's really not fair that you made me do this.
This is very uncomfortable.
Michelle, I found nothing in Jack's records,
but there's something you need to see.
- This was in his office?
- I wanted to make sure what it was first.
The liquid in these vials tested positive
for opiates. Probably heroin.
I think Jack's a user.
A patrol car found the truck
Kyle Singer was in,
parked in an industrial complex
at Fuller and 4th, 2000 block.
Pipe this into the teams on stand-by.
Assume everyone on site is contagious
and use level-one CDC protocol.
Let's get him!
(dialling)
- Damn! Is there any other way out?
- No, we're pinned in.
You must have known this could happen.
What's the plan, Jack?
Give me the shotgun.
Take off your uniform.
(Palmer) I have worked with my administration
on my overall economic plan.
The projections could not look better.
(phone rings)
Dessler.
We 're approaching the complex.
There are three warehouses on the property.
I'll see if we can narrow it down with infrared.
(dialling)
- (phone rings)
- Kaufman.
Adam, pull up infrared satellite
on the industrial complex.
On it.
Kim, log onto the NRT server.
We need to see if they have
any satellites in position.
- Kim.
- OK.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing. I'm fine.
(typing)
Jack or Salazar aren't in the east block.
My team can't do a search until we
lock down. That could take a half hour.
You wanna get out of this? You have to
trust me and do everything that I tell you.
- You understand?
- All right.
Come on, let's go.
I want you to take that chopper
and sweep the perimeter.
(Jack) Chase!
- What are you doing?
- Move these people back
or you'll have to take me out!
We need that chopper!
Don't do this. I spoke with Michelle.
We're close to getting Kyle Singer.
"Close" ain't gonna cut it this time!
I gotta deliver Salazar now!
I'm not letting you go, Jack!
How long is it gonna take you
to find Kyle Singer?
A half an hour? An hour?
I gotta get Salazar in that chopper in the next
60 seconds or 100,000 people will die!
- Let him go.
- Let him go?
Let him go. Track the chopper. I need
you to keep your people under control.
Please. I can't have anything
happen to Salazar.
All right.
This is Warden Mitchell.
I want all teams to stand down.
Agent Bauer will take Salazar
to the SWAT chopper.
All teams confirm the stand-down order.
Let him take the chopper.
Stand down.
All right? Back off.
All right, Jack.
No one will try and stop you.
Get this men to holster their weapons!
Back off! Stand down! Back off!
Let's move.
- Get them to holster their weapons!
- Holster your weapon!
- Lower your weapon!
- Stand down!
Get the snipers down off the roof!
Now! Now!
Get off the roof! Get off the roof!
Back off! Do what he says!
(pounding/voices)
We have Singer plus one.
Central, we have Singer plus one.
- What's he doin'?
- Disabled the com and the locator.
(cellphone ringing)
Yeah?
It's Michelle. We have Kyle Singer.
- I can't hear you!
- We found Kyle Singer!
- They found Kyle?
- Yes!
Jack! Jack! We found Kyle Singer! Jack!
Jack! Jack! Jack!
(inaudible)
..talk about facts and figures
all night, Mr President.
Once again, I see this as a question
of judgment and integrity.
You ignore this issue, an issue
of rectitude and foresightedness...
Congratulations. Now you are an even
bigger enemy to your country than I am.
Visiontext Subtitles:
Tram Nguyen Zelniker
ENGLlSH SDH