I know who started the fire.
I did. But it was an accident.
Maybe someday you'll forgive me.
For burning my house ?
The Greek softbalt tournament is
this weekend since we're partnering
with a fraternity,
I'm ready to meet a fun new guy.
- Who is the lucky girl ?
- Rebecca.
We can go for a coffee
or a movie or something simple.
Maybe after coffee
it'll be love at first sight.
You're Casey Cartwright.
You can do anything you want.
That's how I know you're gonna
go to Washington and be amazing.
- What about...
- Graduation ?
You'll never leave here.
I don't think I can be
anywhere that didn't have you.
So how did we get here, my peeps ?
How did Saint Valentine's beheading lead
to some whacked holiday about love ?
A-How.
Chaucer.
Joshuurr ?
For reals.
According to Chaucer,
Valentine wrote a love-letter,
signed "From your Valentine,"
that the greeting card
companies have turned into
a billion-dollar-a-year industry.
Cards for grandpas,
for dogs,
there are even cards for people
who don't buy cards.
Probably because they're too cheap.
David...
But I digress.
We'll pick this up next week.
Don't believe the hype.
Professor Clarissa sure has
it in for Valentine's Day.
Why can't she celebrate with her
friends ? That's what I'm gonna do.
- How do you know her friends ?
- I mean my friends.
It's still a great holiday
even though I've never actually
celebrated with a girl besides my mom.
That's the spirit.
So who's the lucky...
friends.
Your brothers ?
No, they all have dates to
our "Shot through the heart" party.
And Calvin has Grant.
Cappie and Casey.
Dale ?
No.
He's taking that retainer girl
to a party his church is hosting.
The theme is "Celibate good times,
come on".
Which leaves me one friend...
Thank God.
Because being alone
on Valentine's Day would suck.
I am going to the Omega Chi
Date Dance with this guy, Pete.
We've only been dating,
like, two weeks, but,
he hasn't shown any
Fisher-like behavior, so...
- Sorry.
- It's OK.
Because this year,
no matter what anyone says,
I'm going to have
the best Valen-time ever.
Nice.
The Cupid Range is a good start,
pledges,
but I want to see
a lot of foofy decorations
to get our dates in the mood.
Lacy hearts and other crap.
And a keg of premium beer, too.
Got it.
Fancy.
Is this the KT house ?
It's Valentine's Day.
And since it's our first one
since freshman year,
- I thought get you something special.
- Like you did freshman year ?
Exactly.
What happened ?
Your gift to me was
a bottle of vodka.
Which you drank and promptly puked up.
Remember ?
Actually, I don't remember anything from
that night, I'll take your word for it.
I just don't want
a repeat of freshman year.
Then I will humbly request
a do-over,
because I'm going to get you
the greatest gift ever.
That's OK, Cap.
You're just not a, you know,
box of chocolates
and roses kind of guy.
- Like Evan ?
- Not just Evan.
- I'm your worst boyfriend ever ?
- That's not what I meant.
Yes, it is. But you're thinking
of old drunk vodka Cappie.
Not the new and improved Cappie
with V-Day Kung Fu grip.
What's the new action
figure Cappie do ?
He gets you the most romantic
gift of your entire life,
and then dances on the graves
of Valentines past.
OK then,
Kung Fu-Valentine-Cappie...
I guess everyone
deserves a second shot.
Good shot.
Grant ? What's going on ?
Nothing, just give me a minute.
What... the hell ?
You're not supposed to be home yet.
My class was canceled.
I didn't mean to walk in on this.
I'm bleaching my hair
for our date party.
I've always wanted to do
ever since I came out.
The strip's for the pores...
and...
The trays are for teeth whitening...
And the newspaper ?
Wait, I don't really want to know.
I'm shaving my chest and my neck.
And a little bit off
the top of my feet.
- Good to know, Frodo.
- I can't do this
in the communal bathroom.
It's way too embarrassing.
So... we don't have
separate rooms and...
I get it.
I'm gonna let you
get some private...
There are only 60 Valen-Titan Bears left
for our Children's Hospital fundraiser,
so I want us all to work very hard to
find these little guys a home, OK ?
No one wants to be alone on
Valentine's Day, right Mr. Teddy ?
Lastly, if any of you do not
have Valentine's Day plans,
you are welcome to join me
for single ladies'chocolate fondue
in Pierson's Hall.
Anyone ?
Dismissed.
Hi, Katherine.
Yes, ZBZ ?
Yes, hi.
I was thinking I could volunteer to sell
the rest of the Valen-Titan Bears.
- To help you out ?
- That won't be necessary.
- But you just said we...
- No. I've got it. Thank you.
Are those from Pete ?
I'm supposed to serve food,
not pick up deliveries from
your would-be paramours.
That's right,
run to it, you succubae.
So who's the most loved this year ?
You are, of course.
By Cappie.
He told me a...
I just came from a Panhel meeting
with Katherine. She still hates me,
made worse by the fact that she's
spending Valentine's Day alone.
Which is why I have
to find her a date.
No, you don't.
What if you set her up on a bad date ?
Beaver, anyone ?
We burned down her house,
it couldn't get much worse.
But if I find her an awesome guy,
then she will totally appreciate
me and we can be friends again.
So who do we know, who do we know ?
That's not taken ?
No one.
Wait !
Wait...
Rusty does not have a date.
I think he's OK with it. Mom sends
him conversation hearts though.
- Who else ?
- No, think about it.
Katherine and Rusty are both Greeks.
They are both smart and awkward.
Maybe their shared oddness
could cancel each other out.
- I haven't even agreed with you yet.
- No.
It's my invite from Pete.
"You caught my eye."
Get it ?
Because we met at the softball game.
It's a good thing he's
rich because that's lame.
And here comes Evan.
I wonder what he got you.
It's a little buddy.
He wants to know if you'll
go to our date party with me.
- Please tell me you're kidding.
- Yes on the bear. No on the party.
Valentine's Day ? Really ?
A day to celebrate love with meaningless
cheap candy and trinkets made in China ?
Excuse me,
the bear is made in Chile.
And it's a party.
It'll be fun, we can make fun of people.
I do like making fun of people.
- What time should I pick you up ?
- I'll think about it.
Having an all-access pass
to your boyfriend's life this soon
kinda kills the magic.
It's like for straight guys
when Megan Fox speaks.
Are we becoming one of
those gay married couples
that host dinner parties
and watch Bravo ?
Alright.
What's going on, Rus ?
I've decided to find a date
for Valentine's Day,
- I'm looking for a girl to ask out.
- Now ? It's in two days.
I've had years of
Valentine's Day loneliness.
No. Look, the expectation
will kill you.
It's bad enough
I have to have my first out date party
with Grant on Valentine's Day.
The last thing you want
is to surround yourself
with a bunch of people in love.
It's better than being alone.
Here goes.
Hi, you don't know me,
but I'm Rusty.
- Hi, Rusty. Tabitha.
- Nice to meet you, Tabitha.
I hope I'm not being too forward,
but my fraternity's having
this date party on Saturday...
You're asking me on a first date
on Valentine's Day ?
Well, I saw you...
I thought you were pretty and
this is for you.
"Lick my..."
Oh My God !
Perv.
My mom must've accidentally bought me
the X-rated brand.
Or the box was meant for your dad.
Traumatic, either way.
Well, I gotta say,
much points for the gift.
Well, I gotta say I'm excited
to have you as my date.
I'm excited to be had.
As your date.
Hey, guys.
So, Pete, the Omega Chi
Date Party is this Saturday.
- Why haven't I heard from you ?
- Because I'm taking Ashleigh.
- But you said we were going.
- You did ?
We talked about that,
when we dated last month.
But I just assumed you understood
we weren't going out on Valentine's Day
- after we broke up.
- We broke up ?
- This is how you tell me ?
- Yeah, I figured when I said,
I think we should see other people,
that you got that.
Well, I do now, Pete,
because I don't date cheaters.
I can't believe she just called me
a cheater.
Neither can I.
Taken...
married...
incarcerated...
No. I'm sorry you can't make it.
Good luck with the surgery.
A C-Section ?
How old are these phone numbers ?
Hopefully older than nine months.
- Have we gone through all the phones ?
- Except for Pickle's.
He knows a lot of girls
from the 900 area code.
I should have listened to my professor,
who was smart enough to realize
- that Valentine's Day sucks.
- I get it, Rus.
There's a lot of expectations.
Like finding the perfect gift.
You think Casey would like
a used cell phone ?
You know what... forget it.
Why should I care
that I'm alone on February 14th ?
Because society and the greeting
card industry tell me not to be ?
Are you saying that
because you don't have a date ?
I mean it. I'm over it.
I'm over the hype. I'm finally free.
Hi.
Ash told me about your problem,
and I think
I found you a date for your party.
My friend Katherine
is available and...
you were the first person
I thought of.
So what do you say ?
I think you're too late,
because he just said...
No, I'm in.
I love Valentine's Day.
What ?
What's Katherine like ?
I'm not being judgmental, but...
Down, boy. You're going to find out.
Katherine wants to set up a pre-date
- tonight at Dobler's.
- A pre-date ?
Don't worry. Casey and I'll be there in
case you screw up. Her words, not mine.
So, Katherine...
She was at Greek softball.
She's tall, she's pretty.
- That's good.
- Let me finish.
Stern. The word
"Nordic" comes to mind.
- I think I can handle that.
- I hope she's easier than your sister.
Try pleasing her.
Rewind. Try finding
the perfect gift for her.
Get her something from the heart.
It's just about the two of you.
Imagine Casey, imagine the perfect gift
and then make it happen.
Nice. That's the Spitter I want to see
at Dobler's tonight.
So... What does one wear
to a KT Valentine's party ?
Same thing you wear to any other party.
They're not cavemen.
All of them.
Well, I can tell you what I wore
when I went with Cappie.
Think tiny and wicked.
Seems like it would fit you.
So, why are you buying a dress ?
I thought you were anti-Valentine's.
I agreed to go to Evan's date party.
He got me with his big puppy dog eyes.
He does that.
Why am I even buying a dress ?
My date's probably just
another Fisher in worsted wool.
Don't let Natalie the angry inch
spoil your next date with Pete.
But she totally got in my head.
It's like I'm dating Eddie Cibrian.
But am I LeAnn Rimes or his wife ?
No. Natalie is a deceptive
little trickster.
Need I remind you of
the electric bill debacle ?
- You're still sensitive over Fisher.
- Because you made out with him.
- What's your point ?
-  Right, Pete deserves a first chance.
Case, I bet you're getting lingerie
for Valentine's Day.
OK, I get it.
You guys used to date.
Look.
Hi, Cap.
Don't you love this place ?
Nice try. Lingerie is more
of a gift for you than for me.
What ? It's for Beaver.
Because...
Beaver likes to feel pretty.
And since you're not having
to buy a gift for anybody,
maybe you shouldn't talk. Because it's
not easy finding the perfect gift.
Please.
How hard could it be ?
Well, let's find out. You versus me,
to see who can get the other
the most romantic gift.
Unless you're too scared I'll
outromanticize you or something.
The only thing
I'm scared for is you.
- Game on.
- If you think this is a game
- you've already lost. See you tonight.
- Not if I see you first.
- Porn site crash ?
- Worse, shopping.
I convinced Rebecca to come
to our Valentine's party,
and now I want to show the girl
who claims she doesn't believe in love
- how much she means to me.
- You're missing your trust fund.
You know, she's the first girl
that doesn't make me feel
like I'm the evil guy
that everyone else thinks I am.
She gets my background and...
why we are the way we are.
She deserves something special.
Speaking of...
Thanks, man.
- That's really sweet.
- It's for Grant.
Can I stash it here
until the party ?
- You can't hide it in your room ?
- The room where secrets go to die ?
We see way too much as is.
I'm already worried
that the brothers won't be OK
with us out together
at a date party.
I'd say that any problems
they might have had,
you took care of
at the softball game.
So the only problem now is Grant
and I becoming boring.
Great. Hopefully,
that won't happen to you two.
I doubt it.
Rebecca lives for surprises.
This is it. Success tonight
means my first Valentine.
It's like I'm reliving
first grade through you.
This is my brother, Rusty.
- So excited to meet you.
- Me too.
Would you guys stand back-to-back ?
Just real quick.
- I want to see something.
- Anyway...
Rusty here was awarded
an engineering grant.
Katherine is president of Panhellenic
and, quite possibly, America one day.
- That's great.
- Yes.
Goals are great.
So Casey tells me
you're studying Poli Sci.
I do, yes.
So...
Why is Political
Science called "Poli Sci,"
and Polymer Science isn't ?
Because, politics isn't
an actual science.
Or is it ? I don't know.
You tell me.
All I know is, that there
are no beakers in politics.
So are you excited
about Valentine's Day ?
Yes.
Speaking of Valentine's Day,
Casey and I are battling to see
who can get who the best gift.
And today I came up with some
ideas that are gonna blow you away.
Good luck with those ideas, because
I found you the perfect gift today.
You did ?
Seriously ?
Casey tells me you're a Gamma Psi.
Do you like living in a house ?
I mean, did you ?
Yes.
Your house was probably
cleaner than ours.
Once, when I was a pledge,
I had to clean what I thought
was a quarter-pound of hair
out of a shower drain,
but it was just a rat.
You guys really both like to study.
Maybe you could talk about that.
Yes.
Oh, no !
It didn't go well ?
It was the worst pairing since
Drew Barrymore and directing.
I can officially kiss my friendship
- with Katherine goodbye.
- You still have me.
We won't be at the same party.
- I know.
- And...
I lied to Cappie about
getting him the perfect gift.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Laura said, "Head on up, bitch."
No, that's fine. I was just going
to show off my new dress, anyway.
- It's eclectic.
- Thank you.
I know what this is about.
Yes, we need to discuss
this Rusty incident.
How could you possibly imagine
- we'd have anything in common ?
- I just thought...
Why did you think
that we'd get along ?
- I'm so, sorr...
- Because we did.
He's so suave.
- Really ?
- Yes and handsome.
- You don't have to be polite.
- No. But, really, so...
Give me the deets.
Does Rusty work out ?
I think he did... once.
Listen to me, I'm prattling on like
a schoolgirl. I had so much fun.
- He did too, right ?
- How could he not ? It's you.
So Valentine's Day is a go.
I'm being selfish but I can't think
of anything else but tonight
and the connection that we made.
I am so lucky to have
a friend like you.
I am gonna go prepare. But I
will call you about my wardrobe.
Well...
Hello ?
- What's all this ?
- Comfort food.
I've accepted my fate
as Valentine's Day washout.
Did you get that
non-stick food I asked for ?
Sometimes Bridget
eats with her retainer in,
and kissing her is like
eating lunch twice in one day.
- How long you been there ?
- Long enough to taste my lunch twice.
No, I was just goofing.
We're not an item.
Bridget's Catholic.
Good luck with that.
That reminds me... this is for you.
But don't read it in front of me.
How...
could I ?
So... good news.
You can still have a date
to the KT party if you want,
Katherine totally likes you.
She thinks you're hot.
- Really ?
- That's what I said, too.
- After Dobler's ?
- At least you'd have a Valentine
this once... excluding Mom.
At least Mom can hold a conversation.
I'd rather have no memories than bad ones
- with one-word-answer girl.
- At least that word was "yes".
A lot of guys would be
happy to hear that.
Look Rus,
I'm trying to get back on her good side.
We had a falling out.
Things got... heated.
Please ?
OK. For one month's
free access to your car.
I get you a date and you
blackmail me ? Forget it.
Fine, then you date her.
Just pretend to like her. OK ?
Don't you have a little wheel
you should be running in ?
I'm sorry about the other day.
Pete hurt me really bad
and I don't want to see
you get hurt, too.
- That's what these boys do.
- Why should I believe a girl
who hooked up with a theater
major to win SongFest ?
Because we're in different houses
doesn't mean we can't be sisters.
As president of the
number one sorority,
I want you, president of the number two
sorority to know that we can be friends.
And we, at the number one sorority,
want you, the number two sorority,
to know I don't believe you.
Pete's called me every day
for the past two weeks.
How do I know this is the real Pete
and not you assigning his name
to another number ?
It's Pete. Look, sorry
I've been calling you so...
Don't let him hurt you, too.
So this year,
I dug deep down in my heart,
and made Casey three presents
for us to choose from that
no one else could get her.
Prepare to be amazed.
- Nice.
- Right ?
I raised it from a young sapling,
which I think will show
Casey my budding maturity.
- When you say "buds" ?
- It's not that kind of plant.
Yeah, I don't get it. Next.
A God's Eye with ZBZ colors.
Because I appreciate
her sorority allegiance.
- And I'm a big kid. Get it ?
- I'm just not feeling it, Cap.
I mean, I understand it,
but it doesn't get me here.
OK. All right
A macaroni necklace.
I don't think you're
supposed to cook the macaroni.
- I must've missed that week at camp.
- May I ?
Of course. Yeah, Bon appetit.
Great, the party's in
an hour and I have squat.
And now I have to go get ready.
It's good.
Do you want to walk down together ?
No. I'm going to get
dressed in the bathroom.
What ?
Look...
I'm sorry if I've come off
as a jerk lately, it's just...
No, things have been
a little unromantic.
And I want to spice them up.
Evan may have mentioned
your conversation to me.
I want a real date.
Special. Maybe a surprise ?
I can't wait to be surprised.
Good.
You look amazing.
Thanks. Can I see your cell phone ?
Mine's dead.
Sure.
So, have you talked
to Natalie lately ?
Yeah. I've called her
a bunch of times, actually.
Wait, why ?
Because she has my history textbook
and she won't give it back.
Well, here's your cell phone back.
For you.
It's...
It's way too beautiful.
I feel like I'm gonna turn on the news
and see some dead rich girl.
Nah, I dug the ditch pretty deep.
I had some money put away.
It's no big deal.
This looks like a big deal.
Well, I saw it
and thought it'd look
really good on you.
Let's try it, shall we ?
There you go.
Thank you.
You guys are leaving now ?
- Have fun.
- You too, Case.
Want to exchange gifts now ?
I think gifts are better left
to the end of the evening.
If I can find her one by then.
Where is she ?
Let's get this over with.
No kidding.
Stop drooling.
Hi. You look amazing.
You look very dapper yourself.
Moving on ?
Looks like the pledges did me proud.
- I'm nervous.
- Because we're at a KT party ?
- No, because of Rusty.
- Really ?
You keep saying that.
- How spirited of them.
- Jell-O shot ?
- Of love ?
- Thank you.
Pickle.
Who's your date ?
I'd like you guys to meet
Mrs. Joanne Fletcher.
How sweet, he brought his mom.
That's not his mom.
So you want to shoot some arrows ?
Yes.
I have to admit, I didn't think
you'd want to go to a KT party.
It didn't seem like you.
- No offense.
- None taken.
I have to admit I didn't think I'd find
a Gary Wyatt Grant winner at KT either.
It was a little intimidating.
Really ? Is that why you kept giving me
one-word answers at Dobler's ?
It's the quickest way to get to know
someone. You let them do all the talking
And I liked what I heard.
I was a Boy Scout.
Holy crap.
I made it to the Olympic trials
when I was 11.
There aren't too many overachieving
Greeks like you here at CRU.
I guess I am somewhat of an amalgam.
Let me show you.
Happy, VD.
What's up ?
I feel like I never see you anymore.
I know. You're all holed up
with Grant all day.
- So, you guys good ?
- I think so.
We certainly see
a lot of each other.
Sometimes too much.
But we're working it out.
I get it. The perils
of living under the same roof.
Of course, in my case
it was because Fisher was...
CRU's version of David Letterman.
Hey, guys.
My God !
You look hot.
Thanks, Ash.
Cal ? What do you think ?
I think you look...
- spicy.
- Right ?
I know it's not me,
but I'm kinda diggin'it.
Could be more where this came from.
I'm gonna get us some drinks.
Stop it. I know
what you're thinking.
This is like the same thing
as Michael.
- Michael would never wear that.
- You asked for a surprise,
and you got it.
So enjoy your...
spicy hot out-and-proud man.
God.
It's Tinker-Hell.
- Hey, Pete.
- Hey there.
Get me a drink.
She's after Pete.
She's like a little
Valentine parasite.
Nice work, Tony Hopkins.
I stole it from the Lamda Sig house.
All right, here.
Keep the change.
Well, you look confident.
Are you prepared to lose all control
and attempt to ravage my body
right here on the dance floor ?
Let's see what you got.
Seriously.
It's tragedy
plus time equals comedy.
It reminds us
of our first time together.
And takes us back to
younger, simpler days.
Yeah, it takes us back to the time
you bought me vodka for Valentine's Day
and drank it and threw up.
On me. Left that part out earlier.
But... thanks for the vodka.
It's a callback.
I get it, it's funny.
Gotcha !
Actually, it's tragedy plus time
plus you falling for it.
Because vodka equals
- not my real gift.
- So this is not your real gift ?
This ? No ! Hell no !
I will give you your real gift...
later on.
Then I'll give you
your gift later, too.
Great.
Hey, you two.
You can cut the crap, Nat.
I know why Pete called you.
No, Ash. I just wanted to apologize.
I went too far at the Student Union
and I'm truly, truly sorry.
It's just...
The worst thing that ever has happened
to me, happened on Valentine's Day.
God. It was so horrible.
It was Valentine's Eve.
I was nine years old.
Me and Mom were decorating the tree,
waiting for Dad to come home from work.
A couple hours went by.
Dad still wasn't home.
So Mom called the office
and no answer.
So the police began a search.
And four or five days later...
You tried to light a fire,
and you noticed the smell,
the firemen came and they
pulled out your dead dad.
That story is from Gremlins.
The only reason you're telling
it is because you are one.
So don't feed her after midnight
or she'll turn uglier.
Ash...
Chill out.
Why don't we go get you some water ?
Can I admit something ?
This is my first
Valentine's date ever.
It's mine, too.
I rarely date.
Or go to parties.
I got into Yale Law School.
You must be excited.
And terrified.
I've lived my whole life for the
future at the expense of the present.
So now I have to fit the entire
college experience into one semester.
And I want to be more
than the geeky smart girl.
- Is that sad ?
- Why do you think I rushed KT ?
I want to be more than
the geeky smart girl, too.
I mean, guy.
I think Casey sometimes worries
about it in the opposite direction.
That she waited too long
to find something beyond ZBZ.
It's sweet of you to think of her.
And though I'll never admit it,
I think your sister's doing
a fine job of catching up.
I guess we all have regrets.
I don't think I'll regret this.
I am so glad I changed my
mind about a second date.
- What ?
- What.
Casey said that you had a great time
on our first date.
Was she telling the truth ?
Yeah.
- Well, I mean, sort of...
- Clearly not.
She convinced you how ?
Did she express pity for me ?
Appeal to your sense of charity ?
She belittle my chocolate fondue,
because I could tell
she thought it was lame.
Casey loves fondue.
She really likes you, too.
But... you don't ?
I do, and I'll prove it to you.
I'll tell her that I don't
want her car.
She bribed you with her car ?
Am I that pathetic ?
And what are you ?
Some brother-whore to be bought
and traded like a commodity ?
Casey, hi. Great !
Did you offer your car to Rusty
to date me so we could be friends ?
- Katherine, look, I thought...
- I need to breathe.
I wanted us to be friends
because I respect and admire you.
- And I just want you to be happy.
- Me, too.
Forget about what brought us here.
Just think about what is going on now.
I'm thinking.
Why don't you just give me one
reason why I should forgive you.
Heads up !
My gosh !
First a fire, now this. Katherine's
gonna think we're trying to kill her.
- Are you ?
- I'm the one she's going to hate.
Just when I think I kinda like her.
Really ?
- What are you doing here ?
- Drama, Rus.
Had to bring Bridget in.
There was a...
accident.
Involving her retainer.
She's gonna be fine
but I'm gonna need some stitches.
Thank God !
You're OK !
"Tis only a flesh wound".
Monty Python.
That's funny.
"We are the Knights who say Ni".
I've got you on strong pain killers.
A good thing the arrow was blunt-tipped
or you'd be spending Valentine's Day
in the morgue.
Like the real Valentine.
I bet you'll never forget the first time
you were struck by Cupid's arrow.
Actually it was Pickle's.
He said he was sorry.
Casey, you went to all this trouble
to be friends with me ?
No one's ever done anything
like that for me before.
So, thank you.
- Ni.
- I'll walk her home.
Yeah...
That's probably the strangest injury
you've had all night, right ?
Not really.
You OK ?
I can't find my boyfriend.
Have you seen him ?
What's your problem ?
He's freaking beautiful.
I know.
I just prefer my men handsome.
What's the difference ?
When I came out that one week
I wanted to listen to Indigo Girls
and wear no makeup. Grant's
experimenting with the lifestyle.
- Big whoop. It's natural.
- So I'm overreacting ?
You are a pretty uptight gay.
Lighten up.
If you want it to work,
it's something you're gonna have to do.
Or I could just buy him
a really fancy necklace.
- Is that from Evan ?
- I've decided I like it.
- It's a keepsake I can keep forever.
- I think that was his idea.
Really ?
He said that ?
More or less.
He says that you get him
more than anyone else.
I think he sees a future with you.
I hope it works out.
I'm gonna go get some air.
Can I talk to you for a second ?
Alone ?
What ? I'm not doing anything.
- Except hurting inside.
- She's really upset.
Seriously ? How are you buying
this whole martyr act ?
I'm the good one.
She's LeAnn Rimes.
She burned down my house.
Yeah, Ashleigh didn't think
we deserved to win SongFest,
so she snuck in and set it on fire.
Nat, that's just crazy.
- What ?
I mean... yeah.
That is a total lie, Natalie.
Kinda like the one where you said
that we paid
for your electric bill last semester.
Yeah everyone, that is a lie, too.
No. That's the truth.
You know it, Ashleigh, tell them !
- What ? That you're crazy ?
- You're lying.
You're all lying.
I know what I'm talking about.
I'm not crazy, damn it.
Could someone walk her home
so she doesn't hurt herself ?
- Come on, Natalie, I'll walk you home.
- Hands off me, Carrot-top.
Carrot-top !
That is harsh.
Good luck with that, dude !
Sorry I didn't believe
that Nat's crazy.
It's just that when she called me
a cheater
I felt bad and it kinda hurt
that you didn't trust me, either.
I just didn't want
to be hurt by you.
How about we promise
not to hurt each other ?
I'm good with that.
Where were we ?
Right here.
I thought you bailed.
I was here, doing this.
Surprise.
You are just full of surprises.
So is the ensemble too much ?
I once dumped a guy
for being too foofy.
- OK, too much.
- No wait. I'm not done.
I don't want to be an uptight gay.
All right ?
I want to be as brave as you.
Maybe explore a little.
With you.
Sorry.
Have you seen Rebecca ?
Yeah, she said
that she was gonna get some air.
Carry on.
- Angie. This is Rusty.
- Hi.
Your skin is so soft.
God, I am so sorry
you were struck by an arrow.
That's what I get
for dating a bad boy.
I don't know if you've noticed
but sometimes I'm socially awkward
and I don't really know
what to do... or to say.
I haven't noticed.
I'm sorry that I wasn't much
of a Valentine.
That was the least suckiest
Valentine's Day I've ever had.
Me too.
Thank you.
Hi, Beaver.
Wait up.
- How about we go upstairs ?
- What's upstairs ?
Your room.
I know that.
But why you wanna go...
my God.
Yeah, they turn off
the Slushee machines at midnight.
I was thinking
we could exchange our gifts.
- Here ?
- No better time than the present.
Present. Get it ?
OK. Me first.
"Look up".
Just what I always wanted.
You were so right.
It's really hard to buy a gift.
I totally cracked under the pressure.
You're off the hook from this day forward.
Well, that's good.
Because I don't think I could top
what I did this year.
Bringing me to the Quickie Mart ?
It's not just any Quickie Mart.
You and I came here once
freshman year for snacks.
I thought it looked familiar.
You were buying all this food
and I was wondering
if you got high
when I wasn't looking.
And when I asked you
about it, you said :
"I want to stock the fridge
in your room",
because you knew I was lazy
about going to the cafeteria
and you didn't want me to go hungry.
- Do you want food ?
- And you were at the register, paying.
You tucked your hair
behind your ear,
looked back at me and just...
smiled.
This is where I first realized
that I loved you.
And I've loved you every day since.
My God.
That's my gift.
It's perfect.
So, I...
- I guess I kinda won ?
- Yeah, you so won.
Yes !
Suck it, Valentine's Day !