You really aren't clear
on the meaning of "no."
But I'm very good with yes.
As in: "yes, tomorrow
night sounds great."
I thought if the two of
you could be friends again,
then maybe we could all go back
to the way things used to be.
We can't go back, but maybe
all three of us can
try to move forward together.
Get off!
Look at those jackasses.
We should go finish
what they started.
Easy, bro, easy, bro. Come on.
Zbz is constantly embroiled
in some kind of turmoil,
and no one likes
a dysfunctional drama case.
I would say zbz is ranked Fourth?
- Fourth?
- It's all part of the cycle.
If it really is a cycle,
then it's too late, right?
It's like fate.
As seniors,
we have to fight this cycle.
The truth is we're
not number one anymore.
We were hoping to
throw some killer mixers
and eventually have the best rush
this campus has ever seen.
I hate putt-putt.
And cute golf
attire is beyond even my powers.
Just keep smiling. We don't want
The sisters to figure out
how much this mixer sucks.
This mixer sucks.
I think they know.
It's 9:00am. On a thursday.
I should be asleep.
Nicole's asleep.
I can't even flirt with
the seven pi sigmas who
bothered to show up because
I have coffee breath.
They're not paying
attention to us anyway.
I remember the days when all
they wanted to hump was us.
I hate not being number one anymore.
I thought you were going to get us
out of this, president ashleigh.
I know our social
schedule isn't what it was,
but things are looking up.
And I'm working on
getting our prime table
at dobler's back from gamma psi.
We lost our table?
And may I remind you we had
a pinning ceremony last week?
Heather got pinned to
jeremy from kappa tau.
Hardly good news.
You sound like my parents!
I heard a few sisters
talking about de-activating.
One of them might've been me.
Fore!
But...
But they haven't
heard the best part!
We are having a mixer this saturday.
At night.
With omega chi.
- We are?!
- Yeah, remember?
You and evan are
such good friends now
and you guys were talking about
how you missed the houses mixing
and came up with the idea?
It was brilliant!
We did.
And they can't wait.
Omega chi and zbz, reunited
and it feels so good.
And you decided not
to tell us until now?
That's what makes it a surprise!
It's like our reintroduction
into the social top-ti
and I'll be in charge of making
our pledges hump-able again!
You should be thanking me.
We have three days to
pull off our reintroduction
into the social top-tier with
a mixer that doesn't exist?
Look at the happy faces
on all the children.
They're finally not
looking at me like
they want to kill me in my sleep.
What's up, guys?
New drinking game.
Every time jeremy snores...
- we drink.
- It's harder than it looks.
You have to stop drinking
at the end of the snore.
Or you get penalized.
You just said "penalized."
I Miss you guys.
Where did you go?
Oh, god...
Did you learn how to manipulate
space and time
so you could disappear
without us noticing?
I knew you could do that!
I might be a little bit buzzed.
Yeah, I've been so busy
with so much crap lately.
School, man, is so tough,
ex-girlfriend trouble...
I'm just in the mood to be
with my boys and cut loose!
You're on the moon
right now, aren't you?
You're a hologram.
You're so buzzed.
Is cappie upstair?
It's your little bro.
Naked.
Get out of here, perv.
Greek 308
Greek Team
Fore!
We get it.
We're ranked number four.
No need to rub it in.
I think he was trying
to make a golf joke.
Some people appreciate
my sense of humor.
Some people appreciate crocs.
We had a golf mixer with pi sigma.
The old putt-putt blow-off?
We did the same thing
last year to tri-pi
after their president dumped dino.
Exactly. Which is why we need you
guys to invite us
to a mixer this saturday night.
- Do you guys have plans?
- Nothing set in stone.
We were thinking about
having a low-key weekend.
Think again,
because we're giving you
a chance to mix with zbz!
In the spirit of
reuniting old friends.
It would really mean a lot to
our house during a rough time.
Please, please, please!
Great! One more thing.
We kinda need you guys
to formally invite us,
tonight during dinner.
Maybe you could throw
in a little serenade?
- You don't have to...
- The girls will expect it!
No worries i would do it.
Awesome!
- Thanks, evan. See you tonight.
- All right.
And, watch out for those sand traps!
That wasn't funny at all.
- Thanks, case!
- No problem.
It was an accident.
It seems as
though you saw milady naked.
There's only one way to
restore the power balance. Come on,
drop trou.
He's right.
It's only fair.
Let's see the goods.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, my god, I'm not
at my breast right now.
- "Best?"
- Right!
And I came here to blow off
some steam with my big bro!
There's no one better to
do that with than cappie.
We're actually on our way
out to get something to eat.
- You should come with.
- I don't want to intrude.
No, don't worry about it.
I think I left my backpack upstairs.
Why don't you go get it?
Hurry up,
you don't wanna
be late for our threesome.
How cute is he?!
I'm on board with the threesome,
I just didn't think it
was gonna be with spitter.
He's so sweet and innocent.
I can't wait to corrupt him.
That's just what I thought
when I first met him.
Again: can you just assure me we're
not having sex with spitter tonight?
What would you say
if I told you that grant and I think
we're ready to tell the house?
I'd say go for it, man.
The guys love you and
the guys love grant.
Why should that change when you
tell them you love each other?
"Like" each other.
And that's what I'm
worried about. It's change.
People don't always
react well to change.
I'm assuming that's
why you told griffin
you joined the treble
makers acapella group
when he saw you in
your pink bow-tie.
Maybe we're over-thinking all this.
Maybe sexual orientation
and socio-economic status
aren't that big a deal in
the world. People are people.
Yeah, you know what?
This is only a big deal
if we make it a big deal.
We have the power.
Maybe you go first?
No, you've been gay way
longer than I've been broke.
You're up first.
Do you have a lot
of parking tickets?
I can't afford to. Why?
Forget to pay your bill, chambers?
And apparently you can't
cover a lease payment
with dobler's drink coupons.
And it looks like my
secret's coming out first.
Irish car bomb!
- Your turn, rusty.
- I'm underage.
He's not exactly good with
liquor. Hence the nickname, "spitter."
But he's not spitter tonight.
He's rowdy rusty.
Rowdy rusty.
All right, I love it!
You don't have to do this,
spitter, if you don't want to.
Go!
All right.
You did it!
Sort of.
Yeah. Good job, spitter.
Excuse me, rowdy rusty.
Now what?
No, I think that's quite
enough for one evening, rowdy.
Or...
See our waiter over
there ignoring us?
We asked for our check,
like, 30 minutes ago.
What a douche bag, right?
You want me to say something to him?
"Excuse me, pal, where's our check?"
We're going to dine and dash.
Spitter's not gonna dine and dash.
And as a member of the food
services industry yourself,
you should be sensitive to
the fact that this poor guy
probably works here three...
Wait up!
I'm sure most of you
guys have figured out,
I gave up my trust fund.
It is a really personal
situation with my family
but it's nice to know
my brothers have my back.
Even if I'm gonna have
to start hitting you up
for beer money from now on.
So any new business?
What's with this zbz mixer?
It's this saturday...
I know all that.
But why are we going?
Aren't they all about
mixing with those
kt losers this semester?
Yeah, that's true but come on...
- And this year, they kinda suck.
- And it's not like they're gamma psi.
And last year, they
dissed our pref invite.
I think we should go.
The girls could use our help.
They just want our help
so they can climb back up.
We're doing the mixer
because I said we are.
I'm president and it's done.
We know you've done half the girls
in that house, but that's no reason
the rest of us have to
waste a saturday on them.
Watch your mouth, trip.
You're way out of line.
I say we put the mixer to a vote.
As pledge class president,
I would like to formally
report that we are super excited
about the omega chi mixer!
Thanks for making that happen!
Just doing my job.
When are they officially
going to invite us?
- Any minute now!
- Great.
I hope it's any minute. Can you
ask fisher to hold on dessert?
He's already kept them
waiting 20 minutes!
They're sorority girls.
They can deal with hunger pangs.
Fine.
Sit up straight.
Shoulders back. Boobs out.
And heather, unbutton
your shirt a little.
It might as well be a turtleneck.
Why do I have to learn how to flirt?
I already have a boyfriend.
Not a good one. And this isn't
about finding a boyfriend.
This is for the sisterhood.
Saturday night we want to
leave the omega chis dying
for another mixer with
us as soon as possible.
We're set to starve the
girls for 20 more minutes.
Now where is...
everyone,
i'm sure this man needs no introduction,
and as for his brothers.
As for his brothers...
Actually it's just me.
Let's just get on with it.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Evan's just shy.
Cheesecake! Now!
What's going on?
I'm sorry, but the mixer's
not going to happen.
I really tried, but the brothers,
they voted it down.
What? Why?
They brought up last year's pref,
about how you guys dissed us, they
said zbz's just not a big draw anymore.
And you're not exactly gamma psi?
You're their president.
It's a party.
Order them to party with
a group of hot chicks.
That's just it, Due to
a weird situation that's
recently come up in the house,
some of the guys have
been questioning me.
Why would they do that?
You're evan freaking chambers!
Yeah, it's funny you would say that.
Here's the deal.
I gave up my trust fund.
I didn't want
my parents controlling my life.
I haven't spoken to them
since. I'm broke.
So much for evan chambers.
- Seriously?
- I know, I'm an idiot.
It's probably the biggest
mistake of my entire life.
No, it's the bravest
thing you've ever done.
I can't believe it.
I'm so proud of you.
I wish some of the brothers
reacted the same way.
But coinciding with me not being
a "chambers" anymore, I
seem to have lost
a lot of my influence on them.
I'm sorry, but the mixer's off.
The girls took down that
cheesecake like coyotes on road kill.
What's going on with the mixer?
What do we tell the girls?
Their sugar
is gonna start wearing off
and they'll be demanding answers.
We can't say the mixer's off.
I just keep thinking
about what evan did.
Giving up all that money
on principle and then being
shunned by his own parents?
That must be so hard for him.
He's always felt the weight
of the chambers name.
I remember that being a dilemma.
But still, to actually
give it all up like that?
- I don't think i'd be able to do that.
- Oh, my god, snap out of it!
We're supposed to be figuring out how to
salvage the party here!
What's there to figure out?
There's nothing we can do.
We're not gamma psi.
What if we get gamma psi?
We make the mixer a four-pack.
Us, omega chi, gamma
psi, probably lambda sig.
And not just any
four-pack: a super-fancy
semi-formal four-pack!
Where we have champagne,
a band, twinkle lights!
- In three days?
- We have the founders' day money.
But why would we even want
to party with the gamma psis?
They stole our table at dobler's.
And apparently our social life.
Besides, they're kind of weird.
It doesn't matter if they're
serial killers. They're number one.
If we get them, we get the guys.
It worked for janet gunderson.
Your dorky friend with the
mono-brow in seventh grade?
She befriended me and became
popular by association.
Then I introduced her
to tweezers and she stolen my boyfriend.
See, it's perfect!
We are janet gunderson.
The gamma psis are 12-year-old me.
And we become number
one by association.
I don't think that's how it works.
What other options do I have?
You're the president.
I'm so hung over
and I don't even care!
Last night was amazing.
I did things I never
thought I would do.
You're not hung over.
- It's not spitter anymore.
- I know.
From the small amount of irish car
you managed to imbibe,
you're gassy from
the carbonation at best.
Fine. Maybe I didn't
succeed at the drinking,
- but I did do a dashing dine!
- It's "dine-and-dash."
Boys! I hate to interrupt
your girlish squabble,
but predators of
the deep is back on.
I've never watched so many
episodes of one tv show
since thatjoan of arcadia
marathon with my parents.
Did I say parents?
I meant my friends.
My cool friends.
And it was porn.
Don't you have art
history in ten minutes?
I was gonna head to women's studies.
We can walk together.
And don't you have a bar
mitzvah to work tonight?
I called in sick. And you guys shouldn't
be going to class either.
The next episode is killer whales.
- You can't Miss that!
- Killer whales!
- It's on.
- Like donkey kong! Jinx!
I just figured out why you two
are so perfect for each other!
She's like the lady
version of you. Lady cappie!
I'd like to think of you
as the male version of me.
She's a keeper.
She's a none of your other girlfriends
would blow off work for
predators of the deep.
Just don't screw it up.
That whale just ate that whole seal.
What was up with you
in yesterday's meeting?
Backing up j.p. And trip like that.
Since when did you
become so anti-kt?
I just think they're kind of obnoxious.
As do most of our brothers.
You're clearly biased
because of "that rusty."
"That rusty" is my best friend.
And evan's been a really
good friend to me, too.
He's been through a real
tough time lately, I just...
I don't think he needs all
that crap from the house.
It wasn't personal.
I'm sure it felt that way to him.
I just feel bad.
He's been so supportive of us
coming out soon, like we talked about.
Actually...
I've been thinking.
Things are good the way they are.
So sneaking around,
and coming up with excuses
why we're always together?
You don't think that's
holding us back?
I really like our
relationship how it is.
Besides, seeing the way
everyone gossips about evan,
I really don't want
to go through that.
Guess what?
I stole you a dining hall muffin!
What are you doing here?
Booktacular-ing.
We're readingeat,
pray, love this week
and thought we'd do
a little of all three.
I'm opting to partake in just the
eat part. Not that I don't love you.
What are you doing stealing
dining hall muffins?
- You know that's frowned upon.
- Don't you have a date with lana?
I did, but I've been rescheduling
shamelessly on daley here,
I really needed to make it up to him.
Sparkling cider?
It's non-alcoholic but the fizzies
get up your nose and it's fun.
You're just gonna blow her off?
It's not like she's
never flaked on me.
Our first date she kept
me waiting while
she prank-phone called her old boss.
For two hours.
Excuse me. I have to go
relieve some cider fizzies.
That girl is amazing
and he's flaking on her?!
He's gonna drive her away.
Is lana really worth
all the trouble?
Oh, my god, she's the most
amazing girl I've ever met.
For him, for cappie.
If she's so perfect for him,
why would he blow her off?
It's obvious! He's scared of
how much that he likes her.
But you know he'll never admit it.
I think we're gonna
have to go see lana
about this situation.
You're friends with cappie.
You're broke.
Any other secrets
you want to reveal?
I have a job that requires
me to wear a pink bow-tie.
Stripping at the other
gentleman's choice?
No, actually that probably
pays much, much more.
I'm a cater-waiter.
I have no car, I can't
pay my house dues.
I can't pay my house dues.
I should grovel to my parents
and get my trust fund back.
You can't start doubting
yourself now.
You did the right thing.
As your friend, I will help you.
- We'll figure it out.
- Well, can you help me figure out
how to get these guys
to take me seriously again?
Because apparently the only title
they care about is Chambers.
To think I believed that these guys
were doing what their president said
because they respected me.
Well, you know what?
Screw them.
- Just because a few jerks...
- A few is enough to make a difference.
So make a name for yourself that
has nothing to do with your parents.
Or their money.
You have friends
who really care about you.
I said coquette, not spastic.
Melanie, you look like
you're smuggling something.
This was on the porch!
It's from Natalie,
the Gamma Psi president!
There's a note, too!
Casey, can I see you in our room?
It's OK, Case. Presidential orders.
We'll talk more later?
"Thank you for thinking of Gamma Psi
in regard to this weekend's four-pack.
We regret to inform you
that we have a prior commitment.
But please consider Gamma Psi
in the future.
XoXo. Sisters in solidarity.
Gamma Psi."
You have to stop.
That's your fourth.
Then stop rereading the letter!
It's not gonna change their answer!
Plus, I'm eating the evidence.
There's no point
in eating the evidence.
The sisters will know we're not having
a four-pack if we don't have one!
We've been rejected twice.
We have to accept it.
No, we've been rejected twice
and no one can know about it!
The whole school knows about this party!
I hired a photographer to take pictures.
Pictures that will be
memorialized in hardback.
The yearbook, Casey!
Is Abby hiding in here?
She's late for her lesson
on how to drink seductively
from both a cup and a bottle.
You'd better go find her then,
because this party is proceeding
as planned!
I can't be the one responsible
for running this house into the ground.
You're not responsible for running
this house into the ground.
It's the cycle, or fate or whatever.
Girls might deactivate if I don't do
something. This four-pack has to happen.
Please help me.
Let's make this work.
The Gamma Psis are reasonable girls.
They're so nice,
it's almost disgusting.
So if we appeal to them woman-to-woman,
lay our cards on the table,
maybe we can get them
to change their minds.
OK. That sounds good.
You could talk to Katherine.
She's a Gamma Psi,
maybe you can play
the panhellenic-solidarity card.
It's one thing for me
to ask Evan for a favor,
but I don't want to drag my brand-new
relationship with Katherine into this,
especially since I'm hoping she will
give me this panhellenic board position.
Let's take it straight to Natalie.
I also want to know
where they got these cupcakes from.
Because they're really good.
- Hey, it's Rusty...
- Seriously, Rusty?
You have to be planning this.
What are you doing here?
I know something happened
with Cappie.
I think I'm kind of done with him.
- Jackass blew me off.
- No, wait! That might be my fault.
I told him that joke
about how he shouldn't blow it
because you're so perfect for him.
That freaked him out.
- I don't date guys with issues.
- Someone without a college degree
shouldn't be so choosy.
- Who is this?
- Please!
Can you give him another chance?
This isn't exactly a mystery, Rusty.
When a guy starts breaking dates
with you after things get physical,
it means he just wanted to hook-up.
I have a wedding
between a labradoodle
and a shih-tzu to cater.
Sorry, Rowdy.
It's cool.
She's all right.
I mean, Sheila had
a way better rack.
So did you hear we might be having
a four-pack with Gamma Psi this weekend?
You and Grant gonna go together?
Yeah, I guess,
the same way we always go together.
Pretending like we're not together.
Maybe you should just go together.
Like for real this time.
Because, you're planning on telling
the brothers at some point, right?
What is this about?
All anyone can talk about is
how I gave up my trust fund.
Or they're questioning
everything I do, like Trip.
Trip's still pissed off about
how hard you hazed him during hell week.
I wouldn't take it personally.
Maybe I would.
But what are you saying?
That we should come out
so they'll talk about us instead?
It sounds kind of obnoxious
if you put it that way.
Kind of.
But since you want
to come out anyway...
I don't know what I want to do.
But it's up to me to figure it out, OK?
ZBZs, what are you guys doing here?
You know, the usual:
chatting about global politics, and,
- a house-related leisure issue...
- We need to talk to Natalie about
- the world's most awesome four-pack!
- That too.
- We know about your prior commitment...
- There's no prior commitment.
That is what Natalie tells people
whom she doesn't want to mix with.
Did she send you
the little frowny-face cupcakes?
We were just wondering
if there was a chance you would
put in a word for us
about her changing her mind?
That's Natalie's ouevre.
I don't really do leisure issues, so...
Good luck.
What bakery did she get
those cupcakes... from?
You liked the cupcakes?
I made them myself.
Secret ingredient:
a little bit of love!
What an honor to get a visit
from my two favorite ZBZs!
The honor is all ours! We're so bummed
to hear about your prior commitment.
Especially since it apparently
doesn't exist?
I was trying to spare your feelings.
I was being polite.
I didn't want ZBZ to spend that money
when I know my girls aren't gonna go.
- They wouldn't show up?
- Our gals are pretty selective.
They're always wondering,
"What's in it for Gamma Psi?"
The political stuff gives me
a tummy-ache, but what can you do?
You're fourth.
- Then, I guess there's no...
- There's got to be something we can do!
Anything! Do you guys
need a favor of some kind?
Like doing our laundry or something?
Paying our electric bill?
- No way.
- OK.
What? Really?
Yes. The electric bill.
Ash! We can't...
I got this.
We'll pay your electric bill
until the end of the school year.
What do you say?
What a generous offer.
And of course you will make sure
all your sisters show up tonight?
Of course.
And we can keep this little exchange
- between us?
- Of course.
Chocolate bunny?
Thank you for your service.
I salute you.
I knew it.
I knew you loved her!
Don't startle a man in a strip club.
What if I'd been in lap-dance position?
- How'd you know I was here?
- Beaver told me you were here.
This is an unclean place.
You shouldn't be here.
I have a friend and I want
to introduce you to.
His name is Jesus,
and he pays much greater dividends
than those dollar bills
in your underpants.
Why are you blowing Lana off? We talked,
and she's ready to give up on you.
- You talked?
- Yes. She had her shirt off.
That doesn't matter!
I know you're in love with her
and you can't stand it
or else you wouldn't be here.
You only come here
when your heart's broken.
I'm here because
I want to be around girls
no more complex than strippers,
who are really just nice girls
with bad dads.
Tell me about your father.
Was he bad?
Because I have a very good father
I'd like to talk to you about.
This is what you do.
You did it with Casey because you were
scared you guys were too different.
But lady Cappie
is never going to give you
a hard time about the things
that make you.
And that's why I couldn't
let you do this.
Spitter, what did you do?
The name's Rowdy.
Rowdy takes matters
into his own hands.
She's here to give you another chance.
Hey, Lana.
Listen closely, spitter:
I don't want another chance...
Really? You don't like her?
This looks amazing!
Totally A-, very last minute.
With these lampy light things,
I hope we're not paying OC's bill, too.
I did what I had to do.
And see, the yearbook photographer
is documenting all of it for posterity.
Oh, my god, is that a caricaturist!?
Look, I'm on the moon!
It's classy because it's art.
And he was also half-off
with the ice sculptures.
Ice sculptures? The founders'
day money is supposed to last us
- through next year's rush.
- But that's next year.
- This will get us back on top now.
- When I said you weren't running
this hous into the ground?
I was wrong
I'm the one everyone's gonna blame
if we start losing sisters.
You asked me for help and then you
don't listen to my advice!
I'm the president. I have to do what
I think is right.
I'm going to go greet
gamma psi's president.
So, Tim, lacrosse sounds like
an interesting sport.
- What position do you play?
- Mid-fielder.
That's awesome.
See you around.
What was that?You have
something against mid-fielders?
You said leave them wanting more.
And I have a boyfriend!
This is how you leave them
wanting more. Watch.
You really wear a suit.
Most guys can't.
What are you doing?
Sorry! Um, I was teaching the pledges
how to flirt. That was a demonstration
Great job.
Come on, heather, let's go
find another guy for you.
I don't know what's taking
them so long at the bar.
- I'm gonna go ask.
- No, wait, wait...
Look how talented these girls are.
And limber.
What are they, cats?
Sure.
If you wanted to break up with her,
why didn't you just tell her?
Hey, I was doing the immature guy thing
where I blow her off and wait for her
to get the hint. It's worked for men for
thousands of years, because their friend
don't usually intervene
and screw it all up.
You sure you're not just driving her
away because you love her too much?
I think you love her too much.
I barely know her.
There is something.
I think I want someone a little less
flaky.
She's like you.
You see yourself reflected in her,
and don't like what you see.
- Are you growing up?
- You shut your damn mouth!
Cappie, if I can get rowdy,
then you can...
You guys having fun?
So far ten girls are coming with me
to bible study next week.
Or I just became their new pimp.
- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Sure.
I'm not a dumbass. I know you
don't want me here.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
Can you just tell her the truth?
No touching the girls.
Excuse me...
Viper. This is a misunderstanding.
She's not a girl.
Not a girl?
You're saying strippers
aren't real people?
I got news for you,
these women
are somebody's daughters.
Or mothers. Heck, I got a grandmother
here.
You better think about that,
pipsqueak.
The name's rowdy rusty.
Uh, rus, I wouldn't.
He's really...
And I'm not scared of your
pierced things and your tattoos.
Katherine? You're leaving?
My policy on parties is
basicaly a five-minute walk-through, but
I rather enjoyed the caricaturist
and thought he captured my likeness,
so I stayed a little bit longer.
You're lucky ZBZ paid
for an open bar.
Hey, trip, you're lucky you ever got
into omega chi in the first place.
Looks like you need a drink
as badly as I do.
Oh, I am the talk of the party.
I didn't know how good I had it when
people were nice to me because of
my last name.
I don't even think i'd be omega chi
president if I weren't a chambers.
You have to give yourself
more credit.
And if it makes you feel any better, ZBZ
is going to be more broke than you are
by the end of this party.
What was ashleigh thinking?
She was thinking about how it feel being
president who's losing control of house
Take it from me,
it can make you do some really
crazy things.
But it's the responsibility of
the president to have a cool head
and to do what's best for the house
But you're forgetting how it feels
to have that much responsibility.
Especially in a crisis when
it's your ass on the line.
I guess I'm still trying to figure out
how to be the president's best friend.
Cheers to that.
I just love caricatures, don't you?
Oh, my god, I totally love caricatures!
I knew it was a good idea!
Can I talk with you for a minute?
Not right now.
Natalie and I were just talking about
how much we love caricatures.
Yes. But you two talk.
We're leaving now anyway.
- Leaving?
- But it's 10:30.
We said we'd come,
not that we'd stay.
Thanks again for paying
our electric bill!
Oops! That was loud.
You paid the gamma psis
to come to this party?
This is pathetic. I knew we shouldn't
have gotten involved with this party.
Come on, guys.
Nice job.
Should we take off?
This is kind of a disaster.
So you're on trip's side?
It's cool. We can stay.
I may not have money anymore, Trip,
but I am still your president.
You may not be for long. You're turning
omega chi into a joke.
First by being dumb enough to give away
your trust fund, and now this slag-fest.
Well, I guess it can't get
any worse.
Smile for the yearbook.
What the hell were you thinking?
You kissed my boyfriend!
That is not gonna work anymore.
We're really screwed.
How could you let us
be humiliated like this?
I know it looks bad...
Forget number four we'll be lucky
if we're top ten after this. And since
you spent all our money on this supid
party, we have no way of getting back up
Give me one good reason why all of us
pledges shouldn't de-pledgeright now.
I...
I can't.
How can we have any faith in you
as our president?
Because she didn't know
anything about it.
I did it.
It's my fault.
I panicked and I offered to
pay gamma psi's electric bill.
Ashleigh didn't even know about it.
No, it's true. She's just covering for
me, because she's a good friend.
That's not true.
Ashleigh is the best president
we've ever had.
We need to rally behind her,
and move on.
So you slipped on a wet dollar bill
and fell.
You're still rowdy Rusty,
standing up to viper like that.
Yeah. And I got up after I fell!
Yeah, but then you fell down again.
Why was that dollar bill wet?
Have you thought about pledging
the JC House? Let me tell you about him
Hey, if I can stand up to a guy named
viper, you can break up with lana.
Maturely.
It's not gonna kill you.
Viper didn't kill me!
Jesus knows how to party.
Dude makes his own wine.
Come on. Let's get you cleaned up.
I guess I should explain why
I've been blowing you off.
Whatever.
We were just hanging out.
Are we still, or not?
I guess not.
I thought this was what I wanted,
but I want, um, I want
someone... Different.
All you college guys are the same.
Hook up with a hot townie for a while
before you realize you can't handle it.
Something like that.
Why do you care if I'm ok?
I'm the jerk that tried to
mess with your relationship
to benefit my presidency.
- Sorry.
- It's all right.
- I know you're feeling lot of pressure.
- Maybe I should just resigne
- before trip starts his coup.
- Don't give that jackass what he wants.
There's plenty of other guys in
the house that have your back.
Like me
Thanks man
And please know that when you do decide
to tell the house about grant,
I've got your back too.
I'm not sure that i'm going to be
telling the house anytime soon.
- What do you mean?
- I mean I'm starting to wonder
if he's the right guy for me.
- Pizza?
- I'm buying.
It really does make
your nose tingle.
I think I'm sticking with
sparkling cider for a while.
Rowdy rusty's retiring.
He was too easily influenced by
hot naked ladies anyway.
And he made me behave like a grown-up
more than i'm comfortable with.
I can't handle rowdy rusty.
Let's just give the nicknames
a rest.
now that you're acting all mature.
Shut your damn mouth...
Again.
- slightly more mature.
- Thank you.
Now will you tell me? Why did
you go to gentleman's choice?
I like the lukewarm taco meat.
Come on.
Don't read into it,
You only go there when you're
thinking about a girl.
Last time it was...
I think I see where this is headed.
Don't read into it, dale.
Come on, let's just do another shot
That was the longest night
of my life.
They kept us up talking about the state
of the house until four in the morning.
Girls talk a lot.
Should we get up?
I'm scared to leave this room.
I'm just gonna resign.
There's no reason you should take the
fall for me being a terrible president.
You can't resign.
Don't say it. Don't say that I souldn't
resign because i'm a great president.
I wasn't going to say that
you're a great president.
I was going to say that you can't resign
because that would only lead to further
instability. Which we cannot have. We'd
be playing right into gamma psi's hands.
You're right.
And gamma psi seemed so nice.
With their cupcakes and their
bunny mascot.
Bunnies look cute, then they bite you
with their big sharp bunny teeth.
And they sleep where they poop.
You can't trust a bunny.
So what are we gonna do?
You won't mind taking my advice?
Are you kidding?
Let's discuss the facts.
Gamma psi targeting us for
humiliation is a good thing.
They wouldn't need to destroy us if they
didn't think of us as a threat.
- We're still in the game.
So let's go start playing.
I'm gonna eat a frowny-face
cupcake for breakfast.