Prevsly On "Greek"...
What's with this...
ZBZ mixer?
Aren't they all about mixing with
those KT losers this semester?
I am starting to wonder.
...if he's even the right guy for me.
- Wow. You can really wear a suit.
- What're you doing?
We said we'd come.  Not that we'd stay.
Thanks again for paying
our electric bill.
I may not have money, Trip,
but I am still your president.
You may not be for long.
- Dale, what're you doing?
I saw you making all this progress
and realized that you're real competition.
I've looked at you like a friend,
and you look down on me like The Anchor.
Russ...
Cap, I poured my heart out to you at the
End of the World party,
and you didn't come after me.
But I'm here now.
I'm feeling pretty cheap here.
You were asleep, and I'm totally late.
Ashleigh's gonna wonder where I slept.
You know, it's killing me not telling her.
It's only been a week.
And it's been an amazing week.
You can't keep putting this off.
You have to tell Evan.
We both agreed he should know first
and you said you'd handle it.
It's just tough to get
any alone time with him.
Someone's always
in the Amphora lair...
...lighting torches...
...electing
the next president...
- Oops, I just broke the code.
- Come on, Cap.
I'm just a little nervous because finally,
after all this time,
we're back to being
friends again.
And you're worried
that friendship will fall apart
when he learns we're together?
Well, not to mention,he seemed
pretty against it at the End of the World party.
But this time we're gonna get it right.
We're three years wiser.
Maybe you're three years wiser.
So you'll tell him?
Absotely. I will e-Mail this morning.
- Cap.
- All right, I'll text him. Or E-vite, inviting him
to the conversation.
Yesterday, Ash wanted to know
why I had this smile,
and I couldn't think of
an excuse, so I told her
I was thinking about the rise
and fall of Mischa Barton.
So you have to tell Evan now.
Then we can pick this back up.
- Pick what up?
- This.
- Maybe I should go tell him now. Yeah.
- Then I can tell Ashleigh.
Dale. We need to talk.
Really?! We've done so well this past week
not talking.
I need half your cable bill.
It's due today.
Today?
You could've told me a little
sooner, you know?
I wrote you a message
in my grant project notes.
- I'm surprised you didn't see it.
-  For the love of...
You know what?
I apologized for that already.
Even though I don't think
I had anything to apologize for.
if this is you back with God,
I think I liked the godless Dale better.
It'll all be moot when I win
the Innovation Grant today.
When you win?
I have a shot, too.
I've seen your notes. You still
haven't gotten your wire to re-conduct.
Actually, the same night...
my self-healing wire turned
on for a full three minutes.
- Three minutes?
- Just like your mother.
All right, well, then I guess...
the better man will win.
I think we both know
who that man is.
It's me.
Transcripted by YesCool
Www.addic7ed.com
I slink down Greek Row looking mighty fine
Howling to the moonlight
on a hot winter night
Singing the blues while the other girls cry...
Stop marki and give it your all!
SongFest is in two days!
The drop-down is on the four!
The four! Let's step through it again.
Great job, Beth. The house is so lucky
to have a real Dance major.
And I'm so lucky that it's me.
Hey! Where were you last night?
- Did you have a boy-girl sleep-over?
- Maybe.
Who? The scruffy emo guy from the library?
He's scruffy all right.
And really awesome.
And someone you know.
Are you ready?
Cappie and I are back together.
You got back together with Cappie?
- Seriously?
- Who cares?
Get your asses back in line!
Now!
Well, I guess it was inevitable.
I want you to know I rarely try
to sleep with the same ex twice.
Thanks, Becks.
I'm... almost touched.
Now go dance.
And
five, six, seven, eight!
Wow.
Wow. That is just so...
"Wow", good? "Wow", bad?
"Wow" could mean a lot of things.
No, I mean "wow", I hope you don't
disappear into the KT black hole.
'Cause SongFest is the
second most Blue Ribbon
points after Greek Week,
- and you're one of our best dancers.
- I won't ditch you. I promise.
Good.
Because we are on a mission to take
back number one from Gamma Psi,
I don't want any distractions.
Hang on.
- Katherine texted me.
- What does she want?
I don't know.
But I know what I want: an apology for
what they did to us at the four-pack.
Hey, Cap, what's the...
urn-mergency?
It's a good one.
Wait, what's wrong?
Well...
Let me just start by saying that
your opinion means a lot to me.
OK...
You know that I value...
you.
Am I getting fired?
The opposite actually. Let's think of this as
bringing another member into our team...
...she'll be working
directly under me...
Cap, what're you talking about?
Casey and I got back
together on Thanksgiving.
Wow. OK.
You waited all week to tell me?
I was just
worried how you'd react.
Why? You still think that
I have feelings for her?
No. At the End of the World party
you told me not to go after her.
Why, do you have feelings forer?
No, no. We're just friends.
We're totally just friends.
Man, you know what, I regret
saying what I said at the party.
This is gonna be good. This
is gonna be really good.
It's great. Nothing is gonna change.
We'll all be pals, you know, like...
...like Harry Potter...
...and, um, you know,
the other two.
I appreciate that. Thank you.
So... you're OK with it? Really?
Yeah. Yeah, of course, man. Congrats.
- Come on.
- Thanks.
And... I'll catch you later, all right?
You know, just tell Casey
that I'll see her at Quidditch practice.
- Another good one.
- You can stop.
- I'm sorry.
- OK.
Stop lollygagging, Cartwright.
You don't need to be concerned with
your pasty, four-eyed friend.
The judges will be here any minute.
OK. I'm almost done.
You seem to be preoccupied
with your competition.
Why don't you go speak to him?
I got nothing to say to him.
I'm not suggesting intelligent
discourse, Dale.
If you think he's a threat,
go over and rattle his cage.
Never underestimate the
value of the head game.
Watch this.
Looking good, Milton.
See that?
I don't know that that's necessary.
You want to win, don't you?
Be the best? Come on.
Hey, Rus?
Or should I say Anchor?
That's a sweet light bulb.
If I clap twice will it turn on?
That's...a good one, Dale.
What, you're not going to respond?
You told me not to...
He just fired a shot across your bow.
In your people's vernacular, it's on!
Show him what you've got.
Hey, Dale, if I'm The Anchor,
then you're the canker...
sore... in my mouth.
Oh! Anchor told Kettlewell he's
in his mouth! Good one, Ank.
- Just gonna take that?
- Yeah, Rusty...
I bet you do have canker sores...
...from all the unsavory
women you've made out with.
Oh! Point, Diz-ale! On a comebiz-ack!
It's your turn. Make it count.
At least I didn't lose my
virginity to our landlady,
and then ask her to marry me.
Oh, my God!
I was doing right by her!
You wanna have a conversation?!
Time to focus.
So, what are you up to tonight?
Oh, I was thinking about
busting up some KTs.
Oh, wait, that's probably you.
OK, stop.
- Can we please put this behind us?
- You're the one who hasn't
wanted to talk about it.
Talk about that I like looking
out for my house and brothers?
OK, so you'll like looking out for them
but you don't want to be honest with them.
- I knew this was about me coming out.
- It's not just about that.
It's about this whole Mr. Tough Guy crap,
how quick you were to turn on Evan, who,
by the way, is keeping your secret.
And look at Evan: He came
out about his... money.
Now everybody treats him
different. I don't want that.
So maybe if I show them
that I'm a good brother...
-...they'll take the news better.
- Grant, they're gonna take
the news the way they want to.
If they have issues with it,
then that's their problem.
There's a lot of better ways
to be a good brother
- You don't understand.
- Grant...
...I am the only one in
the house that does.
It is simple, costumes revealing
genitals are unacceptable.
If you read your SongFest handbook,
it's all spelled out in the rules.
I cannot wait for the day when
I am paid to be this organized.
I had to book vendors, organize security...
Walk out on our four-pack
to make ZBZ look like losers.
Is something bothering you, ZBZ?
My name is Casey,
and yes something is bothering me.
You and your sisters screwed us.
four-pack, I don't concern myself
with inter-soritpolitics.
You're a part of Gamma Psi. Your house
went from girl scouts to the Real Housewives
of pick-your-city overnight.
Yes, but I'm also
Panhellenic President.
People like us have to rise
above the petty politics
that exist between houses,
which I thought you could do.
Which is why I wanted to speak with you.
As you kno there's an Vice President of Judicial.
I want you to serve.
- What!?
- You have good ideas, Casey, and drive.
and I need a VP of Judicial who
is not
afraid to disagree with me.
I agree. But not all the time!
I'm not afraid to disagree
with you when you're wrong.
Which you are not,
currently.
As VPJ you would oversee
Greek disciplinary action,
you would help draft
new legislation.
Yes, you get your ownlipboard.
- My own clipboard?
- Just FYI.
Eighty-five percent of VPJs from CRU
go on
to receive JDs or MBAs.If that's something
that interests you?
All of those letters
interest me a lot!
as a Board member, you're
expected to be impartial,
so you can't  participate in
any inter-sorority competions.
So...
So I'd have to drop out
of ZBZ's SongFest skit?
I need your answer by tomorrow. OK?
That's good right there!
I'm so happy my big brother
is dating my big sister.
- You've waited a long time to say that, haven't you?
- Maybe.
Don't worry. I know you're
her little brother, so...
I'm not worried about her.
How's your project going?
I finished my presentation earlier,
but Dale and I are still fighting
over  who's gonna win tonight.
Yeah, Daley did  mention you
guys were having some problems
this morning at Krav-Maga.
Now listen...
Every friendship has its rough patches.
And if you're really friends you'll find a
way to work it out in the End.
Like Harry Potter...
and those other two.
OK. Holy crap, you guys,
I'm graduating!
What is that?
- Crickets!
- Gross!
I hate crickets!
Ever sincePinocchio.
They're too bossy.
They're coming from the fireplace.
"Enjoy your crickets, losers. XO OX"
Wait. The Omega Chis pranked us?
The old crickets-down-the-chimney gag.
This has Evan Chambers
written all over it.
Remember how I said everything
will work out in the end?
Well, maybe I was wrong.
How do I look?
Like SongFest gold
and you know it.
I do. Try yours on.
First, I wanted... I wanted to talk
to you about my meeting with Katherine.
Tell me how it went.
Did you let her have it?
Yes. I told her to stop calling
me ZBZ and call me Casey.
Wow. And then what?
And then she offered me a Panhellenic
Board position. Wait, she offered you a job?
Yeah, Vice President of Judicial.
VPJ, yay!
Which means I would have
to drop out of our skit.
What?!
It's a big opportunity!
No, she's a Gamma Psi, Case.
You went over there to chew her out
and she bribed you!
She did not bribe me, Ash.
You are under a lot of pressure.
You want to win SongFest...
Yeah. So did you.
until Katherine came along.
Crickets?
Really, dude?
You could've warned me.
They're in every crack of our house.
See?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I found this in our chimney,
along with the entire cast of "A Bug's Life."
You must've known what
your house was up to, right?
Well, you did tag our plaque in
your Thanksgiving break -in.
This is this about Casey, isn't it?
- I knew this would happen.
- What?
Things would get all weird
when you guys got back together.
Since you're the one
making it weird, Nostradamus,
I'm not exactly impressed by your
ability to predict the future.
I was just being honest.
OK, Last time you were honest,
you ended up regretting what You said.
I regret that I said that.
OK? I don't understand why you want
to go through that again.
You still don't think Casey and I will wk?
Hey, I hope I'm wrong,
- but given the history...
- Trust me,
this time it will be different.
Thank you all for participating.
Your projects were amazing!
Yes, yes, everyone gets a ribbon,
you're special just for trying...
Announce the winners already.
The finalists are...
Samir Nagra...
Yes!
Kim Cervenka...
- Li Yin Tan...
- Awesome!
Dale Kettlewell...
Yes!
Was there any doubt?
- ...and Rusty Cartwright.
- I did it?!
I did it!
Not bad, for The Anchor.
Your final projects were all so good,
that we need more time to
thoroughly evaluate each one.
As a result, we'll announce
the winner next semester.
Thank you all for coming.
Hey, man, have you heard anything about
the guys dumping a boatload of crickets
into the Kappa Tau chimney?
I'm sure Grant knows.
- Things still bad there?
- Yeah. And getting worse.
Yeah, I know how you feel.
Probably not entirely...
...but, um, yeah,
a few of the guys are still
treating me weird.
- Stand your ground.
- Yeah, you, too.
Hey guys,
we're getting a poker game
started. Wanna join us?
I'll pass.
Yeah, Chambers. Hundred-dollar buy-in.
Can you handle that?
I'll pass.
Actually, I'll stake you in this game.
Consider it payback for all those
shots you've bought us in the past.
Thanks, Grant.
You guys gonna make out or play?
I'm out.
I'm in.
Son of a...
What the hell is this?!
"You hit the...
KT wall."
Krappa Tau is gonna pay for that.
Gamma Psi tonight
I've never seen so many Gamma
Psis together in one place.
They look like those creepy little
kids from Village of the Damned.
Gamma Psi's the best and we got game
So step back
Boy, do not approach
They're good.
They're good, but they're no ZBZ.
I'd feel a lot better if
we had our entire cast.
You guys are gonna do fine without me.
Gamma Psi tonight
Gamma Psi.
Hey, Case. I hope you guys are
ready for a little competion.
I mean, the Mu Gamma Sigs might give
you guys a run for your money.
Natalie,
shouldn't you be protecting
your pot of gold?
Casey, that mean girl says
I can't do SongFest.
What? Who?
Katherine,
did you tell Beth that
she can't do SongFest?
Afraid so. Participants have to be
current members of their ho
Beth deactivated ZBZ last semester
when she went I-Kap, so...
OK. I'll send her home.
- What?
- Oh, you can't use her dance, either.
- What? You can't be serious.
- What?
As VPJ frontrunner,
I think you should understand the rules.
That just happen to knock us
out the day before SongFest.
You just sabotaged our house,
you can't expect her...
I don't have your response
on the VP of Judicial job.
I really stuck my neck out for you,
so I'd like your answer now...
please.
I decline.
So you're gonna
turn this down so you can dance
in a skit that you don't have?
My house needs me.
Moving on.
to be one of those couples
that holds hands?
I don't know. Let me see your hand.
So how did Evan take it?
Pretty well. You know Evs.
Did Ashleigh explode over the news?
Yeah, she was a little worried that
you'd pull my focus from SongFest.
Obviously not. I missed you last night.
We were up until four a.m. trying
to come up with a new dance.
And all we agreed on was that
Katherine is another Frannie,
- only evil-er.
- So tonight's out of the question?
After SongFest is over, I promise.
- Think you can wait that long?
- Oh, ok.
But any longer and I'm
gonna start without you.
- Wow, sweaty much?
- Ok, that is you!
Cap!
Oh... Evan, hey.
Hey, Case... do you mind if I talk
to Cap alone for a few sec?
- What is going on?
- Why don't you ask him?
He walled in our front door cause
he didn't appreciated my honesty
This has nothing to do with your honesty.
It's about the swarm of crickets
that's still in our house.
Ok you guys, you can't let your houses
get in the way of your friendship.
And until you get them to declare a
truce, none of this will ever change.
- Katie is a stowing up on this.
- Crickets, Evan.
Douchebag.
Maybe... what you guys need
is a common ennemy.
Cappie. Who did the Kappa
Tau hate the most?
Ryan Seacrest.
Oh, no, no, no, wait... wait...
Officer Huck.
And who did the Omega Chis hate the most?
Liberals?
- Huck.
- So...
maybe...
we got our houses to team up against him.
Fight over our hatred for Huck together.
Right?
Hey! So I thought we could celebrate
the end of this ridiculous competition
between you to, with a .... pizza.
So? Who won?
- They haven't decided yet.
So neither of us won.
- Well, not yet anyway...
- Hey!
- You're not gonna eat out.
Guys, what the hell?
- He keeps rubbing me the wrong way.
- Is there a right way to rub you?
- Ok, this is ridiculous.
- Well, we need to do something soon.
Because if I have to live like
this until next semester,
- What? You're gonna take me down?
- Oh, I can take you up and down.
- Well, there's only one
way to settle this then.
- Whoa, guys.
And what's that?
Battle Bots.
- You're on.
Wait... how about this?
I just saw someone on the dancefloor once.
That's fine if you wanna get pregnant.
How about this?
Really?
You know, I never thought I'd say this...
but without Beth, we're screwed.
But we can't let Katherine win.
We just have to be the best we
can be with the people we have.
You know what, it's just too bad we
don't have someone who can choreograph.
Oh, for the billionth time Abby, you don't
have to raise your hand to ask a question.
It's more of a suggestion
actually. For a new dance.
No offense, but what do you
know about choreography?
I choreographed three of
my high school musicals,
the third one, was our senior year.
Oh, well we are desperate.
And we're all in this together.
So...
What you doing Spitter?
I have 24 hours to modify a base-line robot
with standardize weaponry to destroy Dale?
Ok.
Gemini wants you to be
careful with your killer robot.
Who's Gemini?
We came to an understanding.
- An official meeting now?
- No, sorry, I was just...
killing a cricket. But I
do have an annoucement.
We're gonna finally get
back at Officer Huck.
Rusty has a killer-robot, so maybe
after he kills Dale, we can like...
- attack Huck with it or something.
- We're not gonna need the robot Beav.
We have help this time.
The Omega Chis.
- Cap, are you drunk?
- Nope, I'm serious.
I talmked to Evan,
our houses are gonna pull
off the plan together.
- Why? Those guys are jerk.
- It's not like we can trust them.
Gemini agrees with Rusty.
True, but...
what better way not to trust someone
that to trust them with someone
you distrust more than them?
That makes no sense at all.
- Exactly.
- It works for me.
Me too.
Oh, Gemini!
Great. Meeting adjourned.
Nailed it.
And so with KT's help we'll
pull off the ultime prank.
And Huck and the school will
remember for years to come.
Why do we wanna do anything with the KTs?
Yeah, we don't need them
to screw with Huck.
- Huh, that's true, but... I think...
- Was this your idea or them?
We came up with this together.
Come on, Chambers.
Guys, just back off, alright?
You guys have been on Evan's ass
ever since he gave up his money.
This has nothing to do with money.
It's about Evan being who he was
before he gave up his money.
And I'm still that guy.
The Evan Chambers we elected as president
wouldn't have taken the back seat to anyone.
He's right, Evan.
I'm sorry.
The Evan Chambers I voted for
wouldn't join someone's else plan.
He'd have one of his own.
We need a prank that
shows how awesome we are.
Or maybe we'd just need another president.
Meeting adjourned.
Thank you Pi
for that wildly inappropriate
rendition of "Wild Things".
Next up, we have ZBZ.
This is it Beav, Casey's up.
Maybe she and her buckle will do "Bound".
Can't say I haven't thought about it.
ZBZ!
What is taking so long?
Well, I guess this means ZBZ
is not coming. Moving on.
Yo Casey!
Teach me, teach me, teach me!
So what, do I start dancing like
right here flesh mob style?
- Ok, no, honey...
- What? Sorry.
Case, we're waiting for the results.
Ash, wow.
Who's that girl?
Oh... she's a friend.
Congratulations, you were so so great.
Thanks.
- I'll catch up with you later.
- Ok.
- So I'm in.
- Well, that means we're both in.
We're waiting further.
Do you have any idea what
comes ou of your mouth?
- No, do you?
- Guys.
We'll meet later at the students' union.
All right.
Hey, richkin.
Wanna grab a drink at Dobler's afterwards?
Oh, sorry I gotta raincheck, but
you looked pretty awesome up there.
I know.
The scores are in.
The winner of this year SongFest,
and "15 blue" event points
is
Gamma Psi!
What?
We were way better than
these demonic munchkins.
They cheated, they had to.
Katherine tailed the votes.
Maybe we should temper with them...
Yeah, well, even if she did, we
can't prove it, so we're screwed.
All we need to do is... is
check the score sheets...
which would be on her clipboard.
So we're gonna ask to see her clipboard?
We don't have to ask.
I guess this is it. No professors...
no projects...
just you and me.
It had to be.
Articulated hydraulic, mano a mano.
Well, here's a fair fight.
There's nothing fait about this Rust
Fair would be me winning my grand.
Because for the last year and a half I'v
spent every waking minute on school.
While you've been out with
your girls and your frat bros.
Hey guys, save it for the Battle Bots.
No, no. 'Cause I sacrifize
and I make the hard choices
while everything just fall in your lap.
You had a D on your midterm, you
almost flake on the extra credit,
and everything just works out.
Hey, I worked hard too!
Not half as hard as I have.
And you know it.
I deserve this.
You don't.
Can you believe it?
Well,
Rusty, all seems good for you,
you know, school, Kappa
Tau, girlfriends...
all he has is science.
And, God, we barely talked this semester.
So I just should let him win
because I feel bad for him?
No, I'm just saying, this
guy has one thing in his life
take that away from him...
You're a scientist, you can do the math.
Good thing they didn't leave a single light
on since we're paying their electric bill.
Found a candle.
Jasmine.
What? It's dark in here.
That's why we brought our flashlights.
I think they were in a rush to hit
Dobler's. Everyone, start looki
- Ooh! I think I found it!
- Let's see it.
OK, the judges gave us
95, 95, 99, and a zero?
- Someone gave us a zero out of 100?
- This one judge. Ryan.
He also gave the Gamma Psis a 100!
That's so shady!
Yeah, all the others gave
Gamma Psi low 80S.
Does that mean they bribed the judge?
Oh! They're like mini-Sopranos.
Well, if that's the case,
then we have our proof.
Yeah, let's go.
Come on.
We were right, Lambers.
This is the ultimate prank.
Let's go downstairs, get some
extra rope just to be safe.
- Cap, come on.
- Sure.
- Guys, you good for a sec?
- Got it, Cap.
Guys!
Evan, get in.
You guys are bailing?
- Run, Cap.
- We're not even done here.
What're you talking about?
Evan, hurry.
Guys! We can't hold this forever!
- They need our help up there.
- Get in the truck. All right.
- You called the cops!
- Sorry, Cap.
Listen to me, I'm doing you a favor.
Run!
But, wait...
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, my God!
Sweet mother of mercy.
The Mach 5!
- We gotta go.
- What? Where are Wade and the guys?
- We can't help.
- Let's get the hell out of here.
Oh, dear lord, that's a sticky wicket.
Don't move!
They went that-a-way!
In this corner, standing
a member of a non-academic frat,
It's Rusty "The Anchor" Cartwright!
In this corner, he's a born
-again landlady lay-er
from Wetumpka, Arkansas,
weighing at he-wouldn't-tell-us,
the ultimate, extreme circuit boarder,
Dale "The Lightning Rail" Kettlewell.
Please let this be quick.
On your marks,
get set...
...Battle Bots!
Close shave, huh, Rus?!
Yeah!
Anchor's away, Dale!
How does that feel?
What's wrong, Dale?
What's wrong with your robot?
This guy's gonna lose to Rusty!
Looks like we got ourselves a new Anchor!
No, no, no, no...
Dale wins!
Dale wins, everybody!
Congratulations, Dale.
Thanks, Rusty. Looks like we finally
found out who the better man is.
- Dale! Dale! Dale! Dale!
- Ok...
Dale! Dale!
Smells like someone's grilling.
I really hope not.
Rebecca, did you remember
to blow out that candle?
Guys...
Back at the house.
We need to talk.
Outside. I don't want you in my house.
I'm glad you made it out OK...
You planned this?
Listen to me, all right?
Yes, we left your guys holding
the cart and called the police.
So we'd get caught.
I had to do it to get my house back.
And your solution was to get
three of my brothers expelled.
Expelled?
God, no, that wasn't the plan.
We thought they'd get community service.
- That's a hell of a plan.
- What was I supposed to do, man?!
Give up my house and take a backseat to
you and Casey like I did. Freshman year?
Come on!
When it comes down to
choosing between friends
and brothers, you have to
choose your brothers.
Yeah,
you made your choice pretty clear.
Wait. Listen. Listen.
You have the perfect girl,
guys who worship you.
My house is all I have left.
Well, you're right about that.
Oh, and if I were you, I would
go out through the back gate.
What happened?
Oh! Thank God you guys are OK.
When we heard the sirens
I thought maybe you guys
were in the Gamma Psi house.
- We weren't there.
- Thank God,
for a second there I thought that
maybe you guys had started the fire.
No, we were there,
but we didn't start the fire.
We hope not.
I left a candle burning, not a campfire!
But, maybe you can explain that to the
police since you love talking about it.
Oh, my God! The police?
We're all gonna go to girl jail like
those prison movies my boyfriend watches!
- It's Katherine!
- Oh, no. That's the mean girl.
OK, I got it.
Katherine,
- I can't believe this.
- I know. It is surreal.
But I plan on doing everything in
my power to investigate this.
Is that necessary? It
could've been an accident.
No, it's unlikely. This is the kind of thing
that rarely occurs unless someone is at fault.
And they will be punished severely.
You should go easy, I mean...
You don't want to
overdo it, you know...
right?
That's big of you, Casey, considering
ZBZ is  the most affected.
Wait.
What are you talking about?
Irregularities in SongFest judging.
I was talking about
your house burning down.
My what?!
Oh, my God!
She didn't disqualify Beth
for no reason! She...
Which means she really wanted me for the
job. Which means she's not Frannie.
We have bigger problems.
You're our president, Ash.
What now?
We turn ourselves in, I guess.
- No.
- No?
We can't turn ourselves in because
we don't know what happened.
It's an old house. It could've been
electrical, it could've been a gas leak...
- Or a raccoon.
We'll know if we did it
when we get in trouble for it.
But until then we say nothing.
- I won't breath a word, I promise.
- Yeah.
We all need to promise.
We need to make a pact.
Yeah. Yeah, everyone gather around.
Put your pinkies up.
We, the sisters of Zeta Beta Zeta,
promise never to tell anyone
outside of these walls
what happened tonight.
Yeah.
Ok.
What are you doing here?
Rain check, remember?
I could really use a friend right now.
I can't believe Wade, Ferret
and Jeremy got expelled.
I lost four of my best friends today.
Sorry, Cap.
Well, it could be worse.
At least our house didn't burn
down like the Gamma Psi's, huh?
Yeah.
Transcripted by YesCool, and chamallow35
Greek comeback on 25th  January
www.addic7ed.com