Previously on Greek:
We'll see what we can do to
get your o-chem grades back up.
Even if I get "a's" in
my other honors classes,
i'm still gonna drop
below the required 3.5 cum.
My "d" is officially a "c".
- Wait, that's it?
- It's good enough for now.
You're a good kisser.
What are we doing?
I didn't kiss evan at the
end of the world party. I kissed fisher.
What?
I was drunk.
And I screwed up big time.
When someone cheats on me,
it's over.
Grant and I kissed. If
anyone from the house saw him,
he's screwed, 'cause he
didn't want to come out yet.
We, at pan-hellenic, are
deducting blue ribbon points
from sorities whose sisters choose
to participate in the undie run.
But it's a 60-year-old tradition
that fosters school spirit and unity.
Moving on...
Nice work saving the undie run.
Some people didn't think so.
So pan-hellenic scholarship applications
are due at the end of the month.
Moving on...
Tomorrow we start our
annual dry weekend, a chance for cru's
greek system to prove it can
actually go 48 hours without alcohol.
This is always so lame.
Excuse me?
Is she looking at me?
I understand it
might be difficult to
muster the enthusiasm for
this event you had
for running around in your underwear,
but do you have a comment, zbz?
I just said
I think... dry weekend
is a little ineffective.
Houses can't have parties
with alcohol so we...
They end up at a packed dobler's
or drinking in some
smelly fraternity basement.
That's not gonna happen. There
won't be underground partying.
Ifc and pan-hellenic are doing
sober patrols of all the houses.
And any house found in violation
faces social suspension
for one month.
Great, now it's gonna
be lame and alcohol free.
I'm sorry, we're in a small room.
Why do you think I can't hear you?
It just seems like all you're doing
is telling people what they can't do.
If the whole point of dry
weekend is to show people
they can have fun without alcohol, why
not give them something they can do?
Something that's fun.
Like?
Me? OK.
I guess we could do a
party, a progressive party.
Where each sority has a
different sober activity.
Like... A drunk-driving
simulator. Or root beer pong.
And karaoke!
Everyone loves karaoke!
Since you have such
a good take on it...
... you're in charge of dry weekend.
Me?
Moving on...
OK, so you combine
silicon tetrachloride,
diphenylmercury and...
Crap, what is it?
What about absinthe?
Absinthe isn't an
organometallic compound.
But it could be the perfect cocktail
for this year's dry weekend.
It's very hip right now.
But dry weekend is supposed
to be alcohol-free, right?
Technically, but for the
kappa taus' underground
wet weekend party, i'm reading
about the "green fairy."
Do you really think
it causes facial tics?
Whatever.
Why are you giving me this?
It's yours. Your mails
still come to the house.
- I moved out months ago!
- Yeah, there's a bunch of it.
It's the anchor.
Your nickname's Spitter
because you spit on a girl.
- What does anchor even mean?
- Maybe it means "news anchor?"
Because I'm always up on what's
going on in polymer science?
Excuse me. You
called spitter "anchor."
If I may, what is the derivation?
It's because he got such a low
grade on his o-chem midterm,
he's holding down the curve
like an anchor. Get it?
Yeah, I get it.
That's my first experience
with nerd-on-nerd hazing.
I still prefer spitter.
Yeah, me too.
Kappa Tau Team
you're here!
I was just making our
escape plan from dry weekend.
I have movies, pedicures and to honor
the occasion, an in-town bar crawl.
The bar crawl is especially
important, because that is
where i'm going to meet a new
boy who isn't fisher.
I hate to burst your new boy bubble,
but pan-hellenic's enforcing
dry weekend this year.
Each sority has to host a sober
party tomorrow night, including zbz.
What? Whose dumb idea was that?
I don't know, just some girl...
Are you done with that, ash?
I am.
He has been trying
to do that all day!
- What? Make eye contact?
- Yes! And I can't avoid him.
I don't want to see him, hear
him, or smell him ever again.
He smells like cupcakes and man.
Speaking of cupcakes and
man, since we're not going
to have alcohol at the party,
we have to have killer food,
which means we'll probably
need fisher to work tomorrow.
Stupid dry weekend!
Knock knock! Can I come in?
Fancy wrapping paper. Who's it for?
It's for my roommate's birthday.
Is he a girl?
OK, what do you want?
Can't I just come over to hang out
without having an ulterior motive?
OK, you have to get
ashleigh to forgive me.
I've apologized, groveled,
told her I liked those silly
arm warmer things she wears.
Nothing's worked.
You kissed her boyfriend.
All right? And if you're
feeling a little bit guilty,
then maybe you should be.
Guilt! That's what it is.
Sorry. Hi.
- Is this grant's room?
- Yeah.
Perfect, I'm here to
surprise him for his birthday!
Have you seen him?
Are you his sister?
What are you doing here?
Surprise!
Close family.
We having a garage
sale for the lord?
No. No tithing today.
Just, putting some of
these things in storage,
until me and god
work some of our issues out.
I don't really need nana's
crucifixion
linens around.
Or my precious moments baby angels.
They're so judgy.
Have you heard anyone
call me "anchor?"
I only said it twice.
It was behind your back.
But that was it, OK? I swear.
Not to god, of course.
This is all because
of stupid o-chem.
I've been busting my butt trying
to make up for this midterm
and now I have to deal
with my reputation?
What more can I do?
Try being known for
something other than grades.
Maybe do an outside project.
I'm thinking about doing one.
That's a great idea.
I've been tinkering
with eco-polymers.
There you go. All you
need is a faculty sponsor.
There's only one professor
I know well enough to ask.
- What do you want, cartwright?
- A minute of your time?
You have exactly one
before my weekend begins.
Since I started here at cru, I've
had this intense desire to study...
another book signing? They
expect me to spend my free time
at some stupid party to kiss larsen's
ass because he wrote a book?
I personally hate books.
And people who write them.
Makes sense, given your grades.
Which was exactly why I was thinking
you might consider
sponsoring this idea...
I don't sponsor projects.
I find them to be a waste
of my time and expertise.
The thing is, I'm really
trying to make a name for myself
- in this department.
- You mean, besides "anchor?"
- You know about that?
- I believe I started it.
And now, it's the weekend.
Saw your girlfriend, grant.
- She's smokin'!
- Yeah.
Yeah, who wouldn't
want to tap that, right?
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you about whitney.
She and I have been
dating since high school.
I'm obviously gonna end things,
but I really wanted
to do it in person.
She's here now.
Hey guys! I hope you don't mind.
I put some stuff up in
your closet. It's huge.
You could fit, like,
a person in there.
You're staying here?
Don't worry. Grant and I
won't do anything naughty...
... until you're asleep.
What's up?
Jeez, if you vibe that guy
any harder, you might get pregnant.
Tonight is my last chance
to meet a new hot guy
before I'm trapped in the house
with my old hot guy. Sober.
When did you two get so friendly?
We're not friendly. We
just have the greeting down.
Trust me, anything longer than an
elevator ride would be totally awkward.
- To dry weekend!
- Cheers to you...
And to weekends... Dry ones.
Awkward like that?
I hope you guys aren't
planning any stealth parties.
Pan-hellenic and ifc
are patrolling this year.
Not to worry. My brothers and
I are amazing at hiding liquor.
Like right now, I may or may not
have a vodka bottle down my pants.
I'm sure I can handle
whoever they send over.
They're sending me.
- What? You have to patrol?
- Nice! A cop on the inside...
who knows all your best hiding places.
Under the stairs,
the tool shed, and that secret closet
off your room where we...
... talked.
Thanks for the warning. Adios.
I can't believe you're ditching me.
I'm pretending you're the lemon.
Bitter's not pretty, ash.
Who's that?
It's katherine.
She was gonna text me
- who I'm patrolling with from ifc.
- Is it a cute boy?
And does he have any
non-cheater friends for me?
It's a boy all right.
- That looks really great, you guys.
- Thanks.
- Here you are.
It is pretty impressive
that you were able
to put this all together
on such short notice, zbz.
- What can I say? I'm awesome.
- And humble.
There's just one little hiccup.
Which is kinda funny,
because it's dry weekend.
Anyway, I was wondering
if there was someone else
I could patrol with tonight.
I'd prefer not to go with evan chambers.
Because you guys used to date?
And it didn't end well.
Bribes, power and...
My point is, it might
be a little awkward.
I know, right?
What is this, eighth grade?
Way to be powerful.
I was thinking, with all your
good ideas on dry weekend,
you might even be
pan-hellenic board material.
There's a spot on the board?
Janette dropped out to focus
on school, imagine that.
If you can't even handle
something as
simple as riding in
a golf cart with an ex,
I think I'm gonna have to find
someone who can. Moving on...
No, don't move on! I can handle it.
I can totally handle it.
Yes? Yes! Good.
Yeah, I can.
I know, beav.
It's hard to understand.
The greek council could've
at least had the decency
to give us a heads up,
so maybe I could
get a nice buzz on before
the patrols started.
That's weird. My nana usually
sends me money for my birthday.
- Times are tough.
- She must not love you anymore.
Regardless, we can't afford
being on social suspension again.
So this weekend, the kappa tau house
will be closed for business.
One weekend sober, big deal.
The rest of my college career known as
"the anchor," bigger deal.
- But you're spitter.
- I've already logged a complaint.
- You're just gonna throw in the towel?
- What else can I do?
Hastings is the only professor
I have a relationship with.
As with all relationships,
spitter, it's a numbers game.
Wade, how many girls
smacked you last weekend
before one would go home with you?
My cheek went numb
after the first dozen,
but then I found a transfer
who didn't know better.
See? Just find a high concentration
of professors to hit on.
Sure, you might get
slapped by 99 of them,
but all you need is that 100th
professor to sleep with you...
- You know, metaphorically.
- Is there a dobler's for teachers?
- Where do smart people hang out?
- Computer stores!
- Ethnic restaurants!
- The moon?
Dr. Larsen's book signing!
There's gonna be tons of professors.
There's gotta be one that'll sponsor me.
And I'll go for moral support.
And the open bar.
- Thanks, but I don't think I need...
- Open bar.
Is grant around?
He's down the hall taking a shower.
I'm just gonna come back.
Actually, can I talk
to you for a second?
Things seem kinda weird
between me and grant.
How...
- terrible.
- And I think it's because of this.
Is grant cheating on me?
No, the "c" is...
It's me.
Of course!
I just assumed from the beautiful
wrapping that it was from a girl!
Should've used a gift bag.
We're all going to Dobler's
for Grant's birthday. You should come.
And bring a date!
Is there someone in your life?
Kinda.
- Do I know them?
- Kinda.
Look at this.
Cap, to what do I owe the pleasure?
You know, spitter's career,
the open bar.
Perhaps a little...
Canoodling.
- I need your help meeting a professor.
- It's a done deal.
I'm so dialed in here.
Gonna find you a match made in heaven.
Not that I believe in that anymore.
What up, Dr. Giddings?
- Maybe you can introduce me to him.
- No, it's a waste of time.
He'll tell you he wants
to work with you, then
when it gets serious, he bails.
He's kind of a project tease.
What about her?
No, Dr. Alpert's saving herself
until she gets tenure.
What about her?
She's a student. She's irrelevant.
- What about Dr. Larsen?
- The man of the hour?
Come on, it's an impossible get.
I've seen him make national science
grant winners cry like little girls.
Anyway, I'm gonna hit the head.
When I get back
we're gonna find you somebody, OK?
- Larsen's the one.
- What? He's an impossible get.
Stick to the plan
and play the numbers.
But if I can land a big fish like him,
people will take me seriously.
I won't be the anchor anymore.
Foregoing the others
to get the "hot girl". It's bold,
it's risky, and I like it.
I'm going in.
There you go.
Excuse me, Dr. Larsen?
I'm Rusty Cartwright.
- I have this idea...
- Hey, the anchor's here!
"To the anchor. To engineer
is human."
"The anchor?" That's an odd moniker.
I come from a long line of seamen.
That came out wrong.
No surprise.
No rager at the Psi Phi Pi house.
Remember, we did this patrolling
thing once at the Omega Chi house?
We really don't need
to chitchat, Case.
Especially about the past.
Let's just get through this.
Apparently we should stick
to elevators.
- What?
- Nothing. Brownie?
- You guys are all good.
- Great.
We can start our
Star Trek movie marathon.
Live long and prospect!
So disrespectful.
Tell Ashleigh what she's missing!
Thanks to our
burnout brother Nitrous,
we have a treat that will delight
all your senses.
I think you'll appreciate
my double entendre when I say,
"These brownies are...
... dope."
Now, beam me up!
Then my team and I realized
that by polarizing diodes,
we could control the movement
of electrons in a low-pressure space.
Is that right?
My team and I are very close
to perfecting a...
two-story beer bong, so...
That's... Fascinating.
Would you excuse me?
I think I see Dale.
It's a weird night.
How'd it go with Larsen?
I blew it.
Maybe we should go.
Or, we can stop
ignoring the obvious.
There's something we both need.
A wingman.
I'm listening.
I don't speak science
and you've got no mojo.
Well, I've got plenty of mojo,
and you've got plenty of...
You know, science talk.
- I could be your translator!
- And I can be your teacher greaser.
By the time I'm done with Larsen,
he's gonna name a star after you.
- And that star'll be called Rusty.
- Right.
- Beaver? What are you doing here?
- Being sciency. Play it cool.
Two chardonnays, please? Extra ice.
- Here you go, sir.
- Thank you.
OK, now let's figure this out.
How about over here?
- Studying on a saturday night?
- I'd rather not hang out in my room.
Still freaked out about your roommate
kissing his sister?
I'd just rather not talk about it.
- There's something to talk about?
- No.
How fortunate I'm here.
- Are you upset because you like Grant?
- How do you know?
No one uses embossed wrapping paper
unless they want to get in guy's pants.
Definitely should've used
a gift bag.
Look, I'm gonna tell you something
as a test of your trustworthiness.
If you pass,
maybe I will help you with Ashleigh.
You can trust me.
So Grant and I...
- ... are dating.
- Grant's gay?
And...
He still has a girlfriend.
I mean, why didn't he tell me?
And why hasn't he
come out to her yet?
Sometimes it takes people
a long time to come out.
Was it that easy for you?
Yeah, summer after sophomore year
of high school,
- I was working at express for men...
- And that's how everybody knew?
Sorry. Continue.
And I told some friends
that I worked with.
People close to me.
Yeah, it took a while,
but you gotta start somewhere.
I don't know, maybe your girlfriend
should be at the top of the list.
Or maybe you should just
let Grant do this his own way.
Can't believe you're telling me to be
more respectful of people's feelings.
Mention this to Ashleigh
when you tell her to forgive me.
What are you doing tonight?
Sundae bar's almost ready.
I was really hoping you'd find
another hasher tonight.
Yeah, I get it, you don't want me here.
But everybody I know split town
because of the dry weekend, so...
- You're stuck with me.
- No.
My point is this is a social event.
With... Guys.
And I'm a girl without a boyfriend.
Yeah, don't worry, Ash.
I'm not gonna stand in your way.
OK, good.
Now, see? This is good clean fun.
I feel kind of sick.
But not... Sick.
Must have been that red asphaltscreening
at the Gamma Psi house.
Hey, let's just finish
checking here,
and...
And then go on our way.
This party clearly sucks,
so I'm gonna get the ball rolling
with some karaoke.
Yay! Karaoke!
Karaoke.
Kar-a-o-ke. That's...
That's a fun word to say.
Is it hot in here?
I love... Music!
I wish I had some maracas.
That's a fun word to say, too.
Maracas.
It's like a furnace.
Did you ever notice
how many cats are in this house?
I hate cats! I hate 'em.
They freak me out!
They're everywhere. On the shelves,
on throw pillows.
Fake cats.
Do you think cats put us
on their pillows?
You guys are here!
These drunk simulation goggles
aren't working.
Is there, like, an on/off switch?
This is awesome.
Let's go see
what the kitchen looks like!
This way.
I guess they do work.
- Hey, Hilary.
- Hey, anchor.
This is my friend.
He helped create the first
synthetic polymers
that use hydrogen bonding
to reversibly fold themselves
into nanoparticles.
David Wong?
Yes, I am.
I was adopted.
By two gay dudes.
- From China.
- I'd love to hear about
how you knew nucleic acids were capable
of performing such ordered folding.
Or... We could talk about you.
But first, let me get you
a glass of wine.
Something to dull the senses
before we dive into my folding stuff.
What are you doing? You were in.
I know. Always leave 'em wanting more.
Besides, you helped me,
now it's my turn. Thank you.
Do you have any bigger glasses?
Dr. Larsen, I couldn't help but notice
you were dry. Another pinot?
Well, thank you.
David wong.
And this is Rusty Cartwright.
The seaman?
Among other things. Rusty's one
of cru's brightest young minds.
Between you and me, you'd be missing out
on a tremendous opportunity
if you didn't hear about his amazing
science thingy.
Dr. Larsen, I was hoping that
you might be interested
in sponsoring a project of mine.
I'm sure you have a wonderful idea,
but I've already committed myself
to sponsoring another student.
- Come over here a minute.
- Yes.
Do you gentlemen know
Dale Kettlewell?
Ready? Go!
Perfect combo!
Sweet,
salt...
Cheese!
Sorry.
You guys are gonna love those.
- So, are you having a good time?
- Cupcakes?
They're good.
There you go, have a cupcake.
Ashleigh? Cupcake?
I said I wouldn't stand in your way.
I didn't say anything about these guys.
Excuse us for a second, please.
OK, since Casey's back, I think we can
handle the rest of the night from here.
You think she can handle this?
Yeah, no offense to the hashers
of the world,
but I think Casey
can put pretzels in a bowl.
That's pretty impressive,
considering she's totally high.
I'm high?
That's what it is!
No! No! I'm supposed
to be keeping people sober.
Katherine gave me a clipboard!
Is this bad?
They were put on sober party patrol,
in charge of the whole greek system,
and they decided to
chuck it all to get high!
Trust me. They sat under that table
for ten minutes pretending to be shoes.
That's ridiculous.
Casey doesn't get high.
Would you tell him you're not...
I'm gonna go look for them.
Dr. Giddings. You're such a caution!
- What?
- I thought Larsen was an
- "impossible get".
- It just happened, OK?
We were talking and found ourselves
bonding over our mutual lack of faith.
One thing led to another.
Between you and me,
I think he's only agnostic.
Yeah, you know, I think
I like the god-fearing Dale better.
- You totally screwed me over.
- Now, spitter, come on.
Now, what's one of the tenets
of a Kappa Tau friendship?
Don't ever let a conquest come
between you and a friend.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy for you.
I just wish I had the opportunity
to pitch my idea to Larsen.
Why can't he sponsor you both?
I don't know, it would kind of
pull focus from my project.
Come on.
You don't need this as badly as I do.
Though I'm not down with JC,
I still have this...
... weird desire
to do the right thing.
All right. I guess it would be OK
if you gave it a shot.
Thanks, man. I won't forget this.
You need a wingman?
This time, I'm flying solo!
- I couldn't find them downstairs.
- They're not up here too.
- Maybe they went outside.
- No, they wouldn't be outside!
The one time Casey got high,
she was terrified of trees.
You know. You can...
Just go. I'll find her.
I'm not gonna leave you
when your friend's missing.
I know, i'm a lot of things,
but I'm not someone who bails
when there's a problem.
I'll go check the pantry again.
Katherine will never find us
in here.
Relax. Try...
Lavender.
That is calming.
And one of my favorites,
pina colada.
- I want to taste it.
- No, don't.
It's my job to keep you
from eating beauty products.
- I just got sad.
- I know.
I wish we had
real pina coladas, too.
Stupid dry weekend.
I used to have so much fun with you.
Before you cheated on me and hit rusty
with a pledge paddle and...
... paid off a lambda sig
and dated Frannie.
I know, right?
You know, I was a little surprised
to see you tonight.
I thought you'd try
to get out of it.
I wouldn't... I did.
Yeah, I guess
I left quite an impression.
I think I've been
such a jerk because...
Whenever I'm around you
it just reminds me
of all the bad crap I did to you.
Do you ever wish we could go back
to freshman year?
You, me and Cappie
hanging in the dorms.
Eating ramen. That was so good!
You two having contests
on who could grow a goatee faster?
Hairy bastard.
I hardly ever see him anymore and...
You...
You two don't even talk at all.
I talked to him.
At the end of the world party.
You... You talked to Cappie?
What about?
You.
He was on his way to see you.
I told him I didn't think
it was such a good idea.
I said...
You guys had been there.
And...
It didn't work out then, so...
What would be different now?
I really wasn't trying
to mess you guys up.
I was just being honest.
You know what?
If he wanted to come, he would have.
That's it! That's it!
I'm trying the pina colada!
No, don't! Don't!
I did it once!
- Was it delicious?
- It was nasty!
So nasty!
But you can smell it. Here.
Excuse me. Hey, Dr. Larsen.
I know you've already chosen Dale,
but I'd never be able
to live with myself if I left this party
without telling you my idea.
Please.
You know, that kind of determination
is what got me on Charlie Rose.
Go on.
It's inspired
by environmental factors
and how we're creating new land masses
with all our waste.
I think we can create eco-polymers
from recycled biodegradables.
You mean like turning carbon dioxide
- into synthetic material?
- Exactly!
There's a method to use
certain recycled materials
in lighter, stronger
and cheaper ways.
I'm impressed.
Really?
But I only work with students
who excel academically.
And since I'd never heard of you
until this evening,
you must not fall
into that category.
But I can offer you a position
assisting Mr. Kettlewell
on his project.
Wait, before you give me an answer,
I think it's only fair that you know.
He's an atheist.
Isn't this perfect?
The four of us on a double date
for my baby's birthday.
Last year for Calvin's birthday
we stayed at this cute little B&B
on Canyon Lake.
Remember how romantic it was, honey?
You guys are such a cute couple.
The cutest!
You know what would be perfect
right now?
Isn't it perfect enough?
- Presents!
- No, no, no!
I mean, this is the kind of present
that should be opened only
when the time is right.
- Why? What'd we get him?
- Well, it's his birthday.
What time could be more right?
Once you open it,
you can't take it back.
And I wouldn't want you
to have to open it here,
now, just because I gave it to you.
Why don't I just open it later?
Don't be silly. Open it!
OK, fine, I'll open it for you.
I'm gay!
And... And I have
inappropriate feelings
for my straight roommate and
this gift is proof of that.
You're what?!
No wonder you never kiss me with tongue!
- How long have you been gay?
- Enough!
Would you two mind
giving Whitney and I some time?
- But, Grant, you don't have to...
- Please.
You've been really great
these last couple days.
It's time to be honest.
Honest about what?
- Let's go.
- We're leaving?
- But it's just starting to get good.
- Come on.
That's the problem in our couple.
We never do anything fun!
That's why I don't date girls.
I'm going to take a little break,
but I'll be back.
Don't even think about it.
Casey and Evan must've left.
I can stay until she gets back.
Or I could drive around and look.
No more.
You don't get to be the good guy while
I sit around being the bitter bitch.
It's not fair.
Fisher, I'm starting
to feel sorry for you.
But then it goes away
and I want to punch you really hard.
- Then punch me, please.
- No, it'll not make me feel any better.
I was right. Doesn't
make me feel any better.
What would? I'm just trying to
make you happy. But
everything I try seems
to make it worse.
Because it does.
It keeps reminding me
of what a great guy
I thought you were.
I can still be that guy.
Tell me what you want.
I don't know what you want me to do.
- You want me to quit?
- I don't know. Maybe?
OK. Then I quit.
- Wait!
- Hello?
Where's casey cartwright?
The zbz casey cartwright?
I'm right here!
We totally got this.
Dude! Be cool! Be cool.
Where have you guys been?
Where haven't we been?
We talked about our lives,
childhood...
... time travel.
I'm talking about tonight.
You only went to five houses.
We had issues with
the karaoke machine!
So, casey cartwright to the rescue.
She's like our sober superhero.
I thought you were gonna
take this more seriously.
The whole point of tonight
was to do the patrols
and make sure everyone stayed sober.
But it's clear that what's most
important to you is having fun.
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
We may have gotten a
little... Side-tracked tonight,
sure, but casey is a great
addition to pan-hellenic.
First of all, she loves it. Right?
Yeah, the binders, the meetings,
the giant copy machine that
makes those cool pamphlets.
How could you not love it?
Right.
We may not have made
it to all the houses,
but this is the only dry weekend
that hasn't totally sucked.
That's all because of casey.
You're lucky to have her.
Thanks, evan.
She may be afraid of trees,
but when push comes to shove,
she doesn't let you
drink the shampoo.
No matter how good it smells.
Thanks, evan.
- Are they stoned?
- Yeah.
Nice work getting hilary's
number. You gonna call her?
I don't know. She was cute,
but for the first time in my life,
I felt a little dumb around a girl.
You're not dumb.
And that's not fair for her
to make you feel that way.
What's she judging you on, anyway?
One conversation?
- One bad grade on a midterm?
- Calm down.
"No one can make you feel
inferior without your permission."
It's actually "without your
consent," but you're right.
The good news is you
got in with Dr. Larsen.
Glad you got what you wanted.
I guess.
Did you see the way katherine
left to go bust the psi phi pis?
She went so fast, she
blurred like a cartoon.
Fisher quit tonight.
Is that... Good?
I don't know.
I thought it was what I wanted.
But if it is,
why do I feel so crappy?
I Miss him.
Do you think you
could trust him again?
I think I want to try.
But I drew a line in the sand.
Cheating is a deal-breaker.
What does that say about me?
It says you're a human being
that understands life
isn't always black and white.
Deciding to forgive someone
can be a sign of strength.
Like you forgiving evan?
Something like that.
So, how'd it go?
I don't see any blood,
so that's gotta be good.
Whitney took it better
than I expected.
She said she knew something
was up when I started
shopping at express for men.
I just hope I didn't force you
- to come out before you were ready.
- No, I'm glad this happened.
I just feel bad
I pulled you into all this.
It wasn't fair.
I'm sorry.
Happy birthday.
I really love it.
You got my check?
We're looking for a new hasher.
If you know of anyone.
Someone who works
hard, shows up on time,
has his own transportation.
Like, a motorcycle.
I know a guy.
Class m license and everything.
Is he trustworthy?
Absolutely. In fact if
you give him a chance,
i'm sure he'll prove it to you.
OK then. He's hired.
Really?
Yeah. But it's only probationary.
'cause you really screwed up, and...
I'm not used to
giving second chances.
I know. And you won't regret it.
I hope not.
I understand you turned down an
opportunity to work with Dr. Larsen.
I'm intrigued.
But it could just mean you're stupid.
I'd rather take a chance
working on my own project,
even if they call me
"anchor" until I graduate.
At least I won't be getting
in line to suck up to larsen.
So what, he was on charlie rose?
I don't want flash,
I want substance.
Stop trying to sweet talk
me, cartwright. I'll do it.
- Do what?
- Sponsor you.
But... I thought you
don't do those things.
Normally, I don't, but
I actually think your ideas
about eco-polymers are not
the worst thing in the world.
I never even told you my ideas.
I'm not deaf. I've heard
you yammer on all year long.
I just pretend not to be listening
so as not to encourage you.
Does this mean we're a team?
I'm already starting
to regret it. Go.