How much will you give me for it?
Fifty bucks.
It's made out of gold.
-Who told you that?
-My mother.
Tell her it's a fake.
I can't.
She's dead.
I'll give you sixty bucks.
So, what's the deal?
-I told you, I don't want to do this anymore.
-Oh, this is our last job.
Liar.
We're all you've got, kid.
Tell me the combination.
25-13-29.
Good boy.
Okay, you know the drill, right?
-Let's do this.
-Get the bag. Let's go.
Don't forget my angel.
What's going on here?
Hey, who are you people?
Oh, my God, no! No!
Oh, my God, I think he's dead.
-Let's go!
-No. What did you do that for?
It was him or us, baby. We gotta go!
Come on.
Where's he going? Go.
Ryan!
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
-Are you all right?
-I lost my shoe.
I'm taking you to the hospital. Come on.
He checks out physically,
just scrapes and bruises.
Have you managed
to contact his parents yet?
Other than knowing his name,
Ryan claims to have no memory.
Are you saying he has amnesia?
True amnesia is extremely rare.
It's most likely post-traumatic shock.
His memory will probably return
within 24 to 48 hours.
What if it doesn't?
Martha, Jonathan.
It's unlikely all Ryan's cuts and bruises
were caused by the accident.
-You think he's been abused?
-He may not want to remember.
What will happen to him?
We've called Child Services,
but they're understaffed...
...and can't come
until tomorrow at the earliest.
So the only place for Ryan to stay
is at the juvenile cell at the sheriff's station.
-That's no place for a child.
-Why can't he come home with us?
-That's a great idea.
-Can we do that?
I'll have to make some calls,
but I don't see why not.
It'd be a big help to us,
and I'm sure Ryan would appreciate it.
-Clark?
-It's me, Mrs. Kent.
-Ryan, did you do all this?
-I hope you don't mind. I couldn't sleep.
-Hey, what's the occasion?
-I wanted to make myself useful.
-Thanks for letting me stay here.
-Stay as long as you want.
Maybe some of you
will rub off on Clark.
What does everybody want?
Let me guess...
...pancakes...
...with powdered sugar...
...not syrup.
-How did you know that?
-I saw you eyeing them when you came in.
Scrambled eggs...
...bacon...
...coffee with milk
and a little bit of honey.
Well, that is some trick there, kiddo.
-Hey, Mom.
-Hi.
Going all out for the new kid, huh?
Actually, Clark,
Ryan took care of all this himself.
You're making me look bad.
What do you want for breakfast?
-Don't you want anything, Clark?
-I'm just gonna have some pancakes.
Ryan, you okay?
Ryan, are you sure you don't remember
anything about last night?
You see, because I still can't figure out...
...why you were out on Route 90
at 10:00 at night.
I said I don't remember.
I'm not hiding anything.
No one said you were, buddy.
Guess your parents want me to leave now.
-Why would you think that?
-Because they don't believe me.
-We just want to help you get home.
-What if I don't have a home?
What if you found out I did bad things?
What would happen?
Ryan, everything's
gonna work out. I know it.
You like comics?
I like this one.
Warrior Angel. Why him?
Because he protects people
who can't protect themselves.
I like being around you, Clark.
It's peaceful.
Why don't you get your head out
of that comic and play a little ball?
-I know what you're thinking. I really suck.
-Nothing a little practice can't cure.
Go ahead. Get your hand up,
keep your elbows straight...
...just guide the ball with your fingers.
-He shoots, and he scores!
-Yeah.
Nice.
Excuse me.
-Yes.
-I'm looking for the boy from the paper.
You know, the one who lost his memory.
-And you are?
-A private detective.
I work for a couple who lost their son.
Is Ryan still around?
No...
...but if you just wait, I'll get Dr. Harden.
I know she'd like to speak with you.
All right.
That's a great sound, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Do you ever think we made the wrong
decision, not adopting another child?
Maybe sharing his secret
with a younger brother would have helped.
He seems to really like Ryan.
I don't think he's the only one.
-You've always had a soft spot for strays.
-Well, the last one turned out all right.
Here you go. One more.
Oh, nice.
I thought you were still in Monaco.
"The backbone of surprise
is fusing speed with secrecy."
Von Clausevitz, On War.
Isn't that a little '80s, Dad, even for you?
I never give my plant managers
a heads-up before a spot inspection.
What could you possibly have
to complain about now?
The plant's doing well,
LuthorCorp stock is up....
I'm not here to complain, Lex.
On the contrary.
Your performance lately has been...
...more than adequate.
That sounds dangerously like a compliment.
I push you, Lex, I don't deny it.
Greatness is a rarefied air
one has to be taught to breathe.
Philip of Macedonia raised his son
among lions to instill fearlessness in him.
Didn't he also try
to impale the kid with a spear?
In an aborted coup attempt...
...but history remembers that boy
as Alexander the Great.
You didn't come all this way
to lecture me on Greek history.
No. I want you to come back to Metropolis...
...where you will hold the position
"special advisor to the chairman emeritus."
That would be me.
-At least the title sounds important.
-It's more than a title. It's an opportunity.
It's what you've been waiting for
ever since you came to Smallville.
I'll think about it.
You want to keep me dangling,
so it looks like you're granting me a favor...
...instead of receiving one?
We don't need to play games, son.
Dad, games are all we've got.
-Wow, you're a modern-day Kaspar Hauser.
-Who's that?
Don't worry. Chloe's the queen
of obscure and irrelevant references.
He's a kid from the 19th century
with amnesia.
He showed up in a German town
without a memory of who he was...
...all he could remember was his name.
-What happened to him?
-Well, his story spread throughout Europe...
...and people from all over came to see
if he was their missing child.
Some people thought
he was the lost son of the grand duke.
-Did he ever find his parents?
-You know....
Yeah, he did.
He found his parents,
and they lived happily ever after.
Why didn't you just say he was murdered?
How did you know that?
You know, why don't we take that picture?
What picture?
You're not putting me
on that freak wall, are you?
It's called the Wall of Weird,
and no...
...this picture is just to check against
missing persons.
Okay, I'm gonna go download this.
I'll be there in a sec.
-She likes you.
-Yeah, we're friends.
She wants to be more than just friends.
-She wants you to ask her to the prom.
-Chloe?
-Yeah, right.
-No, really.
She already picked out a dress. It's pink.
Ryan, you just met Chloe,
and she hates dresses...
...and she's not exactly the prom type.
Maybe she has a romantic side
you never knew about.
Or maybe my mom hit you harder
than I thought.
Let's get a picture of my boys.
So how does it feel having
a little-brother-type figure in your life?
-It's pretty cool.
-I dreamed of having a brother or sister...
...someone to talk to,
help fill the silence.
Someone you can totally trust
and would always be there for you.
That's just how I see you, Clark.
Thanks.
Warrior Angel. I'm a fan myself.
-You must be Ryan. I'm--
-Lex Luthor.
Clark told me all about you.
-You know, I have one of the--
-First-edition panels framed in your house.
-How did you know that?
-You're rich.
That's what rich people do, collect stuff.
I see you've met Ryan.
Apparently, we're both big
Warrior Angel fans.
I didn't know you liked comic books.
A strange visitor from another planet
who protects the weak?
When I was young, he was my idol,
not to mention he's bald.
I have the whole collection.
-Maybe we'll come by later and check it out.
-Yeah.
-Would you like that, buddy?
-Whatever.
Whatever.
That was kind of rude.
-Lex is my friend.
-Don't worry about him. He's going to leave.
Lex's father offered him a new job.
You don't know Lex's father.
He would never do that.
You have to stop making up
stories about people.
I'll see you in a minute.
Ryan?
Ryan just took off out the back.
He looked scared, Clark.
Ryan?
Help!
You're safe now.
Clark, where's your young sidekick?
Sleeping.
He thinks you're his big brother.
Yeah, well, I guess I am, till tomorrow.
-The kid is growing on you.
-You know how it is.
Being an only child, no one else around.
Don't you ever wish you had a sibling?
I had one, Clark.
Really? I didn't know.
When I was 11,
my mother got pregnant again.
It was a total surprise.
I've never seen my father happier.
The day Julian was born
was the only time...
...I felt like I was part of a real family.
And what happened?
The morning of his baptism,
my mother went to his nursery...
...found him in his crib,
he had stopped breathing.
My mother was never the same after that,
and my father got even more distant.
I think he saw Julian as his second chance.
A chance for him to have a son
he could truly love.
I'm sorry.
It's in the past, Clark.
We would have ended up
hating each other, anyway.
My father would have seen to that.
But I didn't come over
to recount my family's tragic history.
My father has offered me a chance
to return to Metropolis.
Did you tell Ryan about that?
I haven't told anyone, Clark.
Well, that's what you always wanted.
I used to think it was.
Now I'm not so sure.
I was a different person there.
A different person around my father.
He wants an answer tomorrow night.
We're having dinner in Metropolis.
If anyone can choose
who they want to be, Lex...
...it's you.
-Knock, knock.
-Mr. Kent, this is a surprise.
Yeah, Ryan's been doing chores with me
all day, so I figured he deserved a break.
I'd like a cup of coffee,
give him whatever he wants...
...and if you can point me to a phone,
I'll see if Martha wants anything.
-All right, it's in the back.
-All right. Enjoy.
-So how you feeling today?
-Much better, thanks.
Good.
Do you think it's okay
if friends have secrets?
Strange question. Why do you ask?
Because I think
Clark is hiding something from me.
Everybody has secrets, Ryan.
Really? What's yours?
If I told you, then it wouldn't be a secret.
I guess you're right.
-Thanks, Skye, you're a lifesaver.
-You're welcome.
-Why the frown?
-She's not a good person, Lana.
You should fire her.
Ryan, why would you
say something like that?
Because it's the truth.
How do you know?
It's a secret.
Thanks for the hot chocolate, Mr. Kent.
Looks like Ryan
has found himself a new family.
-It's time to get back to work.
-When do we get the kid?
When we're ready.
My mom hit him somewhere around here.
Thanks for helping with the clue hunt.
And help solve the riddle of Ryan?
It's my pleasure.
There really is a riddle.
I'm starting to think
he may not have amnesia.
Clark, the kid adores you, why would he lie?
Because he's running from somebody.
I found something.
We got comic books...
...and Twizzlers.
Something every growing boy needs.
What? It's where I would hide something.
If you were a CIA operative.
Who do you think it is?
I don't know.... Mom, aunt?
And the mystery deepens.
I still can't figure out how he knew
that Kaspar Hauser was murdered.
Well, you weren't exactly
wearing a poker face.
Ryan does say weird things.
He even said that you wanted me to ask you
to prom and that you'd bought a dress.
It's not pink, is it?
Okay, you know, I was just looking at it,
it's not like I actually bought it.
How would Ryan know that?
I don't know. Maybe he's an alien, or maybe
he called Miss Cleo. You know, I don't know.
Clark's the best thing
that ever happened to you.
Yeah, he is.
He makes up for not being able
to have your own kids.
He does.
-Has he always been so strong?
-What do you mean?
The way he tore off the back panel
of the garbage truck and saved me.
Don't be silly, he couldn't do that.
If you say so.
What's your greatest fear?
That I won't get this pie done
by the time you have to leave.
Why don't you go outside
and shoot some hoops?
-What are you doing down here?
-Clark, don't be mad.
How'd you know about this?
I heard about it in your mom's mind.
I wanted to see it for myself.
Can you hear everything people think?
Only what's on the surface.
What they're thinking at that moment.
Except for you.
I can't read your mind.
That's how I knew you were different.
Now I know why.
I can't believe you'd do this.
I'll never tell.
You keep my secret, I'll keep yours.
-It's not that simple.
-Sure it is.
I know your dad's worried
that people are going to find out.
I can tell him
when someone's getting close.
I told you about Chloe.
I can tell you about Lana.
-You want to know her secret?
-No.
No, Ryan, I don't.
Why not?
It's about you.
Look, you can't do this.
You don't understand
what it's like to be different.
What it's like to have to hide
so people won't think you're a freak.
Everywhere I go...
...I hear people's thoughts.
I can't block it out anymore.
Is this your mother?
She died.
Why didn't you tell me?
I was hoping I could start over
with your family.
They were so nice.
I wanted them to adopt me like they did you.
So I'd be safe.
-Who's chasing you?
-My stepfather and his new wife.
They've been using me.
My abilities.
To steal.
I wanted to stop...
...but they threatened me.
They hit me.
You have to protect me, Clark.
You're the only one that can.
I'll get it.
You say anything, and I'll kill them.
You know I will.
-So you must be Ryan.
-Can I help you?
Mr. Kent, Child Services.
I'm here to pick up Ryan.
You're early. We weren't
expecting you for an hour.
We can't thank you enough
for taking Ryan in.
It's our pleasure.
He's welcome to stay longer.
Oh, I'm afraid that's impossible.
I need to put him in foster care.
That's the law.
Let's get your stuff.
We think Ryan might be running away
from his stepfather, so we alerted the police.
Don't worry, we'll keep him safe.
Ready to go?
Could he wait and say goodbye
to our son, Clark? He'll be home any minute.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's okay, Mrs. Kent.
Just tell him thanks.
If you need anything, just call us, okay?
Dad, what's wrong?
Child Services came and took Ryan away
about 15 minutes ago.
What?
Why didn't he wait for me?
I wanted to say goodbye.
I don't know, son...
...they said they were in a hurry.
I'm sorry.
On your way to Metropolis.
Yeah, for the big dinner.
I....
I wanted you to have something.
-A sword?
-It's a foil. Every hero should have one.
I guess this means
you've decided you're leaving.
I haven't made up my mind
one way or the other.
If you haven't made up your mind,
why are you giving me a going-away present?
Keep that away from the kid.
-He's already gone.
-I'm sorry.
I know how much you liked him.
For what it's worth, I hope you stay.
Driver? Hey, what's going on?
Driver?
-Inside, come on!
-What are you doing?
Get in.
Mr. Luthor.
-Ryan?
-Shut up.
Okay, go. Go.
Getting the account number
to your trust fund was easy...
...now give me the password.
-I don't know what you're talking about.
-Tell me what it is.
My father has it, I don't.
He's lying.
Password. Now.
You got it?
-Hey, Zorro, what's with the sword?
-It's a foil.
I'm guessing it's a gift
from our favorite millionaire playboy.
He's thinking of moving back to Metropolis.
Well, I'm still here, Clark.
I'm not going anywhere.
Sources at the sheriff's office have given me
a heads-up on Ryan's stepdad.
-You have sources.
-Yeah, a cute officer in Traffic.
I talked my way out of a speeding ticket,
he told me I was plucky.
Maybe I'll ask him to prom.
So Ryan's stepdad is a real catch.
He's a career criminal.
This is Lex's limo driver.
Give me the password.
Don't make me ask again.
It's "Julian."
-Lex, are you okay?
-Yeah, I think so.
Which way did they go?
Straight down Route 90.
Clark, they've got Ryan. Get some help.
Get out. Torch the limo, baby!
Julian. Julian.
Give me the real password.
Don't mess with me.
-I'm not gonna tell you!
-I swear to God, I'll drop him right now.
Once he gets the money,
he's gonna kill you.
Don't listen to him.
He's talking trash to pull us apart.
We're just about to hit the jackpot, baby.
All we've gotta do is trust each other.
You know, this kid has always
freaked me out...
...but the one thing I'll say about him
is he never lied.
You know what?!
That's true...
...he didn't.
Ryan!
-Hey, kid, where are you going?
-Call the police!
Ryan!
You can't hide forever.
You know, your mother really hated you.
Couldn't stand having a freak for a son.
Come to think of it,
I wasn't that crazy about you either.
-Clark!
-It's okay, buddy.
You're safe now.
-Hi, Lana.
-Hey.
-Ryan would like to say goodbye.
-Where are you going?
Edge City.
Chloe's research turned up an aunt there.
She's coming by this afternoon.
I wanted to thank you
for your advice on Skye.
You were right.
She was stealing from the till.
-Hey.
-Wow.
Thank you.
I think you made his year.
So you recover yet?
I don't know, but I'm definitely in love.
Join the club.
Shouldn't you be packing?
I'm not going back to Metropolis.
Come on, Lex, that's all you wanted
ever since I assigned you...
...to what you so eloquently refer to
as the "crap factory."
I know why you want me back.
I'm driving you crazy, aren't I?
I'm not clubbing till 6:00 a.m.,
not getting arrested. I'm on track.
That's what scares you.
You want me back where you can
keep an eye on me.
You're making a mistake, Lex.
You know what those emperors you're so
fond of talking about were really afraid of?
That their sons would become successful...
...and return to Rome
at the head of their own army.
You think you can find
your future in Smallville.
I'm your future.
Join me, Lex. Join me in Metropolis.
How long have you been waiting
to hear me say those words?
I've waited to hear other things
from you for a lot longer.
-I'll return to Metropolis when I'm ready.
-At the head of an army?
We're really going to miss you, Ryan.
It gets cold in Edge City,
so I packed some of Clark's old jackets...
-...something for you to grow into.
-Thanks, Mrs. Kent.
You're welcome around here
any time you want.
I know what you're worried about,
but don't be.
I'll keep Clark's secret.
I know what it's like to have to hide
who you are from the world.
There she is.
You sure you're gonna be all right?
She's a nice person.
She's just as nervous as I am.
Are you sure you don't want to know
how Lana feels about you?
I prefer to find out on my own.
Clark....
Be careful of Lex.
I know you like him...
...but there's a lot of darkness
he keeps from the world.
I've seen it in his head.
I like to believe in people's best.
I want you to have something.
-I can't take those.
-I don't need them anymore.
I have you.
See you.
Bye.
Okay.
[ENGLISH]
www.tvsubtitles.net