- Tell me.
- It's a girl.
You disappear to Los Angeles.
You don't return my calls,
I'm worried about you.
We all are.
I know when a man is willing
to sacrifice anything for his cause,
and you're not that kind of man,
Agent Benford.
I need a favor... a big favor.
It's for Tracy.
Hi, Dad.
What I saw, what you saw,
doesn't have to play out that way.
- What are you talking about?
- I found a way to change the game.
Dear Celia,
I don't know your last name,
and I don't know where you live,
but I know you have two young boys.
Twins, I believe.
And I know you didn't have
a flash-forward.
They all saw FBI agent Al Gough,
alive and well on April 29th.
What this guywas trying to show us
is we can't take
what we saw for granted.
Bottom line, this is a new world.
This is a new day, and I just think
we need to take a moment
and let that sink in.
What we need to have answered right now,
is the question,
is there going to be
another world blackout?
People are terrified.
Let's get back to the big question.
What question?
Do we have free will?
That's the big question,
the central question of human existence
for millennia.
If this is supposed to be
your resignation, forget it.
You're not gonna let me
explain myself?
You were attacked.
You were shot.
You returned to duty to find out
a coworker jumped off a building.
Am I in the right ballpark?
My life's not making
a whole lot of sense right now,
and I think I need a little time off
to figure it out.
Understandable.
I need you here.
I know we've been shorthanded
since the blackout.
But since Gough...
Since Al...
- This isn't about Al.
- Yes, it is.
When I found out about what he did
and why he did it,
it made me think
about my own future.
What I'm supposed to do.
Do I lean into what I saw?
Do I fight it?
What if my getting shot was...
I don't know. Some...
Some sort of a sign
that this baby's not meant to be?
You're gonna let a bullet decide whether
you bring a baby into this world?
If Al's death proved anything,
it's that our choices still matter,
now more than ever.
I believe without reservation
or recrimination that your card
is the ace of spades.
That certainly
answers that question.
I've been wondering
how a Nobel finalist
and recipient of the MacArthur prize,
spends his idle moments.
This isn't the time or the place.
You dropped off the radar.
Without so much as a phone call.
I had to check myself into the hospital
to have my bruised ego X-rayed.
Hello, Dylan.
Remember me?
Why, this is not my pancake!
We're not having this discussion
in front of my son.
I'm done having you dictate
when and where we talk.
Myhill forwarded me
the e-mail you sent him.
- Or the suicide note?
- It's the only logical move.
If you're bent on self-destruction,
I suppose it is.
I have doubts as to the cause
of the blackout.
Our experiment killed
20 million people.
20 million.
The world has been upended.
People need answers.
We have to go public and tell the world
we caused the blackout.
All right.
We have to leave this room sometime.
I have a reservation with
the hotel that says different.
Plus, you haven't opened
your gift yet.
What's this?
Just a little
something to celebrate.
What are we celebrating?
Second chances, I guess.
And the fact that
we can change the things we saw.
I never thought we couldn't.
That's the office.
I told 'em not to call
unless it was an emergency.
I promise.
- Yeah.
- Hey, it's me.
This better be good, Dem.
I'm sorry.
Something came up.
- Did you bring your laptop?
- Yeah.
I'm sending you some video
we got from Barstow P.D..
Remember you had Marcie plug the clues
off the Mosaic board into NCIC?
-  Got something?
- Barstow P.D. caught a homicide.
Eyewitness recorded it
on her cell phone.
When it hit the system,
NCIC kicked back a red flag.
Why?
Stay tuned.
I'm headed back right now.
"Playing Cards With Coyote"
What do we have?
Anything that might help us
id our tattooed friend?
Not really. The victim, Neil Parofsky,
is an aeronautics engineer
who works out of a plant
in El Segundo.
Watch and wallet were missing,
so everybody's thinking robbery.
Is that confirmed by whoever
shot the cell phone video?
Ingrid Alvarez.
She saw Parofsky hand something
over before he got shot,
- so she thought it was a mugging, too.
- Great.
First day back?
- I should have gotten you flowers.
- They're for your wife...
For stitching me back together.
And these are for you...
Hard copy stills
taken from that cell phone.
Video forensics enhanced
the images as best they could.
So now we just gotta figure out
why someone would want to hit
an engineer from El Segundo.
Have Vreede get into Parofsky's life...
Friends, family,
bank accounts, whatever.
What are we gonna do?
What was the name
of that eyewitness?
Ingrid Alvarez.
We'll be talking to her.
If the guy in her video is one
of the men I saw in my vision,
this is our best lead so far...
Our only lead.
I'm putting him away now.
Find out who sent him
and make sure he never
shows up here on April 29th.
Al sacrificed himself to prove
we could change the future...
So let's change it.
Hey, honey.
Everything okay?
You're back early.
Mark had a work thing.
So...
What's going on here?
The usual.
You haven't been gone that long.
It's all right.
I'm sorry.
It's pathetic waking up
every damn morning like this.
Maybe if you'd just talk about it...
I told you.
I don't want to talk about it.
Well, I'm not giving you
a choice anymore.
I've been grieving for you
for two years, Trace.
Hell, I even had your grave
exhumed two months ago
because I was convinced
that you were alive.
If you want to keep hiding out here...
If you want me to pretend to the world,
your mom included,
that you're still dead,
you have to tell me what happened.
After what I saw
in my flash-forward,
I'd believe anything at this point.
Listen to me, Trace.
Four months from now,
I'm gonna be sitting
by your side in Afghanistan.
You saw it, and I saw it.
Isn't that why you came home?
Obviously at some point,
I'm gonna get involved,
whatever it is.
So let's just cut to the chase
and get started.
How about the Simcoe boy?
He was supposed to be
discharged while I was gone.
Not yet.
He was complaining of calf pain,
so we removed the cast, did a doppler,
and the kid's got a DVT.
You're kidding me.
I'm going to be a grandmother
before this boy goes home.
I don't get it. Why are you
so anxious to get rid of him?
Is it his dad, Mr. Simcoe?
What makes you say that?
Just that you guys have
a weird relationship.
I mean, every time he comes around,
you get crazy tense, and...
Dr. Benford?
Actually, Dr. Varley just
told me about Dylan's status.
But what are the ramifications...
Would it be safe to leave
the boy's bedside?
I see here that you have him
on heparin.
Now the risk of complications
at that dose is relatively minimal.
- Is that correct?
- You are?
- Good question.
- A friend of the family.
Frankly, I was hoping to pry Lloyd away
from the hospital for a while...
Steak dinner, some fraternal martinis.
You could see fit to sanction that?
I mean, the boy is essentially
ready to be discharged,
if I've read his chart correctly.
May I?
Barring any complications,
I see no reason why Dylan couldn't
go home in the next couple of days.
Well, it's settled then. Lloyd,
you've been absolved of any guilt,
parental or otherwise.
Lovely.
Thank you for your help.
Of course. Dr. Varley.
Nice legs.
Are you sleeping with that woman?
That is none of your concern.
Everything you do is my concern now,
since you pressed "send"
on that idiotic e-mail of yours...
Which brings me to
the purpose of my visit.
I'm going public with or without
Myhill's cooperation or yours.
- Good luck anyone to believe you.
- Good luck stopping me.
It appears we're at an impasse.
There are two ways to settle this.
The first is so tawdry and public.
I make a general annoyance
out of myself,
kick over as many anthills
as possible...
Enough, Simon.
Or we settle this
in a more civilized manner.
Define "civilized."
Do you remember whose name go first
on the application
for the Sloan fellowship?
Texas hold'em, no holds barred.
You win, we go public,
hang ourselves out to dry.
I win, you keep your mouth shut
and your guilt in check,
and we buy ourselves some more time.
You want to wager
the fate of millions of people
on the outcome of a poker game?
The gods did it all the time...
Dice, chess,
whatever took their fancy.
They loved tinkering with the lives
of those mere mortals.
We're not gods, Simon.
20 million deaths on our shoulders.
Isn't that what you said?
If that doesn't qualify us
for Godhood,
tell me,
what does.
Let the games begin.
What's Barstow PD doing here?
Let's hope 3-star guy
didn't get to our witness.
Do you think
she drives a gold sedan?
Maybe not anymore.
Special Agent Benford, FBI.
Detective Rick Malchiodi,
Barstow P.D.
We think your victim might be
an eyewitness in a homicide.
- That's a hell of a coincidence.
- How's that?
Her roommate said
she witnessed a homicide, too.
Her roommate?
Alvarez...
Ingrid Alvarez.
Came home from work,
found her roommate there
double-tapped to the side of her head.
So looks like they got
the wrong roommate.
I believe it's to you.
How much do you want
to give me this round?
$2,500.
I hope you don't drag this game
out as long as the last one.
When you lose, you'll be able
to console yourself
that I've prevented you from confessing
to a mass murder.
Manchester figure of speech.
$2,500.
I'll call.
I don't understand.
You're saying they killed Blanca,
but they were trying to kill me?
That's what it looks like
to us, yes.
And it's because
of what happened in the alley?
Now, Ingrid, what exactly
did happen in the alley?
We have the video,
but it would really help us
to get your account.
I was working late,
me and one of my clerks.
- Can't say I see you as a blonde.
- And I can't see you as a rock star,
but that's what you say
your vision was.
I was locking up for the night.
You want me to walk you to your car?
I mean, it's kind of late.
I'll be fine.
I went to my car,
but there were men in the alley...
Three of them.
They were fighting, arguing,
but I couldn't hear what about.
But when it got physical, I hid.
I called 9-1-1,
but they put me on hold.
I still can't believe I stayed calm
enough to think to use my phone.
My hand was shaking so much.
Now you told the police
the victim gave the other men something
right before they shot him?
They were arguing
about a case or something.
But I didn't see what it was.
What about the faces of the other men?
Do you think you could describe them?
I didn't get a very good look,
but I think one of them
maybe had gray hair.
The other one was bald,
and he was big, muscular.
It was very dark.
We're gonna sit you down
with a sketch artist.
Whatever you can give us.
And if you can remember
anything else,
it could be a big help.
As they were walking away,
they were talking about something.
It sounded like "QED."
Thank you.
You guys ever read about
that inevitability index thing
that's been in all the papers?
$5,000.
It's a scam...
Some entrepreneurial huckster's
attempt to sell us on the idea
that the odds of the future
happening can be "calculated."
It's all rubbish.
Fate is fate.
- We're not responsible, Lloyd.
- What about free will?
No such thing.
Since when did you become
such a hard determinist?
Simple quantum suicide theory.
I will win this hand
and every subsequent hand
we play ad infinitum. QED.
Don't you get tired of hearing
yourself pontificate?
Don't you get tired of being
a self-righteous prig?
We're scientists, Lloyd.
Not attention-seeking
reality show contestants
looking for their 15 minutes
of fame on a talk show.
- You always do this.
- What's that?
Use intellectual argument
to defend your behavior.
What?
So you sleep with Cabrini's wife,
and you call it electromagnetism.
You fire your assistant
and blame it on Darwin.
- Shut up.
- Now you've upended the world,
and you hide behind
determinist rhetoric.
You're not the only one
who's lost someone.
Who, Simon?
Who have you ever cared about?
I'll call.
You see,
I knew you were bluffing
this entire time. You know why?
Because there's
no such thing as luck
or fate
or "there but for the grace of God."
This game is pointless.
I've already won.
The future's already happened.
Fighting it is futile.
Hey, Nicole.
Nicole?
You okay?
Sorry.
My mind wandered.
I'm guessing Mark
told you what I saw.
He did, yeah.
But only 'cause
he's worried about you.
We both are.
You don't have to be.
I'm gonna be fine.
The future can change.
It's all over the news.
Crazy-huge floral delivery for the
quintuplets. Can you give me a hand?
Don't worry, Olivia.
We can change what we saw,
just like we could
before the blackout.
Everything's back
to being up to us again.
Dad.
My humvee got attacked.
Your friend Mike told me that.
But that was two years ago, Tracy.
- Why didn't you go back to your base?
- I couldn't.
The attack...
We were fired on
by supposed friendlies.
Marines?
Jericho PMC...
Private Military Contractors.
I've heard about them,
but that doesn't explain why.
Jericho works for the military, which
means that I can't trust the military...
Hold on a second.
Why would you say
you can't trust the military?
About two weeks before
my humvee was attacked,
I was working long-range recon on this
village in the foothills near Kunar.
I was alone.
Orders were to stay covert
so the locals wouldn't see me.
But there must have been
someone else out there.
Jericho.
And I watched them...
I watched...
as they wiped out a village.
They killed women,
and they butchered children.
They slaughtered them.
- Why? Why would they want to do that?
- I don't know,
but I told my superior officer,
and about a week later,
Mike and I pulled duty at a forward
roadblock near the Kalikata Mountains.
Out of nowhere, a Haji truck
breached our roadblock.
We took off after them.
Damn!
Embrace the suck, Stark.
Who the hell are these guys?
Those aren't Hajis!
Burro, burro!
We're gonna get whacked!
- Get out!
- Go!
I don't know how I survived.
I thought I was the only one.
What's been going on?
You sounded freaked when you called.
- Did you slip or something?
- No, I just...
I didn't believe it myself.
I took this picture at my house.
My God.
It's Tracy.
- How?
Tracy would kill me if she knew
I was talking to you, but...
she was in a humvee
with three other soldiers.
It got blown to hell, a bloody mess.
Body parts everywhere,
including her leg.
The D.N.A...
- It got basically thrown into the mix.
- Then where has she?
What has she been doing
for the past two years?
It's what I need to talk to you about.
Basically, she's been on the run.
She saw something she shouldn't have
and got in trouble with Jericho.
- They're this...
- Yeah, military contractors.
They were ones who attacked her.
I know this sounds like something out
of a Baldacci novel or something but...
Tracy was dead...
and now she's alive.
So, I really need your help, Mark,
'cause Tracy is scared
to death of these Jericho guys,
and I'm afraid they're
gonna try to find her.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I saw something today,
and it got me thinking
that if this person's future
could come true,
and it did,
even though it seemed impossible,
then maybe these visions are
more set in stone than we thought.
Or maybe we have to work
that much harder.
You're right.
Did you open my gift?
- They're lovely.
- You didn't put 'em on?
I figured you'd just
take 'em right off again.
Right.
We can change things, Mark.
We just have to decide
how badly we want to.
How far we're willing
to go to make it happen.
But I say there's nothing,
nothing that we shouldn't be willing
to do for one another.
So what are you suggesting?
Set a trap, for our suspects,
draw 'em out.
I knowa lot's changed lately, but...
we still don't use
civilians as bait.
- Ingrid knows the risks.
- Then work the case.
- Work the Parofsky angle.
- We've been doing that.
Parofsky was chief engineer
at Micro-Circadian Electronics.
He was recently let go on suspicion
of corporate espionage.
What if Parofsky is selling
his work to the highest bidder?
Ingrid did say that they took a package
from him right before they shot him.
So it was valuable enough
to kill for.
Look, Stan, it's a real lead.
Ingrid's gonna be protected on this.
I promise.
What makes you so sure
they'd try to hit her tonight?
They already tried
to kill Ingrid once.
If we get the word out that we're gonna
release her from custody,
- they might try again.
- Why do you say that?
We went to Utah.
D. Gibbons knew we were coming.
You unearthed the Somalia photos.
Five minutes later,
we're getting shot at.
Whoever we're investigating knows
what we're doing before we do it.
You think we've got a mole.
We have a mole.
Two men with assault rifles
are gonna get into this building
five months from now,
and someone's gonna let 'em in.
We catch these guys tonight.
We can finally put a face
on our enemy.
Careful, it's hot.
Guess there's no chance of
getting any bourbon in there.
Probably not a good one, no.
When did you start whiskey?
- I told Mark Benford.
- You what?
- He can help.
- Are you insane?
- You don't know these people, Dad.
- I gotta get out of here.
- Hold on a second.
- I came to this house because I thought
that I'd be safe, but I see now
that was a big mistake.
Mark's a Fed, Trace.
I mean, he's practically family.
The second that Jericho knows
that I'm still alive,
- they'll find me and kill me.
- That's not true.
Don't you remember
your flash-forward?
The fact that you even had one
proves that you're gonna be alive.
I was with you.
I gave you my pocket knife.
You were on a cot, fell asleep.
We were in some kind of bunker
or cave surrounded by guards,
and there was graffiti
all over the walls.
I think somebody
was calling my name.
Then I stepped outside,
there was a man out there.
He was very concerned about you
and something strange.
The account has been verified.
Then I gave him an envelope.
I don't know what was in it.
"The accounts have been verified."
Does that mean something to you?
But this guy, what did he look like?
- Tall, dark. Scar.
- Khamir.
Khamir Dejan.
He was a field medic with the I.M.C.
He took care of me.
He got me back together.
That's why I left.
I was so afraid that Jericho
would kill Khamir to get to me.
That's not gonna happen. Five months
from now, he's alive. I saw him.
- All three of us were there, Trace.
- How can you be so sure
that everything we saw
will still come true?
Enough of mine
has come true already that...
I'm a believer.
You came back to me, Trace.
Didn't you?
I don't know what could drag us
both back to Afghanistan,
but I have to trust what I saw.
The area is secure.
We're good.
Roger that.
All units stay on tact-2.
These guys are pros. Former military,
based on that video we saw.
You have a lot of amazing birds.
My babies.
The only real family I've ever had.
Each one of them, is special to me.
Hard to believe
I thought of giving them up.
- What do you mean?
- My flash-forward.
In my vision, I wasn't working
at the store anymore.
I had blond hair,
and I was living in New York.
So the next day,
I put it up for sale.
Since we're standing here, I'm guessing
you didn't have a lot of buyers.
It was all for the best.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Planning on changing my life
for a future
that might not even come true.
We keeping you awake, cupcake?
I'm sorry, man.
I was up late with Zoey last night.
I told her what happens to me.
What's gonna happen to me.
Supposed to happen to me.
She wants me to quit,
get out of the line of fire.
Are you...
thinking about it?
I wasn't.
I mean...
Who knows? I quit, I get hit by a bus.
That's my luck.
Whatever.
What am I supposed to do,
become a barista until my death?
That's one way to go.
When this is over,
whether it's tonight or later,
I'd like for you
to have one of my cockatiels.
A thank you gift.
Don't make me insist.
If you truly loved your birds,
you're not gonna want to give one to me,
but thank you.
Very sweet.
- What was that?
- Stay here.
Sabre-2, this is Sabre-1.
- Sabre-2, go.
- Think I may have some movement here.
You want us
to move in on your position?
Could be nothing.
Let me check it out first.
Sabre-2, we have a breach.
All units surround the perimeter!
Nobody gets out!
I got Ingrid covered in the back.
Freeze!
You saw him turning on me.
He was makin' a move.
It was dark.
I didn't get a good look.
But I do know we can't
interrogate a dead man.
What does this all mean?
I'm sorry,
but one of the men you saw
is still out there,
and he's not gonna stop
until he finds you.
We need to put you
in witness protection.
That's okay.
I think that's my future.
I should have trusted
my gut all along.
Judging from your dwindling
amount of chips,
the pain is almost over.
What are you thinking
over there, mate?
Maybe you got a pair of 8s,
working a full boat.
How much do you have left?
Just under 15.
$5,000.
Why don't we make this hand,
winner take all?
If you win, we go public.
But of course I'll win,
and you'll keep your mouth shut.
Fine.
As a physicist, Lloyd,
you really are a genius.
But you were never very good
at concealing your tells.
Four of a kind for Mr. Camp.
Straight flush.
Pot and game to Mr. Simcoe.
Congratulations.
Keep the chips.
Call it a tip.
I got what I came for.
How did you beat me?
Did I tell you Dylan
really loves magic?
Sleight of hand's his favorite.
There are some things
even I won't leave to chance.
That being said.
I'll let you have the first pass
at drafting the announcement.
Thanks for backing my play there.
I just want to make sure
I know which play it was.
Is this about taking
tattoo man off the streets
- or putting him under it?
- What are you talking about?
Look, I know you said
if we get this guy,
we might be able
to change our futures.
But?
I just want to make sure
the plan here wasn't to kill him
so he can't kill me
or come after you in your office.
Whatever gave you that idea?
Because I had it.
The second you suggested
tattoo man might be the guy
who's supposed to kill me,
I thought,
I'm gonna kill him first.
But now you think I actually did...
That I went that far.
I would've.
- What are you doing here so late?
- Trusting my gut.
Your e-mail said
you had something for me.
Yeah, I do.
N.S.A. finally sent back
a new rendering
of that suspect zero photo.
- Looks like the old one.
- It is.
This... is the new one.
What's that on his hand?
It looks like a ring.
Can the image
be enhanced any further?
N.S.A. is working on it right now,
but it took them this long
to get this far.
Tell them to put
their foot on the gas.
If we can tie this jewelry
to the guy wearing it,
we'll have our first workable lead.
Good job.
You look like you had
a perfectly ordinary day.
Worse than ordinary?
I killed a man tonight.
What happened?
I had a shot
at changing my future.
Our future.
And I took it.
Mark, come here.
Come here.
Maybe April 29th's, just gonna be
another day at the office now.
What does that mean?
I told you in my flash-forward
I was in danger, right?
A man was trying to kill me.
But tonight...
I got to him first.
I changed the future, Livy.
We have a second chance.
You have them?
There were supposed to be seven.
After the first atom bomb test,
you know what a colleague
of Oppenheimer's said?
"What a foul and awesome display."
He then added,
"Now we are all sons of bitches."
-= Blackout Team =-