We believe that this man was somehow
connected to the blackout.
He's highly efficient
in advanced computing equipment.
He also seems to have
a penchant for chess.
The man you call D. Gibbons,
his real name is Dyson Frost.
Hello, Demetri.
My name is Dyson Frost.
Got your attention, didn't I?
In my flash-forward,
I saw this symbol.
I remember the images,
but I just can't put them together.
Your have to find her.
Our entire investigation hinges
on what's in your head.
I'm here to make sure
you don't lose it before april 29th.
- We went to Utah.
- Officer down!
D. Gibbons knew we were coming.
You unearthed the Somalia photos.
5 minutes later, we're getting shot at.
Whoever we're investigating
knows what we're doing
before we do it.
We have 'em all.
You're forgetting what we saw...
The part where we're not together.
Hey, honey!
I want to go away with you
and with Charlie.
I just want to get away
from all of this. Yes or no?
I'm sorry. I was in surgery.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Oh, god. What happened?
- I ran into a bullet.
Babe, I'm serious. 6 inches this way,
this bullet's in your heart.
I know.
I'm not sure
I can handle this anymore.
Livy, I was an F.B.I. agent
when you married me.
But it is different now.
We have a daughter.
I mean, if something happens to you,
I don't wanna...
Look, I get that this is
who you are.
But it's different.
I mean, I've got to know
that our family comes first.
Something's gotta change.
Wedeck offered me
a position on the DHS
counterterrorism task force.
It's an improvement?
It's surveillance.
Two guys in a car eating burritos,
listening to phone calls in farsi.
I'll be out of the line of fire.
My biggest concerns will be
boredom and cholesterol.
You're gonna hate that.
But I can take it.
What I can't take
is losing you and Charlie.
Our family will always come first.
I promise.
So, if you need anything,
I'll be staying at the Wedecks'.
I'm sorry. I have no idea
how to do this.
Neither do I.
She's been in there 20 minutes.
I'll call you tonight.
Are you my new partner?
If you are, I insist
you change your clothes.
Can't catch bad guys in pajamas.
Where are you going?
I'm just going to the Wedecks'
for a little while.
How long is a little while?
I hope it's not very long at all.
What's this?
You lost your bracelet.
It'll keep you safe from the bad guys
until you come back home.
Let me put it back on.
Come here.
I love you so much, Charlie-bear.
-= Blackout Team =-
Season 1 Episode 15
-= Queen Sacrifice =-
If you're watching
this message in 2010,
that means the global blackout
was successful.
That also means
we've had a near miss
in Pigeon, Utah.
How do I know all this?
Because I myself have had
hundreds of flash-forwards.
In nearly all of my futures,
I end up dying on march 15th...
Like you, Demetri.
So if you managed to find
this tape in Somalia,
it would seem our fates
are on a collision course,
and the possible outcomes
of the game
are rapidly narrowing.
As for the endgame,
the next move is Mark Benford's.
That's Dyson Frost?
And it's genuine?
It's legit.
Degradation rate in the tape plus the
date of production makes it authentic.
The only explanation,
however implausible,
is that Frost flashed-forward
from 1991 to our present
and saw us in Somalia.
Then in 1991,
he makes a tape he knows we'd find.
That's a 19-year flash-forward.
And march 15th,
the day he dies in his future,
is the date I'm supposed
to be murdered.
Maybe that's the collision course
he's talking about.
Dem, Frost talks
about narrowing outcomes,
another indication that what people see
in their flash-forwards...
are only possibilities.
- Could be warning us.
- Warning us about what?
There's gonna be another blackout.
What?
How? When?
We have to assume
that's Agent Benford's next move...
to find out and to prevent it.
So let's make it a good one.
Find Dyson Frost...
yesterday.
This is magnificent work.
Master circuits built from basic
sketches I designed when I was 13.
When you finish patting yourself
on the back, can we get to work?
I had to go to a lot of trouble to get
all this, not to mention that basement.
Yes, I know, the missing digit.
A terrible loss.
You find anything in those documents
we got in Somalia?
A couple of things.
There were several references
to tachyonic dark matter.
In '91? How is that possible?
The theoretical basis existed.
- But the experiment failed.
- Because they needed us.
Clearly, you're missing
the silver ling.
The blackout.
We're off the hook.
Not our fault.
Frost flash-forwarded in '91
using technology
that we did not develop.
Flosso said our NLAP experiments
amplified the blackout.
We can't dodge that.
- Find anything else interesting?
- I saw this formula
in my flash-forward.
Written on a mirror.
It's the exact inverse of some
of our early NLAP computations.
I don't know, maybe a process
to reverse the blackout?
You're working on blackout protection
in your flash-forward?
I don't know,
but it was this formula,
and there was...
There was more of it
written on the mirror,
and the two of them
are combined somehow.
We need the other formula
that you saw on the Benfords' mirror.
Go see your girlfriend.
Ticktock.
Nothing. I ran face recognition software
on every available database.
Since frost faked his death in 1990,
there is not one record,
- not one sighting of this guy. Nothing.
- He's a thorough guy...
Likes complex things like chess.
He's also got an arrogant streak.
Likes people to know when he's winning.
I've been looking through membership
lists of chess clubs pre-'90.
Frost placed third
in an amateur league in '87.
And the guy he beat
lives in San Francisco.
His name is Ian McKinnon.
McKinnon was the reigning champion
until frost beat him in an upset.
So I traced him
and then I gave him a call.
But when I mentioned Frost,
- he hung up.
- Let's travel.
We need to get to San Francisco
and talk to him, right?
Yeah. But first,
there's something else.
This is Frost's final tournament
against McKinnon.
He uses a very risky play
called the queen sacrifice.
Looks like a total hail mary,
but it's one of the most effective
plays in the game.
So what?
He knew we would see these games.
It's another message from 1991.
Tournament game sheets.
Each of his moves takes either two
or four seconds.
Never more, never less.
In the three games,
he made 50 moves, after which
he resigned.
So this is a code of some kind.
Wait. Is this...
This is morse code.
2-second moves are dots.
4-second moves are dashes.
There are 50 moves,
so 50 characters.
- This is jumbles of letters here.
- Not letters.
Numbers in morse code
have five dots or dashes.
50 divided by 5 is 10 digits.
Is it a phone number?
Prepaid cell.
He really did know the future.
Well done.
Leave a message.
Dyson Frost?
This is Agent Benford.
It's your move.
Now we're traveling.
In english, please.
I know you like halibut.
Some just came in this morning.
No, thank you.
I ate some cereal.
That's not enough.
You need protein.
You are kind, but I can't.
It's too much money.
I want a new beginning.
And new love.
Some miso soup, a little rice?
Not today.
Come here often?
I'm beginning
to feel like a regular.
Don't you have anything better to do
than hang around a chemo ward?
Bryce, you're my friend.
You're crazy if you think
I'm gonna let you alone.
I appreciate
what you're doing, but...
I don't want you
to see me like this.
Is this about your pride?
- A little bit, yeah.
- Hello, it's me.
You've glued pennies to the wall
with my lunatic mother.
I think we've both seen
behind the curtain.
Besides,
the chemo's gonna make you
sick as a dog in 24 hours.
So tonight let's have some fun.
Let's do it.
But I'm buying dinner.
You call SFPD?
What do you think?
- Help you guys?
- Special Agent Benford. Agent Noh.
Detective John Smith.
Yes, that's my real name.
- What do you need?
- What happened here?
Some guy from the chess club
took two in the back of the head.
Don't tell me. Ian McKinnon?
Yeah, Ian McKinnon.
Person of interest?
Not anymore.
Ian McKinnon was unlucky enough to play
a few games of chess back in the '80s,
and now he's dead.
He was our best lead on Frost,
but our leak turned him
into a homicide investigation.
San Francisco bureau
is handling the follow-up,
but I'm not expecting much.
How long between when you first made
contact and time of death?
Eight hours tops.
There's only one conclusion.
The leak we've been tracking,
that's compromised the security
of the whole mosaic investigation
is inside the bureau.
Not just the bureau.
Inside our office.
I've been ordered
to give full agency support,
fresh pair of eyes,
all the rest of that crap.
You got a play?
My dad knew a guy
who used to go blast fishing.
He'd throw a stick
of dynamite in the water
and watch the fish float to the top.
It was ugly, but it worked.
Game on.
Just don't forget
who your friends are.
What's unacceptable is
that one of them is my enemy.
- Step away from your desk.
- What the hell is going on here?
Everyone's required to assemble
in the conference room.
On whose authorization?
Sorry, assistant director Wedeck.
Orders.
- Whose orders?
- I'm not at liberty to say.
That's not part of
the task force agreement.
No calls, and I'll need
your cell phone, please.
- Don't touch me.
- Sir, your phone.
What's going on?
Someone lose their keys?
Simon Campos?
You're in there also.
I'm not really an employee.
I'm more of a visitor.
What is this?
I've not had my coffee yet.
What's this about?
Judging from the way our offices
are being torn apart,
I'd say an inter-agency task force
has been formed,
and is looking for a leak.
We can't just look
for the leak on our own?
I think the point is,
one of us is a mole.
And Mark?
Apparently already vetted.
This office has been swept.
* You are the sunshine of my life *
* Girl *
* Forever you're stay in my heart *
* You are the apple *
Tweezers.
There's your leak.
Get out.
It's voice-activated.
When your office is swept for bugs
at 4:00 AM
the sweepers don't make any sound.
No sound, no transmission.
You've vetted the sweepers?
Since the blackout,
all techs have been agency-contracted.
Blind assignments.
That's how you do security.
They just don't know
about the singing.
So who has access
to your office, Mark?
Everyone in that room.
Time to light the fuse.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as you may have deduced,
we're closing in on a leak
inside the FBI
that is hampering
the mosaic investigation.
Now, anyone want to confess?
Then it's the hard road.
You'll be first, Agent Noh,
as you were part
of the failed attempt
to contact Ian McKinnon.
You got anything to say about this?
We have to do this.
Vogel, you're a son of a bitch.
You know that?
True as that may be,
I'm working with agent Benford today.
I was with you the whole time
in San Francisco.
- You're not the mole.
- Who then?
- Someone in that room.
- If you don't think I'm the mole,
- what the hell am I doing in here?
- He has to think I suspect everyone.
Even you.
How long are we gonna be
stuck in here?
Good question. They've got
their whole procedure to go through.
Re-vet contact histories,
bureau records, computers.
That could take days. They're gonna want
to vet all of our personal files.
Not if they don't have passwords.
- You didn't give up your passwords?
- Not to my personal files, no.
Something on your computer
you don't want people to see?
No, I mean,
nothing that's sensitive.
I'm clean.
It's porn.
Agent Curdy, downloading
naked cheerleaders on F.B.I. time?
It's nothing like that.
It's...
It's just an R.P.G.
What?
It's an R.P.G.
It's a role-playing game.
I play "Warlocks of Avalon" online.
I'm a 7th level druid.
My name is "Argothic."
You have any special powers?
Cape of invisibility, lightning hammer,
elixir of life, healing.
- That's impressive.
- Yeah, it's cool.
You're next. Vreede.
Can I borrow that cape?
There any reason we can't get back
to work, do something useful?
Vogel found a micro-transmitter...
In that key.
You want to be useful?
Tell me who put that in my office.
You think it was one of us?
That's the working theory.
"M"... For "Mark."
Nice touch.
- Unless it was you, Marcie.
- Can you shut up for five minutes?
- Want some sugar?
- I don't use sugar.
We're with you.
You know that.
Thanks.
But we're close.
We'll get him.
Good thing the fate of the planet
doesn't rely on Benford
finding the mole.
Son of a bitch!
Excuse me!
Koreatown's further west.
No. I'm not Korean.
I'm Japanese.
Either way,
you gotta get on the bus.
- You want this car to do that?
- That's the idea.
I look?
You look?
You look like you don't belong here,
and you don't belong under the car.
Hydraulics or nitrogen air bags?
Hydraulics.
Could be fracture in cylinder.
I can help.
Maybe I surprise you, yes?
Okay, ninja girl. But if you break
my axle, I'm coming after you.
Thank you.
This is really screwing
with my trust issues. You know that?
You've been through a lot, Janis.
I took a bullet, Mark.
And I'm seriously a suspect?
You have to admit that getting shot
and living makes for a perfect cover.
Screw you, Vogel.
I'm sure there's a reason,
but you got a number
of unaccounted personal breaks
in the weeks since the blackout.
- 13 in all.
- So?
In the three previous years
at the Bureau, you've taken precisely...
Two.
You know what I saw
in my flash-forward.
I've been going
to a fertility clinic.
You only had eight visits.
- We checked.
- So what?
So I went out to go buy some shoes.
- Come on, Mark.
- Where were you?
What is it, Janis?
Ever since the shooting, I've been
looking at everyone differently.
Suspicious.
Just checking up.
- And you found something?
- Does he have to be here for this?
Marcie has a brother.
- We know about him.
- There's another one...
A half brother.
He's very sick.
He's dying in Missouri
in a full care facility.
It's expensive.
Marcie didn't name him
in any of her applications.
Those absences? I went off-site
to look into some things.
- You never mentioned this before.
- I was waiting.
For what?
- I was seeing if she did something.
- Marcie's paying for this care?
There was a deposit made
to an account for $50,000
three months ago...
Anonymous.
Okay, Janis. Thanks.
I don't know anything for sure.
I'm just trying to help.
- You've done the right thing.
- It doesn't feel like it.
You trust her?
You know what?
Being around you makes me
not trust anyone anymore.
It's gonna rain.
But we're together.
We're having a girl's day.
I don't want to have a girl's day.
I want daddy to be here.
Daddy wants to be here, too.
Then why isn't he?
Here's the thing, sweetie.
Daddy and I love each other
very much.
But most of all, we love you.
And we're always gonna be a family.
That's never gonna change.
I promise.
Come on. Let's go for a ride.
Let's do it.
- Can I ride the ferris wheel?
- You want to go on the ferris wheel?
I went through Marcie's background.
She did declare her brother
in her initial application.
Janis said she didn't.
The original vetting records
were at a regional field office.
When they were routed to DC,
an entirely separate file was created.
It was easy to miss.
You okay?
I moved out of the house.
Olivia and me... we're...
I don't know.
I moved out.
Sorry.
Is this about what you saw
in your flash-forward?
Partly that, partly what she saw.
Is there anything I can do?
But Marcie's still a suspect,
so keep digging.
All right.
Tell your future.
- Can we do that again?
- No, my love. Let'go. Let's go.
- Can we go again?
- No, sweetie.
Why are you following us?
Because it's my job.
I'm special agent Danforth Crowley.
Your husband assigned me to be
your security detail. Your safety
is his number one priority.
You don't know much english,
so I know you don't have a work visa.
I can try to get you
paid off the books.
That's your first job.
Client wants more horsepower,
so we've been trying to remap the ECU.
My guys only work on carbureted
engines, so for them it's like...
Japanese.
German.
You said you were some big-time engineer
back in Japan.
Maybe you can figure this out.
It is no problem.
Yo, Emil.
You didn't tell us about a masseuse.
Listen up.
Cut the music.
I got something to say.
This is Keiko.
She works here now.
She's part of the family.
Treat her with respect,
or we're gonna have a problem.
Everyone get that?
I'll take that as a yes.
Get to work.
Hey, it's me.
I just wanted to thank you
for that security detail.
It scared the hell out of me,
but I guess it helps.
Charlie misses you.
Anyway, I'm at the hospital,
so call me if you...
We need to talk.
I swear I wouldn't bother you
if it wasn't absolutely necessary.
You literally have
the world's worst timing.
I've heard that before.
What do you want, Lloyd?
I need to know exactly what you saw
in your flash-forward.
I wrote a formula
on your bedroom mirror,
and I think it relates somehow
to the global blackout,
but what I saw was incomplete.
Did you see it?
I did.
Part of it.
I've to make a call.
After a while,
I got up from the bed.
Then I noticed something was written
on the mirror.
It was written in lipstick.
Most of it was indecipherable,
but I did recognize this.
Halothane.
It's an anesthetic.
Quantum physics and anesthetics...
That's what Mark and I were
working on in our flash-forward.
I thought QED
meant quantum electrodynamics.
But we were... Building
a quantum entanglement device.
Good.
That clears that up.
- I've to be getting on with my rounds.
- Of course.
I don't want you to think...
I'm harassing you.
No, I know.
You're just trying to save the world.
Good-bye.
So you come here every single night
just in case this guy shows up?
And during the daytime.
I know.
But it's the only way
I can find him.
All right. I respect that.
You saw your fate,
and now you're doing your thing.
When I saw my future,
it was
the best day of my life.
It was the first day
I let myself want
what was in my heart.
So like you say,
I am doing my thing.
Can I ask, what did you see?
Something different than you.
Let's leave it at that.
You are kind
to give me a job.
We're lucky to have you.
Thank you, Emil.
You ever tried sea urchin?
No. Is it good?
It's like eating somebody's thyroid.
I'm sure Keiko loves it.
If she's the woman you love with in your
vision, you have to it eat with her.
This could be a problem.
What if sushi's her favorite food,
and that's all
she ever wants to eat?
Suddenly she's a Mogwai.
You're being ridiculous.
A what?
Never mind.
- What's a mogwai?
- I'm not explaining it to you.
Justify your metaphor, young lady.
Mogwai... You know, Gizmo...
The furry creatures that turn into
gremlins if you don't feed 'em right.
They had dietary restrictions.
Forget it.
It's a very nerdy metaphor.
Just shut up and read the menu.
I don't know.
I'm just not feeling
sushi tonight.
I am.
I guess I can have teriyaki.
You're kind of a spoiled brat.
I never noticed
- that about you before.
- How dare you?
I have cancer.
All right.
What do you want to do?
I'm sorry...
I don't know why...
I just did that.
I know why I did that, but...
It's, you're thinking
about another woman.
You can't just
kiss me...
In little Tokyo,
- no less.
- Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry. It's just...
You're great.
Honest mistake.
Just buy me a burger,
and we'll call it even.
Deal.
- Good morning, Keiko.
- Morning.
Too much sake?
Next time we have tequila.
How's it going?
This car will go very fast.
We need a little more horsepower. We're
not trying to launch it into space,
- you know?
- Immigration!
I.C.E. Nobody move!
- Hands behind your heads!
- Do what I do.
Hands behind your head!
Now! Do it now!
You Emil Gutierrez?
You're under arrest for employment
of undocumented workers.
What's your name?
Do you have an I-9?
I-9?
Surprise, surprise.
Load 'em into the van. Let's go.
It's me. Listen,
I had a great time last night...
and I'm sorry about kissing you.
Actually, I'm not.
I'm glad. So...
Anyway...
They've been in there
36 hours.
Got anything?
All of marcie's background has been gone
through by vogel's people already...
Financials, phone records,
background checks up the wazoo.
I'm doing surveillance tagging
right now.
This surveillance tech isgood.
Wait.
Go back.
Go back there.
How many times does she have coffee?
She has coffee most of the time.
Why?
She doesn't use sugar.
Give me time stamps for every time
she put sugar in her coffee.
Each of these time stamps
corresponds to a day
a key piece
of information was leaked.
Look at that.
No one knew about the pigeon,
Utah, trip...
Crap!
Or the Somali intel
that triggered the attack
in Washington.
Every time she put sugar
in her coffee,
she was signaling her handlers.
Marcie, what you doing?
Down! Everybody down!
- Go!
- Cut her off at the stairs!
Hold fire, hold fire.
Get her out of here.
It looks like you were right, Janis.
I wish I wasn't.
- You could have let me in on it.
- I couldn't say anything.
- Orders.
- You told Demetri.
It was discretionary.
I need people in that room.
So I was manipulated
for the greater good.
Queen sacrifice...
Frost's play.
- How'd you know about that?
- We all have our ways, Mark.
Agent Benford. Dyson Frost.
Don't speak. Just listen.
I haven't come forward since all
your leads end up dead.
But now that your mole problem
has been fixed,
I look forward to meeting you.
I'll be in touch.
You were quite the hero today.
I like a woman who knows how
to handle a firearm.
Fanca drink?
I'm not really your type.
I think you'd be surprised
to learn exactly what my type is.
I reviewed your uncle
Teddy's autopsy x-rays.
The CPR you gave him
was quite aggressive.
Could have even been
the cause of his death.
Yeah, I...
can be quite a tiger.
You murdered him to send a message.
Message received.
I should have known.
A double plant.
Two moles,
in case one is caught
brilliant.
And not one person in the office
would suspect it's you.
Not one.
Well, that would be the point,
now, wouldn't it?
-= Blackout Team =-