On March 15th, 2010,
you are going to be murdered.
- Your briefing said who killed me?
- I have to end this call now.
My daughter's alive.
She saw something she shouldn't have...
and got in trouble with Jericho.
The second that Jericho
knows that I'm still alive,
they'll kill me.
N.S.A. sent back
a new rendering of Suspect Zero.
- What's on his hand?
- A ring?
This morning,
I was thinking  committing suicide.
- My God.
- Everything's changed for me now.
- Who's she ?
- She was in my vision.
In my flash-forward,
I saw this symbol.
- It's a letter.
- What's it mean?
"Believe."
See there,
there...
- and there.
- It's metastasized.
To the liver.
No sign of it in the lungs or bones?
We hoped this treatment
would have stopped the growth.
It doesn't seem
to have had an effect.
What about hormone therapy?
You're stage four.
It's not likely to do much
except make you feel lousy.
I...
I feel all right now.
That's not atypical
for this type of cancer.
I'm gonna be straight.
We're running out of options.
We could try another round of chemo.
I have patients at this point
who have gotten into clinical trials.
How long have I got?
Come on!
What are you doin', man?
Didn't you see me?
I'm talking to you.
What are you doing?
No! Come on!
All right. Come on!
What are you, nuts?
You made your point!
This is a Cherry'63 T-Bird!
I want to report a hit and run.
He's still hitting me!
You made your point!
All right. Okay.
It's all right.
You are so dead, man.
You hear me?
You're dead!
"Believe"
Dr. Varley,
she's oozing an awful lot.
What was her platelet count,
hemoglobin and coags preop?
I'm sorry. Her platelets were...
Platelets 80,000, hemoglobin 10.5.
- Looks like a cirrhotic to me.
- Is she a drinker, Dr. Varley?
Sorry...
Come on, Bryce.
Maneesh, I'm gonna need some F.F.P.
and 2 units of
packed red blood cells
as soon as you can get 'em.
She's oozing everywhere we cut.
Send a D.I.C. panel
and hang a banana bag
with two grams of mag.
Dr. Benford, I'm sorry.
You need to think seriously
about whether or not you're
committed to this profession.
I don't know where I belong.
I'm not a very good doctor.
I never have been, really.
It wasn't what you wanted?
I don't know what I want.
I just...
did it.
And now I'm here.
Have you told your family,
your colleagues about your illness?
My family's been through enough,
Dr. Flemming.
With my dad dying of
lung cancer for three years...
It was a nightmare.
What about your colleagues?
- Surely they would understand.
- I don't want their pity.
Pity ?
You need support. That's
what's gonna get you through this.
Nothing is gonna
get me through this.
My diagnosis is terminal.
You don't know
what the future holds.
None of us do, really.
Your job is to take care of yourself
to try and have the best life
you can for as long as you can.
Live each day
doing what feels right.
You're really here.
Pleased to meet you.
Hajimemashite.
Please speak more slowly.
Yukkuri hanashite kudasai.
What's your name?
O namae wa nan desu ka?
I love you.
Suki desu.
Please sit down.
Okakekudasai.
How are you feeling today?
Gokigen ikada desu ka?
I hope you are well...
Can you give me the directions?
I am lost.
Michi ni mayotte imasu.
Who are you?
Anata wa dare desu ka?
What do you want?
Nani o omotome desu ka?
Hey, how is Tracy?
She's...
She's pretty shut down.
Terrified Jericho's
gonna come and find her.
I've been looking into that for you.
Unfortunately,
private military contractors
like Jericho and Blackwater
are harder to break into
than Fort Knox.
- That's what I was afraid of.
- But this outfit's headquartered
in Santa Monica,
right in our own backyard,
working out of the Burroughs Foundation
for International Peace...
Some kind of think tank.
- Think tank?
- Yep.
It's gonna take a higher
security clearance than I have
to get much beyond that.
Hold on a sec.
Livvie, your phone's ringing.
- Can you get it?
- I gotta go.
I'll put out
some more feelers, all right?
Who is it?
Who was it?
What is this?
It's this weird text I got.
Who sent it?
I have no idea.
Do you...
figured you...
you wouldn't mention it?
You already told me about the drinking.
Before I got a chance to bring it up.
Since we talked about it,
that didn't seem
like such a big deal.
I gotta get dressed.
- Nice job with that tension pneumo.
- Thanks.
You okay?
You look sick.
- I'm okay.
- Come here.
I'm all right.
You're not febrile,
but you're really pale.
Go home.
Cynthia will cover your shift.
I'm gonna be okay.
I just need a minute.
Come here.
Come sit.
- You look terrible.
- I'm just tired.
Graphia says you almost passed out
during grand rounds last week.
- What's going on?
- It's nothing.
- We don't need to do that.
- Come on.
Why do you have a central line?
It's for the chemo.
Chemo?
I have...
renal cell carcinoma.
Stage four.
How long have you known?
About a year.
Had my kidney out
just before I started here.
This is why you tried
to kill yourself...
I was terrified.
I didn't think that I could
face the prospect of dying.
I didn't want to put
my family through that.
I can't believe you...
have been going through this alone.
I can't believe I didn't see it.
It hasn't been that bad so far.
It's rough for a few days after
chemo, but then I bounce back.
Anyway, since the blackout,
things are different now.
I'm gonna be okay.
I've got something to live for.
It's hot.
I forgot the cheese.
I don't need the cheese.
This smells great.
When I was in the military,
this crazy staff sergeant in my detail
made the best food
I ever threw a lip on.
What?
I can't do this.
Do what?
Have you drinking here.
It's just a glass of wine.
Doesn't matter. A glass of wine...
or a fifth of vodka...
It just doesn't work for me.
Come on, Dad. Relax.
I'm not asking you to drink.
That's not the point.
I can't be in the same room as it.
You understand that?
After everything I've been through,
I can't have a glass of wine?
I'm 24 years old,
and I've been through hell.
I can't have a drink?
Baby, I'm not talking about
what you can or can't do.
I'm telling you...
what I can't do.
This is good.
Fine.
I'll go somewhere else.
The NSA's digital forensics team
uncovered this symbol
on Suspect Zero's ring.
Alpha.
And it could mean anything...
The angle of attack in aerodynamics,
the brightest star in a constellation.
Alpha is the beginning of everything.
If we can enhance the ring so well,
why can't we see his face?
We tried to rebuild that image from all
the various camera angles that we got.
But in one,
his skin was all blown out.
In another, it was
a raking profile and so on.
The ring was much easier.
It has hard edges
and a reflective surface.
We captured still images
as the hand moved.
We replaced pixels and then
built a 3-D model of it.
Frankly, we were hoping
the NSA would provide us
an analysis of the ring that
was a little more substantial.
To tell you the truth,
I'm a little uncomfortable
talking in this particular group.
Uncomfortable?
Look, Mrs. Levy,
we don't have time to play games.
I'll be blunt, Mr. Wedeck.
One of the members
of your Mosaic task force
has been red-flagged by the NSA.
What?
Who?
A couple of months ago,
our wiretapping program
intercepted a phone call whose origins
had been professionally concealed
to a bureau cell phone.
Whose phone?
Agent Noh's.
Since when do you guys
wiretap the FBI?
Homeland Security
is the number one priority.
- Homeland Security...
- Wait a minute.
Maybe it's the call...
your call from the woman.
- About your murder.
- Right.
Are you saying that you have
a recording of that call?
How do I get it?
I'm sorry. It's classified SIGINT...
signals intelligence.
The woman who made that call told me
I was gonna be murdered on March 15th.
I'm running out of time,
so if you have any information
on who that was
or why I'm going to be killed...
- I'm not authorized to give...
- Come on!
Call whoever you need to call
to make it happen then!
How about that, Ms. Levy?
Let me make a call.
Benjwa...
doko...
Desu ka Los Angeles?
You just said
"Where is the toilet, Los Angeles?"
Let me see that book a sec.
It's so cool you're learning a language
for someone you haven't even met.
But I am gonna meet her.
I know it.
I'm hearing myself,
and I sound crazy.
But it's a good kind of crazy.
Love crazy.
You think?
Hey.
- Didn't see you there.
- Yeah, I came in late.
Yeah? What's up?
I'm really struggling, Aaron.
Things were going great at home,
or better at least.
Then this thing happened.
Someone sent Olivia a text, telling her
I was drinking in my flash-forward.
Who would do that?
I don't know.
I only told two people.
It's kind of freaking me out, you know?
That's weird.
You trying to say
something to me, Mark?
Like I said,
I only told two people.
Do you know how many hours
I've spent listening to your crap,
your doubt, your self-pity?
- I thought you were my sponsor.
- That's right.
That doesn't mean
I'm your punching bag.
I think I have the right to ask you
if you're communicating
with my wife behind my back.
You son of a bitch.
After all the time
we've known each other,
you think I would do that?
- I don't know what to think anymore.
- You don't know.
Don't know.
Here's some food for thought.
Why don't you get a new sponsor?
Someone you can really trust.
- Got it.
- What?
Demetri's phone call.
I'm taking it down
to audio forensics right now.
- Can I ask you something?
- What?
Did you send Olivia a text?
Your wife?
- Why would I send your wife a text?
- Well, someone did.
Telling her I was drunk
in my flash-forward.
You're one of only
two people I've told.
So?
So as...
I recall you were pretty pissed
that I was drinking and...
the implications that had
for our investigation.
Oh, I see.
You were thinking I was...
so angry and so petty that I'd run out
and text your wife about it?
Get out of my office, Benford.
I don't wanna see your face right now.
Your accent is really improving,
Dr. Varley.
If nothing else, I'll come out of this
having learned a second language.
So how's the search
for your young woman?
Well, no response
to my Mosaic posting yet,
but I did finish my drawing.
You wanna see it?
She's quite beautiful.
I was thinking
about posting it on the web.
At least you know
where she likes to eat.
What do you mean?
Sushi Arahida.
It's a restaurant in Tsukuba.
Not that far from Tokyo.
I taught at the university there.
Is it possible there's more than
one restaurant with this name in...
Tsukuba?
I doubt it, not with this same logo.
It's a little, tiny place.
She's probably a local.
Ms. Kondo, in my flash-forward,
I was sitting
in a Japanese restaurant.
Maybe it's this Sushi Arahida.
- Maybe.
- Thank you!
Do you have a minute?
Listen,
maybe it's none of my business,
but I made a few calls,
did a little bit of research
and there really are
some good options out there.
- I appreciate...
- A friend from medical school,
who's running an experimental trial
with Trifectumab
out of M.D. Anderson in Houston.
So I made a call, and you're in.
- Thank you.
- No. You kidding?
It's the least I can do.
Here.
I've read about Trifectumab.
I'm not sure
about the side effects, though.
We're talking about your life.
Now's not the time to be conservative.
Dr. Benford, thank you.
But you don't understand.
Because of my flash-forward, I know
that I have something to live for.
I can't take a drug
that might kill me or make me sicker.
You're only gonna hear me
say this once.
Maybe the reason you're alive
in your flash-forward
is because you're gonna take
this drug and get better.
Don't give up on me.
Please.
Come here.
Go to Houston.
You need a couple of days,
take a couple of days.
There is no delicate way
to say this,
but on March 15, 2010,
you are going to be murdered.
It's even worse
hearing it a second time.
We've analyzed the ambient noise,
and we've come up with a potential lead.
- What kind of a lead?
- Listen to this.
There is no delicate way...
Now, I stripped away everything
but the background noise.
- We found...
- You found cheesy electronic music.
Not just any cheesy electronic music,
my friend.
It's the Symphony of Lights,
the world's largest outdoor
light and music show.
Plays every night,
in Hong Kong Harbour.
Wanna take a little trip?
I'm sorry,
but I just can't send you to China
after that C.I.A. idiot accused them
of causing the blackout.
Relations between us
are tense enough as it is.
Look, I want to solve Demetri's
potential murder as much as anyone,
but even if she made the call
from Hong Kong,
- there's nothing to say that...
- She concealed the origins of her call.
That alone makes her a suspect.
We have to find out
who she is and what she knows.
I promise you,
I'll have our legats guy in Asia
track her down, but I need you here.
You're not going to Hong Kong.
End of story.
We're going.
What?
Hong Kong.
Wedeck's gonna be pissed.
He'll get over it.
I'm sorry.
Is this your daughter,
Is this your daughter?
Is this your sister?
They told me at the restaurant,
that she lived here.
Please, I came all the way
from Los Angeles. Is this Keiko?
Do you know Keiko?
Keiko, please.
I'm such an idiot.
I travel more than 5,000 miles
because of a T-shirt?
- What was I thinking?
- That you were going to find the woman.
- But I didn't.
- Now you know her name.
- That's something.
- I don't know if it's her real name.
I went to the university.
I went back to the restaurant.
No one can tell me anything.
I don't know
how long I can wait, Nicole.
Maybe you're just trying to rush things
that can't be rushed.
Sometimes,
you just gotta be patient.
Isn't that how love works?
Maybe,
I misinterpreted the whole thing.
Maybe it's just...
Some kind of fantasy.
And a really good way
to run away from my life.
Bryce, come home.
Come home.
Can I come in?
What do you want?
To talk.
- I was out of line.
- Yeah, you were.
I've been a little stressed.
You think you're the only one
who's dealing with issues?
Of course I don't.
I know you're dealing with Tracy...
You have no idea,
so why don't you just
shut the hell up?
Tracy's back, but she's not
the person she used to be.
That person is dead.
- Aaron...
- No, you...
You don't get it.
She's broken,
angry, scared.
She drinks herself to sleep,
every night.
She's a messed up alcoholic.
And I'm to blame...
for all of it.
She enlisted because
she wanted to be just like me.
And now she drinks.
Just like me.
There's not a damn thing
that I can do about it.
Look, we've crossed a line here...
for better or worse.
I don't think
I can be your sponsor anymore.
Sorry.
But I could really use a friend.
You got it.
Welcome to Los Angeles.
Enjoy your stay.
-= Blackout Team =-