John From Cincinnati Season 1 Episode 6
His Visit: Day five (Version Caph)
Capture : Swsub.com
Synch : Gaillots
www.Team-NCIS.com
www.All-about-Subs.fr
Thanks for supporting clean water!
- We've gone off the path now.
- All right, KC.
Way to go, buddy.
That's good.
Perfect.
No.
Oh, I guess I'm just
a stick-in-the-mud.
Just 'cause every
degenerate in america
Jerks off to
his mother's videos...
And she only showed up to make money
off of Shaunie being in the papers,
Why would I think
she couldn't help him
Through his teen years?
Well, I hope it's pumping
at Salsipuedes, Mitch.
I hope you catch
some real soul-searchers.
Good morning.
You didn't have to shout
about her, gram.
Did I wake you up?
I knew already.
Where did you get this?
Shaunie!
You hurt my feelings, gram.
You did.
That extra grand is
for telling me how it was.
You think you might have
had a good time?
That's it, I think I might have.
You fucked me cross-eyed.
I never took a cock that big
and you handle it like a champ.
My god,
the perfect woman.
Do better than you did
with Butchie.
With Shaun?
I don't think
I'll get the chance.
You sure
you want to?
Stick around.
Help me think.
Yeah. That's what
I'm good at.
I had a good time.
Don't be afraid, Joe.
That's a good way to get another
fatal injury there, frat boy.
How did you get
through the wire?
How did you
find this place?
Look, I got
close onto 500 plants
Less than a week from harvest
within 100 yards of here
And it makes me
fucking nervous.
Justice must be served, Joe.
The vato must get his due.
The one that stabbed you?
Well, if there ever
was a crime
That cried to heaven
for redress,
It'd be getting gutted
and left in a ditch.
The police should
be involved.
Well,
as far as that, I..
I flinch from it
in principle.
You saw enough
of that shit over there.
Bill should be involved, Joe.
- Bill jacks?
- I got my eye on you!
Him and me served
around the same time.
Different units.
Bill's good people.
I don't care
how much you say
that I'm thinking, frat boy.
I'm still not giving up herb.
Zippy told Bill we'd be over.
Hey.
No fire trucks headed
to your house last night.
I figure that
had to be a plus.
- Did he stop here?
- Shaunie?
Who else would I
be asking about?
No.
Is he surfing?
He took his skateboard.
He didn't take his wetsuit.
Well, I wonder if
maybe he's skating.
Could you go see?
You busy, Cissy?
Time for your ball-buster
booster shot?
Will you go
look for him or not?
I guess
I probably will.
Is he gonna hit me with
a brick when I find him?
He loves you.
Did you talk to him
after I left?
He was asleep.
Well, did you tell him
this morning she was there?
He heard me say some things
about her on the phone to Mitch.
Was one of them that
Tina had been to the house the night
before to see Shaunie?
He heard me say
she made dirty movies
and he storms
out of the house.
He knows she makes
dirty movies, Cissy.
That idiot friend
of his gave him one.
Well, he is barred
from the store.
Are you sure he didn't hear
you say Tina had been there?
I didn't say
she'd been there, Kai.
Which of those piss pots
gave him her fuck film?
Are you sure he was
asleep the night before?
What are you talking about?
What I'm
talking about is,
If he knew Tina
came to see him
and he didn't get to look at
her, maybe that's why he's upset.
Well, maybe if you'd go and
fucking ask him, we'd know.
Did you happen to
hear from Butchie?
No.
Big surprise.
Why?
For my website.
Me and the Yosts, information
I don't give a fuck about.
You ask Shaun
what he wants.
Does he want
to see her?
Is that what he's being
such a little jerk about?
How can anyone
help you, Cissy,
When you won't see
what's right in front of you?
Which is what?
Which is, whoever
you don't drive away
runs away on his own.
How do you stand
the constant cheeping?
Every one hatched
in this home.
Be aware, if you speak
in that voice again,
I will break every bone
in your body.
What's your policy on
guests smoking herb?
Not permitted.
And your smart-ass friend here
with his charlie mccarthy imitations
Skates on very very
very thin ice...
How about in the backyard?
Which I'm liable as not
to pound his head through,
with my fist,
and hold him gagging,
and thrashing beneath
the surface of,
till he drowns.
The ice.
Chamomile, Billy,
wonderful.
He's imitating my wife,
Who has passed!
Oh for Christ's sake!
What the hell
are we doing here?
Go ahead, Zip.
You're the big cruise director.
Entertain 'em while I
get back my composure.
This young man who's
had his eye on you
wants the vato who gutted
him to face arrest.
Oh god,
are you okay, honey?
Are you in discomfort?
No.
Is he lying to me,
to his own purposes?
No, Billy.
Oh for Christ's sake.
Get out of here,
Both of you.
Come on.
I'll do what you want.
Just let me get my composure.
Where is my food?
Where is my food?!
Come in!
You can just put it...
Yeah.
Thank you.
Oh, that looks good.
Fucking drum circle.
If those strings are
not drawn taut, Butchie,
There may as well be no strings.
Watch me tighten
these babies, Meyer.
No no no, I'll do it.
Thank- thanks for
the offer.
You might want to wait
for the painting phase.
Paint I huff.
Then that wouldn't be
a good phase either.
Motherfucker...
How are you today?
- What?
- How are you?
A morning pleasantry.
How would you be,
drowning in lowlifes?
I'm sure I'd be
gasping for air.
For your room.
Hawaii, I'm saying.
I was talking on the phone.
Oh yes.
Don't ask if
you don't want to know.
- Hey, doc!
- Hey.
How's your friend feeling?
Well, he's got his balls
in that blonde girl's chin,
So if he's not doing good,
shame on him.
And your boy?
Boy's doing good,
as far as I know.
There's lots of quick
healers in this Zip code.
Oh yeah!
Doctors. Patient's in critical pain.
Call Monday.
I'm playing golf.
Yeah, I don't know
what you're talking about.
How you feeling?
Good, fine.
Thanks for asking.
You giving me
a small surprise, doc.
What do the x-rays show?
My x-rays?
What'd they show?
Yeah.
Everything's good,
you know.
Healing up good.
Like gangbusters, you know?
Thanks for asking, very much.
Appreciate that.
Which bones did it
turn out were broken?
- What?
- Which bones in your wrist?
Which of your metacarpals?
Oh most, if not all.
But they decided
not to cast it?
Well, you know
how they are.
My sense would be
you should have a cast on that.
Yeah, well,
chocolate-vanilla, doc, right?
You know? You had your chance
and then you didn't so...
The textbook approach would be not
to cast a patient before an x-ray.
Yeah, well,
push comes to shove,
Fuck all of ya.
You know?
Won't let
a sleeping dog lie!
Hey, take it easy,
Palaka!
What's going on?
You starting trouble?
Never mind!
Never mind.
An acquaintance
sustains a fracture,
Provides his boss entree to ask
after a stranger's condition...
Maybe you should
get out of the sun now?
Yeah, you and me, we could both
contract fatal fucking dysentery
before anybody gives
the first flying fuck!
Excuse me, I got to clean the 4.
Hold my string.
In some situations,
you moron piece of shit
maybe heard as
a blessed solicitor.
- What?
- Hello, Miss. Yost.
Yeah, hello.
I need to talk to Butchie.
You two know each other?
I'm sure your mother
doesn't remember me.
Yeah. Sorry.
But she expressed what I took for
a kindness a number of years ago.
Can we talk, please?
He's probably confusing
you with someone else.
Cissy.
One mother's rebuke
of her son,
Even if vile and obscene,
may be taken as kindness
by another
whose mother is not at hand.
Why don't we go take
some pictures of your wrist
and then I can put
a cast on after?
Thanks, but no thank you.
I'll take care of it
my birthday after next.
Hey hey, wait!
Look at me, I'm talking
to you. Apologize to him.
- I'm scrubbing the pool tiles.
- No apologies necessary.
You shut up.
I jump down there, you'll be scrubbing
your own brains off those tiles.
Well I definitely better
climb out then, huh?
Who better than
the source of my fracture
to force me to give up
enjoying myself?
Forcing treatment on a person
isn't my idea of good practice.
No one asked for your ideas.
Just take him to
get his wrist fixed,
or you're liable to need
treatment yourself.
Your speech pattern inclines
toward the megalomaniacal.
I also grind my fucking teeth at night.
But I'm not your fucking patient.
I'm happy to take you
if you want to go.
Here, drive my car.
Unless you want to ride
on his handlebars?
Just follow me.
I'm gonna follow a bicycle?
It's not far.
I want Tina to see Shaun.
Which one of us was high
last night, ma?
I was not fucking high last night.
I'm just saying, unless I
was loaded, Tina saw him.
And I'm saying...
You mean with
his eyes open?
Is that what
you're saying?
I fucked up this morning.
I said things.
I- I mean,
I said the truth.
I was talking to your
asshole father on the phone
and Shaunie heard me talk about her.
You mean, he was
listening in on the call?
Oh, you fucking moron.
Well, I guess
you were yelling.
I hurt his feelings.
He walked out,
I hurt him so bad.
How bad was
what you said?
That she was a whore,
porn queen, piece of shit.
He is 13, ma.
And Tina's tapes get around.
You know, there's half a chance
that it wasn't fresh news.
- He already had one of her tapes.
- There you go.
He didn't even
open it, you moron.
It was still in its wrapper.
I only came to ask you to...
To get in touch with her.
She left I.B., ma.
I asked if she was
staying last night.
What business did you have
asking if she was staying?
I don't know.
I'll never see him again.
Come on.
You didn't see his face.
You want me to go
looking for him?
I asked Kai.
Yeah, that's good.
I have her number, Tina.
Do you want me to
try her on the phone?
Isn't that what the fuck
I came to ask you?
What is this bullshit?
I'm afraid of my fiancee.
Hey, Tina!
How's your ass?
Got all your tapes.
Came to most of 'em.
I am gonna get high.
I've been fucking high in my life.
Higher than any other
fucking asshole I know.
And I am gonna get
twice as high
as I have ever been.
Do you avoid having
guests in your home?
Do you make excuses to them
when you know you're
ashamed of your flooring?
Are you ashamed
of your flooring?
I would like to know our motive
and our specific purpose, and
I will not directly ask a moron.
I would like to
know our motive.
Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ!
I found him stabbed near this road.
And vato was in his vocabulary...
He doesn't have a vocabulary.
He's a human parrot.
I am a human parrot!
And being a human parrot,
and him now saying vato,
the more likely we're in
the right neighborhood.
Fried-brain hophead!
My fucking fibromyalgia
is in upheaval!
Justice must be served.
Quiet, John.
I'll give 'em justice
with my two bare hands!
Justice...
On the border with mexico.
I think we may all need a spliff.
Well, on that, I take no position.
I'll carpet four rooms
in your house.
Could you at least
turn the radio off?
Hello?
Where the fuck
have you been?
My cell phone just rang.
Oh did it just ring,
you fucking cunt?
I've been calling you for
the past 20 minutes.
It just rang, Butchie!
Did it just ring, or were you sucking
some nigger's prick?!
Yeah, don't answer it.
Don't answer, I will find you
wherever you are
and I will cut your fucking
cunt out of your body.
I'm not gonna listen
to that shit.
Don't fucking hang up on me, Tina.
All right, don't you
fucking hang up!
All right, just let me
try to figure out
what the fuck
I'm trying to do here.
Okay, listen to me.
Listen to me.
I apologize.
All right, listen to me.
Shaunie needs to see you.
Or Cissy wants you
to see Shaunie.
I can't come back, Butchie.
What? You got to go
suck some nigger's prick?
Don't hang up!
Fuck, listen to me.
Shaunie's feelings
are hurt, okay?
He's upset.
About what?
He's feelings are hurt.
Ok, he's lost.
She doesn't know
where he is.
That I came to see him?
No, no, he wants
to see you.
What's he upset about?
Jesus Christ!
What the fuck do I know?
Huh? What the fuck
do I know about it?
I can't even get
fucking high here!
- Are you high, Butchie?
- Fuck you!
All right, fuck you! Why don't you
go mind your own fucking business
And go suck
some nigger's prick!
I'm coming back there.
Don't get high, Butchie.
Don't let Shaun get hurt.
What the fuck do I care?
Oh fuck.
There's someone down in that bush.
How's the reefer treating you?
Believe me,
I've smoked more reefer
than carter made
little liver pills.
Confirm the sighting,
trooper.
I'll confirm it, trooper.
You see that guy there?
- I see that guy.
- Did he stab you? Yes or no?
You know what that's
gonna make him say.
- He stabbed me, yes or no.
- This could end in fisticuffs.
Better she tries to kill me and
fails than tries to kill herself.
Unconscious.
Cissy Yost.
What?
Are you sitting in your kitchen on
7th street thinking of blowing off
your head with your gun you
got back from Kai's trailer?
Have you completely run out
of whatever let you
put up with your
asshole husband for 31 years?
Do you feel that everything you
ever touched in your entire life,
you turned to shit and mud?
Are you ashamed, Cissy,
that once when Mitch was on
one of his bullshit retreats
and you were loaded on acid
and Butchie was 13
and he'd just won his first
contest and you were so proud of him
For not being Mitch, and you went into
his room and he was whipping his skippy,
That you said, "let me
show you how to do that"?
Have you wanted to kill
yourself every day since, Cissy,
And not even known it
and turned yourself into the
worst ball-buster known to man
so no one would be with you
and you wouldn't have to be afraid That
you'd ever do something like that again?
That's how ashamed of
yourself you were?
Do you think now Shaun...
Who you loved so much
and tried to make a life for,
now you turned around and
hurt his feelings so bad?
Do you hurt so bad, you wanted
to just quit and be over?
Everything?
Well, let me tell you
about our offer, Cissy.
We prefer you don't.
We wish you wouldn't.
Our offer is,
keep going,
Feeling just as miserable, or worse.
Hold the gun under the spigot
and turn the water on.
Spare Shaun finding you
dead in the kitchen.
And as a bonus,
you'll also receive his love.
Act now, Cissy.
Baptize that fucking pistol!
Instead of catering to a walk-in trade,
I'd be attorney to
a single client.
A homosexual psychopath.
"Psychopath" is harsh.
Lottery winners are not, Meyer.
Men who hire their attorneys
at gunpoint are psychopaths.
The salary he's offered,
exceeds by $12,000 my income
in any calendar year
since graduation.
What if his relatives
try to have him committed?
I don't think he has
any living relatives.
And I would contest
that motion.
What now, asshole?
I rent this station for $6 an hour...
Isn't this pleasant?
...in order to access and
maintain my website,
Not spend 45 minutes
out of every hour
scanning for viruses
with outdated software.
Here's an idea then,Duane,
I'll reimburse you $4.50,
you take it and buy rat
poison. You bring it here to me
and I'll mix it
with your wheatgrass.
My Yost website got
10,000 hits last night.
It's from Butchie's son, but the
overflow for Butchie could be huge.
Imagine if he still surfed.
That's Butchie's lawyer
filing for bankruptcy.
He must also do
criminal work.
You know what?
Just go away, okay?
Just go away.
Please.
Are you done?
Anytime you're ready.
I want to meet him, this Barry.
I want to meet all of them.
Your new friends.
All right.
Fine.
$5 tip.
He'll get a migraine later.
I asked you not to do that.
You're asking me to go
back to her empty-handed, Kai.
You know, raking is
very relaxing.
You want to feel?
Of course.
Doesn't the Yost boy skate
as well as surf?
It's how he gets around
on land.
Suppose we were to
not fill the pool?
Tell me now before
I go for the hose.
Okay, that's good.
Kai, I called Tina
"what time are you getting here?"
Tina says, "what time is
Shaunie getting to Cissy's?"
And I said, "oh, Shaunie?
Well, Kai can't even get
Shaunie out of the fucking bowl
to ask Shaunie if
he'll go to Cissy's."
Young henry kissinger.
Jesus Christ!
If Shaunie's in the bowl,
he can't hear what you're
saying to me, Kai!
So why are you whispering to me, so
I can't hear what you're saying to me?
I said, I'm not getting
Shaunie in the car,
without telling him
where I'm taking him.
Who told you not to tell him
where you're taking him?
I'm not taking him to Cissy's Until
I know Tina's gonna meet him there.
Tell him Tina's
gonna meet him.
And Cissy said
she'd host the lunch?
If Cissy says that she
wants Tina to see Shaunie,
why wouldn't she want her to see
him in her own fucking house ?
Now, I don't want to
ask her to host a lunch
until I know that Shaun's
in the car with you!
I better not get him
that house,
and have Cissy freak out
in front of Shaun again
'cause then he'll never want
to fucking go back there.
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Oh god.
I gotta get fucking high!
That's how I relax!
All right?
Was he tuning up or
was that a tune?
Rogers and hammerstein.
Not their best phase.
Shaunie!
Your gram sent me.
She feels bad.
She wants to know if
you want to see your mom.
- At my gram's?
- Yeah, at your gram's.
Your gram's the one
trying to make it happen.
She hurts
everyone's feelings.
Your gram's your gram, Shaunie.
Hurry up and decide.
I got work to do at the U.N.
I don't want to
see her at my gram's.
Who financed your video,
Shaunie, with her own money?
Who got you in that contest?
An who's been there for you
every fucking minute of your life?
Hey. Calling my mom.
Where's Shaun?
Kai's taking him to my mom's.
Thanks for coming back.
Why is she taking him
to your mom's?
'cause that's where
you're gonna see him.
- Why does it have to be at her house?
- Hey, mom?
Hold on for a second.
Because that's where it's gonna be.
You said you wanted me to see Shaun,
and your mother wanted me to.
Are you saying your mother
wants to make friends with me?
God's sakes for god's sakes.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Just let me talk to my mother!
Yeah, mom, Tina's here and she wants
to know if you could host a lunch
- for her and Shaun.
- What?
She asked you to ask me that?
Yeah, she's here right now with me.
I'm not fucking talking to her.
No, I mean, yeah.
She's taking a piss.
But she is here and she's
ready to come over.
What does that mean, she wants
me to "host a lunch"?
What do I know? Just lay out some
tuna fish or whatever the fuck you do.
- She's got some balls.
- Yeah.
What do I know?
Anyways, is that the message?
What?
That you want to
have her over for lunch?
I'm not hosting any
fucking lunch.
I'll leave the fucking stuff.
Sure, leave it out.
She'll appreciate it.
You got a previous fucking commitment.
Yeah, that's fine.
Tina: how does he like his tuna fish?
With salt...
And pepper.
Pickles.
And lemon juice.
Two tablespoons of mayo...
Is how I make it.
I don't know how he likes it.
I never asked him.
- Hey.
- Your mom's got a gun.
Yeah, my dad's always in the tree house.
She's afraid of burglars.
Before you and Tina
came over last night,
she had that gun out, Butchie.
I took it away from her,
but then I just found out
she went to my trailer
and got it back.
It's all right about
the gun, I unloaded it.
But I don't know if it's all right
that she wanted to go and get it.
I don't think she's gonna hurt herself.
She looked me in the eye like she had
centuries of ball-busting left in her.
You driving Tina?
What did I do with
my chauffeur's cap?
I walked down to see how
things were going
'cause I'm two fucking blocks away.
Give me a ride back, I'm exhausted.
This is so much fun.
I explained to you before,
I made a commitment.
No, I'm just saying,
this is so much fun.
I'm so glad we reconciled.
Hi, pleasure, yeah. Just returned
from the clinic, dickstein.
Yeah, it's not my idea
of fun, but here I am.
Daphne, my fiancee.
- Hello.
- Pleasure.
Yeah, it's not something
I'd want to do every day.
Medical treatment, but you know,
it's also something not
to be afraid of if...
Excuse me, excuse me.
There's the assassin!
There's the murdering
cutthroat who treated me, huh?
And the prison torturer
from the abu ghraib prison.
- Any changes?
- Oh, well...
It's achy.
You know, throbs, somewhat.
Little bit, it's fine.
It's good.
Physician.
We should bring his mother
and your mother here
so they could both shep nachas.
Do my cast the first honor, please?
That's funny. It's very good. Right.
I played my saxophone before.
Oh, jeez. You all done?
Did you pack it back up?
Maybe.
So...
So you think
you'll be here a while?
I'm not sure.
Should we make one
for my gram?
Sure.
Hot dogs, hamburgers,
potato chips.
Hot dogs, hamburgers.
Seconds will be available.
Who's hungry?
If my words are yours,
can you hear my father?
Can Bill know my father,
keeping his eye on me?
Can I bone Kai, and Butchie
know my father instead?
My father's shy
doing his business.
Kai helps my father
dump out.
Bill takes a shot.
Shaunie is much improved.
Joe is a doubting thomas.
Joe will save not aleman.
Joe will bring
his buddies home.
This is how Freddy relaxes.
Cup of Joe and
winchell's variety dozen.
Mitch catches a good wave.
Mitch wipes out.
Mitch wipes out Cissy.
Cissy shows Butchie how to do that.
Cissy wipes Butchie out.
Butchie hurts Barry's head.
Mr. Rollins comes in Barry's face.
My father runs
the mega millions.
Boy we got some we got some
interesting footage, John.
Yeah, really got some great ideas
on what we could do with that.
- Really...
- I need your camera, Cass.
It's safe in
the trunk of my car, John.
Time to get back
in the game, Linc Stark.
Fur is big, mud is big,
The stick is big.
The word is big.
Fire is huge.
The wheel is huge.
The line and circle are big.
On the wall, the line
and circle are huge.
On the wall, the man at
the wall makes a man,
from the circle and line.
The man at the wall
makes a word on the wall
from the circle and line.
The word on the wall
hears my father.
The zeros and ones make
the word in Cass's camera.
In the word on the wall that
hears my father in Cass's camera,
the good one Mitch catches
doesn't wipe Cissy out.
In the word
that hears my father,
Cissy shows Butchie
something else.
In my father's word,
Cissy shows Butchie and Shaun.
Tina raises Shaun at lunch.
In Cass's camera,
Butchie lays the cord out for
Barry and Mr. Rollins watches,
and he doesn't come on Barry's face.
In Cass's camera, Butchie
knows Kai has kept the faith.
In my father's word,
the wave lifts them up.
I think you overcame
a milestone in stride.
Next thing, it's four hours
later, you've been napping
from unrecognized stress.
in Cass's camera,
Bill doesn't bump
his head on the stairs.
I cannot do this.
I am skating on very thin ice.
In Cass's camera, as long
as he's being stupid,
Bill gives lois a kiss.
In his word, in Cass's camera,
The internet is big.
9-11 is big, but not every
towelhead is eradicated.
In his word, we are coming
9-11-14!
In my father's word,
Bill sees how Freddy relaxes.
In Cass's camera, Ramon
wants to know who's hungry,
In the courtyard and room 45.
In my father's word
to come in Cass's camera,
Dr. Smith calls ocean properties.
In Cass's camera to come,
my father stares not aleman down,
and Freddy sees Bill
much improved.
You will not note
my father's word,
no remember Cass's camera,
but you will not
forget what we did here.
You're even uglier than
Abraham Lincoln!
Which happens he's got
the same birthday as mine!
February 12th, 1964.
Yeah.
100 years after his murder.
Both of us.
We should make these
cook-outs a fixture.
Wanna go look for
the space commander?
Hit the floor, troopers!
Judas priest!
The fucking sun's gone down.
The sun does not go down, Bill.
Genius on science, too.
My father is a genius on
science. The sun does not go down.
You won't get
an argument from me.
Judas priest is
a genius on science.
Judas priest is my father's son too.
I swear to Christ,
I've been playing my harp.
Bill won't note nor long remember
playing his fucking harp, Joe.
Isn't that
the strangest thing?
My father's birthday is
the same as mine.
Well.
This was time well spent.
www.Team-NCIS.com
www.All-about-Subs.fr