It seems the prime minister
is promising peace in our time
Guys listen to this
There is no one left
The others are all dead
God help me, is happening again
They're here
That's how's ends
Who's here?
Sorry
They found us
Get my back
Let's go
addic7ed.com presents
Primeval S03E06
Completed by aydin1954
Bang!
24 seconds, congratulations
That's 3 seconds longer than last time
How did you get in?
Car park, ventilation system
- I suggest you...
- Check all...
Infrared systems are tamper proof
And secure all ventilation shafts
Exactly.
What are they doing?
Checking security.
Not very well, apparently.
They have no idea we are watching them.
- What is this?
- Please do not touch anything.
- I do not want you to change my settings
- Sorry
You know... wha-what are you doing?
You can come out. I'm seen by the management view
whatever that you are.
It's OK.
I don't think he saw us
We are flatmates,
why-why he cannot see us?
We are not flatmates.
And if I ever find your socks in
the bread maker again...
You are fired!
Keeping them warm
Connor!
- Oh, hello!
- These papers were classified!
Probably going to shred them anyway then
This arengement...
is not working
I really don't want to hurt you
You're all talk
Careful.
Him? What about me?
He's more valuable than you
- How valuable?
- Priceless.
You know I got to go
What you're doing today?
Ah, this and that.
She is going out we're on.
Get closer.
It is. The artifact.
They've cleaned it up.
I knew it.
They had it all the time.
I'm assuming no luck
on the X-ray analysis?
Well it only confirmed
what we alredy knew.
No closer to find
what it actully does
No.
Light.
Light! Connor, you've got it!
You... found it.
You got it. You... are a genius.
I know.
What I've done?
Hm, I'm going to enjoy this.
Get the minister on the phone.
Yes mam'.
So you think the laser may unluck it?
Ah, try diffusing the beam.
Good idea.
Allright.
- Diffused
- Fully?
Yep.
Didn't leave the instruction manual
in the box, won't you?
- Ahm, try another angle.
- Angle, OK.
- See anything?
- Nope.
- How about now?
- No.
- Is not working.
- How about now?
- Connor, is not working.
It's got nothin to do with the light
our call is wrong.
We can't just give up, we have to keep trying
there got to be something within...
- Connor, did you see that?
- That was like... incredible
Was that some kind of a map?
The points where the lines are crossing,
looked exactly like...
Cutter's research model! He knew...
Cutter knew.
This is some kind of...
I don't know a key to...
Predicting anomalies.
Whatever we did,
We have to do it again.
OK.
What did you do?
Not 100% sure.
Well, well.
The artefact predicts anomalies.
What you wanna do?
Talk with the minister, I'll phone him on the way.
We are going in.
I am satisfied there was no serious breach of security
Excellent.
A new definition of "serious".
You left him upsail in the ventilation shaft
Yes sir.
That surveliance camera is a waste of time by the way
What cam?
The one on the shaft,
covering the corridor.
There is no camera there.
Am I missing something?
Vents.
- Anything?
- Clear. You?
Smile boys, we are on TV.
How is going?
Ehm, we just opened the artifact.
Connor!
Yo!
- They have seen it.
- They have seen what?
Johnson, she knows we got the
artifact. We got 5 minutes.
- Get my bag.
- Security lockdown.
Secure the main gate.
- Go!
- Closing the main gate.
Wait, stop!
She is already here.
All exits are covered.
- Find the crim and the artifact!
- Let's go! Move, move.
- Move, move.
I know one exit
she hasn't got covered.
Lester is lookin for a safe place.
Whatever you do,
don't break cover.
We'll find you when is clear.
Stop there, drop your weapons!
No sir, you drop yours.
We really don't want to kill you...
sir.
So, mate, with fuel injection,
it's rather like osmosis -
a solvent passes through
a semi-permeable membrane
to form an equilibrium. Yes?
Put your weapon down, Becker,
and surrender the artefact.
With respect, I don't take orders
from you.
You do now.
Danny, I hope you know
what you're doing.
The Minister isn't in?
Did you tell him it was me?
I'm afraid he won't be taking
your call, James.
You've been a bad boy!
They're still on our tail, Danny.
Danny, what are we going to do?
Hold on tight.
This could get a bit lively.
Danny?
Stay in line. Keep your hands
where we can see them.
Keep it moving!
Sorry, ma'am... They got away.
Well, don't just stand there.
Find them.
Tell me where they've gone.
No idea.
You know what freelance staff are
like - always popping in and out.
You can't protect them for long.
The truth is, you can't do much of
anything any more.
Oh, and you're in my chair!
You know, this isn't over, Christine.
When people say that, James,...
it usually is.
Ladies and gentlemen, James Lester
has been relieved of his duties.
Please continue working normally and
this transition will run smoothly.
The ARC.
At least we know where we're going.
Get rid of your mobiles.
I've just signed
a new 18-month contract.
They can trace it.
You do realise this isn't personal,
Captain?
It's purely a question of
national security.
Of course, ma'am.
I've looked at your file, Becker.
You're a good soldier.
I am your commanding officer now.
I assume
there is no conflict of loyalties?
None at all.
Find me the artefact...and you're
looking at a very rapid promotion.
I'll do my best.
I'll raise you 300.
Pass.
Don't want to play with
the big boys? I'm out as well.
Cool lizard.
What? Oh yeah, very rare.
Just like this hand. I'm all in.
I call.
Something tells me this safe house
hasn't been used for years.
Thanks a lot, Lester.
This place looks terrific (!)
It was never going to be a four-star
hotel, was it?
Is it locked?
Yeah.
Leave this to me.
The only part of being a copper
I enjoyed.
Come on.
Wow!
Urgh...
Chateau Lafite. Not a bad vintage.
Why, is that worth much?
About £1,000.
There's no power.
It'll be like Christmas
at my gran's. (LAUGHS)
Please, God,
nobody mention charades!
I'm going to get some wood
for the fire.
Argh!
That hurt.
Huh! Oh, no!
That's just wrong!
This trip wire will act as
an early-warning system.
How long do you reckon
we should wait here?
As long as it takes.
We haven't got any food.
Oh, er...found them in the car.
They're going to find us,
aren't they?
It's just a matter of time.
But we're not going to give up
without a fight, are we, eh?
No.
Come on.
It's like they thought they were
coming back at any minute.
Oh...
Right, let's see if you still work.
Hey.
Probably past its sell-by date.
Brilliant. Corned beef. I love it.
Corned beef...
Abby!
Aren't they beautiful!
Wow!
Whoa!
Hello, hello, this is Connor Temple.
Is anybody receiving me? Over.
Hello?
Hm...
Get it off me!
What are you doing?
Argh! Huh!
Urgh!
What? I just opened the door
and it fell out on me.
He must have got trapped inside.
It looks like
some sort of viewing room.
It's a diary.
It's written in some sort of code.
Can you crack it?
Of course I can.
What happened here?
Where did they all go?
You're cleaned out, Jackie!
Come on!
One of you can afford to sub me.
Sorry, mate.
I'll bet the lizard against
whatever you've got.
It's worth a fortune. Abby told me.
All right. The lizard.
# When the little bluebird
who has never said a word
# Starts to sing "Spring! Spring!"
# And the little bluebell
At the bottom of the dell
# Starts to ring "Ding! Ding!"...
Abby?
# Sings a tune to the moon above
# It is nature, that's all,
simply telling us to fall in love
# In old Amsterdam...
# Argentines, without...
Guys, listen to this.
"There's no-one left.
The others are all dead.
God help me, it's happening again.
They're here."
And that's where it ends.
Who's here?
It's an anomaly!
Does Quinn have access to
a detector?
No. There's no way they can know
about the anomaly.
Then my men can cover it.
You stay here.
It was written by
a Professor John Morton.
He was a military scientist
who came here with his team to do
meteorological tests,
but then something happened.
They found something in the woods,
but Morton doesn't say what.
That sounds like some kind of
bird's distress call.
But what type of bird
would make that sound?
I don't know.
It's the trip wire.
Have they found us?
Get them out the back!
Come on, let's go.
I'll catch you up.
Abby. Go!
Hide in the bunker.
An anomaly.
Let's get to the car.
Danny! Run!
That Lafite was worth
£1,000 a a bottle!
I think it was corked anyway.
Forget that. Get to the car!
OK, OK.
Get in the car!
Get in the car, it's a creature!
Come on!
Go go go go!
Where's it gone?
Look out!
Are you OK?
Yeah.
I can't see him.
Connor, drive faster!
Put your foot down!
Brace yourselves!
Oh, my god,
I think I've killed Danny!
Danny!
Whoo!
Yes! Whoo hoo!
Well done, mate!
Are you all right?
I'm OK, I'm OK, I'm OK.
Good girl.
Connor...
Connor.
Are you all right, Connor?
Put your back against there.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Connor, speak to me.
DISTANT WAIL
It's coming back... Abby. Abby!
What?
Listen to me. Listen.
We can never outrun it. OK?
You two get back to the lodge.
It's the only place we might be safe.
I'll look after him, I promise.
All right?
Now go! Go go!
Connor!
Come on!
Over there. Check it out.
I'll secure the area.
Ow!
Close the door quietly.
(Where are you?)
I'm up here.
What are you doing up there?
What do you think I'm doing up here?
I don't know. Kind of why I asked.
Where's the bird?
Close-ish. So keep your voice down.
Sorry.
What are we going to do?
We're going to trap it.
Brilliant.
How are we going to do that?
Cool.
So what do you want ME to do?
Just stay down there and look tasty.
You what?
You're the bait.
I know it's this way.
Urgh!
Great for dancing.
Not so good for cross-country.
Are you sure this is going to work?
How can it fail?
Only in about 100 different ways.
Come on. Where are you?
Maybe, maybe we scared it away.
Maybe...maybe it's just frightened.
Not frightened enough.
Get back in the car.
Get back in the car!
Come on, come on!
Danny!
Connor! Get out of there!
OK, I'm getting out!
There's more of them.
Quick, hide!
I think they've gone.
Oh, my god!
ROARS
Run!
What?
Look.
Watch where you put your feet.
Good advice... Thanks.
Watch out! Look out!
Danny!
Whoa! Whoa! Stop!
It's a minefield.
How was your hopscotch at school?
Pretty good.
Come on! Come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Watch out!
Come on!
Quick, girls, please, quickly!
Give me your hand!
Let's go!
Go to the lodge!
Stay where you are,
you're under arrest!
What was the explosion?
A creature.
Get us out of here!
Mate, there is more of them.
All in good time.
Trust me, we need to hurry.
Shut up!
What are you looking at?
Connor!
Abby, come on!
Danny.
All right.
What happened?
Where's the artefact?
Let me handle this.
I know how Quinn's mind works.
Fine. Do it.
Shouldn't we report this
to the Minister?
Lester kept him informed
on operational decisions.
Let ME worry about him. He'll find
out what I choose to tell him.
With respect, ma'am, if he discovers
he's not being fully informed...
The Minister is an imbecile.
He can barely blow his own nose.
Do you think I'm going to let
a Whitehall glove puppet
with the IQ of a root vegetable
tell me how to do my job?
Now find Quinn for me.
You never know, maybe the explosions
just scared them all off.
More likely they'll be gathering
somewhere
like hyenas preparing to steal
a kill.
Looks like tea break's over.
Abby, are you all right?
Yeah.
Go. Go!!
Block this up!
Ready?
Yeah.
Again!
Go!
Danny!
Abby!
Sarah!
Connor!
I can't hold this!
Connor, talk to me.
I don't know where they've gone!
Go! Go go!
Use the wardrobe! Block it up!
I've got to go back in that room.
You're kidding!
No.
The record! It's our only chance!
What are you doing?
I've got an idea.
I've got to get to the bunker.
Connor!
Connor! Do something!
I can't hold them off!
Hey! Over here!
Over here!
I'm so much more tastier than him!
Connor!
Come over here, it's dinnertime!
Huh?
Connor!
Argh! Argh!
Aargh! Urgh!
Connor!
Aargh!
Let's attract your attention, boys.
Yes!
Sarah!
Connor!
All right?
Quickly! Quickly!
Where's Abby?
She's on the roof. What?
Sarah!
I'm slipping!
Come on, boys!
Time to go home.
Danny.
Anyone got a belt?
These trousers are a nightmare.
Oh! I wouldn't have bothered.
Good idea to use that record
to attract the birds.
I'm just chuffed
you care so much, Connor.
What?
You're all under arrest.
Oh, you've got to be joking!
My orders are to take you
back to the ARC.
I'm authorised to use deadly force
if I have to.
You're Johnson's man now?
I'm just following orders.
Like a good little soldier boy.
Where's the artefact?
Excellent work, Captain. I can see
you're a man with real potential.
Very kind, madam.
I think I'm going to be sick!
I'd have a little more respect
if I were you, Quinn.
You're looking at a serious charge
of stealing government property.
Hello, Christine.
You're not authorised to enter
this facility, James.
I think you're sitting in my chair.
Captain, would you escort this
troublesome man from the building?
I'm afraid I can't do that, ma'am.
What?
'The Minister is an imbecile.
He can barely blow his own nose.
Do you really think I'm going to let
a Whitehall glove puppet
with the IQ of a root vegetable
tell me how to do my job?'
Yes, Captain Becker recorded it
and I sent a copy to Whitehall.
Oh, that reminds me,
the Minister wants to see you.
Actually, he did seem a little upset.
Christine, I did tell you
it wasn't over.
No, James...
I assure you it's not.
You are my hero.
And mine.
But don't expect any kisses from me.
Haven't you all got work to do?
Sorry, mate, I was out of order.
No problem. Just don't call me
"soldier boy" again. Sorry!
You missed us, didn't you?
Don't be ridiculous.
# Somewhere over the rainbow
# Way up high
# In the dreams
that you dream of
# Once in a lullaby
# Oh
# Somewhere over the rainbow
# Bluebirds fly... #
All right?
Not bad.
What happened to you? Oh, just
another boring day at the office.
Have you been having a party?
Oh, just a few friends.
I'll clean up in a bit.
Yeah, you will.
Where's Rex?
Up in my room.
OK. Cool.
We've had a dragon,
a knight in shining armour...
A damsel in distress would be nice.
Explain to me why Rex is up
for auction on the internet?
Gambling and poker.
Get him back!
We have to find him.
He's lost in an unknown world.
The mark of the beast.
Sling your 'ook!
Take it outside!
You are demons.
And I am in hell.
completed by aydin1954 for addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net