Previously in Primeval...
Johnson's military. We can't storm
in without clearance...
Yes, sir. I'm very well
aware of that.
... based on a hunch that she's got
an active anomaly
and some mysterious woman from the
future tucked away somewhere.
Who are you? Who do you work for?
I'll show you.
But first I have to go to the
Anomaly Research Centre.
What do you know about the ARC?
If you're going to do something,
now would be a good time.
- What's it say?
- Not much.
333 here... here...
What's going on?
Now give me the artefact
or she dies.
No!
- What are we going to do?
- Follow Helen. Wherever she goes.
To the end of time if necessary.
La Prime Team Présente :
Transcript par Chocolate
Resync VO : Grishnak & Darkevil
Merci d'avoir suivi cette
3e saison avec nos subs ;)
Primeval Season 3 FINAL
Right.
So... what have we got?
Stun grenades.
Future predators have
hyper-sensitive hearing, yeah?
These should stop them dead
in their tracks.
Got any earplugs in there?
Use your fingers.
And if you don't want your eardrums
to burst,
I suggest you keep your mouth open.
That won't be difficult for Connor.
Don't be too close
when he throws them.
All right. Let's do this.
No. Not now.
It's Johnson's HQ.
Do you think it's Helen?
It could be.
We go back there and we're wrong,
then, er...
You need to make the call.
Right. Becker...
you check it out. Sarah, you go
with him.
Abby, Connor, you're with me.
Wherever she is, we'll stop her.
Danny, I want to go with you.
Look, I need you to do this for me.
- Yeah, but what if you don't -
- Look, no-one's saying goodbye here.
We're all coming back.
Now, once we're through...
you close the anomaly. It's far too
dangerous to leave it open.
Unlock it in two hours.
Danny. Here.
And take care.
Unlock it.
- Connor.
- Yo.
You might need this.
Thanks.
Let's get going.
What about Johnson's people?
The operation's been closed down.
The place should be empty. Come on.
Come on!
Doesn't get any prettier, does it?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
When I saw Helen,
she was down there.
By the church.
Let's go.
This way.
Is it Helen?
So... where is Helen?
Where are all the predators?
Listen!
Duck!
No-one on the gate then.
Let's hope it's all that easy.
I wouldn't bet on it.
Through here.
This must be Johnson's anomaly.
So, where...
where did you see Helen?
She came from over there.
Run!
Throw these over the side!
It stinks.
Why would Helen come here?
If it was me, I'd just find some
nice little Jurassic beach somewhere.
However crazy she was, everything she
does makes a kind of sense.
Really?
Get back!
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Did you get it?
Apparently not.
I can't hold it!
We've got to get something
to keep the door closed.
Becker is really not going
to be happy with you.
- Why?
- That was his favourite gun.
We got to get him a girlfriend.
Oh, my God.
We're in the ARC.
Maybe it's some kind of...
future version of it.
Helen said it started in here.
This must be what she meant.
She's here! I know it.
Come on.
Come on!
Here! Quick! Quick!
There's no way out.
Becker, there's no way out!
I'll call the back-up team.
And tell them exactly where we are.
I think it's a bit
too late for that now.
Oh my God, they're coming through!
Right. We need to get both of them
on the grille at the same time.
You what?
Come on. We've only got
one shot at this.
Come on, Sarah, you can do this.
Come on!
Come on.
Now!
Do you think that's the last one
of those things?
Let's go find out.
The anomaly's closed.
Let's get out of here.
That's what Helen used...
to control the anomalies.
It looks like it's been dead
a long time.
How do you think it works?
I wish I knew.
Did you just...?
Yeah.
Don't!
It works better on you than it does
on some predators.
Come out of the dark, Connor.
That's it.
Good boy.
You too, Abby.
So you found me.
I must say I'm surprised.
Surprised you had the brains
to figure it out.
Whatever you're up to, it ends now.
Who's going to stop me?
You and Barbie?
Just watch us.
Nick... knew this was important.
But he didn't know why.
Well, he would have done.
If you hadn't have murdered him.
I have spent...
every day since his death...
working it out.
Preparing...
for this...
moment.
I know...
he would have understood.
You keep telling yourself that,
Helen.
One day you might believe it.
It doesn't matter now.
Soon...
none of this will ever have
happened.
What are you going to do?
Oh, you're going to like this,
Connor.
I, Helen Cutter, am going
to save the world.
Since when did you care so much
about the human race?
Oh, it's not humanity
I'm going to save.
You know, Helen. You're in dire need
of some serious therapy.
It's a time map.
Of every anomaly there's even been.
Or ever will be.
Cutter was right.
There is a pattern.
With this, we'll never have to wait for
anomalies to open again. We'll just...
know where they are.
Such a sweet, clever boy.
What a shame you ever met Cutter.
Gotcha.
You know...
if I were you,
I'd make the most of whatever
time you have left.
Believe me...
it won't be long.
Please.
No.
No!
- It's time.
- Open it.
Where are they?
Come on, Quinn. Hurry up!
She was plotting some kind of route.
We've got to find out
where she was going.
How we can follow her.
But how? This thing's
completely dead.
I know a way.
If we can get it working, maybe
I can reconstruct the route
from the computer's memory.
Power.
- We're going to need power.
- Yeah.
Batteries.
In the torches.
Brilliant.
We'll need something to bind them
together.
Medical kit.
How many have we got?
Wires...
Wires.
Don't we need the artefact
to make it work?
No, no, cos...
hopefully the data will
be still on the hard drive, so...
we might not need it.
Site 333.
She named the file Site 333.
333. What is that? A location,
a code, what?
Oh, my God.
What?
The Rift Valley. In Africa.
Four million years ago.
It's the, um... the cradle of
civilisation.
Site 333 is where they found
the remains of the so-called
first family of hominids.
A group of 13 early humans
who all died at the same time.
- No-one ever knew how.
- So Helen's
gone to visit the ape men?
Wha...?
No.
She's gone to kill the first human.
To stop our evolution in its tracks.
She's going to wipe us all out.
- I'm not getting it.
- All right, I'm on it.
Try lower.
Come on.
Yeah, that's good. That's got it.
Here we go.
This is not as easy as it looks,
you know.
Just get on with it.
This will only give us
a small window of time.
All right.
You ready?
Not really.
That's it!
I've got to remember everything...
that she did.
Come on!
So...
333.
This is Helen's route. It looks like
she was going through two anomalies.
We have to find a way to open them.
Let's do it.
Shut the connector.
Right.
Just be patient, Connor.
You'll get it.
Concentrate.
Guys!
Predators.
Just hurry up, all right?
Ohhh... I'm not very good
with pressure.
OK, come on.
She...
put in a series of numbers.
That could be anything. I mean...
It's like some kind of lettering.
No. It's a... it's a sequence
of numbers.
- OK, some kind of code?
- Yeah, but to what?
653... 59.
I've got it.
Please let this work.
6...
5...
3,5,9.
Yes!
Sorry.
Come on.
Nearly there. Come on. Come on.
This is taking too long. We're going
to run out of power.
Hurry up, Connor.
I can only go as fast as it's
downloading.
You've got to get it open, Connor.
Tell me something I don't know.
OK, 75 percent.
It's getting there.
Come on.
80 percent.
They're in here.
95 percent.
100 percent. That's it!
I've got it.
This is it... Go.
- Close it!
I didn't doubt you for a second.
Right.
So...
Where are we now?
More importantly...
where's Helen?
Boots.
She went this way.
Yeah.
Ancient pines... that could mean
this is...
Jurassic or...
maybe...
Maybe Cretaceous.
So, er...
what sort of creatures
are we talking about?
Oh... well...
- A lot.
- Really?
Too many to list.
A lot of theropod dinosaurs,
mostly carnivores, I mean.
Spinosaurus, halasaurus,
avertasaurus, napasaurus.
Oh, good.
- Obviously T-Rex.
- Yeah.
- Raptors.
- Yeah, I got the point.
No, literally...
raptors.
They don't look too bad.
Run!
Abby, this way!
Quickly!
Come on! This way!
Get off! Get off!
Yeah, I'm OK, I'm good.
- Get off!
- That was close.
Well, they're juvenile raptors, so
at least we know we're in
the Cretaceous.
We've got to find the next anomaly.
Will they know how to climb?
No.
No!
What?
- The thing's just died I think.
- What?
Yeah.
We don't know the route.
We can't open the anomalies.
We can't get home.
There might not be a home
to get back to.
Bingo.
There.
See her?
Yeah.
If she gets through another anomaly,
though, we've lost her.
Any ideas?
We could, ah... appeal to their
better nature.
I don't know if they've got one.
Right. Playtime's over.
Stun grenade.
- Come on!
- Oh, I was about to think of that.
- Where is it?
- In the bag.
Got it.
Here you are, Danny.
Cover your ears.
- And open your mouth.
- Two...
- One...
- Hang on. He said not to be too -
Watch your foot.
Connor! Connor, are you OK?
He's alive.
Go.
I can't leave here. I won't.
You have to stop her!
Let's get him somewhere safe.
Finish it!
Wake up, Connor!
Can you hear me?
Just say something!
Oh, come on, don't give up
on me now.
Please!
Please.
Just...
Well, then.
Come on then.
This way.
Why don't you pick on someone
your own... species?
I'm going to save you this time.
That's really... sweet of you, Abby,
but I think...
I've got it covered.
- How?
- I don't know.
But I'm sure I'll think of
something.
You're kind of in no state to...
do anything right now.
Abby, can you just...?
What?
Can we argue about this later?
Yeah?
That was a stupid idea.
I've just aggravated him.
Nice hit.
Thank you.
Let's go, though, before...
the others wake up.
Oh yeah...
- Cool.
- Come on.
- Abby.
- What?
- A little bit of help?
- Sorry.
I think I broke my ankle.
Oh, really?
If not, it's a bad sprain.
Are you OK?
We just need to find somewhere
safe then...
Then we can find Danny
in the morning.
You're too late, Danny!
It's already begun.
But thanks.
You know, if you hadn't taken me
to the ARC,
I never would have got this far.
You killed them!
Humanity is a stain upon the face
of the planet.
And when we're gone,
other species will be able
to develop in peace.
There'll be no war, no pollution.
No predators.
So...
if you wiped out humanity,
then how come I'm still here?
You're really not very bright,
are you, Danny?
You know, I haven't finished yet.
There's more to kill.
But you'd be surprised how few
hominids started the human race.
It won't take long.
Can you kill yourself as well?
I don't care.
Whatever you do, humanity
will find a way to evolve.
You can't fight nature.
You sound just like Nick.
And you know what?
You're both wrong.
Bye, Danny.
Good boy.
I think we'll be safe here, Connor.
And then...
like I said, we can... find Danny
in the morning.
What hurts?
Pretty much everything.
Close your eyes.
Imagine a happy place.
You're on a beautiful beach.
And the sun is shining.
Are you there too?
Yeah.
If you like.
Are you wearing a bikini?
Yes.
If you like.
The water's really warm.
Lovely.
Yeah.
Can I move back into the flat,
please?
Yeah.
Sweet dreams.
See you in the morning.
Hopefully.
What are we going to do?
They'll be back.
I've got an idea.
Right.
Which way home?
Hold on! No!
Nooo!
No!
La Prime Team vous remercie
de votre fidélité
On l'espère, rendez-vous
l'année prochaine.
Un grand merci à Anarwen,
sans qui rien n'aurait été possible.
Merci aux transcripts de Chocolate
et aux resync VO de FLOLO (seriessub)
Prime Team pour U-Sub.NET
et Seriessub.NET