La Prime Team vous présente :
Transcript : Chocolate
Presync VO : Darkevil
-|- U-sub.net -|-
-|- SeriesSub.com -|-
Saison 3 Épisode 9
- Where are you?
- Are you checking up on me?
- You're late.
- Sorry, sir.
Stuck in traffic.
Oh, really.
So... What can I do you for?
I'm meeting the minister
this afternoon.
He might be too late.
Johnson's military. She can't storm in
without clearance.
Yes, sir. I'm well aware of that.
Based on a hunch
that she's got an active anomaly
and some mysterious woman from
the future tucked away somewhere.
OK, sir. You're the boss.
You're in a very understanding mood
today, Quinn.
The lights have changed.
I've got to run!
Sorry, sir. You're breaking up.
Don't do anything I'll regret.
Hang on!
DON'T ANSWER THE : FRONT DOOR.
- Come in.
- OK.
Follow me.
You'd better come through.
DON'T ANSWER THE PHONE.
DON'T ASK ME WHY!
I expect you're wondering
why I'm here.
Rex was lonely.
Guys!
That's cute.
I wanted to...
I just don't want things
to be weird between us.
Absolutely. Me neither.
Me neither. Don't want any...
Any sort of weirdness with...
No weird areas here!
I'm being weird, aren't I?
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
I don't... I don't suppose
now Jack's moved out that...
You know.
They can move back in.
Wicked. That's great news.
Because I think
their lives are in danger.
Living with Lester.
Literally. I think he -
It's fine.
We've missed them anyway.
Haven't we, Rex?
See?
Nice place.
You must love it here.
Oh... Yeah!
It's not home though, is it?
Anomaly alert! Where are you?
(pub LG inside ^^)
For the last time, say your name.
My officers tell me when they found
you, you tried to run. Why?
Who are you?
Who are you working for?
How did you come to be there?
Let me explain something to you.
You're not leaving
until I get some answers.
So unless you really like it here,
I suggest you start talking.
Tell me.
Everyone's dead. What difference
does it make who I am?
You mean in the future?
You know what happened?
The predators.
They destroyed everything.
And where did the predators
come from?
I don't know. I wish I did.
Come on! He did it to me
on my stag weekend.
So this is our chance
to get him back.
Joe, come on!
You promised me no stunts, right?
Just a boys weekend.
Yeah, sure. No stunts.
Oh, no. Oh, come on, guys!
Go! Go!
This isn't funny.
Give them back!
Guys!
Wait! Get me... Yeah, very funny.
Are you...
Gonna help me, or what?!
Guys, come back!
You can't leave me here!
Guys!
Is that the best you can do?
Very funny.
Oh, my god.
Guys!
Help!
It's OK.
Tell me what this is.
I found it in the ruins,
but I have no idea what it is.
- I think it's broken.
- You're lying.
- What about anomalies? Go on!
- Anomalies?
Anomalies are...
rips in time.
Some you can see.
Others are invisible
to the naked eye.
They're everywhere.
You just have to know
how to find them.
And you know how to do that?
- Yes.
- How?
I'll show you.
But first, I have to go
to the Anomaly Research Centre.
What do you know about the ARC?
Take me there and I'll show you.
- You don't give the orders.
- Take me to the ARC, then I'll help.
What's all this?
The anomaly's somewhere over there.
Strange.
My detector's gone all funny.
- So has mine.
- See?
Really weird.
Where's Danny?
I'm sure he's on his way.
Sausage, anyone?
Maybe later?
Ma'am.
Catch!
Intruder!
Get her back to her room.
Come on, let's go.
There's so many.
Better get this place evacuated.
They're incredible.
- What are they?
- Embolotherium.
They're um...
They're prehistoric rhinos.
Peaceful grazers.
Peaceful. Are you sure about that?
As sure as anybody can be on
the basis of a fossilised tooth.
Oh, come on, little man!
I'm trying to help you. Just relax.
Over here!
Nice move.
- I have to get out of here.
- I'm aware of that. Why the ARC?
I have to warn them.
Go, go, go!
Come on.
- What's going on?
- Danny Quinn.
He's in the building.
Lock down the building. Find them.
Dammit!
We're going to take a quick detour.
There isn't time.
I've got to get to...
Help!
- There's someone in there.
- Help me, please!
- Hello!
- Come on.
Through that lot?
- Yeah.
- I'm in the tent!
I'm guessing that's the bull.
Yeah.
Help!
The bull's disrupting the herd.
We can't risk going in
with him like this.
Someone needs to distract him.
Absolutely.
- Me?
- Somebody help me!
- I'm not...
- Please.
Thanks.
Look at me!
Come on!
Ignore the girls!
OK, I've got his attention.
- He likes me.
- Is there anyone there?!
- They've got me surrounded!
- Go!
Go!
- Come on!
- We'll be fine.
We should split up
and try and sneak through them.
Sarah, are you OK?
I'm all right!
Oh, god!
- Are you OK?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Hide.
Stop!
Just stay there, don't panic!
If we make no sudden...
Remember me?
Now you're looking at me.
They're following the bull.
- What?
- Sounds like a baby.
- Hey.
- What?
None of my business.
It's my stag weekend.
Right.
What is it? And what are
those things out there?
Let me get you out,
then we can chat.
Wait a minute.
You're not the stripper, are you?
Do you want to get out of here
alive?
Or not?
Sorry.
That's the baby, right?
I guess so, yeah.
What have you done to yourself?
Listen, don't worry.
We're going to get you out of here.
I promise.
Do I look like a stripper?
- Well...
- Don't answer that.
Abby, it's the mother coming back!
She's heading for the tent!
Get out of there!
Come on, Abby!
You're going to have to help me
get this calf out of here, OK?
Sorry.
She's going round the other side!
You've got to calm the cow down!
She's going to kill us
and the calf at this rate!
Easy.
OK, calm down.
One, two, three!
Calm down. Slowly.
Slowly.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Sweet.
Not him.
Them.
What have you been doing in there?
Never mind.
No.
Come on!
Here you go, mate.
You'll be fine now.
Cheers.
So... thanks...
for saving me from those...
The rhinos. Rare species.
By the way, is...
Is this yours?
Yeah.
- Thanks.
- It's all right.
- What?
- Nothing.
In your own time.
Anyone got any immediate ideas
on how we get a herd of prehistoric
rhinos back through the anomaly?
Good question.
Down there.
Really gently. That's great.
- What are we doing here?
- I don't know.
Right. Stay here.
- We're wasting time!
- This is important. Stay there.
- Quinn, who is she?
- Long story.
Where's Connor?
It's worked!
They're going through.
- Well done.
- Good job.
Thanks!
The anomaly is closing! We need
to get them back through faster!
You're going to hit it!
That's the general idea.
Come on, ladies!
You've got to get the bull
through the anomaly - now!
I'm driving as fast as I can!
Oh, no.
- Keep the bull away!
- What?
The anomaly has closed.
Too late!
They're heading for the campsite.
We've got to get those people away.
Let's go!
- All right, mate?
- Yeah, it's good.
We've got to get them
to change direction.
Are you insane?!
It depends who you ask. Hold tight.
I think it's thunder.
- They're too big!
- Have you got a better idea?
You told Johnson
you didn't know what that was.
- Get me to the campsite.
- What is that?
I'll explain later.
Just take me there now!
- Did you lot hear that?
- Yeah.
You've got to get out of here!
Come on, everyone! Get out!
Go! Go! Go!
Stay calm.
On your feet! Go!
Get out!
Move!
Everyone, move!
You haven't got time. Come on!
Everybody out!
No!
Becker, stop!
If you're going to do something,
now would be a good time!
How did you do that?
- The technology is simple enough.
- Really?
Try me.
Another time.
I don't believe that.
Now will you help me? Please.
I have to get a message
to a man called James Lester.
I'm taking her to the ARC.
We'll meet you there.
I don't understand.
Just get in the car.
Look, this is her book.
- See what you make of it.
- Sure.
Abby, you come with me.
I'm bringing someone in to meet you.
Who?
Out with it, Quinn.
You know I hate...
surprises.
Hello, James.
I'd like to say it was always a pleasure,
but that would be a bare-faced lie.
What's this?
A warrant for the arrest
of Danny Quinn.
What is it
that he's supposed to have done?
We'll start with breaking and
entering and kidnapping.
You know he broke into my HQ
this morning.
Oh, you didn't. You really need
to get a grip, James.
Make sure you read
all the way through.
I wouldn't want you to miss the part
which requires
the immediate
surrender of the artefact to me.
So...
Where is she?
Where is who?
Hey. Well?
Well what?
- Can you crack it?
- It's not a code.
Just loads of charts
and diary entries.
What does it say?
Not much. Look.
333 here,
here,
here.
There's times, places...
I'm going to have to read all of it.
See if it makes any sense.
- The boss would like to see you.
- Now?
- Now.
- You stay here.
Watch her.
Fascinating.
What is?
All this.
Must be strange for you.
Very.
Don't touch it.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I thought...
Nothing.
My eyes playing tricks on me.
Been a long day.
Believe me,
it's only just beginning.
Where is she?
- Who?
- I suggest you co-operate, Quinn.
Or I'll personally see to it that
you spend a very long time in jail.
You're really going to have to work
on your small talk.
Where is she?
I don't know. Your guess
is as good as mine.
Even if I have to go to the ends
of the Earth, I'll find her.
I assume we're talking about
a certain mystery woman.
Quinn knows exactly
who I'm talking about.
She's downstairs, isn't she?
- Yeah.
- Nice work. Subtle.
I thought I told you
to stay away from her.
I was using my initiative.
And it's all turned out
so well, hasn't it?
Mate, turn this around. Cheers.
Guys!
Have a look at this.
Claudia Brown.
Of all the names that could have
been here, why that one?
Coincidence?
I don't believe in coincidence.
- Who's Claudia Brown?
- Hang on.
There's only two people in the world
apart us who knew about Claudia Brown.
- One was Cutter and the other...
- Come on!
I know this might sound weird,
but have we met?
Wouldn't you remember me?
Suppose so.
Of course, people change.
- What are you doing?
- I wouldn't do that if I were you.
My, you have been busy.
What's going on?
Thanks for bringing me here, Danny.
I don't know how I would have
done it without you.
You know nothing.
Now give me the artefact
or she dies.
Helen?
It's close enough!
Back off!
There's no way out, Helen.
I killed Nick.
You know I'm not bluffing.
And you know I have
absolutely no intention
of letting you walk out of here.
Playing games with her life, James.
Go ahead. Shoot her.
- Perfectly fine with me.
- That is not funny.
Depends where you're standing.
Lower your weapons.
Give her the artefact.
- No.
- Do it.
Can't let her kill Christine.
Contravenes health and safety.
In any case, she won't get far.
Just... tell me how.
How you could...
kill your own husband.
I had no choice.
I loved him, Connor.
But he was part of all this.
Part of everything that goes wrong.
This is the beginning of the chaos.
It all starts here.
What are you talking about?
I thought that killing Nick
would be enough, but it wasn't.
So now I have to finish it
once and for all.
You follow, she's dead!
You really think
I'm frightened of you?
I really think I'm aware of that.
Take the artefact and leave.
I'll make sure no-one follows you.
Is that the best you can do?
So where exactly
are you planning on taking me?
You've not worked it out yet?
I'm surprised. I thought you were
supposed to be intelligent.
What are we doing here?
I have snipers all over this building.
They'll shoot you on sight.
- I don't think so.
- We're on the same side.
We have the same goals.
We can share all of this.
We have the artefact, control of the
anomalies. Think of the power.
If you think this is about power,
you're wrong.
- Then what is it about?
- It's all about you.
You started this.
One ambitious little civil servant
who ends the world.
What are you talking about?
I've seen the future.
And it's all your fault.
Never mind.
None of it
is going to happen anyway.
None of it.
- Out of the way!
- Do as she says!
What are you going to do?
You've got what you want.
Didn't I tell you?
You're coming too.
No. Not through there.
What are you frightened of,
Christine?
After all, it's a world you made.
It's too late.
She's gone.
What about Johnson?
- Help me!
- I've got you. You're safe.
Hold on!
We've got to stop Helen
before anyone else gets killed.
- We don't know where she's gone.
- I think we do.
The same place we lost your brother.
The future.
The anomaly at the race track.
- That leads to the same place.
- That's where we're going.
- What are we going to do?
- Follow Helen wherever she goes.
To the end of time if necessary.
*** STOP NOW!
SPOILERS ON FINAL SEASON EPISODE ***
All right, let's do this.
You should make the most
of the time you have left.
Believe me, it won't be long.
-|- U-sub.net -|-
-|- SeriesSub.com -|-
See U next week for
PRIMEVAL SEASON 3 FINALE!