Go!
Not bad.
You, come with me.
Now jump.
Listen to my voice.
I said...jump.
Death means nothing to you, does it?
You're lucky.
I've always liked modern art.
So uncompromising.
It's a very complex model
of the exact locations -
Of anomaly appearances
throughout recorded history. I know.
Don't touch it.
Ah. Any news of Helen Cutter?
I've started a review of security.
You're sure the intruder
was her doing?
Can anybody else create
an exact replica of a dead man?
Keep everyone on high alert.
If Helen's back,
we should all be very worried.
Mick, I am running out of patience.
I'm this close, Katherine.
I just need something
that nobody could fake.
I can't run a worldwide media story
based on pure speculation.
You do it all the time.
The mammoth on the M25
didn't come to much.
We can say what we like about
footballers and politicians.
But dinosaurs are different.
No-one believes they exist in the
21st century. I don't believe it.
Let me convince you.
One week.
If you've no hard evidence,
clear your desk.
Right.
Miss Lewis...
I just need five minutes.
How did you find out where I live?
Tell me about the ARC and I'll go.
What are you talking about?
The creatures.
Haven't you got a drunken pop star
to harass?
I'm giving you a chance to comment
before I write the story.
Go into print and you'll be
laughed out of town.
Not if I er...have the proof.
But you don't. And you never will.
This is the biggest cover-up
since Roswell.
I'm going to tear the lid off it.
Come near me again
and I'll have you arrested.
So, this contraption is going to seal
the anomalies, is it?
in theory.
Yeah.
You want a million pounds for
research and development.
I want something more
than theoretical.
You'll get it. In simple terms,
this machine will reverse
the polarity of the anomalies,
so nothing gets in
and nothing gets out.
James...
Are you sure about this?
Pretty sure.
OK. It's in the city.
It's a hospital.
The new anomaly. Perfect.
Get rid of him.
We've got important things to do.
Becker, take your men.
Look for any creature activity.
Come on.
Power cut.
The back-up generator
should kick in now.
I'm having a baby.
When?
Now.
It's come right through the floor.
So...so, if you walked through,
would you keep on falling?
I don't know.
But the anomaly itself wouldn't be
enough to cause a power outage,
so something's come through it.
Abby.
Teeth marks.
Hyperactive mice?
Your Gran embroidered this blanket
for you.
You'll like her. She's...
she's a smart woman,
but she's wrong about your daddy.
He's a good guy, he just...
just needs a little bit of time,
that's all.
It went through a hole in the wall
there.
What did?
I don't know.
A ratty, chipmunk,
beaver kind of thing.
Well, that narrows it down.
Cutter.
We might have a problem.
A...ratty, chipmunk...
Beaver.
..beaver kind of problem.
How did she describe this creature,
apart from the ratty,
chipmunk thing?
Right. Er...about so big.
Protruding teeth, large,
and some claws.
We've had three other
reported sightings.
We've got dozens of them in here.
I need you both to get this place
evacuated now.
Hi. Er...we have to evacuate
the building.
Sarah, if you see this man
within a mile of the ARC,
you've got to let me know.
Why?
He thinks he knows something.
And does he?
Rather a lot, unfortunately.
What do you think about Cutter?
Erm...Cutter?
I think he's a great guy.
Oh. You mean, what do I think?
Cutter.
OK. I think that he is...
pretty hot,
in an emotionally toxic,
don't-come-near-me,
I'm-a-romantic-disaster kind of way.
Just my type, then.
Is there something going on
between you two?
It's complicated.
Apparently, he used to like
some girl that looked like me.
According to him, actually was me,
in a different evolutionary
timeline.
So, now I don't know if he likes her
or me or the version of her in me,
or whether
it's just the same thing.
No baggage, then?
They're on red alert. Infiltration
is impossible without security
clearance and retina scanners.
That depends on who you know.
What?
What is it?
A diictodon.
Male.
Permian era.
Herbivores and burrowers.
Chew their way through anything.
You are an electrician's nightmare.
Come on. That's cute.
Yeah, I mean,
they're social creatures.
Wait. Stay.
Wait.
And quick, too.
Yes.
Let go. Get off it!
You can't have that. It's mine!
Open the door!
"Final call for everyone
to evacuate the building."
Anything?
No.
"Proceed to your nearest exit."
Cutter?
We're trapped in the operating
theatre with the anomaly and...
a woman who's about to give birth.
I need you here as quick as you can.
"We're on our way."
Where are the theatres?
No idea.
Let's find someone who works here.
I'm a trained soldier.
I can find my way around a hospital.
That's it, little fellow. You're
my ticket to the big time.
Just hold it right there.
No!
What are you doing here?
I work here.
Yes, but what are you doing here now?
Are you feeling all right?
Yes.
You don't seem quite yourself.
I'm Professor Nick Cutter.
Strangely enough,
I hadn't actually forgotten that.
Cutter.
You're back. Great.
Erm...I've verified another date,
so I need you to check it
before I add it to the model. Yeah?
Memo to self. Arrange regular mental
health check-ups for all staff.
What is that thing?
The power cuts have caused
a temporary atmospheric overload.
It's kind of like a hurricane,
only made up of electricity.
Do I look daft?
Oh, I think this is it.
No, you're not having a baby now.
Yeah. Right now.
How difficult can it be to find
an operating theatre in a hospital?
What was that
about being a trained soldier?
Catch it.
What do you mean, catch it?
Catch it!
All right.
OK. Catch it. Get under it.
This.
Maybe we could.
Hello, mate.
My name's Connor. This is...
My name's Connor. How are you?
If I'm not mistaken,
you're a diictodon, right?
Cutter.
This woman is a trained
health professional.
She doesn't look like a nurse.
She's a zookeeper.
What?
How many babies have you delivered?
Dozens.
What kind of babies?
Zebras,
lions,
antelopes...
I delivered a giraffe once.
So, don't worry. The principle
is the same, only hopefully your
baby will have a shorter neck.
I need you to take a look
at these calculations,
but I think that they're as accurate
as possible.
I'm busy now.
You carry on with your work.
I'm trying.
If we feed these figures into
the model, I think -
Be quiet.
Hello.
You've changed. Your clothes.
You weren't wearing that before.
Did something happen
at the hospital?
Yes.
If you're busy right now,
it's not a problem.
I've got things to do too.
I'm leaving now.
You're going back to the hospital?
Yes.
Don't let me hold you up.
Cutter?
Do you remember that drink
we talked about?
How about tonight?
I'm leaving now.
Yeah, I got that.
OK. Bad idea. Forget it.
Maybe another time.
No. There won't be another time.
OK.
Fair enough.
I can handle that.
I appreciate your honesty.
I think.
I'm an idiot.
I'm...an idiot.
I didn't want it to be like this!
I wanted it to be beautiful.
Breathe.
It hurts!
You'll get through this.
You'll soon have a beautiful baby.
It's a girl.
A girl. Ahh! Don't actually
think I'd want to know, but -
I just know it will be.
What's your name?
Nick.
You're a nice man.
Sometimes.
Abby.
What are you waiting for?
It's a distress call.
It's all right.
Just a hunch.
Maybe it'll attract the others.
It's all right.
They're not here.
What is it, mate?
Hey? What are you trying to tell me?
Oh, fantastic.
Now he's Dr Doolittle.
He wasn't making that noise before.
Can you hear that?
Follow me.
Oh, God!
Abby, you're needed here.
It's coming!
It's OK, it's OK, it's OK.
All right. All right. Push.
Oh, God!
I'm not sure this is working, Abby.
It's coming.
That's it.
Ha! It worked.
The distress call attracts them.
What's going on?
It's just the drugs.
I haven't had any drugs.
Go on, go on, go on, go on.
What are we going to do about her?
I don't know.
She's stuck here now.
Because I'm having a baby!
Sorry.
All right. OK. One last push.
Listen to my voice.
"Open the main security gate."
You wanted to see me?
Take a seat.
Have you noticed anything...
..strange about Cutter recently?
How long have you got?
Stranger than normal, I mean.
Well he's not saying much,
and he's suddenly decided to change
his clothes twice today, so...
I'm worried he might be erm...
..unravelling.
I hear you've been looking for me.
Thought I'd save you the trouble.
Get off me!
You should be more careful, Dr Page.
Cutter!
What the hell is going on?
You are so fired.
Don't kill him yet.
Yet?
What have you done?
Guard this door.
Shoot anyone
who tries to get in or out.
Obey no-one else.
My voice is the only voice
you recognise.
So, Cutter's finally gone native.
He would never betray us.
Unless I'm very much mistaken,
he just did.
I know him. And I know he wouldn't
do this of his own free will.
Excellent. No signal.
Did you see the way
she spoke to him?
It was...
pretty weird.
She's beautiful.
It's a boy.
A boy?
Hello, you.
Sorry, we...
(OK. I'm going to have to go.
The nurse will look after you now.
OK?)
Thank you, for everything.
Do you know
what you're going to call him?
I don't know.
I only had girls' names ready.
Do you think erm...
Do you think he'd be OK
if I called him erm...
... Stanley?
I know it's old-fashioned.
It was my dad's name.
See you around, Stanley.
So, who locked you in?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Looks like they missed
the last bus home.
What shall we do with them?
We keep 'em.
Yeah.
For now.
Come on, guys.
You asked for evidence.
Brilliant.
Tell them to hold the front page.
Really?
No. Not really. You bring me a blurry
photo of a gopher with comedy plastic
teeth and you call this evidence?
A child of ten could have faked that.
This is a prehistoric creature!
Get out of my sight.
Give me one last chance.
Why?
Because it's the biggest story
in history.
Do you really want it to go to
one of your competitors?
It's brilliant, Nick.
Beautiful.
We should have worked on it
together.
What am I talking to you for?
It's as if he had no will
of his own. He just responded
to everything she told him.
You're right. Like he was programmed
to obey her voice.
Exactly.
He didn't even seem to hear
the rest of us.
So, what we have to do...
is get her to change
her instructions.
Why would she do that?
Maybe we can do it for her.
Are you all right in there, guys?
Comfy?
He should have checked our passes.
Yeah. Your men are getting slack.
You go on ahead. I want to have
a little word with security.
Something's not right.
Where is everyone?
It's...it's you.
Put Connor and Abby with the others.
"Is there anything in my voice,
Lester,
anything at all,
that's telling you there's nothing
you can do to make me obey you?
Nothing will stop me doing
what I have to do.
Nothing will stop me...
I just need to paste this
into a new file.
"Stop. Do nothing. Obey my voice."
What is going on?
I was just about to
ask you the same question.
What the hell's got into Cutter?
That's not him.
There's two of him.
Two versions of Cutter.
What a nightmare.
We've got to do something.
Connor, er...
we have to play this audio file
over the internal sound system.
We can't do that from here.
You created this.
I er...
borrowed the technology
from the future.
It's made from your DNA.
Perfect in every physical detail.
Physical.
It has er...
limited intelligence.
Enough to follow basic instruction.
It's a human being, though?
Free will is what makes us human.
This...
creature has er...
It's nothing more
than a living photocopy.
Please tell me
you didn't do this to Stephen.
No matter what they look like,
they can never be the original.
Why are you doing this, Helen?
Because I have seen
the final destruction
of almost every living creature
on this once-beautiful planet.
I can stop it, Nick.
I can save us from that.
Whatever's going to happen
is going to happen.
We must leave it alone.
Look what happened last time.
You killed Stephen.
I didn't kill Stephen.
You did.
The course of evolution
can be changed.
I can...
restore balance.
You still don't get it, do you?
No matter how many times
you interfere,
you can't get the result you want,
because evolution can't be bent
to your will.
I really hope you're wrong.
Everyone er...OK?
Helen's taken over the ARC.
I know. Her men are crawling
all over the place.
How many men have you got?
Just me. Should be enough.
Becker, we need to get this
to the PA system.
What is it? Doesn't matter.
Come with me.
The rest of you stay here.
You see, you don't know it yet,
but I do.
Know what?
Your work will lead to
predators being created
here in this ARC of yours.
I'd never sanction that.
I've seen them...in the future.
Troops from the ARC.
No. You've got it wrong.
You haven't done it yet.
But sooner or later you will.
And it has to be stopped. You.
You have to be stopped now.
Before it begins.
If you're so sure of this,
then why didn't you get your...
creature to kill me
when he had the chance?
Why don't you just shoot me now?
Because there is something
I still don't understand.
Tell me what this is.
Well?
Do you know or not, Professor?
Of course I do.
Tell me.
No.
You can go to hell.
Give him ten seconds, then shoot him.
All right?
I can't...
Come on, Temple. Hurry up!
Quick.
One.
Two.
Don't do it.
Three.
You can't appeal
to his finer feelings.
Five. Six.
Tell me what this is.
You don't have to do as she says.
Seven.
You have a choice.
Eight.
OK.
Nine.
I'll tell you.
Put the gun down.
Do you think they made it?
We'll soon find out.
Get off!
Abby!
Argh! Argh!
My fingers!
I can handle this, Temple.
I can't.
I can't reach.
Punch him!
"Do nothing. Obey my voice."
"Stop. Do nothing. Obey my voice."
"Stop. Do nothing."
No! Stop! That's not me!
"Stop. Do nothing. Obey my voice."
Stop! That's not me! That's not me!
"Obey my voice."
"Stop. Do nothing. Obey my voice."
They did it.
"Obey my voice."
Insurance.
It's over.
"Stop. Do nothing. Obey my voice."
Listen to my voice.
Complete your mission.
"Stop. Do nothing. Obey my voice."
Look, I know that you can hear me.
I know you can understand.
You don't have to obey her.
She made me.
You're a human being.
You have a choice.
Don't listen to him.
Follow your instructions.
You're not a machine.
You're a free man.
You don't want to die.
I don't know what death is.
Trust me,
life's better.
Don't listen to him!
Save yourself.
Guys! Come on.
Come on. Everyone out.
Now!
Cutter?
He's in here!
Cutter.
We've got to get out of here now.
Connor?
Are you OK?
Abby?
What's going on?
It's some sort of bomb.
Right, we've got to prioritise
the casualties.
Where's Helen?
She must be still inside.
Nick.
She wouldn't lift a finger
to save you.
Yeah, I know.
Don't go.
This is a mistake.
I'll be fine.
Cutter!
Where the hell's he going?
Helen.
You came back for me?
Yeah.
You always were sentimental.
Where's the artefact?
It'll be wherever you left it.
What does it do, Nick?
Why is it so important?
I have no idea.
Now, are you coming or aren't you?
I'm sorry, Nick. I can't let you go.
What the hell
are you talking about now?
Oh, for God's sake.
You see, nothing's changed, Nick.
The future is more important
than either of us.
You really know how to pick
your moments.
If you'd seen what I'd seen,
you'd understand.
I'm sorry, Nick.
I wish there was another way.
Know what, Helen?
You're not as smart
as I thought you were.
Get round back there.
Fast!
He's been gone too long.
Be careful.
Connor! Connor!
Connor.
Good man.
You hold on.
I'm going to take you out.
Sorry.
Don't.
Don't...do that.
Sorry.
It's OK.
Just sit with me.
All right?
OK.
This...
This matters.
I don't know why.
But it does, so...
You have to find out what it means,
OK?
OK.
It's on you now.
No.
We can do this together.
We've always done it together.
No.
Not this time.
Tell...
Tell Claudia Brown...
Never mind.
It doesn't matter.
Get an ambulance. Quickly.
Nick.
It's too late.
What?
He can't be.
Oh, God.
There was something
I had to tell him.
I won't let you down, Professor.
We should get this man
in an ambulance now!
Two minutes. I can have this thing
up and running.
It's a velociraptor. A young one.
You need all the help you can get.
Let's turn and burn.
Synchro : Flolo
Transcript : Chocolate