Et dimitte a nobis...
..debita nostra sicut
et nos dimittimus a debitoribus nostris.
Only you can save us from
the beast, Sir William.
God bless and keep
you in this enterprise.
Father.
Sir William.
Will you take this for your protection?
It will keep you from fear.
My lady.
Where is he?
Where's Rex?
Jack...where's Rex?
He's with my mate, Tony.
I said he could borrow him.
He loves lizards.
You idiot! He's bringing
him back this morning,
I swear.
He better be here by the
time I get back from work.
He's just a stupid lizard.
Show some respect, Jack!
Reptiles have feelings too, you know.
Who's there?
Connor? Yo.
Something suspicious
has come up on the Net.
What kind of suspicious?
Have a look.
Rex. What?
Huh? Oh, no.
That's just a bearded dragon.
I am gonna kill Jack.
Really? That's a good idea
(!) Any particular reason?
He lent Rex to a friend.
Isn't that what you just said? Me?
What? When?
When you looked at the
screen, you said, "Rex."
Next. I said, "Next," as in,
you know, "We've done that.
What else have you got?"
Whatever. Are you OK?
So we don't need to take any
action? No action. OK, fine.
Action? What action? Nothing, nothing.
What's with all the...questions?
So Jack definitely
said he lent him to...?
Yes. Why?
Stop.
Hello? 'Jack, do me a favour.'
Explain to me why Rex is up
for auction on the Internet.
Gambled him at poker.
You had no right to use Rex
to pay off your gambling debt.
What do you think student loans are for?
Get him back. How? 'Just do it.'
OK?
So where is it? Not far.
Where are you going?
Danny, I am sick of working on
the artifact. I need a break.
No, no, no. We need you
here. Well, I'm coming.
He's gonna kill it.
Yeah!
This is madness. Come on!
Stop! Oi!
Stop!
Get him out of there! MAN: Oi, what?
What is that thing?
You don't wanna know.
It's injured. We have to help it.
Afraid you were gonna say that.
Abby!
Sarah, wait! Get back! I can help.
We're gonna push it back to the anomaly.
If it's gonna die, it's gonna die
in its own world. It's not gonna die.
Where's the anomaly?
It's close.
Abby, how's it injured?
It's got something stuck in its side.
Abby!
Oi!
Danny! I'll make a noise.
Go on.
Go.
Grab something.
Go on!
That was easy.
Why is it coming back?
Ego in Abysso sum! Meam
quaesitionem persequor. Ad Gloriam.
Anyone else? Hey?
Well, we've had a dragon,
a knight in shining armour...
A damsel in distress would be nice.
It's not a real dragon, though.
Dracorex, late cretaceous, herbivore.
It's still dangerous. It's wounded.
Close the anomaly. We'll
try and get it back to you.
What did he say, anyway?
"This is Hell. I carry on
to Glory." You speak Latin?
A copper can't have a classical
education? No, I didn't say that.
It's just it was more, "This is Hell,
my quest continues onto
Glory." I was paraphrasing.
The dracorex must have come through
an anomaly into Medieval England.
This is a waste of
time. It's a maze here.
I'm gonna go and get Connor,
we'll go after the knight.
Abby, take Becker, chase down the
dragony thing. You go too, Sarah.
Erm...Danny?
I think I'll stay here.
I thought you said you wanted to get
involved. I know, but you're right,
I'm probably more of a back room girl.
Look, if you're frightened, it's
nothing to be ashamed of. Yeah.
I'll keep that in mind.
He's on the high
street! He's over there!
Come on!
It's over there.
Don't lose it.
Die!
Our knight?
So what happens when we
actually catch up with him?
We sit and talk to him like
rational human beings. Yeah?
Yeah.
I think we found it.
I don't want it harmed.
We use tranquillisers. Is that clear?
Look, it's my job to protect
you, not the creatures.
All right?
Bye. Thanks.
Stand back, demon.
We're not demons. We're flesh
and blood, just like you.
You are demons and I am in Hell.
Technically, it's London.
But it's an easy mistake to make.
We can help you get home.
My only way home is to slay the
beast and to complete my quest.
Killing the dragon
will not get you back.
It's not a dragon. We can help you.
I know this seems weird, but -
Peasants.
Look, we're never gonna find him.
Danny, he's wearing a full suit
of armour and carrying a sword.
Even in London, that's
gonna get noticed.
Don't worry, he's gonna
stand out like a sore...
..thumb.
Don't ask.
Just unlock the anomaly.
Well...
Look, Lester instructed it.
You sure? Yes, I'm sure.
OK.
Right, as soon as I get
through, seal it again,
and then unlock it in exactly
an hour's time. You got that?
Yeah.
Wish me luck.
No.
I told you, I don't
want it to be harmed.
Abby, what are you doing?
Go, go, go!
Yargh!
If it comes any closer,
I'm going to kill it.
That is not the answer. (ROARS)
I think you should take a look at it.
Hey.
It's OK, we're not gonna hurt you.
Looks as if it's on its last
legs. Yeah, we need to get it back.
Yeah, how? Well...
that's your department.
Oh, dinosaur transportation?
Yeah. Yeah, why not?
Hurry up, we haven't got much time.
Here's your field hospital.
Hang in there, dragon.
I know this place.
Ooh, very nice.
All right, mate?
Nice costume.
Recycled, is it?
Satan?
No, his name's Brian, actually.
The mark of the beast! Sling your 'ook!
Oi, you two. Take it outside now.
Take it outside!
Sir Lancelot? Yeah.
Satan!
Oi!
See how your master cowers before me!
I don't think he's who you think he is.
How many demons must I slay this day?
Sort something out.
I'll keep him busy. What?
Go on.
Can't we just talk about this?
Obviously not. What's that up there?
Ah, that's just made
you cross, hasn't it?
You are too feeble an
opponent to be worth killing.
But do not try my patience again.
State of my pub!
Quick! We can't lose him!
This is worse than the wife's hen night!
Oh, it's all right.
You can come out now.
Gotcha!
Now what?
Come on!
Stop.
We need a vet. I'll call the ARC.
There's not enough time.
I'm gonna have to do it.
You can do this, Abby.
Come on, I need your help. Right.
Right, so put your hands
round there and pull. Yep.
OK. Just really steady.
Not gonna let you die, dragon.
Halt!
Are you a witch? No.
Oh. Why?
You were out there and
the dragon didn't eat you.
I hid.
How long have you been in here
- in the church?
Since the dragon came.
But the knight will save us. Really?
And who is this knight?
Sir William de Mornay.
Where are you from?
Well, I'm from a place
that's very, very far away.
The Holy Land? Bit further than that.
Tell me more about the village.
Why should I?
Good question.
There you go. That's why.
It looks like mud.
It certainly doesn't taste like mud.
Go on.
Hey, slow down. That stuff
can ruin your teeth, OK?
Know what? Here, have the whole bar.
So, what else do you wanna know?
Well, this knight...
You never saw me, this didn't happen.
Right. Good.
Bingo.
We should split up? Split up?
I'm not splitting up. Have
you not seen horror films?
We've got to find him
before he kills someone.
It's me. Talk to me.
The knight's name
- it's William de Mornay.
He was a mercenary who fought all
over Europe for whoever paid him.
He's killed a lot of men, Danny,
and he's looking for redemption,
and he thinks killing
the dragon is gonna do it.
How do you know all this?
My job is to research, so I researched.
Well, you're very good.
Better than you think.
We have to find him. He's lost
in a world he doesn't understand.
I mean, maybe he's not
trying to find the dragon.
Maybe he's just trying to
get home. Well, in that case,
there's a ruins of the old parish
church by the river. Shh-shh-shh.
Erm...I'm sending you
the map reference now.
'OK, you get Becker and meet me there.'
Well, he can't at the
moment. He's helping Abby.
What's he doing?
She's operating on the dracorex.
All right, wait for Becker and meet
me at the church. I can come now.
Sarah, you do not leave
without backup. That's an order.
Do you understand? I
can't hear you, Danny.
'Sarah, do not hang
up!' You're breaking up.
'Sarah, do not hang up the
-' Oh...
shame.
What's going on? How's Abby? She's fine.
She's trying to save the dragon.
Really?
I should be with her.
Maybe I could help.
Well, go on, then.
Really bad time, Jack.
The bidding for Rex is up to two grand.
You better get hold of the cash, then.
Where am I gonna get £2,000 from?
There's nothing I can
do. Abby's gonna kill me.
Really? She'll have to join the queue.
Look, just leave it with
me. I'll think of something.
OK?
Thank you.
How's he doing? I think the wound's OK.
It's the shock that's killing him.
If he survives for another
hour, I think he might make it.
Is there anything I can do to help?
We need to put pressure on the wound.
OK.
Is he OK? Yeah.
My grave.
I am dead and gone to Hell.
I am too, God help me.
William.
I know none of this makes
any sense but I can explain.
You just have to trust me.
Are you the devil's champion?
No, I'm not the devil's
champion and you're not in Hell,
but I can help you.
With God on my side...
..I will not be defeated.
I don't want to fight you.
Because you are a coward.
That's a bit harsh, isn't
it? This will be over quickly.
You are an infernal imp
sent to torment my soul.
You sound just like my mother.
Stop! Sir William!
Stop!
Sir William...there's
something that you must see.
Do you know what this is, William?
It's my grave.
I am dead and gone to Hell.
You're not dead yet.
See...what it says here?
You have many years to live.
Then why am I already
in the world to come?
Look...closely.
My wife lies here beside me.
I have no wife. Not yet.
But you will when you get back.
Lady Elizabeth Langley.
How do you know her? You
will marry her, William.
You will have three children together.
I am just a wandering
knight, far below her in rank.
Listen to me. Just calm down.
You must have done something
to impress her, William.
You will live a long
and happy life together.
It's written here...in stone.
It's your fate, your destiny.
If you let us take you back.
My only way back is to kill the beast.
That is not your quest, William.
Your quest is to leave this
place and marry Elizabeth.
The beast is wounded and likely to die.
Honour is satisfied.
Well, you know where it is?
Take me to it!
Take another step and I will
dispatch her without mercy!
All right. You will
not hurt me, William.
It goes against all laws of chivalry.
Bleeding stopped?
He's gonna be OK.
One tough little dragon, eh?
Becker, change of plan.
I need picking up. Now.
It ends at last.
Out of my way.
No.
Out...of my way.
You show strange courage for a demon.
Oh, I'm a demon all right.
William! William!
Elizabeth is waiting for you.
You have my word of honour.
The dragon will never
come to your village again.
Your quest can end in triumph.
I am weary of killing.
I know.
I crave only of rest and
the pleasures of peace.
And they can all be yours.
If I kill the beast! No! No!
I will never let you kill him!
Then I will cut you both down!
Abby, move out of the way!
William! Drop your weapon
and get down on your knees!
Becker, no! What?!
If you kill him, then history changes.
His children will never be born.
And who knows where it will end.
He has to go back.
No, he's gonna kill Abby. Becker, do it!
You would sacrifice your life...
..for this savage beast?
Willingly.
This is not how demons
behave, is it, William?
No, this is some sort of trick.
No trick and in your heart, you know it.
We're humans...just like you.
You've done enough, William.
Your quest is over.
Yargh!
No!
I thought this might be Hell.
Yeah, we got that.
But if it is not... can it be paradise?
Well, it's not exactly paradise, no.
Thank God, for it is an awful place.
Yeah, sometimes.
But it's home and er...
And your home is...
Through there. Yeah.
Sarah.
Ego vos relinquo in pacis.
What did he say?
He said, "I depart in peace."
It was more like, "I
leave you in peace."
Oh, yeah.
What did he leave you?
It's from Jerusalem.
It's seven centuries old.
Worth a few quid on eBay.
Well, you expect we'll have difficulty
explaining why it's still brand new.
So, look, tell me something.
Where did you find out all
that stuff about William?
You know, a bit of luck,
intuition, a few educated guesses.
Amazing. It's almost
like you were there.
Well, I did tell you I
was very good, didn't I?
So...
what are you gonna do with the dracorex?
I'm gonna wait till an anomaly
opens to the right time period
and then put him back.
You can't keep him, you know.
I mean, for one thing, I don't
think he'd fit in the flat.
I wasn't going to.
Well, not forever.
I've gotta go. Where?
Just some stuff to...do.
Open the doors!
It's Sir William!
The beast is...
vanquished!
My lady Elizabeth.
I believe this is yours.
I've come for the lizard.
Cost you three grand.
How about you bring him to me?
Or I'll come in and get him.
Yeah? You and whose army?
Mine...
actually.
You better come in.
Thank you.
He's found my detector.
It's your responsibility
to keep that safe!
He's gone through the anomaly.
The bug is from the same place
as the artifact. It's possible.
Which means that the future could be
just the other side of the anomaly.
If those things got loose,
humanity never stood a chance.
Connor, get him out of here!
Presynchro : Flolo
Transcript : Chocolate