Previously on Battlestar Galactica...
Aurora, Goddess of the dawn.
I thought  it would be a nice figurehead
for your model ship.
- A fresh start.
- Thank you.
- Starbuck, you're getting too low!
- Come on, Lee, get her out of there.
- You come back!
- Just let me go.
No!
Baltar's trial
may have been the trigger,
but this is a feeling
I've been having for a while.
It's time for a change.
Please, God, don't let this child die.
How can you take him and let me live?
God answered your prayers.
You have to see.
- Look at him.
- And no trace of a fever.
No.
It's a miracle.
I need to know about the other five.
The types we've never seen.
It's true.
We're Cylons.
And we have been from the start.
Even after that Raider scanned me
with that red light,
damn thing just cut and ran.
You think it recognized you as a Cylon?
Maybe that's why it didn't shoot me.
More important,
why didn't I shoot him?
Okay, what the hell's going on?
- I'm off the ship for a few hours...
- A few hours?
Kara, you were gone for over two months.
That's impossible.
How did you get here?
I told you, I don't know exactly.
Damn it, they're still going
in the wrong direction.
One more jump and I'm gonna lose
my way altogether.
It's Roslin.
The old man's not gonna listen to me.
I gotta get to her.
No, wait!
Look alive! And for frak sake,
don't shoot the godsdamned President!
Just let me talk to her.
Talk all you want,
but it ends with the first bang.
We're rollin' down here.
Starbuck's got the President.
Gaeta, take the com.
Move.
Move!
Come on.
Move, come on!
Over by the couch.
Now!
I want to hate you so much.
So much.
You had a vision, remember?
The arrow, the temple.
I went down to that planet with you,
and it was a frakkin' toaster party.
A lot of good people died, remember?
Yes, I do.
I trusted you.
On a vision.
That's it...
a vision!
I saw...
Earth.
I saw it with my own eyes.
And it's calling me back.
We're going the wrong way.
Why can't you trust me?
Shoot me.
If you think I'm a Cylon,
them I'm your enemy.
Shoot your enemy.
Take it!
I'm no more a Cylon than you are.
And you know it.
I wish I did.
I've put my life on the line
for this frakkin' ship.
I have ate, slept, and fought
next to the people that I love.
I have pissed off my friends!
I have broken more rules
than I've followed!
I frakked up, okay! I messed up!
But it's all that I have.
Those people are my family.
And none of us belong here.
Two down. We've got two down!
Shoot me!
If I'm a Cylon, shoot me!
They made you perfect, didn't they?
Down on the floor now!
- Now!
- Let go of me!
Get off me! Get off me!
What are you doing?
I am not a Cylon, Mathias!
- Madam President.
- Gods!
What the frak's going on here?
I thought you were on the move.
She's out of her frakkin' mind.
Gods!
- You all right?
- Get off me!
Get off!
Listen to me, please.
I'm losing it.
The ringing...
The way to Earth...
It's getting weaker.
Don't you understand?
Don't any of you understand?!
It was so... It was so clear.
Like it was coming from the next room.
Stop looking at me like that.
I can feel it slipping away.
Even without jumping, as we move,
it's half of what it was
when I got here.
Half.
If we keep jumping, it'll be gone,
and we'll never find it again.
I thought that's what we wanted.
A way to Earth.
- Do you hear me?
- Get her out of here.
- Yes, sir. Let's go!
- You better work on your aim,
because I'm not gonna stop!
You're gonna have to kill me!
One more jump and it'll be gone!
Admiral!
BATTLESTAR GALACTICA
Season 4 - Episode 2
Subtitles
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )= -
Transcript
- =( swsub.com )= -
Thanks, insults, appreciations...
- =( www.seriestele.net )= -
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -
The excited state decays
by vibrational relaxation
into the first excited singlet state.
Yes, yes, and merrily we go.
Reduce atmospheric nitrogen by 0.03%.
It is not much consolation
that society will pick up the bits,
leaving us at eight modern
where punishment,
rather than interdiction, is paramount.
Please, cut the fuse.
They will not harm their own.
End of line.
Limiting diffusions to two dimensions
increases the number of
evolutionary jumps within the species.
Rise and measure the temple of the five.
Transformation is the goal.
They will not harm their own.
Datafont synchronization complete.
The hybrid
is clearly telling us something.
is always telling us something.
They're supposed to maintain operations
on each ship,
not vomit metaphysics.
All right,
I give up. What...
What is she trying to tell us?
They're in the colonial fleet...
With the humans.
"They"?
They who?
The Final Five.
The Raiders refuse to fight
because they sense
the Final Five might be
- in the colonial fleet.
- They could have been caught or hiding.
No way, stop.
Stop, right now.
Turn around,
go and take a cleansing walk,
and I am gonna try
and forget what I just heard.
The Final Five... Cavil, they're near.
This is far too important.
What their eyes must have seen,
witnessed over time...
- Think they look anything like us?
- That's enough!
Don't you realize what you're doing?
You're openly discussing the Final Five!
That's forbidden!
You're toying with our survival.
Look at yourselves.
Look,
there's millions of Twos have that nose.
Millions of Sixes possess that mouth.
Eights share those breasts,
and Ones have this brain.
We're mechanized copies.
There's a reason
the original programmers clearly felt
that it's a mistake
for us to contact the Final Five!
- No!
- Violating that programming
threatens our survival!
Something has changed.
Thoughts have changed.
Yes, they change. The Raiders changed.
That's where all this started,
with them.
Somehow they exceeded their programming,
and unlike us,
they can't correct themselves.
So we're gonna have to do it for them.
Do what?
We'll reconfigure
their neural architecture,
and shave down
their heuristic responses.
Dumb them down? Lobotomize them?
They're tools, not pets.
But in any case, it has to be done.
Says who?
Says God almighty,
the voice of reason, that's who!
When are you gonna hear it?
You don't have the authority to make
any change without a majority vote.
Well, we'll vote.
The Fours and Fives will be on my side.
There will be a vote.
The Raiders hear what we hear.
The Raiders are simple machines.
No.
Something extraordinary has happened.
Something is calling to us.
Pushing us to discover our origins,
to understand our place in the universe.
The Raiders are part of that,
and the Final Five...
Are anywhere but with the humans.
You're late.
I had to wait
for Cally to nod off, okay?
- She's having trouble sleeping.
- Did you see Kara?
I saw her. She's crazy as a latrine rat.
If anything,
she's more like Starbuck than ever.
She's my wife!
And the President nearly
put a bullet in her skull
because she suspected her
of being a Cylon.
You are one!
We bring attention to ourselves,
we're frakked!
If Starbuck is one of us,
she's playing it big the other way.
The four of us heard the music
and sought each other out.
She hasn't.
We're still missing one.
Baltar.
Not Baltar, but...
when I found him
in the temple on the algae planet,
he was with one of those skin jobs.
The one they call D'Anna.
She saw something in there...
I don't know what. But they talked.
He might know something.
He's got those
one-God nutcases
believing he's some kind of healer.
He brought some boy out from a coma.
Maybe he knows who the fifth is.
Maybe he knows who we are.
Then we gotta get in close and find out.
How do you propose we do that?
Take him out for drinks?
Well, he is accomplished at two things.
Lying in his cell, and lying in a woman.
He'd poke a skin job.
He racked up a Six... That's a given.
There is no way.
You don't have to get
on your back for him, but...
Oh, gee, thanks.
What were you doing?
What were you thinking?
What happened to you?
I saw...
Earth.
The shape of it, the smell of it.
The feel of it on my skin in my pores.
And I swear to you,
it was like I'd been there before.
Like I never left.
You're too stupid to figure out
you just screwed over
the one ally you had.
You didn't have the guts to hold on.
Tell me...
Who's gonna help you?
Yeah, frak me, huh?
It sure as hell isn't gonna be you.
You've gotta remind yourself
that you're somebody else.
You're the President's wet nurse.
You're the one
who doesn't have the guts.
Nice to know you still care, Admiral.
We're going the wrong way!
We have all conferred with our models,
and the results are in.
The Fours and the Fives
have joined us Ones,
and they voted
to reconfigure the Raiders.
Gee, what a surprise.
Well, the Twos, Sixes and Eights
voted against it, so we're deadlocked.
How hopelessly... But you were right.
And I'm machine enough
- to admit that I was wrong.
- What are you talking about?
Something extraordinary
has happened.
Eight.
What's going on?
Boomer.
I'm not going
to sugarcoat this.
I'll just say that this Eight
- has voted to reconfigure.
- What?
Shocked? I was shocked too.
But no one has ever voted
against their model.
No one. Is this true?
We have to be able to defend ourselves.
No, this is unconscionable.
This is wrong. She can't.
- You had something to do with this.
- No, it was her decision totally.
- You cannot allow this.
- There is no law. There's no edict.
There's nothing that forbids it.
It's just...
It's never happened before.
Try and remember you said that
when he boxes your line.
Now, don't be a sore loser.
If you do this, we all lose.
- We think it's for the best.
- The best?
Have you lost your mind?
Our identies are determined
by our models. Each model is unique.
We belong together.
You know this better than anyone.
"Mechanized copies."
- Those are your very words.
- "Something has changed."
Those are your very words.
And I whole heartedly agree.
The Raiders are sentient,
just as we are.
There was a plan.
A divine plan in our design.
- You're butchering them.
- We're reconfiguring them.
You are not God.
No... I'm a mechanic.
The Raiders were designed
to do a specific job.
They stopped doing it. I'm fixing that.
And when the cutting's all done,
they'll go back to being happy warriors.
So let's move on, all right?
I'll pray for you.
I'll pray hard.
All right, you hooch hounds!
Lock it up!
It's time... Shut the frak up!
Pay attention.
We're saying good-bye...
to the best damn jock you...
pink-ass cones will ever hope to see.
Shut up.
Major?
- Let's go!
- Come on!
- I have a drink.
- Let's do this. Come on now.
I'm not thirsty.
To Galactica!
To the men and women of Galactica.
To the Admiral...
... who commands
the men and women of Galactica.
And to our sweethearts,
husbands, and wives.
To our sweethearts!
To absent friends.
Thank you.
That's very sweet.
Excuse me, will you?
Watch your step.
- You say what?
- Excuse me.
You're spying on me, Tory.
I've seen you here.
No. I heard about the miracle.
The child?
Yes.
You mean Laura Roslin
has heard about it.
All right, I have been spying on you.
Well, it's lucky
I was sitting down, isn't it?
I've been watching these people.
The way they look at you.
If you go squealing to the President
that my newfound popularity borders
on the phenomenal,
- then she should be very worried.
- I came here on my own.
And I slept with your boss last night.
Come on, be nice.
- What's it gonna cost you?
- My God.
My giddy-od!
Get a grip, Gaius.
She's not lying. She really could be
a wonderful source of information.
- Why don't you feel her out?
- Feel her what?
- What?
- I'm not talking to you. Actually...
Try and forget me for a moment.
- Ask her what she's doing here.
- I am talking to you.
- Why did you come here?
- Maybe it was a mistake.
Well, I can't stop thinking
about what's happened.
You were found innocent
when everyone hated you. I hated you.
And this healed boy,
the return of Kara Thrace...
I mean, everyone thought she was dead.
- So perhaps there are miracles.
- Perhaps.
Thing is, somehow you seem
to be at the center of them.
Yes, I do, don't I?
I don't understand myself, to be honest.
Just...
Well, it seems that
God has chosen me
to sing his song.
- A song?
- Music. Did you say music?
Yeah, you know, it's funny.
It's a lot like that. It's...
It's like the distant chaos
of an orchestra
tuning up.
And then
somebody waves a magic wand,
and all of those notes
start to slide into place.
A grotesque,
screeching cacophony
becomes a single melody.
I really shouldn't be seen here.
Who the frak are you?!
What, am I supposed to be impressed?
I mean, you're me.
Obviously you're me, so...
Unless you're not me. Huh?
Six?
Is it you, Six...
Like in disguise?
Now, why would she need
to disguise herself from you?
- Well, you've got a very good point.
- Let's talk about Tory.
- Where is she?
- We should talk about Tory,
'cause we both know
where this is heading.
You like her, don't you?
Yeah, well, you know, she's...
She's a sexy lady.
Yeah, yeah.
Hot.
- You slay me. You really do, Gaius.
- Why?
She's more than all these things.
She's special.
And you feel it.
Yeah, fragile.
Yeah, I sense that too.
You're very observant.
Fragile.
Handle with care.
Oh, I'd love to.
You're enjoying that more than usual.
Hair of the dog.
Lee's party.
What do we do now? Put her on trial?
Find Romo Lampkin?
Take a show of hands?
I don't know.
Follow her into an ambush?
- She is driven.
- Yeah.
You gonna keep waltzing,
or are you gonna sit down and talk?
What's going on? Sit.
What if she's telling the truth?
She was supposed to die out there.
She didn't. I can't explain it.
What if she was meant to help us?
And this was a...
A what?
A miracle?
Is that what you want to call this?
Go ahead, say it.
Grab your piece of the golden arrow.
I want to hear
Admiral Atheist say
that a miracle happened.
You shot at her
and you missed at close range.
Doloxan fraks with your aim.
So does doubt.
I pulled the trigger
and I'd do it again.
She put her life in front of a bullet
as if it had no meaning.
You drop an egg, you reach for another.
Maybe convincing you
meant more to her than her own life.
Is that your miracle?
You want to talk about miracles?
The very same day
that a very pale doctor informed me
that I had terminal cancer,
most of humanity was annihilated,
and I survived.
And by some mathematical absurdity,
I became President.
And then
my cancer disappeared
long enough for us
to find a way to Earth.
You can call it whatever you want.
And now I'm dying.
Don't talk that way.
You've gotta face this.
My life is coming to an end soon enough,
and I am not going to apologize
to you for not trusting her.
And I am not...
I am not going to trust
her with the fate of this fleet.
You are so buckled up inside...
You can't take any more loss.
Your son's leaving...
This, me... I know it.
No one's going anywhere.
Okay...
Here's the truth.
This is what's going on.
You want to believe Kara.
You would rather be wrong about her
and face your own demise
than risk losing her again.
You can stay in the room, but
get out of my head.
You're so afraid to live alone.
And you're afraid to die that way.
You're afraid that you may not be
the dying leader you thought you were.
Or that your death may be as
meaningless
as everyone else's.
Zarek nominated me
for the vacant quorum spot, so I...
You're Zarek's wing man.
All right,
all right, you know, stow it, okay.
I've heard it all before.
The guy's a piece of work, I know.
His head's as big as
the house I grew up in but...
I'm... I'm pretty new to all this.
I could use the help.
Besides, I never really
could say no to anything.
Except me.
Especially you.
You know, I think I finally understand
what you meant about
having a destiny.
I've got to do this.
And the fact that I don't
have an explanation why doesn't...
Doesn't really seem to matter anymore.
So say we all.
Good luck on your journey, Lee Adama.
You too, Kara Thrace.
All right.
Lee...
I believe you.
Red and blue sections will go first,
yellow and green will follow.
Starbuck, if you've got a problem,
I don't want to hear it.
My only problem is you didn't preach
that sermon a week ago.
Keep your ears open. Any Cylon contact,
just shut down, bug out.
- Questions.
- When will you play to the card game?
- We're on tomorrow night!
- All right, all right.
Good luck.
And be careful out there.
Attention to orders!
In recognition of honorable,
loyal, and faithful service,
Madam President,
Admiral of the Colonial Fleet,
ladies and gentlemen...
Major Lee Adama...
Salute!
Good luck.
Thank you.
Well, it looks like you got the house.
I'll miss you.
Good-bye, Lee.
Look after yourself.
We want you
to stop lobotomizing the Raiders, Cavil.
Raiders with free will?
Not going to happen.
Do you know
what just really rankles my ass?!
You've been pointing fingers,
falsely accusing me
of manipulation just short of tyranny.
When you're the one
that's been leading the charge here.
We want you to stop.
You're not in charge.
We had a vote.
For the last time,
will you stop lobotomizing the Raiders?
It's unbelievable, isn't it?
Unbelievable.
For the last time,
no.
I was afraid you'd say that.
Come in.
What is this about?
Centurions can't vote, Six.
They're not here to vote, Cavil.
- Am I hurting you?
- No.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
What do you mean, nothing?
You're crying.
It's just something I do during sex.
- All the time?
- Yeah.
I'm really sorry.
Don't be sorry.
Why should you apologize?
You should be thankful.
You have an abundance of feeling.
I've never
really thought of it like that.
You're blessed, aren't you?
I don't know.
I guess.
I suppose I couldn't be a Cylon.
Well, I don't know about that.
Human beings don't exclusively
hold the patent on suffering.
Cylons can feel.
- You believe that?
- Yeah, I do, actually.
I've spent time amongst them.
Man may have made them,
but God's at the beginning
of the string, isn't he?
It's God who made the real soul.
The one true God.
One God?
You know, I'm becoming
increasingly tired of holding that in.
Of denying that essential truth.
Now, this... This isn't funny.
Leave.
I said leave!
Why don't they leave?
The telencephalic inhibitor
that restricts higher functions
in the Centurions...
- We had them removed.
- Say what?!
You dumbed down the Raiders.
We the Leobens, the Sharons,
gave the Centurions the gift of reason.
You have no authority to do this, none.
You can't do anything without a vote!
No, we can't do anything with one,
so we're finished voting.
What have you done?
First thing they learned is
what you were doing to the Raiders.
You can imagine how they felt.
Oh, no.
Sir, the fleet is prepped
and ready for jump.
Execute jump.
Go back!
Go back...
Open cell.
Cuff her.
So...
You quietly cut me loose in deep space.
I'm not afraid to die.
Little easier
after you've been through it once.
Harder.
Especially now
that I'm seeing things so clearly.
You're making a mistake.
Maybe I am.
But I can't take the chance
that you're right
and not do something about it.
Helo hand-picked a crew for you.
I'm giving you a ship.
I hope you can stand the smell.
We liberated the Demetrius.
It's a sewage recycling ship.
The party line will be
that we're going for a scouting mission.
Looking for food.
So you think I'm right.
Maybe, maybe not.
But I know she is, the President.
She's been right all along.
I'm tired of losing.
I'm tired of turning away from
the things that I want to believe in.
And I believe you when you say
that you'll die before you stop trying.
And I won't lose you again.
Now go.
Find a way to Earth.
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )= -