Previously on Battlestar GALACTICA...
I'm giving you a ship. Now go.
Find a way to Earth.
Kara,I'm alone,
this is not an attack.
I knew I'd find you.
Leoben?
I'm here to offer a truce
between human and cylon
and a chance for you to
complete your journey.
The hybrid.
You need to go to her,Kara.
She'll tell you the way to get to Earth.
We're done here.
Get him out of here.
We're ready to jump back
to the fleet on your order.
We're not going back to the fleet.
Captain Thrace,as XO of the Demetrius,
I'm hereby relieving you of command.
You son of a bitch.
Gaeta,abort the jump!
I'm gonna take Leoben
back to the baseship,
see if his story checks out.
We'll be waiting here
till the clock runs out.
looks like he wasn't
lying about a civil war.
This is it.
The comet.
It's the ship!
Thus will it come to pass.
You are the harbinger
of death, Kara Thrace.
You will lead them all to their end.
cylon baseship.
Demetrius,athena.
The baseship is ours.
Then let's go home.
now I have learned from
unimpeachable sources
that president Laura
Roslin has for some time now
been sharing hallucinogenic visions
with two cylons within our fleet:
One Sharon Agathon,sent on the
classified Demetrius mission,
and the other a cylon prisoner
being held aboard the Galactica.
It's not that easy,madam president.
No?You should try it sometime.
Most of the population
has heard that broadcast.
I would assume that's the point.
Look,I take no pleasure
in putting this before you.
In fact,they practically had
to push me through that door.
Well,I'm sure you're
quite happy to stay.
I can't put one foot in front of another
without someone blocking my path
asking me what the hell is going on!
- For the welfare of the fleet...
- excuse me.
As long as I am in this office,
the welfare of this fleet is not
something you need to worry about.
You owe the people a response.
I owe the people?
That's what I believe.
What if suddenly all your
beliefs were called into question?
- Madam president...
- up is down.
Black is white.
Scripture is fiction.
Home is thin air instead
of solid ground,etcetera.
You know,I'm really sorry for
everything you've had to endure.
I really am.
But the people,they deserve a response.
Do they?
Is there any truth to this broadcast?
And what would you do
if I told you the truth?
What if it were you instead of me
and all that's left of
humanity has just been told
that you are sharing
visions with the enemy?
What would you do,mr. Adama?
Would you think that the
gods were testing you?
So Baltar is telling the truth?
Is it true?
Yes.
Demetrius reports their sys ops will
be synced with ours in five minutes.
When you came knocking with that
raider and asked for our help,
you gave away the future of
all the cylons aboard this ship.
You know that,right?
I gave it to the right person.
Save it.
No guarantees.
When we meet up with the colonial fleet,
I don't know if they'll feed
you or frak you,all right?
Since you've been calling
the plays up till now,
I'm assuming you're doing the talking.
Good.
Gods help us.
Sys ops of both vessels are synced.
We're as ready as we're ever gonna be.
Good.
Tell the Demetrius to
set the board to green.
Unless both ships jump in together,Galactica
will blow us out of the sky.
Demetrius,Athena.
Set your board to green.
Athena,Demetrius. Starting to green.
Let's run the horn,guys.
- Sublight.
- Go.
- Helm.
- Tactical.
- Go.
- Nav.
Ftl.
Spun up. Go.
Athena,Demetrius.
Board is green.
I was just thinking how
beautiful she must be.
Your daughter,Hera.
How do you know her name?
We all know her name.
You were blessed.
all right,everyone.
Let's go home.
Demetrius,Athena.
Execute jump.
Clock is running.
10,9,8,7,6,5,4,3,2.Jump.
Sir,we had a problem with the sync
points and the jump coordinates.
It'll take a few minutes to
spool up the ftl drive again.
Gods damn it!
all hands. Battle stations!
Set condition one throughout the fleet!
Launch alert five.
Get me some more
frakkin' birds in the air!
Gun batteries stand
by for target bearing!
Demetrius,Athena. Report.
Baseship bearing 3-3-3
carom 4-9-8 at 15 msu.
Frakkin' thing is sitting
right on top of us.
Mr. Hoshi,order the fleet
to make an emergency jump!
all colonial vessels jump immediately
to emergency rendez-vous coordinates.
Sir,the president's shuttle is en route.
tell them to land on landing bay 1.
Checkers green.
Galactica,Athena.
Last jump must've cooked the wireless.
We've got no com.
They can't hear us.
Frak.
Galactica's scrambling vipers.
They're going to shoot us down.
What the frak?
Eight vipers inbound.
Entering firing range.
Where the hell is the Demetrius?
baseship targeted.
Weapons free.
Something isn't right.
Gunnery reporting. Firing
solution correct.
Main battery standing by
to fire on your command.
- on my command. 3,2,1.
- Weapons hold!
dradis contact!
Galactica,Demetrius,do not fire.
Baseship is disarmed and under
colonial command. Officers aboard.
Demetrius,Galactica.
Authenticate.
Galactica,Demetrius.
I authenticate.
Bravo,tango,8.
Do not fire.
Starbuck and Athena have
control of the baseship.
Battlestar
Galactica Season4 Episode07
colonel,they're with me.
They're with you?
So which one them shot Gaeta?
Lieutenant Gaeta,stay with us.
All right,everybody. Stand back.
And get a cut down
tray in here right now.
we became divided according to models.
The twos,eights,and
sixes have come to believe
that our destiny lies in
seeking out the final five.
The ones,fours,and fives
violently opposed such action.
We know that there are seven
different models of cylons.
You only mentioned six.
The 3s.
The D'Anna's.
They were boxed after the
battle on the algae planet.
Boxed?
Her entire line was
punitively deactivated.
Her consciousness placed
in a boxing facility.
Why?
D'Anna saw the faces of the
final five,which was forbidden.
But if we unbox her,she can
reveal their identities to us.
the final five have been to earth.
If we help find them,they
can help us get there.
Our ship can heal itself.
But most of our raiders
were destroyed in the ambush.
We're asking for your help
here. We can't do it alone.
What could possibly
motivate us to trust you now?
What have you got?
The boxing facility resides
within the cylon resurrection hub.
This hub controls the functions of
every resurrection ship in existence.
It protects itself by periodically
jumping to a new set of coordinates
and then relaying them
back to the baseship.
Madam president,you asked
for a reason to help us.
Vengeance.
You destroy the hub,cylons
lose their ability to download.
All of us.
Why would you be willing to
lose your ability to resurrect?
We're rebels.
We can't go back.
What matters most to us
is being with the five.
D'Anna will be able to identify them.
We'll take you to the hub
if you help us unbox d'Anna.
Give us the coordinates
of the hub first.
No,I won't do that.
I said we would take you there.
Take her out. We're finished.
Wait.
Is your word good,admiral?
I'll give you the coordinates.
But I want your word.
Stand down.
You have my word.
Once their identities are
revealed and we come back here,
we'll be free to leave
your fleet with the five.
Yes.
They're here with you.
The final five are in your fleet.
That's why our raiders turned
back the attack in the nebula.
The weapons hold.
How the frak did you see that?
To be absolutely honest
with you,bill,I didn'T.
What can I say?We got lucky.
Well,let's get a raptor up to those
coordinates that that cylon gave us.
Maybe we can get lucky again.
Sir.
Tigh.
Thank you.
Lords of Kobol,shield your eyes.
Get it with the gun camera.
Hit override.
Kinda pretty,isn't it?
Tell it to the fleet.
No. No. Don't put me under. Please.
Just... just numb everything.
- Felix.
- Just do it.
I- I don't want to wake up... I don't
want to wake up with my leg gone.
Okay,son.
If we go in on our own horse,we
won't last five minutes.
But we go in with that
baseship parked out there,
nobody's gonna notice us for awhile.
What do we fight with?Their
raiders are frakked.
We don't use theirs.
We use ours.
Take half the viper wing.
- Half the wing?
- Yeah.
We'll sneak them in
on the rebel baseship.
Hoshi did some calculations
from racetrack's photos.
We take out the ftl
and the hub's stranded.
We blow the hub and,uh,billions of
skin jobs lose their bath privileges.
imagine.
Once they're gone,they can't come back.
Mortal enemies.
Before we blow the hub,we need
to get a team in to unbox d'anna.
Well,now,maybe we just don'T.
Maybe we just forget the
gods damn boxing facility.
Lie to the rebels.
Well,they're lying to us.
The skin jobs said their raiders won't
fight because the final five is here?
We tangled with those slit-eyed
black bastards for three years now,
and they haven't turned
back before. Why now?
What if they're telling the truth?
What if the final five are here?
The five could know the way to earth.
If they knew,they're
not gonna lead us there
after we've just destroyed
their resurrection capacity.
Maybe they're different,like the rebels.
What if they're not?
What if their sole
purpose is to destroy us?
I say we blow the whole
gods damn thing to dust...
lock,stock,and barrel... and
trust the president's vision,
her scriptures,her way to earth.
Why don't we split the difference?
Unbox d'Anna and find the five.
Keep the five till we get to earth.
Turn them over to the rebels.
They've waited this long.
It'll be on our terms.
It's all pie in the sky,gentlemen,until
we know what's true and what's not.
And we put a lid on it.
The real plan stays in this room.
If the plan gets leaked to
the cylons,all bets are off.
Have someone escort the rebel
leader back to her baseship
so she can inform her
people they have a deal.
"In 36 hours,"the colonies will unite
forces "with insurgent rebel cylons
and their leader
"in an unprecedented
joint military operation
"to destroy the cylons'
ability to download into.
" blah blah blah.
Why weren't we consulted?
I'm sorry.
I'm in the dark as much as all of you.
you know,if they unbox the D'Annas,at
least we'll find out who the fifth one is.
All that's gonna do is
crowd the airlock a little more.
Do you think they're gonna give you a
medal when they find out who you are?
what about you?
He sings,you know.
- What?
- Gaeta.
Whenever he feels the tingling.
Whenever he feels his phantom leg.
Cottle says it helps him get through it.
He sings.
Good morning.
Morning.
What is it about the Galactica
that gives you such a glow?
I come over here,it's like I'm
going from one dungeon to the next.
Oh,I hadn't noticed.
But thank you.
You ready?
Yes.
I want you to find out who's
behind the shared vision rumors.
Who's talking to him?
With Baltar?
You're sleeping with him,right?
Don't.
I've just been informed that
you've been spotted down there
enough times to be a charter
member of his nymph squad.
All right.
I have come to believe in
Baltar's spiritual message.
I don't know how or why.
It just happened.
I wish you knew how many
times I wanted to tell you.
Your friendship and
your trust means... frak.
Clearly my friendship
and trust mean frak.
And I don't really care if
you have to spend the night
on your knees praying
or just on your knees.
I want a name.
I want to know who's
responsible for these lies.
Madam president.
Laura,I am so sorry.
You have a job to do.
The humans are never going to allow us
to have the final five
and go our own way.
Are you sure of this?
Not entirely.
I'd rather be wrong.
But we need insurance.
Trust has to begin somewhere.
Not with us.
It's our ship.
When we jump,we take control
of it with the centurions.
We carry out the mission as promised.
But when we return,we take hostages.
The humans on this ship stay on
this ship until we have the five.
Look at me.
We've changed,but the humans haven'T.
We've come too far to risk
everything on their trust.
alone she sleeps in the shirt of man
with my three wishes
clutched in her hand
the first that she be spared
the pain that comes from a dark
and laughing reign when she
finds love may it always stay true
what a way to discover
such a beautiful voice,huh?
How'd you find me?
Your chief of staff.
Needs to be horsewhipped.
If you came down here to kiss my ass
to get information,save your breath.
The quorum's considering a vote
of no confidence against you.
I won't compromise the
success of this operation
or the safety of this
fleet to indulge the
neediness of 12 perpetually
unhappy representatives.
I can'T.
I was with them on
the,uh,emergency jump.
And I saw something in
the faces of the delegates.
It wasn't the anxiety from waiting.
It went beyond that.
I was anxious.
It was my first time.
But they... they.
they were empty.
The quorum had given up.
And then it struck me that after going
through the same routine so many times,
it was the only way that they
could cope with the uncertainty.
To presume the worst.
You felt their suffering.
Now try holding their
lives in balance every day.
Talk to them.
You don't have to tell them everything.
I know how it works.
Just talk to the quorum.
Let them put a face
to this joint mission.
Let them hear from the cylon leader.
Anything.
Anything to put their fears to rest.
What's the matter?
- Nothing.
- No,nothing.
Nothing at all.
We've been lying here doing nothing.
What?
You've been lying about the
president sharing visions with cylons.
That happens to be
the god's honest truth.
Sorry.
I can't accept what you've done.
What... what I've done?
What have I...?
What are... where's this coming from?
These rumors you've started.
I've seen what they've done to her.
You seriously believe that
I'm making all this up?
I am not saying I'm not
capable,but why would I?
Six revealed it.
Caprica six revealed them
to me through my attorney
in the last days of my trial when
a guilty verdict was a certainty.
I suppose I could've gone public.
- Caused a stir.
- And all this time,you kept quiet.
I'm not saying I'm a saint,tory.
I'm many things.
But I try not to be spiteful.
Got no bloodlust to go get her.
But she's a hypocrite.
The lies.
The secret missions.
Co-opting the rhetoric of patriotism to
keep everyone in the dark,including you.
That's rather worrying,isn't it?
So I had to speak.
The truth is,no good ever
comes from concealing it.
I've got a broadcast.
The first that she be spared the pain
that comes from a
dark and laughing reign
when she finds love
may it always stay true
this I beg for the
second wish I made too
I didn't come here to beg or plead
or apologize or to keep my job.
You know me better than that.
And I didn't come here to create sympathy
by parading my illness in front of you.
On the contrary,there are some
that probably believe that
along with my cancer and drugs,
I have inoculated myself
against compassion.
That is a joke.
I am here because I want
to tell you face to face
that I believe in this mission
and what it means for our future.
I'm here to profess my
trust in our new allies.
I'm here to ask you to listen.
I'm here to ask for your support.
Bring her in.
In our civil war,we've seen death.
We've watched our people die.
Gone forever.
As terrible as it was beyond the
reach of the resurrection ships,
something began to change.
We could feel a sense of time,as if
each moment held its own significance.
We began to realize that for our
existence to hold any value,it must end.
To live meaningful lives,we
must die and not return.
The one human flaw that you spend
your lifetimes distressing over...
mortality... is the one thing.
well,it's the one thing
that makes you whole.
I believe it was no accident
that we were found by Kara Thrace.
It was destiny.
She asked me to leave
my people,and I accepted.
No matter what the sacrifice
even if it should mean my death.
thus shall it come to pass.
The dying leader shall know
the truth of the opera house.
You are the harbinger
of death,kara thrace.
Our destiny.
Our future.
Begins here.
Thank you for giving me
the opportunity to speak.
take her out.
But wish no more my
life you can take to have
her please just one day
wake to have her please
alone she sleeps in the shirt of man
with my three wishes
clutched in her hand
Hera!
Hera.
Bye-bye.
I gotta hand it to you.
If you are a cylon,that
was a great plan.
Dangle yet another way to earth.
Throw in the hub,the final
five,and the real kicker,
put the final five on the fleet.
Even I couldn't pass that one up.
You are having those visions,aren't you?
Thus shall it come to pass.
The dying leader shall know
the truth of the opera house.
What did you say?
Thus shall it come to pass.
The opera house.
The dying leader shall know
the truth of the opera house.
Where did... where did you hear that?
Who told you that?
The hybrid from the baseship
before they unplugged it.
The hybrid.
How does the hybrid
know what's in my dream?
I wish I knew.
This has got to stop.
These visions.
I've got to find out
about these visions.
I've got to know.
Will you help me?
Yes.
Find captain Agathon.
when I spoke to the
quorum,I could feel it.
The contempt.
You were right.
They're not ready to trust us.
No,I was wrong.
We're not ready.
We're deceiving them.
For protection.
For necessity.
Out of suspicion and fear.
Why haven't the final five come forward?
What if they're watching,judging
us on our actions?
We're about to resort
to violence and coercion.
What if they refuse to come with us?
We can't do this.
It's too late.
We have to order the
centurions to stand down.
It's too late.
They're committed.
Then we have to tell
the humans the truth.
No,you can't do that.
They'll never trust us again.
They already know the coordinates.
They'll just go destroy everything.
Go.
Stall for time.
Talk to Adama.
Tell them anything.
Anything but the truth.
I'll deal with the centurions.
Of course.
Have a seat.
We're going to settle this now.
What's to settle?
Your chief of staff is
incomparably talented.
I've been sharing visions with
Sharon Agathon and the six.
So I was only speaking the truth.
Yes.
The hybrid on the baseship spoke of
an opera house and a dying leader.
We're going to talk to the hybrid.
And why would you require my presence?
Because you're in my visions.
What are you doin',baby?
Are you drawing?
Can I see what you drew?
Oh,no.
No!
Why?
Hera?
Hera!
Raptor 1-2-4,you are
cleared for landing...
Hera!
Hera.
Have you seen my daughter?
No,I haven'T.
Hera!
I can't find hera.
Get away from my child.
Get your hands off of my child.
Athena.
Stay back!
Stay away.
Stand down!
Plug it in.
I need to talk to it.
Let god's will be done.
Shut up.
It's time to get some answers.
Tyrol,will you come in
here and take hera,please?
Just do it,tyrol.
Is she gone?
Yeah.
You are never gonna take my child.
We didn't come here to.
JUMP!
To have her please just one day wake
to have her please just one day wake