No, it's "Wo de ming
zi shi Sheldon."
What's this?
That's what you did.
I assumed as in a number of languages,
that the gesture was part of the phrase.
Well, it's not.
How am I supposed
to know that?
As the teacher, it's your obligation to separate
your personal idiosyncrasies from the subject matter.
You know, I'm really glad
you decided to learn Mandarin.
Why?
Once you're fluent,
you'll have a billion more
people to annoy instead of me.
Hey.
You just called Leonard
a syphilitic donkey.
My apologies, Leonard.
I'm only as good as my teacher.
Why are you
learning Chinese?
I believe the
Szechuan Palace
has been passing off orange
chicken as tangerine chicken,
and I intend to
confront them.
If I were you, I'd be more concerned
about what they're passing off as chicken.
I need to use your window.
-Oh, hey. Yeah, No, sure. Go ahead.
Hey, jerk face,
you forgot your iPod!
What's going on?
-Oh, I'll tell you what's going on.
That stupid self-centered bastard
wrote about our sex life in his blog!
Drop dead, you stupid
self-centered bastard!
Thank you.
Okay, where were we?
Not now. I have a blog to find.
The Big Bang Theory
Season 1 - Episode 17 (Finale)
Sync: WorkBook
- www.Qsubs.co.il -
+
Penny, are you okay?
I'm fine, Leonard.
Just go away.
Look, I understand that breaking up
with someone can be very painful...
Go away!
-Okay. Feel better! Bye.
She doesn't want to talk.
Not surprising.
Penny's emotional responses
originate in the primitive portion
of the brain known as the amygdale,
while speech is centered in the
much more recently developed neo-cortex.
The former can easily
overpower the latter,
giving scientific credence to the
notion of being "rendered speechless."
Or maybe she just doesn't want
to talk.
Hey, look, I found an iPod.
It's smashed beyond repair.
What are you gonna do with it?
What else? Sell it on eBay
as "slightly used."
It was Penny's boyfriend's.
They broke up.
Apparently, he posted intimate details
of their physical relationship on his blog,
which I cannot find anywhere.
You know what? I'm gonna go back
and try talking to her again.
Good idea. Sit with her,
hold her, comfort her.
And if the moment feels right,
see if you can cop a feel.
I'm not going to
do that, Howard.
I'm not aware
of any social convention
that requires you
to intervene at all.
What about "damsel in distress"?
12th-century code of chivalry?
Not exactly current.
You'd also have to be knighted
for that to apply.
I don't care. She's upset.
I'm going over there.
Remember to sit on your hands a bit
so they're warm.
I'm her friend. I'm not going to take
advantage of her vulnerability.
Wha...? So you're saying
if in the depths of despair
she throws herself at you
and demands you take her,
right there, right now,
you'll just walk away?
I said I'm her friend,
not her gay friend.
Hey, listen, I know you said that
you didn't want to talk... -I don't.
Sorry.
Wait? Did you say "wait"?
Tell me the truth.
Am I just an idiot who picks
giant losers?
No, no.
-Okay.
So I pick good guys,
but turn them into losers?
Of course not.
Well, it's got to be
one or the other. Which is it?
I'm sorry.
What were the choices again?
I really thought
Mike was different.
I thought he was
sensitive and smart.
I mean, not you smart--
normal non-freaky smart.
Yeah. No, sure.
You know,
and then he just goes and has to
humiliate me by writing about me on his blog
so the entire world can read it.
I tell you, it's not all
that easy to find.
Yeah, really? Well, my friends at
work found it. my sister found it.
Judging by my email, a number of prisoners
at the Michigan State Penitentiary found it.
What exactly did
this guy write?
Not that I need to know the details
of your sex life. I just thought...
Never mind.
No, you know what?
you might as well read it.
Everybody else has.
Go ahead.
Oh, God, I just feel so betrayed
and embarrassed!
I just want to crawl
into a hole and die!
Okay. Well, you know
this isn't that bad.
It just paints the picture
of a very affectionate woman,
who's open to expressing her affection
in non-traditional locales.
Oh, God!
Elevators, parks,
movie theaters.
Out of curiosity,
is this "subway" the transportation system
or Subway the sandwich shop?
Sandwich shop.
Doesn't that violate
the health code?
No, at the sub shop
we were only making out.
Ah, okay.
But my point is that
you have absolutely no reason
to be embarrassed.
Really? Do you think
I overreacted?
Maybe a little. -Because I do that.
I do overreact.
Maybe I should call Mike
and apologize.
No, no, no. That, that would
be under-reacting.
He did break the implied
confidentiality of the bedroom.
And in your case, the elevator,
parks and fast food franchise.
You're right. I should just say
"I am done with him."
Yes, you should.
Go ahead, say it.
But I never gave the man
a chance to explain.
What is there to explain?
It's all right here. The betrayal!
No, you were right
the first time.
This is a man who loves me,
but in his own stupid way,
which is trying to show people
how he feels.
I'm pretty sure
I never said that.
No, you did better than that.
You helped me see it on my own.
Oh, good for me.
Where are you going?
I'm going over to Mike's.
Leonard, thank you so much.
-Oh, sure.
Maybe I am her gay friend.
Howard, I'm going to need
another Mandarin lesson.
I obviously didn't make
my point with those people.
For God's sake, Sheldon, if you
don't like the tangerine chicken,
don't order
the tangerine chicken.
I like tangerine chicken, I'm just
not getting tangerine chicken.
Can we please change
the subject?
Sure.
Tell us again how you screwed up and got
Penny back together with her old boyfriend.
Just roll the dice.
"Enslaved by warlocks.
Stay here until you roll
"two, four or six."
-She was mad at him!
She was done with him!
The relationship was broken beyond repair,
and I walked over there,
and I fixed it.
Boy, that story gets better
every time you hear it.
Actually, I thought the first two
renditions were far more compelling.
Previously, I felt sympathy
for the Leonard character,
now I just find him
to be whiny and annoying.
Eat your tangerine chicken.
I'd love to, but I don't
have tangerine chicken.
Thank you so much
for your stupid advice!
Incredible.
You managed to screw
up the screw-up.
I'm back.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
It's not your fault.
What happened?
Well, I went over to Mike's to make up
with him. -Yeah. No, I know that part.
But he had already moved on.
Already? That was quick.
That's what I said to the woman
who had her legs arond his neck.
Penny, I am so sorry.
How could he do that?!
Well, you know, you did
throw an 80-gig iPod...
Yeah, no, how
could he do that?
I swear to God I am done
with guys like that.
You know, macho with the perfect
body and the hair and the money.
Yeah, that must get old quick.
You know, just once I would like
to go out with someone
who is nice and honest
and who actually cares about me.
What about me?
What about you what?
What about if you
went out with me?
Are you asking me out?
Um, yes, I am...
asking you out.
Wow.
I was just going off
your comment ae nice guy...
No, I know, I got that.
-You know, and honest. -Yeah, totally.
So, but...
it's no big deal.
Yes.
Yes what?
Yes, I will go out with you.
Really?
Yeah.
Why not? I mean...
what do I have to lose?
Yeah.
That's the spirit.
+
Show me your citrus peels.
I'm sorry.
Look, do you have second?
A second what,
pair of underwear?
I was just wondering if
I could talk to you.
It's about Leonard.
Why me? Why not
Koothrappali or Wolowitz?
Well, Raj can't talk
to me unless he's drunk,
and Wolowitz is, you
know, disgusting.
Yes, I suppose he is.
All I'm saying is,
you know Leonard the best.
Not necessarily.
I'm often surprised by
my lack of familiarity with Leonard.
Just the other day I discovered
he not only has a loofah,
he hides it.
Why do you suppose a man would be
ashamed of having a loofah?
I, myself, prefer to have
my excess epithelial cells
slough off naturally,
but I don't condemn
those who seek
to accelerate the process.
...and until recently
I had no idea
that despite his
lactose intolerance,
he can tolerate small
amounts of non-fat ice cream
without producing a noxious
gas that I maintain,
in the right concentration,
could be weaponized.
Leonard might come home.
Can we talk in my apartment?
We're not done?
No.
Eh, why not? We're already through
the looking glass anyway.
Okay, so here's the thing...
I guess you're aware
that Leonard asked me out.
Well, he didn't actually
say anything,
but when he came back
to the apartment
he was doing a dance that brought
to mind the happy hippos in Fantasia.
Oh, that's nice.
Anyhow, the thing I wanted
to talk to you about is,
you know, since Leonard
and I have become friends...
I was just...
You want to sit down?
Oh, I wish it were that simple.
See, I don't spend much time here,
and so I've never really chosen a place to sit.
Well, choose.
There are a number
of options, and...
I'm really not familiar enough
with the cushion densities,
air flow patterns and dispersion
of sunlight to make an informed choice.
All right, why don't you
just pick one at random
and then if you don't like it you can
sit somewhere else next time.
No, no. That's crazy.
You go ahead and talk
while I figure it out.
Okay.
Um, here's the thing.
So I've known for a while now
that Leonard has had
a little crush on me...
-A little crush?
Well, I suppose so, in the same way Menelaus
had a "little crush" on Helen of Troy.
All right, yeah, I don't
really know who they are, but...
Well, Menelaus was the brother of Agamemnon...
-I don't care. I don't care. Listen.
The point is,
Leonard isn't the kind of guy
I usually go out with.
anyone usually goes out with.
Would you be open
to rotating the couch
clockwise 30 degrees?
No. What I'm saying is
Leonard might be
different in a good way.
Obviously, my usual choices
have not worked out so well.
Your last one worked
out well for Koothrappali.
He got a free iPod.
Oh, glare.
But on the other hand, if things
don't go well with Leonard,
I risk losing a
really good friend.
I mean, I'm guessing he's not
looking for a fling.
He's the kind of guy that
gets into a relationship for...
I don't know,
like you would say,
light years.
I would not say that.
No one
would say that.
A light year is a unit
of distance not time.
Thank you for the clarification.
Draft.
you see, people hear the word "year"
and they think duration.
"Foot-pound" has the same problem--
that's a unit of work, not of weight.
Right. Thanks.
-It's a common mistake.
Not the first one
I've made today.
Okay...
I think this will be my seat.
Sheldon, do you have anything to say
that has anything to do with, you know,
what I'm talking about?
Well, let's see...
We might consider
Schrodinger's cat.
Schrodinger?
Is that the woman in 2A?
No, that's Mrs. Grossinger.
And she doesn't have a cat,
she has a Mexican hairless.
Annoying little animal. Yip, yip...
-Sheldon!
Sorry, you diverted me.
Anyway, in 1935,
Erwin Schrodinger,
in an attempt to explain the Copenhagen
interpretation of quantum physics,
he proposed
an experiment
where a cat is placed in a
box with a sealed vial of poison
that will break open
at a random time.
Now, since no one knows when
or if the poison has been released,
until the box is opened,
the cat can be thought of
as both alive and dead.
I'm sorry.
I don't get the point.
Well, of course you don't get
it; I haven't made it yet.
You'd have to be psychic to get it,
and there's no such thing as "psychic."
Sheldon, what's the point?!
Just like Schrodinger's cat,
your potential relationship
with Leonard right now
can be thought of
as both good and bad.
It is only by opening the box
that you'll find out which it is.
Okay, so you're saying I should
go out with Leonard.
No, no, no, no, no.
Let me start again.
In 1935, Erwin Schrodinger...
Two seats right there.
Chung shu shway?
Shay shay.
Sheldon, I think I've
made a mistake.
I can see that. Unless you're
planning on running a marathon,
choosing both stuffing and mashed
potatoes is a starch-filled redundancy.
No, it's about Penny.
A mistake involving Penny...
Okay, you'll have
to narrow it down.
I don't think I can go
out with her tonight.
Then don't.
Other people would
say "Why not?"
Other people might
be interested.
I'm going to talk anyway.
-I assumed you would.
Now that I'm actually
about to go out with Penny,
I'm not excited-- I'm nauseous.
Ah, then your meal choice
is appropriate.
Starch absorbs fluid which
reduces the amount of vomit
available for violent expulsion.
Right. -You also made
a common grammatical mistake.
You said "nauseous,"
when you meant "nauseated."
But go on.
Sheldon, this date is probably
my one chance with Penny.
What happens if I blow it?
Well, if we accept your premise
and also accept the highly
improbable assumption
that Penny is the only woman
in the world for you,
then we can logically
conclude that the result
of blowing it would be that
you end up
a lonely, bitter old man
with no progeny.
The image of any number
of evil lighthouse keepers
from Scooby-Doo cartoons
comes to mind.
yy
You're not helping.
All right, what response on my part
would bring this conversation
to a speedy conclusion?
Tell me whether or not
to go through with the date.
Schrodinger's cat.
Wow, that's brilliant.
You sound surprised.
Ho-tsu shway zai li-toe.
Hi.
-Hi.
Come on in.
-Thank you.
You look very nice.
Thank you.
So do you.
I made an 8:00 reservation.
-Okay, yeah, great.
Listen, um...
maybe we should talk first.
Okay.
But before you
say anything,
have you ever heard of
Schrodinger's cat?
Actually, I've heard far too
much about Schrodinger's cat.
Good.
All right, the cat's alive.
Let's go to dinner.
+
sai nar! Bee ti!
Xing gan jing bi ti
hou quai zoui.
Zhe bu shi lui
ding jiao ta che!
Crazy man.
Call the police!
Bu bie da gei tu shu guan.
Bee ti tsai nar!
Man niu zai wo chuang shang!
Hen duo hen duo man niu!
Ai yah!
Sync: WorkBook
- www.Qsubs.co.il -