O.C
I'm pregnant.
Oh, my God.
That's what I said.
I want to see Ryan.
It's too soon.
I worked so hard...
Not for you, for me.
She is the girl for me.
You're going to ask her
to marry you?
Julie...
KAITLIN:
Are you cheating on Bullit?
No!
Will you marry me?
Oh, my God.
Really?
Nothing?
It may not sound
like a good idea.
It's not a good idea.
We're dating. We just
got back together, in fact,
and you're proposing that for
Valentine's Day we do nothing.
No, no.
We don't have
to spend the night apart.
We could just hang out.
Uh, see a movie.
Oh, God, stop.
My head is spinning
from all of the romance.
Taylor,this holiday, us,
it's a recipe for disaster.
Why? 'Cause I'm needy?
'Cause I've on occasion
been known to stalk you?
There's me, too.
I'm distant
and unemotional.
And preoccupied.
Could we add that to the list?
'Cause it just seems
like lately your mind is
someplace else.
Taylor.
(sighs)
There's no hidden
meaning here.
I just feel if we don't
put too much pressure
on this holiday, we might
actually get through it.
So I shouldn't worry?
No.
Not even when I find a suspicious address
by your bed?
I looked at it when you were
in the bathroom.
Sorry.
It's nothing.
It's an address.Not the address
of some other girl if that's what
you're thinking.
Look, um, I got
to get to work,
but I promise you there's
nothing to worry about, okay?
Okay.
All right.
So we're good?
Yeah, we're good.
All right.
Oh.
Taylor, right?
So it's you.
The O.C.
-=The Last Fantasy=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:Allen
-=www.eastgame.net=-
--I-I don't get it.
Ryan hasn't been
to see you at all?
Well, I left a message with him
when I,when I switched hotels.
I told him I was here
in case he wanted to see me,
but so far,no luck.
Taylor, don't mind me asking...
what are you doing here?
Well, I found this
address by Ryan's bed
and he's been kind of distant lately,
so I thought it may be a clue.
So I came here and then I...
I have emotional problems,
but I'm getting over it.
Well, I'm glad Ryan at least
kept my address,
since, you know,
he's not using it.
Well, clearly he wants
to reach out.
Maybe he's just afraid
or he doesn't really
know how to do it.
Because, you know, I'd love
to talk to him, you know?
Apologize again for that
cancer stunt.
But I'm scared if
I make the first move...
He's going to pull away.
Yes, you're absolutely right.
I've had a lot of experience
with that.
Wait a sec.
Idea coming in.
And here it is, okay.
What if I were to get involved?
I could help you guys
smooth things over,
broker the
peace talks...
You-you'd be willing to do that,
get in the line of fire?
It's just that there's something
kind of, kind of sad about Ryan.
Maybe if he was to mend
his relationship with you,
he could be a little happier.
Well, I am all for it.
Do you have a plan in mind?
Always.
Wow, is this a second breakfast
or an early lunch?
It's either one.
I was craving French toast,
do you want some?
No, thanks.
I'm having flashbacks to when
you were pregnant with Seth.
I know, and all I did was eat
peanut butter and jelly
sandwiches.
I made some of my finest
sandwiches in that year.
Mm-hmm. I haven't had
peanut butter and jelly since.
I can't believe
we're doing this again.
All the times we tried
to have another one
after Seth.
Well, we did have a second one,
it just came later in life.
Ah, the more the merrier.
Oh, I just lost my appetite.
I thought you were starving.
Cravings, up and down
like a roller coaster.
I'm going to get dressed.
Gordon, it's not
Valentine's Day yet.
I don't care, you're my wife,
and I'll give you roses
anytime I dang well please.
Right. Well, these
are certainly beautiful,
but um, I think
I need to remind you...
Oh, I know.
You haven't given me the green
light on that marriage proposal.
But I didn't make $900 million
by being a pessimist.
Did I mention that there
will be no pre-nup?
Well... That is
so generous.
But before we get on with
the rest of our lives...
Right, Valentine's Day,
and I made reservations at the
yacht club as per your request.
And I did take the liberty
of booking us,
that's you and me,
a suite at the Four Seasons.
I mean, here we are,
practically man and wife
and we still haven't
sealed the deal.
I guess I'm just old-fashioned
that way.
Well, if I do say so myself,
you're in for quite a treat.
Can we just not
talk about it?
Well, I can sum it up
in one word.
Don't.
Bang.
Yeah.
(both chuckle)
Oh, sorry, gorgeous.
I'm just a sucker
for that pun.
But seriously now.
I can't wait to take you
down to Chinatown.
Right.
Me, too.
Kaitlin, baby, hi.
Hi.
What's up, nerd?
Wow, who you calling
nerd, bird legs?
You, nerd.
Okay, squirt, you up
for some ping-pong?
You ready to get
your ass kicked?
In your dreams.
You two play ping-pong?
Oh, yeah. We got a table
at the office and Peanut is
getting pretty good.
You think that's lame?
No, it's, it's...
It's like totally normal.
Mom, it's just ping-pong.
There's no reason to get
emotional about it.
Can I drive the Ferrari?
No.
Oh, what the hell?
Get her purring,
I'll be there in a second.
You're really good with her,
you know that?
Well, she's like her mom.
She's a special gal
and a real kick in the pants.
Bye, sweetie.
If the sea otters
disappear completely,
then the entire aquatic
ecosystem will be disrupted.
I know. We need the sea otters
to eat the sea urchins,
otherwise there'd be a sea
urchin population explosion,
causing some
catastrophe
involving the kelp forests.
I guess you're pretty sick
of me talking about otters.
Not at all.
If I have to share you, I'm glad
it can be with otters.
Well, did you know that
my Web site got over
8,000 hits yesterday?
And I'm going to have a video
conference with someone from
Greenpeace maybe next week.
Wow, I hope you can squeeze
me in for Valentine's Day.
Valentine's Day?
Yeah, it's in two days.
You forgot, didn't you?
No, of course not.
Here's a psychic, come on.
Do we have to?
Yes.
Rhode Island.
Not bad.
You'll go there
next year to study art.
You'll do well.
Huh. You're really
good, psychic lady. Do me.
Strong vibration from you, Miss.
Listen, you must
beware of falling objects.
Falling objects?
And you're going to
appear in the news
with Justin Timberlake.
Oh, good, okay, thank you
for your time.
Wait.
This is important.
I see the great love
of your life.
Me, too.
The name is
coming to me.
I see it.
Let me give you
a little help. Seth.
No.
Seth.
It's George.
George?
There's a lot of heat
surrounding this name.
You're leaving me for
a guy named George?
No.
She certainly is.
Your destiny
is with this George.
Okay, um, Seth why don't you
go get me some ice cream?
Okay. All right, listen,
psychic lady.
My boyfriend,
his name is Seth
and if anyone's my destiny,
it's him, so will you please
stop it
with all this
George stuff?
Sorry, Summer.
He did it.
No, you did it.
No, I didn't, you did.
You did.
What was that?
Destiny?
So this has nothing to do
with Valentine's Day?
No, why would you
think that?
Hmm, I don't know, you, me,
romantic dinner,
you have some sort
of surprise.
Hi, Ryan.
Hey.
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
Would you excuse us?
No problem.
Thanks.
At least it wasn't
a romantic surprise.
The note by my bed.
Yeah, I found it, I went
there and I found your dad.
And I don't know, I thought
maybe you were
trying to reconnect
with him.
Taylor, it's my business.
I know, I'm a meddler.
But don't worry, once
I lick my stalking addiction,that's next on the list.
But admit it, you can't tell me
you haven't been thinking about
him, right?
Ryan, come on,
it's just dinner.
Yeah, what are we going to talk about?
I've never met an awkward
silence that I couldn't fill.
Consider it your
Valentine's gift to me.
Oh, not that we're celebrating.
Yeah, I knew I was going
to pay for that.
Ryan, he's your dad.
Yeah, yeah, one dinner.
Okay.
RYAN:
Join us.
She gets her way, doesn't she?
The woman's a bulldozer.
So famous couples
through time?
Yeah, you know, Romeo and Juliet,
Fred and Wilma,
Sandy and Kirsten Cohen.
Do you think that's a good
idea for a collage?
Seth's going to love it.
And I'm very flattered that
Sandy and I made the cut.
Oh.
Whoa.
I have not looked at these
for a long time.
Gosh, check out
that permage.
Top Gun had just come out.
I wasn't thinking clearly.
I guess not.
(gasps):
Is that you
and Jimmy Cooper?
Holy guac.
Yeah, that's us at
a sweatshirt party.
And here we are at the prom.
Oh,
Seth and I have
the same picture.
Did you ever think
that Jimmy was the one?
Well, we had planned
our lives together.
He was going to work
for my father
and I was going to throw
fabulous dinner parties.
We even had names for our kids.
Then you broke up.
We grew up.
I loved Jimmy a lot
when I was your age.
But I changed.
So will you.
When you met Sandy how did you
know that he was the one?
I'd never imagined myself
with someone like Sandy.
But it just felt right.
Summer...
If you're meant to be with
Seth, it'll happen.
You just have
to be patient.
I'm not very good at that.
No one is.
FRANK:
So, nothing? Really?
No. Frank, Ryan thinks
it would be better
for our relationship
if we didn't celebrate
Valentine's Day at all.
It's counterintuitive,
I know.
How's that plan
working out for you?
Not great.
So Frank, how about you?
Speaking of romance...
you're single,
you're ruggedly handsome.
Did you start up any romances
with ladies in Newport?
Well, no. You know, not really.
Oh, my God, Frank,
you're in love.
Love? I am not.
Yes, you are.
It's all over your face.
Your lips are quivering,
your cheeks are rosy.
Yeah, your cheeks
are kind of red.
BULLIT:
Well, what the hell?
Frank Atwood,
how are you, bud?
I'm good, how are you, Bullit?
Uh, confused, that's how.
I thought when you quit
the Bullit business
you were going to high tail
it up to Reno.
Yeah, well, I just
stayed a little longer.
I wanted to spend
some time with my son.
This is your son?
Yeah.
Well, well, that's great.
Oh... here comes
the little lady.
Every ten seconds
she's in the john
painting her face,
not that I'm complaining.
A number that hot,
I don't ask questions.
Hey, Taylor, Ryan.
Hi.
Frank.
Julie.
I thought you were leaving town.
I was... am.
Am!
(stammers)
I'll be gone soon enough.
BULLIT:
Oh, Frank is
third-wheeling
on a date
with his son.
Well, we should get
to our table. I am starving.
BULLIT:
Yeah, and this
one can eat.
And if you ask me, it goes
to all the right places.
Gordon, please.
Well, enjoy your dinner.
Good-bye, Frank.
BULLIT:
Uh, later.
So should we get that check?
Oh, my God, Frank.
Yeah.
What?
Are you in love
with Julie Cooper?
--r dad
and Julie Cooper.
It's just so...
Incestuous, inappropriate.
Well, look at you being
all hyper articulate.
No, I was going
to say it's romantic.
How is it romantic?
It's over, she's
with somebody else.
Who she doesn't really love.
Well, maybe she
shouldn't marry Bullit--
doesn't mean she should
be with my dad.
What if they're meant
for each other?
If we could at least help
them get together,
then they could
have a chance.
Taylor, I remember
what he was like,
how he treated my mom and us.
Ryan. You have customers.
Hola, Luis.
Hey, Taylor.
I'll be right there.
I know Julie
isn't perfect,
but I also know my dad.
She deserves better.
Exactly.
Say, "Go Trojans."
BOTH:
Go Trojans!
Oh, so cute you guys are
going to college together.
Oh, Taryn, we wish you
were coming, too.
Aw, well, you know, my dad can't
just make a phone call
and get me into USC.
Oh, well,
c'est la vie.
Don't listen to her.
Sometimes I feel like
I'm going to be listening
to her snide comments
for the rest of my life.
Next year at this time,
we're going to have
a whole new life.
Without my dad.
Without Taryn,
just us... always.
SANDY:
Hey, baby.
Reservation for tomorrow night
at 7:00, is that okay?
Great.
What are you looking at?
Oh, just baby pictures of Seth.
I was feeling very nostalgic.
Oh, who could blame you?
He was a cute kid.
I should get ready,
I have a work lunch.
Dude, it's a psychic.
I know.
And Summer says
she's not worried,
but I can tell she is,
which is why I dug
into the archives,
and came up with evidence
that we are, in fact,
destined to be together.
It's a piece of
loose-leaf, crumpled.
I dug it out of a trash can nine
years ago.
Okay, explain that.
This, my friend,
marks the first moment
that I fell in love
with Summer Roberts.
It was the spring... 1998.
Is this a long flashback?
Because my break is almost over.
Bear with me.
It was the spring, 1998.
Hey, Luke...
Good news.
Only 11 months and six days
until The Matrix comes out.
Eat it, nerd brain.
We're going to start today
with more readings of
your original poems.
Who are we up to?
Summer Roberts.
Summer.
"I wish I was a mermaid
"and was friends with
all the fish
"A shiny tail and seashells
that would be my wish."
And that is when I knew
Summer Roberts was the one.
Dude, the flashback
did not take that long.
Hi, Julie.
Or should I say Mrs. Bullit?
Julie's fine.
I'm making smoothies.
You want one?
Yeah, sure.
So I haven't really talked to
you since you got engaged.
Congrats all over the place.
Well, thank you, but I'm
not exactly engaged.
I'm just mulling over Bullit's
proposal for a while.
What's there to mull?
I mean, you're totally
in love with him, right?
You probably can't stop
daydreaming about your
future together.
And just think,
for the rest of your life,
you get to be in
a bed with Bullit.
Suddenly not in the mood.
Night after night, you and
Bullit making love
into the wee hours.
You, exploring his body as
it gets older, and older.
The skin slackening,
you still having to perform
your wifely duties.
Taylor, stop.
Admit it, Julie, you've got it
bad for Frank Atwood.
What?
I saw your face last night.
You, Julie Cooper, have
a case of the Franks.
Okay, I do... I did,
or one time or another
may have had a case
of the Franks,
but for reasons that are
both personal and complex,
I'm staying with Bullit.
Julie, you're different now.
You are no longer the woman
who can marry for money.
You need more.
Taylor, I have a child.
I have no job.
I don't even own this house.
Besides, I don't think Ryan
would approve.
God knows I've put that kid
through enough.
Julie, Ryan's only
concern is for you.
He doesn't think his dad's
good enough for you.
Ryan Atwood is worried about me?
Yeah.
How about that.
NEWSCASTER:
Our answer, right after
this break.
(TiVo pausing)
Hey, what are you watching?
(sighs)
It's bad.
It's really bad.
Look.
Coming up next,
could this young woman
be the one to save
Newport sea otters?
Summer, you're a hero.
And guess who's bringing sexy
back to Newport?
That's right, Justin Timberlake
is coming to the Bait Shop.
Just how does such a small venue
get such big names?
(TiVo pausing)
Falling skateboards,
Justin Timberlake...
Everything the psychic
said is coming true.
You know, any second I'm just
going to get whisked away
by some dude named George.
Relax.
Now I know that psychic has
a lot of credibility.
She works at a kiosk,
and she doesn't appear
to charge for her services,
but I think I am a better judge
of whether you and I
are destined to be together,
than her. And I brought proof.
Happy early Valentine's Day,
Summer.
The mermaid poem.
That's how I knew,
even in fifth grade,
that you were the one.
That's pretty
awesome, huh?
Oh, my God.
I know.
I didn't write this.
What?
I remember that day.
Okay, Holly, watch this.
* Yo, I'll tell you
what I want *
* What I really,
really want. *
Oh, my God, Summer,
you are Scary Spice.
Ew, Taylor Dorkson alert.
Ew.
Hey, Summer, are you finished
with your poem?
What poem?
The original poem that
we're reading out loud.
We're going in alphabetical
order, and we're on "R."
I already finished mine,
even though I'm a "T."
I may spend my night
doing a polish.
Okay. We're going to start today
with more readings of your
original poems.
Who are
we up to?
Summer Roberts.
Summer.
Give me your poem.
Summer,
have you no ethics whatsoever?
Okay, you can come to my
birthday party.
Really?
Okay, here.
(paper rustling)
Summer, we're waiting.
(softly):
I wish I was a mermaid....
(sharply):
Speak up, Miss Roberts.
I wish I was a mermaid
and was friends
with all the fish.
A shiny tail and seashells,
that would be my wish.
Lovely.
But this mermaid poem is...
it's our roots,
it's our mythology.
What if our mythology is a sham?
Something that
we invented?
What if we are each other's
Jimmy Cooper?
What?
You know,
the one before the one.
The one that you think is right
before you meet
your Sandy Cohen?
Wait, are we saying that because
Taylor wrote the poem,
she's my Sandy Cohen?
Because as delicious a twist
as that would be,
it's not going to happen.
No.
What I'm saying is what if we're
not destined to be together?
That is your cue, Seth,
to say that I am wrong.
Mm-hmm.
I'm wrong, right?
Cue to say
I don't know anymore.
Julie,
we're about
to close up.
I just wanted to talk to you.
Look, I...
I know you told Taylor
that you were worried about me
being involved with your father.
Nah, that's okay, it's over,
so no need
to talk about it.
Right.
It is over between us.
Good, I'm glad.
But Ryan, I just wanted you
to know that...
I've been with my fair share
of bad guys,
and for the record,
your dad isn't one of them.
Hey.
Hi. So what's the plan?
The Frank and Julie plan?
Yep.
Yay, you're on board!
I talked to Julie.
So did I.
Lady has a case of the Franks.
But lucky for us it's
Valentine's Day tomorrow.
So she'll be going out
with Bullit, right?
We'll just get rid of Bullit
and then we will get Frank
and Julie together
for the most romantic night
ever.
So you come over after work,
and in the meantime,
I'll start making lists.
All right, I'll see you later.
Toodles.
'Sup?
Kaitlin,
were you... eavesdropping?
Look, my mom loves
the Bullit, okay?
He's rich and he's funny
and it's a total
slam dunk.
Okay, sweetie, it's a little
more complicated than that.
Not to me.
Listen, Townsend, I'm playing
for Team Bullit, okay?
And my team,
we always win.
Well, Ryan and I are playing
for Team Frank, and our team always wins.
That's funny,
because you're going down.
Are you threatening us?
Totally. It's war, bitch.
--Hi, honey.
Whoa.
Pancakes?
When is this Valentine's Day
tradition going to die?
I'm sorry that I've been babying
you lately.
I'm just feeling
a little motherly.
That's okay, I'm feeling
a little sulky,
so we're a good match.
Summer's going through
something, isn't she?
She's wondering if I'm her Sandy
Cohen or her Jimmy Cooper.
Well, I hope
I didn't worry her.
So how about you?
Are you okay?
Well, Summer and I have
this history,
or at least I thought we did.
These things
that happened to us
when we were kids
that convinced me
we were meant to
be together.
Now if those things turn out
not to be true...
Seth, how long have you dated
Summer?
Uh, February...
like a million years.
And in that time,
how many things has Summer done
to convince you
that she's the girl for you?
A lot.
So I think
you should focus on that.
The real Summer,
and not the one
that you worshipped
in grade school.
You know what I think?
What?
I think that you found
your Sandy Cohen.
Aw, aw, me, too.
Mm, Mom,
why'd you and Jimmy Cooper
break up, anyways?
It doesn't matter.
Sorry I'm late.
Your dad's working me
to the bone.
Not even paying you.
That's an internship
for you.
He'll make it up to me
after college
when I sign my life away
to the Newport Group.
Jimmy, we need to talk.
I don't know
if I can do this anymore.
Do what?
Us.
I need to end this.
What are you talking about?
We have a plan.
Go to college.
Come back here,
pick up where we left off.
Jimmy, on paper,
all of that makes sense.
But in my heart
it just doesn't feel right.
I don't understand.
You don't just wake up
one morning
and decide to change
your entire life.
Whatever it is,
we'll figure it out together.
It's already been figured out.
I know what
I want to do.
Kirsten, what's going on?
I got into Berkeley.
And you're going?
SUMMER: Don't you see we are
supposed to control
our own destiny?
Mm-hmm.
Or else what's the point of life
if it's just something
that happens to you?
Summer?
Hmm?
You have a visitor.
(whispers):
George.
Hi.
I'm Paul, I'm here for GEORGE.
George?
Yes, The Global Environmental
Organization
Regarding Greenhouse Emissions.
We've been reading your blog
about the sea otters.
I was in the area
and I'm here to offer you a job.
We'd like you
to come work for us.
Oh... GEORGE.
It doesn't matter who it is.
All that you need to know is
that the game has changed.
If you want
to marry my mom,
you're going
to have to step your game up.
Well, old Bullit knows how
to romance a lady.
I've been married five times.
Check this out.
Emerald earrings
for your mom,
matches her eyes.
Just toss these,
all right?
I want something better.
I want out-of-the-box thinking.
Hot air balloon ride.
Hot air balloon.
A blimp?
Oh, heck, squirt, all I care
about is that your mom is happy
and if I'm not
the man for that...
No, Bullit, buck up.
You want to marry
my mom, right?
Of course.
And you want to be my stepdad.
And play ping-pong with you
till I'm old and gray.
Hell, yeah. Let's go.
Then we need
to make a plan.
I want nothing less
than the most spectacular
Valentine's date ever.
Is one of those planes yours?
Two of 'em.
TAYLOR:
Okay, they're gonna
play the money card,
but we can play
the emotion card.
Am I right, Ryan?
Yeah, you're right.
Okay, Frank, tell me what it is
that you love about Julie.
Well, uh...
She's, uh...
I forgot what
we're dealing with here.
Atwoods on Valentine's Day.
I told you.
Look, I really
appreciate this, but you guys
don't have to do this for me.
It's not your job.
We want to.
Mm, text from Kaitlin.
"Y'all are going down.
Team Bullit."
Frank, if we're going to win,
you need
to give me something here.
Okay, Julie's amazing.
All right? She's...
she's pretty.
She totally gets me?
Come on.
Dig deeper here!
Look inside.
What is it that connects you
to her?
We're just...
from the same world.
You barely touched your chicken.
I guess I wasn't in
the mood for it.
Well, you're feeling nauseous
and tired.
So I can't expect you
to be dancing on the tables.
If something else
is bothering you, tell me.
I hate keeping secrets from you.
I didn't know you were.
There's one thing.
Something that I,
I never told you
Is this about Jimmy Cooper?
Can we get the check and talk
about this at home?
Thank you.
Mom, hold up.
There's been a change
in schedule.
Kaitlin, what's up?
We have way
cooler plans.
And your ride should be here
any second.
What is this?
What is this shirt?
Nothing, I'm just getting
in the spirit of things.
Last-minute ambush.
Should have seen this coming.
How'd you find us?
Taylor activated the
GPS on your phone.
Can I talk to you?
Damn GPS. I should
have thought of that.
What are you guys, the KGB?
What's going on?
I'll explain.
Mom, whatever he says,
do not listen to him.
Look, I know you
have plans tonight,
but I was hoping
you'd cancel them.
Oh, you found out about
my case of the Franks.
He's waiting for you.
He knows it's a long shot,
but I said I'd try
to get you to meet him.
I'll drive if you want.
Mom, come on, your ride's here.
Tell your dad that
in another life I'd be there.
I'm sorry.
Mm, told you, Atwood.
My team always wins.
I guess so.
Wait. What?
What the hell?
Driver, could you turn
the AC on, please?
(gruff voice):
Yeah, sure, Ms. Cooper.
--I cannot believe this.
Yeah, that's war, bitch.
(voice breaking):
God, Ryan,
how could
you be so mean?
I'm only 15.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
I don't know what I was
thinking.
Me, either.
You're going down.
Kaitlin...
I'm following your decoy limo.
Then I'll follow you!
JULIE:
Did Bullit buy me
a hot dog stand?
Uh, driver, I don't think
this is right.
You're here.
Taylor?
I don't know what to say.
What is all this?
Go, say it, like
we practiced. Go.
Okay.
Uh, this is sort of a testament
to where we came from.
But I really want tonight
to be about where
we could go.
It's just a promise ring.
I know it's not fancy.
I wish I could offer you more,
but this is all I have.
And that is
that I love you,
the real you.
Frank, I...
KAITLIN:
Mom,
the Bullit's waiting.
Frank, I'm sorry.
I have one daughter left
and she loves Bullit,
even if I don't.
I'm sorry, Frank.
And then after we had
Seth and we were trying
for a second and
nothing was happening,
I thought it was some
kind of karmic payback.
Well, now you know it
doesn't work like that.
Why didn't you ever say
anything?
Part of it was timing.
It had only been
a month.
But then the best thing in
the world happened to me.
Mondale and Ferraro.
Mondale and Ferraro,
path to equality.
No, thanks.
What are you,
a Republican?
Oh, I'm sorry, did you catch it
from your parents?
I hear it's hereditary.
I guess I did.
Well, if you don't want
a pamphlet, here,
have a pin, on me.
I might wear it, but only
because it's stylish.
You know, if you're
not a pamphlet reader,
I could take you to coffee...
...tell you all
about why Mondale and
Ferraro are gonna lose.
If you're so sure they're
gonna lose, why bother?
I don't know, it feels right.
So... coffee?
KIRSTEN:
I guess I had fate on my mind
when I got you this gift.
Where on Earth
did you find this?
I turned the house
upside down.
If it hadn't been for Walter
Mondale and Geraldine Ferraro,
there never would have
been a Seth Cohen.
There wouldn't be a Ryan.
And whoever this is
going to be...
All because of
that one day.
My lucky day.
Okay, I admit it--
I put way too much stock
into that poem.
I'm not the girl that
you thought I was.
You're not.
You, Summer, are better.
See, back then you were
just this fantasy.
You were this little girl,
who, when I would see,
you would either ignore me,
or make an obscene gesture
and keep on walking.
Yeah, I kind
of remember that, sorry.
But now look at you.
You fight for sea otters.
You've befriended
Taylor Townsend.
You're an incredible mom
to that bunny.
I guess I have changed.
You've evolved.
And over the last 950 days we've
been dating...
and, yes, I've counted,
and yes, I counted
the Zach era,
because, really,
who were we kidding?
...I've watched you grow
into this incredible woman.
And that is who I love.
Thanks, Cohen.
What's wrong?
I met GEORGE.
I'll kill him.
This guy came by from
GEORGE to recruit me.
He heard about my work with
the sea otters and invited me
to travel across the country
and talk to college kids
about voting next November.
What about Brown?
I'd have to defer a year,
live on a bus.
Sounds like a great gig.
I don't know that
we could see each other.
So you have to choose
between me and GEORGE.
That's the thing--
I don't know
that I have to.
I do believe that you are my
destiny, I do, Seth.
But I just don't know that
you're my only destiny.
Here.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Mm-hmm.
I picked couples through time.
Oh, and where
are we?
I was hoping that someday we
could go in the middle.
So can I tell you what
Bullit's surprise is?
I can't hold it
any longer.
Sure.
His plane is sitting on
the tarmac
gassed up and ready
to take you anywhere
in the world.
Mom, you're going to be spending
Valentine's Day
anywhere in the world
that you want to go.
I mean, that's
pretty amazing.
Yeah.
Yeah, it really is.
No.
Mom...
Squirt, where the
heck's your mom?
I know I asked you
to be my stepdad.
Do you mind being
my friend instead?
So Julie's had enough
of the old Bullit, eh?
We can still play ping-pong
together.
Come on.
You know, I let you win.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
In your dreams.
You ever see that
movie Casablanca?
No.
It goes like this:
Peanut, I think this
is the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
Come on, luck be a lady,
luck be a lady.
Oh!
I can't believe this,
I didn't win.
Shocking.
Well, if it's any
consolation, though,
this soft serv is outstanding.
Would anyone like seconds?
Yeah, I would.
Yeah, me, too.
Thank you.
Sorry things didn't work out
with you and Julie.
Hey...
I'm sitting here sharing
ice cream with my kid.
It's been a long time
since I've done that.
Tell me that's her.
That's her.
I'm suddenly nervous.
You're going to be great.
I'm having the strangest
craving for a corn dog.
There may be one left.
Seat?
How about that?
Fourth quarter, Team Frank
comes through in the clutch.
Oh, yeah.
True love on
Valentine's Day.
What more could
you ask for?
Yeah...
Hey, uh, so, you know,
we reserved the limo
for another two hours.
What do you say we drive
down the beach?
Uh, that sounds
suspiciously like
a Valentine's Day date to me.
I don't know, that
might make us break up.
What if I said...
...I had newfound faith?
I would say I agree.
I have newfound faith.
I agree.
Okay.
Onward, Jeeves. Yes, yes, yes,
to the beach.
-=The Last Fantasy=-
Proudly Presents