What the hell you doing here,boy?
You're on a date with my dad?
You know each other?
Kiss me.
-Uh, what?
-If you don't feel anything,
I will never mention it again.
One kiss.
www.1000fr.com Present
Capture:FRM@
Sync:FRM@openext
What's cooking, Ryan?
SANDY:
Hey, Ryan?
Ryan?
I shmeared it for you.
Thanks.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
I'm just gonna go see
if Seth's up.
I am up, and I'm out of here.
What? Where you going?
I didn't know you
were planning a trip.
Neither did Summer, but
RISD sent my dorm info,
so I figured I'd
check out my new home
and give her some moral
support for finals.
Are you gonna eat that?
Are you sure that's
such a good idea?
Why, did Ryan do
something to it?
No, not the bagel,
the trip-- I thought
you were gonna give Summer
some more space.
Well, a little space turned
into a lot of missing me.
That's my cab.
E-mail me a Christmukkah list.
I'm gonna be shopping
at the Providence Place Mall.
They have carpeting,
which is weird.
They have a Dave & Buster's,
but parking sucks.
Listen, dude, I really
need to talk to you--
it's very important.
Okay, and I want to
hear all about it
when I land in Providence.
Just call me.
Call me.
So we've had a chance to
review your situation,
and the board has come
to a unanimous decision.
Effective immediately,
you are suspended
from this university
until next fall.
Suspended?
Breaking into that lab
was very serious.
If it wasn't for your
excellent record,
the board might have
involved the police.
I'm sorry, um, I'm just not sure
what I'm supposed to do now.
It's done.
You can go to the dorm
and start packing.
But I have finals, and friends.
I'm afraid you're no
longer a student here.
But my dad is living in Seattle
with the step-monste
And Taylor Townsend
is sleeping in my old bed.
And Seth was moving out here
so we could be together.
Ms. Roberts,
you need to go home.
This is my home.
California, here we come
Right back where
we started from
California...
It's just you and me now.
Summer Bear.
So, I heard
the iron fist of justice
came crashing down on you
swiftly, without mercy.
Yep. Sounds like your plan
worked out perfectly.
Oh, come on, that's not fair.
Back at the reservation,
they taught us,
sometimes the weaker gazelle
must be devoured
for the good of the herd.
Oh, Che, just shut up, okay?
Before I tie you up
with hemp
rope, set you on fire,
and get high off the fumes
from your burning flesh.
Dark.
Mm.
I think the fact that
you would use hemp
proved that I have made a
difference
in your life.
Yeah, Che, you have.
You got me thrown out of school.
You know,
I really liked this place.
I liked
who I was becoming at it.
I mean, this was my life.
And you sacrificed it for the
good of the... the-the cause.
You're a martyr.
You're a hero.
I just wanted to be a student.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to find my roommate
and tell her that
she now has a single.
Are you dirty, Ryan?
KIRSTEN:
Ryan?
Hello?
Hey.
I-I couldn't help but notice
that you
wanted to talk to Seth.
Oh, did I?
Well, since he's
out of town
and he's gonna be
moving out next semester,
you're gonna need a new Seth.
Don't tell Sandy, but...
I thought I would audition
for the job.
Oh, uh, yeah, well, that's,
uh, very thoughtful.
So... how does it work?
Do I ask you
what's on your mind?
Uh, usually you talk
about yourself,
and I solve my
problems on my own.
I've noticed that you've been
spending time with Taylor.
Rea... Have I?
If we're gonna talk
about girls,
I am a far more knowledgeable
resource than my son.
Okay. But you can't
repeat this, all right?
Because if the real
Seth found out
I was telling the substitute
Seth a real secret...
It's in the vault.
Okay.
I kissed Taylor.
Or she kissed me.
Anyway, there was
a kiss, and, uh...
And now you can't stop
thinking about her.
Pretty much.
That is so cute.
Okay, Seth never
does that.
Sorry.
But it is, and so is she.
Yeah, I know, it's
just... me and Taylor?
After everything
you've been through
over the last few months,
if something good happens,
shouldn't you embrace it?
Or at least be open
to the possibility?
You're right.
You're right. Thanks.
Okay.
So do I get the job?
You're on the short list.
Spencer, what brings you
to Casa de Cooper?
Your racket.
You restrung it for me.
That's so sweet.
Yeah, I went with
the Pro-Flex Fiber Tour.
It should, uh... it should
cut down on the tension.
Good, because I've been having
a lot of stress lately.
I could use a little bit
of... relaxing.
String tension, Kaitlin.
Well, now that you
and my mom are over,
maybe you can help me
with my stroke.
Yeah, right.
Look, you got a great
backhand, but, uh,
no offense, I kind of have
a "no jail bait" policy.
Lame.
You know, maybe you
should try, uh,
try meeting guys
from your school.
-You mean boys?
-Exactly. Yeah, because
you're in high school.
You know, that place with desks
and chalkboards and kids.
Those are people
your own age.
I don't know, maybe...
maybe you should try
hanging out with them.
TAYLOR:Hi, Ryan.
I got to go, can't talk.
I'm-I'm not here
to see you.
I'm just covering for
Seth while he's gone.
That's nice.
Sorry that I kissed you.
What?
No, its... it's cool.
It's obviously not okay.
You're totally uncomfortable
around me now.
No, no. Um...
It's... the kiss
is not a problem.
Really? Good, because
usually when I kiss a guy,
it ends in tears.
His, not mine,
because, like,
I'm a bit of a lip biter
and, you know, sometimes
I draw blood and...
Taylor?
Yeah?
What are you doing tonight?
Oh, I'm updating my blog.
It's kind of
Felicity by way
of Anais Nin, the erotic memoirs
of a soulful college girl.
Taylor, tonight,
are you busy?
Oh. Blog, shmog.
-Is-is that a yes?
-Yes, it is a yes, squared.
In all caps, with
a exclamation mark
and a smiley-fed emoticon.
A simple yes will do.
Yes.
Great, all right, well,
I'll see you tonight.
Hey, do you just want to come
up to the comic book store?
There's a flat-screen TV,
SurroundSound,
a bevy of Blu-ray anime.
All right. See you then.
Hey, Eric.
Kaitlin, hey.
What are you doing here?
It seems like people at
this school like to watch
hairless wonders in banana slings.
I'm just trying to fit in.
Oh, cool.
Well, good to see you.
Ask her.
No, you ask her.
Do you bitches have a problem?
We saw you talking to Eric Ward.
Oh, my God, he is so hot.
Do you know him?
I know that his brother
shaves his chest.
Seriously?
That is so...
Gayer than his dad, I know.
You're Kaitlin Cooper,
aren't you?
Yes.
I'm Olivia.
This is Lea.
-Hi.
-Cool.
Do you guys think
anyone would notice
if I sparked a jay
up by the bleachers?
That is so totally illegal.
Is there a reason why you guys
aren't home right now?
Riley, hey! We-we...
Came to cheer on
your boyfriend.
Connor's doing awesome.
That's because he is awesome.
Now, get going.
Those party invites aren't
gonna address themselves.
Okay.
Okay, why do you guys
let her talk to you like that?
Well, she's having a
pimps and ho's party
for her sweet 16,
and it's gonna
be awesome.
But if we don't help out,
we don't go.
So don't go.
Yeah.
That would be social suicide.
Everyone who's anyone
at this school is
going to that party.
No offense.
Come on, Lea.
'Kay, well, if you guys
change your minds,
I'll be by the bleachers.
Sure.
Gotcha.
Hey, man, how's the
East Coast treating you?
Too soon to tell.
I had a layover in Salt Lake
and then I got delayed in Poughkeepsie.
It's hard to get a direct flight
last minute.
Yeah, well,
at least you made it.
Summer surprised to see you?
I'm headed over there right now.
I got an all-night study package.
I scored a brick
of Dunkin' Donuts coffee
and some reasonably priced meth
from this homeless guy.
Oh, I'm sure she'll appreciate
the pick-me-up, very thoughtful.
How are things with you?
I know you wanted to talk.
Things are weird.
And about to get a lot weirder.
That wasn't vague
or ominous at all.
I'll explain later.
Well, good luck.
Back at you.
I know you're unhappy,
but you've been out with
seven different men.
You mean seven versions
of the same man.
Republican
real estate developer
hates his ex-wife,
loves golf.
This is Newport.
You live in a monkey cage,
you have to date chimps.
Well, maybe you could throw
a gorilla into the mix.
I appreciate the analogy,
but, Pam, how do we fix this?
Find me a man
who will surprise me.
Someone different.
Her prayers have
been answered.
I tell you, the women are
well-preserved in this town.
If my slacks weren't
so damn tight...
Bullet, what are
you doing here?
I thought you were going
to be a silent partner.
Oh, I ain't here to work.
I came to see my girlfriend.
-What? No, I am not...
-Car's waiting outside.
Dinner's planned.
I'd invite Blondie,
but she don't look
much like an eater.
Oh, that's a shame.
I'm going to let you two
figure this out.
See you in the morning.
Kirs...
Okay, I'm not having
dinner with you.
A) You repulse me,
and B) I'm busy.
Well, A) that's cool;
2) busy doing what?
A client is unhappy
with our man base,
so I have to go on
a major recruiting mission.
Or you can just put them
in the Bullet's line of fire.
Okay, while the client is looking
for something out of the norm,
"lunatic" probably isn't her type.
-Have dinner with me.
-No.
-A cocktail?
-No!
Then let's just make out.
I can hurt you.
Wow.
Call me.
Isn't this just great?
I mean, did you ever think
that decapitation could be so beautiful?
How many times
have you seen this?
Oh, I watch it every night.
It helps relax me.
Is everything okay?
I'm sorry.
So that's a "no."
I can't do this.
Okay, um...
I've done my fair share of
misreading signs in my life,
but you asked me to hang out.
You sat next to me,
you leaned in with
a slight tilt to your head.
I know, I know,
and I'm sorry.
Uh, you're a great girl.
It's just,
this is too weird.
Well, that makes me
feel so much better.
Me!
Not you, me.
I'm... weird.
Surprise!
Cohen?
Cohen.
Hey, where are you?
Where are you?
I'm in your room.
Summer, I was going
to surprise you.
Well, I'm surprised.
Yeah, me, too.
Why aren't you in school?
Because I got kicked out.
Summer, what'd you do?
I listened to stupid Che
and his stupid plan,
and he sold me down
the stupid river.
I knew anyone that sincere
was not to be trusted.
I miss it already.
I don't know what to do.
Yeah, well, I do.
What?
If he hurt you,
then I'm going to hurt him.
That's funny, Cohen.
See, I knew you could
cheer me up.
I'm serious.
You can at least act like
it's halfway feasible
that I could avenge your honor.
What, you're serious?
No, no, no.
I'm going to go
so Ryan Atwood on his ass.
Come on, Cohen,
I don't like this.
Neither will Che.
No, wait, don't...
So Kirsten told me
she came in yesterday
and applied for the job
of substitute Seth.
She may have.
Well, you know, uh,
if anyone's qualified,
I think we all know it's me,
and I'm thinking the only
reason you didn't ask me
is because no interview
was necessary.
Yeah, well, it turns out I may
not have to fill the position--
I handled the whole
Taylor thing--
although it may be a little
awkward for a while.
Oh.
What happened?
Nothing happened.
Which was the problem for her.
Yeah, yeah.
But now I don't know.
I mean, at first I thought
I was just caught up in
the whole Volchok thing.
And then I thought the
problem might've been Taylor.
You know, because she can
be a little, uh, weird.
She's a touch eccentric.
But now I think
the problem is me.
Maybe it's too soon.
So keep it casual.
You know, just tell her you...
you need to be friends for now.
Yeah, that's a line
every girl loves to hear.
No, if it's the truth,
she'll understand.
Well, I don't have
any other choice.
All right,
I'll give it a shot.
Great, okay, listen,
if there's anything else
I can do for you,
I'll be in my room
reading comics
and listening to indie rock.
All right.
That was a good Seth.
Were you a good Ryan?
I was actually going
to borrow one
from the Julie Cooper playbook,
and wait till Che was asleep,
then smother him with a pillow.
Oh, my hero.
But the guy was at some
all-night candlelight vigil.
Still, he's got to sleep
sometime.
This place reeks of incense
and righteousness.
Oh, that's Che's musk.
Look, be careful.
He's not in his room.
Neither was your roommate
last night.
Yeah, that's because
she's a huge slut.
Wait a minute, what's this?
What, I don't know.
I'm on the phone, I can't see.
Hello, Seth.
News of your vendetta
has reached my ears.
Is that Che?
What's happening?
I'm a pacifist.
Until cooler heads prevail...
I will be underground.
Peace.
He's going to run?
That coward!
I'm going to watch it again
for background noise,
visual cues,
anything that might tip me off
to his whereabouts.
No, Cohen, Che has had
survival training, okay.
He's probably hiding in a cave
somewhere with Osama Bin Laden.
Look, forget about him.
I need you, and I'm here.
All right, but for the record,
I did not back down.
And I love you for it.
Come home.
Okay.
Summer?
What are you doing here?
Oh, I slept out here.
Turns out I like nature.
And Taylor's in my bed.
No, I mean, what are you
doing here in Newport?
Oh.
Long story.
Well, then if you need anything
or just want to talk,
I'm here for you.
Thanks, Julie.
And you should go
reclaim your bedroom.
Taylor has boundary issues.
Mm.
Is that a bunny?
Okay, so if I don't
call your name,
that means you're not coming.
All the hot senior guys
already got their invites.
Jeanie.
Kristen.
Sarah.
She's got to
invite us, right?
She'd better.
We stayed up all night
licking envelopes.
Alexis.
Michelle.
Shana.
And lastly, me, duh.
Wait, what about us?
Sorry,
but I didn't know
you'd ruin the envelopes
with your heinous saliva stains.
The whole school could get
gonorrhea of the throat.
But you promised!
I'm afraid it'd be unsanitary.
KAITLIN:
You guys can all come to my party.
It's tonight, my house.
Well, I rented out Hide,
and did you know that
Chef Hu yells at people?
He's making sushi,
and Danity Kane
is playing a 25-minute set.
Well, sushi's high in mercury,
and Danity Kane sucks.
I've got five kegs,
a quarter ounce
and absolutely no parents.
Sweet!
Bring whoever you guys want.
And don't worry about
any lame costumes.
Thanks.
Yeah, that was
really nice
inviting us
to your party.
It sounds like fun.
Oh, it will be.
You want to join New Match?
I don't understand.
The application fee
is rather steep,
and most of our female clients
are over 35.
Look, you need new recruits,
right?
So sign us up.
Here's a check to cover it.
And I believe this is for you.
Uh-huh, and I think
I know who it is.
Bang!
Am I good or am I good?
What do you think
you're doing?
Well, money may not buy
love or happiness,
but it'll buy a whole lot
of bachelors.
I think you owe me
a weekend as a thanks.
No, I can't.
I already have plans.
Cancel them.
I'm going away for the weekend
with Kirsten and Sandy.
To the Montage,
it's their anniversary.
You're celebrating
their anniversary?
They're having a recommitment
ceremony and, uh...
I am their witness.
Well, that's the sweetest thing
I've ever heard.
See you there.
The Bullet?
Bang.
Taylor.
Ryan.
Boo!
Didn't run away that time,
so you must not be
that scared of me.
All right, look,
I just wanted to come by and
apologize about last night, and...
And I didn't know
you had company.
Roger, Ryan.
Ryan, Roger.
-Roger.
-Ryan.
I've been helping Roger
track down this obscure
Kinji Fukasaku biography.
And it turns out he
watches Blood Bath IV
every night before
he goes to bed, too.
Well, that's...
Kismet? I know.
Maybe it's too soon
to talk about fate,
but...
Yeah, well, anyway,
I just wanted, you know,
to see if you need
a ride home or anything.
Oh, I got my bike, thanks.
Not you.
Well, that is very
friendly of you, Ryan,
since I'm assuming
that's what you want
us to be, just friends?
Well, if you're cool
with that.
Ryan Atwood,
"mon ami" sounds terrif.
But Roger and I
were just gonna
hang out
and, uh, order some takeout,
so if you don't mind.
All right, well, uh, you know,
I'll see you, then.
Bye, friend.
Bye, Ryan.
Nice to meet you, man.
Bye, Roger.
Let's come lat this.
I wanted to show you this.
I really think you guys
should work at this one.
This really why
you work here?
Yeah,
I talked to my dad today.
He was pretty
disappointed in me.
Well, I'm leaving the Antelope
Valley Airport now,
so there's just the $100 cab
ride home.
Just get here soon, okay?
Okay, I love you.
That was fast.
I've come to atone for my sins.
around the block with the kegs.
have to get my mr of h.
What, or convince her to let me
throw a huge party
with underage drinking?
Yeah, I have to get her out
of the house.
Are you going somewhere?
yeah, I'm go to the Mgeh
Sandy and Kirsten,
just for the weekend.
Going to a hotel
with Sandy and Kirsten?
They're not spg r
relationship up, are they?
Please, Sandy and Kirsten?
Yeah, they don't
exactly scream threesome.
Just hld y
So I guess I can assume
you'll be fine
without me this weekend?
Oh, I think I can survive.
Now, if you need anything,
Summer and Taylor
are in charge.
it, Summer's here?
Fine, Che, you're really
going to dehydrate,
ca oon the front lawn,
I'll get you some water.
Hi.
So you don't belie
that I'm thirstyh?
Now you think I'm a liar.
And a chicken and a snake
and a ra
Well, those are
all God's creatures.
Aneyalll.
I made a mistake.
It wasn't a mistake.
You deliberately used me.
Summer, I cannot go on with my
life with this issue unresolved.
So let's go out on the lawn
and have a truth circle.
will be your
opportunity to tell me
how you're really feeling.
I have.
I hate you. Now leave.
This can't be fixed by
some candlelight vigil oretn,y?
And I'm not some tree that you
can just chain yourself to.
We'll see about that.
What? What did you do?
This is fu
Give me the key.
I cannot unlock us
until we are done healing.
Hmm. Okay, then be prepared
to stay here
for the rest of your life,
'cause that's never going to happen.
SANDY:A weekend away
at the Montage.neououe self.
I don't know about that.
Oh, no, listen,
I'm going to be paying you
back later tonight.
Guess who packed Scrabble?
There's just one small
wrinkle totherwisrrd
romantic holidayth forgot to share.
Not to worry.
I TiVoed the Australian Open.
Tiger's going
to take it any
Just one more g.
Tell me at least he's got
a separate room.
Sandy Cohen,
you're looking lovely tonight.
If my date didn't look so hot,
I might scope you out.
llI-I'm jealous.
Now, who is the lucky date?
Hi! Sorry I'm late.
I owe you both big time.
I'll make this up
to you tight.
I am so damn honored
to be here with you
and Kirsten for your recommitment ceremony.
I am crying already.
Realrs
Come on, let's eat.
-Wait until yee Takeshi noep
-Battle Royale.
Canop it.
It's packed in its original
packaging, so no groping...
Suer. Che.
Ta.
Taylor.
Roger, Summer. Che
Roger.
Summer. Che.What are you doing?
Well, I live here again,
sooved som yst inhest
uh. Are you two cuff
to each other?
a matter of fact, we are.
mmer Rts,
you'verned a few
things hallegeroommaf s.
When dSethive?
Ew, no, it's likat.
In fact, d tal himHe's her
Igngisng to make o
How about kig yo
ay, to whiuest room
did you move mings?
I'll show
was that?
Get...
Ththineigh a.
's why're ing and not me
Kan,'s g on?
Juaving a feiend ovt myse.
Itus thin lin,
yannot have a pa
Your motleft me in charge.
ally, she left me inrge.
if you wanKait is be mthanpy
entertaour ts
wi some festiv tribal mus
e diidoo'sin the car.
You lovee didge.We're friends n?
, freak.
Summer, why is this guyndcu to your wrist?
. no, there's no one
handcuffo my wrist.
He doesn'tst.
Also kd of eaky. Okay.
You gu hurp.
I got to tap t kegs
because we're rug
out of tim
Wh?
Kaitlin!
Roger?!
Yon't believe your eyes.
ese girls are wild.
Get out ere now!
Ride with me, Ryan.
So the good news is,
my frequent-flier miles
just reached platinum.
The bad news is, they don't
change the in-flight movie,
and Failure to Launch
does not hold up
on the third viewing.
What are you doing here?
Summer got kicked out of school
and I'm about to head over there.
Can I come with you?
I appreciate your interest
in Summer's future,
but I think this
is a conversation
that's just for the two of us.
Is Taylor going to be there?
I assume so.
I like her.
Say what now?
Why would you even think that?
Because I keep imagining her
on roller skates
and washing windows with a big
bucket of soapy water.
Dude, your fantasies
are so pedestrian.
A sudsy girl?
That's... so average.
Doesn't mean it's not hot.
I guess they call them classics for a reason.
Do you want to drive
or sh-should I?
Again!
Okay, game night!
Who wants to play Pictionary,
huh?
Come on, guys, get high on life!
Hey! Hey!
Cut it out!
I tan on this chair.
Hey, if you are going
to consummate your union, be safe.
Out of my way, wasteoid.
Hey, stay alive.
Don't drink and drive.
Che, shut up!
Where's Kaitlin?
Again!
You guys, your seven minutes is up.
And I'm next.
It's Connor.
Oh, Riley's gonna die.
I mean, it's bad enough you
didn't go to her party.
She doesn't have to know.
Come on, Kaitlin.
Oh...
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, man.
Whoo!You're so hot.
Why don't I ever see you
around school?
'Cause I don't really like school.
Huh.
So are we going to
make out or what?
'Cause the clock
is kind of ticking.
Or we could talk more.
I mean...
Yeah, you seem
really interesting.
I'm not.
Let's make out.
Are you afraid
to cheat on Riley?
No. I don't even like her.
So what's the problem?
Are you... gay?
What?
No!
I don't, I don't,
I don't think so.
Sweetheart, you're so gay.
I know the Jews are good
with numbers and lending stuff.
Now, there's a generalization
that's not even
remotely offensive.
Well, hold on there,
He-bro.
It's just,
if you all control the media,
why does everyone know?
Why not use the media to say
someone else controls it?
It would cause a lot less
resentment that way.
You know, we should talk
about something else.
Dinner was delicious.
Like you ate!
Oh, I know what they say--
"Eat light on
Saturday night."
Less food in the stomach
for the booze.
Bullet, Kirsten
doesn't drink.
Time for bed.
I have a headache.
Uh-oh!
I guess she doesn't do that either.
Thank you, Gordon.
Your point of view regarding
the Middle East is something
I will treasure forever.
Well, all I said
was Iran-Iraq war.
Whoever loses, we win.
Honey, let's see
if we can cancel our room.
Sounds like a plan.
Good night, Julie.
-Good night.
What about their wedding vows?
That was a lie, Bullet.
Told to avoid you, because you
are an ignorant buffoon.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to try and salvage
my friendship with Sandy and Kirsten.
You want some more coffee?
-Let's split up.
-All right, good luck.
You, too.
Taylor?
Ryan?
Roger, hey.
Uh, keep doing
what you're doing.
I was looking for Taylor,
but clearly she's...
Who's Taylor?
Uh...
Is this your boyfriend?
Uh, Taylor isn't in there
with you guys, is she?
No.
Okay. What are you doing, man?
Um, I mean, I think Taylor
really likes you,
and you're kind
of leading her on.
I barely even know her.
She told me if I pretended
to like her,
she'd give me
her Kitano action figure.
It's extremely rare.
Wait, she paid you
to pretend to like her?
That sounds like Taylor.
All right, well, uh... carry on.
Well, well, well.
Looks like you finally crawled
out of your cave.
Seth, perhaps with your
presence,
we could broker some peace.
What are you doing here,
Sandals?
Ruining Summer's life
at Brown wasn't enough?
Cohen, you're here!
Yeah.
Now I want to see what this
guy's got to say for himself.
Please, Seth.
Summer and I are on
a journey together.
Huh?
A journey towards the truth.
You're on a journey...
-to the pool.
-What?
What? No! Cohen!
AAAAa????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????No one came to my party.
So you dress like a ho
for no reason?
-I changed before I came here.
-Oh.
Look, you win, okay?
I'll... I'll serve your command.
The school is yours.
Except that I don't want it.
Just be nicer to your friends.
Oh.
Connor's totally gay.
Hi, 911?
Yeah, I'd like to report
a totally lame partyer.
I'm a worthless coward,
and you're a
glorious m artyr.
Sorry,
I didn't realize
about the handcuffs.
Well, you know,
it's all Che's fault.
It's my fault.
Just know I hate myself more
than you could ever hate me.
I'm capable of a lot of hate.
It's true.
You're my best friend, Summer.
All those other kids,
they only  joined the cause
so it'd look good on their
grad school applications.
But you, but you really
believed in the good
we were doing.
We did a lot of good.
I let you down, I know.
I'm sorry.
I liberated those bunnies
because
I believed that
they should be set free.
I knew the consequences
if I got caught.
Look, I can't spend
my whole life blaming you,
so I accept your apology.
With an asterisk next to it.
And there's a footnote
at the bottom.
And it says
you don't deserve it.
Yeah. (sighs)
You're so much more
enlightened than
I could ever hope to be.
I think I need
to blow my nose.
No, you...
Could you unlock us first?
Okay.
I guess
now we are
free to take
our own paths.
Yours leads toward the airport.
Yeah, okay, yeah.
I should be going.
You ready, Dalton?
Your bags are packed,
Winchester.
-Winchester?
Why do they think
they call me Che?
Your father's G-4
is waiting
on the tarmac.
I thought you grew up
on a reservation.
It was a reservation--
a beautiful reservation--
Before it became
a family
compound
that's all gated.
My dad owns
a pharmaceutical company
and some factories in Mexico.
Well, I guess every kid
finds a way
to rebel against their parents.
Good-bye, Caterpillar.
And defender of
Caterpillar's honor.
?????????????
So he was a liar,
a coward and a hypocrite.
At least he had depth.
I guess I am really
back home again.
Which is great,
except now I have to leave.
Taylor?
Ryan.
What are you doing?
Someone wrote I love poop
on this poor boy's face.
You know, that kind of thing
can scar you for life.
No, what are you doing paying
your gay friend Roger to pretend
he's in love
with you?
Well, what if I did, hmm?
What if I did rent a homosexual
for the evening?
And pay him with rare
collectibles from Asian cinema?
What difference
does it make to you?
Well, it's a little strange.
Well, so am I.
Which is why you ran away
from me last night.
No, it wasn't 'cause
you're strange.
You don't find me strange?
No, I do, but that's
not why I took off.
Look, I'm not really ready
for a relationship right now
or a girlfriend.
Uh... girlfriend?
Cart, horse?
Aren't you getting a little
ahead of yourself there?
Well, I mean, just because
I want to use your body
as a jungle gym,
doesn't mean that
we have to get married.
-I see.
-I mean, my divorce papers
aren't even dry yet.
Look, you're a sweet, smart,
great guy, Ryan Atwood.
And hot.
Did I mention hot?
So whatever happens,
happens.
-Taylor, that's...
-Normal?
Yeah.
Yeah, I have my moments.
You know, this is
my first high school bash.
Have you ever played
Seven Minutes in Heaven?
Thanks to you, Sandy and Kirsten
are packed and on the road.
I'm sorry, Julie.
When God was handing
out brains,
I guess I was sitting
on the toilet.
I swear you make me
all nervous inside.
So you only act like a bigot
and a sexist pig around me?
No, I just feel worse
about it when you're around.
You're such a classy
and elegant dame.
Well, that is true.
Look, I was trying so hard
to make you laugh,
and I know what a hard time
you've been through,
and I...
it just came out all wrong.
I appreciate that, Gordon.
I guess you're heading
on home now, too, huh?
Are you kidding?
I put the room on
the company card.
I've got a mud bath
in the morning.
So, since I ruined dinner,
how about breakfast?
Breakfast?
Okay.
So, uh, should I
call you or nudge you?
Bang.
That was funny.
You have a pretty smile.
My job is to get you
to use it more.
Then you're going
to need better material.
Well, I am working on it.
'Night, Julie.
Can't we be left alone?
It's probably Julie.
She felt terrible.
Well, I bet she did.
She spent the night
with the Bullet.
Hello, I was told you two
are renewing your vows?
I'm a justice of the
peace, here to preside
over the ceremony.
Oh, I'm sorry,
that was an excuse.
Yeah, we didn't call
for anyone.
I was hired by a Gordon Bullet.
-Hello.
-Julie.
Hey, it's Spencer.
I just wanted to, uh, call
and say thanks.
I had a great night.
I would assume so,
it's pretty late.
I'll, uh, give you your cut
when you get back into town.
My cut?
Spencer, you pay
to join the service.
Your date doesn't pay you.
That... that's illegal.
You're not a gigolo.
Right.
Open phone line.
Got it, my bad.
Anyway, you got yourself
one satisfied customer.
See ya.
Spencer, wait...
Spencer?
I wish.
But it's probably for the best.
I am tin roof rusted.
Pam.
So you had a good night?
Worth every penny.
And I'll be telling
all my friends.
And what will you be
telling them exactly?
Okay, seven minutes are up.
You said you wanted
to take it slow.
Yeah, well, I don't think
eight minutes would be rushing.
-Nine seems like a good pace.
-Mm-hmm.
And ten is a nice,
round number.
Mm, mm-hmm.
We could try the
long-distance thing again.
I've got a lot
of frequent-flier miles,
and we survived
one semester apart.
Yeah, barely.
Why don't you move to Providence
with me and get a job.
Oh, right. You'll be in school
and I'll be slinging
baba ganoush on Third Street,
while all the kids are living
the life
that I should be having.
Well, you know, I've really
been enjoying home lately.
Ryan's back and I've been
bonding with the Newpsies.
Maybe, uh, I could put off
RISD for a semester.
We could both go back
together in the fall.
You'd really put off
college for me?
Rhode Island is a big place.
Better we tackle it together.
Cohen, Rhode Island's the
smallest state in the country.
I was kidding.
Right.
There's just one more thing.
This is Pancakes.
Pancakes is very
important to me.
Then you can hold it.
I'm not really an animal person.
Cohen, Pancakes is
my daughter,
or my son,
I'm not really sure.
Oh...
Oh, he's your son.
He kind of looks
like you, Cohen.
Feel how soft he is.
Yeah.
He's beautiful.
Take a look around, Pancakes.
This is your new home.
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
BBBBB
CCCCCCCC
DDDDD
Welcome to www.1000fr.com