Voila.
Oh, yes.
Thank you for the prescription, Dr. Feelgood.
Make sure you take it with food.
Hey, emergency at the hospital?
No. You see this? I'm not on call.
Glad to see you're finally
moving up from wine spritzers.
Ah, I am so psyched.
I can finally text with a full keyboard.
Very fancy.
Now that I'm working
at Coal, I need to be reachable
at, like, all times.
I hope Auggie's
not giving you too much of a hard time.
Hey, can I get your digits?
Yeah, sure.
Don't...
Water a little bit chilly?
Huh?
Those goose bumps are planetary.
Oh, I was shooting in the Valley
today where it was a punishing
hundred and five.
What's the latest Jonah Miller production?
Shooting Wilderness Scouts
planting trees in Balboa Park.
I'll send you a link.
Hmm, that's okay.
Agriculture falls squarely in my no-click zone.
But I have a hookup for you.
Passes to a premiere. Hmm?
Kensington Squared,
the new Abby Douglas rom-com?
I'm already going.
Really?
Yeah, I got tickets from
the guy who wrote the film.
You know Zac McGalvan?
Yeah, we were roommates in film school.
Legends on the NYU beer pong circuit.
And now you get to watch
him walk the red carpet
with Abby Douglas? Ouch.
Too bad you have
to work the event.
You probably won't have time
to hang out with us.
Riley, the red carpet's not
the teacher's lounge.
But maybe we'll see each other
at the after-party.
If you're on the list.
Filter's clogged. The heater's broken.
What is this place
coming to, huh?
I'll have the pool boy
here in the morning.
Who are you?
My name's Jane Andrews.
I'm Sydney's sister.
I've inherited this building.
I'll be your new landlord.
Sync by honeybunny - corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com
I'm sorry about your sister.
But, um...
Well, since you are the new landlord,
I wanted to talk to you about
moving into this apartment
as soon as it's available.
You must be Ella.
My sister mentioned
your social grace.
Oh.
I didn't know you two talked.
Yeah, Syd called me right around the time
the two of you had your falling out.
I could tell you were
pretty angry with her.
And how exactly could you "tell"?
Oh, Syd sent me your e-mails.
You know, the ones where you made those
crazy threats against her.
Uh, are you...
insinuating that I had something
to do with Syd's death?
No, of course not.
I know you loved her, deep down.
I have nothing to hide, Jane.
I didn't murder Sydney.
Why would you?
I mean, you have way too much going for you.
Syd said your career's really taken off.
Isn't...
Abby Douglas a client of yours?
Why do you ask?
I just think she's so adorable.
Doesn't she have a movie coming out?
I saw something on TV about a premiere.
Kensington Squared.
You want tickets?
I'll get you a pair.
Actually, what I want is...
God, I probably shouldn't
even ask, but what the hell.
It would be a dream to see Abby Douglas
walk the red carpet in one of my dresses
Didn't your boutique burn down
and your entire collection with it?
It did.
But I'm ready for a comeback.
And I know that whatever
Abby Douglas wears will be
the talk of the fashion world
the next day.
You know what, Jane?
You're giving me a little
bit of short notice here...
I know. I get it.
An important publicist like you,
I mean, you've got a reputation to protect.
Don't worry.
All those e-mails that you sent my sister,
I'll do my best to keep them
away from the police.
Where are we with the Kensington premiere?
I'm working on the last sample right now.
Tempura'd cod with julienned bell peppers
and a tartar sauce.
This isn't on our menu.
I know, but I thought since,
you know, the movie
takes place in England...
You thought?
If I promote you, it's to run the kitchen,
not dream up new dishes.
Yes, Chef.
Well, which knife do you use
to cut the tension in here?
I'd need a Ginsu for that.
What's up?
We got a new landlord.
I was going to fill you in
on the drama, but it looks like you've had your take.
Yeah, Marcello put me in charge of the kitchen
for this premiere party, and four of our servers quit.
I can help you out.
You?
David...
You've never had a job in your life.
And picking up trash on the side
of the road doesn't count.
Dude, come on, man.
Let me help you.
Okay, look...
I know I wasn't the best friend
once Syd and I started hanging out.
I wish I could have done things
different, okay? Believe me.
Mike, drop the heat on those filets.
Excuse me?
Um, I heard that you guys
are looking for some help.
For one event.
Nothing full-time.
You won't be in the tip pool.
Sounds good.
What kind of experience do you have?
Um, I've worked all over town.
With Patina.
Aug and I go way back.
You can vouch for him, Auggie?
Yeah, yeah, he's good.
Thursday.
Be here at 4:00.
Get started on the garlic... get it roasted up.
Thank you.
Sorry to bother you so late, Ms. Foster.
We just had a few questions.
No problem.
I like the lamp.
Thanks.
It's vintage.
You moved here two weeks ago?
Yes. And you provided
an Oregon driver's license
with your rental application?
That's where I'm from.
Right. Hey, uh,
do you mind if I put some clothes on real quick?
No. Of course.
So what's your guess? Actress?
Singer?
Future stripper?
Yeah, my money's on all the above.
Ms. Foster?
The window.
We got a runner.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm looking forward
to it, too, Toby.
Sure, I know where that hotel is.
Don't mind me.
Well, my rounds finish at 5:00,
so I'll meet you there about 6:00.
Okay, bye.
If I'm eavesdropping correctly,
you just scored yourself another date. Hardly.
It's drinks with a fellow intern.
Hot intern?
Married woman intern.
Yes, but is she hot?
Hey, what do you think of our new landlord?
Well, I can certainly see the family resemblance.
She's got Syd's fangs.
I just hope she doesn't jack up the rent.
I mean, I can barely afford this place as it is.
Even with a roommate
who fronts it for me every now and then.
Lauren,
I thought our domestic bliss
was based on more than my rent subsidies.
It is. Of course it is.
I'm just hoping we can stay together
till my tuition payments leave the nest.
Nothing.
I love this shot. Look at this.
creating a frame within the frame.
Awesome.
Would you look at me right now?
I'm sitting here editing
merit badge videos while Zac McGalvan,
who came to me freshman year
begging for help on his first
script, is blowing up.
How did Zac
get his big break, anyways?
He was caddying at the Riviera,
and one of his regulars just happened
to be none other than Charlie Kitsis.
Remember, my references are
iCarly and The Backyardigans.
He's, this big, huge,
powerful  ber-agent.
Zac got him to read his script,
Charlie loved it, got this director,
threw Abby Douglas in it,
bam-- there ya go, Kensington Squared.
All from being at the right golf
course at the right time.
That's it.
Wow.
Right. Unbelievable.
You know, I think I'm going to start playing golf.
I always wanted to jet around
in one of those little golf carts.
I'd be really good if I could play.
That's a great shot of Abby.
Who's the photographer?
Who cares?
I was the one with the brains at the shoot
that took her out of that floral nightmare
and put her into this lovely Burberry scarf.
Oh, what would Abby ever do without Ella Simms?
Oh.
I hope you're as equally
detailed-obsessed for tomorrow's red carpet.
A little issue on transpo.
Abby wants to go with the gas-guzzling limo
and I told her to go with the stretch hybrid.
She won't budge.
Who cares about the ride?
What is she wearing?
Ah, we settled on this amazing
frock by Jane Andrews.
We actually have a fitting later today.
Jane who?
Andrews.
Never heard of her. Well, everybody else has.
She is making a huge splash on the Hollywood scene.
I loved that Proenza Schouler
she got fitted for last week.
No, no, no.
The Andrews is brilliant.
Look, Abby has already seen the
dress, and she adores it.
Ella, if you're having trouble
connecting with A-list designers
why don't you have me give you Marc Jacobs's cell?
We're in a capture-the-flag league together.
Caleb.
What?
Oh, wait, let me guess.
Andrews is another one of your
"undiscovered" superstars?
Well, it seemed to work out pretty well
with the music video, didn't it?
Okay.
You better hope that lightning
strikes twice, though.
Because you embarrass Abby Douglas,
you embarrass WPK.
Oh, no, no, no.
The only one who will be embarrassed is you...
when this dress ends up in Vogue's Most Wanted.
I don't know. I'm lukewarm.
Look, my chest looks like a landing pad.
I'm Abby Douglas,
not Abby Breslin.
What happened to that dress
you found last week?
Oh, you look way hotter in this, Ab.
What if you wore a bra?
Bras are for breeders.
Okay, let's see...
Here, I have an idea.
Oh, good news.
I ran this dress by the editor of W.
She's holding a full page
for you in an upcoming issue.
No way. Mm-hmm.
That'll be like my thickest glossy yet.
Okay, all set. You can change.
I'm worried about her.
She's just a little nervous.
The dress is perfect for her.
Yeah, that's easy for you
to say, when you're not
the one being trotted out in
front of 200 flashbulbs.
Hmm, I just wouldn't want any
of this to go badly...
for both our sakes.
Tell me I'm getting waxed for this thing.
Right after your facial.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
What are you doing here?
I just want to talk.
I know this is strange, but I need your help.
You were in the courtyard today.
Who are you?
My name's Violet, Violet Foster.
And the thing is, is...
I'm Sydney's daughter.
My God.
You look just like her.
I knew something was going on with Syd
right before she left college.
Honey, why are you here?
The police.
I came to L.A. to find my mom.
But when the cops came,
I got scared.
Violet, why are the police after you?
I'm in trouble.
I came to you because you seem so nice.
You're the only family I have.
Of course.
Why don't you sit down?
Um, I'll make you a pot of chamomile.
And we can talk about everything.
This is Los Angeles Homicide.
Do you have a question for us?
Yes, Detective. What is it?
I'm calling to report a fugitive.
A fugitive? Do you have a name?
Her name is Violet Foster.
We love you!
One more, please! One more!
Have a good night.
Thank you.
Here we go. Oh, man.
Why are they taking my picture?
I'm surprised more celebrities
aren't blind. Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, well, you know what, you better get used to this,
because someday soon, this will all be for your movie.
Oh, yeah, I'd actually have to sell something first.
That would help.
Only a matter of time.
Yeah, the question is, how long
is a matter of time, Riley?
I mean, let's face it:
we didn't just get to L.A., you know.
It's been like a year and a half.
Well, you know what?
Maybe it'll take years.
But you've got the talent.
And I will be right here by your side
as long as it takes.
You always say the right thing.
VIPs only. Off the red carpet.
Let's go.
Sorry. My bad.
Ooh.
I had no idea that the seating arrangements
took so many experts.
You sure you're old enough
to be playing with lighters?
Well, Auggie was a little shorthanded,
so I'm helping out.
Love the bromance, David, but really?
You working hourly? Ha.
Yeah, I owed him a solid.
Or three.
So I hear your starlet's showing up
in a Jane Andrews dress.
Mm-hmm.
Hope you're getting something
sweet out of that deal.
She's our new landlord.
Just showing some neighborly
generosity, that's all.
Yeah, well, your giving spirit's
starting to make me wonder.
First you throw me an alibi,
and now you roll over for Jane.
This is not the Ella that I know.
Okay... I'll be honest.
Jane has a little bit more than
just the keys to the courtyard.
She's got Sydney's private files, her e-mails.
She keeps saying that at any moment
she could embarrass me in front of everyone.
Since when do you care
about being embarrassed?
I don't.
But I do care about being falsely accused of murder.
Look, the last thing I need right now
is to have to defend myself
against a crime I never committed.
Ugh. Chaos is calling.
Well, I'm off to the red carpet.
Hey, this place better be popping
by the time I get back.
And don't burn yourself.
(indistinct conversations)
Good evening. May I help you?
Hey, can I get a sparkling water, please?
Of course.
Let me get you a real drink.
Oh, no, thank you. It's fine.
Somebody's going to end up
paying for it, right?
I'm already here.
Excuse me?
Money's money.
Does it really matter
whose wallet it comes from?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Right.
My mistake.
Mm-hmm.
Do you see him?
No, no, I'm...
I don't know.
I figured he... he would...
Wait, there he is. There he is. Zac. Zac.
Oh, yeah, yeah!
Jonah!
Millah the killah. How are you?
How's it going, man?
Awesome.
This is huge.
I know, right? Insane.
Insane. I'm so happy for you.
Oh, thanks, man.
Hey, Riles.
Hi. Good to see you.
So, uh, what's going on, dude?
I've spent the last year in this crazy bubble.
But what about you?
I...
you know, I could go on forever.
Uh, I finished a new cut
of Living in Reverse a few weeks back.
Dude, you sold that bad boy?
Uh, not exactly.
Jonah just turned down
a six-figure offer from Gary Sarling.
What?
Are you serious?
It wasn't the right situation.
That is raw.
Dude, I'll be doing Abby Douglas chick flicks
for the rest of my life, while
you're up there snagging Oscars.
I don't think so.
Hey, so if I drop anything,
the five-second rule applies, right?
Yeah, I'd drop you.
Stampede's about to hit.
I hope my kitchen's ready.
We'll have five apps ready to pass.
Oh, what are you doing here?
Kitchen staff only.
We were short-staffed, Chef,
so I just asked him to help out with the crostini.
Just trying to help out, sir.
Show time, people. Let's move.
David, will you grab that knife
from over there, please?
Yeah.
David.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Hey, Jane!
I can't... you...
Really bad rec... here.
What's up?
Abby's called me four times already.
Suddenly it's too tight in the hips,
too loose everywhere else.
Oh, it's okay.
It's just a little actor's indecision. It'll pass.
Well, I'm going to drive over to the theater.
No, Jane, save your gas.
I'll take care of it.
No, it's too important.
I'm headed there now.
And, Ella, I really hope
she's not always this difficult.
Say that again.
This isn't the last time
Abby will be photographed
in one of my dresses, Ell.
We're partners now.
Oh, no.
Your worst putt is always
better than your worst chip.
Really?
Hey.
Oh... sorry about that.
The on-ramp to the men's room... totally jammed.
Um, this is my fiance, Jonah.
Jonah, this is Charlie Kitsis.
Of course. Yeah, I mean, you represent
every bomb director in Hollywood.
Oh, you're a brave man,
marrying a girl who loves golf so much.
Yes. Yeah, I like to live on the edge.
The links are where I go when
I need a break from the wife.
It's added an extra ten years
onto my marriage, easy.
Really?
Oh, well, Jonah's more into Mario Golf.
I'll probably be the one hiding out
at Rustic Canyon.
Best public course in L.A.
I know!
Hey, Charlie!
Hey! Come here for a second, meet
somebody, would ya?
So, since when are you Tiger Woods?
A little Google goes a long way.
You are fantastic.
Um, I'll be right back.
Um, she'll be right back.
Uh...
She's very easily distracted.
Well, she's beautiful.
Don't lose her, speaking as a professional here.
Your woman is the best agent you'll ever have.
You mean, because she knows so much about golf?
She told me about that backwards film of yours,
Living in Reverse.
It sounds very cool.
She told you about...
Thank you.
I'm so sorry. I have to run.
You what?
You're not sticking around?
I can't.
There's an after-party.
I can get you guys
on the list for it.
Really?
That's really cool of you.
Thank you so much. That's...
No, I really can't.
Where could you possible
have to go right now?
Jonah, Violet's in jail.
Riley, come on.
Are you seriously going to leave
me here, just like that?
Jonah, she's in jail.
Okay, and?
Is that a bad thing?
Did you ever consider the possibility
that jail is exactly where that floater belongs?
Okay, I know she's a little different,
but that doesn't mean she's dangerous.
I mean, she was just arrested
because she got spooked.
Oh, sure. I mean, innocent people
always run from the cops, right?
Riley!
This is Charlie Kitsis.
This is huge.
And he likes you. He likes you even more
because you are going to make him very rich.
Okay, now, get back in there
and kick some butt, okay?
I'll be home in a few hours.
Riley.
You're not her mother.
She's not even our friend.
She's our neighbor
and she's all by herself
in county jail, terrified.
I have to help her, Jonah.
All right. I love you.
Love you, too.
If you have nothing to hide,
then why jump out your bathroom window?
I'm... scared of the police.
I bet.
Your fingerprints
match the ones we pulled off this lanyard
we found at the crime scene.
It was a gift.
For approving your rental application?
I didn't want her to freak out when I told her.
Told her what?
That I was her daughter.
But she did freak out. Didn't she?
Are you kidding?
She was so happy.
She gave me the biggest hug.
We finally got to know each other.
It was the best week of my life.
Till she was murdered.
Tell me something, Violet.
You ever been arrested?
No, sir.
Then why are you so afraid
of the police?
Unbelievable.
Stood up?
Look, I didn't mean to insult you earlier.
I was looking forward to meeting someone.
And she blew me off.
So, that's my excuse
for acting like an idiot.
I'm Victor.
I'm Lauren.
Well...
I can't say I've ever asked this before, Lauren,
but are you working tonight?
Yeah.
Actually, I am.
Yes, Mr. Mancini, I've been following him.
He's really working the event.
Nothing suspicious, but I'll keep on him.
Bye.
Ask my father if he'd like a tie
or a lawsuit for his birthday.
Excuse me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You tell my father if he
ever has me followed again,
I'm not only going to come after him,
I'm going to come after you. You got it?
What are you doing?
Auggie, I'm sorry.
I was just going to ask
your friend the same thing.
Get out of my restaurant
right now, before I call the cops.
Now!
Good friend you got there, Auggie. Nice.
Oh, thank God.
Let's go. Red carpet time.
There's a torn seam.
No problem. I'll fix it right now.
I don't want it fixed!
I want another dress.
You look beautiful.
Look at my arms in this thing.
Just cut them off already.
And my shoes? Where are they?
These were like, $1,000, and they hurt.
Look, I'm sorry, Elle, but you really need
to fix this.
Or I'm out of here.
Ella, say something.
Honey...
There's a lot riding on this
night. Not just for me.
The Proenza.
It's in my trunk.
Get out of that and I'll be back in a minute.
Ah, I love you!
Ella, do you realize what you just did?
My clients always come first.
I sure hope it was worth it.
Is there a shoe out there?
No.
You just about set?
Yeah. Just one last thing, and I'm gone.
What's that?
Um, the... the money?
Excuse me?
This was just
a friendly encounter
between two consenting adults.
No, you asked me if I was working tonight
and I... I told you I was.
And then we agreed on an amount, so...
I'm sorry. I don't know
what you're talking about.
How dare you do this?
Just pay me.
No, thank you.
Hey, give me what you owe me.
I don't owe you a damn thing.
Aug.
What are you still doing here?
Thought you'd be on your third drink by now.
Just wanted to make sure that you're all right.
Look, Marcello can't hold you responsible for that.
Yeah, well, he can, and he is.
I am responsible.
But then again, I'm not sure
that's a concept you understand.
I mean, what did this guy do to you, anyway,
that was worth my career?
I hit on his girlfriend last week, and the guy
came after me, all right? The guy's bad news.
Bad news, huh?
Yeah, I'll just explain that to Marcello
and maybe he won't fire me tomorrow.
Screw Marcello. You run this place,
and he knows it.
Doesn't matter, David. He's my boss.
See, my world doesn't work like yours.
You've never had to live
with consequences.
Look, I was trying to help you.
All right?
Didn't you try to help Sydney?
The night she died?
How was Charlie Kitsis?
One of the biggest sharks in the business.
Who you managed to totally win over.
He wants me to show him my film.
Jonah Adam Miller,
that's incredible.
Well, then he ditched me
for Ashton Kutcher.
But still, him seeing my movie is...
it's massive.
It's amazing.
You... you are amazing.
Is she back there?
Yeah, she's in the shower.
In our bathroom?
We have scissors in there.
She was scared to be alone.
Wait. What happened?
Did you have to, like, bail her out or something?
Okay.
How much did that cost?
Like, hundreds of dollars?
It's a bond. We get it back
when she shows up to court.
Oh, that's great. Good.
'Cause so far, she's showing herself
to be incredibly dependable.
Jonah, there's something
you should know about Violet.
I think it might help you understand.
Okay.
She's Sydney's daughter.
I'm sorry. What?!
Yeah. She got to L.A, had a joyful reunion
with her mother, and then
had to go through the trauma of finding her dead.
I mean, I'm not surprised she's a little shaken up.
Did you just tell me Violet is Sydney's daughter?
I'm not a little fuzzy from my two rum and cokes?
They wanted to get to know each other better
before they told people.
Riley, in our own little personal slasher flick here,
this is the part where the audience stands up
and starts screaming, "Um, hello?
She's the killer!"
I ran from the police
because of what happened back home.
My parents who adopted me
weren't exactly Brad and Angelina.
Did they hurt you?
I didn't sleep, like, ever.
I was too worried my door would open.
All I ever wanted to do was leave.
I just couldn't manage to save up enough.
Then I tracked down Sydney.
I had to take off.
And I took some of their money with me.
That's why you ran from Detective Rodriguez.
This is my home now,
and even though my mom isn't here,
this is the only place I can
sleep without being afraid.
I couldn't let them
take me back to the Corvallis police.
It's okay, Violet. It's all gonna be okay.
Here.
Hotel security. I need a word with you, ma'am.
I'm sorry. I'm in a rush.
Wait. Did you really think that
you could just walk into a bar
at this hotel and solicit customers?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Okay, this way, please.
The police should be here soon.
Let's go. Walk! Come on.
Look, please, I was just meeting someone.
I've got texts in my phone.
I can show them to you if you want. She's with me.
Well, no one here had seen her
before, Miss Madison.
No, no, no, I know. It was
a miscommunication on my part.
I apologize.
I don't know what just happened, but thank you.
Well, let me take a guess. Craigslist? Chat rooms?
No, um, I'm not actually what you think I am.
And...
I think I should just go.
Yes, you should go.
But just know the only reason
why I helped you out
is because I was once in your shoes.
I don't think we're the same size.
Okay, the only person you're fooling is yourself,
and that always ends up badly.
So, if you ever come back here
to work again, I assure you
hotel security will be the least of your worries.
Do you understand?
Shouldn't you be bobbing for olives
in your after-party martini?
Change of plans.
I canceled the red carpet
close-ups for Jane's dress.
Won't that be the shot heard
around the courtyard?
It doesn't matter.
After I spread the word that
Abby Douglas hated her dress,
Jane's samples won't be fit to mop floors.
Yeah. I don't know if that's gonna be enough
to stop whatever she has planned for you.
Let me take care of it.
You?
Yeah. Jane was married to my father.
The skeletons won't take long to find.
I'll bury her.
Wow.
I don't think anyone's ever offered
to destroy an enemy of mine before.
David...
That's almost...
romantic.
Or we could say that it's all
about the thrill of victory.
Go with romantic...
Let's go work on that alibi.
Word of advice:
blackmail's not the best way
to ingratiate yourself to the tenants.
Blackmail?
What are you talking about, David?
Ella offered to do something nice for me,
and, well, in the end,
I guess "nice" just isn't in her.
Jane, I know all about you
and your desperate attempts to get ahead.
It's sad, really.
And after everything that you put into it,
you torched your warehouse and clothing line
just so you could collect insurance money?
And where did you ever get that idea?
From my dad.
I came across a certain computer file he has on you.
The next time
that you divorce a paranoid psychopath,
you might want to change your online passwords.
I have nothing to hide.
The fire was electrical.
Oh, so it's okay if I call
your insurance company, right?
Or better yet, the FBI?
You're making a huge mistake, David.
I still own this building.
And there are a lot of things I can do
to make your lives miserable.
I think we'll take our chances.
I just got off the phone with Mason.
He agrees with me:
you're not ready for a promotion.
Chef, I'm sorry
about what happened. I swear, that...
No, save your breath.
Maybe you'll get another shot
at running the kitchen someday,
but I kind of doubt it.
Hi, this is Lauren.
We met at the hotel the other
night. Do you have a minute?
Well, after our conversation last night,
I didn't think there was
anything further to discuss.
I want to talk to you about
future employment opportunities.
Hang on.
Violet is the spawn of Sydney? Shh...
Oh, it's too perfect.
Freaky, right?
I mean, it makes sense.
The red hair, you know...
the schizo glint in her eye.
Did Sydney ever mention
having a child to you guys?
Yeah, she always said
how glad she was that she didn't have a kid
because she'd be afraid the kid would have
the same kind of issues she had.
Shh. Coming this way.
Hey, guys.
Hello, Violet.
Hi!
I was actually
looking for you, Riley.
I made these
to thank you.
Aw...
I hope you like peanut butter.
That's so sweet.
I love peanut butter. Thank you, Violet.
Jonah's gonna love these.
Yes, definitely. Thank you.
You know what, Violet, sweetheart,
why don't you actually take the first one?
So you can show Jonah that
it isn't laced with cyanide.
Ella, that was... she was
kidding. That was a joke.
Of course she is joking.
Obvious...
I'll take 'em back.
I'll, uh, I'll try one.
Me, too.
Mm, Violet, this is good.
They're good.
Mm... Thanks.
Oh, no, no. I have to save my appetite
for the farmer's market.
David, are you coming with me?
Absolutely.
Fantastic.
Good seeing you.
Yeah, 'cause we, um...
Yeah, thank you.
Bye.
By the way,
I got the oddest e-mail from Jane.
All's forgiven.
Really?
Uh-huh.
That was easy.
You know what could have changed her mind?
Maybe.
Wow. You weren't kidding
about the toxic waste buried
in your family history.
Just so we're clear...
Mm?
What you did...
amazing.
But last night?
Total one-off.
Why? You can't tell me
you didn't have a good time.
Oh, don't flatter yourself, David.
I always have a good time.
Rodriguez.
I'm listening...
Who is this?
It doesn't matter.
I thought you'd like to know...
Ella Simms had every reason
to want Sydney Andrews dead.
And I'll send you proof.
Sync by honeybunny - corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com