While We Are Still Seeing Straight
And Enunciating Our Vowels.
Speak For Yourself.
We Want You To Know That We
Could Not Be More Proud Of You.
- Thank You.
- Everyone Please Raise A Glass
To My Friend Jonah Miller,
Who Just Sold His First Screenplay!
They Say There's No Heart Left
In Hollywood.
But I Say It's Because It's
All Stuffed Into This Guy.
If I Win An Oscar, I'm Going To
Remember To Thank You Guys.
I Sure Hope That You've Been
Thinking About A Lot More
Than Just Your Acceptance Speech.
You Big Hollywood Screenwriter,
What's Next?
We Are Going To Land The Perfect
Actor For The Lead Role.
Owen Anderson.
That's Assuming He's Even
Going To Read The Script.
Stranger Things Have Happened.
Auggie Riding Off Into
The Sunset With Violet?
Never Underestimate The
Power Of A Full Moon.
Crap. I Got To Take This.
No Shots Without Me.
I'll Be Back.
My Pumpkin Carriage Has Arrived.
- Why?
- Because In 20 Minutes
My Glass Slippers Turn
Into Hospital Booties.
Can't You Go One Night
Without Saving Lives?
And Tonight, Promise Me
They're Neither Of Yours, Yes?
I Really Appreciate You Coming
Here And Waving The White Flag.
Whatever Happened Between You
And Riley Stays There, Okay?
- She Knows You're Still My Friend.
- Thank You.
Geez Louise.
Am I, Like,
In This Crazy Breakup Fog,
Or Are You Guys Getting Serious?
I Don't Know, But Whatever It Is
I Really Don't Want To Screw It Up.
How You Holding Up, Huh?
I Know You Always Imagined This Night
With One More On The Guest List, Though.
If Riley Were Here,
She'd Probably Make Some
Amazing Heartfelt Toast.
Assuming She'd Actually
Even Be Talking To Me.
Ella's Talking To You, So...
Why Don't You Just Sit
Back And Enjoy The Ride?
Okay, Look, I Have To Say...
Ella's Hot.
And She's Fun.
I Always Just Gravitate
To Girls With, Like,
Strong Moral Compasses.
But Ella's...
I Don't Hers Doesn't
Even Have A Needle.
Maybe It's Not Meant To Be.
To Moving Forward.
- What Is Going On Here?
- Brian Jonston, 35.
- Recovering From Coronary Bypass.
- I Know. He's My Patient.
He Had A Minor Skin Infection
After The Surgery.
So You Treated It With Penicillin?
He's Having An
Anaphylactic Reaction.
He's Allergic.
It Says So Here On His Chart.
Is Everything All Right?
It's Fine.
Give Him Ten Cc's Of Cipro.
Check Him Every 15 Minutes.
I Appreciate What You Did In There.
Smart Move.
Look, It's None Of My Business,
But After Everything That's Happened,
Do You Think It Might Be A Good Idea
- If You Take Some Time Off To Recharge?
- No, I'm Fine.
- It Was Simple Oversight.
- Dr. Mancini, With All Due Respect,
Your Patient Almost Died.
The Last Thing I Need Right Now Is
A Lecture From One Of My Students.
Now That Was One Mistake
And No One Needs To Know About It.
Is That Understood?
********************CREDITS*********************
You're A Filmmaker, Not A Rock Star.
Wake Up.
- Where Am I?
- Last Night, While You And David...
Were On Your 12th Tequila Shot,
And Licking Salt
Off Strange Women, I...
Was Working My Butt Off.
I'm On The Cover Of Variety And
The Hollywood Reporter?
El, People, Like,
Subscribe To These Magazines.
Even Deadline Hollywood
Gave You A Shout Out.
Nice Work.
Nikki Finke Was Only
Mildly Sarcastic.
- How Did You Pull This Off?
- What Do You Think I'm doing
On My Blackberry All Day,
Playing Frogger?
No, This...
Is My Job.
Thank You, Ella.
You Are Incredible.
Beyond Incredible Actually.
Especially Now That I
Scored You A Meeting
- With Owen Anderson. A-list Actor.
- Are You Kidding?
No. He Read Your Script.
He Wants To Ask You Some Questions.
How...? I Didn't Even Think
Heller Was Sending It Out Yet.
He's Not.
But I Happen To Know That
Owen Was Going To Fiji
He's to Shoot His
New Comedy Tomorrow,
So I Might Have Slipped
It To Him Last Week.
Who's Up For Some Roscoe's
Chicken And Waffles?
No One. Jonah Needs To Shower,
Change And Gargle A
Vat Of Listerine...
Before His Meeting
With Owen Anderson.
You Do Realize You're Setting Up
Your Star Client With Someone Who
Couldn't Even Make It Up The Stairs?
So?
Just Saying.
Jonah's On The Cover Of Variety.
Congratulations.
Was That Awkward For Anyone Else?
So Not The Cure To My Hangover.
That Is The New Guy That
Moved Into Auggie's Place.
We Traded Zen Chef
For A Poor Man's Van Halen.
Tell Him To Stop.
You Go Get Him, Lor.
You Do Not Bother That Girl
When She's Trying To Sleep In.
Excuse Me! Hi!
- Want To Make A Request?
- Yeah, Shut Up!
Half Of West Hollywood's
Trying To Sleep.
Crap, I'm Sorry.
I Didn't Know My Speaker Was On.
I Hate When That Happens.
Plus, Had I Known
Everybody Was Listening,
I For Sure Would
Have Played Clapton.
I Don't Know Who You Are,
Or Which Tour Bus You Fell Off,
But I Get To Sleep In
One Day A Year.
- And Today Was That Day.
- Do You Always Wake Up This Cranky?
Look, From Now On,
Can You Please Just Have
A Modicum Of Respect For This Courtyard?
Thank You.
See You At The Pool.
She Seemed Nice.
Come In. I Only Have A Few Minutes,
- So Make It Quick.
- Thanks Again For Meeting With Me.
You Look... Nice.
It's A Far Cry From
Smocks And Sandals.
- Have You Been Interviewing With Schools?
- That's Actually Why I'm Here.
This Late In The Year,
None Of The Schools Are Hiring.
But While I Was Researching,
I Found Out That
Ziggurat Software Has One
Of The Most Progressive
Education Foundations In The Country.
I Thought, Since You're Dating The Ceo
You Want Me To Introduce You To Ben.
I Hope I'm Not
Overstepping Boundaries.
But Do You Think He Might Be
Interested In Hearing Some Of My Ideas?
Sweetheart, Aren't You A First Grade
School Teacher?
I Don't Think Ben Needs A Lot Of
Help With His Abc's.
Obviously Not.
But I'd Like To Think That
Some Of The Programs I Started
At 34th Street School Made A
Difference In A Few Lives.
I Think That Ben Might Like...
As Impressive As It Sounds,
I Just Don't Think That You
Have The Qualifications...
Of Someone That Ben
Would Typically Hire.
Maybe Not.
But Can't He At Least Be
The One To Decide That?
Fine.
If He Has The Time,
I'll Give His Assistant Your Number.
Thank You.
But Do Me A Favor.
Don't Get Your Hopes Up, Okay?
Please Tell Me You've
Heard From The Sec
About My Sociopathic
Financial Advisor.
It's Not Good News, Amanda.
There's No Way To
Recover Your Losses.
What Are You Talking About?
That Bastard Stole $15 Million.
It's Got To Be Somewhere.
It Was, But He Spent It.
All Of It.
You're Broke, Amanda.
And If You Keep Borrowing
Against Wpk's Assets,
Your Business Will Collapse
And Take You Right Down With It.
That'll Be All.
I've Heard Of Vip Passes
To Meet A-listers,
I've Never Heard Of Having
To Pass A Height Requirement.
Owen's Pretty
Much A Gigantic Toddler.
He Comes Here Whenever He's In Town.
Look Who It Is.
Cruella Simms.
My Pocket-sized Publicist.
You Are Such A Badass.
Put Me Down Now.
Please.
And You, You Must Be Jonah.
How Are You?
Writer Of One Of The Most
Bitchin' Scripts I've Ever Read.
Thank You.
I Laughed Out Loud All Night.
Incredible.
"Schools For Educational Evolution
And Development." That's Catchy.
They're Called Seed Schools For Kids In
L.A.'s Dangerous And Underserviced Districts.
Privately Funded Boarding Schools.
That's Like A Lost Lyric
From A John Lennon Song.
I Guess You Could Say
I'm Kind Of An Idealist.
Good. We Need More Of You
Young Visionaries.
People Who Have At Least Set Foot In
A Classroom In The Last Decade Or So.
I Swear,
I'm Still Dealing With People
Who Think A Tweeis A Birdcall.
Oh, My Goodness.
I Am Late.
Big Segway Polo Match.
Wozniack Has Been Trying To
Take Our Title All Year Long.
Okay, So You'll Just Let
Me Know About My Idea?
Or I Could Just Tell You
I Love It Right Now,
And I Want To Fund Your Project.
Are You Serious?
You May Not Be The Most Experienced
Person I've Ever Thought Of Hiring,
But Your Presentation Rocked,
And I Didn't Get Where I Am Today
By Not Taking Chances.
The Man's On Fire. Yeah.
Man, I Got To Tell You,
My Favorite Part, The Part Where
Jacob Ends Up In The
Sauna With Rachel's Dad...
Nothing Funnier Than Man Boobs,
Right?
One Of The Most Uncomfortable
Moments Of My Life.
That Actually Happened To You?
Jonah Based His Script On His Life.
Dude, No Wonder I Frickin' Loved
It So Much. The Story's Real?
You Didn't Know... It Was...
Except For A Few Creative Liberties,
All Real Unfortunately.
Like Jacob's Love Interest-
Much Funnier In The Movie.
What Do You Mean?
I Think Riley's Funny.
Wait, Oh, So Riley Is Rachel, Right?
Jacob's Muse?
Where Is She?
I Would Love To Meet That Girl.
You Know, Just For Research.
Just One Little Problem...
No, There's No Problem.
You Can Call Her.
Call Her?
Could You Give Us,
Like, One Quick Second?
I'll See You At The Next Hole.
Be Right There.
There Is Absolutely No
Way I'm Calling Riley
To Reminisce About A Relationship
That Just Completely Blew Up.
Owen Likes The
Dynamic In The Script.
What If He Senses, Like,
The Major Tension Between Us?
No, He Won't, Okay?
Riley Can Play Nice For One Day.
That's It. All Right?
You Might Have Broken Up, But She
Is A Good Person With A Gigantic Heart.
She Is Gonna Do This.
That Transfer From Johns Hopkins,
He's Waiting For You At Reception.
- Excuse Me?
- The Dean Wanted You To Show Him The Ropes.
Been In That Position.
Might As Well Pay It Forward.
You're Mansfer From Johns Hopkins?
You Actually Inspire
People To Stay Alive?
- Are You Stalking Me?
- Don't Flatter Yourself.
I Got The Apartment Listing
From The Admin Bulletin Board.
So If You're Going To Be Mad,
Be Mad At Whoever Posted It.
That Would Have Been Me.
- Come On.
- How About We Start Over.
Drew Pragin.
Let's Hope
You're Better At Playing Doctor
Than You Are At Playing Guitar.
I'm Actually Very Good.
Still Don't Know Your Name.
Lauren Yung, Third Year.
This Is Alice Redding, 75.
She's Suffered From An
Abdominal Aortic Aneurysm.
Not Big On Small Talk, Huh?
She's Recovering From An
Endovascular Stent Graft.
Her Bp's Being Monitored Constantly.
- I Figured Out Why You Don't Like Me.
- Not Liking You Would Presuppose...
- Actually Having Thought About You.
- You Don't Think I'm Serious Enough.
Let Me Guess...
You Were The Only Sophomore
In Your Ap Bio Class, Am Right?
I Can See You Now...
With Your Braces
And Your Knee-highs.
Taking A Scalpel To Your
Very First Fetal Pig.
It's Kind Of Adorable.
Call Me "adorable" Again.
You'll See What I Can Do With A Scalpel.
Yes, Or No. Your Idea Of A Movie Night
Is Sneaking Popcorn
Into The Surgery Observation Deck.
Right, 'cause Heaven Forbid I
Should Take My Job Seriously.
When Was The Last Time You Laughed?
I'm Not Here To Laugh.
Look, I'm Not Going to
Heal Mrs. Redding heart
By Putting On A Clown Nose And
Telling Knock-knock Jokes.
Maybe Not, But It's Not Going To
Kill Her To Make Her Smile Either.
Come On.
From Vanessa Mancini?
"David, If You're Reading This,
It Means I'm Gone,
and Michael Needs To Know The Truth
about The Night You And I Spent Together.
Shortly After Noah Was Born,
I Ran A Paternity Test.
Michael's Not Noah's Father, David.
You Are.
Vanessa."
Somebody Order Delivery?
Glass Walls. What Am I Thinking?
That Maybe We Could Teach
The Bullpen A Trick Or Two?
I'd Love To, But I'm Starving.
Nice Unicorn Band-aid.
Yeah, Courtesy Of Riley Richmond.
- Did She Bite You?
- Just A Paper Cut.
Thanks For Taking The Meeting. I Hope
It Didn't Waste Too Much Of Your Time.
No, Actually, I Hired Her.
You're Kidding Me.
No. She Has This Dream
of Building Boarding Schools
In The Inner City.
Honey, Everybody Has Dreams,
But I Think Her Only Real Experience
Is With United Shoes
And Finger Paint.
Well, My Team Needs A Fresh,
Young Perspective.
And So She's The Perfect Fit.
Happy To Hear It.
But You Didn't Trek Moo Shu Pork
Through The Beverly Hills Lunch Rush
To Talk About Riley Richmond,
Did You?
Riley Who?
Exactly.
I'd Like To Make A Payment
Into My Account Please. $1,500.
According To The University Records,
You're All Paid Up.
I Wish.
Seriously. Zero Balance.
I Checked Online Yesterday
And I Still Had An Outstanding
Balance Of $16,000.
Says There Was A Payment In
That Amount Made This Morning.
Either Our Office
Made A Huge Mistake
Or You've Got Yourself A Guardian
Angel With Some Deep Pockets.
Right.
Thank You.
I'm On My Way Out.
I've Just Come From
The Bursar's Office
And Someone Made An Anonymous
Donation To My Tuition.
Congratulations.
You Didn't Have To Do That.
You Think I Paid Off One
Of My Student's Tuition?
You're Good,
But You're Not That Good.
Dr. Mancini, I-i'm Serious.
I Can't Take Your Money.
It Wasn't Mine.
But Since The Bill's
Already Been Paid,
Then There's Really Nothing
You Can Do About It, Is There?
- Who?
- New Transfer From Johns Hopkins.
Fellow Member Of Aoa. Huge Fan.
Means Nothing To Me.
Welcome To Ula.
I'm Glad You Think It's Funny.
- What Is It?
- Can You Hear Me?
Where Are You?
I'm At The Malibu
Speed Zone Right Now,
With This Really
Random Question For You.
Yeah, What?
Owen Anderson... He, Uh,
He Really Wants To Meet You.
- The Actor?
- I Know, It's Crazy, Right?
I'm Meeting Him Here Today
For Living In Reverse,
and He's Like, "hey, Man,
I'd Love To Meet Riley
just, You Know, To See What Inspired You
To Create These Characters."
So You Want Me To Act Like
Everything's Good Between Us?
I Know I'm The Last Person
You Want To Be Around Right Now.
I Get That.
It's Just The Five Incredibly
Happy Years We Spent Together...
- That Is What This Movie's About.
- I Know.
Do You Think I Can Relieve All
Those Memories Without
Going Through The Emotions
That Went Along With Them?
Why Would I Want To Put
Myself Through That?
I Know, I Know. I'm An Idiot.
I Don't Know Why.
It's The Most Ridiculous Thing
I Could Have Asked You To Do.
I Just... I'm So Caught Up
In The Moment Right Now,
And I'm Still On This High
From Selling My Script.
And I Am Sitting Here Sharing My Life
With Owen Freaking Anderson.
I Mean, Who Wouldn't Be.
You Wrote It With Him In Mind.
I Know, And Now He's Like,
"hey, Man, Just Call Riley."
I'm Like, Sure, Jump Off A Cliff-
Okay, No Problem.
Aw, I Wasn't Thinking.
This... Was Not Really Fair
Of Me To Ask You. I'm Sorry.
Do Not Disturb.
Read The Sign.
It's David...
Come On, Dad, Open The Door.
- What The Hell Do You Want?
- I Don't Want To Fight.
- Where's Noah?
- With Vanessa's Sister.
He'll Be At The House
Until I'm Off Probation.
- Isn't This Your Bat Signal?
- Whoever It's For...
They'll Probably Live
Longer Without My Help.
How Many Of These
Have You Had To Drink?
What Are You, My Father Now?
Come On, Dad.
You Can't Hide In Here Forever.
Vanessa Killed Sydney.
It's Not Your Fault.
Vanessa found out about my affair.
I Did Everything But Put
The Knife In Her Hand.
I Have...
Destroyed Everything That's
Ever Come Into My Life.
Every Marriage, Every Second Chance.
Even My Relationship With You.
And Now The Only Thing
I Have Left Is Noah.
And I Can't Look At
Him Without Knowing...
That I'm The Reason...
He'll Grow Up Without A Mother.
Dad, There's Something You
Need To Know About Noah.
Before You And Vanessa Ever Met...
She And I Got Together.
- What Are You Talking About?
- It Was At That Racquetball Tournament.
She Was New In Town.
You Guys Didn't Even Know Each Other.
Why Are You Telling Me This?
Noah's Not Your Son, Dad.
He's Mine.
I Know It's A Lot To Process.
I'm Just As Surprised As You Are.
Get Out.
I Have No Intention Of
Taking Him From You.
I Just Want To Be Able To Spend
As Much Time As I Can With Him.
You Will Never
Get Close To My Child.
You Will Not Talk To Him.
You Will Not Write To Him.
As Far As He's Concerned,
You Don't Exist.
I'm Not Just Going To Disappear.
You Don't Trust Your
Minions To Do That For You?
No Big Deal.
Just Bumped Into A File Cabinet.
Everything Okay With You?
It's My Heart.
You Actually Have One?
It's Been, Um...
Beating Irregularly.
This Morning I Thought I
Was Having A Heart Attack.
Grab A Seat.
Your Heart Sounds Fine.
Any Other Symptoms?
Shortness Of Breath, Dizziness,
- Sweating?
- All Of The Above. Why?
Are You Experiencing A
Lot Of Stress Lately?
I Want You To Think. Work,
Family Problems, Relationships?
No More Than Anyone Else.
The Truth, Amanda.
That Is The Truth.
I Mean, Wpk Is Doing Well.
And Ben Is Wonderful.
Sounds Like You're
Having Panic Attacks.
Panic Attacks?
That's Ridiculous.
My-my Life Is Perfect.
It's Better Than Perfect.
I'm Writing You A
Prescription For Sertraline.
- I Don't Need...
- Please,
No Arguing.
Now If You Don't Start
Feeling Better Immediately,
I Want You To Call Me.
Thank You, Michael.
And I'd Appreciate...
Keeping This Between Us.
I'll Add It To The List.
You're Here?
You Actually Came.
Thank You.
I'm Not Here For You.
I'm Here For Jonah.
Where Is He?
Owen Dragged On The Racetrack
For A Playdate.
Can We Just Get This Over With?
Of Course. So You Being Here Right Now
Is That Selfish Thing
That Attracted Jacob To Rachel.
It's What Made You Supercouple
All Those Years
And Exactly What Owen
Needs To Hear About.
If You Two Can Keep Things Positive,
There Is A Good Chance We Can Cast An
A-lister For The Part.
Hi. I'm Riley.
Jonah Never Said
that you were a goddess.
Man, I Feel Like I Totally Know You.
Tell Me Everything There
Is To Learn About
The Loveable Jacob And Rachel.
So, First Time We Meet,
At A Halloween Party,
And We're Both Waiting
In Line For The Bathroom.
And Jonah Was Darth Vader...
- And I Was This 600-pound Sumo Wrestler.
- Sumo Wrestler. Huge.
Did You Actually Get
Stuck In That Doorway?
Oh, My God, Yeah.
Not Stuck... Wedged.
I'm Talking Bust Out The Crisco,
Major Emergency.
Yeah, And Meanwhile,
There's This Long Line
Of Drunk Frat Boys Waiting
To Use The Bathroom,
And There I Am In This
Ridiculous Costume,
- Like, Totally Blocking The Door.
- She's, Like...
So I Just. I Holster My Lightsaber,
I Grab This Big Sumo Belt...
And Just Start Yanking
As Hard As I Could.
Oh, A-and She... You Fell...
Yes, Yeah, That's Right.
Oh, And Say What You Said,
Say What You Said.
I Can't Breathe.
That's Classic, Man,
It's So Funny, I Love That.
So Sweet.
Irony Is I Was Actually Planning
On Being A Pirate, But...
Saw The Sumo Outfit...
And Changed My Mind At The Last Second.
No Way.
Wait, So You Guys
Almost Didn't Even Meet?
Dude, Why Didn't You Put
That in the script?
Characters That Change Their Mind
That's Way Too Confusing
For The Audience, So I Wanted
To Keep It Simple And Clean.
I Don't Think It's
That Unrealistic...
For Rachel To Hesitate
Before Committing...
Her Entire Night To Some Enormous,
Suffocating Costume.
Why Don't We Talk About The Graduation
Scene That Happens In Act Two?
Actually, You Know, I Kind Of Want
To Feel Out This Vibe Right Here.
What, This?
This Is Nothing.
Riley Just Has This
Teeny Bad Habit...
Of Changing Her Mind.
He's Referring To Our Engagement.
I Didn't Answer Immediately,
Then All Hell Broke Loose,
And We Broke Up.
Dude, Splitsville? No Way.
W-where's That Story?
Look, They May Have Broken Up,
But That Does Not Mean...
That They Didn't Share
A Storybook Love Story.
Storybook?
You Slept With Him.
Whoa, What? Dude,
Jacob And Rachel's Destinies...
Are Cosmically Intertwined,
And You Cheated On Her?
No, No, See,
I Didn't Cheat On Her...
Because Riley And I Had
already ended things,
So Technically It Was Over.
And Who Was There Waiting?
The Vulture In Versace.
There's That Sense Of Humor
We Were Just Talking About.
You Know What? I'm Done.
I'm Sorry, Owen.
I Like Your Movies, But I Don't
Need To Be Dragged Through This.
Why Don't I Go Talk To Her?
Perfect, That's Really Going To
Help Patch Things Up Here, Ella.
I Am So Sorry About...
Why Didn't You Tell Me
That You Guys Broke Up?
Look, Your Story Felt So Real,
And I-i Wanted To...
Get To Know These Characters
A Little Bit Better.
But, Honestly, Now I Just Feel...
Confused.
Sorry, Man.
Can You Just Come Back Here
So We Can Straighten Things Out?
If I Had Known You Were Behind This,
I Would Have Never Come
Anywhere Near Here.
So You're Just Going To Let Jonah's
Career Slip Through His Fingers?
My God, How Selfish Are You?
Oh, I'm Selfish?
You're The One Who Didn't Even Wait
A Day Before Roping Him Into Bed.
Please, Sweetheart,
Like It Took Convincing.
Honestly,
I Don't Know What He Sees In You.
I Guess You Massage
Someone's Ego Enough
- And You Eventually Become Attractive.
- Do You Have Any Idea...
Why Jonah And I Started Hanging Out?
Okay, He Had An Extra
Ticket To A Coen Brothers...
Film Festival That You Bailed On.
Like That Wasn't The
Best Day Of Your Life.
He Came To Me, Riley,
Just Like He Did Every Other Time
You Slammed The Door In His Face.
How Delusional Are You?
Do You Really Think
Jonah Finds Comfort
In Some Selfish Home Wrecker
Who Hasn't Committed
To Anything More Than A Pair Of Shoes
In Her Entire Life?
You Might Be Able To Talk
Movies And Get Him Meetings...
But You Will Never Win
Over His Heart.
Jonah's Way Too Good For You.
You're Going To Destroy Your Auditory
System By The Time You're 30.
Sorry, What?
Couldn't Hear You.
You're An Idiot, You Know That?
- Coming Through.
- Get Away From Me.
- Found Her Wandering The Streets.
- Leave Me Alone.
Seriously, This Is So Illegal.
Here We Go.
What's Your Name, Sweetheart?
Why, So You Can Call My Parents?
I'm Not A Moron.
Honey,
If We Don't Know What Happened,
- We Can't Help You.
- Good, I Don't Want Your Help.
- Just Let Me Go.
- You Need To Calm Down.
All Of You People Suck.
- Stop.
- Guys,
Can I Have A Second Here, Please?
Alone.
You, Too.
- Are You Serious?
- This May Be The One Time I Am.
All Right, Here's The Thing.
I Don't Really Care What Happened,
But If I Don't Write
Something Down In Your File,
My Boss Freaks Out,
So If It's Cool With You,
I'm Just Going To Fill
This Out With Some fiction.
Fine By Me.
Great.
- What Are You Writing?
- Just That You Crashed
On Your Razor Scooter.
My Razor Scooter?
What, Am I Nine?
At Least Say I Was Driving A Car...
Going 80.
That's Good. That's Very Good.
That's Way Better Than Mine.
And I'll Say Your Car Did What,
Like, A Nasty Flip Off Mulholland?
No, I Hit A Giant Tree...
On Alpine, Exploded Both My Airbags.
Tell Me You Were
Wearing A Seat Belt.
Yeah, And Now My Ribs Kill.
I Think I Got Everything I Needed Here,
Except For A Name.
How About, Dumbo?
- Dumbo?
- Is That Two Ms Or One?
Two, Right?
Just Put My Real Name...
Caitlin Rogers.
All Right.
Not Bad.
You Should See Me With Animals.
Wendi,
Thank You For Calling Me Back.
Your Voice Mail Sounded Urgent.
Is Everything Okay?
Yeah, I'm-i'm Good.
Actually, I'm Really Good.
I Paid Off My Tuition,
So... I'm Done.
- Oh, Well, That's Great, Lauren.
- Thank You.
But Aren't You Forgettin Something?
I Told You I Never Forget A Debt.
- You Owe Me One Last Job.
- I'll Just Pay You Back.
I've Got $1,500.
Too Late, I Already Booked You For
Tonight And I Can't Let This Client Down.
Wendi, I'm-i'm Sure You
Can Find Another Girl.
It's A Busy Night.
Everybody's Taken.
I'm-i'm Sorry, But I'm Done.
I Can't Do This Anymore.
Lauren, Do I Need To Remind
You What You Have To Lose?
One Phone Call
To The Medical Board...
And All This Is For Nothing.
Are You Threatening Me?
Do I Need To?
One More.
Thank God.
I Started To Feel Naked
Without This Thing.
You Know What I'm Good At?
Just Taking Something
That's Really Amazing...
And Then Screwing It Up Completely.
God.
- When Did I Go Wrong With All This?
- When You Started Trusting Me.
I Should Not Have Asked You
To Drag Riley Into A Dog And Pony Show.
- This Whole Thing Was A Mistake.
- No, We Both Had To Vent.
We Just Chose The Worst Possible
Venue Ever.
No, I'm Talking About Us.
We... Are A Mistake.
You And Riley Are Cut From The Same
Snuggly, Fuzzy Cloth, And I'm...
Let's Face It,
I'm Industrial-strength Sandpaper.
No, You Guys Have
Five Years Of Fairy Tale.
And What Do I Have,
Five Years Of One-night Engagements?
I Can Kick Open Doors
For Your Career All Day Long,
But When It Comes To
Actually Opening Myself Up...
And Letting Somebody In, It's...
It's An Entirely Different Story.
And Yes, I Am Selfish, But...
It's Just Because I
Don't Want To Get Hurt.
No, Jonah, I'm Serious.
Why Do You Think That I
Spend Every Last Ounce...
Of Energy That
I Have On My Career...
Or Why I'd Rather Be
At A Business Meeting
Than A Candlelit Dinner?
I'm Not As Tough As You Think, Okay?
I Can't Handle Having My Heart Broken.
I Want To Rewrite My Script.
What?
Owen Totally Responded To The
Authenticity,
But There's One Part
That's Just Complete Fiction
The Ending.
Can We Call Him Right Now?
- Yeah, Why?
- I Want To Throw Him A Hail Mary.
I'm Gonna Ask Him To Reconsider
If I Change The Ending.
That All Sounds Really Great, Jonah,
But You Don't Know How The Story Ends.
Actually...
I Wanted To Ask You If I
Could Bounce Some Ideas off you.
Where Did That Skeleton Come From?
No Clue, It Was Just Sitting There.
- Scared The Crap Out Of Me.
- Mission Accomplished.
She's A Cautionary Tale.
Don't Call Him Over.
- He's Really Cute.
- I Don't Care, Don't Call Him Over.
Come Join Us.
- I Hate You Right Now.
- What?
Hey, Drew, This Is Riley,
One Of Your New Neighbors.
This Is Drew, The Thorn That's
Been In My Side All Day.
Welcome. And For The Record,
Lauren Plays Tough,
But She's A Total Softy At Heart.
- Did You Steal That From Ula?
- Sally Sunburn?
No, They Were
Going To Throw Her Away.
I Thought She'd Be A Nice
Addition To The Courtyard.
Who Brought The Skeleton?
That Would Be Me.
I'm Drew.
- I Live Right Above You.
- What Happened?
- It's Just A Scratch.
- Everything's Okay?
I'm Gonna Get A Drink.
Now I Have To Add Chef...
To Your Growing List Of Credentials?
Hardly.
I'm Guessing You're Not Interested
- In Joining Us For A Burger.
- I'd Love To, But Amanda Would Kill Me
If I Got Ketchup On The Monkey Suit.
No, We're Headed Off To Venice
- To A "save The Something" Fund-raiser.
- You Never Stop Working, Do You?
No, I Do Not, And Neither Will You
If I Use You The Right Way.
I'm Taking The Jet To D.C.
I Thought Maybe We Could Check
Out That School In Person.
You Free Tomorrow?
Am I Free To Fly Across The Country...
In Your Private Jet?
Yeah, I Just Have To Reschedule
My Lunch With Madonna.
- Is She In Town?
- I'm Kidding.
I Don't Know Madonna.
Wait, Do You?
Congratulations, Riley.
I Understand You Made Quite
An Impression On My boyfriend.
I Couldn't Have Done It Without You.
Thanks Again For Making The Introduction.
- My Pleasure.
- Good Night.
Resident Hollywood Power Players. How'd
Your Meeting With Owen Anderson Go?
Actually Just Got Off
The Phone With Him.
He Seems Really Interested
In My Ideas For A Rewrite,
As Soon As I'm Done
he promised me we'll meet again.
- What Does That Mean?
- Jonah's Going To Change The Ending.
Turns Out Rachel And Jacob
Don't Make It After All.
- I'm Sorry, Work's Pulling Me Back.
- Can I See That Phone For A Second?
I Just Want To Call Your Boss And Ask
Him For A Night Alonwith My Girlfriend.
I Think The
Long Hours Are Just About Over,
And Then'm All Yours.
All Right, Okay.
- I Didn't Get A Page, But I Should Go.
- I'll Probably get There...
And They Won't Even Need Me,
So Good-bye.
Okay, Well, At Least Let
Me Walk You To The Car.
Night.
You Hate Me And You, I Don't Know.
Great, I Think I'm Gonna Call
It A Night.
So, Drew, Are You Into
Cardiology Like Lauren?
I Transferred To Ula For
Their Hematology Program.
Hematology, Like Blood?
Why Would Anyone Want
To Specialize In That?
Well, If I Tell You,
You Promise Not To Tell Anybody Else?
I'm A Vampire.
It Was So Much Better
In My Head. Yeah.
You Going To Get That?
Oh, My God.
I've Never Seen You
Ignore A Phone Call.
There's A Lot Of
Things You Haven't Seen.
This Is How My Star Student's
Been Paying For Med School.
It's Not What It Looks Like.
I've Never Done Anything
Like This Before.
Interesting,
Because Wendi Told Me...
You Were One Of Her Go-to Girls.
I'm Not Going
To Say Anything About This
To Anyone.
I'd Appreciate It If You'd Do The Same.
It Won't Leave This Room.
Thank You.
That Doesn't Mean I Don't
Expect Something In Return.
Y-you Don't Actually Want To...
It's David.
If He Hadn't Interfered In My Life,
Noah Would Still Have A Mother.
I Don't Understand What
That Has To Do With Me.
David Needs To Know
What It Feels like
To Have All The Happiness
In His Life Ripped Away.
I Want You To Break His Heart.
Whatever You Have With Him, End It.
- You Can't Be Serious.
- You Break It Off With Him,
Or I Tell The Entire
Medical Community...
That I Got A House Call From Dr.
Lauren Yung.