Previously...
It's not like our engagement
expires at midnight.
If it doesn't happen today,
it'll happen another time.
Or not ever?
Would that be better for you?
Wait... I don't want to
be just a one-night stand.
You're not.
There's something you need to know.
I slept with Ella last night.
Are you guys, like,
over or, like, over over?
There's no putting
empty back together again.
What are you doing
with my mom's ring?
You could get in, like,
so much trouble if my father caught you.
Take that back and
then we'll just act like
- none of this ever happened.
- I have a better idea.
I'll take an IOU.
Amanda does not come all the way across
the country just to slap us on the wrist.
She's been asking all kinds of
- questions about you.
- She's the president of WPK.
The painting
I'm looking for isn't here.
Are you sure you searched
every apartment in the complex?
Searched and shot
film in all but one.
- You called your dad?
- Hell, no.
You owe me one last job.
I want you to break David's heart.
Whatever you have with him, end it,
or I tell the entire
medical community
that I got a house call
from Dr. Lauren Yung.
I am literally gonna be
drinking myself into a haze
at this party tonight.
Dude, check this out.
State-of-the-art fog machine.
If we are celebrating
my script sale,
it's got to be a couple notches over
watered-down beer
and a bowl of potato chips.
I guess I'll have to
pre-hydrate for this one.
Spoken like a seasoned vet.
You don't mind if I rig some lights
from outside your place, do you?
I am sparing no expense
throwing this party.
I am all about turning this
place into club Melrose, but, Jonah,
keep in mind,
that paycheck you got...
there is a little thing
called taxes and commissions.
I always said to myself,
as soon as I make my first stack
of Hollywood Benjamins, I'm
gonna throw a huge blowout
for all the people
who believed in me.
So sweet.
Hold on one sec. I'll be right.
Has...
- Lauren broken her silence yet?
- She hasn't said a word.
I just want some clue why she just
suddenly pulled the plug on us.
Well, who knows? Maybe
tonight she'll loosen up.
Normally, when the alcohol
flows, so do the words.
Who's buried in her work now, huh?
I'm almost done.
So, in honor of your
first day off in, like, ages,
I'm thinking that we go
shopping on third street,
lunch at Joan's and mani-pedis?
- Sounds like perfection.
- Doesn't it?
I could use a day off, too.
This fund-raising crusade
is like pulling teeth.
If anyone can do it, you can.
You've been through so much.
And you're still standing.
I'm in awe.
It hasn't exactly been easy.
Especially watching Jonah
leap into Ella's waiting arms.
But it's getting better.
What about you and David?
You never told me what happened.
Come in.
Ladies.
I admit it. I am slightly intrigued
by the idea of wearing
women's lingerie,
but since I am new here,
I thought I'd return these.
- Found them in the dryer.
- Oh, God.
- How did you know?
- Your name's embroidered on them.
- Very classy.
- They were a gift from my grandma.
Well, grandma had a great taste.
Yeah, sure. I'll be right in.
- I gotta work.
- Wait, what about our girl date?
Team Mancini has
no time for social lives.
When you're working with the top
cardiologist in the country,
there's a certain amount
of abuse that comes
with the territory.
You're the
resident expert on
all things kid-related.
And since your girl day
is a no-go, do you
do you want to come
toy shopping with me?
I should probably get back to
working on my fund-raising thing.
Please tell me
the toys aren't for you.
They're for my rug rats.
- Your rug rats?
- They're for the kids
- in the pediatric ward.
- Oh. All right.
Well, I just thought I'd ask.
Knowing me, I'll probably end up
buying toys made from lead.
We can't let that happen.
So, Jane, what dragged you out
of the 818 so bright and early?
Typically, when a friend
drops by, you ask how she is,
maybe offer her coffee or tea.
I wasn't sure we fell into
the "friends" category.
Don't be silly. I did agree
to let you live here, Amanda.
Not quite out of
the goodness of your heart.
Along with a security deposit,
you insisted I fire Ella.
And I'm still waiting.
I honestly don't understand
what's taking you so long.
Ella will suffer for pulling the
red carpet out from under you,
but personnel changes take time.
You know,
I have a long list
of people who'd move
into this penthouse tomorrow,
if it were to somehow go vacant.
Ella will get what's coming to her.
Now, if you'll excuse me, not
everyone can spend their day
playing dress-up with mannequins.
Okay, Jasper, sweetheart.
Yeah, yeah, calm down, okay?
When you talk like that,
you sound like you're
in a Guy Ritchie movie.
What? WPK billed you
ten grand last month?
That's impossible. I signed you.
Your retainer's for $5,000.
Okay. I will e-mail you
a statement right now.
There has been some sort of mistake.
I will clear this up before you are done
with your breakfast tea and crumpet.
Clear what up?
That was Jasper Barnes.
There seems to be some sort of...
Billin mistake.
I just got an earful
from his business manager.
He is accusing the company
of deliberately trying to
pocket an extra five grand.
- That would never happen, would it?
- On one of my accounts?
No. Never.
Good, 'cause if anyone tries to
steal out of WPK's cookie jar,
they'll be walking out with a
pink slip, wearing handcuffs.
What the hell is going on?
That was a close call with
Mr. Lewis this morning.
Nearly bled out on
the operating table.
- Is he all right?
- He pulled through like a champ.
You want me to start
his post-op blood work?
Actually, I'm going to
need you for something else.
You know, surgeries like this one,
they can really get
the adrenaline flowing.
I can't unwind. But luckily, I think
that's something you
can help me with.
I did what you asked.
I broke up with David.
You wouldn't want me to tell
the people in your building
that they sharpool with
a hooker, would you?
If you did that, you'd
be exposing yourself.
Actually, it's a funny
thing about heart surgeons.
You realize that no one really
cares about your personal life
when you're holding
their heart in your hand.
Now, I paid for a transaction
that was never completed.
So, I booked a room
at the Waverly, and...
I have to scrub in
for a triple bypass.
I hope it goes well.
I'll let you get to it.
I'll call you when
I get out of the OR.
Lauren?
Plan on spending the night.
Dark_Chii, Just-In, peluche0706,
P$!ko^^, simplicity, WoLF971
How much do you love this place?
I used to make my allowance
stretch here for days.
You know, it was really sweet of you
- to cheer Lauren up the other night.
- Yeah, Dr. Teflon Yung...
She had a real moment.
How is she doing?
Are you asking because
you're a concerned neighbor,
or because,
now that she's single, you...?
Lauren? Oh, come on.
Look, the girl's impressive...
she's smart, she's beautiful...
but dating a coworker
who's also your neighbor
is doomed on so many levels.
See, this would be fun for battle...
like, gurney to gurney... as
long as nobody pops an I.V.
Maybe something like this...
To cuddle in a dark hospital room?
- It's goofy, but it's cute.
- Yeah, maybe we should ask an expert.
Cual es tu, uh, juguete favorito?
- Este.
- Si'?
Si'.
All right. Take one of
each. Quiero todo, si?
- Bueno, senor. Gracias.
- Oye, mi amigo.
- Gracias.
- De nada.
So, how many of Sydney's
paintings did you find?
Jane had a bunch in
that storage unit.
Tested all the canvases. None
were hiding a Dutch masterpiece.
Well, someone in this building
knows where that painting is.
Yeah, let's put the bar over here.
Okay, sure.
What do we have for alcohol?
- We got whiskey, tequila...
- You know what?
I'll just have to find another
tactic to get them talking.
Gorgeous, yes. Right there.
Gorgeous. That's right.
Give me more eyes. Eyes here.
Beautiful. Okay, shoulder.
That's right. Gorgeous.
Closer!
Cupcake.
How are you?
I'm on the clock for W, not WPK.
- And, uh, this is a closed set.
- Oh. Will you look at that?
You are actually letting the models
keep their clothes on for once.
How sweet.
Please don't tell me you
traipsed all the way downtown
to give me another
lecture on selling out.
I just wanted to make sure
that you were properly paid
for the Anton V project. That's all.
If you're wondering if
the check cleared, the answer is yes.
And now, if you'll excuse me.
Here. Let's go with the 35.
You must have quite the agent,
to have negotiated that deal,
I mean, 200 grand for a day's work?
Even Annie Leibovitz
would be jealous.
$200,000? Are you kidding me?
Try doing some math
and dividing by ten.
Your check was for $20,000?
Well, your name was on it.
You're my account rep.
You should know.
We're all set for my
friend's party tonight, right?
Sushi trays, kobe beef sliders,
- and French fry bar?
- I'm all over it.
- Okay. Great.
- I love watching you in action.
Morgan, what are you doing here?
You didn't call.
Which kind of shocked me,
considering I'm pretty sure
you had a good time the other night.
I did. I did, but...
Hey, I need two
drinks at table eight.
- You got it.
- I brought you something.
That's a $5,000 watch,
Morgan. Where'd you get that?
Stole it from my dad.
You're not the only one who
gets a rush from stealing.
When I saw you take my mom's ring,
I knew we were made for each other.
Morgan, come here.
Listen, that ring was
the end for me, all right?
That's the last time I'm
ever gonna rip anybody off.
Why am I having a hard
time believing that?
Okay, look.
I just got out of a relationship.
I'm so sorry if I lead you on.
I just... I can't do this with you.
You're not saying you
don't want to see me again?
Because my dad is
sitting right there.
And I think you know he is not the
kind of guy you want to mess with.
What do you think you're doing?
Father-daughter lunch.
He loves to hit the hot spots.
My dad and I are super close.
And he'd love nothing more
than for me to open up to him,
tell him all about you.
So... I'll see you soon. Okay?
Sounds great, man.
Okay, this one... this
is my favorite one so far.
- Great. Here's another one.
- Ella. Come here.
I have yet to master
the art of solo drinking.
Help me sample some of
these delicious cocktails.
Oh, it is like you
looked inside my brain
and saw a flashing Martini glass.
Either you're trying to
set a speed drinking record,
or you had one bad
day at the office.
I was going to
text you on my way home,
but I gave up texting and driving.
- Thank you.
- May I...?
- Here you go.
- Oh, thank you.
Jonah, something seriously
shady is going on at work.
I think I'm being set up.
It sounds like my conspiracy theories
are finally catching up with you.
Unfortunately, I think
it's beyond a theory.
There are financial discrepancies
all over my client list.
It's like a gigantic red arrow
is pointing at my pockets.
- How are you?
- Sweetie.
Oh, God,
I looked like you a minute ago...
Then I discovered vodka
makes a lot of things better.
Thank you, but I'm so
not in a party mood right now.
I think I just had the worst
day at the hospital ever.
Mancini is making my life hell.
Well, it's a good thing
you're done for the day.
There's actually one more
thing I'm supposed to do.
Whatever it is, it can wait.
No work talk. No boy talk.
Tonight, all we do is drink, dance,
and deal with our collective
nightmares in the morning.
- I feel better already.
- See?
I'm going to go get changed,
and come right back out.
You better. Director's orders.
Don't make me get my megaphone.
Okay, we've got ankimo,
kurodai, yellowtail...
all line-caught this morning.
You want first crack?
I'm heading over to the Waverly.
I'll expect you there in an hour.
And, Lauren? You know that cute little
dress you had on the other night?
Wear that.
I don't know what any of this is,
but I'm practically drooling.
It's pupusas. Nothing scary inside.
I taught down here for two years.
- How do I not know about this place?
- Well, between work and traffic,
it's easy to get caught up in your
own world. Especially if you're
sharing the same bed with
somebody for five years.
Now, I don't want to pry, but...
What happened between you guys?
I mean, it must've taken a seismic shift
for it to flame out after five years.
Jonah was so focused on the future,
and I just
wasn't in a place where I was ready
to commit for the rest of my life.
And in the end, I think that we both
just wanted different things out of life.
He likes to make movies
and play pretend,
and I'm all about the real world.
In the game that is called life...
Jonah has rolled
the dice and moved on.
What about you?
Are you ready to get back
out there and take your turn?
I guess that all depends
on what I'm playing for.
Make every drink a triple, and believe
me, I'll make it worth your while.
No problem.
Hey, you made it, with drew.
- Where are you guys coming from?
- Drew took me to the most amazing
- Salvadorian place downtown.
- She was fearless.
She wanted to try
everything on the menu.
I knew you were having a party, but I didn't
know it was gonna be a major blowout.
Hey, you know, once I got
paid for "Living in Reverse",
I just thought, you know something?
Why not give back a little?
Okay, people,
shots are not optional.
- What is this, plutonium?
- Close. It's called a ghostbuster.
How painfully cute!
Who'd you knock up?
No one. I actually kidnapped
Riley today to go toy shopping
for the pediatric ward.
Why not give back a little, right?
I know why you broke up with me.
- This is not...
- Just say it: I grew up in a trailer;
I didn't go to a fancy college,
I have a rap sheet, not a resume.
- I'm not good enough for you.
- That's not true.
No, that not true. Non-of
this is matter to me.
You don't have to lie to me,
Lor. What?
If it's not who I am,
then tell me what I
did, and I'll let it go.
You didn't do anything.
Okay? It's just...
- You don't really know who I am.
- What?
- I'm not good enough for you.
- What are you talking about? Lauren...
- I can't talk about this anymore.
- What?!
- Where are you going? Lauren!
- David, I'm sorry.
Michael! Something tells me
you didn't read about this
little bash on Twitter.
What brings you back
to Melrose place?
I was just in the area.
I thought I'd check in on you,
see if those prescriptions I wrote
you were, making a difference.
Oh, I'm feeling good as new.
Amanda, I thought you'd be the one
phoning in the noise complaints,
not causing them.
Look at you.
- Wow, time has been good to you.
- You, too.
So, I... read about that... What
was it? A heart valve you invented?
Maybe our second
divorce was a mistake.
Wow, that almost sounded
like a compliment.
Jane, before you pull
the plug on this party,
you have to try at least one mojito,
'cause I'm sure you guys have
a lot of catching up to do.
So, who'd have thought, all those
years ago, lying around the pool,
that you'd end up
owning this building?
It does seem to have a strange
gravitation pool, doesn't it?
Ella. Should I have your assistant
scrape you off the patio
tile tomorrow morning?
I was just getting
in the spirit of things,
but I can assure you
that all of my clients
- have been fed and watered.
- Ella, we're off the clock.
Now I know that you and Sydney
used to have a drink or two
when she had the penthouse.
We should do the same.
I'm sure you could handle
your liquor better than Sydney could.
She had a tendency to
not to stop drinking
- until she was unconscious.
- Her coping mechanisms
weren't always doctor recommended,
but at least she had an
outlet through her painting.
Her own art? It was a
step above finger painting.
I rather liked it.
She actually was working on a piece
for me around the time that she died.
And I've been looking
for it everywhere.
Do you know if she had
any of her work in storage?
I wouldn't know. Syd knew
the only artists I cared about
were Manolo, Prada and Louboutin.
If you want to know about her art,
you're going to have to ask David.
What about the Jasper Barnes
account? Issue resolved?
Not yet.
Look, Amanda, something
is happening at work
that I think you should know about.
I think somebody's been
embezzling money from WPK.
- You have any proof?
- I'm working on it.
But I did find out that not
only was Jasper overbilled,
but Jo Reynolds got paid $20,000
when the outgoing
withdrawal was for $200,000.
Anyone you suspect?
I have my theories, but...
No, nothing concrete yet.
So someone is getting
rich off of my company.
Thanks for filling me in.
This one's going in.
I swear,
my cups are wider than yours.
What happened to being
almost professional at this?
Okay, everyone has their off days.
Especially after they've
drunk a few test tubes.
- Anybody got a winner?
- Hey, bro. No, I'm, uh...
Think I'm going to grab a beer
- and retire undefeated.
- What?!
Just gonna call it quits as soon
as some real competition shows up?
We need some balls over here.
- Anyone got any balls?
- Set 'em up, Hollywood.
You're gonna lose.
He's still got it. Excuse me.
He's still got it!
I still got it. Okay.
Why am I suddenly thrilled
that I didn't meet you
till after your crazy college years?
Come on, Lauren, open up.
I know you're in there.
You can't avoid me all night.
Sorry I'm late.
I didn't know that
you were going to be here.
I told you at lunch
I'd see you soon.
Now, let's go get me a cocktail.
I got a better idea.
Let's go up to my place.
This ridiculously hot chick just
asked me for a bottle opener.
You gotta get me one.
I think she's into me.
Nice! I think I...
I have a spare in my...
In her apartment.
There's my Milla the killa.
Where'd you disappear to?
I went to find a bottle opener.
I found drew and Riley
making out instead.
Wow! That must have been rough,
because you look like
you just got hit by a bus.
What? No.
I mean, I didn't expect
her to go join a convent,
and he doesn't appear
to be a serial killer.
The only weird thing is how quickly
the guy went into attack mode.
- At my party, in my old apartment.
- You're not exactly one to talk, Jonah.
I mean, who knocked on my door the night
that you and Riley called it quits?
Jo Reynolds is here?
Did somebody complain
this party wasn't bossy
and overbearing enough?
It's beautiful. Wish I'd been there with
you when you ripped it off.
I got that from a gallery,
Morgan. I'm a collector.
Most of the boys I know
only collect video games.
I bought you
in here so we could talk.
- We can talk, too.
- Okay... all right...
So, the idea that you and I can be
Mr. And Mrs. Smith... I
mean, you gotta let that go.
All right?
Look, Morgan, you're gorgeous,
you're smart, you don't
need to blackmail someone
- into being in a relationship.
- But it is so much more fun this way.
But... okay...
I'm not going to be happy
with some boring guy.
I'm that boring guy now.
Morgan, I've made too may mistakes
in my life, and I'm done.
I'm done repeating them.
David, you'll never be done.
You'll miss the danger too much.
The thrill.
Guys like you weren't
born to live by the rules.
I'm sorry. Don't let me interrupt.
No, not at all.
Morgan was just leaving.
Bye. For now.
Girls do love the bad boys.
Steal any paintings lately?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I own a restaurant.
And the money you used to pay for it
wasn't exactly hard-earned, was it?
And the rumor has it... that you stole
the paintings that Sydney sold overseas.
But that's your business.
I'm just looking for the painting
- she took from me. Any idea where it is?
- I have no idea.
What about the art she
did herself? Her paintings.
I have the one that you saw,
and she gave one to Auggie
right before she died.
Not worth much, aside
from sentimental value.
Auggie...? He's the chef
that used to live here.
- He and Syd had a special bond.
- I'm sure they did.
So, Jane, what do you
say... we turn back the clock
and have a little fun tonight?
After everything we've been through,
I will never be that desperate.
Oh, my God. I feel
like I'm in a time warp.
- Look who it is!
- My God! Jo?
Oh, my goodness.
It's been forever.
Did Amanda invite you or what...?
Something like that.
So, has anyone seen
the queen of publicity?
Isn't this nice? A little
mini-reunion in the courtyard.
Let's do it again in ten years,
shall we?
- Amanda, do you have a moment?
- Does this mean you're here for more
than hot boys in skinny jeans?
Ella Simms told me about
the WPK payout in my name,
and I had visions of
vintage Amanda Woodward
embezzling money
from D&D advertising.
I don't know what you're
trying to accuse me of.
Especially since all the jobs that
made your career came from D&D and WPK.
But I guess that
generosity is lost on you.
You don't have a generous bone in
your body.
But that's about to change.
I mean,
unless you want everyone to know
that you've probably bled
your own company dry by now.
Make the check out to
global hunger project.
Diagnosis, awkward.
No, it wasn't. It's fine.
Hey, that's life.
You're totally cool
with me and Riley?
I'm with Ella.
Man...
that is so great to hear, man.
I guess I can cancel
my trip to home depot
to get that dead bolt
for Riley's front door.
What's that supposed to mean?
Just some friendly advice:
the unannounced drop-in
is a little freakier
when you don't knock.
You might want to call next time.
Dr. McChuckles,
my name is on that lease, all right?
And I lived there for a long
time, so I don't really need you
telling me what I can
and might not want to do.
You don't get to do,
whatever you want with Riley
anymore. She's not your girlfriend.
Okay, so you just
move into this building,
and you start hitting on
every girl who lives here.
Lauren's not around,
so you zone in on Riley?
That's a little desperate, isn't it?
- Who's desperate?
- I think you are.
Desperate's throwing a party like this
to show everybody how awesome you are!
Yo, guys, stop it!
Jonah, stop it.
- You need to stop calling me.
- You never showed up at the hotel.
I lost track of time.
I gotta say, Lauren, standing
here outside your door,
I'm feeling a little neglected here.
I mean, you okay with me
chattin' up your friends...
Tellin' 'em all about
your little part-time job?
Leave me alone.
What's the big deal?
You're a pro.
You do this stuff all the time.
Boy, if I was a less secure
man, I might be offended.
The compromises I made
in my personal life...
they were all about protecting
the one thing that matters to me.
And that's my medical career.
Don't worry, because
this is going to be fantastic
for your medical career.
Hey, don't you dare walk away
- from me, Lauren.
- Watch me.
Hey, you guys. Hey.
Lauren, are you okay?
There's something
I need to tell you.
I've been really scattered
and really overwhelmed
for the last few months, and I've been
telling you all that it's because of work
but it was...
a lot more than that.
Lauren, sweetheart...
Do you think maybe you've had
a little bit too much to drink?
This isn't a drunk confessional
I'm going to forget in the morning.
I lied to you... all of you...
And I know I hurt you.
Six months ago, I fell
behind in my tuition payments.
And, I had to come up with
money
fast... or my dream
of being a doctor
was going to be over.
So...
I did something that I'm going to have
to live with for the rest of my life.
I had sex for money.
I was a prostitute.
Dream or reality?
I heard Dr. Lauren Yung
declare herself a prostitute.
It's not a dream, it's a nightmare.
I mean, she's the last
person I ever thought
would be turning tricks
in her spare time.
Did you have any idea?
I had my suspicions.
Really?
You smell like one part chlorine,
two parts Tequila.
I really tackled drew
into the pool, didn't I?
- You did.
- Oh, well, that's bad.
Normally I find a brawl between
two red-blooded boys kinda hot,
but when it's over your ex-fiancée,
not so much.
I'm sorry.
I acted like a total ass.
I thought we were way past this.
We are.
- Totally.
- Good.
You better be.
Sorry.
I gotta grab my alcohol
poisoning by the horns.
I'm being summoned
to Amanda's office.
- On Saturday morning.
- What?
Do you think
she knows you're onto her?
Well, I'm still alive...
so, no, not yet.
About last night. I...
Obviously didn't want
to tell you like that.
When I heard you blaming yourself
for what happened to us, I...
I couldn't take it anymore.
Thanks. That means a lot.
About the way you took
things slow with me,
the late shifts, mysterious texts,
that guy Rick.
How many times did you
look me in the eye and lie?
And the scary thing...
is how good you were.
That tore me up, David.
I tried not to get
involved with you, okay?
But I... I couldn't help myself.
I've never felt like
this about anyone before.
And I'm suddenly
supposed to believe you?
I get it.
Just know that I didn't want
to break up with you, David,
and I've never said
this to anyone before...
But I love you.
Remember, I know what it feels like
to have your whole world
drop out from under you.
You're my best friend.
I'll always be here.
Call me back, okay?
Boy, I don't know who the jerk was
who threw this party last night,
but he sure let things
get out of hand, huh?
What were you thinking, coming
into my apartment like that?
And then playing
schoolyard bully with drew?
I'm sorry.
Last night was not
my shining moment.
You and Ella have been nesting
like lovebirds in this courtyard
ever since the night we
called off our wedding.
Do you think that's
been easy for me?
It's 8:00 a.m. On a Saturday
and you are in the office.
I guess that's what
it takes to be on top.
It's too late to charm your
way out of this one, Ella.
- I know you're the embezzler.
- What?
After what you told me last night,
I audited your accounts,
and it appears
that you've stolen hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
Do you really think that
you can get away with this?
I overheard you talking
to Jo. You set me up.
How much did you drink last
night? God knows what you heard.
And I looked up to you.
You weren't just my boss,
you were the prototype
of everything I wanted in my career.
- But you're nothing but a thief.
- Who's the thief?
With all the money
missing from WPK's coffers,
there's a lot of jail time at stake.
I have never stolen
anything before in my life.
Then I'll consider this
your first offense...
So you better work real
hard to make amends.
Because you, my dear,
do not have the curves to
pull off a prison jumpsuit.