My name is Sydney Bristow.
Seven years ago, I was recruited
by a branch of the CIA called SD-6.
I was sworn to secrecy, but I
couldn't keep it from my fiancé.
And when the head of SD-6
found out, he had him killed.
That's when I learned the truth.
SD-6 is not part of the CIA.
I had been working for the people
I thought I was fighting.
So I went to the only place
that could help me take them down.
Now, I'm a double agent for the CIA.
My handler is Michael Vaughn.
Only one other person
knows what I do,
another double agent inside SD-6.
Someone I hardly know.
My father.
Sloane's having me followed.
If Sloane suspects a double agent,
he'd turn to Dreyer.
Dreyer will give us an imaging test.
It is very difficult to deceive.
- Are you an agent of SD-6?
- Yes.
- Are you a double agent?
- No.
We've found our mole.
- What is that?
- A star chart.
A snapshot taken from a specific
place at one moment in time.
And the only spot on earth
with that exact view of the stars
is on Mount Aconcagua
on the Chile-Argentina border.
I think we're almost
at our way point.
I'm going in.
Dixon? I've found it.
Rambaldi's journal, I've found it.
Sydney, they found us.
What did you do to Dixon?
Dixon? Dixon, do you copy?
Dixon, please don't be...
Dixon!
Oh, no, no, no.
You weren't wearing your vest!
Why weren't you wearing your vest?
You're gonna be OK.
You're gonna be OK, Dixon.
Just hang in.
Take this with you.
It's a satcom phone. You can
contact the CIA from anywhere.
What happens when SD-6 sees I'm
lugging around a CIA-issue phone?
- Don't let them see it.
- It's like a brick. I can't take it.
Take it. Worst case scenario,
you might need it.
Base Ops, this is Freelancer.
How copy? Over.
B Ops reads you, LC. Go ahead.
Freelancer...
This is code six. I repeat, code six.
Emergency med evac, over.
Copy. Launching
extraction team Lancer.
Set navcom transponder
in three, two, one, mark.
Set!
Who's Freelancer? Who's...?
Just hang in there, buddy.
Just hang in there.
Come on, come on.
Just hang in, buddy. I got you.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
So, what happened
when the chopper came?
The CIA helicopter airlifted us
to a hospital in Buenos Aires.
The whole flight,
I was thinking about Sloane.
What he might do
when he found out.
Learning that I was betraying
SD-6 this whole time.
Then I thought of a way out.
I called Sloane, told him that I'd
dragged Dixon back to the Humvee.
And that I drove him
to the hospital myself.
I couldn't tell if he believed me,
but I think he did.
They airlifted us to Los Angeles.
When we got here, they took us
to Angel of Mercy Hospital.
- Good.
- No.
It's an SD-6 hospital.
Gunshot wounds,
14 hours old. Internal bleeding.
Have you been briefed
on your cover story?
- Is he gonna be OK?
- Mrs Dixon wants to talk with you.
I know my story.
Is my partner gonna live?
I dunno.
Then I had to lie to Dixon's wife.
We were outside
the bank's office in Rome
and this car pulled up.
I didn't even see it.
These men stepped out.
They had guns.
They wanted the bank's computer
codes. I had them in my briefcase.
Your husband grabbed me, pulled
me to the ground. I heard gunshots.
You should've seen him.
I didn't even know he'd been hit.
You just never think
something like this...
He's strong. He's gonna make it.
He will make it.
You don't know that.
Dixon was bleeding so much.
I was afraid if I took my hand off
his wound, he'd lose too much blood.
So I used the satcom phone,
right in front of him.
You said he was barely conscious.
But he heard me.
He repeated my code name twice.
I suggest you put operatives there
for when he regains consciousness.
But it's an SD-6 hospital.
He will make it.
You're in a very difficult
position, Mr Dreyer.
You've been sent to SD-6
to find a mole.
The alliance
must be pressuring you.
- I'm just doing my job.
- We're both doing our job.
When I look at Sydney Bristow's test
results, she didn't falter once.
She's guilty. She's the one.
A dangerous accusation
made by a desperate man.
I'm not desperate, Mr Sloane.
But I am curious why you feel
the need to defend Miss Bristow.
I don't.
I don't need to defend her.
The results defend her.
The results are too perfect.
We all have our speciality.
This is mine.
With all due respect, Mr Sloane,
you're ignoring the facts.
Bristow has made numerous mistakes,
not least, her most recent mission.
Her partner was almost killed.
She could have retrieved
the Rambaldi book,
which is now in K-Directorate hands.
Sydney Bristow is the mole.
If you don't follow protocol on this,
I'm going to the alliance.
Dreyer.
Don't you do a damn thing.
I'll take care of Bristow.
- Is Dixon gonna be OK?
- He's in ICU. They don't know.
- Guys with guns came out of a car?
- It was over so quickly.
What for? Codes, bank stuff?
- Can you not be a reporter now?
- I'm asking because I care.
I just think it's weird for this
to happen. First Danny, now this.
Leave her alone, or I will
kick your ass. I'm not kidding.
Thank God you're OK.
Nobody move! Down on the floor!
Get down on the floor!
Stay down!
I've seen hundreds
of bank robberies.
At first glance,
there's nothing out of the ordinary.
But these men
have skills and materials.
The robbery was a distraction.
While those men
were accessing the registers
these two men hacked into the bank's
mainframe and rerouted funds.
They work for Ineni Hassan.
Why would Hassan
rob a bank in the States?
It controlled his assets,
recently frozen by the US government.
He used the men to transfer
his money, so he could access it.
We put up with him for years because
he provided us with good intel.
Now he's closing shop, relocating.
He's been missing for two weeks.
Hassan is dangerous as a free agent.
We must bring him to justice.
- Where did he reroute the money?
- We need to find out.
If we don't steal back his fortune,
he could buy protection
in the Middle East.
He could then partner with a hostile
country and provide them with arms.
Logan Gerace. An accountant
with one client. Ineni Hassan.
Gerace is known
for his parties in Tuscany.
He entertains dignitaries, diplomats.
He's having an event on Friday.
You'll be there. You'll go it alone.
We have no in to the party.
You won't be on the guest list.
Shouldn't be a problem.
You need to retrieve
Hassan's offshore account number
from Gerace's computer,
dead drop the info at Denati Park,
which is five miles from the party.
- When do I leave?
- Tonight.
So this guy I know was killed.
Danny Hecht.
Nicest guy in the world.
Killed in his bathroom.
The police say there was no motive,
no suspect. Then I stumble on this.
There was a video blackout
that night.
- Weird.
- That's weird.
There's more.
There's a woman, Kate Jones,
who was supposed to be travelling
with Danny to Singapore that night.
So I call around, I find this woman.
Winds up she's lying to me.
Her real name is Eloise Kurtz,
and somebody paid her to talk to me.
- Weird!
- Thank you, yeah.
It gets weirder. The woman who said
she was Kate Jones is dead. Killed.
- Who killed her?
- I don't know, that's why I'm here.
Who killed Kurtz?
Who killed Hecht?
Then somebody covers up
the passenger manifest.
I think whoever did that
gave Eloise that pin.
- Here we go.
- What?
Damn!
- This momma's gorgeous!
- Why is she so gorgeous?
MEMS. Micro electromechanical
system technology.
This is, like,
the next gen's next gen.
This is government issue?
The guy at the science lab...
It's on.
- What, you mean, like, right now?
- Yes.
- Who is it?
- I don't know.
- You should report your boss.
- No kidding.
Sending you to Boston after all this.
You deserve a month off.
What do you think
of this wedding dress?
You can't shop for a wedding dress
in a magazine.
Let's go to that boutique
on Beverly.
I always wanted a reason
to go there, and now I have one.
- Yeah. You're getting married.
- I am. I'm getting married.
How about Saturday?
Hello?
- Joey's Pizza?
- Wrong number.
- So, Saturday? Noon?
- For sure.
SD-6 doesn't want to bring Hassan
to justice. They want revenge.
- Revenge for what?
- Something you did.
When Hassan bought the nuclear
weapon and you stole the core back,
he thought he was double-crossed
and only SD-6 knew about the bomb.
Oh, God!
Last week, he sold SD-6 ten Stinger
anti-aircraft missiles for Oman.
Hassan had a good laugh. He took
the money and he didn't deliver.
SD-6 wants to send out a message
to those they do business with.
Don't mess with SD-6.
The CIA
wants to bring Hassan to justice,
but we want SD-6 to have that money.
Why?
So we can tag the accounts
and see where they take it.
It will give us a profile into how
SD-6 does their banking. Take this.
Attach it to
the SD-6 retrieval device.
It'll copy what you get
from the computer.
- OK.
- Are you OK?
I was getting briefed by Marshall.
This thing sucks.
Literally. It sucks information
from the hard drive into the RAM.
Place it on or near the hard drive
and when this light is green,
it's reading.
- How long does it take?
- 40 gigs in two minutes.
Do you want some candy?
I'm trying to make
the place a little more inviting.
Do you want to take a seat
in the inflatable chair?
Come and see me when you're done.
I should start
with your test results.
You passed just fine.
The numbers were normal.
I'd hope so.
I know what a difficult time this is.
I understand.
- Dixon in the hospital.
- Have you heard anything?
Yes. He's still unconscious.
They're not sure how bad it is.
Look, Sydney.
I don't blame you for not talking
to me the way you used to...
...for hating me
since what happened with Danny.
Believe me when I tell you
it was the last thing I wanted.
I begged security section
not to do that.
No, you didn't.
You don't have to believe me.
- Why would you try and stop it?
- Because of you.
I knew there was something about you
from the first time I saw you.
- A lot can change in seven years.
- It's been longer than that.
I've known your father since 1971.
I met him at Langley.
I knew your mother.
I went to your parents' wedding.
I've known you since you were a baby.
I was out of the country for most of
your childhood, various operations.
But I kept tabs on you.
I checked in, in my own way.
I thought of you as my daughter.
Even from the beginning.
Well, I just wanted
to let you know.
Before you went away.
It was almost like
he was saying goodbye.
Like he knew
that I'm not coming back.
You'll be OK. We'll get through this.
Contact me when you get back.
I know, with his account numbers.
No, I mean
with or without the accounts.
- Just as soon as you get back.
- OK.
- OK?
You wanted to see me?
- Sir?
- Yes.
I need to send a communiqué
to SD-4 Office in Rome.
Attention Spinelli.
- Put it out through server five.
- Yes, sir.
I'm ordering, with Security Section's
full knowledge...
...the assassination
of an SD-6 officer.
Method, close-range hit.
This officer will make a dead drop
at Denati Park, 10pm tomorrow.
That's when the kill
should take place.
Yes, sir.
The target's name is Bristow.
Sydney Bristow.
Find Gerace, get hold
of something he touched.
Looks like a normal phone.
"Hi. You wanna go out Friday?"
"No? OK, that's fine."
But it's actually
a biometric sensor.
It lifts the print
off any smooth surface, digitises it,
and creates a latex duplicate you
can use to get into Gerace's study.
There's only enough latex
for one copy.
So make sure you get
the right fingerprint.
Damn it!
You look so beautiful in that dress.
I don't know who you are.
But Kurtz was wearing this
when she met me,
so I assume you heard
at least that conversation.
You know I'm a reporter, looking into
what happened to Hecht and Kurtz.
So if you killed her,
you would have known that
I'm a threat and you would have,
you would have killed me, too, so...
Unless you didn't kill her.
In which case, I need to talk to you.
My cell number is
3105550153.
Please...
...call me.
Please.
I need to talk to you.
Hello?
Francie? Yeah, hi.
No, I don't know where she is.
I don't think she got back yet.
Agent Bristow has been made. We got
this communiqué off the SD-6 server.
What?
10pm, Denati Park.
They're gonna kill her.
SD-6 is gonna kill her.
I went to tell Davenport.
He's not in his office.
It's Vaughn.
We need an extraction team.
We only have two hours.
I'll tell Davenport.
- He's not there.
- I'll find him.
Get Jack Bristow on the phone.
I don't speak Italian. But I love
everything about this house.
Except the spinning.
Can you do something?
These floors are not for guests.
Can you tell me
where the bathroom is?
It's up the stairs. Watch your step.
- Yeah?
- I got your message.
There's a hit out on Sydney.
I'm getting her out.
- You could be making a mistake.
- I don't think so.
- Do nothing until you hear from me.
- We have a team en route.
I sent a communiqué to SD-4.
They never got it.
- Want some candy?
- No, check the server logs.
Here it is.
Here is a list of all outgoing
messages in the last 72 hours.
- This includes every server?
- Except server five.
It's not on the network, but the
communiqué wouldn't go that route.
Let's look there anyway.
OK, team's in Denati Park.
We've got six armed officers waiting.
By the fountain, the southern
entrance and the western gate.
Snipers at the north end.
Awaiting Bristow. First sighting,
I take her to safety.
- Are they scanning for gunmen?
- Yes. No shooters.
I've got three operatives on lookout.
- Jack.
- Take me to Field Ops.
- Mr Bristow.
- Call them off.
She'll be in the park any minute.
- This is a setup.
- What are you talking about?
Sloane's transmission was sent out
on server five, only to you.
They know someone's listening.
It's a test.
We'll get Sydney out
and argue about this later.
If you pull her out, it proves you
intercepted Sloane's communiqué.
Sydney will be exposed.
- You don't know that.
- Why am I talking to you?
- Abort this mission.
- Wait a minute!
- You could be killing your daughter.
- You're killing her if you don't.
How can you risk this?
If Sydney makes her dead drop
and leaves the park,
she will have proven herself loyal
to SD-6.
- Have them hold till we give order.
- No. Hold it. This is Sydney's life.
You were meant to see
that transmission.
Someone in that park
is going to kill her!
I know how Sloane works.
He's bluffing.
Alpha-2, come in.
Bristow's entering the park.
We have two vehicles
that are not on our list.
- Who is this guy in the jacket?
- Copy that.
Position three.
We have an approaching hostile.
Acquired male target, 75 metres.
This could be our guy.
- Promise you're not wrong.
- Hold your position.
- He could be going for a gun.
- Prepare to take him out.
Stand by.
Copy that.
That's her dead drop.
OK, she's out of the park.
She's clear.
Good work, Jack.
I just lost 30 pounds.
I'm not kidding.
This is why I became a reporter.
It's like the best movie ever made.
- His Girl Friday?
- What's a better movie than that?
Godfather? On the Waterfront?
Citizen Kane?
OK. You're right.
- Raging Bull? Empire Strikes Back?
- OK. Whatever. It sucks, alright?
But it's why
I wanted to be a reporter.
I saw this when I was a kid
and loved it. All the quick...
- Repartee.
- Yeah.
It just looked fun.
Being a reporter looked fun.
But it's not. It's not fun.
It's a pain in the ass.
What's your problem? Well?
What are you doing?
Scoot over.
Is something even in there?
- It's so ugly.
- It's a bug. It's a microphone.
- No. Where did you get that?
- It's a story.
I'm like living in a puzzle.
I can't figure anything out.
I don't know who's doing what.
I'm a mess. Literally.
You're looking at a mess.
And whoever's listening
can go to hell.
- Did you hear that?
- You think someone's listening?
I don't even care.
I just want to watch old movies.
Do you think
I will find a good wedding dress?
- It's not a magic 8-ball.
- Hello!
Tell them to stop torturing me.
Stop torturing Will Tippin.
He's my friend.
Bad people.
- Hello?
- Stop talking about the bug.
Tell the person you're with
this was a wrong number.
- Who was that?
- It was a wrong number.
You sent the communiqué
on server five.
High-level intel could deduce
that your directive was bogus.
Whoever hacked into our network
won't believe we're setting them up.
The point is,
they received the intel.
If Bristow had been their agent,
they'd have stopped her
going to the park last night.
- Say she had been the mole.
- You're convinced she's not?
Well, whether she is or not,
if your plan had worked,
if she had been revealed as a mole,
she would have been
saved by her people,
and you would have effectively
let her go.
You have your answer
regarding Sydney Bristow.
What are you protecting?
Mr Dreyer, I still believe
we have a situation here at SD-6.
I strongly suggest
you keep looking for the mole,
and stop questioning
every decision I make.
- Syd?
- Fran.
- When did you get back?
- Your wedding dress!
- Don't worry about it.
- I am so sorry.
How was Boston?
- Did you get my message?
- I did. It's OK, seriously.
It was insensitive of me to ask you
to go wedding-dress shopping.
Why?
Well, because you were
supposed to be going through this.
And I understand.
And if you feel weird,
I'll do whatever you need.
It's OK.
Francie?
This wasn't about me losing Danny.
It wasn't about me at all.
The only reason I didn't show up
was because of work. I promise.
- Let's go next week, OK?
- OK.
Any news about Dixon? Is he OK?
- He still hasn't woken up.
- I'm really sorry.
- Hello?
- Hello, Will Tippin.
- Who is this?
- Go to 7 th and Spring.
Analysis has reviewed
the information you obtained
from Gerace's computer.
Hassan is more
paranoid than we predicted.
His account info wasn't there?
Yes and no. We know the bank
but not the account numbers.
Those numbers are not stored on any
computer, because it can be hacked.
If they're not there,
where are they?
In a safety deposit box
in this bank.
Omnicorp Incorporated, Geneva.
You're going with Russek.
You'll be Christiana Stephens,
representing Drybergh Diamonds.
You're looking for a bank to
recommend for high-volume storage.
You leave tonight.
Great job in Tuscany.
- So, it was a trap?
- Yes, it was.
If you'd pulled me out, Sloane
would've known I was the mole.
But I would have been safe.
He gave me an out.
- He considers you a daughter.
- Don't remind me.
How did you know not to step in?
It was your dad. He figured
the truth, Sloane was setting us up.
- What?
- It'll take forever to get them.
This might help a little.
- What is it?
- A transmitter.
We can hear you in Switzerland.
When you open the deposit box,
read the account numbers aloud.
- SD-6 will get them, too.
- It doesn't matter.
We'll tag the accounts
and track every move SD-6 makes.
It's not exactly
a crushing blow, but...
Every bit helps.
- Yes, hello?
- Tell me you weren't followed.
- No, not a chance. Who is this?
- You have questions about Jones.
How far are you willing to go,
Mr Tippin?
I need to hear the words,
"I'm ready".
Why? Could my life be in danger?
Say the words.
Yeah, I'm in.
I'm ready.
Excuse me, can you tell me
where Mr Franco is please?
Wait here a moment, please.
Mr Franco. Christiana Stephens.
I have an appointment.
Our security system is powered
by an on-site underground generator
which means that we are unaffected
by the city blackouts.
What is your insurance coverage?
We have no preset limit,
though if your clients
wish to store their diamonds here,
we'd have an independent appraiser
value the merchandise.
How's the political climate
affected your privacy laws?
Well, our first duty is always
to the customer that we...
OK, Russek, I'm in.
Gerace's box is 22364.
I'm accessing the bank's
on-line server. Wait for your relay.
Got it.
- Russek, I got it. Ready?
- Go.
Delta 6-1-3-5 Charlie
7 Echo. That's it.
Get this to treasury.
I don't wanna lose track of a penny.
Money's transferred.
- Are you out of there yet, Sydney?
- Not just yet.
Help! He just fainted.
I'll call an ambulance.
It's an anomaly, sir.
While Sydney was in the vault, there
was a transmission out of Geneva.
Not one of ours.
I picked it up
in Signals Intelligence.
It's just, you wanted me to tell you
if there was anything unusual...
I didn't just get someone
in trouble, did I?
- Hello?
- Sydney, it's Diane.
He's woken up.
It's OK. Go on in.
- I'm going to get some coffee.
- OK, thanks.
- It's so good to see you.
- You, too.
Dixon.
Do you know what...?
Do you remember what happened?
Last thing I remember...
...was walking out,
trying to link to the satellite.
And that sweet smile of yours.
Yep, there it is.
- Yeah?
- We got her.