My name is Sydney Bristow.
Seven years ago, I was recruited
by a branch of the CIA called SD-6.
I was sworn to secrecy, but I
couldn't keep it from my fiancé.
And when the head of SD-6
found out, he had him killed.
That's when I learned the truth,
SD-6 is not part of the CIA.
I'd been working for the people
I thought I was fighting.
I went to the only place
that could help me take them down.
Now, I'm a double agent for the CIA,
where my handler is Michael Vaughn.
Only one other person knows what
I do. Another double agent in SD-6.
Someone I hardly know.
My father.
We have a lot of questions
about your father. I copied his file.
What do you know about case 3-32L?
There are missing pages in my
father's file,
and references to case 3-32L.
- An Agent Calder.
- You read that too.
Calder wasn't CIA. He was FBI.
Why would the FBI
be working with my father?
They wouldn't.
Unless they suspected him
of selling secrets.
Break into the building as planned.
While Dixon sets the explosives,
get the inhaler
and meet the CIA team inside.
By then, Dixon should be outside.
You'll disable the explosive
while the CIA team searches
the lab's main computer system.
- We gotta go. What are you doing?
- I brought a secondary detonator.
Good to go?
Let's go. Sydney? We've gotta run.
Sydney, we've gotta move.
Sydney, we've gotta move! Now!
- What's the matter? Are you hurt?
- No.
Go.
Run!
Go, go, go, go!
Come on, Sydney. We gotta go.
I couldn't move.
Dixon had to drag me to my feet
just to get to the van.
And when he asked me
what was wrong, why I'd just frozen,
I made up something
about having a flashback to Danny.
- You did everything you could.
- I was meant to stop the detonation.
I didn't.
Because of that,
four CIA agents were killed.
You had no way of knowing
Dixon had a second trigger.
- There was nothing you could do.
- I could have told him the truth.
Dixon needs to know
who he's really working for.
- Sydney...
- I know.
- I can't put his family at risk.
- Or yourself.
I know all of that,
but it's the right thing to do.
- Those men died for no reason.
- Those men died for their country.
Sydney, I'm sorry. I'm sorry
you had to go through that.
- You worked late.
- Bar Association dinner.
A lawyer wanted to sue me because
his chicken was undercooked.
Can you believe that?
An obnoxious lawyer?
Have you talked to
your obnoxious lawyer?
I'm meeting Charlie
for lunch this week.
That's good.
- Syd, he's gonna break up with me.
- Did he say that? He didn't say it.
He didn't have to.
He was sneaking around on me.
We saw him with that girl, Rachel.
There's stuff he's doing that
he can't tell me about? Please.
He wouldn't meet with you
just to break up with you.
Guys don't do that.
If they wanna end things,
they just vanish.
Your mom was so pretty.
Yeah, she was.
Thanks.
I gotta go change.
I feel a binge coming on.
How was your trip?
Not good. I was working
with these people who...
They were terminated.
Oh, man.
The economy sucks.
- Hello?
- This is Helen Calder.
You left me a message about my
husband working with your father.
I know that your husband
worked for the FBI
and he investigated CIA agents
suspected of spying for Russia.
My dad was one of the agents
that your husband investigated.
I know that much.
Did he ever mention
the name Jack Bristow?
I'm sorry.
Bentley didn't talk much
about his work.
He looks kind.
He is.
- I thought Bentley was dead.
- Oh, dear, no.
That isn't Bentley.
That's my boyfriend, Gary.
This... is Bentley.
He wasn't so nice.
- When did Bentley pass away?
- 1981, in a car accident.
- Do you have a copy of this?
- I think so.
For 20 years
I thought I knew how my mom died.
She and my dad had been out at the
movies. They were coming home late,
and a postal worker
was driving in the other direction.
Alcohol wasn't a factor.
He'd fallen asleep.
His car drifted over the white line.
Dad swerved and went off the bridge.
I always told myself Mom didn't have
time to know what was happening.
Now, I know that Calder was hunting
down a KGB agent, my father.
Whatever happened that night was no
accident. Calder was chasing them.
They probably lost control
and the cars crashed.
Whatever it was, it brings me back
to the same conclusion.
If my father
hadn't been a double agent...
...my mom would still be alive today.
I'm sorry to lay all this on you.
But I have no one
to talk to about this.
- It's OK.
- I want to report him.
- What?
- I want to turn him in.
For being under suspicion
20 years ago?
What about the file?
There were pages missing.
Maybe he still works for Russia.
Stop, OK? Just stop.
What matters is taking down SD-6.
Your father's helping us do that.
You suggest I do nothing?
We have too much to do
on your relationship.
I wasn't to do anything about Dixon.
Is anything unacceptable to you?
It's your dad. If he sold secrets
or is selling secrets, that's hard.
- I hope it would be hard on you.
- Before you do anything,
let me find out if he's under
suspicion. Just give me two days.
I get it.
You wanted to do it in person,
but instead of coming out with it,
you're making small talk,
which is pathetic.
Francie...
I have always supported you,
no matter what.
The idea that you'd sneak around
and lie about it is the worst part.
- After all we've been through...
- I want to be a singer.
A singer?
I wasn't gonna say anything
till I had everything set up.
That woman, Rachel?
She plays piano.
When you saw us that night,
we were rehearsing.
We have our first gig
this Friday night.
A singer?
Sweetheart,
I'm sorry I wasn't upfront before,
but my being a lawyer
has been the family's goal forever,
and the thought of me doing
something else or wanting to is...
I've been too afraid to admit that.
- You're not breaking up with me?
- Are you kidding?
You're my baby.
Charlie singing? I wouldn't miss it.
- Will.
- Yeah, I'll be there. Yes.
Yes. Best behaviour. I got it.
- Get off my chair.
- How's Sydney? That was Sydney?
You gotta stop doing that.
Anybody call when I was ill?
Yeah, a guy from the DMV.
He ran the licence plate
off Kate Jones's car.
Or the woman pretending to be her.
According to her social security
number, Kate Jones died in 1973.
Hello, Hank? Hello, it's Will.
You come up with anything?
Did it match a licence plate
for a 663 Sam Tango Frank?
You're the best. OK...
Eloise Kurtz.
Eloise Kurtz is proof someone's
covering up Danny's murder.
And she was lying
about having an affair with him.
223 Whitley Place, Hollywood.
Good work in Germany. The inhaler
prototype's safely in analysis.
The Badenweiler factory
was demolished without casualties.
Thanks.
Dixon deserves the credit, not me.
Jack will no longer be working
out of Jennings Aerospace.
His assignment there is complete.
As of today, he'll be working here
with a cover as portfolio manager
for Credit Dauphine.
This way,
he can more actively participate
in the planning and execution
of missions.
- Good.
- Jack?
Two months ago,
FTL vacated their base at Rabat
and their support station at Shaneer.
All the heavy equipment was moved,
including the T47 s.
At the time,
recovery team found this at Rabat.
Last week, we learned FTL
abandoned their transfer facility.
Our recovery team did a sweep
and returned with this.
Is the ink encoded?
That was my first thought, as well.
I'm sorry. You want some fritter?
It's apple.
Analysis studied the music sample.
They found an identical pattern of
numbers buried in higher frequencies.
It's not noise.
It's where they hid the code.
- Have we deciphered it?
- No.
Mirage.
It's a converted salvage tug.
FTL uses it as a floating lab.
Weapon design, data storage, crypto.
An SD-6 commando team
stormed the ship last night
as it passed through
the Panama Canal.
They brought back this.
- What is it?
- FTL's latest code machine.
Without this, we're unable
to read their communications.
- How does it work?
- Very well.
- We don't know yet.
- The team got what they could.
But there was a self-destruct
on the ship.
Needless to say,
they left fairly quickly.
They found out
only eight decoders were produced.
One is now
in the possession of this man.
John Smythe, owner of
Hobbs End Photo Gallery in London.
Also an FTL operative.
One of the code machines
is being held at the gallery
awaiting pick-up next Tuesday.
You leave for London tonight.
We want to know where FTL went
and what they're up to.
Your job is to bring back
the encoding machine.
I would have told you
about the realignment,
but you were in Badenweiler.
I heard about what happened.
It's tragic.
I know about you.
That you were hunted by the FBI
and I know that Mom died
because they were after you.
Sydney.
Every time I think I know
just how awful you are,
I learn something worse.
But this time,
I'm gonna make sure you pay.
- What's this?
- A bug.
- What are you, 12 years old?
- No, a bug.
We didn't know about Smythe.
- They'll scan for listening devices.
- The technology is passive.
Langley cribbed the design
from a Russian device.
It works when hit with
a microwave beam off a satellite.
Then it acts as a microphone.
It's undetectable.
- They'll just think it's a bug.
- Exactly.
What about the code machine?
We won't have time to switch,
so deliver it to SD-6.
When the code's broken, they'll
inform officers using the network.
Thanks to you, we're still
downloading their data.
- How much have you got so far?
- Almost two percent.
In all this time, that's all you got?
If we take too much too quickly
they'll notice, but if we're patient,
we can get all their files
and do some real damage.
Good.
I checked about your dad. He's clean.
No internal investigations.
- I told him.
- Told him what?
That I know about Calder, his spying
for the KGB, the accident.
Damn it,
I asked you not to say anything.
I don't care.
If you were in my position,
you wouldn't be able
to control yourself.
- You're gonna have to learn to.
- Don't lecture me about my father.
Because of this spy trade,
my mother is dead.
You couldn't understand what it's
like to have a parent die that way.
There's a book back at Langley.
They keep it locked up under glass.
Behind it is a marble wall
with stars carved in it.
It's a memorial
to the agents lost in action.
Families are never told
how they died or where,
only that they won't be coming home.
I was eight when my father
became one of those stars.
At the funerals, there's a protocol
the agency representative
has to follow.
What to say, whose hand to shake.
You're admonished. That's the word
they use, admonished,
not to be conspicuously emotional.
Vaughn, I'm so sorry.
The agents
that died at Badenweiler...
...l've been assigned to represent
the agency at their funerals.
Delivery.
Got a package for Eloise Kurtz.
I just need five minutes.
- How did you know my name?
- I won't use it if you're afraid.
I don't know anything.
People who say that
know more than they think.
Do you know how they killed Danny?
Shot him in his bathtub.
- I don't know anything.
- Three bullets, one in his heart.
- I'm warning you.
- Five minutes.
I have pepper spray.
- God!
- I told you.
My eyes!
- I warned you. Now just go away!
- OK!
Ready?
It should take me 20 seconds
to get down the hall.
Excuse me, sir. Hello. Actually,
this is a non-smoking gallery.
Not any more.
I'm afraid if you don't put that out,
we'll escort you to the door.
What kind of a deal
do you think I can get
if I take, say,
the entire collection?
I'll go call the owner.
Yeah?
I'll be right there.
Chester Conlan
is an award-winning artist.
- It is almost Keiferesque.
- I said the same thing.
Is this bothering you, by the way?
Not at all.
I am tempted, but... I don't know.
Sir, I've already offered
to come down ten percent.
Ten... percent is not 20 percent.
I'll eat the tax, but that is it.
Chéri?
I think I prefer the Lamborghini.
You are the birthday girl.
Could you do something with this?
He doesn't sing in the car
or in the shower.
He doesn't even the national
anthem at baseball games.
He doesn't even hum.
Too, like,
"I'm with the band", kinda.
If he had a good voice, he would have
used it somewhere, once.
I would have heard it.
You'll be there, right?
I mean, I need you there.
Of course I will.
When he's not... If he's not good,
he's gonna be so devastated,
you know that.
Or it could be the start
of something great.
- Raid my closet.
- Thanks.
But I got boobs.
Hey. I'm Rachel. Charlie
has told me so much about you.
- Really?
- Going for her MBA, best cook ever.
- You're like this mythic person.
- OK, I like her.
And this is Will.
- Know anything about me?
- And Sydney.
This is my sister, Amy.
- Will Tippin.
- It's Eloise Kurtz.
Sorry, I can't hear you. Hold on.
- This is so exciting.
- A little terrifying.
- We gotta get ready.
- You guys are gonna be great.
- This is gonna be a disaster.
- Stop it.
- Hi.
- Are you alright?
You mean, can I see again?
- I feel horrible.
- It's OK. I was wearing my glasses.
- I'm really not a bad person.
- I never said you were.
Help me out, please.
They gave me $2,000 to say I was
having an affair with Danny Hecht.
Who did?
I was between jobs.
My car was broken.
Anybody in my position
would have done the same.
Can I buy you a coffee
and meet you in person?
Come by my apartment
tomorrow afternoon.
How about three o'clock? I have a
great car mechanic if you need one.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Yeah, I'm here.
Listen. Everything's gonna be OK.
- Fact checker. How's Francie?
- A wreck.
Charlie!
When the road gets dark
And you can no longer see
Just let my love throw a spark
And have a little faith in me
When the tears you cry
Are all you can believe
Just give these loving arms a try
And have a little faith in me
Have a little faith in me...
That's my boyfriend.
Have a little faith in me
When your secret heart
Cannot sleep so easily
Come here, darlin',
I'm gonna whisper start
Have a little faith in me
It tickles. What just happened?
It took a piece of your thumb,
a speck. And this is true genius.
It created a code from your DNA.
That's how the code
from the cards works.
The encryption was DNA-based.
- Whose?
- We know he had a card.
Gareth Parkashoff,
leader of the FTL in Rabat.
That's the good news. We know it's
Parkashoff. Bad news is he's dead.
We need his DNA, but we don't know
where he's buried. Marshall?
Marshall?
- The system's a little sluggish.
- Marshall, get Fisher.
Last month, we received intel
that Parkashoff was assassinated
by Martin Shepard.
Shepard's an interesting case.
His subconscious was programmed
to respond to a phrase.
Say it to him and he'd do
what you asked, even kill.
Say it again and those acts
would be erased from his mind.
He'd have no recollection
of his acts.
We have known for some time
what that phrase is.
- It's by John Donne.
- Right.
Get close to Shepard,
recite the poem
and get him to tell you
where Parkashoff is buried.
Where is he?
He checked himself
into a mental institution
in Bucharest, southern Romania.
If you don't mind...
There's something weird going on
with the computer network.
- Marshall?
- Kind of a bandwidth leak.
Why don't you get me a report
by the end of the day?
Agent Fisher will be your support.
His alias is Dr Carlos Fontanetta.
- Nice to meet you.
- And you.
The Mangalev clinic
is expecting Dr Fontanetta
to check a patient in
the day after tomorrow.
You are that patient.
Your handler's unavailable. Locate
Parkashoff. Relay the coordinates.
Vaughn's at a funeral. Heroes died
because of people like you.
Relay the correct coordinates
to SD-6.
- Go to hell.
- People's lives are at stake.
Your life.
What you think you know,
you don't know.
Then, you explain it to me.
You don't have clearance.
Clearance?
To be told how my mother died?
- There are rules.
- Then you break them.
Think about what you're saying.
Acting cavalier
about breaking the rules.
Think about the last time
you did something like that.
I'm not a perfect man, I know that.
But I am smart enough not to draw
simple conclusions and act upon them.
I'd think that if anyone had learned
that lesson, it would have been you.
Miss DiCamillo is bipolar.
We were doing some relief work
up in the north,
when she suffered a psychotic break.
She's suffering from
auditory hallucinations.
She thinks her government
wants to kill her.
Her previous doctor submitted her
for some experimental treatments,
lithium substitutes,
neurolinguistic programming,
all of which
had no effect on her condition.
I'm trying to find her parents, but,
till then, I need a place for her.
- Is she taking any anti-psychotics?
- Olanzapine, 20 milligrams QPM.
There are other institutions
in Bucharest.
How is it you honour us?
The consulate, they directed me here.
This way. We'll get her admitted.
Miss Kurtz?
I'm coming in.
Easy on the pepper spray.
Your dad was a hero.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
That leak...
There's a hack on the network!
They're downloading files
off the server!
Gotta cut the hard line!
Hello. Alain? We need to meet.
I think we have a mole.
Hi.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
- This is not a problem.
Two more forms
and her admission is complete.
By the way, while you were waiting,
I called to the consulate. Yes.
I'm speaking at a UN conference
on refugees in New York next month.
I called them about a visa.
Naturally, I thanked them for having
recommended our institution,
and I was surprised to hear
that they were unaware
of any such recommendation.
Do I know you?
"No man is an island,
entire of itself."
"Every man
is a piece of the continent."
Who are you?
That is because the consulate
referred me
to the local health department.
That explains it.
We know what you're doing,
Miss Bristow.
- Where's Vaughn?
- He's covering the funerals.
Badenweiler?
Why, did you finally get a date?
That asylum Bristow's been sent to?
The doctor who's running the place,
Kreshnik? He's with K-Directorate.
Fisher?