My name is Sydney Bristow.
Seven years ago, I was recruited
by a branch of the CIA called SD-6.
I was sworn to secrecy, but I
couldn't keep it from my fiancé.
And when the head of SD-6
found out, he had him killed.
That's when I learned the truth.
SD-6 is not part of the CIA.
I'd been working for the people
I thought I was fighting.
I went to the only place
that could help me take them down.
Now, I'm a double agent for the CIA.
My handler is Michael Vaughn.
Only one other person knows what
I do. Another double agent in SD-6.
Someone I hardly know.
My father.
Security has made us aware
of the concern that you may have
a mole in your department.
It would appear so.
There are some in the Alliance who
believe you may have more than one.
It is our intention
to make an example of them.
I know. I'm taking care of it.
What can you tell me
about this woman, Anna Espinosa?
She's with K-Directorate. I don't
like her, if that's what you mean.
I'm leaving for England tonight.
SD-6 has traced a Rambaldi Artefact
to the Engineering Science
Department at Oxford.
K- Directorate is on this.
I need to act fast so that Anna
doesn't get there first.
FTL found the Rambaldi Artefact
in Tunisia. Why'd they send it here?
Analysis. Our department
is among the best in the world.
The lens has to be within two feet
of the keycard to get a reading.
Got it. How do I look?
For the record, that's a question
you never have to ask.
FTL agents are here posing as
campus security. Watch your back.
You, too.
For a journalist,
you have a remarkable grasp
of engineering principles.
What is your background?
- My family was in demolition.
- Really?
- So, is it true?
- What?
Your department's just received
ancient technology from Tunisia?
Who told you that?
Well, you just did.
- What?
- I'd love to see your lab.
See anybody, Syd?
Professor Hoyt. Do you see anything?
No. Get closer,
I can't tell if the card's on him.
- Anything?
- The keycard's in his pocket.
You're too far away.
Get him to turn towards you.
- Excuse me, Professor Hoyt?
- Yes.
Hold... that for 30 seconds.
I'm Molly Zerdin
with the Marisa Foundation.
We're interested in your study.
Really? Which one?
He's studying the crashworthiness
of transportation vehicles.
Your study on crashworthiness
Wonderful. Well, of course,
getting funding is very difficult
in today's economic climate.
The duplicate keycard's printing.
- That is so true.
- Got it, Syd. I'm on my way.
Excuse me a moment.
Tell security someone's trying to
break into the engineering lab.
- Then the FTL guards will know.
- Anna's here.
Copy that.
Calling the guards right now.
- Freeze, right there!
- Thank God.
Someone's done something
terrible to Professor Bloom.
I'm in the lab.
I don't see anything.
OK, I got it.
Got a minute?
Of course.
Eloise Kurtz. She was found dead
two days ago in Echo Park.
- She was a new promotion at SD-6.
- Yes, I know.
- You retired her, didn't you?
- I think the pressing question is,
why you let her talk to a reporter
without running it by me?
- I wasn't hiding it. The reporter...
- Will Tippin.
Yes. He's a friend of Sydney's.
He was looking into the name
Kate Jones, one of her aliases.
I tasked Eloise Kurtz to lead him
down a dead end so he'd drop it.
You underestimated Tippin.
And Agent Kurtz's lack of
field experience put us all at risk.
What were you doing
using a junior agent, Jack?
Ask McCullough. I used Kurtz based
on his assessment of her ability.
He gave her his highest rating.
In any case, I had contingencies.
All of which are now irrelevant.
Tell me something.
How did Tippin get a lead on
Kate Jones' alias in the first place?
I don't know yet.
I'm looking into it.
Your efforts not withstanding,
that reporter may well be
a casualty of his own curiosity.
I'd consider that a last resort.
I know you want
what's best for Sydney.
If possible, we should spare her
the pain of losing someone else.
How do you suggest we proceed?
Leave it to me.
I'll get Tippin off the story.
And if you can't?
Then I'll kill him myself.
You've missed class.
- I know.
- Turned in papers late.
- Listen, my job's...
- Enough about your job.
It's worse since we last spoke.
If you want to be a banker, be one.
I understand. It's probably not
the best analysis of Fitzgerald
you've read,
but, come on, this is not a D paper.
There's no spirit in this paper,
no soul. You fix it by Friday,
or I'll have to re-evaluate
your place in this programme.
Dr Wilkenson.
Yes, I'll hold.
Hello, Dr Peterson, Dr Wilkenson.
Of course.
Yes, I'd like to discuss that.
Yes.
Yes, let's talk about the meeting.
That's what we talked about, yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Hold on a second.
Who are you?
Security said
you assaulted an officer.
This wasn't security
nor standard procedure.
This was a constant tracker.
I've seen him three times in two
days, and I found this under my car.
If there's something you want
to know about me, you ask.
This agency requires the sacrifice
of some personal freedoms.
SD-6 is stepping up security.
McCullough assigned the tracker,
it's his province.
Now, we have a briefing.
Do you think you could focus?
- Yeah, I think I can.
- Good.
The clock you retrieved was designed
by Giovanni Donato.
He died in 1503. His initials
are engraved on the bottom.
Donato was a master clockmaker.
More importantly, he was the only
man that Rambaldi collaborated with.
There's a reference to Donato
in our Rambaldi archive.
Rambaldi commissioned
the clock himself.
And because of his involvement, you
think it's more than just a clock.
That was Rambaldi's style.
Hiding codes in designs
within his artwork. Marshall.
Alright.
I know we're all hungry for lunch,
so I'll use the maximum amount
of brevity possible.
OK. Now, as a clock,
it was far ahead of its time.
A margin of error of less than
one second per decade.
The weirdest part
is the gear assembly.
It's a part that doesn't seem
to serve any purpose.
This number on the back,
is it a date?
We're analysing that.
Know what we found?
Nothing happened that day. It's one
day in history that zero occurred.
We believe this clock will reveal
another piece of the Rambaldi puzzle.
The problem is, it doesn't work.
Without instructions,
we can't risk damaging it.
We've located a descendant of Donato
in Positano.
Luckily,
he went into the family business.
Your mission, Bristow, is simple.
Take the clock to Donato,
get him to fix it, and bring it back.
- That's it?
- That's it.
Dad, do you have a few minutes?
- Yes, of course, could you just...
- Somewhere quiet. Somewhere else.
In here.
Signal jammer.
We have 60 seconds, talk quickly.
Sloane's having me followed.
I confronted the guy.
I thought it may be K-Directorate
looking for revenge.
Sloane insists it's all routine.
Should I be worried?
Only five agents here
know the truth about SD-6.
I've had Sloane's trust, but lately
I haven't been informed of much.
- What's it mean?
- I'm concerned.
While you were in Romania, Marshall
noticed computer abnormalities.
He may realise the SD-6 network
has been compromised.
- Could Sloane trace it to CIA?
- I don't know.
Also, Karl Dreyer's coming in
to upgrade the biometric scanners.
If Sloane suspects a mole,
Dreyer's the one he'll turn to.
If so, Dreyer will give each of us
a functional imaging test.
- What's that?
- Lie detector.
I studied the CIA instructions
on how to take an LDT.
No, this monitors variations
in blood flow inside the brain.
It's difficult to deceive.
Tell Vaughn he needs to prepare you.
If he can't,
he'll get someone who can.
Dad, you seem nervous.
Well, I think...
that should be fine.
- Thanks for coming to me.
- Of course.
No, I think that's nice. Of course.
I think he's gonna love it.
Yeah, I'm sure.
OK, Mom, I gotta go.
I gotta go,
my boss is standing right here.
I love you, too. I'm sorry.
Still no quote from Hecht's fiancé.
I didn't get one.
- We can't have this.
- It's difficult.
- We've quotes from relatives.
- Just stop for a second.
- No, I'm not gonna do this story.
- Excuse me?
I won't run the story,
I won't do the piece.
You pushed me to pursue this,
convinced me of a connection
between the deaths.
Something terrible happened,
I told you this before.
If this story will hurt my friend,
I won't do it.
You haven't told her that you're
working on this, have you?
Like I said, you finish this,
or I will put another writer on it.
You tell her and get the quote.
This goes to bed tomorrow,
three o'clock.
- It's me.
- It's open.
What's the paper on?
It's a redo.
The professor said it had no soul.
So I'm writing a paper with soul.
Lots of soul.
"Laura, all my love forever
and a day. Jack."
- Not your dad, Jack, is it?
- Yeah.
That's uncharacteristically
sweet of him.
I know. He has a heart,
which I'm learning little by little.
He bought all of these for my mom.
I got your message.
You're going on another trip?
That's like...
Is it seven this month?
Is the bank ever gonna let up?
What's up?
There's this... situation at work.
Just... some money is missing
from petty cash.
There might be a formal inquiry.
- They don't suspect you, do they?
- No.
But they're gonna give us all
lie detector tests, which is just...
Can I make a suggestion
for the millionth time?
Why don't you just quit?
You can get a job anywhere.
- I just think it's weird.
- I know.
I still wear this.
I know.
- Hello?
- Joey's Pizza?
Wrong number.
What are you doing here?
I just came by to say hi.
Hi.
Have you had unauthorised contact
with members of any
intelligence agency besides SD-6?
No.
OK, again. You have to stay under 30.
It measures blood flow
to the emotional part of your brain.
To divert it, you engage
the reasoning centre.
- I'm trying!
- You're emoting.
There's no switch you can flick.
- Just split your focus.
- Maybe I've split my focus already!
- CIA, SD-6, school, my friends.
- Sydney, you can do this.
You have to.
Have you had
unauthorised contact
with members of any
intelligence agency besides SD-6?
No.
Better.
Are you romantically
interested in anyone?
It could be a question.
No, I'm not.
- Interesting.
- Ask again.
I don't have to, we've got our
answer. Very good, moving on.
If this were for real,
I'd be dead by now.
Wouldn't I?
No, I'm just
getting started here.
Milo Rambaldi.
Enter.
- You are American?
- Yes.
Only an American would come
to my door without telephoning.
Seth, get in touch
with my airlines contact.
I need a back trace on a passenger
manifest. I'll be in my office.
Seen the passenger manifest
for flight 816?
No. My guy at the airport told me
he was gonna fax it to me.
Seat 11 A. Daniel Hecht.
- Look up seat 11 B.
- Kate Jones, I know.
- Look at it.
- Zachary Collin.
- There was no Kate Jones.
- I don't understand.
Me neither, but there's no longer
one fact to support your theory
that someone is covering up
Hecht's murder.
What about Eloise Kurtz?
A woman hired to tell you
she's Kate Jones,
so you stop looking for the real one.
That's right.
- But she's dead.
- I've notes from my interview.
- You have no recording.
- What about the video blackout?
You wanna build a case
on lack of photographic evidence?
You've got Jenny as your checker
and she didn't make a single call.
Right, she didn't. It was a favour.
She does a lot of work for me,
I was giving her research credit.
Like a gift.
- It was like a lie.
- Yes, it was. A kind lie.
On the eve of your first
front-page story, you get cold feet.
What are you saying? I made this up?
I swear to God, the only reason
I didn't want this story to run
is cos I don't want to hurt
Sydney Bristow. That's it.
You're a talented writer, Will.
But I promise you,
if this happens again,
the only thing you'll invent
are facts on your résumé.
The first Giovanni Donato,
his timepieces
were miracles of precision.
Kings and queens offered him
vast riches if only he would
design clocks for them.
He refused.
But he did make... one exception.
For Rambaldi.
Why?
Rambaldi made him a promise.
What did he promise?
Rambaldi promised him he would live
an impossibly long life.
He even revealed to him
when he would die.
Was he right?
Of course.
This symbol on the front,
what does it mean?
The Magnific Order of Rambaldi.
Rambaldi's most loyal followers,
entrusted with safeguarding
his creations.
Sadly, like most things
that once were pure,
criminals now use the symbol
to infiltrate the order.
What about this date?
It must have meant
something to Rambaldi.
The clock was built
from one of his designs.
He never did tell me what it meant.
What did you say?
My mother... never told me.
I don't think she knew.
There's still one piece missing,
I don't have.
So, it won't work?
It will tell time...
if that's what you mean.
The clock is finished.
I've got Bristow in my sight.
Take the shot whenever you have it.
Mr Donato.
What was Rambaldi working on?
The clock is fixed.
Now...
...it's over.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
The good news is
I went by your professor's office
to drop off the paper,
but he wasn't in.
The secretary
wanted me to leave it,
so I waited around
and handed it to him personally.
Thank you, Francie.
What's the bad news?
I was making lemonade and I spilled
it all over your mom's book.
- I am so sorry, and I think it's...
- Don't worry, it doesn't matter.
- Thank you for handing in the paper.
- You're welcome.
Have you leaked information about
SD-6 to other intelligence agencies?
No.
- Are you a double agent?
- No.
But my father is.
I'm sure he'd be thrilled
if you gave Dreyer that.
Not now for the CIA,
20 years ago for the KGB.
My mother was a teacher.
My father bought her books,
one a month,
shipped from a store
they discovered in Prague.
- We really need to...
- Listen to me!
I thought it was sweet,
a side of him that died with her,
but last night I discovered codes
inside those books.
It's obviously how the KGB
were sending him messages.
No. What kind of codes?
One-time pads. Blocks of ciphertext
in sets of five Cyrillic letters.
- Staple of the KGB.
- Yeah.
We'll deal with that.
I wanna see those books,
but you have this test coming,
and your life
depends on how well you do.
Hello, this is Will.
- Will, it's Mike.
- Mike, how you doing?
Your friend Eloise
brought her car in.
Eloise Kurtz?
She never picked it up
and she needed it right away.
- She did?
- Yeah. You know where she is?
Do you mind
if I come down and take a look?
No problem, you know where we are.
- Will Tippin.
- How kiss-ass of you.
- What?
- Stargazer Lilies and the card.
I didn't make up a single fact.
I thought you knew me
well enough to know that.
I am calling to clarify
you're on the soil erosion story
and not wasting
another minute on Kate Jones.
Are we clear?
Yeah, we're clear.
As you know, for some time now,
we have been operating
under the assumption
that the sum of Rambaldi's inventions
are greater than the parts.
This clock is evidence of that.
Thank you. Hi.
Now, who here remembers this?
The golden sun
from the church in Malaga.
The polymer.
If you look closely, hundreds of
tiny imperfections, nothing unusual.
But what is unusual is... this.
I realised that if you set
this to exactly 12.22...
21... 22.
And then this happens.
Miss Bristow, ladies first.
- What is that?
- It's a star chart.
A snapshot of the sky
at a specific place on earth
at a specific moment in time.
Sorry I'm late.
Sort of like an ancient GPS system?
Yeah, if you have the date and time
it was taken. That's the genius.
These two separately, nothing at all,
but put them together and...
That sound, that boom,
that's my mind blowing.
If we assume that star chart
refers to the date on the clock,
August 16th, 1523, at 2.22am GMT,
then the only spot on Earth
with that exact view of the stars
is the southern slope
of Mount Aconcagua
on the Chile-Argentina border.
X marks the spot. So, we think
Rambaldi has stored something there?
Possibly.
Your mission is to find out.
Marshall will fill you in
on the Op Tech.
And Sydney, before you head off,
I want you to go down to Psych
and see Karl Dreyer.
- What is your name?
- Sydney Bristow.
What colour are your eyes?
Brown.
Are you sitting down?
Yes.
Are you an agent of SD-6?
Are you a double agent?
No.
This is a camera with a digital
signal, uplinked to a satellite,
so whatever's in Argentina,
we'll see right away.
Is there a transmission window?
No, it's geosynchronous orbit,
just point and click.
Yeah.
You seem a little distracted.
Was it the test?
I'm not sure I passed.
They're still watching me.
It took me 20 minutes
to shake their tail.
They wouldn't be sending you
on a mission if you failed.
I don't think they know
the results yet.
Look, I know how much you want
to do this, take down SD-6,
but your life is more important,
so if you think you failed the test,
we have a plan in place to take
you out, a protection programme.
No. I can't do it.
Live in hiding? Not a chance.
Good luck in Argentina.
Six-mile trek
and we should be there.
There are easier jobs than this.
God, no kidding.
You know... I've been meaning
to tell you something.
- I'm proud of ya.
- What? Of me?
- Yeah.
- Why?
Well, I've worked
with a lot of people.
You make it look easy.
The thing I admire most...
...is your courage.
My courage?
After what happened with Danny.
The way you came back.
Your commitment to the job.
And I know what we do
isn't for ourselves,
it's for the good of the country.
Still...
...thanks.
- You're saying it's a bug?
- No, it's a tarantula.
It hops channels so fast.
You can't intercept the transmission.
My guess is it's encrypted, too.
- Where can you buy this?
- You can't, it's government issue.
My sister's man is Secret Service.
His transmitter couldn't touch this.
I'd say it's intelligence.
What's the frequency, Kenneth?
What do you think
Rambaldi's all about?
I wish we knew. There's a thousand
places I'd rather be right now.
I think we're almost at
our way point. 22.42 by 70.01.
- What the hell are we doing here?
- Feels like a wild goose chase.
Ah, damn it. I can't get
a line of sight to the satellite.
It's a low earth orbit.
We're blocked by the mountains.
Give me a hand here.
- I'm going in.
- Alright.
I'll hike out, acquire the satellite
and call for support.
Syd... be careful.
Dixon, I've found it.
Rambaldi's journal, I've found it.
Sydney, they've found us.
K- Directorate.
- Dixon?
- They're here, Anna's here!
- Sydney, get out of there!
- Dixon, do you copy me?
Have you Sydney's results?
I think we've found our mole.
What did you do to Dixon?
Put the book down.