Seven years ago,
I was recruited to work for SD-6,
which I was told
was a covert branch of the CIA.
I was trained as a spy,
warned not to tell anyone what I did.
I thought I was working
for the good guys
until I told my fiancé about SD-6,
and they had him killed.
That's when I learned the truth,
that SD-6 is part of the enemy
I thought I was fighting.
Now, I'm a double agent, working
with the real CIA to bring down SD-6.
My only ally is another double agent,
a man I hardly know. My father.
That was three years ago when
I met him first, Leonard Dreifuss.
He helps bankroll SD-6 operations.
This guy's very hands-on.
Not just in this business.
He's a real slime.
He runs a division in Geneva.
A transport guy,
he'll get anything, anywhere fast.
Sloane relies on him,
he's a big target.
- OK. Listen.
- A Memphis crew provides firearms.
- Graphite, titanium, plastics.
- Memphis?
Memphis, Egypt.
I just started work with you guys,
but if we're gonna bring down SD-6,
we have to eliminate
their source of arms, Ineni Hassan,
Three of Her Majesty's favourites.
And now, the new design,
as I promised.
I named it the Benni,
that's my son's name.
It holds 12 rounds
and it's semiautomatic.
What the hell is this?
No!
That was... Sorry.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
That was six months ago.
I have friends from the Middle East.
Hassan's not one of them.
- I don't blame you. Listen.
- There's more.
A geneticist in Kuala Lumpur, he...
OK, stop. You have to listen to me
now. OK?
We're talking about the plan,
I'm giving it to you.
I'm giving you the plan.
Tomorrow you're back at SD-6,
nothing should change.
You'll detail your mission
on a paper bag. Bag.
Then you'll call this number.
Memorise it.
After three tones press a digit.
1-6, each corresponds to a trash can
at a specific location.
We'll review your information,
create a counter-mission.
We'll contact you posing as a wrong
number, Joey's Pizza. Any questions?
Yeah. Can you show me what
a bag looks like again?
You listen to me.
I appreciate what your job is,
even if you're too young for it,
to establish a protocol between
the CIA and their agent.
But I'm not here to pick up
Langley procedure.
I am here for one reason only
and that is to destroy SD-6.
- Hey!
- Then I am out.
I want no more spy crap, that's why
I went to you in the first place.
I will hand you, in record time, the
people who will render SD-6 useless.
- Record time?
- Two months, tops.
And then I am out. I walk.
Draw me a map.
Draw me an SD-6 map, all its allies,
how far you think it reaches.
- Do I look like I'm in junior high?
- Just draw me an SD-6 family tree.
- Do you see a retainer?
- Just do it!
What's your problem with me?
Maybe it's that I'm a woman.
Maybe you don't like my attitude,
I am sorry about that,
but I really don't feel
like wasting time here.
There is only one way we're going
to immobilise SD-6 and that's my way.
So forgive me for being
forthright or female,
but this is how it's gonna be.
Since I've been at the CIA,
I've only seen this map grow.
This is what
you're in the middle of.
If shutting down
the LA cell was all,
we would have raided
that office years ago.
This is not about cutting off
an arm of the monster,
this is about killing the monster.
The work ahead of you,
your father's work,
it's complicated, it's political,
and it is long-term.
- Here, memorise this.
- I did.
OK. I guess we'll wait
to hear from you.
Hey, wait.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Hey, see you in class.
- For sure.
- Look, this one's chipped.
- That's OK.
That's one of my mom's.
OK. These are heavy.
Put this down right... right here.
No problem.
- Thank you.
- That's almost it.
- I'll need a massage later.
- OK. Good to know.
- Finally.
- I know, I'm sorry.
Litvack called and I had to rewrite
The Parking Lot.
- They had no horseradish.
- Cool.
- That's annoying.
- There's a woman eating newspaper.
- Eating?
- She's pregnant.
It's a condition some get before...
- Eating newspaper's a condition?
- Yeah. This is how I make a living.
And Litvack says my writing's
judgemental. Who cares?
She's gonna swallow it.
- What are you doing Thursday?
- Probably rewriting.
Charlie got an offer.
Hey, that's great. Where?
Fleming Letterman. That's
corporate law, downtown office.
I heard of that.
Dinner Thursday, you are required.
I'm totally there. Congratulations.
Hey. Do you want...?
Do you want any food?
Yeah. I just want to do the closets
first so I feel like I live here.
Here.
Thanks.
- Syd, I can't take it.
- Will, let's not do this.
- You know, I can't let this go.
- Will, come on.
- You took Amy's passport and...
- I know what happened.
I'm spinning, Syd.
It's the bank.
What was going on with Danny,
was he in trouble?
I need you to...
- Shut up?
- Accept what I've told you.
- You've told me nothing.
- I started imagining things.
Maybe you're not imagining it.
Syd, this is what I do.
- I may find something the police...
- Stop it!
Please.
I'm trying to move on here.
I need your help to do that.
OK?
- Miss Bristow.
- Hey, Marshall.
I don't get overly personal,
I don't like to cross that line.
You probably don't notice,
but I'm not much of a social person.
I like myself,
I mean, I enjoy myself,
it's just I don't feel pressure
when I'm by my...
Do you ever feel that?
You can say anything you want to me.
I just wanted to tell you that
I'm really sorry about your fiancé.
And it's nice to have you back.
Thanks.
Let's start with what we know.
We've received two pieces of intel.
First is this memo
from GRU headquarters.
It seems certain files
were reported missing last week
from the 7th floor of the Aquarium.
- That's Foreign Intelligence.
- Then we got the second.
Abul-Hasayn Navor,
military attaché from Sudan,
whom you'll remember from last year.
He's on his way to Moscow
to meet these two men,
Kazamir Shcherbakov
and Luri Karpachev,
both ID'd as members
of the Russian Mafia.
We think they stole the documents.
The codes indicate
that these lost documents
pertain to the Soviet-American
nuclear arsenal during the Cold War.
Buying 20-year-old
intelligence records. Why?
That's the part we don't know.
You're leaving tomorrow morning.
The job is to prevent the transaction
and retrieve the stolen files.
- Marshall, tell us what you got.
- OK. Who here has trouble
falling asleep at night?
Well, anyway, myself on occasion.
I find it difficult to nod off,
mind racing, ideas, et cetera.
This kind of pertains
to the sleeping thing.
I created this just for Navor. Now...
You take this little round thing
here, it's pretty cool,
and you just touch it
with your finger or your...
Barely touch it
and you're knocked out.
It's like free-basing
Thorazine, boom!
You only get two times on this.
It only works twice, so you don't
want to use it three times.
- Do we need to wear those gloves?
- No, you can make it a nice ring,
or perhaps an attractive cuff link.
I'm wearing gloves
cos I touched this
the other day, knocked my head
and was out for 20 minutes.
You can see the...
Right, but that's not...
I'm trying to be Pavlovian about
these puppies. No pun intended.
- They keep coming back.
- You mean Navor?
How is that man
able to walk after Atbarah?
- It'd be him or someone else.
- Let it be someone else.
We kill ourselves,
but the bad people keep coming back.
- Sydney, do you have a minute?
- Yes, of course.
I'll be in tech ops.
It'll take you some time
to adjust to being back.
I want to make sure you're alright.
I'm fine, thanks.
Good. I need to show you something.
I'll leave you two alone.
It's OK, the room's clean.
No-one's listening.
- Hello, Sydney.
- What is this?
I'm here to tell you what you
already know. That I work for SD-6.
- Or so they think. Sloane did this.
- Why?
Because it will facilitate
what we're doing,
if they know that you know.
It wouldn't hurt if you acted
surprised when you left the office.
Since I've known the truth
about you...
...l've asked myself questions,
thousands of questions...
...but this one I have to ask you now.
When Danny was killed...
Dad... did you know?
Did you know that's
what they were going to do?
Yes.
Don't you ever speak to me again!
Abul-Hasayn Navor
is attempting to purchase files
stolen from the Russian Government.
Sloane is sending us to Moscow to
prevent Navor from getting the files.
Dixon will impersonate Navor.
My job is to break into Navor's hotel
room and take the money for the buy.
So, what's next?
- Hello.
- Joey's Pizza?
I'm sorry,
you've got the wrong number.
- It's me.
- How are you doing?
How am I doing?
Things have been better.
I'm working with friends
who have no idea who they work for.
- Sloane had you meet your father?
- Yes, he did.
So what's my countermission?
Navor's been short-listed
for six months.
He attempted to purchase
a nuke from Libya.
You knew about Moscow?
No, we didn't. Thank you for that.
Don't mention it.
- That was cold. So what's my move?
- Carry out your assignment.
Get the documents. When you get
back make sure you hold the files.
We'll execute two brush passes
at the airport.
The first at the gate.
We'll duplicate the material
and return them
in a second pass
at the airport kerb.
- That's it?
- That's it.
- Want a Slush-O?
- No, thanks.
- They're delicious.
- No, thanks. I said I was cold.
Good luck.
No, I can imagine.
That must have been devastating.
Did he say anything
after he drove over your cat?
Did he make any threats?
To you or your cat?
Sure. No, OK.
You have my number at the paper.
OK. Bye.
- A man ran over his cat.
- I understand.
People drive over cats!
- You never answered my question.
- Which?
- What are you doing for dinner?
- Jenny, you're 19.
- I'm 20.
- I'm not having this conversation.
I'm ancient compared to you.
Look how red my eyes are.
- You don't look too bad.
- Pull me that file on Daniel Hecht.
- What, that murder? Your friend?
- Yeah, do you mind?
- No.
- Thanks.
- You don't take me seriously?
- No, I don't.
- Dixon, do you copy?
- Wow, that's loud.
You told Marshall you wanted
it louder, I was there.
OK, my headache and I are 10-17.
- Break a leg.
- You, too.
- I'm on 15.
- Get the cash quickly.
That is the plan.
Shcherbakov and Karpachev
just showed up.
Standing by for your call.
Wow! The bodyguard's out, Navor's in
the shower. I'm going for the money.
Move fast, they've spotted me.
- Are you my Sudanese friend?
- Mr Shcherbakov?
Karpachev. I'm the handsome one.
- No protection with you?
- Why? Should I not feel safe here?
Here? Here you should feel very
safe, yes. Come, let's sit down.
I know the guy who owns this club.
He thinks I brag too much.
It's true, I do.
Yes, I brag too much.
That's the problem with Sudan,
there is no place for fun.
It's a nice change,
being out of the Sudan.
You said you travel often.
Yes... but not often enough.
I can see you don't have the money
with you. Is that correct?
No, not at the moment.
But the money is very close.
I've got bad news.
Dixon, this wasn't a buy,
it was a hold-up.
There's no money here.
- Fantastic.
- What?
The vodka.
Dixon, don't panic.
I'll be there in two minutes.
Any word from her?
No, I don't expect to hear
anything till she gets back.
- Your girlfriend is Alice?
- Shut up.
- I'm just checking.
- Get out.
OK. Alright.
I'm in the bar.
I can see you.
Are those the files?
If they are, cough.
Are they documents?
Are they on disk?
How many?
Get ready to make a switch.
Just like a drug deal.
Would you like to taste the coke?
How do I know
you haven't made copies?
Those disks are encrypted.
OK, enough nonsense.
Where's the money?
- Stay here, I'll go get the cash.
- Sounds good.
Who are you?
At first I thought Navor sent you.
Now I don't even think that.
Two three-and-a-halfers. Move fast!
Use the 3rd and 4th copies.
It'll take about 90 seconds.
- We're talking seconds.
- I hope they're not corrupted.
- Moving to the main terminal.
- We know. We're doing what we can.
Let me see that data as soon
as it goes up. I'm seeing it.
- We got it. Give me the other one.
- Come on!
So he says,
"I asked for butter an hour ago."
I'm thinking,
"No, you asked the other black girl,
you rich entitled son of a bitch."
Some people go out,
this is my theory, to abuse waiters.
- No question.
- Creepy, isn't it?
There are bad people.
Hello.
Sorry I'm late.
This is for the offer.
- And for helping me move.
- Thank you. Wow, look at this.
Now we have drink when you come.
- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Sure.
I'll be right back.
What's going on?
We've known each other
for three years. Confirm that.
Yes.
It feels a lot longer, right?
We know each other pretty well.
Yeah, we do.
You know I'd never do anything
to hurt you.
- And you know I'm a curious guy.
- Will, what did you do?
- You gave me no info on Danny.
- Oh, God!
I looked around a little bit and
I found out a piece of information,
which you might not know,
but maybe you do.
What?
The night that Danny was killed...
Did you know that he was booked
on a flight from LAX to Singapore?
- Yeah. I knew that.
- You did? You knew that?
Yeah.
Danny had a medical conference.
He wanted me to fly out, meet him
afterwards, have a week in Bali.
I spend all day, every day,
trying not to see him
the way I found him.
And I know you mean well,
and I love you for that,
but please, let this go. Please.
- Syd, I'm sorry.
- It's OK.
I get it, I won't bring it up again.
OK. I just need a minute.
- Syd, I feel horrible.
- No, it's OK.
I'll be right there, OK?
OK.
Doomsday Six. That was the name
of the operation.
During the Cold War,
six armed nuclear weapons
were smuggled into
and buried in the USA.
In December '89 this was disclosed
to the US Government.
The bombs were quickly
recovered and disarmed.
- That was the info on the disks?
- No.
They revealed a seventh nuke,
buried still, right now, in the US.
- Where?
- We don't know yet.
Those disks were encoded
with a sectional encryption.
Analysis is still working on it,
this is all we've got so far.
Milovich lvanov,
Buckingham, Virginia. Who's he?
We assume he's the man Navor was
looking for. He has no file.
- You think he's minding the nuke.
- Yes, I do.
Go to that address,
report back on lvanov.
Any aliases, where he lives, works,
what he drinks, the whole deal.
Thanks.
- Yeah?
- I'm going to see Ivanov.
Who?
Sydney? Sydney!
We have a name and address,
we can't sit on it.
Sir, we cannot move
on that information.
We can and we will.
We are risking her place in SD-6
and her life.
That may be,
and we might sacrifice a double.
- She's going to see a sleeper agent!
- It's a nuclear weapon.
Do you expect me
to wait until she contacts us?
Have you read her file?
Do it. You'll learn that
she's an asset doing our work.
- She was supposed to contact you.
- She couldn't.
If we send in a team,
we risk blowing her cover.
We can't afford to do that.
- Read her file.
- I've read it.
- What do you want?
- Five hours. Give her five hours.
- Five hours.
- Thank you.
- Impressive.
- Yeah.
Balls of steel. That's what I'm
going to call you from now on.
Hey, have you met Balls of Steel?
We've got a red wire, a yellow,
a blue, a blue-white, a white!
A black, a white-black, an orange,
a purple, a purple-white...
- OK. Cut the blue-white wire.
- Cutting the blue-white wire. OK.
- Hold!
- Don't tell me to hold.
- I'm sitting on a ticking nuke!
- Are there two timers or one?
Just... I only see one.
Alright, try the blue wire.
- Try it?!
- No, cut it!
Hello?
You called SD-6 instead of the CIA.
You should've called me.
- What would you have done?
- Access scientists.
- I had two minutes!
- You didn't contact us.
- I did contact you!
- You are irresponsible.
Yes, SD-6 has a nuke,
and, yes, it's my fault.
After I called,
SD-6 knew I'd found it.
But we'll track it and steal it back.
It's in Cairo.
- What?
- When SD-6 picked up our nuke,
they put it on a plane to Egypt.
Are you ready for this?
They sold the thing to Ineni Hassan.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
Reflected on both our records, FYI.
- What?
- I've been there, Hassan's.
- I can go back.
- No, can't do it.
- Why not?
- It will get back to Sloane.
We'll just have to make sure
they never see me.
Thanks for meeting me here.
I'm sorry about hitting you.
- You're off to Cairo. Devlin said.
- Yeah.
That's why I had them call you.
I need your help.
SD-6 can't know
that's where I'm going.
I'll take care of it.
Dad.
It was you, wasn't it?
Who bought the ticket...
to Singapore.
You were in Taipei.
I'd arranged a flight for you as
well. You could've gone anywhere.
I went to Danny's apartment,
except I got there too late.
Just minutes too late.
Thank you.
I have to go... obviously.
- I'm in operations. If Alice calls.
- I need you.
Yeah. I know.
Just call me if there's anything.
- Let me say about Bristow.
- Don't bother.
Don't apologise, you're not
in trouble, it was my call.
She is intimately familiar
with the Hassan base.
She'll disable the weapon,
we're all over it.
You don't have to be. You're being
pulled off the Bristow case.
What? Why?
Devlin wants a more senior officer.
You were right.
This girl is pretty important to us.
- Yeah, I know.
- He wants you to oversee
the presentation at
the DCI non-proliferation meeting.
Which under the circumstances
is pretty ironic.
Yeah?
Yeah, send him in.
- You heard from Sydney?
- Yeah. What's wrong?
She went up north.
She just needed to get away.
- Is she OK?
- She will be.
I think it's hard for her,
accepting the news about what I do.
- Are you alright?
- Yeah, of course. Why?
I don't know, you seem a little...
What?
Nothing.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah. OK.
I'm in.
- I think I found it.
- Copy.
- Yeah, I found it.
- Copy. Commence disabling.
Open. I'm going for the core.
Radio silence until completed.
Do you have to talk
like such a robotron?
- Radio silence requested.
- I guess you do.
Alright, robotron,
I'm holding the core.