Seven years ago,
I was recruited to work for SD-6,
which I was told
was a covert branch of the CIA.
I was trained as a spy,
warned not to tell anyone what I did.
I thought I was working
for the good guys
until I told my fiancé about SD-6,
and they had him killed.
That's when I learned the truth,
that SD-6 is part of the enemy
I thought I was fighting.
Now, I'm a double agent, working
with the real CIA to bring down SD-6.
My only ally is another double agent,
a man I hardly know. My father.
Rambaldi's become a priority.
We need that code.
We learned the K-Directorate agent
stole the key to the lock box.
It was Anna, wasn't it?
Obviously, we need the key
and they need the box.
Six hours ago
I contacted K-Directorate
and we settled
on an arrangement.
You and Anna will meet
at a neutral location,
under cover of both agencies'
security forces.
Together you'll open the lock box.
Oh, my God!
Zero, zero, one, one, zero...
- Did you get it?
- Did you?
Dixon, I may need transmission.
I've lost her signal.
- Zero, zero, one, zero. Get that?
- Got it!
- I'm giving SD-6 the wrong number.
- No. Give them what...
I'm not giving the right sequence.
No way! Forget it!
Sydney, it's critical. Sydney, give
them the number! That's an order!
- An order?
- Yes.
We have to have a long talk
when I get back to LA.
- Dixon, I've got the code!
- Go!
Zero, one, zero, zero, one...
Zero, zero, zero, one, one, zero,
zero, one, one, one.
Just two ones... and...
One, one, zero, one. That's it!
One, one, zero, one.
You did good.
- You do not give me orders!
- Maybe I do.
- I could have misled SD-6.
- You're not thinking.
Stop talking for a second!
If SD-6 got a bogus code,
what happens when
K-Directorate get the right sequence?
They would think I made a mistake.
And Anna didn't? She'd have
given them the correct code.
They'd know it said Athens.
K-Directorate would head there.
SD-6 would have nothing
and suspect you!
We have to be very careful here.
Wildly, crazy-careful.
If SD-6 suspects you in the least,
it's over!
Anna's been the enemy
for three years.
In Berlin, I realised she wants SD-6
to burn almost as much as I do.
To the CIA, the only thing worse than
SD-6 getting critical information
is if K-Directorate gets it first.
Anna is still your enemy.
You're not into mysticism?
- Mysticism?
- Neither am I
but keep an open mind, it'll help.
The code was written in 1489.
The guy who wrote it
was some sort of Nostradamus.
His name was Milo Rambaldi.
This binary was written
by a 15th-century fortune-teller?
Why have I never heard of him?
His designs were so advanced,
they assumed he was insane.
On some drawings,
he made lists of numbers.
ID numbers of technology
not made until now. This year!
It's real! It's a hunt.
This man spent the last ten years
of his life on one project.
We don't know if it's a weapon,
a fuel source, a transport system.
Based on the little we know,
its technology is beyond
anything we have ever seen.
How's your wife? I forgot to ask.
Good. And yours?
Actually,
Emily's a bit under the weather,
but thanks for asking.
- Did you read the report?
- They found nothing.
This is Anthony Rossi,
transferring from Jennings.
He's working on the UCO file.
You met Marshall. This is Bristow.
I know your father.
We read the code you recovered.
We sent the team to Athens.
I just had a call from SD-3.
There was no evidence
pertaining to Rambaldi.
We were there first.
It turns out we made a mistake.
But... so did K-Directorate.
In our rush to decipher the Rambaldi
enigma, we misinterpreted the code.
It left us with two series of digits.
We assumed longitude and latitude.
He was using a compression scheme.
I should have seen that.
Instead of Athens, the team should
have gone to Malaga, Spain.
Which is... where you are going.
There's a 500-year-old church
sitting on Rambaldi's coordinates.
- What am I looking for?
- We don't know.
The only clue we have are two words
that were part of the code.
- Sol d'oro.
- Golden sun.
I was hoping you'd come.
- You said nothing to Charlie?
- I needed to talk to you.
- It's a match book with a number.
- Yeah, Rachel, who 'loved tonight'!
- Ask Charlie about it.
- Yeah.
- What else can you do?
- Have you ever spied on anyone?
I know it's totally beneath me
but Charlie's been so distant lately.
When I ask what's wrong, he says,
"Nothing, baby, everything's fine."
You don't believe him?
He has law review in an hour.
- And you wanna follow him?
- So much, I cannot tell you.
I think spying on your boyfriend
is regarded
as a bad relationship precedent.
What if he's cheating on me?
- You're a really good friend.
- Yes, I know.
So this thing happened
with Will the other night.
- What? Did he come on to you?
- No. No.
I kissed him.
- What?! You kissed Will?
- I know, stop it!
We were in the apartment after you
left and we'd had all those drinks!
I don't believe it!
There he is. Start the car.
Start the car!
- No. Wait till he's a block away.
- Look at you, gettin' all into it!
- Everyone knows you wait.
- I don't know you wait.
You wait.
What's he doin'?
OK, I guess he's not goin'
to law review.
H-E-C-H-T?
You're certain? OK. Thank you.
I promise, I won't call you.
Danny's meant to be registered
at a conference in Singapore.
You said. Litvack wants
the Baptist Church copy.
I checked all the conferences,
he's not registered.
I know!
- Will Tippin.
- Hey, it's me.
- Hey. Hi. How'd your trip go?
- OK.
- Fine, thanks, how are you?
- Good, busy.
Listen, you don't feel weird
about what happened, right?
A little.
- Me too.
- We'll talk about that later.
Francie and I saw Charlie last night
with another woman.
- What? You're kidding!
- She spent the night at my place.
She's here now. She's sort of a mess.
- Oh, God!
- The bank called.
- I might have another trip.
- You take a crazy amount of trips.
Would you drop by later,
check she's OK.
Yeah, of course.
- Thank you. I should go.
- OK, go. I'll talk to you later.
That was Sydney. You're different
when you talk to Sydney.
Don't analyse me.
Can you get the number of the guy
who works for the airport?
What's his name? Luis Escorza.
What?
If you want me to do something
for you, you say, "please".
Please, Escorza! OK?
You know,
"please" is implicit, Jenny!
Dad!
- You've a meeting with Sloane?
- McCullough.
- Psych evaluation?
- Routine. Nothing I'm not used to.
Nothing I look forward to.
But such is the nature of the job.
So, Berlin. It worked out.
My meeting with K-Directorate,
we got the code.
That was smart.
Well, I should go.
I'll see you later.
Dad...
...could we have dinner?
How about Thursday?
Do you have plans?
No. Thursday. Dinner.
That'll be fine.
Analysis is working on the piece
she brought back from Spain.
This is not glass. We know that.
It's a synthetic polymer.
They believe it was made
at least 500 years ago.
Before we had synthetic polymers?
So the mystery continues.
Meanwhile we have another situation.
Last year's United Commerce
Organisation Ministerial Conference.
Some groups led planned attacks
against it. Zero Defence among them.
Word is, they will be at this year's
conference in Sao Paulo.
Luc Jacqnoud should be
in Morocco in 48 hours.
Isn't he in La Sante
for stabbing a police officer?
Released early.
He has ties to French justice.
Intel reports he'll be
in Morocco to meet a client.
- ID on the client?
- None. That's your job.
You're Kate Jones and Justin Burnell.
You're with Mindspring
Learning Tours, arriving Wednesday.
You are to monitor the meeting,
ID the client
and make sure whatever it is
Jacqnoud is up to doesn't happen.
- Is Mokhtar the contact?
- He's meeting you at the airport.
This is an Egyptian commando.
We recruited him two years ago.
Marshall?
How is everyone? Hi. Alright.
You're going in with the usual tech.
Camera, comm gear and sat' relay.
But this... this is new.
This looks like a normal purse,
right?
You would wear it
going out with your lady friends.
Put your feminine things in there.
But... parabolic microphone!
It has a laser transmitter
with a 300-yard radius.
I also added a low-frequency wind
filter to eliminate unwanted sounds.
Not that you're going to be in wind.
Probably not...
But if you were...
like a light breeze, like a...
or even something stronger,
like a gust. Like...
This? Nothing. Silent wind filter.
You feel lighter than air.
And as you continue
moving downward,
you feel more and more relaxed.
The escalator continues down,
and the closer you get to the light,
the more relaxed you feel.
The escalator seems
to continue forever
and you feel safe and... relaxed.
Still listening to my voice,
keep going,
and the farther you go,
the more comfortable you feel.
Completely safe...
...and comfortable.
It's only a matter of time
before I find out the truth.
- Jack?
- Just give me a minute, will you?
- Sorry I'm late.
- It's alright.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
We knew Jacqnoud was travelling.
We thought he was going to Bahrain.
We don't know why SD-6
is so interested in UCO.
Sure you're OK?
- Yeah, I just...
- Did you fight with your wife?
- My what?
- Your wife?
What wife? I... I have no wife.
No? There's a picture in your office.
You and that woman.
She and I are not remotely...
You thought I was married?
- I guess so. What's the big deal?
- Nothin'!
So... when you get an ID
on who he's meeting,
and details of that meeting,
call the usual number.
Hit the eight key.
We'll dead drop in the trash can.
Why did you ask me if I had a fight
with my girlfriend?
- I don't know. Did you?
- Huge!
Good luck in Morocco.
Thanks.
Look at you.
It's been a while.
Hello!
How've you been?
Busy!
Too many people with dangerous toys.
Any news on Jacqnoud?
A friend tells me he's meeting
a client today at a market place.
I've got a spot for us.
- Any word on the client?
- Big mystery. We don't know.
Come, I'm parked right over there.
Charlie has called my cellphone
six times!
- You still haven't seen him?
- No.
I want him to suffer. I'm not even
gonna tell him where I am.
How was Chicago?
Did you get there OK?
Yeah, Chicago's fine. Let me say
one thing, so someone's saying it.
There might be an explanation.
He got in a car with a woman
I've never met...
Just talk to him. Tell Charlie
what you saw. You owe him that.
Maybe... After he calls me
a few more times!
Call me if you need me, OK?
Love you.
How's the view?
You wanna give this a test run?
- Can you hear me?
- Loud and clear.
- Jacqnoud just walked in.
- Who's he with?
Looks like he's solo.
You ready?
- I'm going shopping!
- Bring us back somethin', would you?
That's the plan.
- Are you picking this up?
- Yeah.
The mike's hot!
Do you have anything
bigger than this? Back there?
I don't understand.
Don't understand you. Sorry!
The meet just got here.
Got him.
Mokhtar, do you know this guy?
I'm gonna try and get an ID
right now.
Nice to finally meet you.
Everything worked smoothly
getting here?
Yes, thank you.
Oh, merci beaucoup.
Merci.
How are we doing?
- You mean phase three?
- What were the results?
You'll be very happy.
Good. If Patel's to be our delivery
man, I'll need a piece tomorrow.
As long as the financial arrangements
are made that shouldn't be a problem.
Bon. Salut!
- Damn. The bodyguard, I know him.
- What?
From Corsica two years ago.
The sonofabitch broke my arm.
Mokhtar, pack up.
We gotta get out of here.
- What's happening?
- Syd, get out of there!
- You. I know you.
- I'm sorry. Are you talkin' to me?
I think you remember me too.
I'm sorry. I don't know who you are.
Tell me why you are here.
Or this time...
I do more than just break your arm!
He wanted to charge me $50!
That's too much.
Dixon!
Dixon! Do you copy?
Dixon?
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine.
We have to go.
- Hey.
- Hi.
How was your trip?
- It was awful.
- Syd, I'm sorry.
What goes with Charlie?
I'm meeting him for coffee.
He knows something's up.
If he has no excuse,
if he... can't explain why
he was kissin' a whore
instead of goin' to law review,
I'm gonna kill him.
- Don't say that.
- She's on a rampage.
She wasn't gonna go out with him.
I forced her to call him. Hi.
Hi.
Let me ask you something.
Do you think it's gonna go alright?
I do.
Love you.
- See you, Will. Thanks
- Good luck.
- You look exhausted.
- Pretty good assessment.
So,
I was thinkin' about what happened.
You know...
That... you know, that kiss.
Yeah. And I think
I figured out why I was so weird.
Why?
Well, because...
How often do you... you know,
do you kiss someone
that you're that close to?
I mean, never.
Anyway, I... I know that it's
awkward between us now, but...
...I think that I've figured out a way
for it not to be so awkward any more.
What?
OK, that didn't work, did it?
I have to go have dinner
with my father.
Ooh, well, I feel like an idiot.
No, don't. Don't.
Oh, my God, I feel...
Oh, my God.
Would you like to order, ma'am?
I'll wait, thanks.
I'm meeting someone.
Thank you.
So, you gonna tell me what's up?
Do I have to start guessing?
- I saw you.
- Saw me what?
I saw you outside our house
with a woman.
What you doing? Watching me?
I don't have to answer.
What were you doing?
She's a friend.
A friend you went out with
instead of going to law review?
- Her name's Rachel, right?
- No.
- I trust you.
- I give you reason to!
I am not gonna let you lie to me,
Charlie. Now, explain yourself.
Francie, I love you
and I'm not playing around.
We were just hanging out.
That's all.
Right. Hang out,
hang out with Rachel.
- Hello.
- Sydney. Sorry to call so late.
It's alright.
I won't be able to make dinner.
Work is... I can't get away.
- You understand?
- Of course.
Don't worry about it.
I'll just see you at...
I'll just see you.
OK. Bye.
I'm sorry to call you.
I just didn't know who else to call.
My father and I were
supposed to have dinner tonight.
For the first time since I was a kid.
I can't remember the last time.
He just didn't show.
He said he had work.
And he didn't have work.
This isn't just about my dad.
In Morocco, that man who died,
he was a friend.
He was a good man, who thought
he was fighting for the right side,
that he was working for the CIA.
He was lied to. And now he's dead.
I had his blood on my hands.
- Sydney.
- I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Like I don't even know who I am
any more, or what I'm doing,
or why I'm doing it.
You just threw your beeper
in the Pacific.
I know.
OK, listen to me.
There's something you need to know.
When you first walked into my office,
with that stupid, bozo hair...
...I thought you were crazy. I thought
you might be a crazy person.
But I watched you
and I read your statement.
And I've seen... I've seen how
you think. I've seen how you work.
I've seen who you are.
In this job, you see darkness.
The worst in people.
And though the jobs are different
and the missions change
and the enemies
have a thousand names,
the one crucial thing,
one real responsibility you have,
is to not let your rage, resentment
and your disgust darken you.
When you're at your absolute lowest,
your most depressed,
just remember that you can always...
You know? You've got my number.
I put the recording you made
through voice print.
The man that Jacqnoud
is meeting with is Malik Sawari.
He specialises
in industrial demolition.
This is his latest innovation.
It's called the BLU 250.
Commissioned by a Swiss corporation
to blow out mountains
for high-speed trains.
There's a third piece.
- You will be very happy.
- Good.
If Patel is to be our delivery man,
I'll need the piece by tomorrow.
The man they're referring to
is Dhiren Patel.
The winner of the Edgar Peace Prize?
Patel is India's delegate to the UN.
A former President
of the Human Rights Commission.
He would not work with Jacqnoud.
- So what's the connection?
- Irony.
Jacqnoud is using Patel
to send a message to the UCO.
- Which is what?
- Abolish the organisation.
We've traced half a dozen threats
to Jacqnoud.
This has it that this last act
will be his most violent yet.
You think he'll plant
an explosive on Patel?
I do. And I want you two to stop it.
You leave for Sao Paulo tonight.
The job is to find Patel, recover
the weapon and safeguard the UCO.
Any questions?
- Any luck?
- I don't see Patel anywhere.
That's unusual. Buying
an international flight with cash.
He was travelling alone, right?
Excuse me?
Daniel Hecht
was not travelling alone?
- I have a 20 on Patel.
- Let's get him out of here.
- Something's wrong. He looks sick.
- Sick?
- He just went down.
- Does he have a drink?
- Yes.
- Get the glass.
Is he OK?
Did somebody call a doctor?
Excuse me. I'm a doctor.
- Can I help?
- Yeah.
Guess who's here. Sawari.
I tell you, if they bomb this place,
it'll be tomorrow at the opening.
Well, they fed Patel some kind
of powdered sedative compound.
It looks like a designer benzo.
Keep an eye on Sawari.
I'm following Patel.
Confirm something. The person
travelling with Daniel Hecht,
the name was Sydney Bristow?
Right? No? Are you sure?
OK, then, tell me who.
Just give me the name.
C'mon.
What about you owe me one?
Alright.
You remember my assistant, Jenny?
- No. The other one.
- What are you doing?
Yes. Give me the name,
and she'll go out with you.
- No, she won't.
- She'll go out with you.
- Hold on a sec. Just say you are.
- I'm not...
- Please.
- Fine.
Hi! Yeah. OK.
I'd love to go out with you.
OK? Right, give me the name.
The person who was travelling
with Daniel Hecht. Yeah, I know.
Kate Jones?
Kate Jones.
- There was any problem?
- Ready to go.
Sponge.
Scalpel.
Careful with that.
- That's equivalent to 300lbs of TNT.
- Yes, don't kill us.