Hello?
Andi, hey.
Yeah, everything's
on schedule.
Dinner might be
a little bit late.
No, i want
to cook for you.
Heh, no.
No, you won't get
food poisoning.
All right,
i'll see you in a bit.
"Debone chicken."
All right.
Aaah!
Why?
Why did you
betray us?
Tony?
Tony!
I swear i was
tricked by the devil!
Look into my eyes.
I didn't betray you!
I...
I-I know.
I know, I know,
I know, Sam.
Come here.
Did i hurt you?
I didn't mean
to hurt you.
Needs a little garlic.
What it says next?
Uh, debone chicken.
Ok, easy enough.
Oh.
That's how you do that.
I'm, uh, leaving
my apartment,
Dropping out of
society altogether.
Except for my bon
appit magazines.
They're what
keep me sane.
But it's just
not safe to be
around anymore.
Where are you gonna go?
Oh, steve and I had
this little ramshackle
place in the country.
We...were gonna
retire there.
But now it's perfect
for what I need.
To fight against...
the devil.
To do what?
To defeat him.
I'm going
to rebuild the army.
Pass the paprika.
Tony, I think
the better way
To defeat the devil
is with Steve's plan.
Random acts of kindness,
pay it forward.
That's what's going
to stop the devil.
Hey.
Hey! You're early.
Yeah, sorry,
I just felt guilty
with you doing everything
on your own.
No, it's fine.
Were--Were you talking
to someone?
Just me.
Just, I was--I was
reading the...cookbook.
Oh. 'Cause I heard 2 voices.
Yeah. I like to give
different voices
to the ingredients.
[Deep voice]
grr, zucchini.
Well, it smells great.
Yeah.
Um...
It's the paprika.
So are we still
on for lunch?
Definitely.
Anything you want
from the meat truck,
my treat.
You, sir, are an
amazing boyfriend.
Heh. Bye.
Bye.
What's goin' on
here?
Take a look.
Hey.
So, you're back
together, huh?
Yeah, decided
to give the poor thing
one more shot,
See how she handles
herself, you know?
I hope you guys both
know how lucky you are
To have strong, proud,
intelligent women.
It's hard to find love.
I should know.
Don't--Just don't, man.
Don't mope.
Don't go down that road.
You want to find a girl,
We will help you
find a girl!
You must have your eye
on somebody.
I got nothing.
Of course
you've got nothing.
You choose to got nothing.
All right, man, come on,
show me the list.
What list?
What list?!
You got this list.
The one--Benji!
The one you've had
in your back pocket
For 10 years,
all right?
So let's see,
what would you like?
You would like
a girl who's funny,
sure,
Smart, piercing
green eyes,
Delicate wrists,
independently weathy,
A trained masseuse.
Essential.
Uh-Huh. A fan
of mixed-Martial arts.
Tough.
Familiar with the works
of Ms. Sue grafton.
Intellectual.
Sue grafton, really?
Oh, alphabet novels
are sick,
And g is for gumshoe
is so off the hook.
Point is, Ben,
We all want
to date this girl,
But it isn't gonna happen,
you know why?
She doesn't exist.
Now listen to me, ben,
I am going to spit some
scientific fact at you.
The longer most men
are in a relationship,
The happier they get.
The opposite is true
for the lady folk, ok?
So we would just
like to see you happy
Making a woman miserable,
like we're both doing.
So, kill
the ridiculous list, ok?
Kill the list.
Head's up.
Ow!
Nice header there, becks.
Oh, look at you, man.
I kick a soccer ball
right at your head,
And you're grinning
like an idiot.
I'm not grinning.
Maybe this
will put a smile
on your face.
You see number five
over there?
And the one over there
by the jungle gym?
And that one
over by the tree?
Don't tell me
they're all souls.
No.
They're all related.
They all have
different mothers,
But the same father.
Ok.
But they don't
know that, see?
As a matter of fact,
i don't think
Any of the mothers
know that, either.
That this man...
is the father.
He now goes by the name
Jack King.
Yep, ol' jack's
not only their father,
He's also the proud father
of a few hundred other children.
A few hundred?
Yeah.
He's a true narcissist.
A man after my own heart.
I mean, what is he,
a serial rapist?
Wow. You go
to the dark place fast.
No, nothing like that.
No, Jack's method
of conception
Is somewhat
less conventional.
I can assure you that
the sperm in our bank
Comes from the highest
caliber contributor.
Here is our donor book.
You can start
flipping through,
But i have to say,
I think i have
the perfect guy for you.
Yeah, i'd have to say,
he's pretty much
the total package.
So where
do we find him?
Devil says Jack
opened up shop again
at a new sperm bank.
Oh, fun.
Whoa.
Vessel.
Huh? Oh.
What?
That doesn't look
all that--Whoa!
Oh, sweet lord in hell!
Oh, thank you, devil.
Thank you so, so much.
May I? Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He's duncan mcleod,
the highlander.
The highlander
doesn't have a scythe.
He's duncan mcleod,
the highlander,
who now has a scythe.
All right, let's just
get on with it.
Ok, take it easy, easy.
Sweet, let's go.
Hi.
You ready for lunch?
Oh, um, actually,
I already ate.
Oh.
It's my fault.
I challenged Sam
to an eating contest.
I won, heh.
Yeah. Yeah, Sock brought in
a bunch of food.
It was paella.
It's spanish for rice.
But i promise you I'll...
I'll make it up to you, ok?
Ok.
No problem.
Hey, so, uh,
Did the devil happen
to mention to you
What this
semen demon's
special powers are?
I don't think so.
Ok. 'Cause my head
has gone
To some pretty
awful places
with this one.
Hi, uh, we'd like
to become donors.
Mm-Hmm.
Fill these out.
Just so you know,
We have an extremely...
rigorous
Selection process.
Oh, that's good.
So do i.
What college
did you attend?
Harvard.
I went to Oxford.
Yeah, but i also went
to yale medical school.
I research alternate
power sources.
I have a 4-Foot
vertical leap.
Hey.
There he is.
Come in.
Hey, Jack.
Hello, heh.
You're not here
for a deposit, are you?
I don't know,
we may be making
one big deposit today--
You back to hell.
Hmm, no.
Come on, you don't think
i really belong in hell!
I was just trying
to make the world
a better place!
And I did!
No, no, please,
don't do this!
I--I have children
to think of!
Hundreds and hundreds
of children!
Did you mean
to cut his head off?!
Uh!
Whoa! Oh!
They're over here!
Aaah!
No, this way.
I don't know
what to do! I cut him!
Cut him again,
Cut him again!
You morons!
You're carving up
a masterpiece!
You're destroying--
Aah!
All right, now, now,
Hold on one second.
Before you send me back,
tell me...
how do I look?
Stupid question.
I know I look great.
Sso we good?
Yeah.
I feel kinda hungry.
What do you want to get?
I don't know.
I feel like ham
for some reason.
Let's do it.
Ben?
Hmm?
Want the rest
of my pretzel?
I can't finish it.
Are you kidding?
I know you love your pretzels,
are you sure?
It's my fifth one
of the day.
Oh, my god, come on,
that is not safe.
All right.
What's that?
Uh, nothing.
It's...it's nothing.
What? Let me see.
No, it's just
this stupid list
About everything
I want in a girlfriend,
And it's long, and I'm going
to cut it down, so I--
This is really great.
Really?
Mm-Hmm.
You know, because
the guys think
it's unrealistic,
And they think my standards
are too high.
Really? Oh, ben,
they are wrong.
This girl
is out there.
You just gotta go
and find her.
Yeah?
Mm-Hmm.
Soul mates exist.
I really
believe that.
Have you met yours?
Yeah.
When I was 12.
I was at the mall,
And I was sipping
an orange julius,
And I looked up
and there he was.
Phil collins.
You hang on to
your list, Benjamin.
Your Phil Collins
is out there, ok?
Oh, that's so funny.
What?
I have almost
none of these things.
Hmm.
For you, milady.
Oh!
Ow! What are you doing?!
I saw you!
What, what?!
I saw you, sam!
You killed that man!
Ow, ow. You saw that?
Yeah! How could you
do something like that?
Huh? How?
I promise you--
I promise you,
There's an explanation.
Fine. Please,
Explain to me
how you chopped
Some guy's head off!
Right. Right, exactly.
Ok? Think about that.
Think about
how crazy that is.
Me? Sam Oliver,
Chopping a dude's
head off? I mean...
Who does that?
Ok? I mean, come on.
There has to be
an explanation
for that, and there is.
Then what is it?
Um...
that's the--
That's the thing,
Is...I can't tell you.
Ok.
I have no other choice.
I have to call the police.
Wait, wait, wait,
Andi, no, you don't!
All right?
What you saw me
doing today,
That was--That--
That was my other job,
all right?
Listen, and I need
a little time
to talk to my boss,
And once I do that,
I can tell you the truth.
Sam! None of this
makes sense!
Yeah, but it will!
I promise, ok?
Just...Andi,
I'm begging you, please.
I need a day.
Just give one day.
I mean, do you really think
I would do something like this?
You have 24 hours.
What's this?
It's the vessel,
all ready to go.
Just shoot it on down.
What's this?
Nothing.
Just a message
for the devil.
Kind of personal.
All right, fine, I--
I'm kind of in a bind here,
And I really need
to talk to him
about something,
And I didn't know
what else to do,
so I wrote him a note.
Can you please--
Can you please
just send it?
Whatever.
Thank you.
Next.
Are you familiar
with this actress?
The woman does everything.
Amazing range.
It worked.
You got the note.
And you've got a problem.
The soul is still out there.
What do you mean?
I caught him.
I dropped him off.
Not all of him.
You missed a piece.
Hey. This isn't
a hook-Up spot.
You want to get
your jollies off,
do it in the alley.
What did you--
Did you kill him?
Is he dead?!
I don't know, Sam,
I'm not a doctor.
He's still
breathing.
Oh, thank heavens.
Now, look,
Can we just talk about
the fact that the soul
is still on the loose?
I told you
I got him.
Really?
This footage was taken
less than an hour ago.
Hey, that's him.
How is that
even possible?
Jack's all about multiplying.
He's like a starfish.
Cut off a limb,
grow a whole new Jack.
You must have
missed a piece.
Ok, fine, fine.
I promise,
I'll catch him.
But I need
to talk to you.
Something happened.
I need to tell Andi
the truth about you.
What do you mean,
something happened?
Well, she sort of...
saw me chop
Jack's head off.
And why did she
sort of see that?
Because she followed me.
Because you're getting
sloppy, Sammy. Jeez!
She said she's going
to the cops!
I don't see
another option.
I have to tell her.
I mean, I promise,
I can make her
keep the secret,
But I don't--I don't
see another way.
Well...
maybe we can
work out something.
Anything.
Well, one day,
I will come to you...
and I will need a favor.
Done.
Before you say yes,
think on this--
Could be a big favor.
In fact,
it probably will be.
Well, hell, let's be honest,
it'll be terrible.
Doesn't matter, I'm in.
All right.
Well, then you keep Andi
from talking,
And you can tell her...
about us.
But you'll owe me.
Do we have a deal?
Yeah.
We have a deal.
You promised the devil
a favor.
Is that--Is that what
you're telling me?
That's great, Sam.
Another deal
with the devil.
That's, um,
always a good plan.
What choice did I have?
It's the only way he would
let me tell her the truth.
I have to tell her. Today.
You want us there
when you do it?
Yeah, i could use
a back-Up.
You got it,
homeboy.
Hey, Ben,
Could I use
your conditioner?
Hi, guys.
Oh, hi.
Yeah, um, it's the one
in the green bottle
With the kelp extract.
Nice. Thank you.
What?
It just helps
to tame the frizzyness
And to really maintain
manageability--
Not the shampoo,
dumb dumb, the girl!
When'd you hook up
with Sara?
What, no? No, i--No.
I just...got married.
What the hell
are you talking about?
She needed a green card,
And I felt sorry
for her, ok?
And, look, it just happened
all really quickly.
Ok, so she's living here now?
Just for a little while,
you know,
Just to make it look real.
You are too stupid
to exist.
Why? I like Sara.
I think she's great.
I think she'd make
an excellent citizen,
And she paid me 1,600 bucks.
You know, I take it
all back, buddy.
That is awesome.
That is outstanding.
She is beautiful!
Beautiful!
We got married!
Andi, before I tell you
what I have to tell you...
you should take this.
I'll take it.
Ahem. Andi,
What I'm about
to tell you
Is going
to change everything
You think
you knew about...
the world,
The universe,
life, death, everything.
It'll explain
all those times
I've been weird
Or showed up late
to something.
It's that part
of my life I told you
I couldn't talk about.
Sam works for the devil.
What? What? It's not
that big of a deal.
My other job
That I was
telling you about...
I'm a bounty hunter
for hell.
Andi, hold on!
Where are you going?
Is this your idea
of some sick joke?
Before I was born,
my parents got into
some trouble.
And to get
out of it, they...
they sold my soul
to the devil.
Oh, shut up.
Hey, I'm not
joking, ok?!
Wait a minute!
When a soul
escapes from hell,
I have to capture it.
What you saw us
doing the other day,
That was
an escaped soul.
You only have
a few hours left.
If you don't come up
with a real explanation,
I'm going to the police.
Wait, Andi!
Andi!
How'd it go?
Where the hell
were you guys?
I was dying over there.
She didn't believe
any of it.
Sorry, I had
to wait for the chili
cheese fries.
My wife called.
Oh, where
are you going?
To get the stupid soul.
You do know
that the creator
Didn't make you
in his image, right?
The Bible was just
being nice.
Where's Jack?
The soul's not gonna
come back here, Sam.
He knows
you're onto him.
Any other bright ideas?
Yeah. I found his date book.
Shows due dates
for all his
upcoming babies.
But you're too
distracted by this
business with the girl.
She didn't
believe you,
did she?
No.
They never do.
So what's
your solution?
I'll think of something.
I'm a little concerned
This thing with Andi's
going to continue
to be a problem.
I want it handled.
I said I'll take care of it!
Yeah, I know,
You've said that
to me before.
Too many times.
I just may have
to handle this
problem...myself.
Aaah!
Seattle pd.
Hello?
Andy it's me again
Please give me a call
back when you get this.
You can't go to police,
all right? You're in danger.
Not from me...directly.
Just give me
a call back, ok?
Guys, I can't
find Andi anywhere!
Ok, relax,
all right?
Take a deep breath.
Relax?! What if she
goes to the police?
Uh, Sam, I wouldn't
worry about that.
Are you kidding me?
You know know what happens
if she goes to the police?
The devil is going
to fix the problem, ok?
And we all know
what that means.
He has a very different
definition of "fix"
than we do.
All right, Sam, listen
to your uncle sock, ok?
Everything is going to be
all right.
Andi's life
is in danger!
She'll be fine.
We...kind of
solved that problem.
What does that even mean?
Solved it how?
What are you doing?!
Let her go!
Sam, Sam!
Hey, hey, hey!
This is the only way
to stop her.
What, tying her up
And throwing her
in the trunk
was the only way?
She is very comfortable
in there, ok?
I threw her fresh blankies,
some pillows,
A little bundle of--
Potpourri.
Solving the problem?
This isn't solving the problem.
This is adding a felony
on top of the problem!
Better this
than what the devil
would do to her.
He's right, Sam.
Ben speaks truth.
This is a solid plan.
All right, all right,
so what's the plan?
What are we going
to do with her?
Uh...
We didn't actually--
We didn't think
through that far.
Hey, hi, how are ya?
Brought you a juice box.
Sam,
what are you doing?!
Get me out of here,
all right?
I can't breathe in here!
Ok, here, here.
God, what are you doing?!
Get me out of here!
Andi, i can't.
No, listen, you know what,
you know what,
I believe you.
Ok? You work for the devil.
Andi, I know
you're lying, ok?
I'll know
when you believe
what I'm saying.
Fine. If you can't
let me out of here,
Then can I please
have that juice box?
The potpourri back here
is burning my throat.
Yes, absolutely.
Closer.
Get me out of this trunk
right now!
I'm going to rip
your throat out,
you mother--
Let me guess,
the wife?
Yeah, she wants me
to bring home
some half and half.
Oh, my god,
the nerve.
All right, look,
you tell her
1,600 bucks
may buy her
u.S. Citizenship,
But it does not buy
your wonder twins,
all right?
Yeah.
Tell that lazy
fog breather,
Go get your own
half and half.
Sam! Sam!
Sam! Sammy,
we're here.
Andi, let him go!
Keep breathin', buddy.
We got you. Breath!
When i get
out of here,
I swear i'm going
to kill all of you!
That was horrifying!
Really, Sam,
horrifying?
Really?
You stick your head
in there, man!
You'll see your own death!
I don't want
to stick my head
in the trunk!
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, that's--That's it.
That's how we make her believe,
we scare it into her.
Right here?
So that's tony's little
gourmet hideaway, huh?
Yeah, I asked the landlord
where he was forwarding
tony's magazines to.
Oh, good.
Always wanted
to build a log cabin.
Hey, what's that?
They're demons.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what are you doing?
What are you doing?!
No, no, no, no.
It's not safe for you
to be coming here
like this.
Ok, it's ok. We're--
Shut up.
Get in a circle.
Out of range
from you-Know-Who.
What's
his problem?
Ok, it's safe.
What is wrong with you?
The devil might have
followed you here!
What's he going
to find out here?
All of the recruits,
the soldiers for
the new rebellion.
Look, don't get me wrong,
we are happy to have you,
It's just a little
risky, is all.
Tony, we're not here
for the rebellion.
You're not?
What--What are you here for?
We kind of have
another problem.
Ok, all right,
all right, ok, now!
Ok!
Let me go,
you psychos!
Hold on, doggie, whoa!
Take it nice
and easy-Like, all right?
Oh, she's got nipple!
Ok, ok, calm down,
calm down!
It'll be clear to you
in a few seconds.
You're going
to see proof, ok?
Andi, you remember Tony?
Please tell them to let me go!
I do not want to be here.
They will, Andi.
We just need to show you
something first,
And then you'll be free
to do whatever you choose.
What? Show me what.
Andi...
Tony is a demon.
He's a demon
from hell.
Show her.
Ok.
Oh, word of warning,
Please do not
pee on my carpet,
I just put it down.
Ok.
Where's a good spot?
Phhbbt.
Oh-Ho!
Sweet home Alabama!
Tony!
See? It's true.
Why?
Ah, that always happens.
And it always hurts.
I gotta go get her.
Oh, don't worry.
There's nothing
around for miles.
She has nowhere
to run to.
Uh, did you leave
the keys in the car?
It's possible.
Thanks for the lift.
Oh, well, believe me,
it's always a pleasure
Hanging out
with you boys.
Hey, don't be strangers.
We won't. Tone-Ster.
Can you do that thing
one more time? Please?
For me? Come on!
Please, once?
Oh! Ha ha!
Oh, now I see why Steve
loved you so much.
That's inappropriate.
That's a compliment, tony.
I know, but it's
still offensive.
Hey, thanks again, tony.
No problem.
Sam?
I hope everything
goes well with andi.
Be patient.
I'm sick
of being patient.
It's like every time
I get close to her,
something happens.
I don't know.
Maybe it's not
supposed to happen.
Do you love her?
Yeah.
Do you know
how rare love is?
You can't just turn away
just because you hit
a few speed bumps.
Steve and I,
We, heh,
we had our issues,
But we worked
through them
Because we knew
at the end...
only love matters.
Love is worth...
any sacrifice.
Oh, look at me.
Diarrhea of the mouth.
All right,
I better get back,
Because, um,
I get a little nervous
When I spend
too much time
out of the circle.
Be safe.
You, too, Sam.
And hey, wi@need you.
Viva le resistance.
No sign of Andi,
no one's seen her.
She never clocked in
for her shift, either.
Yeah, and she never
went home last night.
She could be anywhere.
I doubt she went
to the police.
I mean, what's she
gonna tell them?
"Oh, I saw
a big, gay demon."
Ok, she's probably
hiding,
Praying heavily
right now.
Jack's calendar.
I forgot about this.
If we're gonna keep
the devil off our backs,
There's one place
we need to be.
Is--Is she dilated?
How's her breathing?
Who are you?
The one she'll be
thanking later!
Oh!
Which one's yours?
That one right there.
And...that one.
And maybe that one.
Jack's got a busy week.
Real bumper crop
of babies.
All right,
we need to split up.
I'll take
the emergency exit.
Sock, you take the front,
ben, go around to the side.
Got it.
Where have you been?
Wha--
You promised me you'd take care
of this Andi situation.
I tried to, but she
ran away from me.
I can't find her.
Oh, I fixed that problem.
She's in the trunk.
This is your last chance
to get it right.
Andi! Are you ok?
I don't know!
Come here.
I don't know
how the hell
I got in here!
Are you all right?
You're safe! You're safe.
Look, I'm sorry
you're freaked out.
I didn't know
how else to--
You know, Sam, no, it's ok.
I understand.
Ok, after what I saw,
And what Tony is...
I believe you.
Andi, listen to me.
You have
to promise me
You will not tell
anyone about this.
Ever.
I promise.
You do? That's great,
that's great!
Listen, I--I have
to go do something,
But when I get back,
why don't you come over,
And we can talk about this--
No.
No, no, I can't.
Why?
I can't handle it.
It's too much.
Andi, I love you.
I know this is
a weird time to say it,
But...
I love you.
I'm...
afraid of you.
Excuse me.
Where is the place
that women have babies?
Aren't you a little old
to just be figuring that out?
No, I--
I know where women
have babies,
I was, um, referring to
Where the room is, yeah.
It's down the hall.
Just make a left.
Ok. All right. Cool.
Hey, is that
a Sue Grafton novel?
Y is for yes.
How do you...feel about
mixed martial arts?
Hey.
Have you seen
the baby ward?
Huh? Oh, no,
I thought I was
Following around
a pregnant woman
for a while,
But turns out it was
just a bloated dude
With a bad case
of the farts,
you know?
It's him.
Run.
Jack, don't--
don't run.
Stay back!
Jack, it's over, man.
You're not getting past us!
[All screaming]
Ugh.
Good-Bye, old friend.
I got it.
Oh!
Come on, you little
sneawhere are you?Tch.
Oh...
I'm sorry,
don't mind me.
I'm just having a...
a bit of a rat problem.
You have delicate wrists.
How do you handle jujitsu?
Benji, need some help!
Runaway hand,
come on!
I will be back,
and me and you, ok?
You can't hold me off
forever, Jack!
I think
you're right.
Sam?
Andi, get out of here!
Wait here,
I'll be right back.
It's in here.
Yeah, yeah, it's in here.
Ok, let's go ahead
and bag him, yeah?
Ha ha!
Where are you?
Get out of here!
Naked guy!
Naked! Naked guy
on my back!
Somebody help! Doctors!
Oh-Ho, Benji!
Oh, Ben,
that was horrible.
Oh, god.
It looked horrible.
I can still feel it.
Is there a mark?
Andi!
Think she'll show up?
Andi?
Sure, she'll
definitely be here.
You know she said
she was afraid of me?
Oh, come on,
you're loveable.
Oh, who could be
afraid of this guy
right here?
Look at him!
Look at that
little cheek!
Hey, hey.
What? Oh.
The old ball and chain.
I got some
wedding rings!
From ebay.
Cool, well...
well, speaking of cool,
Um, I wanted
to thank you
For the pep talk
the other day.
'Cause I--I didn't
give up on my list.
And I found
my Phil Collins.
And her name is Cassidy.
Yay.
I am very happy
for you, but no.
What?
Oh, you know,
you're married.
Um, not really.
Um, yes, really.
Look, think.
What if immigration
come crawling around?
They are cracking down
on these green card
marriages!
Listen up,
problem solved.
You tell them that you have
an open green card marriage.
Thank you, Sock.
Listen.
You made a deal,
And I expect you
to live up to it.
I'm sorry, but...
I'm gonna go on a date
with Cassidy.
I'm not
letting you go.
Fine, then I'll just
report you to immigration.
Fine, then I'll report
you extorted money
from me,
And we'll both
go to jail.
You know, screw it,
i'll just give
her back her money.
Well, well,
now, Benjamin,
Let's not make any rash
decisions here, ok?
'Cause at the end
of the day,
There may not be
all that much "money"
to give back.
We'll talk
about it later
While we enjoy
our floor seats
At the blue collar
comedy tour.
Lowest common
denominator.
Yeah! Oh.
Andi! Hey.
Um...
so...
So...
Weird day?
Sort of.
Although,
you've been a weirdo
for months, Sam.
It's just now
at least
I understand why.
You were trying
to protect me.
It's true.
It's completely true.
Although,
I've gotta say,
I'm stunned
you've managed to
survive this long.
I mean, I should
have never been
afraid of you.
I should have been
afraid for you.
Yeah, it's a miracle
any of us are still alive.
Yeah.
Outside the hospital
when you told me
that you loved me...
did you say that
because you meant it,
Or because
you didn't want me
to go to the cops?
Both.
Uh-Oh.
Look at this. Look at
how sweet you two are.
I knew that locking her
in the trunk of my car
Would work out
for the best.
You loved it,
didn't you? Come on.
Don't sweat it,
It's just part
of the job.
Really?
Mm-Hmm.
So does this job
pay anything?
Yes. Sam has
to get us a beer
whenever we demand it,
So, you know.
Beer. All we can handle.
Beer.
More beer!
Beer, beer, beer, beer.
Throw your hands up, beer,
throw your hands up!
Darling...
Yeah, what
a lovely place.
So rustic,
so remote.
What are we doing here?
Sam, sam, sam,
I think you know
the answer to that.
Remember how quick
you were to give up
that favor?
So impetuous.
You really
ought to think
before you act.
There's something
going on in there.
Beyond the circle
I can see or hear.
I need an inside man.
I want details.
Names, dates, you know,
that sort of thing.
You want me to spy on Tony?
You want me
to betray my friend?
Oh, please, don't be
so melodramatic.
But, yes,
if you want to use
those words, yes.
Ugh.
Hey, come on.
That's the deal
you made, man.
You tell Andi
your secret,
You owe me a favor.
Or we could discuss
the consequences
For you and Andi
if you refuse.
Well, Sam?
It's your answer?
Sam?
Hey!
Thought I saw you
out here.
Why don't you
come on in?
I don't--
I don't know--
I think you could be
a real help. Come on inside.
There's, uh...
there's some people
I really want you to meet.
Come on.
Cold out here.
Yeah, it's freezing.
Listen to : Thin Lizzy