Alan townsend's flight landed
in rome 2 hours ago.
Taking into account time
stuck in immigration
and adding an hour for the cab ride
he should be safely within
the walls of vatican city... right...
about...
now.
- He'll call, Sam.
- I wouldn't sweat it, man.
I have to get ready for work.
Watch my phone.
He's so bossy.
I love it.
I knew you'd rock a Turtleneck.
- What are you doing?
- Upscaling your look.
- No. I'm fine with my look.
- Sammy, I know you want to resist it.
But I really expect you to rise to the
heights of political power here earth.
Seize control of the planet
and hasten the apocalypse.
What you wear reflects
directly on me as a parent.
And as a stylist.
Try these slacks.
I'll go dig up a pair of Beatle boots.
I have more good news.
I'm granting you a little
break from catching souls.
- You are?
- Yes, I'm sending you to a tutor.
Someone who'll give you a higher
education in the ways of the wicked.
She's expecting you today.
- What's with the circles?
- You like it?
It represents the 9 circles of hell.
I contracted an advertising firm
to help me spin a few branding ideas.
I think it's nifty.
I have another surprise for you.
A gift.
Something to put a little
testosterone in your tank.
- You got me a motorcycle?
- Go on, hop on!
I want to see those thighs
vibrating with pure aggression!
All right, what's the catch?
Catch? There's no catch.
My generosity, in this instance,
is more a softening the blow.
I got him.
- Got who?
- Alan townsend!
He never made it to Vatican city!
I had his plane grounded in Vegas,
and he went into
a sin spiral so decadent
that he was back in hell before
carrot top took the stage!
I stabbed you in back fair and square
man. It's impolite to leave me hanging.
I hate you!
Hey, don't walk away mad, son!
I'm not done showering
you with spectacular gifts!
Perhaps now is not the time.
-= 209 =-
" No Reaper Left Behind "
Sub VO : ¤Aka¤
Subs-Addicts"
[Sub-way.fr]
Hey. What are you doing here?
Sock and Ben asked me to come
over and watch over your phone.
- Where'd they go?
- They said they had to go exercise.
You know what? The call's not coming.
The devil got Alan.
No. God, Sam, i'm so sorry.
Don't feel sorry for me.
Feel sorry for the devil.
Because I have had it up to
here with that son-of-a-bitch.
- He is in my sights!
- What does that mean?
And why are you dressed
like a 70s porn star?
It means I'm done playing nice.
- I'm taking him on!
- How are you going to take him on?
I mean, he's the devil.
He's packing a lot of evil.
Yeah, well he's also wearing blinders.
He's convinced that I'm a pushover.
That I'm afraid to fight
fire with fire. Well, I not.
And I will.
This is only motivation.
What are you doing up there?
Listen. I broke up with you, OK?
We're over.
Now I had hoped that you would
respect my decision about.
Damn it, Nina!
That is a 62-piece Handy dad socket set.
It's coming out of my paycheck!
OK. Nina, acting out like
this isn't healthy! All right?
I mean, have you ever considered
dicting your rage
into an anger journal or graffiti art?
OK. Look. Let's not lose sight
of what we shared.
You know, the tenderness.
The pillow talk.
Our lazy afternoons watching Ellen.
Dancing along.
Yeah, hi. I'm Sam Oliver.
I have an appointment.
I'm not taking appointments today.
I was told to come here for tutoring.
The devil sent me.
That bastard. He knows I'm on a cleanse.
Let yourself in.
I'll meet you in the study.
It's the room with the chalkboard.
Let's get the formalities
out of the way, shall we.
My name is Sally,
but I'd like you to call me teacher.
- My name is Sam.
- I don't remember asking.
Now, am I to assume you are
the devil's offspring?
So I'm told.
And am I to assume you are in training
to bring about the end of days?
Right. I'd like to ask you a few
questions. Morning show talking points
let me get a better understanding
of what you already know
regarding hell and damnation
and where I need to fill in the gaps.
- Right.
- Do you read Latin?
Have you ever read the Bible.
Either Testament?
Have you ever heard of the Antichrist?
Yes! Wait.
No. I was thinking the other guy. Sorry.
And on a scale of zero to 10,
where would you rank your blood lust?
I'd have to say a solid 2.
- I can't help you.
- What?
Why must the devil insist
on wasting my time?
It's very apparent
that you need preschooling.
You know what?
I don't want to be here anyway.
- You don't?
- No! I don't any of this.
I don't want to learn about
the devil's business!
Wait! You know what?
There is one thing you can help me with.
How do I destroy him?
You want to destroy the devil?
Your father?
Yeah. You're an expert on hell
and the devil. How do I kill him?
How do I blow him up? Chop him up?
Acid dip him? Whatever. I'll do it!
You're a liar.
- What?
- You said your blood lust was at a 2.
I'd say you're running at at least a 7.
So you're here all by yourself?
Yes. My mansion.
12,000 square feet of gilded cage.
But the devil pays the rent.
So who am I to complain? Right?
Must get a little lonely.
Yes, it does.
Undoubtedly that was
the devil's intention.
Can I ask you a favor?
- Maybe.
- Can I come back tomorrow?
The devil's expecting me to show up.
If I could come and hang out,
be out of my hair for a couple hours.
And you'd be doing me a huge favor.
Why not?
I certainly could use the company.
Great!
- 'Til tomorrow.
I tell you it was horrible.
Nina's eyes actually roll in the back in
her head when she attacks-like a shark.
I'm thinking about buying a gun.
- What?!
- For protection.
Ben-look, Ben's having crazy ex
problems right now.
I've seen my share of nutty bitches.
Ben buying a gun
is a mistake, all right?
Why?
'cause Nina's picking a fight, right?
And she wants you to fight back.
- Don't play the game.
- You think she playing game?
Of course she's playing a game.
They all play games, man.
Look, your rationship went cold,
all right?
She's trying to relight the fire.
Only second time around
that fire isn't fueled by love or lust.
It's fueled by anger and petty revenge,
which rarely leads
to satisfying hate-sex, all right?
- Maybe you're right.
- I know I'm right.
Listen. Next time Nina comes
stalking around, you ignore her.
Tune her out.
She'll lose interest. I promise.
$400.
I need afternoons off for the next week.
Devil business.
I'll see what I can do.
Thanks.
- What?
- There's something I need to tell you.
Something potentially upsetting.
I met a girl.
Yeah. She works for the devil.
Kind of a professor,
an expert on hell. Very knowledgeable.
Plus I think she's into me.
I just wanted to be up front.
Just wanted to make sure you
were cool with what I have to do.
I'm planning to seduce this woman.
So that I can
get the devil's secrets out of her.
Secrets that I think will help me
beat the devil once and for all.
I get it. Do what you gotta do.
You're not bothered?
Well, you know, it's difficult to feel
threatened when you're not
really a seducer.
Well...
I seduced you.
You mean, you followed me around
for 7 years like a puppy.
And then wore me down
with your subtle charms.
That's not really called seduction.
It's called... erosion.
Here.
Maybe this will help speed things up.
You understand
i'm in a war with the devil.
I know.
Delivery from bargain bench.
You just entered a world of pain,
my friend.
Work bench blue around here only.
That apron makes you look
like a swedish hausfrau.
I don't even know what that is.
So nobody ordered this computer
equipment? There's no John Oliver here?
John Oliver?
That's my dad.
This is fantastic.
I can't believe they delivered
everything so quickly.
What are you gonna do
with all this crap?
I'm Kinda going
stir crazy in this garage.
And I can't go out in the world
for obvious reasons.
So, I am going to bring the world to me.
Chat rooms and Blogs, Facebook.
With the help of this computer,
I am going to have a life again, Sam!
A rich, full life!
Right here in your garage!
- Cool, dad. Cool.
- Yeah, go forth and ride, Mr. O.
You ride that internet,
you weird glorious bastard.
Where are the fries?
I didn't order fries.
I got us carrot dippers.
- I asked for fries, Ben.
- I know.
And?
I decided you needed
to take a break from fried foods.
- No! Never. Why?
- I tell you this as a friend, Sock.
You have oily hair,
and people are noticing.
I what?
This is hair gel, Ben.
- This is expensive persian hair gel.
- And the beard?
To tell me that sheen
comes from a bottle?
What sheen? What the heck is a sheen?
What did you hit?!
I didn't hit anything. Something hit us!
Holy, crap! Nina!
Benji, maintain. Remember what
I told you what you gotta do?
- I need to ignore her, right?
- That's right.
I see nothing.
That's right. She's not right there.
Just look through her. Just ignore her.
That doesn't scare me.
What say we listen
to a couple tasty tunes?!
- Sounds great! I love music!
- Me, too!
My mom made me a mixed tape!
Jammin'
- Aight?
- We're Jammin'.
- Think it's over?
- It's over, Benji.
We bucked the angry
right outta that beast!
- Pretty sure I have glass in my eye!
- Nobody likes a crybaby, Benji!
Suck it up.
Black on black.
Sexy.
What do you want?
I just wanted to find out how
your first day of school went?
- It was fine.
- I see. And how was Sally looking?
Still as beautiful as ever?
I dunno. I didn't notice.
- Did she ask about me?
- Not really.
Seriously? Nothing at all?
From what I gathered she's not a fan.
- Was there any contempt in her voice?
- Sure, yeah. A bit.
- Fantastic!
- You're happy about that?
Sure. You know what that means?
I'm under her skin.
Now's the perfect time to strike!
I want you to give this to Sally.
A vegetable steamer?
Yeah. I happen to know she wants
that more than anything else. See?
She dog eared the page in the catalogue.
- Where'd you get this?
- I dug it up out of her trash.
You are a stalker.
No, no. Sammy.
I'm a fool for love.
Why do you need me? Why don't
you just give her the present yourself?
You mind if I open up to you a little?
Imperfect father to well dressed son?
I have difficulty
maintaining relationships with women.
Mostly because I mistreat them.
You know, I lead them on. I bag'em.
Tag'em. Kick'em down the stairs.
And I blame it on my deep
commitment to selflove.
It's my achilles. Anyway,
I appreciate your help.
You're my Cyrano.
Now you get out there
and you reel her in for me!
Hey, you may want to run.
I neglected to pay for that.
I'm in here!
You're very prompt.
What's that?
It's a gift. For you.
I got you a gift.
From me.
Oh my god!
How did you know I've been
lusting after a steamer?
Well, I remembered
you were on a cleanse.
So I assumed you were
into healthy foods.
Naturally the mind jumps
to steamed spinach.
How sweet.
Thank you.
I love it.
Right...
I like your skirt.
It really shows off your figure.
And your hair.
It looks especially nice today. Very...
very... bouncy.
Sam, what are you doing?
- What do you mean?
- Well, the gift. The flattery.
- Are you hitting on me?
- What? No.
But
now that you've planted the thought.
Which is a great, great thought.
How about it?
Will you let me take you to dinner?
My, you are surprisingly aggressive.
Well, I'm the kind
of guy that likes to move fast...
When I see something I want.
I mean someone I want.
Not something.
Which could be misinterpreted
that I see you as a piece of meat.
Which, as a woman, and an equal
in every way.
If not superior in that it's common
knowledge that women are better pilots.
And gymnasts. The point being,
you most likely don't
appreciate being compared...
To meat that is.
It's not uncommon
for a student to get a crush
on their teacher.
What I'm feeling right now
is no school boy crush.
I'm fascinated by you.
And I know you're intelligent.
What I need to know. What I don't know.
Is if you could ever take me seriously.
Of course I can.
Great.
Then it's a date.
But we must keep it a secret
from the devil.
Think about it. His favorite teacher
fraternizing with his favorite son?
I mean,
he could come unhinged.
I once witnessed him just cut a man
in half for giving me a foot rub.
Yeah, I'm cool going the secret route.
I'm on pins and needles, Sammy!
Tell me, did she love the gift? Did she?
Yes, she did.
You're not lying to me, now,
just to protect my feelings?
No. She really loved it.
A breakthrough! Finally!
And I owe it all to you, kiddo.
No. Really, you don't have to thank me.
Seriously. I didn't...
Now, this is my phone number. OK?
You give it to Sally.
Tell her i'm waiting for her call.
No. Don't tell her I'm waiting.
That sounds desperate.
Tell her I am expecting her call.
I don't get it.
Why don't you just call her yourself?
I'm the devil.
I don't Chase Tail, Sam.
Tail Chases me.
I called you in because I keep getting
complaints of two fighting in gardening.
We weren't fighting. He attacked me!
- Bullpucky!
- It's true!
I was trying to educate Mr. Chand...
Chandrasekrahn.
On the obvious difference
between seasoned mulch
and redwood bark chips when he
came at me with a edge trimmer!
You had it coming.
This Dick's always up in my grill!
- Hey, you wanted to see me?
- Yes. Yes. Just one second.
You know what? You two need to start
a dialogue about mutual respect.
I want this resolved before I get back.
What's up?
I was just wanted to see how
your war with the devil was going?
It's, it's moving ahead.
I have a date with my teacher tonight.
That was fast.
Just took your advice.
Just jumped right in with both feet.
That's...
That's great.
Can you.
Listen, I'm really jealous.
- What?
- I'm really jealous of this woman.
And I'm jealous that you
might go out with her.
And I'm jealous that something might
actually happen between you two.
And I know I can't even say anything
because I'm the one that put us on hold.
Do you want me to cancel this date?
But I know you can't.
And I can't ask you to.
No, you know what? Don't even
say anything. It's OK. I get it.
- I do.
- Bastard! I will cut you!
OK. I should probably
get back to my meeting.
- You got another im from Sam's dad.
- Again?
Says, why you haven't signed up
for his fantasy hockey league?
You know what? Why don't you tell him
I only have time to service
one fantasy his wife.
I'm gonna let you tell him that.
Get into the training room.
Move, move, move!
I want to talk to Ben.
Well, you don't get to talk to Ben.
All right. He's fragile.
Want to send him a message.
It goes through me.
Get! Get!
Well, I just wanted to say that...
I feel terrible about the way
that I've been acting.
You mean like a girl who eats cars?
I'm not gonna
try to make any excuses here.
But it's not like
I used no self-control.
I mean, your head didn't
end up on a pike, right?
If that's all...
Thank you.
Look, I'm just trying to apologize here.
Do you have to be so rude?
OMG. Maybe you didn't hear
it the first time.
Or the tenth time.
You and ben are over.
Look at me when I'm talking to you. Ben!
I want to talk directly to Ben.
That's not gonna happen. I'm sorry.
Are you standing in the way
of our relationship?
No, I'm standing in the way
of your craziness.
So he grounded his plane in Vegas?
And Alan's secrets went
back to hell with him.
That is brilliant.
You are up against an evil genius.
If you keep filling my glass with more
wine, I might start blabbing
some devil secrets of my own.
God knows I'm sitting on some doozies.
I'm having such a wonderful time, Sam.
It's been such a long time
since I've been out on a date.
Really?
What about you, Sam?
Is there anyone special
in your life?
Nope. Nobody in my life.
What?
I lied.
There is somebody.
Her name is Andi.
If you've got a girlfriend
what are you doing here with me then?
Because we can't be together.
It's really complicated. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for misleading you.
Don't be.
I admire your honesty, Sam.
So here we are at a crossroads.
Do we call it a night? Or do we
press ahead and see where things lead?
How does that song go?
If you can't be with your true love.
The lyric is
"if you can't be with thene you love.
Honey, love the one you're with."
I should know. I wrote it.
Or at least i
provided the weed that provided
the tryst that provided the inspiration.
- This isn't what it looks like.
- I'm not talking to you.
And you! You're a teacher!
He's your student for goodness sake!
Does your perverted
libido know no limits?
What? You're insane!
You're actually insane!
And I don't ever want
to be with you, ever!
I'll deal with you later.
There you are.
Ben's not here.
Ben's working a midnight shift.
So I'll thank you
to haul your stalky-ass outta here.
I don't want to talk to Ben.
I want to talk to you.
Well, I don't want to talk to you.
So, come on.
Slip it out. Slip it quick.
Would you drop
this at the curb. Thank you.
May be some recyclables in there.
So would you be a doll and separate
the plastics?
Good times! Later.
That's a good little trick.
Really spooky. I'm so scared.
Too bad it's pointless.
You can stand there staring
at me all night, turn into a big
acid drooling monster. I don't care.
Because quality sleep,
little lady, comes first.
12 hours a night.
5 hours a day.
- I'm not here to scare you.
- Really?
I need to see Ben.
Sock, I need see him.
And I need to tell him how sorry I am.
And, frankly you're just,
you're standing in the way of that.
I would do, no.
Anything to have ben back.
The question is
what would you not do to protect him?
OK. Let me just clear this up.
You're thinking you can demon-bang
your way through me to get to Ben?
Well, I thought about
bringing a friend. But I wasn't
really sure if you like girls or guys.
That... What? I like girls. What are
you talking about? Get out of here.
OK well, I just thought...
You just thought? You just though what?
You're weirdly close with Ben.
No! Not weirdly close. All right?
Awesomely committed. How about that?
There's a big difference.
So you can just forget about
trying to seduce this guy.
If I feel the urge to trade my dignity
for a little Drowsy Nasty,
i'll listen to Jewel.
Or hit the porn drawer.
So there's absolutely nothing
I can do to change your mind?
No. Not that I can think of. I'm sorry.
Well, then you don't leave me no choice.
Is that mine?
Sam, you wanna toss me one of those
copper spray nozzles? Quick. Quick.
- What are you doing?
- I'm building a flame thrower.
You mind if I ask why?
I'm burning down Nina's lair.
Gonna drive her out of town.
Also would you toss one of
those 3/8th couplets right there?
Doesn't that sound a little severe,
I mean, even by your standards?
She crossed the line, Sam.
She did that demon trick.
All right, she invaded my dream world.
This is my safe place.
No one penetrates my safe place!
- Hey, Sock, have you seen Andi around?
- I heard she called in sick.
Andi, hey, I heard you were out sick.
I hope it's not because of me.
Hey, kiddo.
Gloomy sky today.
Fits my mood.
What are we doing here?
Good question. What the hell
are we doing here?
2 love-struck idiots.
Caught under the spell
of the same witchy woman.
So, you're not mad at me?
How could I be?
What man can resist Sally?
Here.
- A vessel?
- Yes. It's for Sally.
She's an escaped soul?
I let her out of hell, Sam.
I set her up in this house.
Got her a good job,
shower her with affection and still...
It's a matter of honor, Sammy.
Honor.
I was convinced
I'd seen the last of you.
Yeah. Was thinking we could talk.
Yes, about last night?
I'm so sorry. What a disaster.
I should have known better then
to try and sneak around on the devil.
I'm not here about last night.
The devil sent me.
To vessel you.
To send you back to hell.
I'm sorry it's come to this, Sam.
I really like you.
- I like you too.
- Yes, I thought we made a
real connection at dinner last night.
If the devil hadn't interrupted
we most certainly would have
ended up in bed together.
Is that something that
still interests you?
Being with me?
I have a better plan...
To keep you out of hell.
- You do?
- I'll tell the devil the truth.
This was all my doing.
That you're innocent.
I was trying to seduce you.
So that I lied and
took credit for his gift.
What? The steamer was from the devil?
I'm sorry, Sam. I don't quite
understand. Why the gun?
I mean, why don't you just
tell the devil the truth?
- I mean, why all this drama?
- Cause you still have something I want.
Something you can trade
for your freedom.
The devil's secrets.
Secrets that I need.
Are you blackmailing me?
Think of it as a trade.
Share what I need to know,
and you'll stay out of hell.
I'll get out of from under
the devil. It's a win-win.
You're expecting me to betray the devil?
Well... yeah.
I can't do that.
You can't?
I thought you hated the devil?
Well, I do. Sometimes.
But other times.
Other times I find him quite...
charming. I mean, he is the devil.
The second most powerful
being in all of existence.
Now I've never experienced the high that
people say they get from knowing the
love of god. So I can't really compare.
But I certainly know the rush
that comes with being
pursued by the dark
lord.
This doesn't have to happen, Sally!
We can still strike a deal!
- Well, this is a first.
- So, are ready to talk trade?
- Put the gun down, sammy!
- What are you doing?
How about that entrance?
Snazzy?
God, what are you grinning about?
He could have killed me!
Is that the kind of welcome
that I get? Come on.
- Who's your hero?
- You are an ass.
I am the dark lord of asses.
I heard your confession, Sally, darling.
After all these centuries
I finally know...
You're into me.
Yes, so let's cut to the chase.
I didn't come here to try to earn your
love and respect. I came here to earn
a trip upstairs.
You make no mistake.
If it were not for that very
thoughtful vegetable steamer,
you would not be getting lucky today!
Come on.
I don't feel right about this.
Maybe I should call Nina
and talk things out over coffee.
Too late for coffee, Benji.
I might be able to get her in couples
counseling. Work through the issues.
What issues? There are no issues.
You two are over, all right.
You missed a spot right there.
What are you doing, Ben?
We're setting your house on fire.
Why does it always come to this?
Why? This happens a lot?
Yes, I've lost track of
how many times angry villagers
have chased me with lit torches.
It's a flamethrower.
I guess that's just to be expected
when the world sees you as a monster.
- I don't see you as a monster.
- What?
You don't?
What about all that
tormenting stuff that I did.
- And what about what I did to your car?
- I had it coming.
I should have never put
my grandmother's needs over yours.
I mean, she just held the keys
to my inheritance.
You were my girl.
I made the wrong choice.
Yes. Yes you did.
Truth is, I missed you.
I missed you too.
What?
- Buddy?
- What?!
I think Nina
and I are getting back together.
I know how super important
your quality sleep is to you. But
quality sleep is to you. But
do you think you can get past
what Nina did?
For me?
You can melt an iceberg with
those deep brown zeros buddy.
- I know. Bring it in.
- All right.
Get the tank!
Get the tank! The tank!
Get the...
That could have gone better.
You want me to talk to Sock?
Get him to join your fantasy
hockey league?
I'd rather you didn't.
I hate fantasy hockey, Sam.
- What?
- I hate the internet.
I hate trolling dating sites
for women I can never meet.
I hate posting a daily blog
that only's er gotten 8 hits.
- I hate my life.
- I'm sorry, dad.
Don't be, Sam. Because
you know, I've been thinking.
And I think I know the way
you can help me.
Anything.
Send me to hell.
- What?
- Send me to hell.
Let me go look for Alan
townsend for you.
Let me help you get out of your deal.
I can't do that.
Look at me, Sam.
I should have died.
But I can't die. And
I can't live either.
Not like this.
There are answers in hell, Sam.
Answers to fix both our problems.
I was your father once.
Let me be that again.
Please,
let me help.
What's this?
A cell phone.
I found it in Ted's pocket.
I think he would have wanted
you to have it.
Thanks, Sock.
Atta boy.
Be safe, Mr. O.
And thanks for keeping
an eye on king Charlie.
He's such a good rabbit, Ben.
If it's okay, I'm just going tell
him that you went on a long cruise.
Yeah. Of course.
Come on, Sam,
this is exciting stuff. I mean,
I feel like an astronaut
blasting into space!
I love you, dad.
I love you too, Sam.
Give'em hell, Mr. O!
Count on it, Sock! Count on it!
I heard about your dad.
I'm sorry.
Do you want some company?
I called the bargain bench. Turns out
they have a great return policy.
Good.
So, aren't you going to ask me?
- About what?
- About Sally.
No... i am not.
Nothing happened.
Well, you know, it's really
none of my business.
It's my phone.
Text message.
It's from my dad.
What?
"I'm in.
Will keep in touch.
Should've brought water."
He made it.
Team Subs-Addicts"