- Someone need my help outside?
- Oh, young man?
Could I trouble you to
carry this to my car?
Heavy.
- Ok, so this is the vessel?
- That's a toolbox.
And it's for you.
Why do I need a toolbox?
I need you to go
handle some plumbing.
What, so now I'm your handyman?
That's not part of the deal.
Actually, it is.
I own you, Sam.
If I ask you to take
out the garbage in hell,
that's what you'll do.
- Right.
- Don't fret.
This job won't be so bad.
Promise.
Am I glad to see you. I'm Mimi.
Sorry about the get-up.
So what happened here?
Ok, I know this sounds weird,
but my washing
machine is broken,
and I needed some clean clothes,
so I
sort of tried to use
the dishwasher instead.
Yeah, I never would
have thought of that.
I mean, it's all soap, right?
The thing is,
some of the laundry items
got stuck in the spinny
thing in the bottom,
and the whole thing
just died on me.
Wait.
This is the embarrassing part.
The articles in question
are of an intimate nature.
Yeah, I don't know if I'll
be able to get these out.
I think I might have to--
cut them out of here.
Oh! I really wish you wouldn't.
They were a present.
Uh, ok, I'll--
let me see what I can do.
Just out of curiosity, how...
how were you referred
to the Work Bench?
Oh, my boyfriend handles
all the household stuff.
Jerry.
He loves to take care of me.
This is from our trip to Cabo.
He's handsome, isn't he?
Yeah, he...
He--he's a fine looking man.
Season 1, Episode 9 - Ashes to Ashes
For www.forom.com
Are you serious?
The devil has a
mistress named Mimi?
I mean, does she have any idea
that her boyfriend's the devil?
None. He's Jerry.
They went to an all-inclusive
resort in Cabo last spring.
- Unlimited pina coladas.
- I love it. I love it. You know,
if I was the dark lord,
I would do the exact same thing,
I'd have a mistress in every
continent of the planet.
- He probably does.
- He probably does, doesn't he?
God, he's living the dream.
I wanna be the
prince of darkness.
No, no. What's below prince?
- Uh, duke.
- The duke.
I wanna be the
duke of darkness.
Maybe could you
talk to him for me?
- Set up a little internship or...
- No.
- Not even a chance?
Hey, have you
talked to her yet?
No, not since I tried to
give her the necklace.
So you don't know
where you're at.
Not a clue.
Incoming. Incoming.
You guys must have done
something enormously horrendous
- to get food cart duty.
- Oh, yeah.
Some idiot posted a
picture and profile of Ted
on a bi-curious website.
He totally blamed us.
- You do it?
- Of course.
Nice.
Can you actually cover
my shift tomorrow?
I have this family
dinner thing.
Yeah. Yeah, I could do that.
Great. You're a
life saver. Thanks.
You see that?
She's just acting like
everything's normal.
Maybe it's not as big
of a deal as you think.
Ben, last time I talked to her,
I made her cry.
Tears, ok?
Now it's like nothing
even happened.
You know what?
I know what she's doing.
She's acting like a dude.
- No, no.
- Yes, yes.
And that is awesome.
She's acting like a dude.
You know,
anything gets too emotional or too hard,
you just ignore it, right?
Eventually it'll just go away.
Which makes Andi even more perfect,
if that's possible.
Except for the part where she
ripped your heart out
and stomped on it.
That was rude and lame.
I--I can't ignore it.
I--I have to talk to her.
Well, it's pretty obvious
she doesn't want to talk Sam.
Well, what else am I gonna do,
wait till she wants to discuss things?
I don't...
Wait, I get it.
I know what you're doing.
- You're acting like a chick.
- Shut--shut up!
No, no. I will not shut up.
You are acting like a chick,
and she is acting like a dude.
That is so sad, Sam.
I don't know whether to hug
you or kill you out of mercy.
Son of a bitch. Very funny!
I know it's you!
You're not gonna scare me,
so you can just let me out!
I'm glad you don't scare easy.
Why do you have to do that?
Well, it's kind
of in my nature.
You know,
supreme spirit of evil and all that?
Yeah, kind of like your
nature to be an "a" hole?
Oh, that's beneath you, Sam.
You know names hurt.
Yeah, well,
I've got another name for you, Jerry.
Doesn't ring a bell.
What is your deal with Mimi?
Does she have any idea
what you really are?
Sam, I'm not interested
in talking about her.
And don't bring it up again.
We're here for this.
That's your soul,
Dennis Grayson.
He ran this very funeral
home 10 years ago.
He had a very
interesting way of, um,
picking up extra cash.
- He sold body parts?
- Yeah.
People would bring their
loved ones to be cremated.
Before he'd fire up the ovens,
he'd pick them over like
a Thanksgiving turkey.
Anyway, he's back now.
In a way.
What way?
Well, call it a ghost,
or a spirit.
He incinerated his earthly form,
so you can't see him.
But he'll still be
a pain in your ass.
Great.
What's all this?
Oh, I...
I enjoy spending
time with these, um,
- ceremonies.
- Right.
Yes. People start
asking questions--
"Why would god do this?
Is there even a god?"
I like to be here to try
and provide some answers.
Here's a list of the
people the soul is after.
I'd concentrate on this one.
Sarah Negly.
You find her,
you find the soul.
This is a priority, Sam.
Quicker you find him,
the better.
Oh, it's Mimi.
You'd better get
over there first.
The washer's still a mess.
How--how'd you meet Jerry?
Oh, uh, at an art show.
He just swept me off my feet.
Always knew the
right thing to say.
Had this old world charm.
He's a real gentlemen.
That's a rarity these days.
That might be him.
He said he might call.
Hello?
No, I don't want the newspaper.
No, no, thank you.
That, uh, that wasn't him.
Right.
I'm--I'm sure he'll call back.
He's a really busy guy.
So you--
you know Jerry personally?
Oh, a little. Very little.
I--I've worked with
him time to time.
Odd jobs.
- What can you tell me about him?
- I don't really--
Does he talk about his work?
I mean,
he told me he's an importer,
but he's so secretive
about his job.
I--I think he works
for the government.
Oh, that's--that's an
interesting thing.
Maybe--I don't know.
You know more than
I would even know.
Please...
You're my only window
into his world.
Any little thing you could give me,
I'd appreciate.
- Oh, all right. Whatever.
- Ok, thank you.
Oh, and I promise,
I won't tell him we talked.
He would kill us.
Yeah, right, he would. That's--
That's a funny
thing to joke about.
Killing.
I'm officially a dick.
I just spent half the night
telling Mimi how great Jerry is.
Why would you do that?
I don't know.
I just felt sorry for her.
You know,
she wanted to know all about him,
and I couldn't bring myself
to tell her he's the--
Unholy spirit,
the poison of god,
the despicableness
of the earth.
Yeah. Yeah, that.
She's just sad and lonely.
Oh, man. The devil and I have
the exact same taste in women.
Is she really flexible, too?
Let's just do this.
That's good, actually.
I could use a little blow-out.
No, Bert.
Unless you want to spend eternity
trapped inside that thing.
I think I'm looking
pretty good today.
All right.
The devil said we find Sarah Negly,
we find the soul.
Hey, guys, why don't we,
go out the back door?
What?
Ted might see us.
Ted's at a linoleum conference.
Benny!
Hey, grandma.
You're Ben's grandmother.
I cannot believe that
we haven't met yet.
I am Sock.
Comprende?
- She speaks english.
- Bueno.
I'm Sam.
I'm friends with your grandson.
Ben.
So...
That is quite the cart 'o
party supplies you got there.
Throwin' a little
triple kegger?
Break out the old booze luge?
Suckin' back?
Uh, it's just for
a family party.
Nothing huge,
very tiny. Grandma,
this is my family
discount card.
Me and the guys gotta run,
but I will be by later
to come help you.
Yes, grandma, I will be by
later to come help you later.
We are out of here, ok?
Ok, bye.
Come on, guys, let's go.
- It was nice meeting you.
- Nice to meet you grandma.
Oh, god.
Dude, your family has
no idea who we are.
It just never came up.
But now you're
having a big party
with all your friends and
family coming from all over?
I didn't think
you wanted to go.
I mean,
it's gonna be pretty boring.
Right, yeah,
because we hate parties, right?
We hate music and booze.
We hate orgies.
Yeah, and what's with
your grandmother staring
- like she wants to kill me?
- Yeah.
Ok, look.
A lot of people in my family
believe my grandmother has...
the eye.
She says she can predict the
future and see evil spirits.
Really? Nice.
Granny knows you're
BFF's with satan.
Don't take it personally.
No, no,
why would I ever take it personally?
So the eye, huh?
I like it, I like.
It's like some kick ass superhero.
Benny's grandmother is the eye!
I can't believe we've
never met your family.
- What is up with that?
- Like I said,
it just never happened.
Listen, Benny,
you don't have to be embarrassed
of your grandmother.
We all have crazies in our families.
Excuse me, but I'm not ashamed
of my family in any way, ok?
They're not the ones
that embarrass me.
And what are you embarrassed by,
Ben, huh?
Oh, my god. Can you believe
I pulled that out of my head?
Wait a second.
Are you ashamed of Sock?
- Half right.
- Holy crap.
You're--you're ashamed of us?
Yes?
We were looking
for a Sarah Negly.
My mother?
She died a few years ago.
Are you sure?
Uh, yeah, I'm pretty sure.
I'm sorry,
was your mother cremated by any chance?
I mean,
that's her urn on the mantle.
- If that's all...
- Wait!
Have you heard of
a Dennis Grayson?
He's the son of a bitch
who cut up and sold
pieces of her body.
- Get out of here.
- Who do you think you are?!
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
An earthquake or something?
What's happening?
Sir, you might want
to come with us.
What for?
Oh, god!
Open the door.
Come on!
Sam!
Oh, my god.
Sam, we have to get in there!
Mr. Negly?
Now we know how the
ghost soul kills people.
It needs the ashes of the
dead to make itself a body.
I can't believe how
it killed Mr. Negly.
I don't know what to do.
The devil's making
this impossible.
Come on, Sam. You gotta step
back from this, all right?
Step back from what?
- Whining like a little school girl.
- Enough with that already!
No, Sam, it's not enough.
Not until you change, all right?
You need to channel
all this negativity
into some positive-ity.
- I'm serious, man!
- And do what?
I don't know.
Ask Andi out again.
Ok, she doesn't want
to go out with me.
You need to ask her out,
and when she says no,
you have to ask her out again,
and again and again.
All right? You need to be persistent,
like the ocean,
little waves of Sam crashing
on the soars of Andi
until she gradually wears down.
Or she gets a
restraining order.
Ah, stop it!
Stop with the negative energy, ok?
You're bummin' me out.
You know what?
You need to go to her.
You need to ask her out right now.
Ask her out.
Come on. You have the power.
The positive energy,
fill your heart, body and soul.
No, loins. Go to her.
Go, and show her the
power of your joy.
Go, Sam.
Come back to me a hero.
Hey, Andi.
- How's it going?
- Good.
Liking those new pricing guns?
Yeah, they're great, huh?
Hey, you want to go to
a movie this weekend?
You know what?
I can't do this weekend.
No problem. Next weekend?
- I don't think so.
- No problem.
Another time.
You just let me know.
I'll be here.
- Ok.
- Hey...
- Hey.
I think it's cool that you're
a guy about everything,
but maybe you don't
want to do that.
What are you talking about,
I'm a guy. What?
I just think maybe you
might want to figure out
what you're doing with him.
I mean, he's just waiting
for you to make a move, Andi.
I mean, one way or another.
I know, I know.
But, Ben,
this is just really complicated, ok?
It's been so frustrating.
I honestly
don't know what to do.
Well, does he still
have a chance with you?
Maybe.
Maybe is all I
can say right now.
Ok. Maybe's better
than no, right?
- All right, Ben, bring it back.
- Wait--wait! Ow.
Damate carpet.
Yeah, I checked the
names on this list.
These are the people
Grayson cremated.
Yeah, right after he sold the
kidneys on the black market.
Yeah, the family sued
when they found out.
He lost the business,
killed himself.
Now he's back to
settle the score.
Let me see.
There's so many
names on this list.
I mean,
how do we know who he'll go after next?
I don't think we can.
If we don't collect
all the ashes,
the families of all
these people will die.
- That's impossible.
- No, no.
No, nothing is impossible.
Illegal, yeah, stupid,
most definitely,
but not impossible.
Melissa Lambon?
The Work Bench is
about to make your day.
I don't remember
entering any contest.
No, no, no. You know what?
All I know is your name
was on our invoice.
I won't tell if
you don't. Deal?
- Deal.
- Ok.
- I like you.
- That's nice.
- Husband's ashes, 9 o'clock.
- Found it.
- All right,
your free prize is carpet.
You may choose
a style and color from
any of these samples.
They're all so lovely.
I--whoa, check-- Ha, check--
Oh, I almost
dropped it. Check--
Check this one out.
Take a check out.
That would look really
nice in my bedroom.
Just keep going.
Yeah, I feel like the weirdest
drug dealer of all time.
Think you can snort this stuff?
Pretty solid day.
We got a lot of work done.
Yeah. We also
promised to install
about $30,000
worth of carpeting.
Yeah, they'll probably forget.
So what now, boys?
Mom's still in Vegas,
I got the car for another 2 days.
What say we pour a bottle
of tequila in my face?
Nah, I can't.
I gotta go and help my family...
- Do stuff.
- Oh, right.
Secret family reunion.
Yeah, have fun at
that big party
without your friends
who embarrass you.
You guys don't understand,
all right?
It's a matter of survival.
My grandmother's unforgiving.
Why do you care what
she has to say?
She's the matriarch, all right?
I mean, she rules the roost.
I mean,
to her I'm a huge disappointment.
I'm the black sheep
of the family.
She wanted me to be a priest!
Instead, I'm making
minimum wage
at a home improvement store.
- Why is that our fault?
- It's not your fault.
But what I'm saying is,
is if you guys go to the party
and anything goes wrong--
What?!
I could get booted out
of the house completely.
You know,
my uncle Hector got drunk at a wedding.
Grandmother just doesn't let
anyone talk to him anymore.
- Where's uncle Hector now?
- He lives in the house.
No one can talk to him.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
All right, all right, yeah,
we won't go to your party!
We will not go to the party.
All right?
Thank you. Thank you.
No hard feelings, right?
- No.
- All right, great.
- Take you home.
But just out of curiosity,
Sock embarrasses you
more than me, right?
- Absolutely.
- Damn skippy.
I win.
- Thanks for the ride.
- No problem, buddy.
He listen. Pop the trunk.
I need to get the ashes inside.
No, no, don't worry,
don't worry.
I'll get them properly and
respectfully stored, ok?
- Get some rest.
- All right. Just take this--
Jeez, what are you doing here?
No, what are you doing, Sam?
Did I tell you to
desecrate remains,
or did I tell you
to capture a soul?
We're not desecrating anything.
If we don't collect the ashes,
all those families will die.
Oh, brother.
What are you, a boy scout now?
Just find the guy
and put him away.
It would help if we knew where
he was going to strike next.
I gave you a list.
What, do I have to
draw you a map, too?
Maybe I should change your
diaper while I'm at it.
Baby want a ba-ba?
What is your problem?
I am busting my ass here.
You stop worrying
about the living.
Start concentrating
on the dead, Sam.
- I mean it.
- Fine. Are we done?
No.
I'm getting messages from Mimi.
Strange, demanding messages.
That's never happened before.
Now, exactly what are
you saying to her?
Nothing.
But all that woman ever does
is talk about how
awesome you are.
She just waits around
for you to call.
Well, she's free to spend
her time however she chooses.
I made no promises.
- My conscience is clear.
- You don't have a conscience.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
What a break.
She's put her life
on hold for you.
You should let her go.
You should stay out of things
that you know nothing about.
Do your job,
and keep your mouth shut.
Or I'll shut it for you.
Hey, Sam.
That's nice. Who's it for?
Andi.
So you're finally
making your move, huh?
No. I tried.
She, uh,
she said she couldn't accept it.
So what are you going to do?
I don't know.
We're kinda in this weird limbo
thing right now.
She's acting like
it never happened.
Ah, maybe it never will.
Wait, Sam, do you have any idea
how long I had to
chase down your mother
before she'd even talk to me?
2 years.
2 years, seriously?
I was practically a stalker.
- Worked out ok.
- Persistence is king, Sam.
I mean,
how long have you known Andi?
5 years.
- What?
- Uh, well, no... it's just...
Yeah, that's a long time.
But, hey, you know,
you can always hope
for a miracle, right?
You don't think I
should wait for her?
That's up to you, son.
I'd hate to tell
you to give up,
but I'd also hate to
see you spend your
whole life waiting.
I don't know what
do with this list.
How the hell are we
going to figure out
where the soul is
striking next?
I just don't want the devil
to sew my lips shut again.
Or any other parts of my body.
Yeah, that's cool, man.
You are totally not
listening to me.
We should be at
that party, Sam.
- Ben's family's party?
- Yes,
Ben's family's party.
We are family.
He can't just pretend
we don't exist.
He can't ignore us
like we're some
people to ignore, you know?
Yeah, you're right.
- We should go to that party.
- Yeah, yeah, good.
- Because--
- Because?
Because we need his
grandmother's help.
She's got the eye, right?
To see the future.
Maybe she can help
us figure out
where the soul is going next.
Uh, Mimi?
We're gonna-- we're gonna go.
We'll come back tomorrow to
fix the washing machine.
Ok.
Mimi, are you all right?
Jerry called.
Said he was coming over.
So, as usual,
I get ready, and as usual,
he doesn't show up.
- It's pathetic.
- No. Mimi, no.
That is totally messed up, ok?
You cannot let Jerry
treat you like that.
I mean, look--look at you.
Look at how hot you are!
You're like a big plate of
"yeah!" sittin' right there.
Come on. You know what?
You are comin' out with us.
No, I'm--I'm not in the mood.
Well, that,
my pretty young lady friend,
is what beer bongs are for.
Let's go! Come on,
I'm not taking no for an answer,
young lady.
Let's shake that
tail feather, huh?
No, no, no!
- You can't come in here!
- We got presents! Look.
Bought your grandmother a book.
It's in spanish.
- It's french.
- What?
You know, it's never too late
to learn a new language.
- Uh, maybe I should just go home.
- No, nonsense.
Meems, you get in there
and enjoy yourself, ok?
We'll be right behind you.
I-I-I don't even know how
much I can stress to you guys
my ass will be
living in the bench
if you mess up my life.
Ben, we need your
grandma to use her... eye
to tell us who the
next victim is.
Sam, I don't know
if she can do that.
It's our only shot.
If we don't find out who the soul
is going after next, people will die.
Come on!
Benny...
Come on, come on!
Just be cool.
Ice. Ice. Promise.
I haven't done this in years.
Jerry won't take me dancing.
Huh, well,
I hate to break it to you, Meems,
but Jerry might be into dudes.
You are so much fun!
I know, right.
Oh, I can't imagine
what Jerry would do
if he saw us together.
He'd go berzerk.
- You think?
- Totally.
- He's got the worst temper.
- Oh, really?
Abuelita...
mi amigo, el es un tipo bueno.
Y... el solamente
necesita su sabiduria...
y regalo.
Hello, ma'am.
I need your help.
With an evil soul.
Someone on this list
is gonna get killed very soon.
If you could tell
us who that is,
we might be able to
stop it from happening.
Uh, she says she needs
more information,
and she has to look at
the palm of your hand.
El diablo!
Sam!
Sam, you should come inside.
We'll get some
iodine on that hand.
You know what,
I--I need to get home and heal.
Goodnight, Mimi.
Sam, can I talk to you?
Just for a minute.
Sure. Yeah.
Look, I just wanted to ask, um,
I-I know it's weird,
me asking you for advice.
I hardly know you.
Yeah, I'm--I'm
probably not the guy
who should be advising you on--
Do you think I should
break it off with Jerry?
It's just, I've been hanging on for,
god, on and off,
more than 20 years now, and...
always going back to him.
Always hoping he'll make a commitment.
But now I don't
think he ever will.
And maybe it's time stop
waiting and move on.
What do you think I should do?
I...
I--
I think...
you should leave him.
Do you feel that?
Sam! Sam!
- What was that?
- Do you have any, um--
Ashes? Dead people's ashes?
Uh, my mother was
cremated a few years--
I-I would love to
pay my respects.
Where is she?!
Was this an earthquake?
Where are they?
Where are the ashes?
Why? Do you need to--
We need to save them
from the earthquake.
They're in a bag on the shelf
over the washing machine.
Oh, we got 'em, we got 'em.
Yeah. Sock, wait!
- Guys!
- Oh, no!
I left the backpack at the party.
The vessel's inside it!
You gotta protect yourself, Sam!
Protect your orifices!
I see it! I see it!
I got it!
- You got it?
- Yeah!
Nice hands, body!
Sam, that's bad, right?
Duct tape. Duct tape, Sam.
Oh... all right, hit me.
Hit me hard, come on.
What the hell happened?
Are those my pantyhose?
What? Oh, these?
I... I thought these were mine.
Uh, we weren't able to
fix the washing machine,
and the pipes were backed up.
That's...
That's what the booming was.
The wet-dry vac got jammed.
We gotta get a new one.
We'll be back to
clean this up later.
Ok. Sam.
How did we not know
Mimi was on the list?
She must be using
her maiden name.
Interesting, Sam.
Don't care, open the trunk.
Are you sure we have the
soul and not just the ashes?
Forget that question.
Come on, come on!
Caught your ass, ash man!
Caught your ass, you ash! Yeah!
Can you not taunt the soul?
Let's just get to the
center and find the vessel.
Ok. Ok.
Ben, yeah, we need to get back
into the community center.
I don't care that you're
with your grandma.
Just bring the keys.
Almost there, buddy.
I'll be glad to blow-dry this
chalky bastard back to hell.
Oh, he's a feisty one!
Sock?
What did you say you did with
all the bags of ash we collected?
The ash? I took care of it.
Right. How exactly did
you take care of it?
Where did you put it?
Nowhere.
- It's still in the trunk.
It's still in the trunk!
I'm just gonna be really fast,
ok, grandma?
There's hatred in her eyes.
I saw hatred in
the woman's eyes.
- Do you have it?
- I just got here!
Benny, open the door. Open it!
Ok.
We have a whole lot
of ash in there!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Come on!
- I found it.
- All right.
Cover your faces.
I feel much safer now.
This is really
ineffective, Sam!
We're alive!
I don't know how much
time I have left.
- What?
- Ben, what'd she say?
She said I'm doing god's work,
and I finally have
her blessing.
That's great.
You know, she's worth millions.
Thank you.
Oh, congratulations on a job well done,
once again.
- Thank you.
- No, no, no, Sam.
Thank you so much.
Mimi's moving to New Mexico.
That's too bad.
Isn't it?
She said something about not
waiting around for me anymore
and starting a new life.
Now, where on earth would she
get those ideas, Dr. Phil?
It was her choice.
I just told her what
her options were.
You're really broken
up about this.
Sam, don't confuse sentimentality
with practicality.
I spent a lot of time
corrupting Mimi.
And I was this close to
destroying her self esteem.
You're lying.
You sent me to her
house to protect her.
You were the one
breaking all her stuff
so I'd be there to save
her from the soul.
Well, you have me all figured out,
do you, Sam?
Yeah, I do.
I think you really
cared about her.
Want to see how much
I cared about her?
She's dead.
- What?
- That's right.
With the snap of my fingers,
Mimi just got hit by a bus.
Gruesome.
You can't tell her
from the pavement.
And that's on you, buddy.
- You sick son of a--
- Oh, calm down, hero.
I'm screwing with you.
Mimi's fine.
- Greatest movie ever.
- I know.
I saw it like a zillion
times when I was kid.
Except for that part
with the vampire bats.
You know, I've only ever seen
that through my fingers.
It's yours. Only a quarter.
No. Finders, keepers.
But, um, if you try to take
this copy of Highlander 2:
The quickening.
I'm gonna fight you.
Sam! You made it.
- I'll give you 50% off.
- Thank you.
Hey, so, New Mexico, wow.
You heard, huh? Is he upset?
If I say yes, are you gonna
change your mind and get
back together with him?
- Because, then no.
- I'm not gonna change my mind.
I've never been more sure of
anything in my entire life.
Thank you.
- I didn't really do anything.
- Yes, you did.
You gave me the
little push I needed,
showed me what I
was missing in life.
I can't wait around
for Jerry anymore.
I've wasted so much time.
I deserve better.
You do.
Cady, come here.
I want you to meet my daughter.
Cady, this is Sam.
This is your daughter?
Yeah, and I'm gonna
miss her so much.
And maybe the two of
you can hang out.
I'd feel a lot better knowing
somebody was
looking out for her.
Yeah. So you're not going to go
to New Mexico with your mom?
No way. It's too hot.
Mom, you can't sell
my ninja turtles.
Ok. All right.
Donatello, her first boyfriend.
- I'll see you around, Sam.
- Yeah. Nice meeting you.
Hey, Mimi... how--
how long was it that
you've known Jerry?
On and off,
more than 20 years, long time.
But that's all behind me.
I'm starting a new life.
The devil has a child.
You know, I never thought
that the devil had genitals.
What, like a Ken doll?
I don't think
she's his daughter.
She's really nice.
I don't know, Sam.
I don't like it.
This satan's trying to get you
to hook up with his daughter.
You know,
I bet she wants your man seed.
What? No.
Yeah, sure, think about it.
You knocked her up, right,
then the devil has a little
Sam baby running around
catching souls for
him when he grows up.
After, you know, you kick.
Which I hope will not be
for a very long time.
You know what,
I think I'm going to give Cady a call.
What about Andi?
I don't know. What have I been
hanging onto, a glimmer of hope?
I could wait forever and
miss out on living my life.
- Let's do this.
- Yep, let's do it.
Now.
Is it wrong, what we're doing?
Huh? No, no. Man, we're heroes.
It's totally cool.
We should say something.
We saved your families
from a giant ash monster.
You're welcome.
Amen.
- That was nice.
- Thank you.
Thanks to Raceman
for the transcript
Subtitles made by the Bloc Team
For www.forom.com