I'm back with the groceries.
Finally. I'm starving.
- Get everything on the list, Ben?
- Of course.
Got your special potatoes.
- Got your special soy pizza pouches.
- What up?!
- That's for me.
- What's in there?
That's pri... It's my private food.
No secrets, Ben.
Cherry tomatoes,
sourdough rolls, and peanuts.
Why is that so private?
'cause I don't want people to
know what I eat all the time, OK?
- Got, scratchers.
- Nice, Ben. Give it.
Let's see.
OK, come on.
Pa needs a new jet pack.
Zip.
God, I never win anything!
I think I won $1,000.
What?
- I won $1,000!
- We won. We won!
That's so weird. I paid for that ticket
with my own money.
This is so great.
I wanted to take Andi away this weekend.
- I'm gonna go cash it out right now.
- What?
- I hate that guy.
- That's my money.
Let me check this out?
My lucky day.
This ought to be just enough.
Give that back.
You shouldn't be traveling around
with this much cash.
It's financially imprudent.
Live and learn.
That is my money.
And we're going to use
it to bail Morgan out.
- Now, police station. Hop to it.
- Who the hell is Morgan?
That's right.
- The two of you have never met.
- Wait till you meet him.
You're gonna love him.
All I'm sayin' is you're
Kinda bein' a Pill.
You know what they say about
money and evil and everything.
- Shut up. Just shut up.
- I think I hear our boy.
Look, i'm tellin' you, if your
wife doesn't like how late you work,
you just tell her
your girlfriend doesn't mind at all.
- Morgan, you are a piece of work.
- I'm terrible.
Hey! You came.
Sorry about all this.
Look at you.
How are you holdin' up, kiddo?
Great. They let me sleep in the back
office. Couch was comfy.
What did you do?
I just accidentally stole a limo.
You believe this guy?
Hilarious.
So can I go now?
You must be Sam.
It's good to meet you.
- You know me?
- Hey, I'm being rude.
Let me do it properly.
This is Sam Oliver,
bounty hunter extraordinaire.
This is Morgan, my son.
It's nice to meet you.
Dad's told me terrific things about you.
You're his son?
One of the good ones,
like you yourself, Sammy.
Hey, I guess that makes
you two half brothers?
Hey, we're havin' a good old-fashioned
family reunion here, aren't we?
Look at that.
- = 204 =-
" The Favorite "
Sub VO : Galliots  &  ¤Aka¤
Subs-Addicts"
[Sub-way. fr]
- Hey, make a new schedule?
- Yeah, my first one.
I put you on deliveries all week.
Perks of dating the boss.
Thank you. Wanna come?
I got a laser tag gift card.
I can't. I got all this work to do.
I hate that this new job's already
interfering with our lives.
Andi, how often has my job with
the devil messed up our plans?
I was gonna take you away this
weekend with the thousand bucks I won.
You won $1,000?
Yeah, and then the devil took
it to bail out his stupid son.
The devil has a son?
Oh, my god.
That is... That is so scary.
I is it?
It's not that scary.
There are little devils running around,
and that doesn't give you chills?
You know, it's not chilling.
He's pretty normal, pretty normal guy.
Considering.
So, yeah.
I'm gonna go do deliveries.
- Thank you verry mutch.
- What is Ted doin' here?
I don't know. It's like he's still
working. He was fired,
- but he just can't stop.
- It's so sad.
Tragic.
Excuse me. Ma'am.
Hi. I'm sorry.
We've had reports of a pervert harassing
women in the parking lot today.
Real psycho, so be careful.
All right.
- Thank you.
- Have a good day.
Plus I almost let it slip to Andi
that I'm the son of the devil.
Not smart.
Wasn't thinkin'.
God, just hate lying to her.
You're old-fashioned that way.
Here we go. Here we go.
Excuse me. I was wondering if...
Get away. Leave me alone.
- Happy?
- Always.
How are you?
Do many people find
those women attractive?
Yes. I think they are beautiful.
So for you,
beauty entails injecting
silicone into your chest cavity.
OK, ladies, enough fashion talk.
Poblano quesadilla.
- No, thank you. I have a class.
- Cool. If you're done with that,
- can I read that? Thank you.
- Sure.
Hot.
This is delicious.
I am starting to like human food.
How's demon food different?
Usually it's still squirming.
Or screaming.
Check it out.
A sex and intimacy quiz.
We should take it.
We'll score through the roof. All right,
"do you feel emotionally closer
to your partner after sex
or emotionally farther apart?"
Well, closer, obviously.
- Thank you.
- Well, what's your answer?
I don't know. It's hard to say.
Come on. Don't be shy it's just for fun.
It's fine, then.
We'll go to another one.
"How would you rate your overall
satisfaction with your lover in bed?"
Again, I have to give you a 10.
- What your answer? Come on. Be honest.
- I don't wanna do this anymore.
Are you, unhappy with me?
But in that way, the sex way,
are you unsatisfied?
It's not you, Ben, really.
You're amazing. I've just never.
I've never really been that into sex.
It's not that important to me,
so don't even think about it, OK?
Nina, we should talk about this.
Hey, do you think
Morgan would like these?
Why would I care what hat guy likes?
Am I detecting a little
sibling rivalry here?
Don't worry, Sammy.
There's no real competition.
I'm always gonna like him
a little better than I like you.
- That really hurts my feelings.
- Still, you know, I...
Just can't help feeling a little
disappointed about the kid, you know?
See, Morgan is that perfect mix
of relative morality and selfishness.
But there's something missing, you know,
something that makes me think that...
He maybe just doesn't want to help
me rule the netherworld by my side.
Don't care.
You, on the other hand, are a conundrum.
For all your whining and complaing
and lack of fashion sense,
you always get the job done.
You want to do the right thing.
I hate that about you.
But I guess that's the quality
that makes you so effective.
- Are you giving me a compliment?
- No. Mostly I just hate that about you.
You know, it's so damn perplexing.
If I could just take the best parts
of you and the best parts of Morgan
and just squish 'em all together,
i'd have the perfect son.
Is he dead?
Yeah. Killed by your latest soul,
edmund FitzGerald,
big-time shipping magnate
from back in the day.
Real weirdo, if you ask me.
Lot of wild rumors about
the man and how he died.
What rumors?
They say on his deathbed, he ate
his gold so that no one
else could have it.
There was a ring in this
shop that belonged to him.
Now he's back to collect what's his.
He will kill anybody
who gets in his way.
I think that Morgan is
gonna like these a lot.
I'm parked at the far end over there.
You can probably carry
this the rest of the way, right?
What? I'm just saying
you look pretty sturdy. Thick ankles.
I gotta catch my breath.
Hang on. Oh, my god.
Over here. Right here.
- What do you want, Wysocki?
- How much money you make today, Ted?
Phew. 4 hours, about $6.50.
But I think things'll pick up, though.
- Yeah. I have a proposition for you.
- What?
This lovely sturdy lady would like
some help carrying this box to her car.
If you carry it and she gives
you the customary tip of $5.00.
Although classy people leave 10.
I will gladly split it with you.
Shouldn't he get the entire
tip if he's doing all the work?
That is a business decision that you
shouldn't have any part of, ma'am, OK?
But to answer your question,
I am subcontracting the job.
Therefore we should split it.
And it's heavy, so 15,
probably the least you should pay.
I'll do it.
Bert, I thank you.
All right, watch your back.
Knees. It's heavy.
He's got it. All right.
Hey, I need extra shifts.
- What?
- I need extra shifts. I'll do anything.
Clean the toilets. Garbage duty, late
night, early morning, double shifts...
Whatever you got, load me up.
Let's party.
Who are you?
All right, look, look, I've recently
come into some financial issues
that may or may not be
online-poker-related, OK?
But more importantly,
I know that you're short-handed.
The socket wrench is here to fix
all your problems, boss lady.
- I'm afraid.
- Me, too.
Because I'm gonna go sickhouse
on this job, all right?
The work will be done.
It'll be better than done.
The work will be good.
You seem quiet tonight.
I've just had some stuff on my mind,
just been thinkin'
Well, stop it.
OK. Sure.
What's wrong?
I don't wanna talk to a certain
person over there.
Who was that?
That was brad, a demon that I used
to date. We just had a short thing.
It was a totally
superficial relationship,
nothing like what you and I have,
entirely physical. That's all.
- Physical?
- Yeah. That's it.
As in sex?
No. Well...
What? I don't.
Sorta.
'cause I thought you
weren't that into sex,
- that it wasn't that important to you.
- It's not. I just mean that.
I just mean that brad
was really shallow.
Spit that out.
We are talking about this.
- Will you get out of here?
- Morgan got himself arrested again.
I don't know how I'm gonna
get through to that kid.
Yeah, I don't have any more money, so
you can forget about me bailing him out.
I don't need your money, Sam.
I just wish some of your good
qualities would rub off on Morgan.
OK, can I use the bathroom now?
Special delivery.
Now, the next item FitzGerald
wants to Reacquire
is an old portrait of himself.
It's in the Asher gallery downtown.
The address is on the back of this.
Now, I suggest that you
grab that portrait tonight.
If it stays there too long,
FitzGerald will show up and reclaim it,
and more people will die.
Since when did you care
if people get killed?
I don't. Good call.
In truth, I have a small favor to ask.
And by favor, I mean
you don't have a choice.
So, training the son of the devil.
That was never in the job description,
Samuel. Can't believe you agreed to it.
The devil didn't exactly
make it optional, man.
The son of the devil?
Does he look like you?
- Wait until you meet him.
- You'll hate him. Super tool.
He's pretty.
God, he looked dead
even when he was alive.
Evenin', Bitches.
Hey, Morgan. This is Sock, Ben.
Guys, Morgan, son of the devil.
Hey. It's good to meet you guys.
You help out your buddy even though
you don't have to. You're good friends.
Yeah. We are good friends, so...
Thank you.
Devil get you that car?
No. Would you believe an ex-girlfriend?
I'm not one to kiss and tell, but did
she have a title, and was it princess?
Well, some people
probably like that car. I...
Also do.
All right, um, we need to get our hands
on that painting before the soul does.
There's a burglar alarm sticker
on the window, so obviously there's...
- A burglar alarm.
- Good one, Sam.
OK, great.
Which one of you guys
is surveillance guy?
The tech guy?
Fighting guy?
So what you're saying is you have,
you have no plan, no real skills.
Yes. I would say yes to that.
- Good eye. Good eye.
- We still get the job done.
No, you do. You do. I can't argue
with results. Hold one sec.
Right? You see?
See what I'm talkin' about? He's a Dick.
Yeah. Think he'd let us drive that?
I bet if we asked him, he'd say yes.
- You guys are Jerks.
- You know, I bet you're right. Yeah.
You see the suit he's wearin'? It's...
- Looks great on him.
- You don't buy that thing off the rack.
What the hell are you doing?!
So, in my experience you guys got, like,
3 or 4 minutes before the cops get here.
You better grab your painting.
I'm gonna go to a party.
If it's ragin', i'll text you.
Sam, the painting! Come on!
Sam, come on!
So you're gonna unpack all these
sprinklers, all 500 of them?
Restock the paint
and ship out all the damages?
You know it.
Sock, I'm having a really hard time
believing you're gonna do any of this.
Well, that is because you've never
seen me in hustle mode, Andi.
It is insan-i-tay.
Thing about hustle mode, though,
is I need to be alone.
I get sweaty I take off my shirt.
I'm a little bit shy
so you go for now, come back later,
and be amazed, all right?
All right.
So to continue, ground rules. You do not
work for the bench anymore, OK?
You work for me.
- I'm the judge, jury. Boss man!
- Executioner.
All right? I get the shifts.
You do the actual work.
And if Andi comes along, what do you do?
- Run.
- Run. Attaboy.
Got it.
You smell that?
That is a work bench scent.
Industrial rubber.
Turpentine.
Lawn Fertilizer.
It is wonderful, and it's home.
Thank you for this. You don't know how
much this means to me.
I will do anything you say.
Just let me be here, in the bench.
- I like your attitude. A lot, OK?
- Thank you.
Just don't do anything to mess up and
make me have to can your ass?
All right, I'm gonna take a nap.
You wake me up in 4 hours.
4.
4 hours.
Don't tell me the other
2 clowns got killed.
No. No, they're fine.
I'm not here on official business today.
I have a matter of personal
nature to discuss with you.
I need your help.
Speak.
OK. So, I'm sort of in a relationship...
with a demon.
Are you, now?
Never would have pegged
you for a horn hag.
Well, that...
She's a great girl.
Everything's going awesome,
except for one thing.
Spit it out, kid.
I'm on break in 5.
Right. OK. My...
My question is...
Can humans satisfy demons,
or can only demons do that?
Yes, humans and demons can get it on,
all the time in fact.
I see.
Are you trying to tell me
you're having a little trouble
in the bedroom department?
No. No, actually. No.
I'm doing a little research...
look, if you wanna know how to please
a demon, I can help you.
Seriously?
- 'cause that would be great.
- Of course.
Drop by my place tonight.
I'll give you a little
one-on-one tutorial, as they say. And,
I like to make learning fun,
so bring along
plenty of plastic garbage bags.
I think. I think no.
Thank you, no, but.
That sounds like somethin'
i'm a little uncomfortable with,
but thank you very much
for the kind offer.
- Fine. Figure it out for yourself then.
- No, Gladys, please.
Is there any advice you can give
me that doesn't require actual...
Touching?
Well, I guess she finds
you physically repulsive.
Have a nice day.
This guy gives me the creeps.
How much longer do
we have to hang on to this?
We gotta figure out a way to lure
FitzGerald out into the open.
I say we advertise this painting
is for sale, he shows up to claim it,
and then we trap him.
- Maybe Morgan has some ideas.
- Morgan? Why would we ask Morgan?
I don't know. Dude seems to
know how to get things done.
All he did was almost get us arrested.
Why do you love him so much?
I don't know.
He's just got this aura, you know?
He's the kind of guy that walks into a
room, and people's eyes just go to him.
- He's got "it."
- He does not have "it."
Some people do.
It's like that undefinable presence,
like Clooney, Pitt.
- Rickles.
- Yeah. You know, I used to have "it,"
like 4, 5 years ago.
I remember that.
That was a really good summer for you.
I was really into kale at that time.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Just keep in mind he's the son
of the devil. You can't trust him.
- You're the son of the devil.
- Do you trust me?
- Not really.
- Wanna hand me that dish?
What the hell, Sock?!
I'm gonna kill you!
Look! Look! Look!
- The soul, he's here.
- What? Where?
Get it off!
- Don't let 'em in your ear!
- On my back!
The back! The back!
Get the back!
- Can't vessel'em!
- Bathroom! Run!
- It's on me. Is it on me?
- Shut up.
What are you all doing in the tub?
We were playin' a game of hide-and-seek.
You were it, and you found us. Good job.
Really?
The painting. It's gone.
He took it back.
So sick.
I had the creeps all last night.
It sounds awful.
No idee and the get soul.
And no that painting was our only lead.
- What's he doing with all his stuff?
- What do you mean?
He must have hundreds of things.
I mean, thousands maybe.
He's gotta have someplace
to put it, right?
Hey, that's a really good idea.
Someplace big, like a warehouse.
You said he was in shipping, right?
Who is that?
I can see you.
Que?
I know it's you, Ted.
OK, listen, you can't be here.
You got fired.
I know I did, Judas.
- OK, why am I Judas?
- I don't know. Why are you?
I didn't fire you, Ted.
You got yourself fired.
Well, look at you, Miss Fancy pants,
all drunk with power.
You have to leave.
Sorry. Talk to the boss.
- That's me.
- Nope. My boss.
No need to yell.
You cannot subcontract your job to Ted.
Lookit, I promised you
the work would be done,
and it is being done
in a top-notch fashion.
- What's the problem?
- The problem is the company fired him!
I know that.
That's why he agreed to work for 40%,
and I get 60 finder's fee.
Everybody's happy.
Do I look happy?
All right, listen to me.
I will cut you in, OK,
but it needs to come out of Ted's end.
- Get rid of him.
- Wait. Wait. No. No, Andi. Brother.
OK, listen,
are you honestly gonna fire Ted again?
He's already been fired, Sock.
It should have stuck the first time.
OK, do you know
that he comes here all the time?
Yeah, just to be in the bench presence.
He loves this stupid place. It's like
his whole life, his whole identity.
And to take that away,
that would just be cruel.
Well, I didn't do anything wrong.
Plus, he's got other things in his life.
No, Andi.
Think about it.
This is all he's ever known.
This is the only job he's ever had.
He eats here. He sleeps here.
He brings imaginary girlfriends here.
If you force him to leave again,
you will destroy him.
Hey, we think we found where
the soul's hiding his stuff.
There's an old shipyard FitzGerald used
to own. It's been condemned for years.
I'm on it. My shift's covered.
All right, so which one is FitzGerald's?
I guess we'll have
to search 'em one by one.
- What?
- Hey, did you call Morgan?
How did you find us?
Dad wanted me to meet you here,
said you could use my expertise.
I guess FitzGerald's keepin'
his loot in this old container.
I don't believe this.
He doesn't help me with anything.
You just gotta learn
to work the old man.
He's actually a little
bit of a pushover.
I can't believe he was able
to get his hands on all this.
Right.
The guy's got impeccable taste.
I'll give him that.
A biedermeier.
- Limoges.
- Limoges. Good stuff.
Venetian crystal.
This stuff is worth a fortune.
Look at this.
FitzGerald made a list of
everything he ever owned.
Looks like he got it all.
Except for mary ann.
Who's mary ann?
Maybe this is her.
You think she's still alive?
We should find her
before FitzGerald does.
Let's go.
This is all Sock's fault.
I mean, he put me in this position.
Now if I fire Ted,
he'll probably die or something.
Yeah, but ask yourself
is that a bad thing?
- I don't know what to do.
- What the hell is Morgan doing here?
He's here?
That's not what
I thought he'd look like.
Hey, he's a Jerk.
Try not to kill him.
Hey, hey.
You ready to get crackin' on that soul?
Yeah, we're tryin' to track down
his wife, so until we do that,
- we're pretty much stuck.
- Yeah, mary ann. I got her address.
Dad hooked me up.
- Hi. Morgan.
- Hi. I'm Andi.
You're Sam's girlfriend.
OK. It's good to meet you.
How are you?
Heard a lot of good things about you.
- Thanks.
- You're a lucky lady.
He's one in a million.
He's just brave, smart.
- He's just an all-around great guy.
- Thanks. Yeah, I agree.
OK. You ready to get goin'?
Got a good feelin' about this.
- Don't say it.
- I'm sorry.
He's not that bad.
I told you not to say it.
Babe, i'm right here.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I just heard humans can
please demons in bed.
Ben, I told you this wasn't a problem.
Yes, it is!
Sex is an essential component
in a strong relationship.
It is the cornerstone of...
Something. I don't know.
I read it in some female books.
- What exactly are female books?
- Look, I know what it is, all right?
You can't be yourself sexually.
You change into human form, and tr...
And pretend to be something you're not.
And I want you to be happy.
So I...
I'm gonna have sex with
you in your natural body.
Now, I would simply ask
that you be careful that
your wings don't poke me in the eye.
Also, please be aware my skin is
very sensitive. It chafes easily.
Also, please don't talk
while we're doing it.
I mean, your demon voice
is a little mannish, OK?
Now, I'm gonna have a cocktail first.
I hope you don't mind.
Do you have a glass?
So you want this?
I can drink from the bottle.
I don't know what I can tell
you about my late husband.
But if you're looking to get your hands
on his estate,
you can forget about it.
He made sure there was nothing left.
Actually
we're here to warn you, and,
I know this is gonna sound crazy.
It's just that...
Edmund FitzGerald might be back from the
dead and might be trying to kidnap you.
I would have been
a little more delicate about it,
but yes. It's true.
He had this list of everything
he ever owned, everything he loved,
and you're the last thing on the list.
Well, now I know you're
a couple of crackpots.
Edmund loved only things,
possessions.
Nothing else mattered.
No, he did.
Mary ann was on his list.
That's not me.
That was his boat, themary ann.
She sank to the bottom of
the pacific 50 years ago.
But if edmund's ghost
is looking for that,
well, he'll never find it.
Serves him right, the son of a bitch.
Well, I feel compelled to point
out that you're attacking the dead.
And to say there's nothing really
wrong with having an appreciation
- of the finer things, which clearly
- Actually, we were just leaving.
You're wearing his ring.
What?!
You're gonna get us killed. FitzGerald
is gonna come looking for that.
He's not even gonna know it's missing.
We have to take it back right now.
No. I like it.
You are such a Dick.
Now I understand why the devil
is disappointed in you. You're a moron.
He said that?
He said he was disappointed?
You don't care about
anybody but yourself.
You do whatever you want, and
it doesn't even matter who gets hurt.
Why would I care,
when the world's full of guys like you,
responsible and ethical?
I don't feel that.
Never felt it.
In fact,
I've never felt anything for anybody.
It's very liberating.
Do you really think i'm gonna kill
myself for the family business?
Not a chance.
But you, you spill your blood,
you work hard, and you do
a good job so that when the time comes,
I can stand on your shoulders
or dead body, if necessary,
in order to get to the top.
You're evil.
I'm the son of the devil.
I mean, what'd you expect?
I'm done with this. I'm done with you.
After today, no more training.
Well, I think dear old dad has some
serious quality time planned for us,
so I don't think you're gonna
be done with me anytime soon.
You hear that?
My lucky day.
Wait!
- What was that?
- They're inside the vents.
- Run.
- What?
Run!
Sam, back here!
Wait! I am not the one
you're looking for. I swear.
I'm not the one you're looking for!
I'm not the one you want!
I swear! I'm not the one you want!
Sam, back here!
Just give him the ring.
That's what he wants.
It's stuck!
The pool!
Jump in the pool!
- It worked.
- Yeah, I know.
- Got it.
- What are you doing?!
Why did you do that?
Wait. Wait.
I'll give it back to you.
It's yours.
You want me to put it in your mouth?
Please don't bite me.
Happy?
Good.
We get to keep those, right?
I can't keep running away from you.
Or shoveling food into my mouth,
for that matter,
so I think I'm ready to
tell you the truth now.
Truth would be nice.
So you know I used to be an Angel.
Yeah, I know demons were Angels.
But what I didn't tell you is...
that you're not my first human.
I see.
Before the fall, some Angels
came to earth and married humans.
There were even children born.
They were called nephilim.
I was one of those Angels.
I didn't have a kid or anything,
but I did fall in love.
When god found out, he...
banished us from paradise
and smote those we loved.
So the guy you loved died.
So if you're feeling like
I'm holding back from you, you're right.
I have been holding back
in a lot of ways,
sexually and emotionally,
because if I ever lost you
the way I lost him, Ben.
I can't tell you what's gonna
happen in the future,
but I can tell you
that I'm crazy about you.
And I'm not going anywhere.
Is that enough for now?
I think it is.
And...
I think I'm ready to be with
you completely,
heart and body.
And when you say, "body,"
you mean, this one, right,
without the tail and horns?
I'm just checking.
Just checking.
I made my decision.
Ted, only official employees
can work here at the bench,
so I cannot allow you
to continue taking Sock's shifts.
Didn't think you had it in you.
So cold.
That's why I called home office,
and they're letting me hire you
back on a 6-month trial basis.
- You are a benevolent, gifted leader.
- On one condition.
- You'll be hired back as a trainee.
- Trainee?
I was working in this stor
when you were still experimenting
with alternative
lifestyles at summer camp.
Take it or leave it, Ted.
Fine.
One more thing.
Our new trainee is gonna need a trainer.
I don't think so. No.
I do. And if you wanna continue
working here, you'll agree.
Besides,
I think you'll make a fantastic trainer.
Conscientious, dedicated.
You guys are gonna be a team,
joined at the hip for 6 months.
Touche, Andi.
Touche.
Who's the pretty boy?
Hi. Morgan.
It's nice to meet you.
He's sort of the son of your boss.
So's Genghis Khan.
You expect me to be
impressed by a gap ad?
These also came, a bunch of gold coins.
- I'm not sure what to do with them.
- Not a vessel, not my problem.
I can't believe you.
And you say I'm selfish.
I did all the work, and I saved your
life. We're not splitting this 50/50.
We never found if I wouldn't
have lured him to us with the ring.
So that was on purpose?
That was all a trap?
- That wasn't you being an idiot?
- You're a Jackass. You know that?
Listen to this.
Fighting like 2 brothers.
I'm gettin' all misty.
Look at you?
The hero.
You captured your first soul.
I don't know.
I'm just tryin' to make you proud.
You can learn a thing
or two from this guy, I think.
Unbelievable.
Hey, let me see those gold coins, Sammy.
Now, Morgan,
Sam has made quite the investment in you
by bailing you out of jail.
But at your well-deserved R&R
at my villa in the Caymans,
I want you to start thinking
about how you're gonna repay him.
What?! Why does he get the gold?
Well, you don't want that. That's
blood money. People died for that.
You don't mind a little blood
on your hands, do you, Morgan?
No, I prefere blood on my hands, dad.
Then it's settled.
Hey, that's not a very happy Sammy face.
No, you know, he did nothing to capture
that soul. I saved his life.
Don't worry about it. I'm just tryin'
to give the kid a little confidence.
That's all. Don't wanna demoralize
him his first time out.
- You demoralize me all the time.
- Well, you can take it.
- Whatever.
- No, Sammy, look.
I don't have to reward you
with trinkets and paltry pieces
of gold that some soul has vomited up.
You're much bigger than that.
You are.
In fact, I'm beginning
to reassess this whole situation.
You know, maybe Morgan isn't
the one I should be priming.
Maybe the perfect son is you.
No. No, I'm not. Seriously.
Put it out of your head.
I don't know.
It's becoming clearer and clearer to me
that you are the one
who will be sitting at my right hand.
Morgan can have that job.
I don't want it.
But don't you see?
That's what makes you so perfect.
I am so conflicted now.
I don't know who to root for.
You could root for Morgan.
Do you mind making one last delivery?
It's a big freezer.
Sure.
OK, good,
because it's goin' to your mom's place.
What does she need a giant freezer for?
I don't want you to be afraid.
Dad!
Team Subs-Addicts"