Considering the severity
of the accident,
I'm very happy with your recovery.
You're a fast healer, young lady.
When can I go home?
Very soon. I have a few questions first.
- Have you experienced any dizziness?
- No.
- Headache?
- Nope.
Hallucinations?
- What do you mean by hallucinations?
- Anything out of the ordinary.
I've had patients with head
trauma see all sorts of odd things.
Space aliens,
pink elephants, you name it.
You know, the night of the accident,
I did see some things
that seemed impossible.
- But you're saying that that's normal?
- I'm saying it's hardly unusual.
And based on your vitals,
it's nothing to worry about.
I suggest you put it out of your mind.
Here. These should help.
Okay. Thanks.
Nobody likes a litter bug.
- Did she buy it?
- Hell yeah.
I've been mopping up after doctors
for 20 years. I got the lingo down.
Did you give her the bottle of tic tacs?
- Of course.
- I hope she likes peppermint.
You coulda got her any flavor
you wanted to in the world
- and you got her peppermint? Really?
- Yeah, why?
Because, Ben, everybody knows
that peppermint is for jerks.
Right?
I'm... gonna go clean
the men's room now.
Season 1, Episode 14 - Rebellion
For www.forom.com
Thank you very much.
Have a good day. Later.
Hey, ladies,
got ourselves another delivery.
What do we got?
I give you...
"Beers of the world!"
- They're beautiful.
- Guys, come on.
Free wine,
free chocolate, free designer soap...
This stuff doesn't belong to us.
Benji, if the moron
who lived here before us
was too lazy to leave a forwarding
address, then he deserves to get got.
Besides, who ate all the free melons?
I have no blood sugar,
which is an emergency.
- Who wants beer real?
- I'm in.
- Guinness and lucky charms for me.
- You, sir, have a very refined palate.
I'm bored.
Are you bored, Sammy?
- No.
- You know what I could go for?
A banana split.
With hot fudge. Yeah.
What do you say?
No, thank you.
What, you don't like banan splits?
What are you, some kind of a commie?
C'mon. My treat.
What part of "no" don't you understand?
Forget the ice cream.
Do you have a soul for me or not?
Boy.
I guess I better get right to it, huh?
All right. It's your standard case.
The guy was a lawyer, of course...
We have a lot of those in hell.
Cubby Bryce.
Died a couple of months ago
your typical ambulance chaser
who got his kicks bilking his clients
of all their hard-earned savings.
He's back once again,
bleeding people dry.
Literally.
Gross.
- Yeah.
- Where can I find him?
Actually, you're sitting on him.
Anything else?
Nice.
Hey, you're back!
- Hi.
Hi. Um...
Sorry... OK...
- Hi.
Well, that wasn't awkward at all.
- Hey.
- I'll be back to get you at 5.
- OK. Great. Thank you.
You look great!
Have you ever been hit
in the head with a shovel?
No, no. I can't say I have.
OK. Well, that's how my head
felt after the crash. And you know what?
Somehow, through that pain,
I found clarity.
Which isn't really
coming across right now.
Life is short.
There is no time to waste.
- That's all you and I have been doing.
- Wasting time?
We kissed the night of the crash, right?
I didn't hallucinate that.
No, that definitely happened.
And it was pretty amazing, right?
- Yes. That it was.
- OK, then.
We're going on a date.
- What?
- Yeah, a real date.
No more wasting time.
Saturday work for you?
- Yeah.
- Good. I thought it might.
Oh, my gosh.
Would you look at what we have here.
Don't worry, Josie.
I get your message loud and clear.
What message, jackass?
You know, you coming to my work.
Wearing the scarf that
I gave you last Christmas.
This?
It was the first thing I
found at the bottom of my closet.
You know, it's really nice to see
that even though I've clearly moved on,
that my "mark" is still all over you.
Like dog pee on a pretty,
pretty, little tree.
Excuse me.
- Yes. Hi.
- Hey, Ted.
There, don't you look sexy.
I hurt my back at work and
I'd like to discuss my legal options.
Give me a call back when you get this.
Thanks. Bye.
I just left a voicemail for Cubby Bryce.
Is that the escaped soul?
Yep. He's an ambulance chasing lawyer.
I figure we set a meeting,
and when he shows up we ambush him,
send him back to hell.
Cubby Bryce.
Why does that sound familiar?
He's got a bunch of
billboards around town.
What kinda name is Cubby?
Who's named Cubby?
- Your name is "Sock."
- Your name is Sock.
- Did you mousse?
- Don't touch my hair.
You did!
Boy's got a date planned...
He's trying to get all seximified.
Mission accomplished.
Sock and I are excited.
We've been waiting on the sidelines
for you to hook up with Andi
since high school.
All the romantic tension
between you two reminds me
of my favorite movie of all time...
"Meat Hammer 5."
In the beginning of the movie, there's
this big, long, talky-talky scene.
Goes on for 4 minutes.
But then,
the talking ends, hammering begins.
You got it, right? That's my point.
So now, the talky-talky
between you and Andi is done.
- Let the hammering...
- No, no, Sock, I get it. I get it.
Good. Loud and clear.
Let's have a toast for our boy's date.
What do you say?
Hey, guys.
Sam, we need to talk to you in private.
Our apartment.
May I offer you a
sangria before we begin?
No, I'm OK.
- What's with all the mystery?
- Wait until the door is closed.
- Why?
- The Devil can't penetrate a circle...
He can only enter through corners.
Inside a circle,
he can't see or hear us.
This is so exciting.
Tell him.
- Tell him, tell him, tell him.
- I want you to tell him.
All right.
Steve told me about your
little conversation the other day,
and he feels that we can trust you
with our greatest secret, and I agree.
But I have to caution you...
We're part of an underground
alliance of demons
- planning to overthrow the Devil!
- What?
I know, I know, it sounds so crazy!
What are you talking about?
How can you overthrow the Devil?
We used to be angels, Sam.
We knew the face of God.
But then we followed Lucifer
in a revolt against the Lord
and we were cast out
of Heaven for eternity.
Recently we've begun to
feel that the Devil's leadership
is taking us in the wrong direction.
We're tired of living lives of evil.
We're going to defeat him,
and we believe that you can help us.
Me?
- How?
- Well,
for some reason, you're special.
The Devil talks to you.
You're uniquely positioned
to be our inside man.
I'm not going up against the Devil.
That is insane.
You won't be alone, Sam.
And think of it this way...
With the Devil out of the picture,
he can't collect your soul.
His claim on you will be no invoid.
- Really?
- Think about it...
You could have a normal life again.
No more risking your neck chasing souls.
No more putting the people
you care about, and danger.
I guess...
I can't say no.
Welcome to the revolution, Sam.
So Steve and Tony have a
plan to knock heads with the Devil?
That's what you told me.
I can't really be in the
specifics right now, but it's big.
Sam, come on. Just give me
one little detail, one little hint.
All I can say is that if this works,
I'll be free.
I can finally get out from under...
my current cell phone plan
and sign with your provider. Thank you.
How long have you been sitting there?
Do you think I'm an idiot, Sam?
- No, I...
- Because I know what's going on.
OK, listen, I...
- It wasn't my...
- I ask you
to go get some ice cream and you refuse.
In a rather rude manner, I might add.
So I'm thinking, and I realise,
who says no to ice cream?
Nobody, that's who.
So you're mad about ice cream.
I treat you with respect, and
you treat me like little bits of dirt.
What's up with that?
- You are so weird.
- All right.
I'm done.
The little hairs. The little hairs.
OK... Do you trust me?
Yeah. I do. OK. Yeah.
Stings.
Good day to you, my fellow comrades.
I'm sorry,
aren't you going to yell at us?
What? Yell at my peeps?
I would sooner cut off
my arm and yell at that.
- What do you want, Ted?
- Josie's phone number.
I think we made quite
the connection the other day
when she lovingly draped
this scarf over my body.
OK, listen, Ted.
You have my blessing, all right?
- Really?
- 100%, give me your hand.
I want you to go forth
and hit that thing.
- Thank you, Bert.
- Please don't press so hard.
- I have sensitive palms.
- There you go. OK.
Right.
Are you crazy?
Josie will eat him alive.
I know! I know! God.
What I wouldn't give to be on the phone
when Josie shoots down Ted man walking.
- What's up?
- Get in.
It's time for you
to meet the underground.
- This is your secret headquarters?
- Not till we get inside.
See, we can't afford to take chances.
OK, let's move on to new business.
Maude, give us your insurrection report.
Last week, I planted 6 dozen flowers
in a public park on Bower.
Begonias.
And I let a homeless
person shower in my house.
Excellent.
- Do good, people.
- Do good.
Now, who else wants
to talk about their week?
I've got something.
My name is Bob and I'm a demon.
Hi, Bob!
I had a rough week. Started off great.
I rode around on Monday
collecting recyclables.
Then I dropped coins
into expired meters.
Then, I tried to eat a child.
I knew right away it was wrong,
so I untied the kid
and called my sponsor Randy.
We had a pretty tough talk.
- Thanks, man. I owe you my life.
- Thank you, man.
Everybody,
this is Sam, the one I told you about.
- Hi, Sam!
- Hi.
Sam, any thoughts on
what you've heard so far?
I... don't think so, no.
Sam, what's wrong?
Look, I guess I'm a little confused
on how feeding the parking meters
is supposed to take down the Devil.
Kindness is our greatest weapon, Sam.
The Devil brings evil into the world.
We undermine him with goodness
and charity.
When we make the world a better place.
We'll have lucifer on
his knees begging for mercy!
So you're all just gonna be... nice.
Nice. Yes. We can't lose!
How long do you think
this is even gonna take?
300, 400 years, tops.
OK, see, I don't have 400 years!
I'll be dead and in hell!
From a bunch of rebel demons, I
was expecting something more aggressive.
- We do fun runs.
- I gotta go.
I got it.
Sam. Sam. Sam.
Wait.
Look, I'll be honest, I...
Hang on.
This is hard to say. I love Steve,
but his peaceful resistance
plan is not very...
efficient.
To someone with a
mortal lifespan like you,
a century must seem like forever.
You guys die so quickly.
You're like goldfish.
What we need to do
is we ram a nuke down
the Devil's throat, right now.
That should be the plan.
Good luck with that, Tony.
Sam.
You need a ride home?
I'm good.
Hello?
Cubby Bryce, attorney-at-law.
I caught your message
about the workman's comp case.
I pulled my back out stocking
shelves at the work bench
and I'm thinking of suing.
Well, it sounds like you've
got the makings for a fantastic case.
I'm happy to come to you.
When is a good time?
You could swing by the
bench tonight after work...
- Have some privacy.
- It sounds perfect.
Perfect.
So your average on a back injury suit
can range anywhere from a couple
of grand all the way up to 6 figures.
7 figures if you're willing
to bend the truth a little.
7 figures? Are you serious?
Are you willing to wear
a cast or a neck brace?
Dude, I would be willing
to put on your underwear
with you still in 'em for 7 figures.
Tell me more.
- Sock.
- What?
No more questions.
Look here.
- I got lots of time.
- No, you don't.
Easy! Easy! Easy!
I surrender.
Just let me grab my stuff
before you send me back.
Keep it in your pants, Bryce.
I need a beer.
- I'll second that.
- Drinks are on Cubby, boys.
Snagged his wallet.
So, any insider tips what
I should be expecting this weekend?
I don't know.
I'm pretty sure you asked me out.
Shouldn't you be making the plans?
OK. All right. Fair enough.
- I'll think of something incredible.
- Anything.
As long as it involves fireworks,
and a hot air balloon,
maybe a couple limousines.
Oh, OK, OK.
- That was...
- Yeah.
How about I just come over?
Let's... let's do that.
- OK. I'm gonna...
- Yeah. I'll see you.
- Bert Wysocki.
- Hola Ted.
I want to thank you
for helping me with Josie.
- We had a date last night.
- What? You had a...
You asked her out and
she actually said yes?
Let me just say that the
date was quite satisfactory.
What do you mean "satisfactory"?
What are you talking...
- Did you two touch parts?
- Not yet, no. But...
she did call me over to her place
tonight to help her hook up her DVR.
And I think we all know what that means.
That means she
wants you to hook up her DVR.
No, hooking up any sort of appliance
is classic gay porn terminology
for getting it on...
And I'm pretty sure that that
translates over to the hetero arena.
- Why are you laughing?
- Ted, I'm sorry. Listen to me.
I am so sorry, really I am,
that Josie got your hopes up like this,
but, there is no way that
she'll ever be your girlfriend, OK?
- She's out of your league.
- I know that.
You know that?
But she'll date me for the
same reasons that she dated you.
The girls like to date down.
- Excuse me?
- It's clearly her thing. Her psyche.
Going out with guys,
that she's way too good for
makes her feel safe and superior.
It's a bonanza for guys like us,
because we're dating up.
We're proving our luck,
it's a win-win situation all around.
You know what, Ted?
Shut up. You're wrong.
You know why? Because there's no way
that Josie would ever think
that she was better than me, OK?
So, thanks.
Sam,
- we have something for you.
- You are gonna love us.
Love. Us.
Sam, you are about to see that when
demons set their minds on something,
they get the job done.
Behold... our gift to you!
We've prepared a human sacrifice!
All for you, Sam.
- What are you doing?
- How is this for me?
Well, this gets you out
of your contract with the Devil.
How?
Well, bob here used
to work at legal in hell.
He knows how to work the system.
What you do is fill out
the standard 357j transfer waiver,
but attach the intangible
properties rider.
It's irregular, but permissible.
This guy's soul takes your
place in hell and it's iron clad.
The Devil can't reverse it.
Here, just jam this through his heart,
easy as pie.
Guys, no.
I'm not sending an innocent
person to hell in my place.
Sam, he's hardly innocent.
He's a drug dealer.
He tried to sell me weed in the park.
It's a gatewy drug.
What is wrong with you guys?
Sacrificing a person is evil!
He's right.
All this time we've been
trying to combat our demon natures,
and then we go and
do something like this.
We should be ashamed of ourselves,
you guys.
Would you return this man in the park?
Upsy-daisy. Come on, buddy.
Please forgive us.
Well, I guess that's it for this week.
Hey, thanks to Stewart
for securing this theater space.
Don't miss his turn as puck,
because he is fabulous.
Wait! We shouldn't feel ashamed.
We were not built to be pacifists!
We are demons!
We need to play to our strengths.
We're demons!
We don't need to kill
the Devil with kindness.
We need to kill him. Period!
- He's right!
- Yeah!
Now, now, we have the tool
we need to destroy him now!
Sam is the Devil's friend!
Uh, to be clear,
I'm not friends with him.
He's just kinda clingy.
Then make him your friend.
Use his weakness to your advantage.
- How?
- We need you to summon the Devil.
Get his cell number.
We can use that to bring him here.
Get that number and
we'll handle the rest.
Well, even if you can summon the Devil,
are you sure you're
gonna be able to hurt him?
You bring the Devil,
I'll bring the pain.
Josie! Josie, open the door.
It is so clear to me now, lady.
Everything is so clear.
I know what was wrong in our
relationship, do you want to hear it?
You think that you're better than me!
- Don't deny it. Don't even try.
- Are you crazy?
No, no. Not anymore, lady.
Not anymore, OK?
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it.
On some small level, I knew it.
The whole time we were going out,
you looked down on me.
You know why?
You date down!
What does that even mean?
- Where are you getting this?
- From Ted!
Ted? Ted is an idiot!
He doesn't even realize
he's wearing a woman's scarf.
Well, then why did
you go on a date with him?
- I work 80-hour weeks.
- So what?
I don't date where I work.
If a guy takes the
trouble to ask me out,
I'm inclined to give him a shot at bat.
Well, that makes sense!
So you believe that I went out with you
just because I think
you're some sort of loser?
For the record,
I dated you because you're sweet,
you don't care what other people think,
and you make me laugh.
I...
am all those things.
So, um...
Wanna make out?
- Hey, Tedster.
- Hi.
- What's that there?
- It's wine.
Thanks for the wine.
That was nice of you. Don't actually
need the tool box, though,
because I already
"hooked up Josie's DVR."
Twice.
You play a dirty game,
my friend, but you play it well.
I'll see you back at work.
Good night.
- Plastic, please.
- Hey. What's going on?
Oh, I just came in to congratulate
you on a job well done.
And I wanted to get
these packs of triple eggs.
OK.
Thank you. You have a nice day.
Wait. Wait. Hold on.
Listen, I don't want
it to be like this, OK?
I'm sorry I've been rude.
Look, if...
I'm gonna be off here in 10 minutes.
You wann go grab an icecream?
Yes, Sam.
I would like that.
So, a little birdie told
me somebody's got a date with Andi.
You know my rule.
Date anybody you want. Just
don't tell them about our little secret.
- Oh, boy.
- Thank you.
- Look at it.
- Go on... try it.
- Aren't you gonna eat yours?
- Can't.
I'm just gonna watch you eat yours, OK?
What do you mean you can't eat it?
A little'departing
gift'from old so-and-so.
He knew how much
I loved ice cream. Jerk.
Go on, go on, take and bite.
Oh, boy. So...
Andi. Huh? The love of your life.
I thought you didn't believe in love.
I don't believe that humans
can feel through pure love but
I know that it exists.
I've experienced it myself.
I'm not human, remember.
You actually loved somebody? Who?
You mean God?
Didn't you try to
overthrow him or something?
Let's just say we had a little fight.
I may have been a tad impetuous.
But you loved him.
With everything that I was, I loved him.
And he loved all of us, too.
I'm sorry.
Well.
I haven't talked about
the fall since it happened.
- Why not?
- There's nobody who would listen.
No, it's just me.
All by myself.
Except till now. I've got you.
- So you see us as friends?
- I do.
I don't.
For one, you own my soul.
Oh, whatever.
I don't even think about that, Sam.
I can't even get in touch with you.
If I want to talk,
I have to just wait around
for you to zap me wherever
you want me to be. It's not fair.
No, you're right. You're right.
You're 100% correct.
What is this?
That is my private...
and I do mean private cell phone number.
- What area code is this?
- Phoenix.
Now, listen.
I don't give this out,
so you keep it in a safe place,
and you only use it if you
absolutely have to. I'm a busy man.
I'm glad we talked about this.
Do me a favor...
have an other bite.
You've done a good thing, Sam.
For the entire world.
What now?
I call a convocation of demons.
We summon Lucifer...
and we use this.
The sword of the Archangel Michael.
It splits the rock of Colossae.
Rescued the body of Moses
from the Devil's dragons,
and vanquished Lucifer
himself int the first heveanly war.
So... you're gonna stab him?
To destroy the Devil we must
first cut out his forked tongue,
a tongue that has spouted
lies since the beginning of time,
then we chop off his hands
that have twisted innocent
souls into sinners.
And then we cut out his heart,
a heart that knows only hate.
Only then can the Devil truly die.
Is he gonna hurt?
His pain will be excruciating.
Let me see that.
The number of the beast.
You should be very
proud of yourself, Sam.
Hey, you excited about your big date?
That's it, "yeah"?
The girl of your dreams is coming over,
you're moping around.
- What is wrong with you?
- It has nothing to do with the date.
What?
All right, listen,
- inside the circle.
- Dude! No, whoa!
The Devil won't be able to hear us.
Come on, inside.
- Dude, that stuff is expensive.
- Just get in.
All right.
I found a way to take down the Devil.
- Really?
- That's great.
So what are you crying about?
I feel bad about double-crossing him.
- What the hell?
- He's the Devil.
Sam, he's the Devil, OK?
All he's ever tried to do is screw you.
And with the Devil
out of the picture Sam,
- you get your soul back, your soul.
- So buck up.
Are you bucked up?
I think so, yeah.
I'm bucked up.
Please, stop hitting me, OK?
I'll get it.
It's her.
Hi. Hi.
I'm sorry,
that one was because I'm jealous.
Have a good date, OK?
You two kids have fun.
- Enjoy it.
- Bye, see you later.
Can I offer you a beer of the world?
- I'm not really thirsty right now.
- No?
We have plenty of food.
If you feel like, uh,
a papaya or a steak.
- This is really cute.
- What, what, what?
Because you're trying to slow it down,
but we're on an actual date.
I guess I just...
I want this to be a date we remember.
Sam,
it could be the two of us
in an empty room, and I'd remember.
I can't think of anything more
perfect than just being here with you,
the one person that I really care about
and trust more than
anything in the world.
What?
I gotta take my brain meds.
No, they're not that bad.
They're actually minty.
No, I...
What's wrong?
Andi, I'm really glad you can trust me.
- I will never lie to you.
- I know.
But I might from time to time
leave out big chunks of information.
What?
I know I've been acting
a little strange for a while,
and there's a good reason.
I just can't tell you what
that reason is. All I can say is,
there's a part of my life
that I can't talk about...
at all.
A tiny, tiny part.
Really small, nothing to do with us.
What am I supposed to say to that?
I hope you can say you're OK with it.
Then we can still be together.
Because that's what
I want more than anything.
But if you can't do that,
I'll understand. It'll suck.
But I get it.
OK.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
I told you, I trust you.
I mean, I really can't think of a secret
that would change
the way I feel about you.
That is the last time
you come between me and Tony.
- Steve, not a good time.
- Make it a good time.
- Sam?
- I'm afraid Sam
has to cut your evening short,
but may I say
you look good enough to eat. Come on.
I am... I'm so sorry.
- Secrets?
- Secrets.
Did you really think I wasn't gonna
find out what you and Tony are up to?
- Trying to kill the Devil is suicide.
- Steven, it wasn't my idea.
- Uh, I heard shouting.
- Liar.
- You are a liar!
- Steve, Steve,
I'm sorry we kept you out of it,
but we have a fool-proof plan.
It involves deception,
it involves violence.
You know what, this all pacifist thing
is a little hypocritical
coming from you.
OK, here we go. Here we go!
Ask him how he talked me
into joining Lucifer's war on god.
That is ancient history, Tony.
And yet, getting my ass kicked
out of heaven remains fresh in my mind.
You know the therapist said
that this is one of my triggers.
What are you gonna do, Steve?
You gonna take a shot at me?
Give into that demon nature, huh?
Show a little fang?
No.
Cause I don't do that anymore.
There's a better way.
And I'm gonna redeem myself
in the eyes of our creator.
And I am gonna regain
my rightful place in heaven.
And in the meantime, Sam and I are
gonna be kicking ass and taking names.
- Come on.
- Tony, Tony...
No, everything is in place.
The Devil dies tonight.
Are you sure that thing
will be able to kill him?
Positive.
We're all going to be free.
Wait, wait!
- Steve, not now.
- Not speaking to you.
I'm begging you all,
please call this off.
If we murder the Devil in cold blood.
We become more like him.
The only way to defeat him
is to turn our back on his ways.
Who is with me?
Anyone?
Steve, I'm sorry.
We're going through with this.
And if you want to leave, I...
completely understand.
But I would love it if you stayed.
My place is at your side.
You know that.
I'm so glad.
All right, Sam, let's do this.
Hey, you guys, we're just grabbing
some of the beer for the roof.
We're not... and I repeat...
we're not trying to see you bone.
Relax, they're not here.
I think they're in the bedroom.
Dammit.
All right, hold your arms out.
- Sock?
- Yeah?
How long you plan
on us being on the roof?
I don't know.
That's up to Sam, isn't it?
- Cubby Bryce.
- What?
"Cubby Bryce."
Cubby Bryce.
- Cubby Bryce.
- The soul we captured. What?
- We're drinking his beer.
- What?
I knew his name sounded
familiar. I mean,
his name's on every
single one of these labels.
So I don't understand. What,
did the soul live
here before we moved in?
Had to. And that can't be a coincidence.
You think the Devil has something to
do with us moving into this apartment?
Ben, I don't even want to go there man.
I found this joint in a real estate ad.
- Devil has nothing to do with it, OK?
- I knew this was too good to be true.
So you find this place yourself, right?
- Yes, I do, 100%.
- And what's this?
- What?
- Look who signed the lease, Sock?
- Satin.
Satan, Sock.
He signed the lease himself.
OK, this doesn't make sense to me, OK?
Why would the Devil
want us to move in here?
Because he knew Sam
would meet Steve and Tony...
and help with the revolution.
It's a trap, Sock.
Sam! Sammy!
OK.
Here goes.
Sorry.
- I should take this.
- Oh, man.
- Hello?
- Sam, what are you doing?
I'm kind of in the middle
of a rebellion right now.
- Can I please call you back?
- No. Listen very carefully.
The Devil put us in this apartment.
- He knows what you're doing.
- He knows, Sam. He knows.
He's setting us up. The Devil's onto us.
- What do you mean?
- We can't go through with this, OK?
- What? We're way too close.
- No, no!
Hey, gang.
- We're having a party?
- No!
Neat.
Boys.
But did you really think I'd
leave the actual sword of the Archangel
lying around for you to find?
I got it in Korea town.
Oh, Sam...
Look what you did.
Stabbing me in the back.
Quite a show, huh?
- You killed them.
- Yep.
Why did you have to kill them?
Well, they were sort
of trying to kill me, Sam.
They weren't exactly loyal employees.
Very helpful of you, though, to get 'em
all in one location like that.
Made my job way easier.
Oh, come on, man. Relax.
My whole plan depended
on you conspiring against me.
- It's all good.
- Why'd you do it?
I was tired of them, Sam.
I have enough annoyances in my day.
Exhibit "A."
No.
That's not why.
They weren't just annoying.
They were right.
Steve was right.
His peace plan?
That was really a threat to you.
Yes. I'm so terrified by
people who are super friendly.
Come on, you wouldn't have gone to
all the trouble if you weren't afraid.
What they were planning was gonna work.
Well, that's an adorable
theory but completely wrong.
Love, generosity, decency.
It weakens you.
If everybody in the world were good,
you'd have no one to tempt.
You wouldn't even exist!
It would destroy you!
Well, what are the chances
of that ever happening?
By the way...
I'm changing my cellphone number.
Thanks to Raceman for the transcript.
Subtitles made by the Bloc Team
For www.forom.com