You know what? I'm thinking of
getting rid of my cell phone.
I gonna go a Blackberry?
I'm gonna go old school pager
and pay phone.
What? You selling dimebags out
of your mother's car again?
I'm sick and tired of people being able
to reach me whenever they want.
You know, it's like, " I wanna talk
about. "I have a medical emergency."
I don't care? I just want to get off
the grid for a while. Crazy-guy style.
All right,
I'll catch you guys back at the house.
What the hell? Where am i?
Great. No. This is just great. See, I
was supposed to be getting a hot stone
massage but instead, I'm with my buddy.
Wonderful.
The devil brought us here, you idiot.
"Idiot." Nice.
Real mature, bro.
You're short.
Maybe next to a weird
frankenstein monster like you.
Yeah, what are you? Like 5'4", 5'5"?
All right, fellas. Take it easy.
Just take it easy.
Everybody just... breathe.
Yeah, would you look at that?
Makes me sick.
All the co2 spewing into the air,
polluting our planet,
choking our beautiful mother earth.
Did you know that global warming is
the biggest threat facing us today?
Really?
You care about global warming?
Yes, I care.
'cause it can destroy our planet.
And if that happens,
that jackass upstairs
can count all the casualties as
innocents.
That means I get any
of their souls. Zero.
So yeah, man. I'm goin' "green."
You want me to start driving an electric
car? You just say it. I'll do it.
You know what I would really love?
Is if one of you would step up
and prove yourselves worthy
of being my second in command.
OK. But I can see that's not possible.
So, since time is of the essence,
we're going to have a little contest.
2 vessels.
One escaped soul.
The first one of you who brings
this guy back to me in hell
will become my right-hand man...
My human representative in this realm,
serving at my side
as we create hell on earth.
The loser, however, will be cast out.
No financial support,
no clothes, no car.
Just an eternity of endless
toil as one of my minions.
Put quite simply,
your life will be garbage.
My life is already garbage.
Well then we'll just have to
find a way to make it worse.
Good luck, my sons.
-= 208 =-
" The Home Stretch "
Sub VO : ¤Aka¤
Subs-Addicts"
[Sub-way.fr]
- Hey, I'm here to kick you ass.
- What?
I don't care what I have to do to win.
But I am going to catch this soul.
- I deserve to be by dad's side.
- I couldn't agree more.
No. No. Seriously. I want you to win.
I'll even help you if you want.
I don't know what mind games you're
playing, but I'm not buying it.
One more thing.
- What the hell man?!
- Ass-whooping Morgan style.
Believe.
Jelly is Jelly whether
it's grape or cherry.
- But I don't like cherry.
- I just.
Why is there a small
Mexican lady in our kitchen?
It's my grandmother.
Also, she's not Mexican.
- What, but you're...
- Not mexican either.
You're not? So what are you?
What are you, black?
Ethiopian? You're not asian, that's out.
Don't tell me...
American samoan!
We've been friends for how long
and you don't know I'm Puerto Rican?
Benjamin, I don't see colors, all right?
No seriously, I don't.
I'm red-green colorblind.
It's called dichromacy.
It's very painful for me.
So what it boils down to is that,
no I can't ever be a jet fighter pilot,
but yes, I can have a commercial
fishing license. And that's good.
But it's no jet fighter pilot.
Look at all the junk food
I found in the fridge.
- You eat all wrong.
- How you doing, grandma?
You rember Sock?
Good to see you too.
I'm going to plant some veggies
so you can eat like men.
How do you expect to find a decent girl
when you don't take care
of yourself, Benjamin?
Actually Benjamin has a pretty hot thing
going with a nice young lady named Nina.
My personal shopper.
- Thank you, Sock.
- Sure.
Nina's my personal shopper.
She helps get me my hats and shoes,
assorted menswear.
What did you say you were going
to plant back there, grandma?
Because I'm actually
into eggplant myself.
Maybe you could take
a look at the garden
and see if maybe we can make
a nice eggplant plant plant.
Maybe.
Vamanos, chico.
Don't forget You have your cousin's
confirmation party tomorrow night.
I hate Hector, grandma.
But I will be there.
What's up?
You don't want grandma to
know you're dating Nina?
The woman can see evil, Sock. See it.
Remember knew Sam
something to do with the devil?
You don't think she'd
figure out Nina's a demon?
Yeah, probably. But
maybe she'd be proud that her
grandson is railing a hot demon.
A demon who is way out of his league,
I might add.
- She would disown me.
- That seems a bit much.
But I do know how you
mexicans have a spicy temper.
OK. So we're all set.
Congratulations.
Welcome to the Workbench team.
And this is for you.
Thank you so much.
This is such a blessing.
And let me promise you,
i'm gonna work my sack off.
I was thinking that maybe we could drive
the cemetery tomorrow and look for Alan.
I'm working a double shift tomorrow.
Well, i'm giving you the day off.
- What?
- No it's just...
I seriously doubt Alan's gonna
help me get out of my deal.
He's too afraid of the devil.
It's worth a shot, right?
Yeah, I guess it is.
OK, well, I think we should
pretend to be mourners.
'cause then it's less
conspicuous that way.
And there's a funeral
we can hit at 4:00.
We're crashing a funeral?
Yeah, don't you want us
to get back together?
- I do.
- OK. Good.
- OK. So how we gonna do this?
- I think we should split up.
Ben, why don't you take the funeral?
You can keep a lookout from there.
Me and Sock can pretend to be
mourning at grave sights and,
I don't know,
why don't you go back to the work-shed?
Actually, Andi, I think maybe
I better handle the funeral.
Why?
It's going to require some real acting.
And I just don't think
you have the chops, Benji.
I find you to be over-the-top.
Hey, go big or go home, dawg.
- What is wrong with him?
- I don't know.
So, do you like funerals or...?
How'd you know her?
She was my high school english teacher.
Same.
God, what I wouldn't give to be
sitting in her classroom one more time.
You know, just reading, learning.
Reading.
I don't know if it'll help
but me and some other students
are having a candlelight vigil.
- You should come.
- Definitely! That'd be awesome.
I mean, yeah. Yeah. Yes.
That will be very sorrowful.
Alan! Hey, wait! Wait!
Hold on! I just wanna talk!
There he is!
It's OK.
It was her time.
- She was only 46.
- Shut up.
You know what I mean.
By those who loved her.
A prayer frompsalms.
"For we know that neither death,
nor life, nor angels...
"nor any other creature...
"Shall be able to separate us
from the love of god...
Which is in Christ Jesus."
- What's going on?
- Nothing. Just boys being boys. Right?
Read the...
Read the Bible.
Hey, sorry. It was a
really powerful service.
- How's it going?
- He won't talk.
Well, maybe he just needs
a little bit of encouragement.
Know where we are, Alan?
At the track. Look familiar?
We know you were
a gambling addict, Alan.
And you're out of hell
on a technicality.
So if you sin once you'll
be sent back immediately.
Now if I remember correctly,
gambling is a sin.
So here's the deal.
You tell us how you got out
of your deal with the devil or
we open this door and we leave you here.
Now, maybe you'll march on home
to your little cemetery
there and everything's hunkydory.
But maybe-just maybe.
You take this fresh $100 Bill I got
right here and these racing forms
hop on in there and see how
the ponies are running today?
Place a couple bets like
the good old days, whipperoo!
Guys, this is not cool.
All right? Just take me home.
You sure? Because the races are
gonna start any minute now.
- Please, I'm serious.
- They got slot machines and Keno.
Wait, guys, guys. Wait.
- Video poker, scratch-offs, twinquin...
- Sock, stop.
Just let me bet this race!
I need someone to bet $100
on the sixth horse to show.
It's a lock! Someone help me out here!
Why are you people ignoring me?!
Hey, guys, thanks for the impromptu
torture session.
- It's a great way to break up the day.
- Sorry to bother you.
If you just told us what we needed
to know, we would leave you alone.
- Not possible.
- Why not?
'cause if I talk to you,
i'll be back on the devil's radar.
And he'll be trying to tempt me
back to hell, non-stop.
Although going back
to hell would be better living
cooped up on this little postage stamp.
Must be tough.
What choice do I have?
I brought Vietnamese food.
I thought maybe we could go
watch a movie, flying later?
- Yeah. Great. Thanks. I...
- You going somewhere?
Got on your going-out chain.
I have to go to my little
cousin's confirmation.
And I was gonna invite you, sweetie,
but you know, everyone's
gonna be speaking spanish,
there'd be all these strange
people to meet.
I knew you'd hate it.
It'd be wicked boring.
That sounds like fun.
I'd love to go.
That's really sweet, thank
you. Really. But it's OK.
- Do you not want me there?
- I do, it's
just. It's not that. It's...
It's my grandmother. She...
Sort of has the eye.
The eye?
She can see evil.
And since you're a demon,
i'm not sure she'd approve.
Well, you're a grown up, ben.
Why can't you just standup to her?
Because she's scary.
That lady does pilates every day.
Her core? Right here?
The lady's rocking a sixer.
Is that her?
I won't be long OK?
So just stay here, relax.
Watch some Tv, do the dishes. And,
we'll talk about it later, all right?
OK. Ya Voy.
What are you doing?
What? You can't let her be bullying you.
Besides, i'm like 90% not-evil.
That's less evil than most humans.
She's gonna love me.
Please don't do this.
Don't do this. Don't. Don't.
I'm Nina.
It's so nice to meet you.
Abuelita, Nina's a friend of mine.
And she was thinking
of coming to the party.
That thing is not going to my party.
You keep her away from me.
Far away.
Listen. Listen. Look at me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I promise this whole
thing will work itself out. OK?
I'll call you when I get back.
I'm sorry.
Sorry I slapped you. It was wrong.
Even if it was incredibly satisfying.
So, you still up for lending
me a hand with this thing?
Helping me win this?
Cause I'm having a teeny bit of trouble.
I can't believe this.
Aall right, his name is Bud Brown.
Pretty bad dude.
Adultery, theft, murder.
Says he owned a chop shop by the piers.
Have you checked that out?
- Not yet.
- What about his apartment?
- I didn't read that far down.
- What have you done?
What I'm here, aren't i?
- What is he building in there?
- I don't know.
Hey, let me see your vessel.
I think it's different than mine.
Pretty sure they're the same.
All right, so the devil didn't
say that the winner was the one
who vesseled him, just the one
who sends him back to hell. So
I'm gonna go in there capture him.
Then I'll give you the vessel
you can drop it off at the DMV,
and then boom. You get the credit.
Good plan man.
I was just wondering if you
guys bought spare auto parts
because I have an old car I no longer
use, and it's got some good stuff.
- Get out.
- I don't think so, bud.
It's not working.
So you can get us in at 7:30, right?
OK. Great. But will you just make
sure that I get a window seat?
I was the middle the restaurant
I could just
Barely hear myself think.
No. Thank you very much.
All right.
See you tonight.
- You're alive.
- What the hell did you do to my vessel?
I broke it,
and I gave you a real fire extinguisher.
What?
Why? I almost got killed in there!
I know. I just figured once you were
gone, this whole competition
- would get a whole lot easier.
- Are you an idiot?
I don't know how I can be any clearer.
I. Don't. Want. To. Win.
Sticking to your story. Nice.
No. Morgan,
you gotta believe me. What are you...
Boring!
Seriously, we didn't have
any bigger globes than that?
Hey! Where you been?
Dealing with Morgan
and this stupid contest.
I'm trying to let the idiot win,
and he won't let me.
I wish I looked like Morgan.
He's such a handsome gentleman.
Yeah, and he has a perfect
body for clothes,
you know what I mean? The way
his suit hangs off his broad shoulders.
He's Kinda Barrel-chested, narrow waist.
And it's subtle but you look
closely you can notice all
the awesome muscle tone underneath.
OK, yes. He's great.
He's also incredibly lazy.
That's why I've gotta make sure he wins.
If the devil's stuck
with him for the rest of eternity, the
whole world's gonna be a lot better off.
What are you guys doing?
We have an idea about how to
convince alan to tell you the secret.
I appreciate the thought,
but I think alan's a lost cause.
We got it. Alan's sick of being
stuck at the cemetery, right?
But he's gotta be there because
the ground's consecrated.
What if we sent him to a city where
every inch of the ground is consecrated?
Yeah. Where he can actually
have a real life?
Where the devil couldn't find him.
All right, alan, we
made a little film for you. OK.
It's a little rough still, music
spotting's in places. But...
But it'll give you a good idea of how
fun life is gonna be in Vatican City.
'cause it is.
It's gonna be off the Chain.
So, what do you think?
We can help you with plane tickets,
a passport, everything.
- And in return?
- You help me.
You tell me what you did to get
out of your deal with the devil.
- Let's do this.
- Serious?
Yeah, I can't live like this anymore.
It's driving me crazy.
I'm going to leave this with you.
But if this winds up on Youtube,
I will sue your ass.
- Have fun.
- Let's go.
- Has it started yet?
- Not yet. Here.
No need. I brought my own.
Hawaiian sandalwood.
It was her favorite.
- How you holding up? You OK?
- Doing OK.
- You?
- Well, you know, baby steps.
I was thinking it might be good
to do something Kinda fun tonight.
Shake it up. Get out
of my own head for a while.
- I could definitely go for that.
- Yeah?
What do you say to a little
round of bowling?
Or not. Just an idea.
Leisure activity.
No. It's not that. It's just,
you know...
She just loved bowling so much,
it wouldn't really seem right.
Of course, bowling.
I know what an idiot. I'm sorry.
I can't believe I forgot that.
When she rolled that 300 last year,
she was so proud.
I know. The elusive 3 Hondo.
Man, that lady could roll.
So I brought a poem.
I thought maybe I could read
to the gang tonight.
You should save that for thursday night.
What's thursday?
We're having a Memorial service for her.
Another one?
This one's gonna be more intimate
Just her closest family and friends
sharing their memories
and stories one more time.
- A final goodbye.
- I don't know.
- Maybe we can go bowling after that.
- What time does it start?
You see grandma out there,
planting some healthy food?
Don't tell her, but I'm gonna
throw those veggies in the trash.
Come on Chico,
let's go in the living room and wrestle.
Maybe this is a bad idea,
but I like your Grandson
way too much just to let this go.
I'm not evil.
You're not seeing me
for what I actually am.
A fallen angel.
While I may know what hell is,
I've also seen the highest
reaches of heaven.
And
I can tell you honestly,
that's where I'd rather be.
- Have you met St. Peter?
- I have.
What is he like?
God!
When you're around him, you just
you feel this incredible sense of calm.
It's quite amazing.
You're so lucky.
Nina, you probably
don't want to do that?
Ben, it's OK. We're fine.
We're just having a chat.
Chico. No!
Oh, my god! Abuela!
How's your grandma?
Minor heart attack.
But she's doing fine. She's gonna
be there a couple of more days, so...
Minor heart attack?
If I go out, i'm going out huge.
Double heart attack.
Left ventricle all over you.
Have you talked to Nina?
She flew off right after it happened.
You know, I specifically asked her not
to talk to my grandmother.
That I had it under control.
Did she listen to me? Not at all.
In all fairness,
the Chihuahua did attack her.
I don't know what to do.
What do you guys think about my pants?
- Are those pinstripe?
- Yeah, it's a very subtle stripe.
But still noticeable. Well played.
Thank you. I'm going to a memorial
service tonight. Gotta look good.
You still chasing
after that funeral chick?
- Persistent.
- Yeah, I know.
I'm gonna convince that
she's done grieving tonight.
I think it's safe to expect a little
tongue action after this memorial.
Maybe during.
I don't know. We'll see. Who knows?
I'm gonna go back to the hospital.
Thanks, friends.
No problem, Benji.
Always here for ya, man.
Hi, I'm here to honor the deceased.
Of course. Please sign in.
Were you one of Mrs. Simon's students?
I was. Yeah.
But I'd like to think I taught
her as much as she taught me.
Well, I must say, her students certainly
loved her.
Please go in. Have a seat.
- How are you holding up?
- I'm pretty good. You know.
I'll tell you what happened.
I woke up today
and I said to myself out loud,
"Sock you are done mourning."
- Really?
- I did, really. Yeah, I've grieved.
I've just grieved so hard.
I've grieved for so long.
Now I have to move on.
I want to embrace life.
I want to make out
with strangers. We all should.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Yeah.
We need to put this
death behind us and live.
You got it.
It's what Mrs. Simons would have wanted.
Mrs. S.
I'm so happy I met you.
You're an amazing man, Sock.
I am. I know.
This is nate, my boyfriend.
He's really been crushed by all this.
Yeah. Your what?
Sock was just talking me
through my grief.
And it helped, it really helped.
Maybe you can help nate too.
We all really need each other right now.
We can pull through this.
OK. I'm out.
Excuse me. Before I begin the
remembrances,
I have a very important announcement.
As you know, Mrs. Simons was a
philanthropist as well as a teacher.
So her dying wish was to bequeath
her entire fortune to her students.
So,
all of you students who attended today's
special memorial will receive $10,000.
You will then be asked to donate that
money to a charity of your choice.
Any worthy charity.
As a way of honoring
mrs. Simmons's memory.
Thank you.
And, I'm back.
Hi. Do you have direct flights
to vatican city?
Rome's the closest?
Rome's good.
No, it's for a friend.
His name is Alan townsend.
Order up!
He'll call you back.
Sorry. You were being rude.
And given the fact
that you two let the soul go,
I should think you'd both be
a bit more ashamed.
You fellas ready to order?
- Hi. Yeah, I would love the chicken...
- He will have nothing.
I'll a cup of coffee, black, 2 sugars.
Dad, allow me to apologize.
You have any idea how
disappointed I am in you two?
I mean, to think that one day one
of you might actually help
me guide mankind
on a path to destruction.
It just simply boggles the mind.
- But dad, let me explain.
- No, let me.
You know what I see
when I look at you, Morgan?
I see a big, Lazy puppy dog
with lazy puppy-dog eyes
and a little puppy-dog brain.
So eager to please and yet so...
Incapable.
Thank you, dear.
And you.
Such a whiny little baby.
You won't be laughing tonight.
When that soul finishes
what he's been working on.
- What's that?
- A portal
allowing his buddies,
a bunch of degenerate souls,
my hard-earned souls by the way,
to escape from hell.
He needs to be caught.
Now.
Whenever you're ready.
Is that really how he sees me?
As a big, lazy puppy dog?
- Come on, be honest, man.
- You really care what he thinks?
- Yeah. He's my dad.
- Yeah, but he's the devil.
He's never gonna be a real dad.
He can't. It's impossible.
He's all I got.
I just want to make him happy.
I've lived my entire life
trying to measure up
and then failing miserably.
You know, you want to do him right?
Let me help you win this. OK?
Morgan, you have to believe me.
I don't like working for him, I don't like
knowing him. I don't want any part of this.
- You being serious?
- I promise.
OK, good. Let's go do this.
Sorry bud.
We're gonna have to put an end
to your experiment.
Sorry boys.
You're too late.
Hurry up! Get him. Get him!
The vessel's not working!
Not on these two.
The vessel will only work on him.
Go! I'll keep these guys busy.
Morgan! Run! Get out of here!
Sam, the vessel's gone.
Thank you for saving my life.
Bud-the soul.
You sent him back to hell.
You won the contest.
No. No! I...
I didn't do anything.
You did everything. I just...
I gave him a little push.
There's no vessel right?
I mean, there's no way to prove
which of us sent him back. Right?
- I guess you're right.
- You a good liar.
We'll just lie, tell the devil you won.
There's no proof otherwise.
I can do that.
I do like lying.
You sure you're cool, man?
Just say you run a charity that
helps the community or something.
I got this.
I know a lot about charities.
Good, good, good man. Good.
- Hello, Mr. Wysocki.
- Hello again.
Hello. And you are?
This is my associate Ben.
He runs a non-profit based
organization that I'm very,
very passionate about.
I'll be donating the money to him.
- What type of charity is that?
- He reads to the blind people.
And delivers food
to hungry orphans on Christmas.
Sock, please allow me.
While it is true that I am involved
in various community activities,
the most important thing that I do
is work my laboratory.
You see,
how can I put this? I'm creating a
machine that will help the entire world.
An invention that will
help liberate mankind.
Please, do tell?
It's a straw.
A self-sucking straw.
And it will help people who
have problems using their Jaw
enjoy the wonders of using a straw.
- There you go.
- Sir,
I'd like to call this invention
the straw-to-matic.
A self-sucking straw?
OK. Sounds good to me.
I just needed to put something
on the form here.
Straw-to-matic.
Good. There's your money.
All the best. Thanks for everything.
And I'm sure somewhere up there
mrs. Simons is smiling.
- Yeah. Yeah probably.
- Good day to you, sir.
And to you.
A self-sucking straw?
How long have you been sitting
on this gold-mine, Benjamin?
I guess I thought about it when I was 8.
8? You thought about this when you were
8, you didn't tell anybody until now?
I told my mom and dad
but they didn't get it.
Of course not they're idiots.
Now listen to me,
we're gonna take that 10 grand
use it as seed money to build
something that's called a prototype.
After that happens, ka-ching.
What do you mean "living expenses?"
He's talking to Alan.
You want full row of seats to yourself?
You know how much that costs?
No, that wasn't part of the deal!
- Whatever. I'll call you back.
- What?
He has a list of new demands.
He's afraid of being tempted so he
wants to fly in an aisle all by himself,
he wants money for a one
bedroom apartment.
No. He can't do this.
Well he says the deal's off
unless I meet all of them.
We're talking thousands of dollars.
Would you-would you
excuse us for a moment?
Be right back.
Walk normal. Walk normal.
Just walk normal.
- What are we thinking?
- Honestly I'm torn.
I know, me too.
On the one hand, we got Sam's soul,
and yeah, that is important.
But then on the other hand
you got the straw-to-matic.
I mean, that's a straw that
sucks on your lips, Benjamin.
Sucks on your lips. I mean, it hurts
your Brain at how amazing that idea is.
- That's a once-in-a-lifetime idea.
- Yeah. Lightning in a bottle.
You know what, it's not like
Alan's going anywhere.
Not at all. But somebody could think of
the straw-to-matic beat us to the punch.
Here's what we do.
We make our millions and then
we help Sam deal with Alan.
Why is there an envelope
full of cash out here?
- That is...
- For you.
We wanted it to be a surprise
to help you with Alan.
How did you know about Alan?
Do you want the money or not?
Yes, thank you.
There he is!
Congratulations, man. I
knew you'd win the contest. Knew it.
Even bet my secretary that you would.
Now she owes me a dinner at Houston's.
No, Morgan won.
He pushed the soul through the portal.
- I had nothing to do with it.
- Come on, Sammy.
You think I don't know how
things go down in my own house?
Enjoy it, man.
You're my second in command.
What the hell is going on here?
Well, we're celebrating Sammy's win.
Very impressive.
No. I keep telling him
that I didn't win, you did.
Hey, drop the false modesty all right.
We all know that you wanted
this from the very beginning.
You screwed me?
You've been playing me
since the beginning?
No. I wasn't. I...
You don't have to explain
anything to him.
He's a nobody. He doesn't
even deserve your attention.
But don't you worry.
Even though you lost,
you get a nice consolation prize.
10 bucks and a bus pass.
Enjoy!
Please, I'm not taking your pity prize.
Really? Even after you find out
that everything else is gone?
Your keys. Your wallet. Your clothes.
Your car. Your condo. Everything.
You looking for these, buddy?
You're a dead man. Dead man.
That guy?
Lots of bark and no bite.
I can't believe it.
This is actually happening.
I'll call you guys when I get there.
Isn't there something
you want to tell us?
- Right.
What most people
don't know about the devil
is that he can't resist a competition.
OK, so what does that mean exactly?
You know that whole devil
went down to Georgia thing?
He challenged a guy
to a fiddling contest.
He's so incredibly vain,
he doesn't think that anybody
can beat him at anything.
- For me, it was poker.
- So, I have to beat him at poker?
You do what you're good at.
Figure out what that is
and challenge him.
However, there's one more step to get
the devil to agree to the challenge.
- OK. What's that?
- I can't tell you that right now.
- What? We had a deal!
- Look, until I'm safe,
standing on consecrated ground,
I have to keep one ace up my sleeve.
I promise you I'll call you as
soon as I set foot in the Vatican.
You have to believe me.
I want to help you.
I just wish I could be there to see
his face when you do beat the bastard.
Call me the second you land.
You believe him?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
You?
Yeah, I do.
- For your grandma.
- Thanks.
How's she doing?
Better. Doct said it should be a couple
more days and then she can go home.
Ben, I'm really sorry
about what happened.
Sometimes when I get startled
I just lose control.
I know. It's fine. Let's just forget it
and move on all right?
But we still have to figure this out.
I mean, did you
talk to her yet about us?
I did. And it's handled, baby.
- Good. What happened?
- I told her I dumped you.
So now we can just date secretly and
see where that takes us. It's win-win.
Are you kidding me?
I don't have any other choice here.
What do you want me to do?
I want to go to the hospital right now
and tell your grandma that you love me,
and you want us to be together.
- You serious?
- Why not?
For one thing, visiting hours
are over. I couldn't get in.
Ben you could get in.
I don't want to put her under that kind
of stress. I mean, not in her condition.
- You told me she was feeling better.
- She's in the ICU!
Our relationship's in the ICU!
Ben, you're letting her bully you.
- And now you're bullying me.
- You're not giving me any choice.
I just want you to be a man.
Have a backbone.
Backbone? -You want backbone?
How about this-it's over.
Don't say that unless you mean it.
I mean it.
You broke my heart once,
and I forgave you.
But not this time.
This time you're going to wish
you never met me.
Tough beat, my brother.
She's amazing woman.
I would kill that ass.
Alan just texted me.
His flight's about to take off.
I can't believe this.
I'm going to beat the devil.
I know.
How does it feel?
I feel like me again.
Does that make any sense?
Yeah. Totally.
I did it. I beat the devil!
I'm done!
Sorry.
I don't care.
It feels so good.
So what are you going to do
with your new-found freedom?
- I might learn a new language.
- Really?
No. Probably just gonna nap a lot.
Thank you so much, though.
- For sticking with me.
- Of course.
OK. Sorry.
Sorry, I just had to do that.
Yeah. Yeah. We just kissed a lot.
And I want to do it again.
Me too.
But, we should...
we should wait until tomorrow.
I'll be out of my deal with the devil.
Then we can kiss as much as we want.
You're right. It sounds like a plan.
Thank you.
Hi. This is your captain speaking.
We just got word from flight Deck
that we need to go ahead and make
an unscheduled maintenance stop.
We apologize for this inconvenience,
but the good news is, we'll
be stopping in Las Vegas!
You will each receive
$100 in casino chips.
To tide you over
while we're on the ground.
So please, enjoy your time in the
gambling capital of the world.
Can I get you something to drink?
Team Subs-Addicts"