Is this a carjacking?
Are you carjacking me?
I'm the devil!
Before you were born,
your mom and I sold
your soul to the devil.
- You gonna tell Andi?
- I'm not gonna tell Andi!
If she knows,
she'll never go out with me.
You can make her
go out with you, Damien.
You're just going to bring
escaped souls back to hell.
- That's cool, right?
- How am I supposed to capture him?
This will help. A vessel, hand-crafted
in the bowels of perdition
by the inequities of the vile.
- That'll work.
- Word of caution...
I don't accept failure.
You finally found the
one thing that you're good at.
You sent an escaped soul back to hell.
Oh, fiddlesticks!
Dude, I need to find
another place to live.
I can't do this anymore.
You can't move back to my house.
We gotta figure something else out.
Morning.
What?
Was I snoring?
Little bit.
You want to get some food
before we meet up with the guys?
I just gotta change first.
OK.
You know, you're the first
girl to infiltrate our bowling circle.
I like you a lot, too, Sam.
Just so you know,
you might get your ass handed
to you today. We bowl a lot.
It doesn't look that hard.
Trust me, it's harder than it looks.
Don't worry. The guys won't judge you.
Hi, lady and gent. Let's do it.
I thought we agreed
to lose the costumes.
Excuse me? Lose the costumes, Sam?
That's like Mick Jagger
without Keith Richards,
or Bono without the Edge.
It's not right.
So don't go messing
with our bowling chi, OK?
- I'm sorry.
- No, come on. I love it.
All right, bitches.
Let's throw some balls around.
That's us.
Yeah, all right!
Lucky streak is up, rook.
Lucky streak is up.
Season 1, Episode 12 - Unseen
For www.forom.com
I'm telling you, it was weird.
It's like the ball
had a mind of its own.
It's beginner's luck.
I wouldn't read too much into it.
No, it wasn't. There was definitely
something else going on, you guys.
You have got to chill out.
She is not the spawn of satan.
- We saw her naked, remember?
- Definitely no mark of tne beast.
You should hear the way she snores.
Seriously, it's not normal.
It's like she's a creature
from the underworld.
Oh, god, I love that movie.
Kate Beckinsale, black spandex.
There's something wrong with her.
What? Kate Beckinsale is perfection.
What's wrong with you?
- No, you nimrod. Cady.
- Oh, Cady.
All right, what,
so she snores, she's a kick-ass bowler,
she's got a super-duper hot body,
she's cool, and she's into you.
What else do you want?
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
I'd get excited
about this meeting if I were you.
I just saw Ted.
Looks like he's on the warpath.
You owe me a coffee.
Want to get one before the meeting?
- Do you guys want one?
- We're good, thanks.
Did you mean who else does he want?
Now that the holiday rush is over,
a few announcements to make. First off,
great big thank you to ira greenblatt
for working double shifts
on Christmas eve.
Way to show that spirit of the season,
buddy.
I got your back at Passover, dude.
But on the more negative note,
it has recently come to my attention
that some of the merchandise
in this store has gone missing.
I fear that
we have been victims of shoplifting.
What was stolen?
I'm not at liberty to discuss
that information right now, Andi.
But I don't think
I need to tell you guys
that shoplifting is a very,
very serious crime.
- Hurts us all, Ted.
- Yes it does, Sam.
Yes, it does.
And that's why we are going
on the offensive.
We will be installing an extensive
video system throughout the store.
I'm sure that will be
a deterrent for our so-called
"customers" with sticky fingers.
So let's get out there, people.
Remember, keep those lookin' balls open.
- Let's get these guys!
- Let's get 'em.
All right, boys, let's roll.
- Hey, will you cover for us?
- Where are you going?
I finally found a sick apartment.
Gonna go check it out.
- Did you not hear Ted's speech?
- I live here, Ben.
It's not stealing if it's
your own house, come on.
Take a look, boys.
What do you think of this?
How much do you pay for this, again?
Only $1,200 a month.
It was a total steal.
- You're a freakin' Jesse James.
- I know.
Sock, have you not seen your paycheck?
You don't make $1,200 a month.
All I need is 4.
So where are you going to get the rest?
From your mom?
From you guys.
What?!
We're gonna be roomies.
I forged you guys' signatures
on the lease! Isn't that wicked?!
No, Sock,
the last thing I need right now
is my name on another contract
I didn't sign.
Dude, you should have talked
to us first!
Look, if I'd have of waited,
this place would have gone
like hot cakes, all right?
We'll get the porn channels.
We'll put a foosball table over there,
maybe a little tiki bar,
a hookah pipe.
I don't know, whatever we want.
It's on you, dude. I mean,
- we did say we wanted our own place.
- Benji's in. Sammy, it's down to you.
I don't know, man!
Look... Ben, excuse us. Come here.
OK, listen to me.
I did not want to play this card,
I really didn't,
but you leave me no choice.
The fact of the matter is, you owe me.
You owe me, all right?
I've been there since the beginning,
helping you send
escaped souls back to hell, man!
I've been the friggin' Robin
to your Batman.
What does that make me?
You're the weird english butler guy.
Listen, I need a bat cave.
Sammy, I deserve a bat cave.
- I'm Batman?
- You're Batman.
You want to move out?
Well, I'm 21, and I can't live
with my parents forever.
Well, no, not forever, Sam.
But we thought you'd be around
for at least a few more years.
Come on, mom, dad.
We all know that Sam's gotta bust out
of this joint sometime, right?
- Plus, my place is awesome.
- It's not like I'm moving to Australia.
- It'll be 5, 10 minutes away.
- 20, max.
- I don't know, Sam.
- Sam, I don't think
- you're ready to live on your own.
- Those are mine.
- Thanks.
- Your mom's right, Sam.
It's a dangerous world out there, and...
Dangerous? Dad, really, dangerous?
I think I can handle living downtown.
Well, what are you going
to do about food?
I'll cook.
I watch naked chef a lot.
How hard can it be?
This move will be good for me,
all right?
I'll learn to do things on my own.
For the first time in my life,
I'll be totally independent.
If it's that important to you, then...
You have our support.
Yes!
Thank you, dad.
Finally leaving the nest, huh?
Finally coming out of the closet, huh?
Oh, a homosexual joke. Very witty.
You're quite a hot shot now, huh, Sam?
What with moving out and all.
All right, can we just be adults
and get on with this?
Oh, sure we can.
You're a big boy now, huh?
Here, let me help you with this,
big boy.
A playground, clever.
Well, I thought you'd appreciate
the irony.
Right. Can we get on with this?
- Someone's testy today.
- No, I'm not testy.
I've done this so many damn times,
and I'm tired of you treating me
like I'm a 4-year-old.
I know what I'm doing.
As you wish, Mr. Oliver.
In life, the soul is known
as Herbert Scrim.
A total hermit, lived in the woods.
He made the unabomber
look like a social butterfly.
OK, so what's his deal?
Well, Herbert was a hunter.
And he killed anyone who dare
run through his neck of the woods.
And now that his hunting grounds
have turned into a city park,
there's a lot more prey.
Where do I find him?
In there.
But you be careful, Sammy.
This soul's a tricky one.
All the years that he lived,
he was hardly ever seen.
I know, I get it, but what's his deal?
Like, electroshocks, bugs, what?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You've graduated, my man.
You're moving on up.
This time, it's just you,
and your new found confidence.
- Why are we doing this, again?
- Come on, Andi, they're our friends.
Aren't you curious
about their new place?
No, you are up to no good, I know it.
Our first house guest.
No, I think it's my waterbed.
Boo-yah!
Hi. It's you.
- Hey.
Look who's finally becoming a man.
You just made it look like so much fun.
- Where did you guys find this place?
- We lucked out.
I think, um,
it actually used to be a meth lab,
- like 2 days ago.
- You didn't tell me that.
Oh, jeez.
Ah-ah, Josie, hands off my stuff.
- You mean my stuff.
- I was going to give that back.
- All right, R2-D2 or Princess Leia?
- Definitely R2-D2.
Last time I checked,
you don't live here.
Benji, who would you rather bone?
A hot chick in a gold bikini,
or a bleep-blop robot?
- Point taken.
- Thank you.
So, Sam...
Where's Cady?
I haven't... told her I'm moving yet.
- You haven't?
- No.
So did you tell Sam
about Cady's little psycho visit?
No, but that is not my place.
Not your place?
Sam is your friend. If I was dating
Ted bundy, I'd want you to tell me.
- OK, that's very different.
- No, it is not different.
I think you owe it to him
to say something.
No, if I say
one little negative thing about Cady,
I'm gonna look like a weird,
jealous freak.
- Are you jealous?
- No. No, I'm not.
I mean, Sam and I are just friends.
- I've said it a hundred times.
- Andi, I'm your best friend.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not.
Look... if you have feelings for Sam,
you should say something.
Especially when this Cady girl
seems to be nothing but bad news.
No, no. He is with Cady.
I just have to accept it.
You know,
he didn't even tell her he moved.
Maybe he's already
figured it out for himself.
This is the second body dumped
in the park in the last 2 weeks.
Police are asking anyone
who have seen or heard anything
to please come forward.
Reporting from Burberry Park, this is
Maureen Glenroy. Back to you, Rick.
That's gotta be our guy.
Devil said he was a hunter.
Why is he killing so many people?
Must be the thrill of the kill.
How many people does he need
to kill before he's satisfied?
He's an escaped soul from hell, Benji.
He's never satisfied.
Oh, hey, look, look, look.
First housewarming gift.
Very funny, Devil.
Open it, go.
Oh, dude, dude! Magic bullet, oh!
I've wanted one of these forever.
- What is it?
- Vibrator?
Are you kidding me? A vibrator?
No. This is actually the coolest kitchen
appliance known to man.
All right, bar none,
the best counter top food processor
out there on the infomercial market.
I've been saving up 3 easy payments of
nineteen ninety nuff for this bad boy.
"No confusing buttons, no messy cords.
"A battery-operated processor
that is both functional and fun.
"Nothing could be more simple."
- How does it...
- See?
Does it work...
What the hell?
Dude!
You missed a spot.
What are you doing here?
Just brought you a white hot chocolate.
Went to your place today,
but your parents said you moved out.
Were you gonna tell me?
Yeah, no,
Sock found us a place, and it just...
it happened really quickly, so...
You didn't think I needed to know?
No, of course you needed to know.
I just...
I'm telling you now.
- So we're OK?
- Yeah, yeah, we're OK.
What's with the cameras?
Ted's waging a war against shoplifters.
He's installing
a whole new security system.
Think he's watching us right now?
Probably.
You want to give him something
to look at?
What?
Uh, nothing. Nothing.
Are you... are you all right?
Yeah. That was weird, right?
Yeah, that was really weird.
Are... you're good?
I should...
I should clean this up.
Do you want to have dinner tonight?
You know, I got a lot of stuff to do.
I'm... I'm... I got boxes to unpack.
My apartment's a mess, and...
But I'll...
I'll call you. I'll give you a call.
OK. Well, I'll let you get to it.
Maybe there was a flaw
in the glass already, Sam.
No, it's like
she somehow made it happen.
Maybe you made it happen.
You're crackin', man.
It's giving me the creeps.
Every time I look at her,
it's all I can think about.
I don't know.
Maybe I should break up with her.
OK, boys. All right.
You guys ready for a little braingasm,
ultimate gaming experience?
This is a thing of beauty.
All right, let's fire this bitch up.
Let's go.
Oh, my god.
- Heaven.
- Let's go.
What did you do?! What'd you press?
I did not touch anything.
Look, the sooner we figure it out,
the sooner we can be lounging.
Let's ask these guys what's going on.
- Or ladies. Never know.
- I was beating your ass, too.
- You were not.
- Yes, I was.
- Hi there.
- Hi, sorry to bother you.
- We just moved in next door.
- Oh. Hi, great.
Welcome, I'm Steve.
Sam, and this is Sock and Ben.
- Sock. Well, that's an unusual name.
- Is that the UPS guy?
- It's the new neighbors.
- Is he hitting on me?
- He's not hitting on you.
- This is my partner Tony.
- Hi, fellas.
- Hi.
Would you guys like to come in?
I just made a pot of ginger tea.
No, no, thanks. We're straight.
No, no, thank you.
Actually, we just came in to...
We were wondering if you could
help us with something.
With what?
All right!
You are quite the handy man.
Hey, you fellas have
a couple light bulbs out.
- I could fix that for you.
- No, that's all right.
We hardly use the kitchen, anyway.
Whoa, whoa, speak for yourself, man.
I practically am the naked chef.
Not that I cook naked.
You guys want a drink or anything?
- I would.
- Yeah, sure.
We don't have anything in the fridge.
That is maybe the saddest
looking refrigerator I've ever seen.
Tell you guys what.
Tomorrow night, you're coming over
to our place for a home-cooked meal,
and I hope you're not watching
your carbs, because I am thinking pasta.
Oh, my god. You guys are in for a treat.
Steve makes the most delicious lobster
mac and cheese.
He poaches the lobster
in a beurre blanc...
- Beurre blanc.
- Sauce, with mascarpone cheese.
- Unbelievable.
- Oh, beautiful.
The mascarpone perfectly neutralizes
the natural sweetness of the lobster.
The food network.
- So what do you guys say?
- I say what time do we show up?
It's a date.
Get together. With some dudes.
All right,
listen, I'm just going to say this once.
I am not into dudes but I think
I kind of love Steve and Tony.
I know. They're awesome, huh?
I gotta hand it to you, Sock.
This place is pretty good.
Didn't I tell you you'd love it?
Did I not tell you you'd love it?
All right, let's go out to the woods,
catch this soul bitch.
- I got places to be.
- Like where?
Like, the Work Bench.
You picked up an extra shift?
Hey, man, I got rent to pay now.
That's really responsible of you.
I know. No, I'm just messing with you.
No, I got to hook up
with this chick at the pool.
Met her in the elevator.
She is so into me.
Hey, nice headband, bro.
It's good.
Don't these trees look familiar?
It's a forest, Sam.
They all look the same.
- But I feel like we're going in circles.
- This park is ridiculously huge.
How are we supposed to find the soul?
We should get a bird's eye view.
All right.
- Who's climbing it?
- Ben.
Come on, guys,
I've never climbed a tree before.
- Come on.
- What?!
Well, my parents were
a little overprotective. So what?
All right, you know what,
it's time you became a man.
I'll give you a boost. Hold this.
Hang on to my baby!
I don't know
if she's under warranty still.
Give me your foot.
I can't believe I'm climbing a tree.
I can't believe I'm actually
climbing a tree.
I feel like Spiderman.
- The view is amazing, guys.
- The soul?
- Keep your eye on the ball, buddy.
- OK.
OK.
Benji! Oh, my god!
Ben, are you all right?
Oh, don't move.
Dead guy, dead guy, dead guy!
I'm an injured man. Take it easy.
You fell out of a tree. Shake it off.
Victim was Frank oore. He was 31.
God, I can't believe the soul was right
underneath our noses the whole time.
Poor Frank.
I always knew jogging was bad for you.
- We should go jogging.
- Are you kidding me? Did you...
Did you not just hear me
say jogging bad?
No, Sock, think about it. What better way
to lure him out into the open?
All right,
wait, let me get this straight.
You want us to go jogging
in the creepy woods where
the soul has been killing people?
- Yeah.
- OK, let's go.
I knew this was a bad idea, Sam.
Why did I let you talk me into this?
All right, stop. Stop, stop, stop.
I can't... I can't breathe.
Let's stop.
All right,
all right, let's take a breather.
OK.
I'm not loving this outfit either, Sam.
- I feel like a giant traffic cone.
- Sock, we want the soul to see us.
I'm pretty sure the space shuttle
could see us, Ben.
All right.
Come on. We gotta keep moving. Let's go.
Come on.
Come on!
OK.
OK, let's go.
OK, I got another one.
- Super Girl or Wonder Woman?
- Wonder woman.
Definitely Wonder Woman.
Something to be said for a woman
who's into bondage, you know?
Love it.
Who was that? Cady?
- I don't want to talk to her right now.
- I don't know.
You ignore the spawn of Satan,
something bad might happen.
- What was that?
- Come on.
Oh, my god.
He broke her neck.
- I think he's close.
- Yeah, you think?
What was that?
Where is he?
Don't... move.
- What?
- Why?
God! Oh, god!
Guys, get me out of here!
- Calm down, Sock, we'll get you out.
- No, get the soul!
- You just said to get you out!
- I know! I know, stop!
- You have to get me out! Get me out!
- Make up your mind! What do you want?
Get the soul! Get it!
What?
- He's here, he's here.
- What?
OK, come on. Come on out, Herbert!
It's over, let's go!
Oh, god. Guys, look out!
Sam, Sam!
Ben, Sam!
Sam! I don't know how to do it!
How do you make it work?
Oh, my god!
Hey, come on.
Come on!
I said come!
I'm so sorry.
I hope they didn't scare you.
No, no, it's... We love dogs!
Dude, this idea of yours better work.
It will. There's only one way
to make an invisible soul visible.
Paint ball!
I kill at paint ball.
Hey, maybe you should ask
the devil to help us on this one.
He's not going to help us.
He loves watching me freak out.
Sam Oliver, your assistance
is required in aisle four.
I gotta go help Ted install
those new security cameras.
Will you guys take care of this?
Ready? Come on.
These cameras cost me
an arm and a leg, Sam.
Watch it up there.
The innocence of youth.
I bet the last time you sat
at one of these little desks,
you had dreams of great things.
And look at you now, Sam.
Working a minimum wage job,
living in a dumpy apartment,
and doing the devil's dirty work.
- Seeing red now, Sammy?
- Very funny.
Why didn't you tell me
Herbert was invisible?
Well, I said
that nobody ever saw Herbert.
I figured with your genius wit,
you'd piece it together.
Don't you know that being invisible
is the perfect camouflage?
I'm surprised at you, Sammy.
With all your new found confidence,
I thought you'd pass this test
with flying colors.
Looks like you're going to fail.
No, I'm not going to fail.
Just give me something to work with.
Like these?
Glasses?
They help you see the true face of evil.
You don't want to do that, Sam.
Trust me.
Unless you brought
a change of underwear.
Well, go on, say it.
You're not as good
as you thought you were.
- You need me.
- Forget that.
Take them back, you can have these.
I don't need you.
Oh, grumble, grumble, grumble.
I guess we're taking off
the training wheels.
Yeah, I guess so.
This'll be fun to watch.
Oh, yeah.
Good luck, Sam.
Hey, Andi.
Cady, hi.
You know what, Sam's not here.
I think he's making a delivery...
or something.
That's OK.
I actually wanted to talk to you.
Oh, OK. Well, what's up?
Something going on with Sam?
Well, what do you mean?
He's been acting a little weird lately.
Yeah, he always acts weird.
I wouldn't worry about it.
Yeah, it's just he's been
a little distant with me.
You know, like I'd call him,
leave him a message,
and he hasn't called me back.
You know, maybe he's just preoccupied.
You know, with the move and all.
Yeah, the move.
I just can't help but wonder if maybe
it has something to do with you.
Me?
I know you and Sam had a thing.
Cady...
Listen. Me and Sam are friends.
That's it.
Well, I just...
I really care about him, you know?
I just wish I knew what was going on.
We can see the soul
when we paint ball him,
but how the hell are we supposed
to track where he is?
Maybe you should have kept
the glasses the devil gave to you.
We don't need him.
We can do it on our own.
Guys, please, would you knock it off?
Can we just not talk
about demons and devils for 5 minutes?
I want to go in there.
I want to eat my gourmet mac and cheese,
and I want to hang out with my 2
favorite domestic gods, all right?
Just a minute.
- Nice threads.
- Thank you, I know.
Steve and Tony took me shopping.
It's like living next door
to queer eye for the straight guy.
- What's up with the power tools?
- I don't know.
Hey, right on time. Come on in.
All right!
- Nice place.
- Well, it's home.
- Hey, who needs a drink?
- We brought beer.
That was very thoughtful.
Give that to him.
- I'm going to go get the hors d'oeuvres.
- You guys make yourselves comfortable.
- You, bar.
- Bar. All right, I like it.
- Yeah, you clean up nice.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, my god.
You have an'89 glenfiddich
in a spode bottle?
Glenfiddich, yeah. You a fan?
Well, I mean, I knew it existed,
I just never thought I'd see
one up this close. It is beautiful.
And tasty-looking.
- Let me pour you a glass.
- OK.
You guys do a lot of charity work.
Well, we enjoy helping others.
It's good for the soul.
Yeah, I once gave a homeless guy
in front of the Work Bench
half my sandwich, so I can dig it.
- You remember that.
- I remember.
- Oh, that was kind of you.
- Fresh out of the oven.
Who wants pancetta-wrapped shrimp?
God, yes.
Help yourselves, there's plenty
more where that came from.
But save room for the mac and cheese.
This is better than my mom's cooking.
- Well, you know what emeril says...
- Pork fat rules.
Oh, man!
Don't worry about that. I've got
something that will take that right out.
Come with me to the kitchen.
You boys continue.
Tony spills food on himself all the time.
I have to buy these pens in bulk.
Hey, Steven, what are those things?
Those are, uh, power sanders.
We're putting up some crown molding.
- That's impressive.
- I'll you what's impressive.
Check out the security system in here.
I'm in home security,
so privacy is super important to us.
We got top of the line cameras all over,
and those motion detectors,
they protect us against
all the threats you can't see.
Really?
Yeah. And this shirt is done.
- Good as new.
- Thank you.
Dinner's served.
George C. Scott says,
you gotta dress brave to be brave, boys.
- That was general patton, you idiot.
- Same guy.
All right, let's do this.
Go time.
What the...
You gotta be kidding me.
- Morning, Ted.
- You see?
You see what I mean?
Yeah, you really are a morning person.
No, the cameras.
Somebody stole the cameras.
Are you serious?
- That's not funny.
- Yes, it is.
This is horrible.
Now I gotta buy cameras
to watch the cameras.
- Well, is anything else missing?
- I guess not.
- Well, you should be thankful.
- Thankful?
Thankful?
Whoa, what's with all the people?
What is... a charity run?
Yeah, right through
the soul's hunting ground.
You might as well just put
a freakin' bulls eye on my back.
All right, you know what, you know what?
You go kick invisible's ass. I got this.
Sock, how are you going to do that?
In the words of Gandalf the Great,
they shall not pass.
- It's "You shall not pass."
- Whatever, Ben, it's a movie, OK?
Whatever.
Go. Go, go, go.
- What was that?
- A squirrel.
- Is that him?
- Woodpecker.
You're not much of a nature guy,
are you?
I told you,
my parents were a little overprotective.
Well, what is it?
He's close.
Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
I'm sorry, stop!
I can't let you through here today.
We're with protect the trees.
We've got a permit.
Sorry, all permits have been revoked.
Give it, come on. Give it, give it.
- Excuse me?
- Give it!
We're just trying to protect the trees.
If you really want
to save and protect trees...
Show them some love.
Physically.
Come on out, Herbert! You coward!
That's right, yeah. Don't be shy.
Go on, pick a tree.
And just hug it, and don't ever let go.
All right, everybody, enjoy.
I'll be back in ten, OK?
OK.
Get out the vessel!
- What? I thought you had it!
- No, you had it! Do you remember?
No, I didn't!
Sock!
Hey, let him go!
Guys?
I'm coming!
Back off, Herbie!
Face, Ben, face!
Quick, throw me the vessel!
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Oh, man.
- We got him.
- That was disgusting.
I'm officially over smoothies.
OK, would somebody tell me
what's going on with my cameras?
Is this somebody's idea of a joke?
'Cause it's not funny.
Please tell me you're the genius
who stole Ted's security system.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
So... how's Cady?
She's good.
Good.
So you guys are good?
Andi, this is kind of weird.
I know, I know,
listen, she came to see me.
She did...
what did she want? What did she say?
You know, it's actually
not what she said, more how she said it.
What do you mean?
Listen, I know that your personal
life is your business,
but I really would be careful with Cady.
I just get a weird vibe,
and I thought you should know.
All right.
Hey, classy digs, Sammy.
I really like
what you've done with the place.
Look, I don't have time to play
host today. I gotta go meet Cady.
I sense tension in your voice.
Trouble in paradise?
You don't need to worry about it.
Hey, hey, come on now.
I told you before,
you're much more than just an employee.
I care about you.
All right, fine, you know what?
There is something.
Ah. See, I knew it, I knew it.
Go on. Lay it on me.
Get it off your chest.
You having trouble satisfying her?
No, I'm doing just fine, thank you.
Come on, I'm just trying
to have a little fun with you.
Don't be so sensitive.
Talk to me.
All right, listen. I'm gonna ask you
something, and for once...
I need you to give me a straight answer.
Sounds serious.
Will you tell me the truth?
All right.
Is Cady your daughter?
No.
- See, I don't believe you.
- And that's your problem.
If you really like this girl,
you shouldn't let anything
come between you.
Anyway, I just wanted
to congratulate you, man.
Looks like you caught
Herbie all by yourself.
I guess you really
don't need me all the time.
Well, thank you.
Hey, why don't you keep these
as a souvenir?
You never know when you're going
to need to see somebody's...
true colors.
Hey.
We need to talk.
I know. I know.
Listen, I know I've been distant,
and I'm...
and I'm sorry, but...
- The truth is...
- I don't want to hear it, Sam.
Look, I want to take some time.
I'm gonna go down to New Mexico.
I'm going to see my mom
for a couple of days.
I need a little space.
Wait, what? No.
- Things are good.
- Things are not good.
Sam, you don't return my phone calls.
You don't want to hang out with me.
You didn't even tell me you moved.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Look, I think, um,
I think this will be good for us.
We'll just take some time,
and we'll think things through.
We'll talk when I get back.
You know what, I never thought
I was a goat cheese person,
but this stuff isn't bad.
You should try the crap dip.
I'm telling you, Steve and Tony,
new idols. I love those guys.
- They're going in my top 8.
- That's quite nice of you.
- Hey, buddy... hey.
- Hey.
Can I get you something, or...?
- Yeah, crap dip?
- No, no, I'm good.
Oh, don't worry about it,
Sammy, come on.
Cady will come crawling back to you
in a week
when she realizes how much
she misses your man muscle.
Absolutely. It's just a hiatus.
Hey, have you guys...
have you guys seen my shirts?
Yes. Yes, Steve and Tony have them.
- They need to be laundered, right?
- That's right.
You guys think it's weird we replaced
our parents with a couple of gay dudes?
Weird, Sam? No. Genius.
Steve? Tony?
Guys?
Sometimes I think it'd be easier
just to wear a hat.
- What? No!
- Do you think I look fat?
No, you look great.
I think you've lost weight,
- 'cause the horns look bigger.
- Think I lost weight?
You look great. I'm really trying.
I know, you've been so disciplined,
and I really think...
What's a matter with you?
You look like you just saw a ghost.
No, worse. Demons.
What? Where?
Next door, Steve and Tony.
They're both demons.
Oh, my...
Thanks to Raceman for the transcript.
Subtitles made by the Bloc Team
For www.forom.com