Hospitals are hectic. But there's
a certain time every morning,
after the bedpans have been emptied,
that a calm washes over the place;
and you can't help but feel peaceful.
Holy Vishnu! Look, we've been working
together a while, could you not whistle at me?
You're right, Newbie, we have
been working together for a while.
Of course, I wouldn't know the exact
number of days unless I consulted
my Friends For Life calendar that I
keep taped inside my hope chest. Still...
I've learned to make Dr.
Cox's rants work for me.
I catch up on paperwork;
I look after patients...
Carla, can you check room
air pulse ox on Mrs. Shipp?
You got it, Bambi.
...I take care of those official
things that just have to get done.
You're a jerk.
You're a jerk!
...Long story short, there,
Molly, I will always whistle at you
like you're a blonde with big bombs and I'm a
construction worker just released from prison.
That clear?
Crystal!
Super!
Uh, listen, while I have you here
-- I'm applying for a fellowship,
and I could really use a letter of
recommendation. I was thinking that,
when you wrote it, instead of using a girl's
name you could refer to me as "Dr. Dorian."
I think it sounds a little more professional
and, frankly, each time you call me a girl's name,
I die a little inside.
Look, Janice, Denise, Tiffany
Amber Thiiiieeeessen! Lemme go ahead
and share a little something special with
you that I like to call Perry's Perspective.
One: If someone's standing in front
of me in line at the coffee shop and
they can't decide what they want in the
half an hour it took to get to the register,
I should be allowed to kill them. Two: I'm
fairly sure if they took porn off the internet,
there'd only be one website left, and
it'd be called "Bring back the porn!"
Three and most importantly of all: The
only way to be respected as a doctor
nay, respected as a man -- is to be an island;
you are born alone, you damn sure die alone.
Isn't that right, spike?
The point is, and you just might want to
jot this down: only the weak need help.
I should get that tattooed on my neck.
Good afternoon, Sacred Heart!
Hey! Your Chief of Medicine
just said good afternoon, people!
Dr. Jeffrey Steadman,
world-class suck-up.
Especially since the residency
director position opened up.
Dr. Cox, you know Dr. Steadman.
You're a doctor? Here,
all this time I had thought
that you were some kind of parasitic creature
who lived shoulder-deep inside Big Bob's colon.
If only, sir.
Well, I'm off to fluid rounds.
To fluid rounds!
Mm! In the new Sea World
dolphin show, Sean opens
with this impression of a blowfish that
will totally crack you guys up! Show them.
What the hell, that's not
funny! All he did was this
Hey, you're not doing it right.
It's never fun being the fifth wheel,
especially when one of those wheels
is Elliot's boyfriend. Still, I
had decided to take the high road.
Hey, J.D., is this regular? I
asked you to bring me a diet.
That is diet....
I don't understand! I'm so careful about
what I eat, I'm just keep putting on weight!
It's all the regular soda, Sean!
Enjoy.
Muahahahahahahaha!
All right, that's enough.
Scrubs 3x05 - My lucky night
Transcript : Michelle V.L. M.
Synchro : foromuser10 pour www.forom.com
So, I'm leaving the day after tomorrow,
to work on this project studying
the fishing industry's impact on Maui
dolphins.They're an endangered species;
if something isn't done soon they could
actually be wiped off the face of the earth.
Fascinating stuff, Sean.
Oh, hey -- I used
to date that girl.
Hello, boys.
Hi, I'm Elliot.
So, you guys used to date?
Nice to see you, Sean.
You, too, Mary...Angel...izabeth...?
Goodbye, boys....
You know, it's always awkward
when you run into an ex, isn't it?
Tell me about it. I don't
know how J.D. and Elliot do it.
Do what?
Oh, no! I've got to stop this! Kick him!
Oh!
You okay, baby?
Yeah....
How they have sex every year and
still manage to stay friends....
We haven't actually had a chance to
talk about that yet. But thank you.
Hey. C'mere a sec -- we
wanna do stuff to you.
Crap. The Janitor. And
he's with Sloppy Joe Guy!
Okay, just distract them before
they do whatever they've got planned!
We were thinkin'....
I've got a riddle for you!
This isn't how you said it would go.
Troy! We're listening.
Two coins add up to thirty cents
and one of them is not a nickel.
So what are they?
It's a riddle. You figure it out.
Troy, get your hat.
We're going to the bank.
Post-op diagnosis: acute cholecystitis.
Estimated blood loss: a
hundred and fifty CCs and...
"I don't know much / but I know I love you
ooh ooh ooh / And that may be all I need to"--
place a transfer to recovery
room awake and stable.
Hey, baby!
Notice anything different?
Your tongue went counter-clockwise!
No!
Green scrubs!
I'm covering for one
of the surgical nurses.
We could use the extra cash,
plus we get to work side-by-side
for the next two whole
days. Isn't that great!
So great!
Right?
So...
So, J.D. and I slept together.
It's not that big a deal.
You know Betty from work --
I see her every day, right?
How would you feel if I
told you we slept together?
Well, I'd be disturbed, Sean,
because Betty is a harp seal.
Yeah, but a harp seal who's
smart, funny, and totally gets me!
Oh, my God! Is anyone in
more hell than me right now?
Dude. We're goin' to the caf. so I
can tell all the boys about my date
with Strangely
Attractive Intern! You in?
I think that Turk is a
little more mature than that.
She's right.
But still, honey, what I think
you're missing here is that,
not only is she attractive,
but she's strangely attractive.
Guys, I can't go!
"I'll miss you" high-five!
I know, isn't that a coincidence!
Well, thank you for coming by!
I'm sure we're gonna be in
touch with you real soon.
Our nanny just walked out the door. Gimme a break,
she's experienced, she has great credentials....
Oh, no, no, she's got great,
huge, perky credentials.
She's out. Besides, she's too expensive.
About that, now, I've actually been thinking
about going after that residency director job.
Residency director?
Yeah-heah!
But Perry, you realize if you did that, you
would be taking a positive step in your life.
I know.
First place we made love?
Oh, gimme a break. We've
never..."made love".
Whew, it is you. I'm
so proud I could poo.
Seriously, though, it's great! And it's
a board decision, so I can help you out!
No, no!
Yes!
No! I'm serious, Jordan,
I don't believe in it.
I'd make you swear on a Bible, but I know how
contact with holy stuff makes your skin sizzle.
So just...promise me?
Oh, fine. No help.
Great.
Holy cow!
You're hired.
I cannot believe you're
still angry about this.
I'm not angry.
DIE! DIE, DIE, DIE!
ROT IN HELL!
I got it.
Okay, yes! J.D. and I work together!
But it's not like we're crazy close!
I mean, it's not like we have all these inside
jokes! And we definitely don't do this....
Good evening, Elliot! This is your
great aunt Sally. Are you there?
I have to get that.
I guess you're at Sean's. Hey,
good thing we're so crazy close,
or I wouldn't know how to
impersonate your aunt Sally!
By the way, I ran into Eye Patch this
morning -- said to tell you, "Honka! Honka!"
It's just an inside...joke.
Doctors!
Okay, come on: Two coins.
Thirty cents. No nickels.
Come on! You can do this! You
went to Harvard, for God's sake!
Relax! I figured it out.
Okay.... You gave me a
penny...and...what appears to be a button,
on which you've written
twenty-nine cents.
Can't we just kill him?
No, no, no... That's
what he wants us to do.
Just a real nice
helmet, there, princess.
Actually, it's not a
helmet, it's a Hairmet
it has extra room so you
don't mess up your hairdo.
Fair enough. I'm gonna go ahead
and write you a prescription
for two testicles; and you feel free
to get this filled out whenever you want
but right now, I'm goin' after
that residency director gig,
and you're joining me for a really
stupid board member meet-and-greet.
Will you write my recommendation?
Oh, hell no!
Goodbye.
Oh, gimme a break! I'll write
whatever you want! Just...we gotta go.
Okay, fine. Lemme just
fix my hair. Oh, wait!
I don't have to!
Oh, good God!
Scalpel.
Scalpel what?
Scalpel, please.
Here you go, baby. Sorry: Dr. Baby.
Shall we proceed, Dr. Baby?
You know, Buppy, this guy
looks a lot like your waxer!
The Todd says, What now?
Nothing! She meant her waxer,
'cause we're...We're working, guys.
No, no, no. I wanna hear this.
It's no big deal. I make Turk wax his
chest so he doesn't give me a rash.
Oh, okay. Does she also
make you wax your vagina?
Sterile high-five!
Are you even gonna talk to me?
I'm sorry, okay? I didn't
tell you that I slept with J.D.
and that was a mistake. And,
yes, we do talk all the time
and have all these inside jokes,
and he met my great aunt Sally
when she came to the hospital with my
demented great uncle who wears an eye patch
and goes "honka! honka!" when he poops.
And now you hate me.
Elliot, I don't hate you. Okay?
I'm not even that mad at you.
You're not?
No. How do I explain this...
You know when you have really
bad news to give to someone?
So you try to make them
look like the bad guy
by taking a small thing and
blowing it way out of proportion?
Totally. So glad that
has nothing to do with us!
Elliot, the trip that
I'm leaving on tomorrow...
it's actually a lot
longer than I let on.
What, like three days?
No....
Four days?
Six months.
Five days?
Love your Hairmet.
Love yours!
It was amazing to see how much
Dr. Cox actually wanted this job.
And how much he was willing
to put up with to get it!
So, the wife and I ended up
buying Egyptian cotton bed sheets!
Gee, you're too much. What's the
thread count on those bad boys?
I guess it was just amazing
to see how much he cared.
Gotta go.
Well, well, well.... Snip my
pickle and call me schlo-mo!
You're not actually applying
for residency director.
Oh, I don't know, Bob. Here, I
like to think I've accomplished
plenty of things much more difficult
than this. Why, just yesterday morning
I somehow managed to hack into your
voice-mail and change the outgoing message to,
"Hi, this is Big Bob. Why, I'm
not in right now but, at the beep,
leave your name and your penis size!"
Perry, have you ever wondered why
you've never risen above clinical staff
at this hospital? I mean, come on, pal,
who do you think the board listens to
concerning promotions around here?
Why don't I tell you after the beep?
Beeeeeeep.
Bob Kelso. Ten inches.
It's like a baguette!
Hi!
Hey.
I can't tell you how awesome it was just
getting to be with you today and watch you work.
I know, right!
Yeah!
But you know what? Schmitty heard that
Nurse Green's been dying to cover surgery,
and I said you wouldn't mind
if she took your place tomorrow.
Because, between me and you, Schmitty's
been trying to hit that for like a minute,
and I had to hook him
up! You understand, right?
Sure. I'm...I'm glad we
could help Schmitty hit that!
Yeah.
Relationships can be tricky. Especially
the ones that have barely begun.
Look, Elliot, I'm crazy about you, but I've
been going over this in my head all week.
I've been in a long-distance relationship
before, and it was a disaster.
I've reached the point where I honestly
believe a couple has a better chance
if they just cut the cord and
know that if it's meant to be,
fate will bring them
back together. You know?
Yeah.... Totally....
It's typical. Elliot's in a relationship,
so I can't stop thinking about her.
I just have to accept it and move on.
So I guess...
I guess this is goodbye.
Good what?
Look, this doesn't have to be
some huge sad thing, you know?
It's okay. They didn't see you.
What the...?
I know. It's just hard for me.
I'm gonna scrubs my hands and do the
"scrub my hands" dance! Scrub my--
Christopher. I know it's a complicated
procedure, but this afternoon
I want you to assist
me on a gastric bypass.
Gastric bypass?
I'm goin' to the show?
Well, you've earned it -- you really
turned it up a notch in surgery yesterday.
I don't know if you had a lucky charm in that
room, or what, but something was different.
Hey! Hey, Baby! What's up?
You know, I've been thinking:
that was a lot of fun working together.
And how long you been
thinking about that?
Ever since Dr. Wen offered me a gastric
bypass because I was so amazing yesterday,
and I realized you're the reason why.
Really?
Yeah! Yeah. It's just like in high
school -- I had this girlfriend
who annoyed the crap out of me, but every
time she came to one of my basketball games,
I played like crazy out of my mind because
all of a sudden I was playing for her.
I wanted to make her proud.
You understand what I'm saying?
You're saying I'm so annoying you can't
stand working with me for even two days,
but now that you have something
to gain, you want me back.
Exactly. Thank you!
I didn't hear an apology
anywhere in there!
All I heard was nonsense.
The truth is, you never asked me
how I felt about us working together.
Plus, you embarrassed me in front
of my co-workers. You were a pain.
You know what? Maybe I was a pain,
but do you know how many times
you're a pain and I just let it go?
Like when we're at home and you follow me
from room to room, even
when I go to the bathroom!
I like to be with you.
Pain!
Or how you've decided that me making
eye contact with you is my way of saying,
"Please, grab my breasts."
Don't.
Or that Aaron Neville impression
you've been working on?
I don't do an Aaron Neville impre...
Laverne!
But the biggest pain of all
is that you know I'd go into
that operating room with
you if you just apologized;
but you're too stubborn
to do that, aren't you.
I am now!
Tell me this, there, pippy:
Are you allergic to bee stings?
I don't know. Why?
Oh, it's just that it looks so painful
and possibly infected that I must flick it!
You know what? Okay? This
never would have happened
if my Hairmet hadn't gotten stolen at
your stupid suck-up fest last night!
Now, I took the liberty of writing
the recommendation you promised me.
All you have to do is sign
right below where it says,
"He makes me proud to be a doctor,"
and right above where it says,
"P.S. He ain't too hard
on the eyes, either!"
Tell you what, Newbie: This must
be a very...very proud day for ya.
You can't make me feel
guilty for asking for help.
That's just the way the world
works, okay? And you know what?
Most people actually like helping
out the people around them.
Take Carla, for instance! Don't you
think she'd do anything in the world
to help out Turk, no
matter what the situation?
Look! He didn't apologize! So
just back the hell off, okay!
He messes up and I'm the one who gets...
Still, I don't even believe that you
think asking for help makes you look weak.
I think you don't do it because you're
afraid of putting yourself out there.
And that's why you're
never gonna get anywhere.
Thank you for this!
Laverne, did you ever notice that in
hospitals, even though you're surrounded
by like hundreds of people, it's still
so easy to get lost in your own thoughts?
Have you been drinkin'?
What's wrong with me? Here I am trying
not to let fear ruin my life anymore,
and then Sean moves away and I don't
even have the guts to tell him how I feel.
how I feel. I mean, life's too
short not to go for it with Elliot.
Plus, now Sean's out of the
picture? Stop being such a chicken!
such a chicken! I know it's
a complicated procedure,
but I can do it without Carla
there! What am I so scared of?
what am I so scared of? That I might actually
get this job, and have no one to blame it
on if I fail? Good Lord, I'm
pathetic! When was the last time...
when was the last time he ever apologized
for anything? I wanna help him, I do,
but in a lot of ways I guess
I'm as stubborn as he is.
I wish I could make some sense out of...
I wish I could make some sense out
of this. Thirty cents, to be exact.
Damn riddle! Easy,
Janitor; you'll get this.
Sean! Sean!
Sorry!
No problem, little lady! I've never
left a soul behind! Got your ticket?
No. No, I just
I just have to talk about
Hello.
Elliot?
Sean! Sean! Okay.... Look, I know
you hate long-distance relationships,
but six months is nothing! I mean, it'll be
hard and we'd be going a long time without sex,
but I can totally go that long
without sex! Sean, I am a sex camel!
Look, the point is I'm not ready
for this relationship to end;
so, even if you break my heart right
now, it's okay, because I'd regret it more
if I didn't take this
shot. So, what do you say?
Hey. We solved your dumb game.
We been to the libary!
"-brary," Troy. "Li-BRAR-y."
Anyway, "What two coins, when you put 'em together,
makes thirty cents and one
of them isn't a nickel?"
A penny and...a 1972 dime with a Roosevelt
imperfection, today worth exactly twenty-nine cents.
Nope, nope, nope. The correct
answer is: A quarter and a nickel.
No. Because you said
one of 'em isn't a nickel.
Right. The other one is.
You lied to me.
No. It's a riddle.
Ooh! Your face is red!
Like a strawbrerry!
Pride's a funny thing...
Don't have kids.
So, shall we all just agree that Dr. Steadman is our
new residency director and get the hell out of here?
If anyone wants to stop by my condo
to celebrate, my husband made sangria!
Howdy, fellas. don't ya dare get up,
I don't want to see any broken hips.
A lot of times, pride can
be pretty hard to swallow.
Would you please help me?
So! I think we should make
Perry residency director.
You honestly think the board would
pick him because you had his love-baby?
Oh, I don't know.... Of course,
if they don't, I'm gonna bitch
and moan about it until
these nice gentlemen are dead.
All those in favor of Dr. Cox?
So I guess this pretty much
makes me your bitch now.
Oh, Perry, you always were.
Oh, golly, God!
But still, in a good relationship,
pride never gets in the way.
Christopher, you okay?
You look a little nervous.
He'll be fine.
Carla! Look, I...
You can tell me later.
Ohh...M'kay. Let's do this! Scalpel!
Scalpel what?
As for me, even if I wanted to put my
pride on the line and go tell Elliot
how I feel, I can't --
I have to work tonight.
Say, Newbie, seeing as you are
partially responsible for me being
the new residency director, I'm gonna go
ahead and give you the rest of the night off.
I don't know, it's just kind of
my own personal way of saying...
I can't actually stand
the sight of you. Ha!
I still don't think I should go see her.
Doctors Leeve and Winnerback, please
report to the E.R. Leeve and Winnerback.
Here, buddy. Baby wasn't mine.
What the hell...?
It's a riddle! Two guys destroyed
your bike with a crowbar and a bat.
One of 'em wasn't me!
Oh, J.D.!
Elliot, there's something
I have to tell you.
Hey, buddy!
Sean's taking a later
flight to Sea World because he decided
to make this long-distance thing work!
I'm so happy, I can't stop crying!
Oh, those are nice!
Ohh, these? I thought Elliot would be sad
with you guys splitting up, so I just wanted to....
Oh, that's so sweet! You can
just put them next to Sean's.
Yeah.
Okay.... I'm not sure they....
You okay?
Yeah...
Not sure they can...reach
the water, but...
J.D.?
www.tvsubtitles.net