Got somthing on your face...
oh oh what?
Me.
my god I feel like such a hoebag
but I'm still glad I did it
I do declare spending special
relationary time with my girlfriend...
makes me happier then a
bullfrog in a beetle bin
Why are you talking like that?
Cause I'm smitten with my
girlfriend lady...
and this is my smitten voice
Why? What voice do you use
when you're smitten
My normal voice
You know what? You hide it well
but you're a very strange person
M'aam
How'd I do...
17 that's impressive...
but I'm going to kick your arse...
and, time me
What's going on seabizzle?
We're seeing who can last the
longest in Mr Silar's room
He has a fungal infection under the
fat flaps in his stomash
It smells like the time I put Izzy's
doo-doo diaper in the microwave.
you guys are playing smelly-belly
Time?
16 seconds.
Come on - I win
See that's what I'm talking about...
that's how it goes when you fight me
Hold On Turk Let's
not declare victory...
until we give a shot
to Dr John Dorian...
and his nostrils of steel
Your nose can't handle smells
of that magnitude
Make some room...
uh-huh, on the clock uh-huh...
you have got to be kidding me...
that is the most disgusting thing
I have ever smelt...
and a sugar free latte for...
the winner
Victory tastes delicious
You guys aren't even friends...
why do you spend so much time
competing over every thing...
because we're men...
and that's what men do...
now a quick look to Turk...
to see if that is what men do
Huh whatta you know...
don't forget I crushed you in
find the vein in the junkie...
yeah but I beat you good at gossball
That's nothing yesterday
I won fee muffins for life...
by guessing how many coffee beans...
there were in that there jar
Actually they had a recount...
and you came in second
What?
Who came in first?
#You know the muffin man
the muffin man#
If anyone need me I'll
be in my office...
going to town on these bad boys...
why are you guys obsessed...
with reliving everything you've won
Because we're winners...
and that's what winners do...
back to Turk for confirmation...
damn it.
if you'd ever won anything...
you'd know what we're talking about
Oh I've won something Perry
We threw our nerd farther then yours
Suck It Bitch
Guys I think their
nerd is unconscious...
we should probably roll him over
That's the moment I realised
I wanted to be a doctor
Scrubs - Season 7 Episode 6
My Number One Doctor
Subtitles by STS
Every doctor has their own way
of dealing with patients
Turk was all about efficiency
Why are you standing on a chair?
Because from this spot I can see
into 4 rooms...
without actually going in...
check it
Patients of Doctor Turk...
how are we?
OK...
all good
Fine...
muffled answer...
guy had some tongue surgery...
he's actually OK though
Elliot referred a more
personal approach
Shannon what's happening girlfriend?
yeah I know I cant pull off
calling someone girlfriend...
but she likes it so
I do can't help it
Shannon's back...
it's been so great
getting to know her...
see that's the great thing
about being in private practice
You get to treat the same patients
all the time...
oh come on you guys...
[whispers] shhh
people are sleeping here...
[whispers] well I guess you
think it's so funny...
[speaks normally] Why am I whispering...
listen Barbie, I'd love to take
credit for this idea...
but it was all Big Bobby Kelso...
ah come on heck
Quick announcement
I have signed sacred heart...
up for website called
Rate your Doctor...
where patients can evaluate
and score their doctors
I think it's going to lead to a better
patient care...
and if along the way...
you all become paranoid
and overly competitive...
happy birthday to me
Dr Kelso I became a doctor
to save lives...
heal wounds...
and occasionally drop the M.D. Bomb...
to pull hot tail in bars...
you know what else works?
Cosmonaut. Try it thank me later
Noted
Oh I reckon my lady is as purty...
as a porcupine on roller skates...
that doesn't even make sense
That's what we smitten folk
call a metaphor...
you young lady...
have a head that's as empty as...
a whipperwheel in a tub of moonshine...
there you go...
he's out of his freaking mind...
how does that woman go out with him?
Well I would say that love is blind...
but we both know that isn't true...
my love for Enid falls
a percentage point...
with every pound she gains
Since our wedding day
I am 136% less in love with her...
you really going to comment
on your wife's weight...
when you have muffins
stuffed down your pants
I like them warm
So you're experiencing...
vomiting and shortness of breath...
neither of which are consistant
with your ALS...
[JD] It's hard to be comfortable...
around terminal patients...
but Shannon made it easy
So how's the ALS progressing
Oh it's been a blast...
her legs are fully paralysed...
and her arms are on their way
That does sound fun...
yeah but you know what
I think I'm ready for all this...
said goodbye to all my friends...
hell I even had my funeral already...
she looked so beautiful in her casket
I'm sure you did
I wasn't in a casket
I know that...
come on who would do that...
except for vampires
I told you he was gullible
Shannon I hate to leave...
but I really want to get these down
the lab for testing
OK
I can stay...
so you went to your own funeral huh...
people sad enough for you?
most of them...
and anyone that wasn't crying
got a talking to
You should have invited me
I can cry on cue...
say dead puppies 'dead puppies'
Connecting with patients...
always come easier to me
then it did to some others
Have a good day Mr Woolmer
Wow... you actually learned
your patients name
If you don't kill them
in the operating room...
you can take them out dancing
I doubt it
I'm amputating his foot later...
but he's still going to give me
a good review...
you see we're D.B.F.Fs Huh?
Diabetic best friends forever...
you don't usually bond
with your patients
You're not going to change who
you are as a doctor...
to get good ratings are you?
Hell to the no
Are you?
{laughs] oh please.
So you're declining chemo...
because wikipedia says
the raw food diet...
reverses the effects of bone cancer
Well - Hey any info you have...
that I can pass on to
my other patients...
would just be super and by-the-by...
while you're on your computer...
perhaps you could jump over to a
site called rateyourdoc. org...
patients of Doctor Turk...
would you like any ono-on-one time...
with your surgeon
Please. Sure.
Yeah. Love to.
A private consultation
with my surgeon...
would be very much appreciated
thank you
Damn someone's done
their healing too fast
There, I gave you 5 stars
Thank you and now I have
to take your laptop from you...
as I've deemed you just too
damn stupid to use it.
You see those bell peppers
that you're munching
They're going to do a
truckload of jack...
against the cancer raging
inside of your body...
of course I've only been a doctor
for some twenty years...
and the person who wrote...
that wikipedia entry also authored...
the Battlestar Galactica
episode guide...
so what the heck do I know...
but if you feel like living page me...
so 'Lady' is an unusual name
Oh tell me about it
I was conceived after my parents...
saw the movie 'Lady and the Tramp'
That's so sweet yeah
Oh gotta go and meet my guy out front
Nice meeting you Carla
Sir you'll never believe this...
'Lady' is normal
I'm sorry did you
also win free muffins for life
I didn't think so
Now let me read the final
Harry Potter novel in peace...
everyone's already read that...
yes but if anyone divulges
any details to me...
what happens Murphy?
You draw Harry Potter Glasses
on their face...
in permanent marker That's right
Now I don't give a hoot...
about the janitor and his gal pal OK...
so shove off
You wouldn't dare draw on me...
and I already know if Harry...
lives or dies at the end
So Lady's completely normal huh?
Can you believe that?
HI Elliot wassup?
Good News
Your symptoms aren't ALS related
you just took to many baclofens...
you probably just mixed up your meds...
[JD] In a hospital little mysteries...
get solved every day
You look nice
I'm just glad to get out of that uni
and into my regular clothes.
That's why she likes him...
he's pretending to be normal...
[shouts] NO WAY.
too much?
mmm-huh...
[JD] Sometimes the answers right
in front of your face...
you gotta be kidding me
there has to be an error...
are you guys still looking
at that stupid website?
I told you those ratings
are meaningle.......
I'm number 1
The number 1 doctor yes yes...
number 1 number 1
I gotta make a big phone call...
call mommy...
and sometime you never could
have seen it coming
You gotta be more careful with
your medications
I mean the Baclofens aren't so bad...
but if you took too
many benzodiazepines
You could have died...
then that's definately what I'll
do next time
Grape?
Why would you purposefully overdose?
You know the answer to that
I've said my goodbyes...
and soon I won't be able to
move my arms...
or even speak
I am literally going to die...
entombed in this body...
a lifeless burden to Gayle...
who's Gayle?
My home care nurse
I know she's sweet but
she's a little silly for my taste
Oh God she flying.
how is she getting her scarf
to blow like that
I get to go next
Elliot
I want things to end on my terms...
and in a few months
I won't even be able to do that
Why are you telling me all of this?
I mean this goes against
everything I stand for
Shannon I'm your doctor
I know...
but you're also my friend
One blueberry please...
because i can
So.. What do you want to do tonight?
Well it's Friday which is date night
So perhaps we should see a movie...
and then get some ice cream...
while we walk and hold hands
I vote Yes
What the hell are you doing?
Khaki?
You never wear khaki
My uniform is khaki
Your uniform is blue...
no yes...
leave me alone...
yeah right
Are you coming?
well I might as well
Miriam here has already ruined
the book for me
The rate your doc website...
also had a comments section
Oh come on
what's up with Dr Cox's hair?
One week he's bald The next week he...
looks like Shirley Temple
signed Michelle M.
Oh it's called rate your 'doc'. org
I'm on a completely different
more awesome site
See Woah.
Can I borrow your laptop
Just for a second please Thank you
Yep.
Still number one
Now to put the cursor back...
on Doctor Turk who's lower down...
on the ranking list scrolling down...
scrolling scrolling fake watch
Scrolling
There he is...
all the way at the bottom
right above Dr Murphy here
How can I be last?
All my patients are dead
Doug, do you remember that guy
you put in the morgue drawer?
Turns out he was just heavily sedated
Oh yeah you're right...
all the comments are from him
My ALS patient just told me...
she tried to kill herself
Shannon?
What are you going to do?
Well Barbie you have two choices...
you can either tell on her
or look the other way
Now me I'd go ahead and crank up
the Moody Blues...
and suffocate her with a pillow
cause I'm a helper...
as always thank you...
welcome.
Someone named Coco Blasco wrote...
that she's sick of me saying...
'That's what I'm talking about'
but sometimes it is
what I'm talking about
Tell me this...
do you like her?
Well I've never met
her before but nah...
in fact I may hate her
I'm talking about Lady...
if you like her...
you can't keep lying to her
about who you are
Hogwash Lie forever...
it's the natural form
of communication...
between men and women
Hell Enid still thinks it's
too snowy to go outside
I spray the windows
with shaving cream...
to keep her out of the yard
her wheelchair tears up the grass
Until you let Lady know the real you...
your relationship is not real
and it's going to end...
but I want it to end
That's his sad voice
I can't lose to JD
I don't care what it takes
I thought he was your best friend
Winning is way more
important then friendship...
my gran gran taught me that...
his patients love him
how do we undo that...
after you're done rating me
on rateyourdoc. org...
go to my website the toddtime. com...
be sure to check out the
'Tranny Todd' feature
It lets you see what the big dog
looks like with girl parts
M'aam the key to a speedy recovery...
is less moaning more boning...
as sure as my name is
Doctor John Dorian...
that's what I'm talking about
I said it again yeah
Ah damn
Hey
I've been looking for you...
you can't imagine what it's like
to know you're going to be...
trapped in your own body...
just waiting for your misery to end
Elliot you can't let this girl do
this again...
you gotta tell Gayle
so she can police it...
but may be dying is
the right choice for her...
but i don't think it's
the right choice for you...
you know as doctors
sometime we have to...
protect ourselves first
I know you better than anybody...
you believe in the sanctity of life...
if you let this girl kill herself...
it's going to haunt you forever
I can handle it...
you remember when you were
treating that teenager...
and you broke his i-pod...
you felt so guilty you let
him take you to prom...
yeah but I left early
and I barely put out
I just don't want you to get hurt...
you're right
I'll tell Gayle
Thanks...
do you know I'm the number one
doctor in the hospital...
yes JD I got all......
Oh hi are we going out?
what's with the jumpsuit?
Well first of all
if we're going to make it...
not a jumpsuit shirt, belt, pants...
oh O.K.
Secondly I think it's time you knew
the real me...
all right here we go
I'm not like normal people
I don't have super powers
but I'm working on it...
for instance watch me move this pen...
it worked at home I don't know why...
maybe my table is slanted...
anyway in my spare time
I also enjoy stuffing animals...
usually with other animals...
for instance a badger
will hold five squirrels...
a squirrel will hold most of a cat...
a mouse will hold a shrew and a vole...
you get the idea circle of life
I have broken the sound barrier...
but you must never ask me how
I don't believe in the moon
I think it's just the back of the sun
Huh I love a good train wreck...
furthermore, I think if you look
closely at...
stop it you
she doesn't know you're joking...
oh he's joking
Thank God...
and so the lying begins
You big joker...
go change and I'll meet you outside...
what just happened?
did I just blackout?
did the pen move?
you have to dole out your crazy
in little pieces...
you can't do it all at once...
oh, all right
Hey watta say 23?
Oh my God another new nickname...
but what does it mean?
play it cool 23
you'll find out eventually...
that's what they call me...
why do they call me that?
It's your new website rating
What?
How did I drop so low?
you know after I fix
that gall bladder...
you might want me to do something
about those flat boobies
All I wanted to do was
win at something...
for once and when I finally do...
you have to go and...
Excuse me
but do you really want me here...
for a lecture that I'm not going
to feel the least bit guilty about...
dismissed...
him I expect this from but you...
you're my closest friend
In college we shared a toothbrush
I was not aware of that we did...
look, is there anything I can do
to make it up to you
Here you go buddy...
your very own unicorn...
she's glorious
Turk My Bad...
is there anything I can do
to make it up to you
Here's your Unicorn
Turk, she's beautiful
Oh look at her mane
Turk
I gotta tell ya Unicorns aren't real...
stop it they're not real...
there's nothing you can do...
what if I let you beat
me in basketball...
while the nurses watch?
Can we yell white lightning
everytime I make a basket...
we always do
Gayle's bringing the cat around
so I guess this is......
Don't You know I hate the G word
Elliot thank you for everything...
you've been an amazing friend to me
White Lightning
Dude, enough practise lay-ups
I'm getting hoarse
White Lightning...
are you even listening to me?
[JD] when you have something you
have to get off your chest
There are a couple of things you can do
You can test the water...
check this out
I found it at a garage sale
Oh my God that is disgusting
Yeah I know I think so too
I just wanted to make sure
we were on the same page...
[JD] Or you can come completely clean
I talked to Kelso about the whole
Todd thing...
and you're back at number 1
That's what I'm talking about
I figure as you can't say it anymore
maybe I can have it
No...
[JD] of course if you're really
the number one doctor...
you might end up
keeping things to yourself
Is there anything else I need to know?
No Nothing else...
[JD} Even if it will haunt you forever
Subtitles by STS