Since the geriatric wing was being remodeled,
Turk were herding old people
to their new rooms.
That's a closet, mr. Jenkins.
Come on, mr. Benedetti, you're only a few thousand tiny steps away.
JD, we need to find a way to
move these gomers faster.
All aboard! The love train.
That was a fun fantasy, I wish it didn't have to end.
Hey...
That's a nice jacket, Ted.
- What is it, wool?
- It's a poly-nylon blend
do you really like it?
No. Bathroom's just put of paper towels.
I know it's confusing, but these
are your new rooms, ok?
Please, try to stay put. Great.
Bye-bye.
Since Elliot revealed that Dr.Kelso was 65,
the board was forcing him
to retire in a few weeks.
This is even worse than when they decided
female staffers couldn't
wear open-toed shoes!
Ob-obviously, this is much worse...
but that sucked too.
I feel like I've given my life to this
place and got nothing in return.
I mean, is there an MRI machine
in my basement? Maybe.
I guess I just wanted to end my
career on my own terms, you know?
- Oh...
- We gotta help him save his job.
- You guys are gonna help, right?
- Of course.
First we gotta handle something.
Dr. Cox had a patient that he couldn't
be able to diagnoaveva unse in two years.
And he went back again.
Look, Alex, I'm afraid I still don't
know what's causing all of this,
so I'm gonna go ahead and treat your
heart palpitations with betablockers.
Turk and I couldn't resist play the
little game called "poke the bear".
Turk, yesterday I had this patient
I just could not diagnose.
Wow, you must have felt like a real jackass.
I did feel like a jackass, but then I was
able to figure out what was wrong with him,
because I'm not a jackass, I'm a good doctor.
Ok, now just stay calm, so he
doesn't know what you're up to.
Oh, no, Turk's breaking!
Quick, distract the bear with a casual greeting!
Oh, hey Dr. Cox, how are things?
My God, that was amazing. I never
felt so alive in my whole life.
My heart stopped for a second.
- We made it. I love you, man.
- I love you too.
You smell like an athlete.
- I need one of those.
- A hug?
No, a black friend.
I think it would make me much cooler.
I should be offended, but he's right.
Why are you so gloomy?
I thought you'd be super-psyed that
Kelso's being forced out of his job.
Dr. Kelso's being forced out?
I did not know that.
Will you excuse me for a moment?
I'm free! I'm free! I'm beautiful and I'm free!
I'm free! Give me some sugar!
It's finally over! I'm free!
Holy cow! Buddy, are you all right?
Ted?
Are you not talking 'cause your
mouth is filling up with blood?
You're gonna pass out, aren't you?
Oh, boy there he goes.
Yipes!
Itasa Scrubs Team Presents
Scrubs Season 07 Episode 09
" My Dumb Luck"
Transcript: gi0v3, Supersimo, Mezzi, Twilighter, JDsClone, Teorouge
Revision and synch: gi0v3
::Italian Subs Addicted::
[www.italiansubs.net]
At certain times in our lives,
we all get introspective.
Taking it all in, too?
Why don't you have a seat, son?
Actually, sir, uhm, my shift is
bout to start, so I should...
Son, I don't care if the cure for cancer was laughter
and you had Nipsey Russell
in your backpack. Parking!
I'm gonna get all nostalgic, crap.
What's that strange red puddle
loosing towards us?
Oh, that's just Ted's blood.
Apparently he bit of a chunk of his tongue.
Anyway, when I started here, I was only 26.
Aaaaand done!
- 23 stitches.
- Here's some painkillers.
I want to take one of those
every four hours, ok?
No trying to talk.
I keep thinking about Kelso.
He reminds me
of my grandpa.
He's pervy, demeaning,
and a tinsy bit racist,
but you crave his love anyway,
because he smells like peppermint.
I've always respected Kelso.
He's got a though job.
And I bet deep down, everybody here
want us to help him keep it.
Ted, no talking.
We do know a board member.
Why would anyone
wanna save Kelso's job ?
- For starters... - You know what?
I don't honestly care one way or the other.
- About Kelso?
- Or about anything.
But then again, you two are
young enough and attractive enough
that I'm not angry when people assume
we're friends, so what the hell?
Here's what you do.
Board members hate confrontation.
There's a board meeting tonight.
Just show up at the hospital, with all the
movers and shakers in support of Kelso,
They'll cave.
All right.
Ok. I'll support Kelso.
But in return,
I want you to put me in a full body
cast and take me to the airport.
- I'll explain later.
- Why would we do that?
Because I'm the bigger's mover/shaker
in this dump. Come on.
You handle this.
And be nice.
All right. Are you familiar
with the term "delusions of grandeur"?
I believe I coined that term.
look, I'm a simple, unassuming janitor
who can control people's
actions with his mind.
Observe.
Explode!
If that would have worked, it would
have freaked you out. You'd loved it!
Fall.
Hello?
I think this might be the thousandth time
I've peed in a cup for you, doc.
Well, then, to us.
- Hard to celebrate?
- Yeah.
I got it.
Jeez Louise, can you believe
how many files I have on this guy?
The only way I've been able to
bind them together was with this bi-bond.
- Do you hang on that for a second, will you?
- Sure.
I don't think he realized
we were making fun of him earlier.
Say, what's up
your arm?
Oh, boy.
I'm sorry, dude,
that was awesome.
Dr Cox we're sorry.
Dont' worry tough. Turk and I are
gonna help you diagnose this patient.
That's terrific,
because I'm so darn lost,
I just keep procrastinating.
I check my emails,
I pick up a copy of "House weekly"
to see which of my favorite celebs
is bringing back the fedora.
It's Johnny Depp,
by the way.
- He doesn't think we could help.
- I look good in a fedora.
Turk, focus. We're being insulted.
I'm tired of your not focusing when
someone insults us. It ends up all on me.
Hey, if you really wanna be useful
make like an orderly and take
that urine sample down to the lab.
Follow me.
Money, right?
How does it have anything
to do with what Dr. Cox said?
What did Dr. Cox say?
Good afternoon, Mr. Mandelbaum.
Uhm, shouldn't we stop him?
Nah, the security guard
will keep him out of traffic.
You know,
when I was an intern,
they made us work 60 hours shifts.
Yeah, quite a few colleagues got
drummed out because they couldn't cope.
The rest of us were so sleep-deprived
we could barely manage to stay sane.
I'll never forget the day we caught
Seth Finkel gently cradling a cadaver head
which he swore belonged
to his ex-girlfriend, Millie.
A year later Seth actually did kill Millie.
Ironically, Millie donated
her body to science
and that spring, we caught another
intern cradling her dead head.
Life's little cycles.
Oh, boy, that was almost...40 years ago.
Sir!
Honk!
Honk, honk!
Honk honk honk!
You tell her, Mandelbaum!
Hey, slick.
Will you come to the board
meeting tonight to help Dr. Kelso?
Now why on Earth would I do that?
For some reason she thinks if you call
a man "slick" he'll do anything for you.
It also works on lesbians, so.
Come on!
You know that deep down inside, you're
okay with Kelso running this place.
Deep down I hate Bob Kelso
and wish he would die painfully.
Here's the research you wanted.
Thanks, slick.
Look, Kelso's a pain in the ass.
You know what I say:
Bring on the next pain in the ass.
Hermione!
- Have you seen Mr. McRae's urine test?
- I'm on, slick.
You don't remember where
you left that cup of pee, do ya?
No clue. We have to find
it or he's gonna kill us.
Us? Try you, he's not killing me!
Why is it gettin' harder to...walk?
Uh-oh.
Dude!
That was lucky!
So, have you killed anyone yet?
What? No.
Well, you will.
Super!
It's a rite of passage for doctors.
If you're lucky, it'll be a
patient who's on his way out anyway.
My first kill was a 19-year-old girl.
She came in with severe abdominal pain.
I thought it was appendicitis.
Turned out,
she was preagnant and didn't know it.
It was ectopic and she
was bleeding internally.
I should have checked for that.
But by the time I discovered
my mistake it was too late.
Sometimes I look at this whole hospital
I actually see the faces
of all the patients I've lost.
- Boogaboogabooga!
-Aaaah!
Priceless.
But I do see them sometimes.
We don't need Dr. Cox.
You know, we'll round up everyone else,
and not just the doctors,
we'll get all the
non-medical personal too.
Good idea! Ted!
Who would you say is the
leader of the support staff?
Well well...
Look who has come crawling back,
through the desert of shame,
to the oasis of hope.
Begging for just one sip,
of cool Janitor forgiveness. Well...
the answer's no.
- Please, Janitor!
- All right, I'm in.
Dog gone it, I cannot resist
that adorable mug of yours.
I'd have to throw a cup of acid on it,
to keep it from having power over me.
Ok, so we just have to
round up everyone else.
That should be easy.
That was impossible.
Where did I leave that stupid pee?
- Dude, retrace your steps.
- Ok, I remember we were walking this way,
and you had to stop Mrs. Butler from
wandering out of her room again.
Oh, no! Mrs. Butler...
Back in here.
- Then I got paged to surgery.
- Right!
And I came with you to cheer
you on, and I hold your fedora.
And then we went out
to the ramp to celebrate.
- There it is.
- Why would it turn purple?
You know,
those 2 reminds me of a couple
of dogs I had when I was a boy.
JoJo and Spike.
One day JoJo got his head stuck
in the mailbox,
and Spike went over to try to
help him and got his head
wedged in there too and they both suffocated.
They were extremely dumb animals.
But close.
Sir, my shift started 2 hours ago,
I should really go.
You know, there are some things I sure
as hell will not miss about this place,
like how more often than not,
medical skills didn't  matter.
It all comes down to dumb luck.
- Ok, I'm googling "purple pee".
- Google that bitch!
That's it!
We left it in the sun!
If urine exposed to U.V.
light turns purple,
it's a sign of a rare genetic disorder
called "Acute Intermittent Porphyria".
Sintoms includes bloating,
high blood pressure,
seizures... Cox's patient
has all of those.
We figured it out.
Ah ah! 1, 2, 3!
- In his faaaaaaaaace!
...or how you can often have
more questions than answers.
I just don't understand why no one
will help us save Kelso's job...
That's easy. Word get out that
he wants Kelso gone.
And no one wants to cross him
'cause he's a scary guy.
Now, I'm not scared of him,
but that's because... I'm magic.
- Is he dancing?
- No, no.
Or how every day in this place
is made up of little battles.
Or how around here once the ball starts
rolling there's not much you can do to...
Sorry, Sir, did you have another?
Or how around here, once the ball starts rolling
there's not much you can do to stop it.
He's outta here.
Or how patients don't appreciate
their doctors anymore.
Or how medical skills doesn't matter,
it's all just a dumb luck.
Oh, you already said that one, sir.
Sounds my blood sugar is low, and unless you have
a candy bar in that gay little napsack of yours, shut it!
Or how if you get to the cafeteria past 5,
they're always out of pies.
Dammit!
What do you buy, like one
pie for the whole hospital?
You ask him, if I do that he'll say something
mean over to hurt my feelings.
We want you to reconsider helping Kelso.
Could I get a "Hell, no!"
from any random doctor?
- Hell, no!
- Thank you, whomever.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I've got to go
far, far away from annoying people.
Especially whiny childless blondes
with stainded-coffee teeth.
Oh, look at that,
he got you anyway.
What the hell is this?
What's the occasion? Did Barbie finally
wax her tiny annoying mustache?
Stop saying mean things about me!
I'm not even talking to you!
We diagnosed your patient, buddy.
He's got acute intermittent porphyria.
- What?
- If it makes you feel any better,
it did almost take us 3 hours.
Oh, for the love of God.
1985 was going to be my year.
Economics was in folk swing,
Enid's implants
hadn't exploded yet.
And best of all, they made me chief
of medicine, so I was the king, right?
Wrongo.
I realized fast that in order
to keep this whole place going,
I had to make one unpopular
decision after another.
Regardless of who hated me for it.
And that was a lonely realization, son.
And here it comes
my biggest fan.
Bob, there is finally a diagnosis on Mr.
McCray. He has acute intermittent porphyria.
Now his insurance company
wants him discharged immediately,
I'd like to fudge the
paperwork a little bit,
keep him around longer and teach
him how to manage his desease.
- No.
- I realize that your heart is made up
mostly of muffin bits, the souls of little babies,
and the dental grip you swallow every
time you suck your teeth to get out
the muffin bits and baby
souls stuck in there, but
What do you care? You're not
being in around anymore!
Dammit, I'm still chief! Now,
if you wanna fusìdge the paperwork,
I want a promise from you
that you will publish a paper
on the case. Will you?
Deal.
He'll never publish a paper on that case.
He knows just ho to play me.
Sure, he likes to pretend that
I win more than he does, but
he walks away victorious more often than not.
There's got to be a way to
get Dr. Cox to change his mind.
Perry does not sway so easily.
Unlike your husband, who'll probably
cave if you'd show him your cans.
Don't even have to show him both.
Left one's cooler.
- Looks like a sea lion's face.
- It does. Turk drew it for me.
Come on, Jordan, think.
There's got to be a way.
Oh, my God. Enough.
You know, there might be something
I could do to change his mind.
So here's the truth:
I was only able to diagnose your patient
when I left his urine outside in the sun,
where it turned purple.
Then I googled "purple pee", and
the internet gave me the answer.
The universe makes sense again.
But, please don't think this is going to
make me change my mind about Kelso.
What if I was to sweeten the deal
with a sketch of Carla's boob?
That's an otter!
Even though I knew it was coming, eventually,
it still shocked me when the board said
I had to leave Sacred Heart.
But you know that, don't don't you?
You've been sitting here
listening to me yap all day.
By the way, what's your name, son?
Boone, Sir.
My God, what a ridiculous name.
Boone. Boone.
My name is Boone.
Well, I guess you should go, Boone.
Really?
Thank you, Sir.
So... So you think my next 20 years
here will be a nightmare?
No.
I think you'll love it.
I have news, Mr. McRae.
You have acute intermittent porphiria.
Now, while that is manageble,
I'm afraid...
There is no cure.
And then we got a respond that
we didn't  expect.
Oh, man. I couldn't be happier.
Excuse me?
Just knowing what it is, makes it
so much easier to deal with, you know?
And then I saw something click in Dr. Cox.
What Mr. Mc Rae was saying
is that the enemy you know
is always better then the one you don't.
The board meeting is about to start.
It's just the three of you?
I'll probably say a few words as well.
Mostly about the potential of
mind control in modern medicine.
Oh, this should go well.
Wait! There's more people coming!
When?
Right now. Love Train!
- Well, you could have made a bigger entrance.
- Let's get this over, before I puke.
Well, Bob, your employees
really stood by you.
- They pointed out to the board that...
- Hey.
Well, you run a tight ship,and
actually we'd like you to stay on.
Girls, thank you for saving my job.
The one thing I wanted was to end things
on my own terms, and since you're letting me,
you can shove it up your ass, Rodney.
I'm out of here.
"Little Victories"
by Matt Nathanson.
I'm taking this with me, dammit.
Thanks for everything, Ted.
Sincerely.
You're welcome, sir.
I'm wondering if he even cared
about this place at all.
Yeah.
He did.
::Italian Subs Addicted::
[www.italiansubs.net]