Jonah?
What's the problem, Pete?
Mitchell got arrested.
What for?
Well, we grabbed a couple horses
you know, from one of those ranches
outside of town and Mitchell got caught.
Well... Mitchell is an idiot.
But the thing is...
the ranch that we were at,
it belonged to Johnston Green.
The mayor's wife kind of got
knocked around a little bit.
Not bad, though. Nothing bad.
But... wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Who's idea was it, yours or his?
It was his.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
Apology accepted.
She'll be coming 'round
the mountain when she comes
- She'll be coming 'round...
- Knock it off, Mitchell.
Where's Jake?
You better go get him,
'cause when Jonah comes for me,
he's gonna want to have a little
conversation with Jake.
If he has to go looking for him
it's going to make things a whole lot worse.
Whatever.
Just keep it down in here, all right?
Better tell him to get ready.
In fact...
you all better get ready.
Right.
Mallo Cups.
- That's what they were called.
- God, I love those.
- The best.
- I always got so much more
candy than you, remember?
'Cause you cheated.
You'd trick or treat the whole
neighborhood in one costume,
then you'd go do it again in another.
Come on, Eric, everybody did that.
Well, except for you.
Jake and I had Halloween down to a science.
I was always the bag lady so I could stuff
all of his costumes into my garbage bad.
I think we hit the Stevens' house,
like, seven times in one year.
He did always share his haul with me, though.
Just like a little Bonnie and Clyde.
So adorable.
Is it inappropriate that I keep
asking questions about him?
Why would it be inappropriate?
I don't know.
Do you have a thing for Jake?
No...
- Okay, except, maybe, yes,
just a little bit. - A little.
- I'm sorry, this is really weird.
- It's not weird.
Look, it was a long time ago.
Just be careful, okay?
Why?
There's a lot of things about
Jake you don't know, okay?
Is that Jake's car?
- Oh, my God.
- What?
What is it?
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- Can I help... you?
- I'm here to see about posting
bail for a friend of mine.
Mitchell Cafferty.
Hello, Jonah.
Jake.
Been a long time.
5 years. So...
- I understand Mitchell's been causing some
trouble. - Come on, don't act surprised.
He doesn't get out of bed in the morning
without running it by you first.
I'm not sure that's true,
but I'm here to bail him out.
All right, then let's talk bail.
- First you're going to give back
the food you stole...
- Wait, hold on a second.
I'm not sure you've noticed,
but the world's coming apart at the seams.
What belongs to who is getting
to be a fuzzy science, Jake.
- But I'll see what I can do.
- All right, and then you're
gonna stay away from this place.
- Not just you-- Mitch, Joe Kelly...
- Since when are you in a position
to speak for this town?
- Do we have a deal?
- Shut up, Mitchell!
We have a deal.
Oh, I see you're awake.
Must be noon.
I've been up for a while.
Hey, close the front door.
What, were you born in a barn?
Were you born in a barn?
Almost a week you've been here and that
joke's really not getting any funnier.
Found some stale corn flakes in the pantry.
- Since no one else seemed to be eating
them... - Well, knock yourself out.
Here, you want a little milk with those?
There you go.
Oh...
It's still warm.
Yeah, it was even warmer when it
was in the cow ten minutes ago.
- And that will do it for the corn flakes.
- Mm...
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
- By the way, where's the funnel?
- Oh, yeah.
I put it in the random drawer.
I couldn't sleep last night, so I rearranged
some kitchen space
put all the non-essentials
out of the triangle.
- Triangle? - The workspace that
connects the three critical areas--
sink, stove and prep.
I was in the process of
having my condo in D.C.
renovated before I got stranded here.
You know, Mimi,
when I was a young boy growing up,
I always felt like there was something
missing in my life.
Now I know.
It was the triangle.
Sink, stove, prep.
We have sarcasm in D.C., you know.
These'll do, Bob.
Please tell me that's diet Cream soda.
There used to be a whole case of diet here.
Gracie promised she'd hold on to it for me.
Not to worry, dear.
I tucked it away when
we agreed on the price.
Oh, you're right.
- It's lovely.
- It's an antique.
Are you sure about this, sweetheart?
I'm sure.
Dale, there's a case of soda hidden
along the back wall next to your cot.
Would you bring it up, please?
You're still sleeping here?
Be right back.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- You were cooling your thermometer
in that glass of water, weren't you?
- No, I wasn't.
All right, so what if I was?
I'm fine. I'm tired of being babied.
You have a temperature of 350 degrees.
You are going to rest.
You are going to take
the pills that April gave you.
You are going to admire this
ridiculous pumpkin with me
and then we are going to try to eat said
pumpkin together.
Because we use every part
of the buffalo in this house.
- Is that understood?
- Most of it.
But no more meds.
It's been three weeks,
I'm not going to be the reason
this town runs clean out of antibiotics.
All right, now you listen to me.
There may come a day when this
town needs you to be a hero again
but today is not that day.
The world's changing.
Don't I know it.
Not a lot of work for a guy
hauling freight these days.
The old side business has sort of become
a full time gig.
We could use a guy like you out there.
There's a lot of stuff out on the roads
waiting for anybody to take it.
I want your word.
You and your guys are going
to stay away from town.
Already said I would.
Ask again, a guy might think
you were calling him a liar.
- And that's my car.
- Well, you left it out there.
- Yeah, but it was destroyed.
Lovingly restored.
I told you there was a lot of good stuff
out there on the roads.
This one I didn't even have to fight for.
Besides, she was mine first.
Emily...
- Why are you talking to him?
- It's okay, all right?
It didn't have anything to do with you.
He's my father.
It has everything to do with me.
You have no idea how bad
it got after you left.
He was calling.
He was everywhere.
He was coming by the house.
He wanted to talk to me.
He wanted me to forgive him
for what happened with Chris.
I will never forgive him
for what happened to Chris.
- And now you're back and he's back.
- Oh, he's not back.
All right?
After tomorrow, he's done, he's gone.
- When's it supposed to happen?
- Tomorrow morning at 11:00.
- So, we get the food back
and Prowse leaves us alone.
- Well, that's what he said.
- Yeah, we'll see what he does.
- Either way, I think it's
important that we do this.
- Okay. I'll run it by Dad.
- What's going on?
Get in here.
Gray Anderson's back in town.
- Is he okay?
- I can't believe it.
I hitched... Oh, thank you.
I hitched a ride with a...
with a supply truck that was running
bottled water to a FEMA camp
out near Rogue River.
FEMA's running.
Well, that's good, at least.
Well, about ten miles outside of
Topeka, we hit a roadblock.
I mean, nothing official, just a couple
cars rolled out onto the highway.
And as soon as we stopped, it was like...
like a dozen guys just came out of nowhere
and yanked us out of the truck.
I... fought one of them
and took off on foot.
The driver...
they just beat him to
death right on the road.
They killed him for...
just a few cases of water.
You guys have any electricity
yet, any lights or anything?
- There was a heck of a pulse.
- No.
Some simple circuits are still working
like flashlights and
electrical razors, but...
we pretty much lost everything
with a circuit board--
radio, computers,
newer cars.
- What's happening in Topeka?
- It's a mess.
Nobody knows where the hell the governor is.
And the fallout from Lawrence
hit 'em really hard.
Whoa, whoa... They... They hit Lawrence?
- Wh-Why would they hit Lawrence
and not Topeka? - I don't know.
- What about any other major cities?
New York, DC...?
- Oh, they didn't get New York.
What, New York made it?
Yeah, well, after 9/11, they got pretty good
at security and apparently,
NYPD caught three guys
right before they flipped the switch.
They had a rented van,
a 20-kiloton bomb in a steel drum.
And what about DC?
It's gone.
Hey.
- Did you hear?
- Hear what?
Mr. Anderson's back.
He says New York is still there.
New York?
- My parents?
- They might be okay.
My parents.
Hey. Took you long enough.
Your sister went to bed a little while ago.
I'm pretty sure that she still hates me.
Although tonight was the first
time she said "good night"
without the dirty sign mixed in.
I wonder if she knows that I
know what that means.
I have some bad news.
Mimi...
- What?
- Washington DC's gone.
You know, stirring them doesn't
make them taste any better.
So... Cindy Mather is dead?
If she was in DC...
then probably.
It depends how close she was
when the bomb went off.
And Joel Stafford?
He's gonna ask me out.
That's what Cindy said.
Did they feel it when they died?
- Joel... Cindy, the Thompsons
next door... - It, um...
it would've been fast.
- And Doug.
- Who's Doug?
Mom's boyfriend.
I thought you knew.
Are you out of your mind?
You made a deal with Jonah Prowse?
Yeah, Mitch for the food and
Jonah stays out of Jericho. Why?
- Because you can't make deals with
guys like that. - Wait a minute,
we talked about this. We-We agreed.
Look, I know about Prowse.
He hauled materials for Stevens
before I came into the mine.
He was stealing five percent off
the top, intimidating suppliers.
The guy did four years at Lansing for
extortion and assault.
You want to negotiate with that guy?
He's got a good point, Jake.
- What happened to clearing this with Dad?
- Look, no disrespect to your father,
but he hasn't been out there.
I've seen what happens when people
lose their hold on law and order.
You start striking bargains with the
bad guys, it's the beginning of the end.
Just calm down, all right?
We need food more than we need to keep
Mitchell Cafferty.
Now, I'm supposed to make a trade with
Jonah in an hour.
- If I go out there empty-handed, I don't
know what he's gonna do.
- It doesn't matter.
Because he'll know that we won't
roll over for him.
Look, Jake...
we either hold this territory or we don't.
Eric?
Gray's right.
I know this is only half
the soda we swapped for
- but I really need that jewelry box back.
- Oh, sorry, sweetie.
We made a deal.
I just found out my parents could be alive.
- They might be coming home at any time.
- Oh, that's good news.
I'm happy for you.
That jewelry box belonged to my mother.
Her grandmother gave it to her, it's...
it's worth a lot more than some diet soda.
I wish I could help you,
but I already traded it away.
- To who?
- All trades are confidential.
No one wants to buy a jewelry box that comes
with an argument about who it belongs to.
I'm sure that your parents will understand.
These are hard times for all of us.
Okay, fine.
Dale, um, could you lock
this up in the back, please?
- Looks like you forgot someone.
- The town said no to the deal with Mitch.
How can I fix this?
Ooh!
You scared me.
Hey, that's a good ghost.
Oh, that's for you...
No candy in here, guys.
Gray!
Jonah's men just took Mitchell.
They're headed out the front.
Hey!
Gray, no!
- Instead of what? Starting a
firefight on Main Street?
- I got to go out after them!
- Are you out of your mind?
- This has got to be answered, Jake.
What, are you gonna turn the other cheek?
- How long before you think these guys
are back...? - I can talk to Jonah.
- You can talk to Jonah... Find him!
He lived up to his end of the deal.
- And why the hell are you protecting
this guy? - I'm protecting this town.
- He can get things we're gonna need.
- What can he get?!
- He can get food!
He can get gas, he can get ammo.
Could you get that stuff
if we needed it tomorrow?
Could you?!
Because he can!
We'll do this my way now.
You said you could get me a car.
- Is this thing gonna die on me
halfway out there? - Charlotte?
Not a chance. She's sturdy.
- So, uh, be careful.
- I'm only going ten miles.
I meant with him.
I talked to Emily.
Yeah? What'd she tell you?
Enough.
Hey, Darcy,
Allie and Sam got a grill going outside.
I think we're barbecuing Spam.
They were asking for you.
So, uh...
I know about Doug.
- What do you know?
- I know that he's probably gone.
I know...
- I know that he meant a lot to you.
- Robby, you don't know a damn thing.
So are my kids close to him?
- Why don't you ask the kids?
- I don't want to ask the kids.
I'm ask...
Why did you come for me?
- I told you the kids...
- No, no. In D.C., you could have
just taken the kids.
We sat in traffic for two hours
that afternoon on the Beltway.
- You didn't have to wait
for me. Why'd you do it?
- Why?
- You hated me, Robert.
- I did not...
- You hated me.
You blamed me for breaking up the marriage.
And even though you left me for your work
long before I ever looked at another man.
I'll tell the kids you're
not feeling too well.
Doug and I had been dating
for about three months.
I met him at the gym.
I liked the way he looked at me.
And I liked the way that I felt
about myself when he looked at me.
It was nice.
I was thinking about
introducing him to the kids.
Now I'm, I'm back in the house of secrets
with a man who looks at me like...
like that.
God, Robert,
why on Earth did you come for me?
Quite the runner, Mitch.
Hey, knock it off!
Let him go!
Break it up. Break it up.
All right, it's all right.
To what do I owe this pleasure
A lot of people in town
who aren't going to let this stand.
They're angry.
They're talking about coming out here
to get him by force if necessary.
Did you ever in your life think anyone would
care this much about Mitchell Cafferty?
Look, you don't want it to come to that,
I don't want it to come to that.
I'm here to negotiate.
Last time we negotiated,
it didn't work out so good for me.
Keep Mitch and keep the food.
You can sell the food to the town through
Gracie Lee's market
and take your cut off the top in supplies
that we have and you don't:
fresh water, crops,
salt from the mine.
I'm listening.
In exchange, you'll guarantee that your...
your business stays away from town.
We'll send a trailer to pick up supplies.
You don't come to us.
I'll think about it.
Now let's talk about what I need.
- I want to talk to Emily.
- She doesn't want to see you.
She blames me for Chris's death.
- Things might be different if she knew
whose fault it really was. - I didn't
sent him on that job, all right? You did.
I tried to talk him out of it.
He needed a lookout,
someone to watch his back.
- You left him alone!
- A lookout?
He needed a father.
- All right. Maybe it is time
Emily learns the truth about what you did.
- I told her.
I told her, I told her everything.
- Did she forgive you?
- No.
Neither do I.
Get her to see me,
- or I'll do business wherever
the hell I please. - I can't.
Then I guess we don't have a deal.
Oh, hey, Eric,
can I borrow you for a minute?
Sure. What's up?
Come on in. I, uh...
I am seeing a lot of
unfamiliar faces around here
and I did some asking around,
and apparently, there are eight new families
since I left town and 14 since the attacks.
Yeah, some families had relatives come
from nearby towns.
- A few more people from Colorado. Why?
- Do we know anything about them?
Where they've been, what they know?
I don't think I like where this
conversation's going, Gray.
Well, neither do I,
but I'm also sure that we can't
be too careful or too prepared.
You mean Robert Hawkins?
The man has two kids.
He's been nothing but helpful.
He shows up two days before the end
of the world with enough cash to buy
the old Thompson house.
Look, I'm not suggesting anything.
I'm-I'm just saying that we should
know a little more about who
we're sharing our foxhole with.
It costs us nothing to find out.
Is there something you want to tell me?
What do you mean?
That jewelry box is missing.
Did you steal from me, Dale?
Say something.
Why did you lie to her?
- Why did you tell her you didn't
have the box? - We made a fair trade.
I shouldn't have to explain myself
to some spoiled little girl.
- You don't know her.
- Oh, I know her and everybody like her.
They think the rules don't apply to them.
I could understand others
trying to steal from me
but after everything I have done for you?
- Everything you've done for me?
- I took you in.
- -And what?
You let me sleep here?
I was the one who looked for the train.
I was the one who walked five miles
every day dragging food back here.
You wouldn't have a store
if it wasn't for me.
- Dale, honey...
- You know what?
No, I'm done.
Here's your keys back.
Dale, no!
Hey.
Where's Mary?
Uh, Wednesday, night off.
- What are you drinking there?
- I don't know.
I think it might be kerosene.
I haven't quite figured out the still yet.
So how'd things go with Jonah today?
I think I might have gotten us into a fight
we don't want to be a part of.
Nice.
How about you?
How was your day?
Well, I think I'm becoming
Graynderson's yes man.
The worst part of it is I'm
not sure if that's a bad thing.
Big day for the Green boys, huh?
- Yeah. You avoiding going home telling Dad?
- Hell, yeah. You?
- Same.
Yeah. You remember that time we set
the carpet in Dad's office on fire?
All you had to do was stick to the story,
we would have been fine.
- You wanted me to tell Dad I had a seizure
and knocked over his desk lamp.
- Yeah.
Any other brilliant ideas
to get us out of this one?
Not at the moment.
Well, I say we finish these drinks
go home and try to explain all this to Dad
in a way that won't kill him.
I think you've had enough to drink.
You want to come with me
so we can finish our conversation?
- No, I'm done talking for the day, Rob.
- I'm not kidding, Darcy.
- Let's just go.
- No, all right?
- Not this time.
Why don't you go home?
Hey...
I came back for you
because you are my wife.
Hey, uh, I'm not sure how you feel about
tomato soup
but I don't know.
It usually makes me feel better, so...
How's it coming?
I've been going over
all of my pending audits
and I can only remember half the details
of half my cases.
This one is for "almost there," and
this one is for "not even close."
- You don't need to be doing all this.
- What the hell else am I going to do?
Oh!
Get out of my way.
- I'm just trying to help you.
- Well, stop it.
Look, I know what you're going through.
All right? I lost my folks
when I was 18 years old,
and the first few days were, were bad.
Everything and everyone that I ever cared
about was incinerated four weeks ago.
And you mean to tell me
that you know how I feel?
- I'm trying to be nice to you.
- Well, stop being nice to me!
You don't owe me anything.
You don't owe anyone anything anymore.
Em. What are you doing here?
I came here to talk to you,
but when I got here...
- Hurry.
- What?
He went into shock or something.
And one, and two, three, four. Five...
1,001... 1,002... 1,003...
1,004... 1,005.
- He's not breathing.
- Okay, one more breath.
Let's get him over on his side. Come on.
I've given him three courses of antibiotics.
It must have been too much for his system.
He's become septic.
How do we treat it?
Wait a minute, April.
If the Med Center were operational-- maybe.
If we could MEDEVAC him into County Hospital
in Rogue River, maybe.
If we had any heavy-duty meds
left in the pharmacy, maybe.
Without that...
12 hours.
Maybe a day.
I'm so sorry.
What kind of meds?
What?
You said he needed heavy-duty meds.
What, what kind would he need?
Something strong enough to blow out the
infection fast.
Let his body heal itself.
Cipro, probably, but we ran out weeks ago.
- They'd have it in Rogue River, though.
- Jake.
That's 90 miles away.
- I'd better get going, then.
- Wait a minute.
I'm going, too.
Eric. no.
If Gray's right about how dangerous...
Go.
Go now.
You wanted to talk.
Let's talk.
- You want to sit?
- No. I'm not here to catch up.
Jake Green's dad's sick.
- That so?
- Yeah.
I don't care what you think of him, okay?
I'm here to ask for your help.
I'm not a doctor, sweetheart.
No, you're not.
You're a thief.
- He needs meds.
He needs Cipro.
- Don't have it. Sorry.
But I may be able to help.
- Your mother used to make that same face.
- Stop it.
You do not get to talk
about her. Or Chris. Okay?
I heard you're getting married.
What kind of guy is he?
- How many questions do I have to
answer to get your help? - More.
- What's he do? The guy.
- He's an investment banker.
Emily.
I've stuck by our agreement to stay away.
But the past few weeks,
I've seen a lot of bad things.
I just want to know
somebody's looking out for you.
It's just you and me now.
Your mom's gone.
- Chris is gone.
- Is that what this is?
- Hmm?
- What?
You want us to be a family?
Want somebody to invite
you for Thanksgiving dinner?
If you think for one second
that I would do that again, you're crazy.
I think if you want my help
saving Johnston Green's life,
you got a funny way of asking, young lady.
You're gonna get my help.
You're my kid.
But I think you and I need to
start seeing more of each other.
Dale.
Where have you been?
I've been looking all over for you.
How did you get this?
Thank you.
My God, this is what the fight was about.
Where are you staying tonight?
Ah... A friend's house.
A friend's house?
Come on.
You can sleep on the couch at my place.
- I don't think this is such a good idea.
- No choice.
Well, then at least let me do
some work on the car.
There's no time.
- I have to go now.
- What? Wait.
- You said it was sturdy.
- Well, sturdy, yeah, but what if
you need to outrun something?
- Why? How fast will it go?
- I don't know.
30, maybe 40 miles an hour, best
case, downhill, and not for very long.
See, this is what I'm saying. Maybe
you should go on horseback.
- A horse is slower than that.
- A horse is less likely to explode.
I'll take my chances.
Okay, well, then, at least open her up easy.
Make sure you have enough car left
in case you need to ask for a lot in a hurry
and remember, the gas tank on this thing
is on the left-hand side
so if somebody decides
to start shooting at you
make sure it's not on that side.
Anything else?
Come back in one piece.
I will, I promise.
I thought you were gonna go.
I'm waiting on Eric.
Oh.
Um...
- Watch out for giant irradiated
hands out there. - Always do.
Okay.
You going somewhere?
Yeah, my father needs
medication, stuff we don't have in town.
Jake and I are going to
Rogue River to find it.
You sure that's a good idea?
Not really.
Listen, you be careful out
there, all right? You don't...
you don't stop for anything,
you don't even slow down.
I mean it.
We'll be back before morning.
Do you mind keeping an eye on things here?
Of course, yeah, don't worry about it.
Aw, what the hell?
This is what we're driving?
Yeah, I mean, it's not actually a...
Yeah.
What in the world?
I thought the deal was we'd go get the food
and he'd stay away.
It was.
Em?
I couldn't get you the meds you needed, so
I got you the second-best thing.
A fast car.
He said it's a gift.
You know there are no gifts with him.
I'm really sorry you got dragged into this.
Nobody dragged me.
Go save your dad.
Eric? Load up.