GARFIELD.
HEATHCLIFF.
MY GOD,MAN,ARE YOU
DEAF,DUMB,AND BLIND?
GARFIELD IS,BY FAR,AMERICA'S
FAVORITE FAT CAT.
IT'S A MATTER OF TASTE.
I FIND HEATHCLIFF CHARMING.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
STILL HAVING THE GREAT DEBATE?
GARFIELD.
WELL,JUST SO YOU KNOW,THE
STORE'S BEEN CLOSED FOR AN HOUR.
WHAT?
I'VE DONE ALL YOUR CLOSE-OUT WORK
AND YOU'RE BOTH BUYING ME BEER.
FINE.
THIS DISCUSSION IS TABLED
UNTIL WE GET TO THE BAR,
WHERE SAMUEL WILL MODERATE.
YEAH,GREAT. JUST
LET ME GET MY JACKET.
AH,THERE HE IS.
LOOKING SHARP,MAN.
YOU DON'T THINK MAYBE YOU COULD
HAVE TAKEN THE APRON OFF THOUGH?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I WANT YOU TO MEET MIKE VOLTA.
MIKE,THIS IS SAM.
HOW'S IT GOING?
HEY.
SIT A SPELL. WE'VE
ONLY ORDERED APPS.
YEAH,I CAN'T. I HAVE PLANS.
I'M SUPPOSED TO MEET
ANDY AND THE GUYS.
WELL,THEN ISN'T IT NICE
YOU DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
NOW SIT.
SO THERE I AM.
ONE MINUTE I'M TAKING
ROOM SERVICE TO SUITE 14
AND THE NEXT THING I KNOW I'M IN BED
WITH THIS HEAVENLY CREATURE NAMED LINDA.
OH,YOU HOUND.
WHICH WOULD BE GREAT IF HER
HUSBAND DIDN'T WALK IN WITH A GUN.
OH,MY!
CAN YOU BELIEVE
IT? UNNECESSARY.
WELL,YOU WERE
BANGING HIS WIFE.
THAT IS SO TRUE.
BANG,BANG.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE
HOW I GOT OUT OF IT.
IT'S KIND OF
EMBARRASSING,ACTUALLY.
I STARTED CRYING.
OH,HO HO,PERFECT.
PERFECT.
YOU STARTING CRYING?
COME ON,IT'S KIND OF GENIUS.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW
HARD IT IS TO SHOOT A MAN
WHO'S CRYING LIKE
A LITTLE GIRL?
IT'S NOT THAT HARD.
OH,MY GOD.
YES,OF COURSE I'LL MARRY YOU.
I HAVE TO CALL MY MOTHER.
AH,YOUNG LOVE. SO
SWEET. INNOCENT.
QUITE THE CHALLENGE.
THAT?
IS NO CHALLENGE AT ALL.
PROVE IT.
CAN YOU EXCUSE
ME FOR A SECOND?
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT ABOUT?
THERE'S A VESSEL
UNDER YOUR CHAIR.
YOU TAKE IT,YOU FOLLOW
MIKE,YOU CAPTURE HIM.
QUICK AND QUIET.
WAIT. HE'S A SOUL?
AND A DANGEROUS ONE,HE'S
AS SLICK AS THEY COME.
I WANTED TO PERSONALLY MAKE
SURE THAT THERE WERE NO MISTAKES.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND. I
THOUGHT YOU LIKED THIS GUY.
HE DISGUSTS ME.
CAN YOU BELIEVE HE HAD THE
STONES TO INVITE ME TO DINNER?
HE ACTUALLY THOUGHT HE
COULD CHARM THE DEVIL.
IF YOU HATE HIM SO MUCH,WHY DON'T
YOU JUST TAKE CARE OF HIM YOURSELF?
THAT'S NOT MY JOB.
ME,DEVIL. YOU,MINION.
I'M NOT GONNA SULLY MY HANDS
WITH THAT PIECE OF GARBAGE.
NOW GET TO IT!
DON'T LET HIM START TALKING.
JUST POINT AND SHOOT.
POINT AND SHOOT.
Mike: CLAIRE,WHERE
DID YOU LEARN THAT?
WHOA,WHOA,WHOA,SAM.
WE'RE A LITTLE BUSY,HERE.
DAMN,MAN. NOT COOL.
SHE HAD A TONGUE RING.
WHAT'S THAT YOU GOT THERE?
IT'S A VESSEL.
FOR REAL?
AW,SON OF A BITCH.
LET ME JUST SAY ONE
THING IN MY DEFENSE.
SORRY.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
reaper 第1季第17集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
时间轴：酒囊饭袋 southwing
WE WAITED AT THE BAR FOR
YOU FOR TWO HOURS,SAM.
THIS ISN'T FAIR.
I MEAN,I CAN'T BELIEVE
THE DEVIL CAN...
YOU KNOW,ZAP YOU AWAY
WHENEVER HE FEELS LIKE IT.
ANDI,THAT'S HOW
THE DEAL WORKS.
I'VE COME TO ACCEPT IT.
BEING RESIGNED TO MY STUPID
FATE MAKES MY LIFE EASIER.
I CANNOT ACCEPT THE FACT THAT THERE
IS NOTHING WE CAN DO ABOUT THIS.
ANDI,I'VE TRIED TO GET OUT
OF IT. MY DAD HAS TRIED.
ALL SIGNS POINT TO
ME BEING SCREWED.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
NEXT.
HEY,GLADYS.
THIS IS ANDI. MY GIRLFRIEND.
YOU DON'T LOOK
MENTALLY DEFECTIVE.
DO YOU HAVE SOME
SORT OF DEFORMITY?
YOU MEAN LIKE HORNS
STICKING OUT OF MY HEAD? NO.
I LIKE HER.
PLACE THE VESSEL
ON THE MAT. Next
I THINK YOU JUST GOT
OFFICIAL DEMON APPROVAL.
OOH,THAT'S GOING ON MY RESUME.
OK,????????PUSH.
AH,COME ON! IT'S NOT CLOSING!
YOU'RE NOT STRONG
ENOUGH. COME ON.
KISS ME. KISS ME NOW.
AH,NICE. GET A LITTLE
TONGUE IN THERE,SARA.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THE IMMIGRATION OFFICER
IS HERE TALKING TO TED.
CHECKING OUT OUR STORY.
MAKE IT LOOK REAL.
BEN AND SARA GONZALES?
YES? WE'RE MR.
AND MRS. GONZALES.
AGENT PAPELBON,IMMIGRATION
AND CUSTOMS.
I'VE BEEN ASSIGNED
TO YOUR CASE,
AND I NEED TO DO
SOME VERIFICATION.
ARE YOU TWO AVAILABLE FOR
A FORMAL INTERVIEW TOMORROW,
-SAY AROUND 4:00?
-OF COURSE.
WELL,THAT IS,OF COURSE,
UNLESS THE NEWLYWEDS
ARE BUSY HAVING THE SEX.
WE ARE INSATIABLE.
ALL OUR FRIENDS SAY SO.
SAVE IT FOR THE INTERVIEW.
WHOA! WAIT,WAIT! PUT
IT BACK! PUT IT BACK!
SAM,MIKE VOLTA IS FREE.
DID YOU HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THAT?
NO! NO! I SWEAR! I DROPPED
THE VESSEL OFF THIS MORNING.
-YOU ARE AN ASS.
-MY APOLOGIES,KIDDO.
I'M NOT MYSELF,SAMMY.
THIS SOUL MAKES ME
LOOK LIKE A REAL CHUMP.
HE MIGHT AS WELL
JUST SPIT IN MY FACE.
I MEAN,HELL IS BECOMING A
REVOLVING DOOR FOR THIS CHARACTER.
WELL,HOW'S HE GETTING OUT?
WELL,THERE CAN BE
ONLY ONE EXPLANATION.
SOMEONE IS HELPING MIKE
VOLTA FROM THE INSIDE.
WE HAVE A MOLE IN HELL.
AND I WILL FIND HIM.
THE TORTURE TRAIN IS GOING
TO BE ROLLING DOWNSTAIRS
UNTIL SOMEONE TALKS.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'M NOT WORRIED.
LIMBS WILL BE QUARTERED
AND LOINS WILL BE SEARED.
BETTER CHECK YOUR MAIL.
MIKE,HEY!
RIGHT. THANKS,HONEY.
GOOD MAGIC.
HEY THERE,BUDDY.
YOU MIND IF I PUT
ON MY PANTS FIRST?
YEAH,YEAH. HURRY IT UP.
YOU REALIZE I'M JUST
GONNA GET OUT AGAIN.
AND AGAIN.
SEEMS LIKE A BIG WASTE
OF EVERYONE'S TIME.
IF I WERE YOU,I'D
JUST LET ME GO.
SORRY,MIKE. CAN'T DO IT.
CAN'T BLAME A GUY
FOR TRYING. RIGHT?
AT LEAST LET'S MAKE A MEMORY.
WHAT THE HELL...
SAY CHEESE. CHEESE.
PLACE THE VESSEL ON THE MAT.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
WELL,I JUST WANT TO
MAKE SURE HE GOES IN.
THE DEVIL SORTA
TRIED TO BREAK MY NECK
WHEN HE GOT OUT THE LAST TIME.
NO OFFENSE. I'M SURE
YOU DO A GREAT JOB..
-SATISFIED?
-COMPLETELY.
NEXT.
-CAN I HAVE THE COMICS WHEN YOU'RE DONE?
-OF COURSE.
THANKS.
SAM. OH,SAM.!
-HEY.
-OK,ALL RIGHT.
SEE YOU TOO.
I'M JUST GLAD YOU'RE
ALL RIGHT,YOU KNOW.
YOUR "BOSS," WORD HAS
IT,IS ON THE WARPATH
OVER A SOUL WHO KEEPS,UH...
SO I'M JUST-
I'M GLAD TO SEE THAT YOU
ARE NOT AMONG THE BODY COUNT.
NO. I'M FINE.
WELL,GOOD. WELL,IF I
CAN HELP YOU IN ANY WAY,
PLEASE LET ME KNOW.
HEY,HOW ABOUT HELPING SAM OUT
OF HIS DEAL WITH THE DEVIL?
WELL,THAT'S A... THAT
IS A PRETTY TALL ORDER.
YOU KNOW,I MEAN,ONCE
YOU SELL YOUR SOUL,
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
A ROCK SOLID DEAL.
I CAN'T THINK OF HOW ANY
WAY THAT YOU CAN BREAK THAT.
YEAH,BUT HE DIDN'T EVEN SELL
HIS SOUL. HIS PARENTS DID.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
ANDI,MY DAD'S BEEN LOOKING
AT THE CONTRACT FOR MONTHS.
IF THERE WAS A
WAY OUT OF THIS,
HE WOULD'VE FOUND IT.
WELL,MAYBE TONY
CAN LOOK AT IT.
WILL YOU?
YES,YES,SURE,
-BRING IT ON BY AND I'LL TAKE A GANDER.
-GREAT.
HERE WE GO. TRIP
DOWN MEMORY LANE.
WE PUT THESE TOGETHER
WITH PHOTOSHOP.
SEE? THERE'S OUR FAKE WEDDING.
FAKE APPLE PICKING.
FAKE HONEYMOON IN MEXICO.
WELL,WHAT DO YOU THINK?
PRETTY GOOD,RIGHT?
I MEAN,'CAUSE WE
TOTALLY LOOK MARRIED.
THESE ARE SO WEAK.
THEY'RE IDIOTIC.
-WE NEED SOME NAKED PHOTOS OF YOU IN HERE ASAP.
-WHAT? WHY?
IF YOU WANT ANY CHANCE IN HELL
OF MAKING THIS MARRIAGE
SEEM BELIEVABLE,
YOU HAVE TO SELL
THE PASSION,THE HEAT.
ALL RIGHT,WHAT THE
SPANISH CALL "EL FUEGO."
NAKED PHOTOS IN A
FAMILY ALBUM,SOCK?
YEAH,BEN,THAT'S WHAT
LOVING COUPLES DO,OK?
JOSIE AND I HAVE ENOUGH
PHOTOS OF EACH OTHER'S JUNK
TO FILL A LIBRARY.
PLUS JOHNNY IMMIGRATION
WILL BE SO SHOCKED,
HE'LL HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO
BELIEVE YOU GUYS ARE TOGETHER.
THAT MAKES SOME SENSE.
YEAH,THAT'S WHY I SAID IT.
ALL RIGHT,I THINK I MIGHT
HAVE A FEW SNAPS THAT WORK.
GIVE 'EM.
THESE ARE LOVELY.
-TASTEFULLY GRAPHIC.
-THANK YOU.
OK. GOOD. BENJAMIN,RIP
OF THAT SHIRT.
WE GOT TO GET YOU LUBED UP.
NO. I'M NOT TAKING
NAKED PICTURES.
OH,COME ON,DON'T-
DON'T BE EMBARRASSED,YOU
LITTLE SHY GUY.
ALL RIGHT,I'LL
GET NAKED WITH YOU.
I'M NOT EMBARRASSED,IT'S
JUST STUPID.
BENJAMIN,WE NEED TO
GO ABOVE AND BEYOND
IN ORDER TO GET
THEM TO BELIEVE US.
OTHERWISE,IF THEY DON'T,
YOU'RE GONNA GO TO JAIL AND I'M
GONNA GET KICKED OUT OF THE COUNTRY.
I'M NOT GONNA LET THAT HAPPEN.
SO STOP YOUR WHINING AND
GET YOUR SHIRT OFF,NOW.
FINE. BUT NO FULL FRONTAL.
WELL,LET'S JUST SEE
HOW IT GOES,ALL RIGHT?
HOLD IT.
-HEY,SAM.
-OUT ALREADY?
YEAH,I JUST STAYED DOWN LONG
ENOUGH TO WORK ON MY TAN.
-WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
-I CAME TO GET YOU.
NOT "GET YOU" LIKE A
MONSTER. GET YOU TO GO OUT.
OUT WHERE?
I SUGGEST CLUB
RENDEZVOUS FOR TONIGHT.
THE LADIES THERE
ARE UNBELIEVABLE.
MAYBE TOMORROW WE'LL
HIT THE GADABOUT ROOM.
IT'S A SATURDAY
NIGHT INSTITUTION.
WHY WOULD I GO OUT WITH YOU?
BECAUSE IT'S FUN.
BECAUSE I LIKE YOU.
AND BECAUSE WITH
ME AS YOUR WINGMAN,
YOU'LL BE SWIMMING IN
SWEETIES WITHIN THE HOUR.
DO YOU OWN A TIE?
LISTEN,IF I DON'T
BRING YOU IN,
THE DEVIL WILL KILL ME.
I'M SORRY. IT'S MY JOB.
AND I RESPECT THAT.
BUT DO YOU WANT TO
KNOW THE REAL REASON
THE DEVIL'S OUT TO
GET ME? JEALOUSY.
HE WATCHES GUYS LIKE US OUT
THERE ENJOYING OURSELVES.
BUT WHAT DOES HE ENJOY?
UH,MAKING PEOPLE MISERABLE.
EXACTLY. BECAUSE DEEP
DOWN HE'S MISERABLE.
HE WOULDN'T KNOW A GOOD TIME
IF IT BIT HIM ON THE ASS.
HE'S THE OPPOSITE OF
FUN. HE'S A FUN SUCKER.
THINK ABOUT IT. I
MEAN,WHAT'S MY CRIME?
I LOVE WOMEN. THEY LOVE ME.
IT DOESN'T MAKE
ME A SINNER,SAM.
ALL RIGHT. I
GUESS THIS IS YOU.
YOU KNOW I'M GONNA
HAVE TO CATCH YOU
WHEN I GET THE VESSEL.
AH,BACK TO CAT AND
MOUSE. GOOD TIMES.
JUST GIVE ME A HEAD START,OK?
AH! IT WASN'T EASY. BUT WE
GOT IT DONE,BUDDY. TEAMWORK.
WINSTON,A DRINK FOR MY MAN.
YEAH,I TOOK A LOT
OF ELBOW GREASE.
LOT OF LIMBS RENT
FROM A LOT OF TORSOS.
BUT EVERYBODY STARTED
SINGING LIKE CANARIES.
NOW HELL IS SEALED
TIGHT AS A DRUM.
AND NOW,IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN,
THERE'S A DEMON ABOUT PITCHFORK
DEEP IN MIKE'S ASS AS WE SPEAK.
MIKE WAS JUST IN MY ELEVATOR.
NOT NOW,WINSTON. NOT NOW.
I'M NOT GONNA
LIE TO YOU,SAMMY.
I HAVE SOME SERIOUS
EGG ON MY FACE.
YOU KNOW,I'M STARTING TO
FEEL THAT MAYBE TORTURE
ISN'T THE WAY TO GET
WHAT YOU WANT,YOU KNOW?
LIKE MAYBE PEOPLE JUST TELL
YOU WHAT YOU WANT TO HEAR
SO THAT YOU STOP PULLING
OUT THEIR FINGERNAILS.
I DON'T GET IT.
-WHY ARE YOU SO OBSESSED WITH THIS GUY.
-I'M NOT OBSESSED.
I SIMPLY DEMAND A
MODICUM OF RESPECT
FROM THE SOULS IN MY DOMAIN.
I WON'T BE DISSED,SAM.
BECAUSE I GOT TO TELL YOU,
HE DOESN'T REALLY SEEM
LIKE THAT BAD OF A GUY.
THAT'S HOW IT BEGINS,SEE?
"HE'S NOT THAT BAD OF A GUY.
-ALL HE'S DOING IS CHASING TAIL AND HAVING FUN."
-WELL,YEAH.
AND WHILE YOU'RE STANDING
THERE DEVELOPING YOUR MAN CRUSH,
YOU COMPLETELY IGNORE
THE DESTRUCTION HE CAUSES.
-WHAT DESTRUCTION?
WHAT DESTRUCTION,SAM?
THIS IS WHERE I CAUGHT
MIKE. IS HE HERE?
NO. HE DOESN'T
NEED TO COME BACK.
THE DAMAGE IS ALREADY DONE.
JAMES AND LUELLA CARVER
LIVED IN THIS HOUSE
FOR ABOUT AS LONG
AS THEY WERE MARRIED.
24 YEARS. HAPPY,SOLID YEARS.
YOU KNOW,THEY NEVER EVEN
CONSIDERED BEING UNFAITHFUL
TO ONE ANOTHER.NOT ONCE.
THAT IS UNTIL MIKE
VOLTA ENTERED THE PICTURE
AND SET HIS SITES ON LUELLA.
THIS IS WHAT MIKE VOLTA DOES.
HE TAKES LOVE AND COMMITMENT
AND DESTROYS IT
EVERY CHANCE HE GETS.
BUT,HEY,OTHER THAN THAT
HE'S A GREAT GUY,RIGHT?
I'VE SEEN ENOUGH.
I WANT HIM BACK,SAM.
NO MORE EXCUSES.
I'VE NEVER SEEN A FAMILY
ALBUM WITH SO MUCH NUDITY.
IT'S,UM,JARRING.
GOT TO KEEP THINGS
FRESH,HAVEN'T YOU?
SO,SARA,HOW DID YOU TWO MEET?
I WAS WAITING IN LINE
FOR THE FERRIS WHEEL
WHEN HE COMES ALONG AND ASKS
IF WE COULD SHARE A SEAT.
YES,THAT'S EXACTLY
HOW I REMEMBER IT.
ok.BEN,TELL ME
ABOUT SARA'S MOTHER.
DO YOU TWO GET ALONG?
BARBARA? YES,WE
GET ALONG VERY WELL.
IT SAYS HERE HER
MOTHER'S NAME IS SUSAN.
I GET CONFUSED. MY
MOTHER'S NAME IS BARBARA.
SAYS HERE YOUR MOTHER'S
NAME IS CANDACE.
IS EVERYONE'S
MOUTH REALLY DRY?
OK. YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M JUST GOING TO
CUT RIGHT TO IT.
IT'S OBVIOUS YOU
TWO ARE LYING.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO
RED FLAG THIS CASE.
YOU'VE GOT THE WEEKEND.
I SUGGEST YOU BOTH
OBTAIN LEGAL COUNSEL.
EXPECT TO BE IN FRONT OF
A JUDGE MONDAY MORNING.
YOU WILL BE ON A PLANE
HOME MONDAY NIGHT.
AND YOU WILL BE IN JAIL.
THANKS FOR THE LAUGH.
SAM'S BEEN IN THERE A WHILE.
-HOPE EVERYTHING'S GOING OK.
-YEAH.
THINK MIKE WILL BE
AT THE CLUB TONIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S WORTH A SHOT.
-SAM SAID IT'S ONE OF HIS FAVS,SO AWAY WE GO.
-ALL RIGHT.
SPEAKING OF WHICH...
IT'S KIND OF AN UPSCALE JOINT.
MAYBE WE SHOULD
SWING BY YOUR HOUSE
SO YOU CAN GET
CHANGED OUT OF THAT.
NO. NO. I'M GONNA WEAR THIS.
WELL,LOOK WHAT YOU'RE WEARING.
I'M A GUY,ANDI.
GUYS DON'T HAVE TO
GET DRESSED UP,OK?
IF I WEAR THIS OUT TO A CLUB,
I'M TELLING THE WORLD ONE
THING AND ONE THING ONLY-
-"I DON'T IRON."
-NO!
I'M TELLING THE WORLD
THAT I DON'T CARE
ABOUT WHAT YOU PEOPLE
THINK ABOUT ME,OK?
BESIDES,THE LADIES WANT IT.
WELL,YOU KNOW I
USUALLY DON'T GO
TO PLACES LIKE THIS ANYWAY.
RIGHT. RIGHT.
-YEAH,IT PROBABLY DOESN'T MATTER.
-NOPE.
SO WHAT ABOUT THE HAIR THOUGH?
WHAT-WHAT IS
WRONG WITH MY HAIR?
I DON'T KNOW. YOU EVER
THINK ABOUT CUTTING IT?
GO FOR A LITTLE TASTY
WAIF PAGEBOY THING?
LIKE THAT SKATER?
REMEMBER HER?
SHE LOOKED LIKE A
BOY,BUT SHE WAS HOT.
-I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS ANYMORE.
-THERE'S OUR BOY.
HEY,IS THAT THE CONTRACT?
THAT THING IS MASSIVE.
SAM IS SO SCREWED.
HEY.
OH,MY GOD.
THAT WAS SO AWKWARD.
YOU WALKED IN ON
THEM HAVING SEX.
NO. IT'S LIKE THEY DIDN'T
WANT TO GIVE IT TO ME.
MY DAD GAVE ME THIS WHOLE GUILT
TRIP ABOUT HOW I DIDN'T TRUST HIM.
OK,STILL WATCHING,STILL
WAVING. HI,SAM'S HOT MOM.
-ALL RIGHT,LET'S... LET'S GO.
-BYE!
SO WHY WOULD A SOUL TELL YOU
WHERE HE'S GONNA BE PARTYING?
HE WANTED ME TO
GO OUT WITH HIM,
JUST TRYING TO GET ME LAID.
-SO DID YOU TELL HIM YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?
-HOLD ON.
HEY,HEY,BENJI,IT'S SOCK.
WE'RE ALMOST TO THE CLUB.
WERE YOU ABLE TO GET IN?
YOU'LL-
OK,DO YOU WANT ME TO
TELL THEM THAT RIGHT NOW?
YOU WANT TO TELL THEM
THAT. YOU WANT TO TELL THEM-
OK,HANG ON.
I LOVE YOU GUYS. I
CAN'T WAIT TO HUG YOU,OK?
OK. ALL RIGHT,OK.
SEE YOU IN A BIT.
HE SOUNDS HAMMERED.
IMMIGRATION INTERVIEW
MUST HAVE GONE WELL...
YEAH. THE WAY
HE'S CELEBRATING.
OW,PARTY! YEAH!
FEEL THE BEAT!
BENNY. BENNY. BENNY.
WHAT IS WITH YOU,MAN?
HEY,HEY,SAMMY.
IMMIGRATION BUSTED MY ASS.
-THEY BUSTED IT WIDE OPEN.
-WHAT?
AND I'M GOING TO JAIL,OK?
SO THIS IS MY LAST
WEEKEND OF FREEDOM,
AND I'M GOING
OUT IN STYLE. OK?
BENNY,BENNY.
OH,MY GOD. WE GOT TO
GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
WE GOT TO GET YOU-
CASSIDY,I'M GOING
TO THE BIGHOUSE,BABY.
AND I'LL NEED YOU
TO WAIT FOR ME,OK?
OK! YOU'RE ALL RIGHT!
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT!
THIS IS MY BIG
NIGHT. MY BIG NIGHT!
HEY,BENJI.
BENJI,COME ON! BENJI!
FREEDOM! SWEET FREEDOM!
TAKE MY PICTURE NOW.
I FEEL THE NIGHT
AIR ON MY NIPPLES.
I'M ALIVE. OH!
-HEY,OK,YOU ALL RIGHT?
-OH,I CAN'T FEEL MY THING.
DID YOU GUYS SEE
THE CAR THAT HIT ME?
OH,THERE IT IS.
HEY,YOU!
-SAM,LOOK.
-GET BACK HERE,YOU BASTARD!
YOU THINK YOU CAN FOOL
AROUND WITH MY GIRL?
THAT'S HIM. THAT'S MIKE.
-HE WAS WITH GLADYS.
-WHAT?
HEY!
WELL,LOOK AT THAT. SHE'S HERE.
WHAT DOES OL' GLADENSTEIN
THINK SHE'S UP TO?
IT MAKES SENSE. MIKE
ESCAPED FROM HELL SO EASILY
BECAUSE HE NEVER GOT THERE.
GLADYS IS THE LEAK.
SO DOES THAT ALSO
MEAN SHE'S HIS LOVER?
OH,THIS IS GOING
TO BE SO GREAT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? GET HER!
GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE!
I CAN'T GET A CLEAR SHOT.
OUT OF MY WAY,GLADYS!
OVER MY DEAD BODY! GET
THE HELL OUT OF MY HOUSE!
I AM NOT TALKING TO
YOU. I'M TALKING TO HIM.
GIVE IT UP,MIKE.
LET'S GO. MOVE!
NO! DON'T DO ANYTHING,OK?
NOBODY HAS TO GET HURT. PLEASE.
THEN LET ME WALK OUT
OF HERE OR SHE DIES.
OH,COME ON. REALLY? HA HA!
GO AHEAD,DO IT. SEE IF I CARE.
SERIOUSLY. YOU COULD
HAVE PICKED ANYTHING
IN THE WHOLE BIG BAD UNIVERSE
TO GRAB AS A HUMAN SHIELD.
YOU GRAB THE ONE THING
THAT I CARE THE LEAST ABOUT.
ZERO. NO FEELINGS.
I MEAN,YOU COULD HAVE GRABBED
THAT OLD TV GUIDE OVER THERE
AND HELD A KNIFE TO IT, AND I
WOULD HAVE BEEN MORE CONFLICTED.
SO YOU KNOW WHAT,GIVE IT UP.
PUT THE SHIV DOWN.
YOU'RE GOING BACK TO-
OH,GOD. GO GET HIM!
-GUYS...
-WHAT?
I THINK SHE'S DEAD.
OH,MY GOD.
OK,SAM ???? PICK HER UP!
OH,SHE'S HEAVY. I DIDN'T
THINK SHE WAS THIS HEAVY.
I'LL GET THE DOOR. GET THE
DOOR. ALL RIGHT,I GOT HER.
WATCH HER HEAD.
YOU ALL RIGHT? ALL RIGHT.
GO AHEAD,GET IN.
NO,YOU GET IN.
FINE! GO!
THIS IS SO AWFUL.
WHAT DO WE DO?
WHAT DO WE DO WITH
A DEAD DEMON BODY?
I DID THIS. THIS IS MY FAULT.
NO,MIKE DID THIS.
YEAH,BUT I ENCOURAGED HIM.
I SAID THAT WE
DIDN'T CARE ABOUT HER.
AND NOW LOOK AT
HER. SHE'S DEAD!
OH,OH,GOD,I FEEL
TERRIBLE. I'M GONNA BARF.
YOU GUYS,WE HAVE TO THINK.
WE CANNOT DRIVE AROUND
WITH A DEAD BODY.
WE SHOULD BURY HER.
SOMEPLACE BEAUTIFUL.
OR LIGHT HER ON
FIRE LIKE A VIKING.
GET A STACK OF WOOD.
LET'S GO TO TONY'S.
HE'LL KNOW WHAT TO DO.
-SEATBELTS,RIGHT? SAFETY FIRST.
-YES.YES.
ALL THE LIGHTS ARE
ON,BUT I DON'T SEE HIM.
ALL RIGHT,LET'S JUST
GO INTO THE WOODS
AND FIND A PLACE
TO DIG A GRAVE.
I'M GONNA SAY A
PRAYER WHEN WE DO IT.
SOCK,SHE'S A DEMON. I DON'T
THINK SHE'D WANT PRAYERS.
I'M GONNA SING SOME
SABBATH WHEN WE DO IT.
THAT'LL BE REAL NICE,SOCK.
-YEAH.
ANDI,GRAB A BARREL.
ARGH!
AAH!
SH-SHE'S DEAD.
SHE'S DEAD.
YEAH. WE'RE ABOUT TO BURY HER.
YOU SOBER?
Andi: THAT'S IT.
Sock: ONCE AGAIN.
HEY,HOW ABOUT HERE?
NO. NO.
WE GOT TO BURY GLADYS
IN THE PERFECT SPOT.
Benji: WHERE IS
THIS PERFECT SPOT?
I'LL KNOW WHEN I SEE IT.
IT'LL PROBABLY HAVE
A WATERFALL. NO!
ALL RIGHT,THAT'S IT,SOCK.
WE'RE BURYING HER RIGHT HERE.
WHAT'S THAT?
HEY,GUYS,I SAW YOUR
CAR IN THE DRIVEWAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN
MY NECK OF THE WOODS?
WELL,REMEMBER
HOW WE WANTED YOU
TO TAKE A LOOK AT MY
DEAL WITH THE DEVIL?
SURE.
WELL,WE BROUGHT A
DEAD BODY TO BURY.
ALSO.
HMM. OK. LET'S DO THAT.
WATCH OUT.
OH!
OH,GOD.
UH,I DON'T THINK SHE'LL FIT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE COULD FOLD HER.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT,OK,I'LL
DO IT. I'LL DO IT.
I OWE HER THAT MUCH.
COMING IN,GLADYS.
SAM.
I'M GONNA HAVE MY BUDDY LOOK
AT THAT CONTRACT RIGHT AWAY.
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER,
WE'RE GONNA BREAK THIS
DEAL WITH THE DEVIL.
I PROMISE.
THANK YOU. THAT'S GREAT NEWS.
OK,GUYS,COME ON. EULOGY TIME.
HERE LIES GLADYS.
AND SHE IS BEAUTIFUL.
OH,THE GODDESS OF THE DMV.
WAIT A SECOND.
SHE A DEMON?
YEAH.
YEAH,SHE'S THE ONE THE
DEVIL'S BEEN LOOKING FOR.
THE SOUL KILLED HER.
REALLY? JUST A SECOND.
UH!
THERE WE GO.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
SHE'LL BE FINE.
MORTAL WEAPONS,THEY
CAN'T KILL US.
GLADYS?
AH! AAH!
WHOA! WHOA!
THANKS.
NO PROBLEM.
GLADYS,THE DEVIL KNOWS
SOMEONE'S HELPING MIKE ESCAPE.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE HE FINDS OUT IT'S YOU.
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
WHERE IS HE?
DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
AND I WOULDN'T TELL
YOU IF I DID KNOW.
THANKS FOR NOT
BURYING ME ALIVE.
GLADYS,JUST TELL ME ONE THING.
WHY RISK IT ALL FOR THAT JERK?
I MEAN,HE TRIED TO KILL YOU.
YOU DESERVE BETTER.
I JUST GOT TIRED
OF BEING LONELY.
NEXT.
CAN I HELP YOU?
YES,I BELIEVE YOU CAN.
HELLO,GLADYS.
YOU KNOW,I HEAR THAT
CONFESSING ONE'S SINS
IS GOOD FOR THE SOUL.
FIRST OFF,YOU'RE
A COMPLETE MORON
TO EVEN BE IN THIS SITUATION.
NO ONE DISPUTES
THAT I AM A MORON.
I TRIED TO STOP HIM,BABY.
NO,YOU DIDN'T. NO,I DIDN'T.
YOU HAVE ONE CHANCE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE CHARGED,THERE'S
NO AVOIDING THAT,
BUT IF YOU PAY THE FINE,YOU
MIGHT AVOID JAIL TIME.
HOW MUCH MONEY DO YOU HAVE?
UH... NONE.
I DO HAVE A SAVINGS
ACCOUNT WITH 2,000 BUCKS.
NO,NO,HE DOESN'T. NO.
WHY ARE YOU TELLING
HER THAT,BENZINE?
YOU'VE BEEN SAVING THAT MONEY
FOR FORMULA ONE RACING SCHOOL.
REMEMBER? THAT IS YOUR DREAM.
THAT IS OUR DREAM.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED
MORE THAN TWO GRAND.
TRY DOUBLE THAT.
OH,I GUESS I CAN BORROW
THE REST FROM MY GRANDMA.
YOU COULD.
WILL THIS COVER SARA,TOO?
SARA HAS NO CHANCE.
THEY'RE GONNA DEPORT HER.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO TELL HER.
HEY.
HEH HEH.
GOT YOU A PRETZEL.
I'M BEING DEPORTED,AREN'T I?
I'M SO SORRY,
AND IF IT'S ANY CONSOLATION,
I HAVE TO PAY A HUGE FINE.
I KIND OF FIGURED
THIS MIGHT HAPPEN
AND I MADE ALTERNATE
ARRANGEMENTS.
I HAD A VERY CANDID DISCUSSION
WITH OUR IMMIGRATION OFFICER.
HE HAS AGREED TO
ACCEPT A B-R-I-B-E.
A BRIBE?
IF WE PAY HIM,HE IS
WILLING TO 'LOSE' THE FILE.
I DON'T GET KICKED
OUT OF THE COUNTRY,
YOU DON'T GO TO JAIL.
OK,BUT WOULDN'T THAT BE
DOING SOMETHING ILLEGAL
TO COVER UP SOMETHING ILLEGAL?
I MEAN-
MM-HMM. SURE.
I MEAN,IF YOU'RE WILLING
TO PAY YOUR LITTLE FINE
AND JUST THROW
ME TO THE WOLVES?
THERE ARE NO WOLVES.
THEY'LL JUST BE SENDING YOU
BACK TO WHERE YOU CAME FROM.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
TO MANCHESTER,BEN?
SMOKE STACKS.
CROWDS. BLEAK.
ALL THAT'S LEFT FOR ME
TO LOOK FORWARD TO THERE
IS MY OLD STOOL IN MY
FATHER'S MUSLIN PLANT.
THAT'S RIGHT. MUSLIN.
IF WE POOL OUR MONEY TOGETHER,
WE CAN PERSUADE HIM
TO LOOK THE OTHER WAY.
HOW MUCH MONEY DO YOU HAVE?
I CAN GET 2,000
RIGHT AWAY,BUT-
WITH MY 3,THAT MAKES $5,000,
WHICH IS MORE THAN
ENOUGH FOR A BRIBE,RIGHT?
BEN... I OWE YOU AN
APOLOGY,SWEETHEART.
EVER SINCE YOU
AGREED TO HELP ME OUT,
I COULD SEE THAT YOU
WERE VERY SPECIAL.
SO SELFLESS,SO READY
TO HELP OTHER PEOPLE OUT
AND SO RARE.
WITH ALL THIS
IMMIGRATION BUSINESS,
I KIND OF LOST SIGHT OF THAT.
FORGIVE ME?
SURE.
IT'S FANTASTIC.
I'LL NEED THE MONEY BY 5.
OH,CASH ONLY,PLEASE.
SAM,SAM,LOOK.
Sam: HEY. HI.
GLADYS,WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
IF YOU'RE STILL
LOOKING FOR MIKE,
THERE'S A CHURCH
OUT ON RANGE ROAD.
HE'LL BE THERE TONIGHT AT 5.
WHY?
HE LIKES TO CRASH WEDDINGS
AND SLIP IT TO
THE BLUSHING BRIDE.
CLASS ACT.
WHY ARE YOU
TELLING US THIS NOW?
YOU WERE NICER TO ME
THAN MIKE EVER WAS.
THIS IS MY CAT,FANCY.
IF YOU'D LOOK AFTER HIM,I'D
GREATLY APPRECIATE IT.
HE HAS A SKIN CONDITION,
SO YOU MIGHT HAVE TO
SQUEEZE HIS PUSTULES
EVERY NOW AND THEN.
YEAH. GLADYS,WHAT HAPPENED?
I'VE BEEN REASSIGNED.
BACK DOWN TO HEAD OFFICE.
NO. NO. SAM. WE
CAN'T LET THIS HAPPEN.
I MEAN,YOU GOTTA DO SOMETHING
LIKE WHAT? I
DUNNO,TALK TO THE DEVIL.
GET HIM TO LET HER GO.
NO,ANDI. I LEARNED
A LONG TIME AGO
THAT ASKING THE
DEVIL FOR A FAVOR
IS A BAD IDEA.
BESIDES,GLADYS IS A DEMON.
I BET SHE HAS A LOT
OF FRIENDS IN HELL.
THIS IS NOT A
BIG DEAL FOR HER.
YOU THINK?
SHE'LL BE FINE.
BUT I COULD BE WRONG.
THE CEREMONY SHOULD
START ANY MINUTE
MIKE'S PROBABLY KNEE-DEEP
IN SOME HONEYMOON BY NOW.
LET'S GET IN THERE.
HEY. Sam: WHOA,WHOA,WHOA.
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
WHAT'S WITH THE FANCY PANTS?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU TOLD ME DRESS UP.
I DID NOT. YES,YOU DID.
WHAT,YOU GUYS
COULDN'T EVEN WEAR
ONE OF YOUR TUXEDO T-SHIRTS?
I MEAN,I KNOW EACH
ONE OF YOU HAS ONE.
ACTUALLY,THERE'S JUST THE ONE.
WE SHARE.
IT'S A ROTATION.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
LET'S JUST DO THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
HI. HELLO.
UH,NO. SORRY.
I SAW "WEDDING CRASHERS"
AND YOU'RE NOT GETTING IN.
OK. SORRY.
THAT'S IT? THAT
WAS YOUR BIG PLAN?
HE SAW THE MOVIE. WHAT
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
WHAT? ALL RIGHT. PLAN B TIME.
SET THE JOINT ON
FIRE,SMOKE 'EM OUT.
SPLIT UP,CIRCLE
AROUND THE BUILDING,
FIND ANOTHER ENTRANCE.
MY PLAN B WAS BETTER.
HEY,DID YOU HAPPEN TO
SEE THE BRIDE ANYWHERE?
UH,YEAH. ACTUALLY,SHE-
SHE JUST RAN UP THAT WAY.
UH... MIKE?
Man: ALL RIGHT. YOU GOT ME.
BUT TELL ME.
ISN'T THE BRIDE JUST GLOWING?
MIKE?
JUST COME OUT. MAKE IT EASY.
Mike: HOW 'BOUT YOU
RECONSIDER MY OFFER?
YOU AND ME NEED
TO JUST GET CRAZY
AND HAVE SOME FUN
TOGETHER FOR ONCE.
YOU KILL PEOPLE,MIKE.
YOU TRIED TO KILL GLADYS.
AH,COME ON. I KNEW
SHE WOULDN'T DIE.
YEAH,WELL,SHE GOT
SENT BACK TO HELL.
REALLY?
TOO BAD I WON'T
BE JOINING HER.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO BE CAREFUL
OF THAT SHUTTER FINGER,SAM.
HOW MANY FLASHES
DO YOU HAVE LEFT?
CRAP.
YEAH,YOU COULD
HAVE DONE IT MY WAY,
BUT YOU HAD TO BE A HERO.
I USUALLY WORK ALONE,SAM,
BUT WE MIGHT'VE MADE
A GOOD TEAM,YOU AND ME.
YEAH,I'VE SEEN WHAT YOU DO.
I'VE SEEN THE CONSEQUENCES.
BUT SAM,THE CONSEQUENCES
ARE THE BEST PART.
THE MOURNING AND SUFFERING
OF HUSBANDS AND CHILDREN.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOUR
LOVED ONES CRYING OVER YOU.
THAT HOT,LITTLE
GIRLFRIEND OF YOURS,
I BET SHE'LL NEED A
LOT OF COMFORTING,SAM.
A LOT.
ALMOST,SAM.
SO CLOSE.
NO MORE FLASHES LEFT.
AND IF YOU CAN'T SEE
ME,YOU CAN'T CATCH ME.
IF I WAS A NICE
GUY,I'D MAKE THIS QUICK.
BUT I AM NOT NICE.
OHH!
BOY.
I LOVE YOU GUYS
SO MUCH RIGHT NOW.
HUH.
CAMERA REALLY
DOES ADD 10 POUNDS.
IT'S SARA.
MAYBE SHE'S GOT AN UPDATE.
HEY,WHAT'S THE GOOD WORD?
DID HE TAKE THE BRIBE?
HELLO,MY DARLING.
YEAH,HI.
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH IMMIGRATION?
OH,NO. THIS IS VERY AWKWARD.
THERE WAS NO
BRIBE. I MADE IT UP.
WHAT? WHY?
WELL,I'M AFRAID I'VE GONE
"ON THE LAM," AS THEY SAY.
BUT YOU HAVE MY MONEY
AND THEY'RE GOING
TO SEND ME TO JAIL.
BEN,WE DID TRY TO
DEFRAUD YOUR GOVERNMENT.
WE BOTH KNEW THERE WAS A RISK
OF IMPRISONMENT,DIDN'T WE?
THANK YOU,DARLING.
BUT I'M THE ONLY
ONE GOING TO JAIL.
BEN,YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
JAIL WOULD ACTUALLY BE
VERY,VERY GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU NEED TOUGHENING UP.
YOU'RE VERY EASILY DUPED.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE GOT TO HOP.
BUT LISTEN TO ME.
VERY GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
AND PLEASE KNOW
THAT IN MY HEART,
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE
MY FIRST HUSBAND.
I LEFT YOU SOME MAC AND
CHEESE IN THE FRIDGE.
YOU WEREN'T GONNA
EAT THIS,WERE YOU?
NO. GO AHEAD.
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
DON'T TELL ME THAT,KENNETH.
I PROMISED SAM
THAT WE'D BE ABLE
TO GET HIM OUT OF THIS DEAL.
THAT'S NOT THE PROBLEM.
HOW WELL DO YOU KNOW THIS KID?
WELL... PRETTY WELL. WHY?
SOMEONE WENT THROUGH THIS
AND VERY CAREFULLY REMOVED
EVERY PAGE THAT REFERENCES
WHO SAM'S FATHER IS.
WELL,THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
WHY WOULD THEY DO THAT?
MY GUESS,TO HIDE THE IDENTITY
OF SAM'S REAL FATHER.
WELL,WHO IS IT?
YOU KNOW,FOR A GIRL TAKING
HER MAN TO THE JOINT,
YOU ARE REFRESHINGLY
UNDERSTANDING.
THAT'S BECAUSE AFTER
ALL THIS IS OVER,
MY BOYFRIEND'S NOT
GONNA BE MARRIED ANYMORE.
THAT'S WEIRD. HA HA.
I'M GONNA MISS YOU
GUYS WHILE I'M IN JAIL.
IT'S ONLY 8 DAYS.
IT'LL GO FAST.
I GOT YOU SOME STUFF.
THERE'S A CALLING CARD
FOR THE PAY PHONES,
SOME MAGAZINES,OH,AND
EARPLUGS,
IN CASE YOUR CELLMATE SNORES.
THANK YOU,MAN,THAT'S
VERY THOUGHTFUL.
I GOT YOU A PRESENT,TOO,BEN.
YOU DID? YEAH. PICK A HAND.
OH... THIS ONE.
THAT ONE? YEAH.
OHHH!
IT'S A MANLY BLACK
EYE. ALL RIGHT,LOOK,
YOU CAN'T GO INTO THE CLINK
WITH A PRETTY MUG LIKE THAT.
RIGHT? RIGHT?
YOU'RE A GOOD FRIEND. I KNOW.
GOOD.
I LOVE YOU. I LOVE YOU.
COME ON. LET'S HAVE A 3-WAY.
HUG,I MEAN.
AH,THERE HE IS.
MAN OF THE HOUR.
YOU REALLY WENT ABOVE
AND BEYOND,KIDDO.
TRULY EXCEPTIONAL JOB.
THANK YOU.
NO. I MEAN IT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I CAN
SHOW MY GRATITUDE THIS TIME.
TURKEY JERKY? HUH?
I KNOW HOW YOU CAN THANK ME.
YEAH? GO AHEAD.
LET GLADYS GO.
WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
BECAUSE IT'S GOOD BUSINESS.
DO TELL.
MIKE WOULD NEVER HAVE GOTTEN
OUT OF HELL IN THE FIRST PLACE
IF YOUR EMPLOYEES
DIDN'T HATE YOUR GUTS.
SOULS ARE ESCAPING
ALL THE TIME.
OH,BUT IF I MADE A
GRAND GESTURE OF MERCY,
SPARING A VALUED EMPLOYEE,
THAT WOULD TURN THE
TIDE AND BOOST LOYALTY.
IS THAT YOUR ARGUMENT?
YEAH. BASICALLY.
YOU REALLY TAKE
THE CAKE,SAMMY.
YOU THINK YOU CAN
FAST TALK THE DEVIL?
I'VE DEBATED DANIEL WEBSTER
AND YOU,SIR,ARE NO
DANIEL WEBSTER. HUH?
NO MATTER WHAT
ARGUMENT YOU MAKE,
WHAT WORD YOU SAY,
YOU WON'T CHANGE
MY MIND. HA HA.
PLEASE.
OH,COME ON.
TURN OFF THOSE
PUPPY DOGS NOW,SAMMY.
PLEASE. DO THIS FOR ME.
COME ON. STOP. ENOUGH.
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING
YOURSELF,MAN.
ALL RIGHT. FINE.
SHE'S OUT.
IS SHE GONNA BE OK?
YEAH. SHE'LL WALK IT OFF.
HEY,YOU WANNA SPLIT THIS?
SURE. HA HA HA.
Kenneth: DO YOU
BELIEVE IT NOW?
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
TONY,THE KID JUST GOT
THE DMV DEMON RELEASED.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU SAW
THE DEVIL SHOW MERCY?
I DON'T KNOW.
TONY,YOUR REBEL FORCES
WERE ANNIHILATED,
BUT SAM WAS SOMEHOW
MIRACULOUSLY SAVED.
WHY WOULD THE DEVIL SPARE HIM?
SAM WAS JUST AS GUILTY
AS EVERYONE ELSE.
LOOK AT THEM.
THEY HAVE A VERY SPECIAL
RELATIONSHIP,TONY.
VERY SPECIAL.
IT'S TIME YOU
RECOGNIZE THE TRUTH.
ALL RIGHT.
I BELIEVE IT.
SAM IS THE SON OF THE DEVIL.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入