- What's all the mystery, Sammy?
- I just need to talk to you in private.
All right, fine.
We're alone. Give it up.
No, in the car,
where no one can hear us.
You know what? If this is about your
weird little man crush on me,
- don't worry about it. We all know.
- Get in.
Fine.
Dude, it's freezing in here.
What the hell, man?
Yeah, that sound was my nipples
crystallizing into diamonds on my chest.
- Hi, Sock.
- What, god! Oh, Sam!
- Dead dad!
- Take it easy it's OK. It's OK.
Calm down. Calm down.
Mr. O?
What the hell, Sam?
- Your dad's alive?
- Well, sort of.
- What do you mean sort of?
- Technically speaking, I'm not dead,
- but I'm just not so much alive either.
- What? Why?
Well, I made that deal with the devil so
I wouldn't die, and now I Kinda can't.
That's why we had to keep the air cold.
- Right.
- It's to keep dad fresh.
Frigid. Yeah. OK.
Mr. Oliver, i'm really, really glad
that you're alive and everything, but...
I just about had a heart attack.
I think I might still be having one.
Sam, why the hell would
you ever do that to me?!
Because I knew you'd wanna be here.
- Why? What for?
- When Ben's shift ends.
Oh, my god. This is brilliant. OK, good.
Hey, get down. Go. Get down. Get down.
Hey, remember, say...
this time, all right? OK.
Hola. Benjamin.
- Let's go for a ride, man.
- No, thanks.
I mean,
today was a really stressful day.
I was at the returns counter,
and people were yelling at me.
I just wanna go home, slip into a warm
bath, just forget today ever happened.
All right. Well, we were gonna hit
Anderson's ice cream shop,
get a little snowblast, extra oreo
crumble, but, whatever. No big deal.
Actually that sounds
really relaxing, too.
- All right, I'm in.
- Let's do it.
-= 205 =-
" I Want My Baby Back "
Sub VO :  ¤Aka¤
Subs-Addicts"
[Sub-way.fr]
- How old is this?
- Stop. Look. Listen.
Listen to the hotness.
You know, Kristen is actually a pretty
cool person and fun to be around.
If you stopped sexualizing your sister
all the time, you might realize that.
You know what? It's like you're talking.
I can hear the stupid words fallin'out
of your mouth, but they hold no meaning.
Take me and Nina.
We're friends,
but we have our sexual side.
But then we keep it in a box
and take it out when we need it.
We enjoy it.
We play with it.
We put it back in the box
when we're all done.
There is no box that can
contain this sexuality, Ben.
All right? Uncontainable.
It's how I was born.
In fact, the delivery room doctor said I
was the sexiest baby she'd ever seen,
- so...
- Fine. Your loss then.
These things are great.
Bumper cars with deadly sharp blades.
- Will you stop that?
- All right, grumpy.
Here's the vessel for your next soul,
Tracy reed.
Thought she was a vampire
when she was alive.
Seriously, she was a vampire?
Well, you do know that vampires
don't really exist, don't you, Sam?
She's just a murderer
who liked to drink people's blood.
Lookin' sharp, Buffy. Lookin' sharp.
All right.
Anything else?
Hey, you're bein'extra snotty today,
aren't you?
This couldn't have something
to do with a certain reappearance of a
decaying,
Frankly gross father figure, could it?
You know, you can joke all you want,
but I feel kind of bad for him.
You feel bad?
Why should you feel
anything for that guy?
Don't you recall? He's the architect
of your situation here.
He sold your soul.
And you feel bad?
Sorta.
Well, then I feel I have to impart
some fatherly advice to you,
ironic as that may seem.
Don't let people walk
all over you, buddy.
Screw that guy.
He had no problem screwing you.
This is it.
Vampire soul lives here.
You had to wear the squeaky ones.
They look good with these pants.
What do you want me to do? They do.
It's just it's not subtle.
It's like you're announcing to the evil
souls that we here is all I'm saying.
You know what, Sam? I risk my neck
for you on a daily basis, all right?
If I'm gonna die, i'm gonna die
lookin'tasty in a fashionable
principles. Get some.
It's so emo in here.
I love it.
You can't have it.
You're not taking it from me.
We're not here to Rob you.
Yeah, we're just here to
send you back to hell.
I'll kill you.
You can't touch it!
Oh, god! Oh, god, Sam!
Vampire on my back, Sam!
All right. Yes.
That wasn't too bad, actually.
Totally.
- Baby rattle.
- Yeah, and there's a carriage.
"Pregnancy, birth, and baby."
That's a baby, right?
- That's a baby.
- We've got a baby.
Next.
Hey, there, Glady-cakes.
- Place the vess.
- Way ahead of you.
We were wondering what to do with this.
The soul in the vessel, it's hers.
- An iboh.
- What's an iboh?
Intentional birth out of hell.
It happens.
Souls have been known to escape from
hell to have their children here.
Better schools.
OK, great. So this has
happened before then. Perfect.
We were wondering if there was,
like, a procedure in place
- that can handle these circumstances.
- Yeah, there is.
Have fun raising it.
No. We can't raise the baby.
Any idiot can raise a baby,
which makes you more than qualified.
No. What if this one's evil, Gladys?
Its mom had fangs.
Nobody's gonna wanna
breast-feed a fang baby. Yeah.
I think you're OK.
- It's probably just a regular baby.
- Probably?
Yeah, but if you're worried, I can stuff
it down the return chute if you want.
I'm a little worried, yeah.
Why don't you just ask
your little girlfriend for some help?
She dates you.
She must know a lot about babies.
She happens to have an important
job that she's busy with right now,
unlike you and your stupid stupidness.
Next.
There is an envelope
for you up at the front.
You took down all
my motivational posters.
Guess your want your employees
to only soar to regular heights.
- Envelope, Ted.
- Yes, you may.
Thank you.
That's sweet.
Sam taking you out on the town?
- Yeah. We're a little stressed lately.
- Stressed?
Maybe it's not Sam.
Maybe it's the job.
You know what they say.
This job makes a man go insane,
especially if that man is a woman.
- Get out, Ted.
- Thank you, boss.
We got a clean-up in aisle 3.
I don't think we're gonna learn anything
about taking care of a baby from
honey, I blew up the kid.
Just wait until the kid's done on the
rampage. We'll learn plenty. Trust me.
- What are we gonna do with it?
- Why don't you know?
I mean, you're the one with
those little rabbits
and birdies and small creatures, I mean,
this is your wheelhouse, buddy. Step up.
Yeah, man. Come on.
It's probably hungry.
We need mother's milk.
Well, sorry.
I'm not lactating right now.
Where do we find someone
with fleshy milk dispensers?
A baby?
Where did you get a baby?
A friend.
We're borrowing it from a friend.
- "Borrowing it"?
- Looks like a little doll.
- Can I hold it?
- Sure.
Hi, little baby.
Oh, my god.
I'm so jealous of that baby right now.
I wish I was cradled to her bosoms,
cradled like a baby.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Excuse us.
- Did you hear yourself just now?
- What happened?
You were looking at
a little infant nuzzling
against your stepsister's breasts,
and you said you were jealous of it.
I said that out loud?
- Oh, my god.
- You're sick, and you need help.
Benjy. I'm dyin'over here, man. What do
I do? How do I make this sexual...
tension disappear?
You, Nina and i, we play racquetball.
It's a great way to
release the aggression.
It sounds like a lot of work.
All right, well, there's also,
you know, drugs that people take
to lower testosterone
and help dull the sex drive.
- Isn't that chemical castration?
- You don't need to name it.
You just need a solution
to your sick problem.
I hate it when you
call me sick like that.
Well, deal with it.
Right. OK, all right,
here are my options, right?
I medicate my boys into submission...
Or I work out for 15 minutes a day?
As far as I can see it.
Terrycloth wristbands are for fashion,
Benjamin, not for exercise.
Chemical castration it is.
Good. Let's go.
OK, now do a monkey. Do a monkey.
More monkey. Monkier.
Sam, you are here.
- Hey, guys, look who it is.
- Look who's back in town!
I'm back. I'm back.
You can't live in fear forever.
Plus, I came to warn you.
I think they're dispatching some
demon assassins to kill you.
We know. Ben's dating one of them.
Yeah, we're a power couple.
You what is that? Is that do you...
Do you guys have a baby?
Hey, look at you.
There we go. It's OK.
There you go.
Yeah, aren't you just a bundle
of cuteness? Yes, you are.
- Is it a girl?
- Probably.
I don't know.
We didn't even check.
You haven't changed a diaper?
For how long?
Have you burped her? Have you fed her?
Have you cleaned her?
Guys, this is a precious
and delicate little gift.
You can't treat it like a turtle you got
at a market and forget about it.
Do you want it?
She's beautiful.
You know, steve and I were
on an adoption waiting list.
When he passed away, just another one
of those dreams that I had to let go of.
Well, now's the moment, tone.
You gotta seize the dream.
Seize it right out of our hands.
Maybe there's a reason
I came here today.
Maybe I was meant to come.
Maybe it was fate.
I can't think of a better
person to take care of her.
Yeah. You're gonna be a great dad.
I'm a daddy.
- Congrats, papa Tony.
- All right.
And Stevie.
After Steve, I'm gonna call her Stevie.
I already named her Magnum P.I.
Little Stevie.
- Hi. Are you open?
- Are you Miss Prendergast?
Your table's right this way.
You came.
That's great.
- I came to meet Sam.
- I didn't invite Sam.
No. Apparently you didn't invite anyone.
Did you just rent out
this whole place for us?
- It's Kinda my thing, you know?
- This is "your thing"?
Date ambush?
You've gotta be kidding me.
Don't go. Look,
you don't have to feel uncomfortable.
I brought you a nicer dress. You could
change, maybe even put your hair up.
No, let me just make one thing
clear here, OK? I am with Sam,
period.
My misunder standing. I didn't realize
you guys were in it for the long haul.
We are.
Not gonna lie.
It's pretty bush-league on your part.
I mean, I did go through all
the effort to set this up.
But you know,
you gotta do what you gotta do.
You're such an ass.
OK, but if Sam wasn't in the picture,
you'd stay for dinner, right?
- Not a chance.
- Why?
You're obnoxious,
you're arrogant, and you're rude.
And your father is the devil.
- I didn't think that mattered to you.
- Really? And why would you think that?
Given your current relationship,
why wouldn't I think that?
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Since Sam and I have the same father,
I just figured you'd accepted Satan
in your life.
Yeah, you know that Sam
is the son of the devil.
Did I just speak out of turn?
I assumed you knew.
Looks like both of
our nights are ruined now.
Sorry.
- When's your doctor's appointment?
- Noon today.
Just takin' the dog
out for one last walk.
That's gross.
It's for the best.
Did you hear that?
He's back.
- I'll take care of it.
- Do it.
Dad!
What are you doin'?
I just thought I'd stop by
and set up the badminton net
and bang the old shuttlecock
around with you.
I don't really have time now.
Well, maybe tomorrow then.
- Yeah. I'll try.
- Good, 'cause, you know, Sam, I...
I really make the effort to
spend some more time together.
This bein' undead, it, kind of frees me
up from everyday obligations, you know.
Don't have to work. Don't have to eat.
But, hey, lots of free time.
- Come one game. Come on.
- Dad, I really. I have to go to work.
- OK. Well, that's too bad.
- Maybe next time, call ahead.
Call ahead. Great idea.
I will do that, Sam!
Sam, anything you wanna tell me?
Any little details that
might be important for me to understand
while I'm dating you?
I'm... allergic to tree nuts.
Any other nuggets
of info you wanna share?
- Like what?
- I don't know.
Like maybe Satan is your real father?
I was gonna tell you.
I was planning on telling you.
- When?
- Andi, I...
Who told you? Was it Ben?
No, it was Sock, right?
What? They know?
Sam! OK, you know what? How long were
you planning on keeping this from me?
I was waiting for the right moment to
tell you so you wouldn't freak out.
- What?! Get over.
- OK. All right. All right.
What made you think
that you could deceive me like this?
I should not have kept the secret
from you. Another secret.
I just... I thought it would be better
to keep you in the dark for a while.
No, Sam. It's pretty clear
why you'd keep this a secret.
I mean, come on.
You're the son of the devil, OK? I...
Me being in the dark is better for you.
- Because I was afraid of this.
- Of what?
- This! Upsetting you.
- Well, too late. I'm upset.
I know,
and I didn't want that to happen.
I didn't understand what it all meant,
and I still don't.
I know. You're fired.
- Andi, what?
- Yep. You're fired.
I'm pretty sure you
legally can't do that.
OK, you know what? I don't care.
I mean, I have to do something.
So then fine. You know what?
You're on dumpster duty forever.
You know what else?
Not!
- OK, I deserved that.
- Clean that up!
Yes! Right away! On it!
Andi, come on. I just.
Hear me out, all right?
You just can't come
bursting into people's offices.
I might have been naked in here.
- What are you doing here?
- Just wanted to talk to you.
It seems we're having a small
accounting error in purgatory.
- So I owe money now?
- No. A soul. We're missing one.
Not your fault.
Just kind of slipped through the cracks.
Tell me who it is so you can
get the hell out of here.
You already know who it is, the baby.
- The baby?
- That soul
escaped specifically to have her baby
out of hell, and you know what?
No one gets out of hell,
not even offspring.
I'm not sending a little baby to hell.
I can understand your hesitation, but...
You mustn't allow yourself to
be fooled by its pudgy cuteness.
Kid is a bad seed.
It's destined for evil
- like its mother.
- I don't know what to tell you. I...
We gave it away.
That just won't work, Sammy.
I know that this'll be hard for you,
so don't rush.
Just have it back by say,
this time tomorrow.
Because if you don't retrieve this kid,
I will...
And it won't be pretty for
anybody who gets in my way.
I can't believe you got
drugs from a doctor so easily.
Excess testosterone, Benji.
People get intimidated.
It is my gift and my curse.
Also, I weaseled some pills out
of him to help with your scalp itch.
Thanks, man.
- When are you gonna take yours?
- I'm working my way up to it, OK, Ben!
I just wanna hang on to my manhood for
a couple more hours. Is that all right?
I just got off the phone with Tony. He's
cookin' us lunch at his new apartment.
He's not gonna let go
of that baby easily.
No, no, but lunch is perfect, though.
Tony is both a supersensitive
demon and a culinary perfectionist.
All we gotta do, bag on his cookin'.
He starts bawlin',
runs down to the market, grabs some
locally grown organic garbage.
Once he leaves, boom, vessel the baby.
Bob's your uncle.
Dad, what are you doing here?
I came for your brains.
I'm just kiddin'.
Actually, I just thought we could
maybe hang out, watch the ballgame.
Now's not a good time.
Sam, can I speak to you for a minute?
All right, let's make this quick.
- What is your problem, Sam?
- We have to be somewhere.
OK, you know what? I gotta say
that I'm a little disappointed in you.
- Why?
- Because I'm gettin' the sense, Sam,
- that you're blowin'me off.
- What are you talking about?
You're blowin'me off, Sam,
and frankly, you're shirkin'
your family responsibilities.
Dad, this is not
my responsibility to baby-sit you.
OK? What about mom?
Get her to let you move back in.
She doesn't want me to, Sam. She's
you know...
I'm startin' to believe that
she actually blames me for this,
as if it's my fault
that I turned into a zombie.
It kind of is your fault.
- So you're pickin' sides now.
- Yes. Yes, I am.
All right? This is all your doing.
All right,
all this happened because of you.
You made a deal with the devil,
and then you lied about it.
I'm your father,
so I demand a little respect.
No, you're not!
You're not my real father!
What did you say?
I said that you're not my real father.
- I suppose the devil told you that.
- Yes, he did.
I'm guessing it's true.
You know I'm not allowed
to say anything about this, that
the deal with the devil forbids
me from telling you anything.
Well, there's my answer.
Sam, I...
I just want you to...
Remember who raised you,
who was there for you growin'up, Sam,
every step of the way,
who loved you. I did.
No matter what anyone tells you,
I love you.
And that's really all
that matters, right?
Sure. That's all that matters.
Now I gotta go send a baby to hell,
so thanks...
Dad.
Well, I am so glad you
guys were able to come out.
It's important for Stevie to be
around people that I consider family.
Family's important.
And you also get to hear about
the important milestones,
like guess what happened last
night for the first time.
- What? What?
- She gurgled.
She gurgled. That's wonderful.
Isn't it, though? It's just wonderful.
But don't let my gushing stop you guys.
Please, there's food, mimosas,
ice tea, whatever you need.
Right? Whatever you need.
Is the salad OK?
It's good.
It's. It's adequate.
Sock, what is wrong with the salad?
Nothin'. Nothin', Tony.
It's just, you know, I...
To tell you the truth, I had a salad
the other day that was loaded
with shiitake mushrooms, and it
just Kinda blew my mind, that's all.
No problem. I have shiitake in
the kitchen. I'll throw them in there.
I don't even think it's the mushrooms
that are the problem.
It's not?
No, it's... tomatoes.
What's wrong with the tomatoes?
They're very ripe.
That's unacceptable.
I apologize.
There's a grocery right
around the corner.
He's got fresh ones.
I'll be back in a jiff.
- Just keep eating.
- Wait.
You know,
we could take care of the baby for you.
- Yeah, We could watch the baby.
- Why not?
OK, yes. OK, sure. Right. I don't wanna
be one of those smothering parents.
OK. I'll be back in a minute.
You guys have my cell number
if there's a problem, right?
- Absolutely.
- OK. OK, tomatoes.
- I can't believe that worked.
- Well, the tomatoes are a little ripe.
All right, let's shove a spike
through this baby's face.
OK, Sam, go. Do it.
Sam, come on. Do it. Do it.
Do it.
- I can't do it.
- Come on.
It's a little baby. Look at it, with
its big eyes and its little fingers.
I can't stick a stake in it.
What if the devil is tricking me,
trying to get me to stab this baby?
I thought he said it was gonna be evil,
do monstrous things like its mom
It doesn't look anything like a monster.
So then what do we do?
I don't know. It's lookin'
at me all cute and stuff.
Cover it up. Cover up the baby.
Here we go.
There. Now you can stab
that baby guilt-free. Go.
That's gonna smother the baby.
Do you like that?
Peekaboo.
- Peekaboo. Peekaboo.
- Ben! Ben, you're not helping.
OK, wait, wait, wait. I got it.
What if what if we sing it to sleep?
That way, it won't be looking at me,
and it'll just make it easier
on the both of us.
- Good, good, good.
- Yeah, I like it.
Twinkle lullaby
and good night
you gotta get a spike in your baby eye
As luck would have it,
my neighbor had a couple of fresh ones.
So...
What's goin' on?
This isn't what it looks like.
Stay away from my daughter.
Hi. What did they do to you?
Tony, nothing. Nothing.
What is this?
No, tony,
the devil told me she has to go back,
that she's a bad seed, an evil monster.
The devil is full of lies.
This baby's innocent.
She's not a monster!
Oh, god! Benji!
Tony, the devil wants her back.
I'll raise her to be good, Sam.
Babies aren't born evil.
- Humans make them evil.
- You can't stop him. He'll kill you.
- What would you have me do, Sam?!
- I'm not just gonna hand her over.
He won't stop coming for
you until he gets the baby.
We have to make the devil not want it.
How do we do that?
Baptism.
What if we baptize the baby?
If we get her baptized,
it washes away original sin.
Will that work?
If she's christened,
she'll be pure, a blank slate.
The devil won't have any claim over her,
at least for now.
That just might work.
Yeah, that just might work, baby.
Daddy's gonna get you baptized.
Yes, he's gonna have you baptized.
Hey, we're all set.
My grand-mother called
and spoke to father Ortega.
Now, he's willing to do the emergency
baptism as long as we have
- parents standing in.
- Here comes the mama.
Hey, Andi. Thank you for doing this.
You don't know how much it means to me.
Yeah, sure, Tony.
Well, there's father Ortega.
Andi, this is little Stevie.
- She's beautiful.
- Yeah, Stevie, this is Andi.
She's gonna be your mama
for today along with papa Sam.
You're not standing in as the father?
I can't. The whole, demon thing. Yeah.
I can't enter onto consecrated ground.
I'll light up like an oversoaked flambe.
But Sam's half-human,
so he's probably OK.
And I can't imagine a sweeter
couple than you and Sam to,
watch over little Stevie
at her christening.
- Right?
- Fine. Let's just get it over with.
Something going on with you and Sam?
Son of the devil.
You know, I was.
I was right there with you.
I thought Sam was full of evil
just waiting to burst forth.
Heck, I even tried to kill him.
But then Steve appeared to me,
and he let me know that
Sam is worth saving.
I just don't think his
fate is tied to the devil.
Do you know that?
Well, you don't know anything for sure.
The devil says this
baby belongs in hell, but
I look at that angel face,
and all I see is the good.
And that's what I see
when I look at Sam.
I can't prove that. That's something
that you need to look for in Sam,
find for yourself.
Right?
- Why are you staring at me?
- You didn't burst into flames.
Why would I burst into flames?
Tony said that he couldn't
walk on consecrated ground
without lighting on fire.
Just thought it may be the same for you.
- What, you didn't think to warn me?
- No. I was testing you.
- And you would've deserved it.
- You're probably right.
So are we good?
I don't know yet.
You know, when I look at you,
I see the Sam that I've known for years,
the Sam that I know would be here
doing good,
trying to save this baby.
But it also really worries
me who your father is.
It worries me, too.
Look, Andi, I think there's good
inside me. I hope there is.
But, you know, if you ever see
anything that doesn't seem right,
run for the hills.
OK, welcome, everybody.
We could just gather around.
We're ready to get started.
Just have to take care of
a little business first.
OK, just need you to sign
and date the bottom, both of you.
- The stroller!
- Oh, my god.
Thank you, Sammy.
I'll take that.
She's just an innocent baby.
Come on. Let her go.
Poor Sammy.
I get it.
You see yourself in her,
the poor innocent who gets screwed
by someone else's bad choices.
But I told you before,
she is no innocent.
How do you know for su?
Because she's destined for evil.
Nature versus nurture.
No amount of loving parenting
will change this kid.
Look, I've been around a long time,
and from everything I've seen,
nature always wins.
- Doesn't it, honey?
- All right, fine.
If she's gonna be so terrible,
just let her stay
- here on earth.
- What are you babbling on about?
She's destined for evil, right?
I mean, isn't that what you want,
people to do evil things?
Let her grow up and go
totally sick on the world.
I want souls, Sammy.
That's my deal.
But imagine how many more
souls she could deliver to you.
How many people will she hurt?
Boyfriends, friends.
People she can mess up, who will
probably turn evil themselves, right?
I mean,
you could have one soul or dozens.
You don't even know what she's
gonna be when she grows up.
What if she's a teacher?
What if she's a psychiatrist?
Think how many people
she can damage like that.
Hey, maybe you'll become a Politician,
even President.
Yes. Yes, absolutely.
That's what I'm saying.
There you go.
Here you go.
- What a performance, man.
- What are you saying?
Did you really think I would fall
for that "she'll be evil" bit?
You're really bummin' me out, man.
You think i'm such a dummy.
I know how this story ends,
how this kid is gonna turn out,
the same way I know how
you're gonna turn out.
You can't stop nature, Sammy.
And I'll very much enjoy the look
on your face when I'm proven right.
What are you doing?
- Hey, sis. What?
- What's this?
Th-this? This is,
this is nothin'. This is
a pill the doctor told me to take.
I have a small problem.
Well, not small. It's, you know,
more of an average-sized problem.
And, I need to take these
to tame my...
vivaciousness.
I need to take
my free and curious, outgoing nature
and put it inside of a box
to make myself a better
brother and person.
I'm too spirited.
It would break my heart if
you were any less spirited.
I won't let you.
I never want
your wonderful spirit to change.
Kristen, I...
you have been so loving and attentive,
and if you change that wonderful spirit,
that will change me,
- and that'll be sad.
- Yeah.
You're right. I don't know what
I was thinkin' with the...
you are very, very,
very sweet and perceptive.
You are a good person.
This is good, right?
This is yeah.
You are an amazing sister.
Now, we need to make sure
that you don't change.
What can I do to help you?
- Help me?
- Yeah. Anything.
I will do anything for you.
Just tell me what it is you need
from me, and I will give it.
Serve's up!
In your face!
Serve it up.
Thank you. I'll see you next week.
Go away.
Testy.
- Everything all right?
- No, I know why you're here,'K?
You have some sick need
to mess with me and Sam.
Not gonna work,
so thanks for stoppin'by.
I'm not gonna mess with you. I'm just
surprised you're still datin'him.
- Bein' the son of the devil and all.
- You know, Sam is a good guy.
- He's not you.
- Really?
Yeah, and with everything
that hangs over Sam's head,
he still manages to be
a good and decent person.
I think he'll always be that way.
That's amazing.
No, no. I'm impressed
by your intuitiveness.
You can see evil.
I'm still tryin'to hone that knack.
Evil's a tough one to spot.
You know, it lurks...
Down in those deep, dark corners.
It's hard to see.
And they say the worst evil
comes in a friendly form...
nice smile, familiar eyes...
and it's never recognized.
Well, until it's too late.
Especially if you're in love.
They say evil is impossible
to see if it's got your heart.
But good for you that you so confident
about Sam. I mean, That's great.
I must have missed it,
but good eye, Andi.
Good job.
Well, this is the place.
You're gonna move into this?
Yeah. Unit 18.
- It's a great storage facility.
- To live in?
Yeah. It's climate-controlled, quiet.
The first month is free.
Are you sure mom won't
let you move back?
No, Sam.
She made it pretty clear we're over.
She blames me for
everything that happened, and
she's got every right not to forgive me.
But, hey, what do you think we,
put a flatty on the wall,
some chili pepper string lights,
get my old seahawks posters framed.
Could be a real man-cave, right?
Dad...
I can't stay mad at you.
You're my father.
What?
You know, if...
If I am a good person,
it's because of how I was raised, and...
you raised me well, dad.
You're a good son.
Anyway,
let's, get this sucker unloaded and
- move in.
- Wait. Dad.
I have a better idea.
A little turn to the left. OK.
All right.
Hey, guys.
- How was the ride over?
- Good. Good. This is great.
Hey, I got a bunch of refrigerator
magnets from the bench,
so you can style and decorate
it any way you want, OK?
That's fantastic, Ben.
'K, I wanna be really clear
about something, Mr. O.
you are a garage roomie only? I don't
want you wandering inside the house.
- It's off limits to the mostly dead.
- I understand completely.
- OK, then. Welcome aboard.
- Stay cool, Mr. Oliver.
I will. I will.
And, you know, this place is so roomy.
I'll have to have a party
and invite you guys over.
Totally.
- You are a good son.
- I second that!
Team Subs-Addicts"