Right now, terrorists are plotting
to assassinate a presidential candidate.
My teenage daughter is missing.
And people that I work with
may be involved in both.
I'm FederalAgent Jack Bauer. Today
is going to be the longest day ofmy life.
- I've rewritten the speech.
- What are you gonna say about our son?
That seven years ago he was involved in an
accidental death. I want you to stand by me.
- Nina, what is goin' on?
- Jack said CTU had been infiltrated.
- We can't trust Jamey.
- Are you saying Jamey's a spy?
Talk to us, Jamey.
Who's got Jack's wife and daughter?
I didn't know any of this was gonna happen.
There is no time, Jamey. Palmer is exposed.
Jack's family is in danger.
You have to start talking to us now!
Jack Bauer, CTU.
You'll be tempted to intervene,
but believe me, Jack,
ifyou do, your family dies
and we'll get Palmer anyway.
After he shoots Palmer,
he will handyou his weapon.
You gotta be kidding me.
Gun! Gun!
- Bauer, what's happening?
- I didn't do this.
Do you understand?
Please, don't hurt my family. Please!
That's it, we're done. Kill the wife and kid!
- Eli.
- Yeah?
I still need 'em alive.
Senator, stay here
until I secure the area.
- Fine.
- Let's get him out.
All right, we're on the move.
Berkin, stay with the senator.
Hey, hold on, there.
Senator, we're clear. Let's go.
Let's go!
Let's go. Inside.
- Frank Simes?
- This is Bauer?
- Yes.
- You gotta help me out.
I understand you're obliged to follow
procedure, but please hear me out.
- I did this intentionally.
- That I believe.
- I didn't mean it like that.
- You called me at 6.30 this morning
to get clearance to bring
a weapon to the breakfast.
Exactly. If I wanted to shoot someone, I
would've used my own gun. I didn't need his.
- What happened?
- I saw him, walked over, identified myself.
When I said I had to take him in,
he went for my gun.
I had to create a scene
to get Palmer out of the room.
If you wanted to get him out of the room,
why didn't you tell us there was a problem?
- I'm working under a restricted mandate.
- Cut the crap, Bauer.
- Your own people called you in as a suspect.
- What?
Tony Almeida from your office called one of
my men and told us you presented a threat.
Almeida doesn't have the same information
that I've got. You're running out of time.
You had a shooter disguised
as a photographer in here. He's escaped.
Palmer's life is still in danger.
Frank, don't go.
I've gotta get outta here! Come on!
Get me Palmer's security. And a list of
photographers who checked in this morning.
Yeah, I'll wait.
You sold classified information.
People are dead cos of you.
The only chance you got of
helpin' yourself is by talkin' to us now.
Jamey! The guy you work for,
what's his name?
I call him Gaines.
I don't know if that's his real name.
Do you have any idea where
he might be holding Teri and Kim?
Jamey, stay with us, here.
I needed the money. That's all.
- I didn't think anyone would die.
- Yeah, well, they did.
You better get it together
if you wanna help yourself.
Is Gaines the one watching us
through our surveillance?
And you set that up?
I can't do anything in here.
I have to get on the floor.
We can't cut their video, cos Gaines'll get
suspicious when he sees you walkin' around.
I know what to say to him.
Did Jonathan get a shot off?
He hasn't checked in.
Find him and tell him to get over here.
I need to know what happened.
What the hell is goin' on?
- Gaines.
- It's Jamey.
- Why are you using a phone?
- It's OK, we're clear.
- I had to remove our tap.
- What the hell is happening?
You know that new engineer
they brought in - Milo Pressman?
He was getting close to my entry
to the surveillance system.
You said you could take care
of this for me, Jamey!
And I did. I removed the tap. You don't need it
any more. I'm just trying to protect you.
You wanna protect me? Get me Bauer!
- They're taking him to Division.
- Division? Division? I gotta get him back.
- And you will.
- When?
I need him now, and if that's not
gonna happen, I will move on.
Look, don't do anything until I call over there
and find out what's happening.
All right. Get back to me.
- He's not waiting around much longer.
- I'm going to work up the name Gaines.
- Where have you been?
- I had to go out.
There was some incident
this morning with Palmer.
We know. We're working on it.
What are you doing?
Nothing. I'm waiting for
the key card from Tony.
Forget about that.
You're taking over all of Jamey's projects.
- Why?
- Doesn't matter. She's no longer on the team.
Fine, but if I'm gonna take over
an entire department, I want a bump in pay.
Just do it, Milo. You'll be taken care of.
It appears that someone may have had
a gun. Right now, Senator David Palmer...
Bam!
- That's all we have.
- Mark, call me the minute you find out.
- I will.
- What did he say?
Just that they have someone in custody.
They don't know who.
I don't know why you just didn't listen to
Secret Service the first time they told you.
Sherry, don't overreact.
- Remember Annapolis?
- Yeah.
When they pulled me out of the auditorium?
But it turned out to be nothing.
Yeah, well, that doesn't mean this is nothing.
Oh, David, I really don't think
we should be takin' chances today.
I've been trackin' this assassin
since midnight! He was here.
I know what he looks like. I can help you,
but you've gotta let me contact my people!
- Sit down, Bauer!
- Back off!
Alan, it's OK. I got it.
You're not helpin' yourself here, Jack.
- I need to get back in this case.
- That's not going to happen.
I have no choice
but to turn you over to the FBl.
- Can I speak to you off the record?
- No.
We can talk on the record.
I know you're a good agent, Bauer. You want
to tell me what's really going on here?
If you ever repeat what
I'm about to tell you, I will deny it.
You'll understand as soon as I explain.
My wife and daughter are being held hostage.
If I do not get out of this, they will be killed.
- Who's holding them?
- The people that want Palmer dead.
They used me to smuggle a weapon
through security and give it to the assassin.
Did you?
- Yes.
- I'm not sure you want me to believe that.
I had to. They were gonna kill my family. But
I got Palmer out of the room. I saved his life.
This sounds crazy, but you've gotta believe
me. Phone my house, send a cruiser over.
My family is gone, they have been taken.
You have to let me go.
If I can get out there, I can be the conduit
to these people. I can bring them down.
I don't have the authority to release you. I'm
gonna turn you over to District for a debrief.
You tell 'em what you told me, maybe
they can help you out of your situation.
- They won't.
- Alan, you and Mitchell take him down.
- Sorry, Jack.
- You will be if Palmer dies.
I'll take him.
Keep movin'.
Don't move! Don't move!
All right. Go ahead.
- Hold it right there!
- Get down now!
Stay down!
- Don't shoot! It'll explode!
- Do not fire.
We don't need an explosion in here.
Take it outside!
Bauer!
Get outta the way!
Bauer's heading south. Do you copy?
Bauer!
- Open the passenger door!
- Don't shoot!
Open the door! Don't panic.
I don't wanna hurt you.
- There he is!
- Drive the car!
Drive! Drive!
Drive the car!
- Turn left into this driveway now.
- OK.
Make a right at the end of the parking lot.
- Turn right! Turn right!
- OK! OK!
Dammit!
Back it up.
- No, no, no. Back up the other way.
- All right!
Go forward. Go into the construction site.
- Go, go, go!
- OK.
Slow down. Let this truck pass.
Turn in there. Through the gates.
Parking spot on the left. Take it.
Calm down. I just need to make
one phone call and then I'll let you go.
Put the car in park.
Now get out of the car.
Please get out of the car. Get out of the car.
Come on.
OK.
Get under the scaffolding.
Up the stairs. Quick. Go.
Go.
- Open the door.
- It's locked.
How could you do this?
Betray your country. Be responsible
for the death of people you work with.
I didn't know any of that
was going to happen.
Oh, that's right. You just
tapped on the keyboard, right?
So, how much they payin' you, huh?
A million? Two million?
300,000.
I could use 300,000 bucks. Everybody
around here could use some extra cash.
I had a husband who left me and my son
with nothing. I had to do something.
- And this is what you did?
- Yeah, that's right.
I work twice as hard as anyone here,
and I make half as much.
- Do you think that's fair?
- You didn't have to take the job.
You don't know
what kind of pressure I'm under.
Oye, eres una vergüenza.
Got Milo working on the name Gaines.
What else has she given you?
- Excuses.
- Well, we gotta keep Gaines calm.
Call him and say Jack's on his way
back to CTU from Division.
- Keep him on the phone as long as you...
- I'm not saying anything until I get immunity.
In writing, signed by Chapelle.
- Hello?
- Jack!
Thank God you're OK.
They wanted me to kill you.
That's why I put the flak jacket on -
I couldn't think of anything else.
- Why did they want you to kill me?
- You started piecing it together.
- Nina, I am so sorry.
- No, it's OK. I'm fine.
What's happening with Teri and Kim?
They're being held hostage. They said they'd
kill them if I didn't help them take out Palmer.
Where are you now?
Secret Service had me in custody,
but I just got away.
- Where are you?
- I'm back at CTU.
They've tapped into our surveillance.
Don't worry about it.
We found their inside person. It's Jamey.
No, no, no, that's not possible.
Walsh cleared her.
We've got her right here.
She's already confessed.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. She had access to everything.
Did she mention Teri or Kim?
She just knows there was
someone named Gaines.
- What else?
- She's not cooperating.
What do you mean?
She wants a letter of immunity
from Chapelle before she says anything.
- Is she there?
- Yeah.
Put her on the phone.
- Talk to him.
- No.
Jamey.
- She's listenin'.
- Jamey?
Yeah?
I know that Nina and Tony don't understand
what you're going through, but you know me.
I don't care about protocol
and I am true to my word.
If you help me bring down Gaines and
help get my wife and daughter back safely,
I promise you I will get you out of this.
- You don't have the power to do that.
- Of course I do.
Right now only four of us know about this.
I can take care of Nina and Tony.
I can get this done. Jamey, please.
No. You'll say anything.
I want the immunity first.
What do you want me to do, Jack?
She has a son named Kyle.
- Bring him in.
- Wait a minute, Jack. You can't do that.
- You gotta be careful.
- I also need a car.
Put a CTU com unit in it, box of 9mm ammo,
a locksmith kit, the whole package.
- And then?
- I'll try and get out of this situation.
- I'm gonna go find Teri and Kim.
- Where do you want the car?
Corner of Temple and Mercer.
OK.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Who are you? What's goin' on?
A few hours ago someone
kidnapped my wife and daughter.
I don't get it. Then why are you
runnin' from the police?
What's your name? Lauren?
I'm Jack. I work for
a special branch of the government.
Last night I was given
a very important assignment.
Right now someone is trying
to stop me from doing it.
You don't believe me, do you?
If I were you, I wouldn't believe me either.
What I wanna know is, why do you have me
here? You got a car, you got a place to hide.
I can't afford to be taken back into custody.
If they get close enough, I have to make them
believe I'm willing to do something crazy.
Like shoot me?
I'm not gonna shoot you.
You know somethin'?
I think I believe you.
- What are you doing?
- You're not the only one who has problems.
I just came off of a hellacious night shift,
I'm due in court in 45 minutes
on a DUl charge, of which I'm guilty,
so, you know,
good luck with your crisis, OK?
Don't!
Lauren, I have killed
two people since midnight.
I have not slept for over 24 hours.
So maybe... maybe you should be a little
more afraid of me than you are right now.
Sit.
- Are you OK?
- Oh, no need to worry.
- We heard there was someone with a gun.
- Um, it's not clear what happened.
And I'm afraid I'm intact and as grouchy
as ever. So let's all get back to work.
- Where's Keith?
- He left about a half-hour ago.
- Did he say where?
- No.
- Look, I'm a little worried about him.
- Why?
He wasn't being himself.
He stormed out of here like he was angry.
- I'm sure he'll be all right, Anna. Thanks.
- OK.
Should we... send someone after him?
No. No, he's OK.
He just needs some time alone.
I'll call Secret Service.
David.
I know how you feel about telling our side
of the story first, but there is no time for that.
Maureen is gonna go on air at nine o'clock.
That's 40 minutes from right now.
Isn't there anything we can do to stop her?
She won't budge.
And why would she?
"Candidate's son faces murder charges.
Cover-up suspected. " It's a huge story.
I cannot believe that you are just going to
accept this without puttin' up a fight.
There's nothing to fight. It doesn't matter
who breaks the story, me or Maureen.
- We have to deal with it and get past it.
- You've done the impossible for your career.
- I'm just asking you to do it for your son.
- No.
You're asking me to rewrite history.
And if you wanted my help, you would've
asked me for it seven years ago.
Oh, for crying out loud, David!
- I need today's schedule in my office.
- Yes, sir, right away.
- Almeida.
- It's Jack. Where's Nina?
She's workin' up some information
we got from Jamey.
- Is Kyle there yet?
- No, not yet.
- What about the car?
- Nina sent it. Should be there... ten minutes.
- Good. Anything else from Jamey?
- Nothing useful, no.
Tony, Secret Service told me that you were
the one who told 'em to take me outta play.
Yeah. I felt I had to, Jack.
Given the information you had,
I think you made the right choice.
I didn't realise what you were goin' through.
You didn't need me givin' you attitude.
Yeah, well, I appreciate that. Look,
I wish I knew earlier who I could trust.
I'm just glad you were there
when Nina came back to CTU.
Yeah.
- I'll call you as soon as I get to the car.
- All right.
Bye.
Hey, Lauren. Come here, to the window.
See that tool there,
looks like a hedge trimmer?
What, the bolt cutters?
Yes, the bolt cutters.
Could you get them for me, please?
Hey. Hey. I'll be watching you.
Good.
Do it with a burst. Give it everything you got.
I know how to use bolt cutters.
Good.
That was Frank Simes from
the Secret Service. What are you doin'?
- Pouring myself a drink, Mike.
- It's not even nine in the morning.
- What did Simes say?
- The CTU agent who created the disturbance
at the power plant was named Jack Bauer.
He tried to take the gun off
one of the Secret Service agents,
but claimed the gesture was misinterpreted.
- Maybe it was.
- Yeah, well...
As Bauer was being taken
into custody, he escaped.
- How the hell did he do that?
- I don't know.
But they haven't found him yet.
He's still out there.
Jack Bauer. Jack Bauer.
You know him?
I've heard the name.
Get up.
- What are you doing?
- Don't worry. I'm not gonna hurt her.
- Get up and go in the other room.
- Don't even think about touching her.
Move it!
- No.
- Don't touch her!
You stay outta this or I will hurt her.
Come on.
No! Get away! No! Get away!
Shut up!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I won't fight you.
- Mom?
- It's gonna be all right, honey.
Come on.
- Come on.
- All right.
- Fine.
- OK.
Mom!
- Maureen Kingsley.
- Thanks.
- Maureen, hi. Thanks for getting back to me.
- I'm about to go on air, Sherry. What's up?
- Don't go with the story.
- Excuse me?
The story about Keith.
Just leave it alone for right now.
The s... Hold on, please.
Can you give me one minute? Thanks.
The story about Keith is exclusive
and it's documented.
I'm not making false allegations about him.
There was an assassination attempt
this morning on my husband,
but it's being covered up.
Go on.
The man they arrested
works for the government,
and he may not have been acting alone.
Are you telling me that there's a conspiracy
inside the government to kill your husband?
I am telling you something's going on
that hasn't been reported.
And if you give me a couple of hours...
I'll milk some of my sources.
OK, look, I won't kill the story about Keith.
I'm not asking you to.
Just... hold off on it for a couple of days.
Mom.
- I'm sorry. This is all my fault.
- No, no, no. It's OK, honey. It's OK. Shh.
If I hadn't snuck out,
this wouldn't have happened.
Listen to me.
We are going to get through this.
We're gonna be a family again.
You and me and Dad
are gonna have our lives back.
This is not gonna be a part of that life.
You understand what I'm saying?
You're not gonna tell Dad?
Where did you get that?
- CTU. Myers.
- Nina, listen, it's Teri.
Teri, where are you?
Hello? Hello? Teri?
Hello? Teri?
The number's blocked.
Stand in that corner.
No, I don't wanna go on with the governor.
Put him on first. If he's got a problem,
have him talk to Mike.
- It'll look like he's introducing you.
- Good. I want it to look that way.
- OK.
- Dave, I'll talk to you later.
- Where'd you go?
- Oh, I just went out.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
Um... you didn't tell the press about me.
It's gonna come out soon, anyway.
Look, I've talked to my lawyer,
and he's got his best people workin' on it.
- His best people. Right.
- Look, Keith, don't be this way.
You're gonna be cleared. You're gonna get on
with your life without it hangin' over you.
Sure.
You ready to go?
Kingsley's gonna break the story.
Have we prepared something?
No longer necessary.
- What?
- I just got off the phone with her.
She's gonna sit on the story for now.
- Why would she do that?
- I don't know. Maybe you got through to her.
No, I didn't. It's something else.
Ready?
Maureen Kingsley decided to
hold off on the story for some reason.
- Thank God, David.
- You have any idea why she'd do that?
No. Maybe her sources weren't
as solid as she said they were.
What? Aren't you relieved?
- I wanna talk to her.
- After she gets off the air, we'll call her.
Don't you think it's smarter to let things be?
- It's smarter to know everybody's motives.
- Come on, let's go.
Come on.
- Where do you work?
- Cable's coffee shop on Ventura.
Home of the 3.99 all-day breakfast.
You married?
I used to be. But my sister moved in with us
after she got into a really bad car accident.
She couldn't take care of herself, and my...
my husband Henry told me I had to choose.
- You chose your sister?
- Yep.
- Is this your first DUl?
- First in a couple of years.
- You got a problem?
- What, a drinking problem?
I wish it were that simple.
At least then I'd have a support group.
Nope, what I'm afraid I have is bad luck.
Sorry I had to get you involved in all this.
Just let me go.
As soon as I get my car.
I used to be in the military.
Used to do field work for the CIA.
I've been to some horrible places.
I've seen some pretty terrible things.
I don't think I've ever been
this scared in my whole life.
No, I told you I'm not saying
any more until I get counsel.
- I think you will.
- Why do you think that?
Cos we're bringing Kyle here.
What?
- I'll kill you if you touch my son.
- We're not gonna lay a finger on him.
But if you don't help us find Gaines, we don't
have a choice but to bring him in here.
No, you won't.
- No.
- We will, Jamey.
Imagine the effect it'll have on him,
seeing his mother in restraints.
- Arrested for being a traitor.
- No. This is not fair.
That's a picture he's gonna
carry with him the rest of his life.
Nina...
Please.
Don't do this.
Kyle can't see me like this. Please, Nina.
He doesn't have to.
You just have to start talking to us.
The bottom line is, Jamey,
the best thing you can do for your son
is to help us get Gaines now.
Why?
Once we have you in custody, Gaines will do
anything he can to keep you from testifying.
And if he can't get to you directly,
where's he going next?
Your son, right?
Kyle...
I'm just...
confused.
I need time to think.
Take a couple of minutes.
Lauren, I'm in big trouble.
I need your help, please.
I've gotta get to a car, but if I step outside,
they'll take me into custody.
- And you want me to pick it up?
- Yes.
- Bring it back here. Park it round the side.
- Why didn't your friend drop it off here?
The person dropping it off was just following
orders. He couldn't know it was for me.
Aw! Do you realise how insane this sounds?
Yes, I do.
OK, let's just say for the sake
of argument I believe half of it.
Just tell me one thing. Is your wife
and daughter really in trouble?
Yes, they are.
- All right. Where's the car?
- Over on the corner of Temple and Mercer.
It's a silver sedan, government plates.
The keys'll be in it.
Keep going, Lauren. Keep going. Come on.
No.
- Hey! Hey! Excuse me!
- No!
Dammit!
Jack! He's out the window! I see him!
All right, this is Hayes. I got a 20 on Bauer.
- So, what have you got?
- I tried "Gaines" under various spellings.
I came up with a long list of those with
records and those with criminal associations.
Crosscheck it with everything else we got
tonight. Plane crash, Alan York, Penticoff.
Got it.
- She's had enough time to think about it.
- Yeah.
Jamey's son Kyle's gonna be brought in.
Call me in ITS when he gets here.
- Wait. What kinda trouble is she in?
- No trouble.
Don't treat me like I'm stupid.
You tell me to take over her stuff,
you and Tony are gone for an hour,
now you're bringing her son in?
- She's in trouble. I wanna know what's...
- You're not an internal affairs agent.
Keep quiet. Call us when Kyle gets here, OK?
- He's gonna figure it out.
- It won't be a secret much longer anyway.
But we need to bring Milo in. Whatever
Jamey gives us, he'll be the one to work it up.
- I hope it's somethin' substantial.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
- Get her out of those!
- Jamey?
What's the number?
- Hang in there. Come on. Come on, now.
- We need medical help. We're in ITS.
Hurry!
Grab her legs.
Watch her head. Jamey, what have you done?
- What?
- It's Milo. Should I bring Jamey's son in?
No! Keep him out of here.
It's Gaines.
Visiontext Subtitles: Kerrie Slavin
ENGLISH SDH