Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles...
There's a warehouse in the desert.
They're building something there...
metal.
- Who are you?
- Winston.
Where's the metal?
I talked to your mom.
She found something.
Is it real this time?
I detected this audio
transmission on an unsecured line.
- Got a breach... man shot out.
- Shut the place down!
You mind telling me where you keep
your demolition materials?
God, I hate funerals.
Anybody who knew anything
is already dead.
Well, I'm not.
Did you know my husband, Sarah?
The whole place was wired,
every house.
Every move anyone ever made
was being watched.
Mom, you've been sick.
Chasing robots will do that to you.
Midnight is the witching hour...
If you believe that kind of thing,
and most people won't admit it.
Midnight is the time when a door opens
from our world into the next,
and we are visited by the dark spirits
of the shadow lands.
The incubus, the succubus,
the old hag.
Visitors are known by many names,
but each story bears the same marks.
The demons come after midnight
in the first three hours of the new day
when we are alone and vulnerable,
deep asleep and helpless,
when we cannot move.
They lay on us,
press on us, suffocate us.
Take from us what is most precious.
Our lives, our love,
our sanity.
Our sleep.
If you believe
in that kind of thing.
Where are you?
In an industrial park near downtown.
God, mom, it's almost 12:00.
I was hoping you were asleep.
Well, it didn't take.
What are you doing?
I got a lead off the surveillance tapes
of Charm Acres.
And how many hours of people sleeping
did you have to watch?
All of them.
So where are you?
Western Iron and Metal.
They supply specialty metal tooling
equipment to desert Heat and Air.
They're connected to Skynet?
You should get on the computer,
find out who owns the place.
I'm on it.
Sarah, you had another nightmare.
I can't stay here anymore.
You've only been here one night.
Feels a lot longer.
We don't have enough data
to prescribe a treatment.
The first night
only establishes a baseline.
I'll be fine.
You go home now,
things'll only get worse.
You think two weeks without sleep
is bad? Try two or three years.
It happens.
Everyone needs their sleep.
Not everyone.
You do.
I'm gonna get you some coffee.
But I have to warn you,
this is a decaf-only facility,
all right?
- Can I help you?
- Who are you?
I'm your roommate.
Dana.
- When did you get here?
- Last night while you were asleep.
Not really asleep. More like thrashing
and screaming in your bed.
What's with the lighter?
- What lighter?
- The one in your bra.
Trying to give up smoking.
- In a sleep clinic?
- Yeah, I've got sleep problems too.
The doctors think it's related
to my chronic fatigue,
which they believe was caused
by my eating disorder,
which is why I had
the lap band surgery.
You know, the stapling your stomach.
But are the doctors
satisfied with that? No!
They wanna take away all my vices.
Well, that's not gonna happen.
- Girl's gotta sin sometime.
- Hence, the smoking.
Yeah, that and the younger men.
- Mom.
- Hey, tiger!
It's visiting time.
Cameron's in the cafeteria.
Do me a favor.
Let's keep this our little secret.
There you go.
Scrambled or hard boiled?
Scrambled.
You need a carbohydrate that makes up
at least 15% of your daily allowance.
Those won't be as good as yours.
You made pancakes?
I added a teaspoon of vanilla
to your recipe.
- I don't have a recipe.
- The recipe on the box.
Not as good as hers?
Not as good as food.
Tomorrow I'll bring you
something real to eat.
- They have anything to say?
- About what?
About what?
About why you're not sleeping.
They figured out why?
Besides the fact
the world's about to end?
You used to sleep well.
I shouldn't be here.
I should be at home.
We're fine at home.
Everything's fine.
This was a mistake.
No, this...
This is necessary.
Mom...
you're useless like this.
You haven't slept in two weeks.
You fell down the stairs.
If you don't take care of yourself,
something worse might happen.
You need to get better.
I need you to get better.
Don't forget...
You're not her.
Please... get some sleep.
You're dead.
I killed you.
And I killed you.
One of us
is gonna have to step it up.
Episode 2x16
V 1.00
Subtitles: Projet-SG
So...
You wanna know who I am?
That's the first thing
most people ask,
first thing that comes out of their
mouths when the gag comes off...
And they keep asking it over
and over again.
Psychiatrists say
naming things gives people
power over them.
They're dead wrong on that.
I already know who you are.
Yeah, right.
I forgot.
And...
you found Western Iron and Metal.
Of course,
I never expected anything less
from the girl
that used a cross-dresser
and a hypnotherapist to find us.
You know, I gotta admit,
I didn't see that one comin'.
You won't see the next one
coming either.
Oh, I beg to differ, ma'am.
I beg to differ.
So who do you work for?
I work alone.
Somebody blew up our factory
while you were getting patched up.
Was that your boyfriend
on the phone?
What are you guys, some kind of a...
Bonnie and Clyde type operation?
I said, was that your Clyde
on the phone?
Why don't you come closer,
and I'll tell you?
So you can bite my face off? No.
I don't think so.
See those seeds?
I go through about a bag
in three hours.
Little habit I picked up
when I quit smoking.
Before I finish that bag,
you're gonna talk.
Special recipe.
It'll have you singin'...
Like Sunday choir.
What's wrong?
Gel too cold?
Most people don't like
the electrodes first time.
Makes 'em feel like Frankenstein.
You'll get used to it.
I'm willing to bet you sleep
better tonight.
What's happening to me?
Let me show you something.
These are our observation machines.
And this is your chart.
There are 5 stages to the sleep cycle.
The fifth stage is the most active...
Increased respiration rate,
blood pressure, brain activity.
Rem sleep,
when most dreaming occurs.
It's rare, but sometimes...
night terrors like the ones
you're experiencing can...
I never said I was experiencing
night terrors.
You don't have to.
Your chart tells us
everything we need to know.
Night terrors can be caused
by a brain tumor.
Cancer.
Which, as far as we can tell,
you don't have.
MRI showed your brain was clear.
No heart disease,
nocturnal asthma or sleep apnea.
What's wrong with you
is in your head.
And by your head, I mean your mind.
Therapy to reduce anxiety
is part of the usual treatment.
Have you ever...
Seen a therapist?
A lot of people find
talking one-on-one
to be very helpful in breaking down
what's really going on.
Tried it.
Didn't take.
How 'bout a prescription?
Diazepam usually helps.
Don't like drugs.
Speaking of drugs...
Has your roommate
been smoking again?
I'm not interested in being
anybody's mother.
I've got two kids of my own,
and that's enough...
Did you know about this?
Besides all the other obvious hazards,
nicotine is a stimulant.
Hits the brain in seven seconds
and adds 20 heartbeats per minute.
I quit smoking years ago.
I've got too much
excitement in my life.
Yeah, don't we all?
Well, I have to file
a report on this.
I'll be back later
to attach your electrodes.
It's a dream catcher.
It's supposed to catch nightmares.
Hector made me one too.
- Hector?
- The cleaning guy.
You know, Papi Chulo
with the neck tattoo?
You look tired.
You should take that
as a compliment.
I ran into nurse Ratched
in the hallway.
She smacked my bum for the cigarette
and gave me some sleeping pills.
The good stuff.
So... what about you?
Drowning, being chased,
teeth falling out?
Being chased
should probably cover it.
You're running away from something
you don't want to deal with.
At least that's
what they say, anyway.
And you?
I burn alive.
Yeah, my whole body
just catches fire.
I try and I try.
I can't put myself out.
Anxiety about quitting smoking.
Yeah, that... or I was
a witch in another life.
They say if you die in your dreams,
you die in real life.
Oh, I've died a thousand times.
Never gets any easier.
Of all the nightmares it's caught,
surprisingly it hasn't spilled them out.
Do the bad guys ever catch you?
That's a...
Quite a collection.
Bullet wounds, stabbings.
Emergency C-section.
But that's plenty old,
that last one.
Your child must be...
15, maybe 20 by now?
They'll kill you...
Just like they killed everyone else.
- They?
- Your bosses, Kaliba.
They blew up your factory,
killed 30 of their own people.
Lady, you're insane.
Why would anyone
blow up their own factory?
- To hide what you were building.
- And what was that?
The end.
You are very...
dramatic.
Diana...
thought you were a good man.
What do you think she'd say
if she saw you now?
You...
You leave my wife out of this...
You crazy... bitch.
Dana?
Dana, wake up.
Your electrodes came off last night.
Did you take them off?
I don't remember.
Are you a sleepwalker?
It's happened once or twice.
You didn't mention that
in your intake.
Must have slipped my mind.
I'm sorry.
So you don't remember
getting out of bed last night.
I don't remember anything.
Salvador Dali
often explored the subconscious
in the dream world in his work.
Are your dreams like this painting?
Everyone's dreams are different.
Guess it depends
on what's stuck in your head.
Come on!
What's it like to dream?
It's sort of like
you're in a play or a movie.
It looks real and it feels real...
How do you know it's not real?
Sometimes you don't.
Be careful...
Yes, thank you.
What's wrong?
Something strange is going on here.
Like what?
I woke up last night
and saw the nurse
giving my roommate a shot.
Okay, well, it's a medical clinic.
So what's strange about that?
She was passed out.
She had already taken sleeping pills.
So... you think the nurse is...
What, like the angel of death?
After she gave her the shot, she went
downstairs to a room in the basement.
Well, she looks all right.
She's not.
No one is.
Mom...
- Did you sleep last night?
- You think I'm making this up?
No. I don't think
you're making this up.
It's just...
You're a mess.
You don't be fooled, John.
Don't be fooled by anyone's face.
You don't know
what's behind anyone's face.
You talking about
the guy at the factory?
The one who shot you?
The one you shot?
We don't talk about that.
- We can talk about anything.
- No, we can't.
Is he the one in your nightmares?
It's always the same.
He comes out of nowhere.
He grabs me.
Takes me hostage in a van.
What does he want?
To know who I am,
who I'm working with.
He has me tied up, drugged.
He isn't real.
He can't hurt you anymore.
He's in my head.
I can't get him out.
Look at me.
You did what you had to do.
You defended yourself.
I'm not supposed to defend myself.
I'm supposed to defend you.
Nap time.
Don't worry.
We'll get her to close her eyes.
Come on.
My wife...
What was she wearing...
at my funeral?
Black.
Hair...
Down or back?
Down, and earrings, pearls.
I bought those for her birthday.
Your salary must be good.
It's the best part of the job.
And the worst?
You saw the tapes.
So you know.
First one was the hardest.
Frank?
Your neighbor.
His son played lacrosse.
He borrowed my lawnmower...
every Friday.
He never cleaned the bag.
Why would they want him dead?
He kept the books.
Handled the overseas business.
He was a drunk.
Overseas.
So your bosses are foreign.
They fixed me up after you shot me.
Put me in a private clinic.
And I thought
it was because they were...
being kind.
Then I realized...
they were just patching me up
so I could do my job.
What's your job?
Like I said...
First one was the hardest.
You were my first.
You seem surprised.
I just...
I just figured a badass gal
like yourself...
Never.
I'm... glad I didn't
break your streak.
I can help you disappear,
you and your wife.
They'll hunt us down.
They'll slaughter us.
There are ways to keep 'em
off your trail, things I've learned.
Like what?
You ditch the van.
Get a new car.
Check into an expensive hotel,
the most expensive you can find.
They'll always expect the opposite.
You have my phone.
When I get back to my people,
I'll call you.
But we have to move fast
so they don't know what's happening.
Her smell.
It's what I miss the most.
Like clean laundry.
Didn't see that one comin'... hmm?
Get out of the room.
She's in there!
- Get her out of the room!
- She's in there!
Remember I told you
something strange was going on?
The nurse.
My roommate's dead.
She died last night in a fire.
They claim
it's some kind of accident.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe you should come home.
No, not now.
I'd like to give you an update
on Dana's condition.
There's a rumor going around the clinic
that she didn't pull through.
That's not the case.
Dana is in extremely critical condition,
but she is still alive.
This has been a traumatic
experience for all of us.
Patients, if you choose
to leave the clinic,
you may return at any time
to complete your treatment.
However,
it would be of great value to us,
and we think to you,
if we could evaluate your sleep patterns
during this time of duress.
Whatever you choose,
we fully support your decision.
Miss Baum.
I hear you've decided to stay.
I have.
An incident like this
increases cortisol levels.
You may find it even more
difficult to sleep tonight.
Here.
These should help.
Diazepam.
Like I said, standard
treatment for insomnia.
You should take them now.
Good.
I've been meaning to say thank you.
For the dream catcher.
You make them for all the patients?
Just the ones who need 'em.
The ones who have nightmares.
Did you know her well?
You know, she ain't dead.
Right. Sorry.
She kept saying she dreamt
she died in a fire.
Maybe I shoulda made her
a bigger one, huh?
A nightmare didn't burn her.
A cigarette did.
She shoulda taken charge.
Taken charge?
Of what was goin' on
inside her head.
Controlled it.
- You believe it then?
- Of course I do.
Coyote. Does it have
mystical significance?
Does it protect you,
guide you?
This?
No.
It's just for my girl.
She thinks it's sexy.
- Tell me a story.
- Go to hell.
What most people know
about torture's bullcrap.
It's not the pain causes people to talk.
It's the talking causes people pain.
So tell me a story.
You told me a story once
in the warehouse,
a story about your son.
That's when you let me go.
Thinking back on it, it's funny.
You don't strike me
as the sentimental type.
Your story, not mine.
Yeah, but you believed it.
You believed it...
because you have a child.
I've seen your scar.
My story is your story.
That's why you told it back to me
when I asked you.
This is what is important.
This is who you're protecting.
You have a son.
He's your accomplice.
See?
That wasn't so hard.
So your son...
is your accomplice.
You're not Bonnie.
You're Ma Barker.
- He's just a boy.
- A boy you'd die to protect.
Any mother would.
You'd be surprised.
The enemy's like a weed.
Leave any part of it underground, it'll
pop right back up when least expected.
You gotta kill the root.
Or in this case...
the seed.
You won't get anywhere near him.
He's not alone.
I won't have to.
You're his mother.
He'll come to you.
He won't come anywhere near here.
He knows better.
He will.
He will when you ask him.
We don't need to talk anymore.
I won't call him.
I'll die first.
You'd like that... to die.
But it's never that easy, is it?
Hey, wake up.
You okay?
You called me.
The nurse. She gave me a shot.
Some kind of sedative.
Let's get outta here.
She's gonna keep hurting people.
We have to do something.
Think you can hack the combination?
In my sleep.
It's some kind of scanning program.
It's neural activity, brain scans.
- There's files, thousands of them.
- Am I in there?
I don't know.
It's by patient number.
All right, there's a ton of data on you.
It's a whole profile.
Delete it.
All of it.
This is a Skynet experiment, John.
They're stealing everything.
- Mom...
- Sleep is the perfect cover.
Brain's still active,
but you don't remember a thing.
- They run a sleep clinic.
- They're not people. You get rid of it?
Nurse Hobson?
There's a problem in room 22. No data.
Miss Baum's electrodes
must have slipped off again.
Thank you for explaining.
- Is that everything?
- Almost.
- I don't want a trace left.
- I know.
All of it, John.
Get rid of it.
I don't want any of me
left in there.
All right, it's gone.
It's all gone, okay? You're all gone.
Whatever she gave me
is starting to hit.
This is a restricted area.
How did you get in here?
I don't know.
I must have been sleepwalking.
Through a locked door?
Sorry.
I'll go back to my room.
Did you know...
that when a human falls in love,
the same areas of the brain light up
as when a human is intoxicated?
What does that have to do
with my nightmares?
We don't know yet.
We don't fully understand
why humans need to dream.
Humans like you?
You drugged me.
What you're experiencing
is sleep paralysis.
You want to move, but you can't.
Believe it or not,
your body is actually
protecting you right now.
You were talking to someone
when I entered the room. Your boy.
The one who came to visit.
Call to him.
I'd die first.
I'm sure you'd like that...
to die.
It's never that easy.
What is this thing?
Mom.
What are you?
It's her son.
He helped her blow up the facility.
He's the one we want.
We'll give him a few more hours
to show up.
I don't know.
Maybe three.
She gave me a few problems.
Nothing I couldn't handle.
Yeah, I guess
we don't need her anymore.
You can trace her cell phone
to this location without her alive.
Makes no difference to me.
It's not a problem.
I'll take care of it right now.
Hell...
It's what she wants.
You're real.
You're real!
A spirit sits on a man's chest.
She is strong, beautiful.
She is here to steal his children.
She is here to steal his future.
He is paralyzed.
The terror in him will burst his heart
if he cannot control it.
She is a nightmare, a demon woman,
the oldest and most enduring story
told by man.
The witching hour
is controlled by witches.
She's a bad dream.
She's a bad bitch.