In the future,
a computer program called Skynet
will declare war on the human race.
Machines have traveled back in time
taking human form
to terminate John Connor,
the future leader of the Resistance.
Sarah Connor, John's mother,
teacher and protector.
Cameron, a Terminator reprogramed
to defend them at all costs.
Derek Reese, John's uncle
and a commanding officer
with the Resistance.
Together, they fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
The battle for our tomorrow
starts today.
Episode 203: The Mousetrap
v 1.00
http://Projet-SG.net
Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles...
Come if you want to live.
So, you've been sitting in the same spot
since you bailed out on english.
- And your name is?
- It's Riley.
Never brought a girl home before?
- No.
- We can move in today.
As soon as I figure out
what to do with all this stuff.
- We'll take it. All of it.
- Cromartie killed 20 FBI guys.
He's here for me.
- I'm looking for the Connors.
- Sarah Connor?
Mr. Dixon wanted to marry Sarah Connor
before you.
So take your wife.
Get as far away from here as you can.
Forget me. Forget John. Just go.
It's not safe here.
You know we always thought
we'd raise kids in this house.
You just can't plan
for anything now.
For the road.
Did you get me that soda, babe?
I've only been wanting a TV in here
for like a hundred years.
Or maybe 200.
That long?
Well, a while.
Ex-baby daddy
wouldn't have one in the bedroom.
Look at where that got me.
Well, that, six beers,
and the rhythm method.
- Too much information?
- Yeah, a bit.
Do I need to call the cable guy?
I feel like I'm not even wired in here.
There you are now.
But I wouldn't mention it to anybody.
Especially the cable guy.
Clever boy.
Beast Wizard,
the Kingdom of Fuel
will never be yours.
Now, now Seth.
That's no way to treat your brother.
Beast Wizard 7.
The low budget film nobody saw,
when it was released direct-to-video
two years ago,
has earned $6 million
and newfound star status.
When it's star, George Lazlo,
inexplicably killed 20 members
of an FBI hostage rescue team
in a shootout
at his Reseda apartment.
The massacre you may recall,
also took the actor's life.
A friend of mine from culinary school,
did craft services on that movie.
She liked the guy.
He ate with the crew.
This town can screw you up.
What are you doing?
This is the absolute center
of the house.
Excellent. Good work.
The house is moving.
- What?
- Moving.
The east by southeast section
of the house is moving.
- Really? Where's it going?
- Down.
At a rate of 0.93 millimeters
per year.
And what?
Does that affect the security system,
or sightlines for the night scope?
How does this affect the safety
of one John Connor?
It doesn't. But next summer
we're going to have to repaint.
Did you get Kacy's TV set up?
I hope you didn't steal cable
for her.
Nobody that pregnant should be forced
to watch network television.
- It's bad for the baby.
- You don't know anything about babies.
I know they grow up.
18 november.
Johnny?
That's the code, right?
- Where are you?
- We...
were on our way out of town.
We're leaving.
- Why?
- Just...
can... can you hang on a second,
please, John?
Okay, I'm...
I'm back. Just...
Just listen, okay...
I just need
to say goodbye to your mom.
I didn't get a chance
to say good-bye and...
She wouldn't give me
her phone number.
I was just hoping maybe you could...
You know, maybe you could just
have her give me a call?
Hang on.
It's for you.
Hello?
He took my wife.
What do you want me to say, Charley?
Just hel... Help me Sarah, please.
We were just leaving town.
And he just... He just took her!
I mean, with John standing right here,
what am I supposed to say?
Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't know who else to call.
Please.
Please just help me, Sarah.
You shouldn't have called here, Charley.
You were right to leave.
I don't want to know where you are,
in case I need you.
I'm not going to need you.
It's better for you if I can't find you.
You understand?
Wait, hold on a sec... Are you...
Are you asking me where I am?
Yes, I am.
I'm just at some fruit stand.
It's...
It's just somewhere off the 14.
Just...
South of the California city turnoff.
I think.
Please.
I really need your help, Sarah.
Stay safe, Charley.
I told you not
to give him your number.
There's something alive up there.
- Is it something that can hurt us?
- It's a bird.
I'll kill it before it flies away.
- Maybe later?
- Maybe never.
John's gonna buy computers today.
Go with him.
Do not let him out of your sight.
- Is there anything I need to know?
- Not let him out of your sight.
And don't touch that bird.
Cromartie's got Charley Dixon's wife.
Where's John?
I sent him to get the new computers.
He's with Cameron. They don't know.
Well, where are you going?
You know where I'm going.
Come if you want.
- You can't go.
- And yet I am.
It's a ploy to get John.
It's a trap.
I know that.
You don't see John here, do you?
It's the absolute wrong thing to do.
It wouldn't be the first time.
Just wait. All right.
Just wait.
Hurry up.
Cameron, Cameron.
Let me help you with that.
I didn't need any help.
Yeah, you did.
Right.
- Hi.
- I'm bored. Do you wanna hang out?
I forgot.
18 november.
- Where are you?
- Promenade.
The magazine stand
in front of the coffee bar.
I'm captivated by the Lohan.
I could be there in like,
15 minutes, you know.
The world could end in 15 minutes.
- I'm gonna vote I doubt it.
- You never know.
- Lotta Lohan.
- Just stay there. Okay?
Hey.
Can you drop me off?
Was that Riley?
That's none of your business.
Your mother told me
to keep an eye on you.
Yeah, well, that doesn't mean
you have to go everywhere I do.
Yes, it does.
Just because my mother said it,
doesn't make it so.
I'm not a child anymore.
I could go to the store, see a friend,
or do whatever the hell
else people like me do.
There are no other people like you.
Just drop me off.
I had heard the trees in this forest
grew lovely fruit.
Yet truly, I had no idea.
I must warn you, my lady.
My striped friend
is an excellent climber.
- Hello.
- Agent James Ellison, please.
Speaking.
My name is Catherine Weaver,
Mr. Ellison.
I'd like to talk to you
about an opportunity.
I'm not interested
in any opportunities.
A job opportunity, Agent Ellison.
I presume you won't be returning
to the FBI,
once your leave of absence is over.
- How'd you get my number?
- I'll tell you about it at lunch.
Shall we say...
1:00?
My assistant
will give you the information.
No.
I don't know who you are.
And... I'm very busy.
You're not busy.
Come to lunch.
We'll talk about who or what,
actually killed your colleagues.
Come on. Come on.
- Where would he take her?
- I don't know.
- Then how are we going to find her?
- You don't know?
- No.
It could be watching us right now.
We need to go.
What we need to do is find my wife.
She won't tell you the truth,
but I will.
It took your wife to get to John.
You think it gives a damn about her?
Your wife's dead.
- It's her, hmm?
- Make sure it's really her.
They can imitate our voices.
You need to be sure.
Baby.
Charley...
- Honey, are you okay? Are you hurt?
- No.
Is he there with you?
Yeah, he's in the next room.
I can hear him.
- Where are you?
- Outside Mojave.
In an abandoned building.
About... four...
five miles off the highway.
- The 14?
- Yeah.
There's a...
a billboard for a,
I don't know, a law firm.
A dirt road runs in front of it.
- It goes East...
- Make sure it's her.
It's her.
You think I don't know my own wife?
Charley.
Make sure.
All right, babe, I need you
to pay attention right now. Okay?
The first night you and I
ever made love, where was it?
- What?
- Just answer the question, please.
The first time we made love,
where was it?
The beach...
Which beach?
Charley, I don't know...
What?
Malibu.
Paradise Cove.
Okay, and what happened
at dinner that night?
What do you mean, Charley?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
Just please, Michelle. Answer.
What happened at dinner?
Oh, God...
The magician took my watch?
I love you, baby. All right? Just...
We're gonna come get you,
just please... Just please hang tight.
Michelle?
Please.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you... No, no.
Please don't tape my mouth.
I won't scream.
I swear I won't scream. I won't scream.
In 1897, James Atkinson
invented the mousetrap.
Its spring slams shut
in 38 thousands of a second.
It is a record
that has never been beaten.
It is hard to build a better one.
You know what really creeps me out
about these magazines?
They all just want
to convert you into their cult.
It's like...
All in the titles.
It's us.
And people, and okay.
You know some of us people
aren't okay.
Some of us are...
popular mechanics.
Exactly.
Some of use are...
guns and ammo.
Yeah, you're more a yarn collector.
You're the yarn collector.
Yarn collector.
So... You coming back to school?
No, I don't think so.
My mom wants to...
Home school me for a while.
Sounds like a good time
will be had by all.
What?
You miss me?
Ease up, cat fancy.
I don't even know
your top ten brands of scratching post.
Cat fancy...
Dude.
Your sister.
We should go. Now.
Wait.
How do we get inside here?
Getting inside's not the problem.
Try to hit something metal.
Wait.
Don't touch her.
They never let you
have a good day, do they?
I'm gonna take the tape off.
Don't move.
Do not move.
You understand?
Not one inch.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
You shut up.
Listen to me.
You're sitting on a bomb.
If you move. It will go off.
Baby. Hey.
We're gonna get you outta this chair.
And then we're all
gonna get outta here.
But, just please...
You have to listen to her.
Please.
Where is he?
If I'm not back in 15 minutes,
leave without me.
Just get me out.
Get me out of here.
Get me out.
I'm trying, Charley.
I'm trying.
But the more I sit here,
the more I wanna stand up.
My legs are on fire.
- It's the adrenaline.
- I know it's the adrenaline.
I just have to get up.
They're on fire.
They're full of ants.
If you move.
You will die.
We all will.
Baby. Look at me.
It's all gonna be all right.
I promise.
It's never gonna be okay.
Never.
There's a bag in the truck.
Red handles.
I'm gonna need it, Charley.
What are you doing here?
I know he brought you.
But you didn't have to come.
Yes, I did.
For Charley?
I just did.
Frankly, I thought it'd be easier.
I thought you'd be dead.
He killed the car.
We're gonna have to walk outta here.
What?
It doesn't make any sense.
He messes with the car and not us.
We're human.
Not that hard to kill.
Molding clay.
Son of a bitch.
Cut her free.
Was it fake?
This whole thing was a fake?
He wants John.
Doesn't have to kill us to get to him.
If we're stuck here with no way back.
Should have known
when you weren't dead.
John, 18 november.
Where are you?
2007. Promenade.
Is Cameron with you?
Yeah. Why?
I need you to stay out.
Don't go home. Don't go to Kacy's.
Don't go.
All right, Mom.
What's going on?
- Stay out until you hear for me.
- Why? What's happening?
Don't go anyplace familiar.
Find a place to hide until I call you.
Just promise me, John.
So, what do you think?
All right. I promise.
Okay, you can do better than that.
Cat fancy.
Stay with Cameron.
Don't call me. I'll call you.
Okay, fine.
Well?
That's awesome.
That was your weird sister, right?
No, it was my weird mother.
Run! There's a bomb.
Get out! Go! Go!
Everyone good?
I'm good.
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
- I'm okay.
The cell tower out back.
He blew it.
After he tapped
your call to John.
He has John's number.
And the code.
That won't work now.
Baby, baby. You okay?
Charley, move.
- 18 november.
- 2007.
Change of plans, John.
How far are you from the pier?
A few blocks, I don't know.
Wait for me there.
And turn off your phone.
What is going on?
Where are you?
Don't worry about me, John.
Just get to the pier.
- I'm sorry. I have to go.
- What?
- I thought we were going to the movies.
- I have to meet my mom at the pier.
Seriously?
Look John,
I'm not afraid of your mother.
Not like you are.
I have to go.
I'll call you.
Don't forget the secret code!
Come on.
I figure it's five miles to the highway
if we head due west.
Across the desert.
We need a car.
We need to get to John.
Oh, God.
How bad is it?
I can't tell.
I can't tell if the shrapnel
knicked an artery or something...
She could be bleeding out,
inside, I don't know.
- We have to go.
- Go? Go how?
On foot.
No way, Sarah.
I'm not moving her.
And I'm not making her walk.
I'll send someone back
for you as soon as I can.
I can walk.
No one has to wait on me.
So...
You know who I am.
You know what happened.
George Lazlo was a shooter.
George Lazlo is dead.
It's all in the report.
And yet here you are.
Five years ago,
a small commuter jet went down
in the Eastern Sierras.
On its way
from Sacramento to Portland.
My brother was on the NTSB team
that investigated the accident.
He found these.
And brought them to me.
My late husband and I
have spent three years and $20 million,
trying to reverse engineer
this technology.
We've not been successful.
Yet.
Red valley, new Mexico.
Eight years ago.
22 witnesses report seeing a man
with some kind of robot leg,
try to kill a boy
later identified as John Connor.
Son of Sarah Connor.
It was your case.
She believed
robots were after her son.
I know what she believed,
Ms. Weaver.
You know
what really killed those agents.
You did not even pretend to ask me
what those were.
What do you want from me?
I want what you want, Mr. Ellison.
I want answers.
But more than that,
I want you
to help me find another one.
Where's John?
Get out.
Out!
Sarah, slow down!
She's bleeding out.
I need to get pressure on it, Sarah.
Damn you, Charley.
I told you to stay away.
Sarah, you've gotta stop now,
please!
- You should have stayed away.
- I'm here now and she's here now.
You've got to stop. Now!
Little help?
- I don't swim.
- Yeah, I just figured that out.
Mom, I'm good.
Let's go.
We do not lose heart.
Though outwardly
we are wasting away,
inwardly,
we are being renewed...
Day-by-day.
For our light and momentary troubles
are achieving for us
an eternal glory,
that far outweighs them all.
We know that if the earthly tent
we live in is destroyed,
we have a building from God,
a house not made with hands,
eternal in the Heavens.
For God who's given us the Spirit
as a guarantee,
and as long as we are at home
in the body,
we are away from the Lord.
We walk by faith, not by sight.
And so we fix our eyes
not on what is seen,
but what is unseen.
For what is seen is temporary.
What is unseen...
eternal.