Previously on terminator:
the sarah connor chronicles...
where's the metal?
Who are you?
My name's winston.
I talked to your mom.
She found something
out in the desert.
It sounds like it has something
to do with those three dots
she's been after.
Is it real this time?
Well, the bullet in her leg
sounds real.
You stay.
I'll go.
You made your call.
This is what living
with it means.
I detected
this audio transmission
on an unsecured line.
Got a breach.
Man shot out at heat and air.
Well, you know the drill.
Shut the place down.
Authorities are still trying
to determine
the cause of the blast
which killed all 32 employees
of the desert canyon
heat and air plant
earlier this week.
A vigil is scheduled
for today
in charm acres...
the high-desert enclave
that served
as a company town
for the workers
and their families.
Area schools and many
of the town's local businesses
will be closed
in observance...
native americans believe that
when their pictures are taken,
their souls are stolen
and locked
in the photograph forever.
I think you're safe.
God, i hate funerals.
I hate skynet.
How come
this sounded so easy
when we were talking about it
on the way up here?
And now that i see
all these people...
just find somebody
to talk to, john.
Mom, everybody who knew
anything about the factory
is already dead.
Well, i'm not.
Yeah, well,
i guess you're lucky.
I'd feel luckier
if we could find somebody here
who knew what was going on
out there.
You'd never guess
he had it in him.
No.
I see it.
That seat taken?
Are you gonna say
annoying things?
Annoying things?
"I can't believe
it's happening."
"It comes in waves."
"I just feel numb."
No, i will, uh, try not
to say those things.
I'm john.
Zoe.
Yeah.
So you know somebody
in charm acres, john?
Or are you just a sucker
for a small-town, homey vigil?
My mom, uh, worked
at the factory.
So she, uh...
you know, came to pay
her respects.
So you got
dragged along.
Little drag,
also some push.
It seemed like
the right thing to do.
A stupid thing to do,
if you had a choice.
Did you have
a choice?
Funeral crasher.
Stupid funeral crasher.
Am i crazy,
or is that girl
creepily staring at us?
That would be
my sister.
I don't like that.
Uh, no,
no reason to.
That's my mom.
My dad worked
at the factory.
Sorry.
I picked out a suit
this morning,
you know,
to bury him in.
I picked out a gray one,
even though henry said
i should've picked out
a black one.
He looked better
in gray, though.
Speak of the henry devil.
We're about to do
the candle lighting.
Hi, i'm john.
Is that
your boyfriend?
You know, he keeps applying
for the job.
I'm just not hiring.
It was nice
to meet you...
john.
Do not stand
at my grave and weep.
I am not there.
I do not sleep.
I am a thousand winds
that blow.
I am the diamond glint
on snow.
I am the sunlight
on ripened grain.
I am the gentle
autumn rain.
When you awake
in the morning's hush...
i am the swift uplifting rush
of quiet birds
in circled flight.
Do not stand
at my grave and cry.
I am not there.
I did not die.
Excuse me.
He hated having
his picture taken.
You wouldn't know it
by looking at him there,
but he did.
Excuse me,
i'll leave...
no, no, no.
It's... it's okay.
It's actually refreshing
to see an unfamiliar face.
Everybody here... all i see are
the people that they've lost.
All i see
is what's missing.
I'm sarah.
Diana winston.
So did you know
my husband, sarah?
Gene used to project
old movies
on his garage door.
Every saturday night
during the summer,
there'd be couples
out in the driveway
with their beers
and popcorn...
watching casablanca
or out of the past
or his girl friday.
I just went
for the free beer.
I've been to a lot
of places for that.
I can't remember...
the last movie
that ed and i saw together...
or when.
I used to just leave
his dinner in the fridge
for whenever
he came home.
It wasn't the easiest place
to work.
I was only there
for a few months,
but long enough
to figure that out.
I can't tell you
how many times i wanted to...
make a call or write a letter
to those people
and ask them what kind
of security they had ed doing
that kept him out of the house
seven days a week.
But you never do that.
No one does that.
Not here.
Yes, ma'am.
Do you have him,
mr. Walsh?
No, ma'am.
He's proven a...
bit harder to locate
than i had anticipated.
You assured me
it'd be a very simple job.
I know, ma'am.
Everyone i've spoken to
thinks that he's dead,
died in the explosion
at the factory.
I can tell you
he isn't.
He didn't.
I've got a good lead
on him, ma'am.
I hope so, mr. Walsh.
I must've missed the memo
about wearing plaid today.
Oh, yeah.
Don't worry.
It's not a company policy.
It's just something
a few of us do.
Paying homage,
you know?
To whom?
Weaver, lachlan weaver.
Today's the anniversary
of his death.
Did you know him?
Yeah, he was...
he was a great guy.
You know, he's a genius,
funny as hell.
They both were,
you know,
back then.
Good morning,
mr. Ellison.
Mr. Murch.
Ms. Weaver.
Beautiful day,
isn't it?
I'm going to say a few words
about my friend gene miller.
But before i do, i want to take
this opportunity
to thank everyone
at desert heat and air's
parent company,
the kaliba group,
for their generous donations
to this service,
and not just
for the beautiful flowers
you see around our chapel,
but also for the generosity
and kindness they've extended
to the families
in this very difficult time.
Is this all it costs
to buy us?
Flowers
and a few kind words?
Where's anybody
from the company?
Have any of you seen anybody
Has anybody ever seen anybody
from the company?
No.
You have not.
Diana.
Stop.
Let us pray.
First six years of our marriage,
we lived in nine states.
Ed was
in the military, so...
when he got the chance
to settle down...
you know,
the nice company car,
the big house,
the even bigger salary...
i pushed him
to take that job.
Head of security
for desert canyon heat and air.
Come on, what kind
of heat and air factory
needs that kind
of security?
What did you do there?
Me?
Um...
coffee and sandwich cart...
waitress on wheels.
I never knew
what went on there.
No one does.
Ed never said
a damn thing about it,
and every time i'd ask,
he'd just shut me down,
so i stopped asking.
We all did.
None of this
is your fault.
Ed was a decent man.
Whatever went on there,
he was a decent man.
Decent people
can get caught up in things.
I found these when i was going
through ed's things.
I've never seen them before
in my life.
This one goes
to a storage locker.
You don't have
a storage locker, do you?
No.
I've been meaning to go there,
but then i get scared.
So i tell myself some doors
are better left unopened.
Not this one.
Looks like
you could use a lift.
What's that?
A lift.
You want one?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Uh...
yeah.
Great. Thanks.
Appreciate it.
Condolences.
It's not my funeral,
but thanks.
I'm an osha
investigator.
I'm looking
into the explosion.
Big change
from being a cop.
Yeah.
23 years, baltimore,
4th precinct,
pikesville.
You a local?
My... my wife
worked up at the plant.
She, uh...
she knew
a lot of these people.
My condolences.
So what do you think?
About what?
What happened.
I think it's too early
to tell.
Would you
even if you knew?
Tell?
Yeah.
No.
You know, people say
it wasn't an accident.
Is that right?
They say something
was going on up there
other than heating
and air-conditioning.
Something
as in what exactly?
That's
what i'm asking you.
Suppose you knew something
was going on out there.
What would you do?
Absolutely nothing.
Absolutely nothing?
That's what i said.
Thanks for the ride.
No problem.
I think i'm... i'm gonna walk
the rest of the way.
No problem.
Good luck
with your investigation.
Empty.
I did not know
that man.
I loved him,
but i didn't know him.
Sometimes
that's for the best.
He called me.
Ed did, three days ago,
for the last time.
He must've dialed
by accident.
My name's winston.
I install air-conditioning,
all right?
Please don't hurt me.
I have a wife.
What happened
to him, sarah?
I can't die here.
Somebody tell me
i'm not gonna die here.
You won't die here.
I hate these people.
I don't relate
to any of them.
Great.
Thanks, zoe.
Hey, what
if we just kept driving?
Got on the highway
and didn't stop
till we hit
somewhere amazing?
The grand canyon.
I went there
when i was a kid.
My mom and i took mules
down into the canyon.
Sounds cool.
Uh, it would've been if my mule
wasn't completely schizo.
He ate my spare shirt.
I've never been.
Got a postcard
from there once.
Okay, seriously,
if you start talking
about mike thompson,
i'm getting
out of the car.
Boyfriend?
Ex.
And he was a good guy...
until he ditched me.
What happened?
He was just like
the rest of us.
His mom worked
at the plant.
Mike was just
a normal, funny guy.
He liked watching
his monty python movies
and playing lacrosse.
What happened to him?
Apparently, his mom had violated
some confidentiality agreement
or something
at the plant.
They just...
up and left
in the middle of the night.
Mike never said
a word about it.
I woke up one morning,
and he was just gone.
A few months later
i got a postcard
from the grand canyon.
He was a real prize.
Shut up, henry.
Why don't you think
about somebody
besides yourself for once, huh?
You're not the only person
who's lost someone.
Zoe's not in love
with you.
What?
She doesn't love you
the way you love her.
Get out of the car.
What?
I want them out!
Henry, just go!
Go!
Are you gonna go?
No.
Hey, what are you...
what are you doing?!
Get out.
Make a right
over here.
What the hell
is going on?
Shh.
Look, i can't deal
with another funeral, henry,
not right now.
Hey, do you want to see
something really messed up?
One day you'll be out here,
and they're lying there
like that,
dead.
And the next day
they're gone.
Like mike.
Yeah, like mike.
What's killing them?
Idiots with guns.
No bullet wounds.
What are you,
dr. Quinn medicine woman?
Maybe it's the water.
They always
did want to be rich.
That's what henry said.
His mom wanted
the good things.
Careful what
you wish for, huh?
What do you mean?
Insurance money...
the company's agreed to pay.
We're all rich.
What did henry's father do
at the plant
anyway?
He went to work in the morning,
came home at night,
didn't talk about it.
Same as everybody else
that worked there.
I don't get it.
What's so secret about heating
and air-conditioning?
The secret is, is it wasn't
heating and air-conditioning.
What was it?
Some kind
of government project.
That's what i think.
There's some smart people
around here,
real smart.
So you think what...
that somebody
sabotaged the plant
and killed
all these people?
Your father?
It wasn't
an accident, john.
Moo.
* there's a land
that is fairer than day *
* and by faith *
* we can see it afar *
* for the father *
* waits over the way *
* to prepare us *
* a dwelling place there *
* in the sweet *
* by and by *
* we shall meet *
* on that beautiful shore *
* in the sweet *
* by and by *
* we shall meet *
* on that beautiful shore *
the guy who shot me
is either a serial killer
or a true believer.
His wife thinks
he was murdered.
She's right.
But nothing
about the, uh, the thing
you think you saw?
The drone or whatever?
I don't think i saw it.
I saw it.
Who's he?
Looking for something.
I figure the best way
to find out what it is,
is to let him find it.
He made you.
He'll try and lose you,
but he doesn't know me.
I'll handle it.
You always do.
Skynet's here, reese.
I can feel it.
What?
You called me
"reese" again.
That's what you used
to call him, isn't it?
Kyle?
You know, maybe you should try
to let him go.
Maybe you should.
Is henry gonna be okay?
Henry smokes
a lot of weed.
You know, my father died
before i was even born.
Yeah, well, my father's a pile
of ashes somewhere,
so i guess
we're both screwed.
I thought you picked out
a gray suit to bury him in.
Why am i even talking
to you?
You don't know me.
You don't know
what i'm going through.
Stop trying to make it seem
like you're some kind
of sensitivity expert.
You don't know
anything.
She's not crying.
She's not doing
a lot of things.
Mr. Ellison,
come in.
You've changed
your tie.
Is that plaid?
Yes, um,
i went home at lunch.
I hope
you don't mind. I...
i spoke to mr. Murch,
and he spoke of, um...
lachlan's death.
My sympathies.
Yes.
Thank you.
I remember
when my father died.
He was, um...
he was a tough man.
We didn't get along.
Even so, it took me
a long time
to come to terms
with his passing.
I threw myself into work
so i wouldn't have to.
Was this recent?
Recent enough.
Then you understand.
I do.
So how's savannah doing
with this?
Do?
How is she dealing
with her father's death?
Dr. Sherman was very helpful
in that regard.
Now he's gone, too.
Children are nothing
if not resilient.
I'm surprised
she's not here.
Why?
Being the anniversary,
i mean.
Yes.
I guess
that is surprising.
Dr. Sherman
felt it was important
for a child to maintain
a regular routine.
Today's not the day
for excitement.
Would you excuse me,
mr. Ellison?
I'm feeling emotional.
Yes.
Of course.
Victoria?
Ms. Weaver.
And i'd have to say
that this is one of them,
where it seems every single
logical step we take
leads to
the most bizarre place.
You mean crashing
that poor guy's wake
and eating
his widow's shrimp skewers?
Yeah, derek,
i mean that.
What's the point?
You know
what the point is.
Your mom thinks that factory
was linked to skynet.
Yeah, and you think
she's nuts.
Doesn't mean i think
she's wrong.
She hasn't looked
at her father's picture
since we've been here...
not once.
Neither
has her mother.
Yeah, and?
If you had a photo
of kyle reese,
you'd look at it,
wouldn't you?
Maybe there's something
i don't understand.
He's not dead.
That's a big leap.
Let me repeat
what she said.
If you had a photo
of your brother,
would you
or would you not look at it?
He's not dead.
We should find him
before he is.
What are you doing
in my parents' room?
Your father's alive,
isn't he?
Get out.
Hey.
Let me go!
Zoe, i know you're scared,
and i know you want
to protect him,
but you don't know
what's been going on.
Get away from me,
you freak!
Let me help you.
You can't.
Yes, i can.
No.
Derek?
Hey.
Where are you?
In a garage.
Garage, where?
It's a long story.
Where are you?
We're at a wake...
a fake wake.
The whole place was wired,
every house
in the neighborhood.
Every move anyone ever made
was being watched.
Skynet work camp.
This is how
they were set up.
People working
for the machines
monitored by other people
working for the machines.
Who are you people?
I need to know what they
were building in that plant.
I need to know who owned it,
and i need to know right now.
I don't...
how would i know?
Because the tunnel led
to your garage, that's how.
My husband's garage.
Look, we don't know
you people.
For all we know, you could be
responsible for this.
You could be
some terrorist organization.
We are some kind
of terrorist organization.
And believe me, if someone
hadn't blown up that plant,
i would.
Now, where's your husband?
He's dead.
No, he's not dead...
yet.
Wait, wait.
Please,
he's innocent.
He is. John, you have
to believe me.
No, i don't have to.
I was with him
when he got the news
that everyone was dead,
he was freaked out.
And he was trying to figure out
what to do,
and he didn't know
what to do.
He was scared,
like we all are.
What were they building
at the plant?
I don't...
nobody knows.
How can you not know?
How can any
of you not know?
How can you just sleepwalk
through your lives?
Just tell us what they were
building at the plant.
Just stop it!
He told us
he was gonna play dead!
He told us everybody else had
died, that he should've died,
and that it would be better if
that's what everybody thought!
That is what he said!
Now, you think i'm sad,
that i am pathetic,
that i what...
that i just sleepwalked my way
through all of this.
Well, maybe you're right.
Maybe i looked the other way.
Well, we all did,
every one of us.
And maybe that's not
what you think you would do,
but that is
what most people do.
Mom, you don't owe
them this.
So there's not plant now,
no plant, no charm acres.
But it is a lot
of insurance money,
enough for my family
to get lost and start over.
So i didn't ask
any questions.
Why would i start now
when we are so close?
Look at this.
I pulled this
from the archives.
Mike?
Daddy?
You may not like
asking questions,
but me, once i get started,
i can't stop.
Mom.
I think i know
where he might be.
Hey!
Excuse me.
I've been watching you.
You want to know what i see?
What do you see,
diana?
Ed would say
you don't smell right.
Well, i guess
ed would know.
Look, i deserve
the truth.
I opened up to you.
Sometimes it's better
not to ask too many questions.
You're crying.
No.
Yes, you are.
Come here.
I want to tell you something.
I remember
when my father died.
He was a tough man.
We didn't get along.
Even so...
it took me a long time to come
to terms with his passing.
Do you understand
what i'm
i miss daddy.
What do you miss
about him?
He used
to read me stories.
I can read you
a story.
He did it better.
You know...
anytime you want to see
your father, we have videos.
It's not the same.
Why?
I can't sit on his lap.
Come,
sit on my lap.
Your lap is cold.
I know.
Where are we, john?
What is this place?
I don't know.
Transcript : yyets.net