Work's different now
I'm a resident. I feel more confident,
more like a, hell,
I'll say it, a doctor.
Good morning, people.
- You're gonna be fine, ma'am.
- I work here.
Doesn't change
the fact you're gonna be fine.
Why in the hell
are you wearing a coat?
Cos I'm a doctor.
Babs, if you're worried
about people seeing your ass,
do what all the other girls do
and tie a sweater around your waist.
I look doctorly.
You look like the guy who buys
a bronze star, pins it to his lapel
and tells everyone to call him Sarge.
Nobody likes that guy. Not a soul.
- I was in the military.
- Where did you come from?
If I find out you're wearing a bronzy
without having served,
I'll make things
uncomfortable for you.
Coat-wearing doctors
do not take this crap.
- You were never in the military.
- Yes, I was.
- Which branch?
- The janitor branch.
I'm watching you.
That's right, Sasquatch.
You see, things have changed.
We've begun to adapt to new situations.
My back is on fire.
If Dr Amato was any shorter, I'd be
passing him instruments with my feet.
Dr Turk, I need you down here.
Coming down.
Even other people
are starting to see us differently.
Hey there, Doctor.
Oh, me? Of course,
because I'm a doctor.
I've got the outfit.
I've got the heart-hearing thingy.
Stethoscope.
Paging Dr Know-it-all to the cafeteria.
Oh, sweet baby James.
Most importantly, we've started
to treat each other with respect.
Dude, you're such a loser, man.
I look spiffy. I'm trying
to separate myself from the pack.
You already have. You're the biggest
geek to come through here.
- Yeah.
- Don't laugh.
- You're a frat boy with a back problem.
- Yeah, I am.
Oh, do me, do me, do me!
Be careful about yelling
that out in a bar.
You guys get to be something.
The Dork, Jock, firecracker
from the School of Hard Knocks.
No offence, Carla. Damn it, what am I?
- You're white.
- The whitest.
- Yeah, you are.
- Oh, come on. JD's white.
I ain't hearing that woman
cos I'm talking to him.
OK, it's a tie.
T-Diddy?
You got me in the ICU for a cold?
Mr Blair, you have a sinus infection
with orbital extension.
You were admitted delirious
from your 106-degree temperature,
naked and very adamant
about staying that way.
- I was hot.
- I'll second that.
- Sharp coat, sport.
- Yeah, it's spiffy.
Shocker! You care more
about appearances...
Finish that thought quickly.
I'm not breaking my gait.
...substance, style,
what's important, coat, not...
- Too slow.
- I think you really got through to him.
My God, you hear like a bat.
Idiot. I wish I had a guy that would
stop me before I did something stupid.
Mistake!
I don't know why he's an opera singer.
Listen, Tiny Dancer,
I wouldn't be flapping my mouth
if I'd forgotten
to get a blood culture on Mr Blair.
And for the love of God, do you at least
remember what you were doing
the day they were passing out
common sense?
Maybe you were running late
cos you couldn't find the right thong
for those low-rider jeans you love.
Maybe you were bopping along to
whatever boy band makes your heart race
and you just drove on by.
I don't know, I'm just guessing.
But one thing's sure.
You wound up at the dumb-dumb store
and put about as much of that
in the car as you could fit, didn't you?
And then I did something
I've never done before.
If you flipped the page you'd see
that I pan cultured him yesterday,
but that would spoil the pleasure you
take in pointing out people's slip-ups.
Too bad, Buster Brown,
I'm a resident now,
I'm not gonna make the same
intern mistakes I made last year.
I'd appreciate if you wouldn't
yell at me in front of my patient.
Buster Brown?
Focus all energy on lip not quivering.
- How's the back, sweetness?
- Perfect.
I'm sorry the last couple of nights
I haven't given you the Turkey-Jerky,
but rest assured your man will be back
in action before you know it.
You take your time.
Hey, big fella, we're together
on a thyroidectomy this afternoon.
- Could be a long one.
- Oh, that's great, Dr Amato.
- How was that not funny?
- I don't know, dude.
You guys are getting to be
like Starsky and Hutch.
If Starsky was a ventriloquist
and Hutch was a puppet.
I would watch that.
Why do you keep getting him?
The other surgeons are busting my chops
for skipping guys' night out.
Dr Amato's your punishment?
No, I enjoy needing you to lower me
on the toilet in the morning.
Check that out.
It looks innocent,
but Elliot was late this morning.
Once you've been here a while,
you learn to read between the lines.
Mrs Bumbry, I wish I had better news,
but you didn't qualify
for the GI clinical trials,
so we'll keep plugging away.
Great. So how was the sex with that guy?
What guy? I wasn't... I...
Elliot, I have other patients, Mrs
Bumbry needs a nap. We're all very busy.
I've never done anything like this.
I just met him and slept with him.
God, I miss one-night stands.
The best thing was,
since I knew it was just a fling,
I wasn't afraid to ask him
for exactly what I wanted.
- Which was?
- Shirt on, lights off, no talking.
Well, you just be careful.
You wouldn't believe how quickly a
reputation can be made in this hospital.
You're a bit of slut, aren't you?
As soon as we get out
of this sterile field,
I am going to need the man
who hit that to hit that.
Wait a minute, I'm Elliot Reid.
People, listen up,
this rumour ends right now.
She slept with him
and she hardly knew him.
- Does that happen a lot around here?
- Not enough.
That infection keeps hanging around,
so I want to put you on a broader-
spectrum antibiotic intravenously.
But I'm feeling better.
I'm gonna tell you something my mom
used to tell me when I was scared.
In the case of sinus infection
not responding to antibiotics,
the recommended protocol
is imipenem, 500 mg, IVQ, six hours.
Got me through a lot of hard times.
I love it that Mr Blair trusted me.
It's one of the best feelings
you can have as a doctor.
- How's it going?
- You can't wear that.
- You mean after Labour Day?
- You know what I mean.
It's a white coat.
Anybody can wear a white coat.
Jerk.
You're what we call "a goner."
I'm kidding. There's nothing here.
So Mrs Bumbry here
has inflammatory bowel disease, huh?
And the drug they're testing
at the clinical trial could help.
But she doesn't qualify.
You OK, Mrs Bumbry?
I liked Bow Wow
when he was Lil' Bow Wow.
Rappers, they grow up so fast.
If you're gonna survive in medicine,
you've gotta accept rules are rules.
Anyone from that
clinical trial around?
Hello! Hello! This lady's
supposed to be in this trial.
- OK.
- What the hell did you just do?
When you speak of this, and
I know you will, could I be shirtless?
I think it would be even more
impressive if I was shirtless.
If you're a criminal,
even if you aren't afraid of Starsky,
if a Hutch puppet jumps out at you,
"Freeze, sucker!" you're done for.
Does it have a real gun or puppet gun?
- Puppet gun. They'd sew it to his hand.
- OK. I'd watch that.
What's up, fellas?
I don't care what hospital you go to,
surgery is still a boys' club.
I'm just as cool as those guys.
Bye, Turk.
T-Dog, settle a medical debate for us.
I think Elliot's
got a modest rack at best.
But my favourite attending here
says when he was tuning in Tokyo,
the reception was excellent.
Elliot's a friend of mine,
so I don't want to talk about that.
So, Dr Turk, how is your back?
My back's as swollen
as Elliot's big-ass breasts.
- I was paged.
- Patient's complaining of anosmia.
Anosmia?
I always thought it was very funny
that losing your sense of smell
was called anosmia.
Anosmia, you know, like Schnozmia.
Don't you find that very funny?
- He doesn't.
- I'm calling Dr Cox.
- Nobody needs to call Dr Cox.
- This is only temporary, right?
Of course it's temporary.
Could also be slightly more untemporary.
You mean permanent.
Just when you think
you have this place figured out,
it finds a new way to get you.
I'm waiting.
Unfortunately, you've
put us in somewhat of a legal bind.
Way to go, Ted. Good God, man,
you couldn't scare a child.
Who would want to?
Do you have any idea how much money
this hospital makes from that GI trial
into which you enrolled your patient?
I'm gonna go ahead and guess $ 7.
Sometimes it comes right at you.
Keep smiling, tough guy.
First I'm gonna...
Finish that thought, Bobcat,
cos I'm not breaking my gait.
- What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
Sometimes it sneaks up on you.
When she dated JD, she'd just wear
a T-shirt in the morning.
So every time
she reached up high for the cereal,
everybody got two scoops
of booty flakes.
The two scoops, they were packed
with flavour. You know what I'm saying?
Right? Right? Right?
I told you I didn't want
these antibiotics.
When your first grandkid
is born and you smell his head,
call me and tell me how great it is.
Mr Blair, I'm sorry this happened.
Sometimes it hits you in places you
didn't know you were vulnerable.
Yeah, well you should be,
it's your fault.
No more silly medical mistakes, huh?
Nice going there, Newbie.
Damn.
Ted, you seem different.
I bought some relaxation tapes.
They're working.
A patient's blaming me
for losing his sense of smell.
God, you cut off someone's nose?
Where is it? Do you have it on you?
You're disgusting.
No, I just gave him IV imipenem.
Kelso's gonna blame me.
Just get rid of the nose.
I don't have the nose.
Maybe you should calm down.
- Maybe you should calm down!
- My bad.
Imipenem.
"Unlike gentamicin and tetracycline,
imipenem has never been
associated with anosmia."
My God, we're OK.
Great. Thank you, Ted.
- It's my birthday.
- What?
Nothing.
And many more...
Elliot!
Come on. It's so tough to be a surgeon.
If you're not in, you're out.
Dr Turk. Down here.
I saw you switched off on our
exploratory laparotomy this afternoon.
Yeah, it's because I... I had to...
- It's because I'm short.
- You're not short.
I know I'm the surgical
assignment booby prize,
but if my other choice
is being in that boys' club,
I'd rather they made fun of me.
- What could they possibly make fun...
- Stop it.
It's possible to be a good surgeon
without playing their game.
- You're really short.
- I know.
No, Dr Murray, I don't want
any fries to go with this shake.
- I don't even know what that means.
- Excuse me.
You want to ask me how many
ceiling tiles I've counted?
Maybe you want to call me a name
like tramp, ho or slesident,
which is half slut, half resident.
- No.
- Then what is it, Noelle?
- I want to know where the G-spot is.
- The what spot?
For the 100th time,
you had nothing to do
with me getting involved in the Bumbry
case, but for God's sake,
the bigger problem facing us now
is how do we get you
to stop annoying me?
Yeah, I'm the problem. Can't you
just for once stay out of your own way?
Can't you for once
not be such a busybody?
Oh, sore spot.
- What spot?
- Sore spot.
Damn it!
The next step is to find out what
did cause Mr Blair's loss of smell.
- Hey, pal.
- Excuse me, Doctor.
Oh, no, I'm not a doctor. I'm a janitor.
Oh. I just assumed because of the coat.
Right. Well, janitors wear
white coats around here too.
You guys do a great job
keeping this place clean.
- We thank you.
- No, I'm a doctor...
Look at the books, woman.
Is that a man's back?
Check out who I have assisting
Dr Rumpelsurgeon.
You know what?
His name's Dr Amato.
That girl you slept with,
her name's Dr Reid.
- You should show them some respect.
- Yeah? Says who?
Says me.
- Dr Kelso.
- Carla.
You look as good as I feel.
Mrs Bumbry's 53.
Mrs who is what?
The patient Dr Cox
got into the GI clinical trial.
She was disqualified because her chart
said she was 63 and the cut-off is 55,
but the genius who admitted her
got her age wrong.
She's actually a perfect candidate.
And Dr Cox knew this?
- He knew the whole time.
- Fan-damn-tastic.
You better do the heel-toe out of here
because you know I'm going
to take this out on somebody.
Bye-bye.
May I join you?
By all means.
Knowing I was right and he was wrong,
I thought I'd enjoy this walk more.
I couldn't help but empathise
cos I'd been there and saw the signs.
The shameful averted gaze.
The nervous shifting.
And, of course,
the wild, uncontrollable urination.
I'm thrilled you approve, but, for the
last time, I'm up here. I'm up here.
- You were wrong. I was right.
- I beg your pardon?
Anosmia isn't a side-effect
of IV imipenem.
Plus, Mr Blair had nasal
polypectomies and septoplasty
and his loss of smell is caused
by manipulation of his sinuses
and the infection,
so I didn't make a mistake,
and you were wrong
when you said, "Nice going, Newbie."
Here you've put me in a tough situation.
I can't honestly decide
whether to say "duh" or "doy"
or a very sarcastic,
"Oh, really?" My God, Fiona.
I know it wasn't your fault.
The patient probably knows.
But he seemed a little distraught.
Maybe being able to blame somebody
for a second might make him feel better.
And, I know, maybe it's me,
but doesn't that seem like something
that goes along
with wearing that fancy white coat?
It does, doesn't it?
- Kinda.
- I'm so proud of you. Put it there.
The tarantula.
That girl asked me to give her
my top ten sexual positions,
and after the two that I knew,
I started naming insects.
That really sucks. I'm sorry.
I'm not sure. I mean,
I was mad at you at first.
But it's actually kind of empowering
to have this... persona, this identity.
I'm not just some nameless,
faceless white doctor,
I'm Elliot Reid, Tramp.
Well, that's great.
If you're happy, I'm happy.
The weird thing is she said
she'd already tried stink bug.
I still don't know why I was desperate
for everyone to know it wasn't my fault.
Dr Cox, Dr Kelso
has something he wants to say to you.
So I hear there was an age mix-up,
that I was unaware of,
and... anyway...
- You're OK.
- I'm sorry.
I guess it comes down to how
we want to be seen by other people.
I proud of you, Robert.
Put her there.
I think it's important you understand
I had no idea how old that patient was.
For the record, she could've been 170,
I still would've stuck her in that trial
so fast it'd make your teeth
fall out all over again.
- That's perfect.
- I would too.
Some people want to be seen
as the rebel.
Some people just want
to be seen, period.
Some people have limits on how far
they'll go to protect their image.
- Dr Turk, I need you down here.
- Coming.
When I stopped worrying how other
people saw me I started to look better.
Mr Blair, I just wanted to say again
that I made a mistake and I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
- Good luck.
Come on, baby.
Let's see if we can find you a ride.
Laverne!
Careful.
So we're done with the coats?
It was a fun day, though, wasn't it?
See you tomorrow.
Maybe tomorrow I'll get a bad haircut
and push round a mop all day.
I know. You don't have to do it, OK?
Mistake!
Yeah.
www.V2.Frigorifix.com
www.tvsubtitles.net