??? i promise you will not be disappointed.
- my dad makes the best breakfast in queens.
- great.
well, not just
queens--all of new york.
- you haven't had breakfast
at the four seasons.
- neither have you.
i just know everything
they do is first-class.
- tell 'em, matt. you're rich.
- justin...
- no, it's okay. i have had
brunch there a few times.
- matt, you are going to love...
- my guadalajara scramble espectacular.
- mmm.
i dream
about eating these.
mm-hmm. and you'll
keep dreaming.
only grapefruit and egg whites
for you this morning, mist.
hot!
mija, where's the fire?
slow down.
- i have to meet daniel at the office.
- on a saturday?
he's working so hard to keep
this company from sinking,
and besides, matt and i are
going to a ranger game today.
- wow.
- i don't get hockey.
- all that ice, and no one's figure skating?
- betty, i didn't even know
- you liked hockey.
- no, she doesn't. actually,
i have to go for work and--
and i owe him. he stayed in
my office for, like, an hour
- when i worked late.
- yeah, i read every issue of "mode"
over the last three years--
a lot of boobs.
i'm just saying.
oh, don't forget to meet me
at my mom's place.
um, i'm staying there
- while they fix my apartment.
- moms love betty. they don't love me.
- actually, we haven't even met yet.
- well, she's away, but, uh,
she's dying for meeting betty.
- uh, she says betty sounds like
the daughter she never had.
- aww.
- it's, uh, 2921 madison avenue.
- what apartment?
- uh, the whole building.
- how rich are you?
- how much money do you have?
- justin! hilda...
what?
- anybody home?
- oh, crap. i forgot i have
a haircut appointment.
- hi, archie!
- hi!
- that's the councilman?
- yeah.
please come in,
your excellency.
- ignacio, i keep telling you,
please just call me archie.
- no, sir,
stay and eat. then you can
have a haircut.
- he's cute, hilda.
- and he's single, and he likes her.
that's why he comes here
every week to get his "haircut."
- go out with him.
- yeah, i don't know.
- he's nice, but he's missing something.
- what, a wedding ring like your last boyfriend?
oh, no!
okay, i'm leaving.
have fun.
behave.
okay.
hilda, he's a nice guy.
give him a chance.
- don't.
you're crazy.
derek jeter
is a good-looking guy.
sorry, but he doesn't
do it for me.
- are you kidding me?
that guy gets so much--
- don't be gross.
fun. the guy
gets so much fun,
- you wouldn't believe it.
- i like fun.
i hate that you have to go
to work on a saturday.
i know, but until "mode"
gets back on its feet,
- it's gotta be seven days a week.
- you know, when you're gone,
- i think i'll take a little
hike in prospect park.
- whoa, whoa, whoa. no no no no.
hey, look, why don't you
just hang out?
i'll bring you some soup,
watch tv, you can stay warm.
i have cancer, daniel.
it's not like a bowl of soup
and a nap, and i'll be over it.
look,
will you do it for me?
please.
okay.
your meeting
with miles foster's at 4:00.
wilhelmina's on the way.
i put out a spread
in the conference room--
cheese, olives, salami--
- not the kind that makes you gassy.
- betty, that was once. it was a flue.
yeah...
i wouldn't risk it.
also, great news--
the doctor you want for molly
is in town for the rest
of the week.
- here's his number.
- dr. simon? that's fantastic.
betty, thank you so much
for everything today.
- i know you're not getting paid.
- oh, stop, daniel.
if you need my help,
i'm always here.
and you get to go meet
your boyfriend right now.
matt is not my boyfriend.
if i've learned one thing
from molly's illness,
it's that if you have
something good,
you have to enjoy it.
i am enjoying it.
i just don't want
to put a label on it.
you know, what's the point?
boyfriend, girlfriend--
- what does that mean?
- um, i think it means
you're getting serious.
daniel, all i'm thinking
about right now
is going
to a hockey game.
go, rangers! whoo-hoo!
so i learned miles has
wall-to-wall meetings
- with every editor in town.
- well, no surprise.
whenever he shoots a cover,
issues fly off the newsstands.
i know.
we get him first, though.
we have a good chance.
i'm afraid
we can't afford him.
i know. he costs more
than our entire photo budget.
well,
let's make it tasty.
- promise him complete creative control.
- yeah, great.
make him want us
more than we want him?
- just make sure you play it cool in there.
- i always play it cool.
well, right now you've got
that upper-lip sweat you get
- when you're desperate.
- it's water. i just washed my face.
if that's what you say.
we've got
a lot riding on this,
so let's make it happen.
??? to have you here in mode.
we're such fans
of your work.
that "brady bunch"-inspired
shoot you did
with brad and angelina
and the six kids--genius.
how on earth did you get
jennifer aniston to play alice?
i don't know
what's hip or cool.
i just... take pictures.
i'm trying to do something that
makes me feel happy inside.
well, wilhelmina and i
would certainly love
- to make you feel happy inside.
- daniel.
sorry. did that sound weird?
you know what i mean.
yeah, yeah, no worries.
this all sounds good.
let's do it.
and you will have
complete creative control
- with no editorial interference.
- fantastic.
and we appreciate you
taking a cut in your fee.
and it's off.
you, uh, you do understand that
we're in a bit of a crunch.
so i have to suffer?
mnh-mnh, sorry.
i am a freakin' genius, man.
you said it yourself.
i can go down the block
to "vanity fair,"
and they'll pay my fee.
so listen.
you have until friday.
if you have the money,
i'll sign the contract,
and if not... sayonara.
we need him.
yes, we do.
so this is gonna have to come
out of our own pocket.
wilhelmina, if you want,
i can cover this.
no, that won't be
necessary.
i'll cover my half.
come on. i have
more resources than you.
- how about i pay?
- how about you worry
about your end,
and i'll worry
about mine, okay?
i got this. no problem.
hello?
matt! hello?
matt! hello.
oh, good.
someone's here.
i'm back early. left my bags
by the service entrance.
if you could go
and, uh, bring them in.
hi. i'm betty.
oh. victoria hartley.
i didn't realize you were new.
but i'm very good with names.
i won't forget.
oh, you'll enjoy it here.
the first, uh, monday
of every month,
- i give away my old shoes.
- oh, no.
um, i'm betty... suarez.
i'm dating matt.
really?
mom, you're home.
uh, yes, i-i caught
an early flight.
and, uh, betty's here.
uh, have you guys met?
betty, mom.
mom, betty.
super.
let's, uh, head on out.
uh, not you, mom.
maybe next time.
it's nice to meet you,
mrs. hartley.
yes.
and nice to meet you.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译: 校对:
时间轴:我爱狮心小s
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
ugly betty 318
- dying to meet me." matt, she
didn't even know who i was.
- i--
- she thought i was your maid!
- i know. i screwed up. i'm sorry.
why did you tell me
that i was
- "the daughter she wished she had"?
- yeah, i don't know why i added that details.
- it's weird, uh, especially
since i have a sister.
- what?
- no, no, i don't have a sister.
it's a bad joke!
- so what, were you, like, hiding me from her?
no, i was hiding her
from you. i--
look, my mom
is tricky, betty.
she's judgmental
and controlling,
and no one i date
is ever good enough for her.
well, then why didn't you
just tell me that?
moms love me, matt.
she'll love me.
- she just has to get to know me.
- you know, i just didn't want to put you
through the victoria hartley
taste test.
but you have to
put me through
the victoria hartley
taste test.
she's your mother. and if my
family didn't like the taste
of someone i was dating,
well, then that would matter.
- can we drop the whole taste thing?
- yeah, let's.
look, i'm just saying,
it matters if your mom likes me.
it matters for us, you know?
when can i meet her again?
seriously?
yeah. i can handle anything.
dinner, lunch, coffee--
i'm really good at coffee.
how about a party?
she's having this... thing
on friday night.
- hmm. i didn't get an invitation.
- okay! okay, okay.
would you like to go
to a party with me
- at my mother's apartment friday night?
- ooh, friday?
i think i have an online
scrabble tournament.
i'm just kidding. yes!
let's do it.
you're the best,
you know that?
okay, let's go. i don't want
to be late for the game.
- keep the change, buddy.
- thanks.
willie...
selling your possessions?
isn't that, like,
one rung above appearing
on a reality show?
i have to, marc.
it's not just that photographer.
running meade costs a fortune.
- i can't let daniel leverage me
out of the company.
- but you're rich.
- in certain things--
real estate, clothing, attitude.
- mm.
but daniel has cash,
and i don't.
- your taste is extraordinary, ms. slater.
- i know.
that sable is spectacular.
is the lining hand stitched?
oh, yes, by a seamstress
from paris
whose great-great-grandfather
was furrier to napoleon.
wow. really?
- how the hell should i know?
- oh.
hey, why can't you just ask one
of your rich friends for money,
like the donald or sumner
or martha?
and have one
of those bitches own me?
no way.
my money, my equity.
wow, you're, like, the world's
sexiest economics teacher.
marc, if i panic now,
i will lose everything.
so with a few
short-term cutbacks
here and at the office,
i'll be fine.
- ms. slater, may i--
- let's cut the bryn mawr niceties, okay?
- do you want my things or not?
- we do.
don't worry ms. slater, we're very discreet.
good.
come back on friday with
the check for the down payment.
oh... for god sake.
marc, stop crying.
if you'd like,
you may try on the sable...
one last time.
hey, betty, a little bird
told me about your fancy dinner
- with your rich boyfriend.
- oh, was the little bird
looking at the calendar
- on my desk?
- well, what am i supposed to do?
you never open up to me
anymore.
- when we were roomies,
we shared everything.
- no. amanda, you shared everything.
and some of it
was weird.
you know, b., you are playing
this matt thing perfectly.
a few more moves,
and you will be
- in the gold digger hall of fame.
- i am not a gold digger.
i could care less
about matt's money.
and...
cut, print, oscar.
don't change a word.
you nailed it.
amanda, i really like matt,
and he likes me.
- and now i just need
his mom to like me.
- hmm.
the show was tragic.
but if i know henri,
he'll be back on top in no time.
excuse me.
marc! it's 4:00.
i'm sorry, it's time
for my afternoon caviar
and champagne.
i'll have to call you back.
good grief.
what the hell is this?
marc!
what is this?
it's an almond,
and that's seltzer.
where is the beluga?
where's the krug?
we can't afford it
with our new office budget.
i was worried that you
might react this way,
- but remember, you said that
you wanted to make sacrifices.
- you're right, you're right.
this is exactly
what i was talking about.
it's what we need.
so, um...
almonds, you said?
yes.
almonds...
mmm. is there anything else
that i can...
do for you?
i'm fine. i have
everything i need.
so...
eight years ago,
molly was diagnosed.
- they didn't catch it early.
- yes, i can see the cancer
was rather advanced.
- that's why the treatment
was so aggressive.
- but it worked.
i mean, look at her.
she's healthy.
listen, all that matters
is her ability
to respond to my treatment,
and based on what i'm seeing,
there's only a small chance,
but it is a chance.
i'm about to begin work
on a new clinical study.
i will send the information
to your office.
you'll let me know
what you want to do.
- could we have a couple of days
to think about it?
- molly, no.
dr. simon, we don't need
to take a few days.
we have our answer.
we're in.
mrs. meade!
i was wondering if you could
help me with something.
oh, you're worried about
victoria hartley's party.
- daniel told you?
- he tells me everything.
oh, by the way,
hilda should totally go out
with that councilman.
so, uh, you--
you know mrs. hartley?
oh, yes.
see, i've never been
to anything this fancy.
- what do i need to know?
- oh, betty, please, you know which fork to use.
- outside in.
- mm-hmm. and the bread plate is on...
- my left.
- and the big glass is for...
- red wine!
- so you're fine. what's the topic?
- uh, topic?
- all these east side cows always
have a topic of conversation
they like to introduce
during the meal.
- last week, mine was the romanov dynasty.
- oh, no, i don't know what the topic is.
- what if it's something
that i know nothing about?
- well, do you have the phone number?
- yes.
- dial it.
- uh...
- we'll get one of the maids to tell us.
oh, that's a great idea.
okay.
hello, yes, may i please
speak to consuela?
there's always
a consuela.
hola, consuela.
Como esta?
that's all i got.
you're up.
oh, um...
hola, senora.
hola. um...
me llamo betty suarez.
Y queria saber si sabias,
uh, el tPico de discusiN...
por la fiesta esta viernes?
oh! oh, perfecto!
gracias! ha! torture!
the topic is torture!
isn't that great?
that's a little obvious.
arianna did torture
at her luncheon last year.
we waterboarded liz smith.
i just read this article
in "the new republic"
about the ethics of torture.
oh, i'm so happy.
thank you.
i'm so glad.
hey, willie, i just got
a bulletin from engineering.
major fashion news
all the tvs need to be turned
off. they're doing some sort
of test or something.
no computers, either.
- there's a virus going around or something.
- marc, what is going on?
nothing, it's just tech stuff.
it's completely normal.
- don't read any papers tomorrow--bad ink.
- don't make me hit you.
okay! i got a call from
my source at "fashion buzz,"
and there's a story
going around
that might have something
to do with you.
but i've saved
the best piece of gossip
masquerading as news
for last.
which fabulous
fashion world editor,
"mode"-ivated by a recent
reversal of fortune,
has begun to sell off
her clothes willy-nilly?
oh, and this tidbit
positively slay-ter-ed me.
her daily snack
is now a healthy combination
of food-stamp-friendly nuts
and soda water.
it's all so delicious...
and humiliating.
i'd tell you more,
but i'm on my way out
to a local thrift store
to purchase
one of wilhelmina slater's
former possessions.
oops.
did i say her name?
wilhelmina slater
i'm sorry.
because you know i'd never
mock someone when they're down.
i have no idea
how it got out.
i swear i didn't
tell anyone.
it's fine, marc.
obviously,
there's a mole here somewhere.
and i promise you,
i will find it,
and i will have it removed.
cancel my calls and meetings.
i'm done for the day.
- can i get you anything?
- no, i'm fine.
- willie--
- i said i'm fine.
there are some
who would argue
that under
certain circumstances,
torture is permissible.
but others would say--
ow! justin,
that is tight!
don't you want
to look good for matt's mom?
- yes.
- well, this is one of those instances
where torture is necessary.
good luck.
elena, that's
one too many plates.
- remember? betty's leaving.
- oh, that's all right. just leave it.
- no, i'll take it into the kitchen.
- no, no, don't bother.
it's no bother.
what is going on?
hilda, remember how you
asked me to let you know
when you do that thing
with your eyebrows
that makes you look
like the son of sam?
hey, everyone.
thanks so much
for having me over.
hey, archie,
great to see you.
councilman?
- bienvenido, seOr.
- hey, hey.
welcome. here--here,
take the wine.
- thank you.
- it's so good to see you. come on in.
- bye, hilda.
- unh-unh. i am gonna get you for this.
oh, come on, hilda.
try and have a good time.
archie is great.
you deserve a good guy.
willie.
willie, the auction house people
are here to do the pickup.
one second.
willie?
wilhelmina, are you here?
hello, marc.
you know what?
- i am not happy about this.
- come on.
just give him
a chance.
i hope
you' hungry.
because ignacio's
been cooking up a storm.
well, i can't tell you how good
it is to get a home-cooked meal.
- really, thank you so much
for having me over.
- please, you must be always having dinner
- oh...
- with mayors and governors and princes
and bishops--
no, it's more like
chinese takeout
- alone in my apartment, really.
- he's so modest.
the man's a celebrity,
and he's so modest.
papi,
he's a queens councilman.
he's not justin timberlake.
thank you, hilda,
for keeping my feet
on the ground.
you see that? hilda could
be good for you.
hey.
excuse us
for a second.
stop scowling.
i don't like surprises,
elena.
mom...
here's your medication.
thank you.
- thank you.
- enjoy.
wow. everything's
so fancy.
and everyone looks so...
perfect.
yeah, only 'cause they've
had an army of people
working on them all afternoon.
and you look beautiful.
thank you.
you look so...
- hello, honey.
- ah.
don't you look handsome?
i love that tie on you.
- where'd you get it?
- you bought it for me.
oh. well, aren't i clever?
- um, you've met betty.
- oh, yes, of course.
i'm, uh, i'm so happy
that you could make it.
and i won't ask you
to bring up any of
my bags tonight.
matthew, don't just
stand off to the side.
make sure you circulate.
edith, i love
your new labradoodle.
- well, that didn't go so bad.
- right, and remember,
- you still have "torture"
to look forward to.
- mm-hmm.
- stuffed mushroom?
- ooh.
i'll be right back.
excuse me. hello there.
- oh, uh, hi, judge wincroft.
- we're right over there.
- mmm.
- he has an s&m dungeon
- in the basement of his weekend house.
- hmm. this is great.
uh, betty.
i'd like you to meet
judge wincroft.
it's very nice
to meet you.
matt, i don't know where
my mushroom cap went.
excuse me.
dinner is served.
but first, i would like
to introduce everyone
to the newest piece
in the hartley art collection.
beginning in december,
it will be on display
at the louvre.
but right now it is here
in my living room.
oh, my god,
is that a mushroom cap?
oh, it's ruined.
what is an appetizer
doing on my painting?
actually, miss--
it was me, mom.
that's my mushroom cap.
i was fooling around, tossing
stuff at, uh, mr. randolph.
i-i apologize.
oh, no, that's fine.
if the artist were alive,
he'd get a good laugh,
but he's dead,
which is why it's so valuable.
into the dining room,
everyone.
so unlike matthew
to do something like that.
i guess you bring out his...
playful side. hmm?
i'm so sorry.
it's okay.
don't worry.
marc, i thought
i would be fine,
selling everything...
but i'm not.
so then don't.
but i need the money.
why, god? why?
what have i done
to anger you?
i just hate seeing you
like this.
are you taking a picture of me
on your cell phone?
no. no. oh!
this is killing me
as much as it's killing you.
do you think i like living
without your luxuries?
that's just it, marc.
they're not just luxuries.
these things are who i am.
each fur tells a story.
each piece of jewelry
is a piece of me.
it reminds me that
i've achieved something,
because, damn it, i have.
i came from nothing,
and i've accomplished something.
- but your father was a senator.
- oh, shut up.
it's the woman
from the auction house.
what do you want me
to tell her?
take it. take all of this.
do with it what you want.
i don't care anymore!
just bring me the money!
- marc, do you like what you see?
- uh-huh.
well, get used to it,
because starting now,
mama is downsizing.
not where it counts, baby!
all right. so i am gonna
run by the office,
close the deal
with this photographer.
then i'm gonna be back
with a couple of steaks,
bottle of wine.
- you and i are gonna celebrate.
- have you read about the treatment, daniel?
- some of these side effects are rough.
- i know, but, i mean, molly, it could work.
10% chance, and considering
my history, more like 2%.
yeah, but it's still 2%.
i mean, come on,
think about our future.
there is no future, daniel.
this, what we have right now,
is our future.
- don't say that.
- i'm dying, daniel.
no!
i realize that it's so hard
for me to understand
what it is
you're going through.
molly,
i'm not going anywhere.
i'm gonna be right by your side
through all of this.
i promise. please.
i'm sorry, honey.
i know how i want to live
the rest of my life,
- and it's not like this.
- molly, don't--
i can't do it.
so anyway, this council meeting
went on forever,
and it was just so hot in there,
i actually fell asleep.
i mean, i even snored.
- you didn't.
- well, it could have been embarrassing,
but i managed to turn
my snore into a "nay."
that's hilarious.
isn't that hilarious, hilda?
really.
oh, yeah, that is funny.
well, i know i'm gonna hate
myself in the morning,
but i'm gonna treat myself
to one more new potato.
this was an incredible meal,
ignacio.
it was my pleasure,
your honor.
i just hope we can make
a habit of this.
- right, hilda?
- oh, yes. absolutely.
you should just come
whenever you want.
everybody,
please be seated.
- are you sure there's nothing i--
- don't worry about it.
matthew, i thought it would be
fun if we split couples up.
- come. i want you back there with me.
- um, mom, i want to sit with betty.
no, stop. the name cards
were placed hours ago.
- it's all been settled.
- it's okay.
ignacio, come help me
with dessert.
oh, yeah. excuse us.
oh, justin.
- i'm trying to enjoy my new potato.
- mm-hmm.
hey. excuse me.
so how awkward
is this for you?
what? no!
why would this be awkward?
because they're working their
butts off trying to fix us up.
archie, i'm sorry.
honestly, i didn't know.
they just sprung this on me.
please.
it happens all the time.
i'm a reasonably
attractive man in his 40s
with a midlevel government job.
i'm a... catch.
and you, your eyes
have a story
that they wish to tell,
and i have my whole life,
and i listen well.
that's a justin timberlake song.
oh, i'm so glad
you got that,
'cause that would have
been really weird.
oh! thank you.
i'm so pleased you could
all be here tonight.
there's just so much
to talk about,
so many interesting
things happening.
but, um, you know me.
i like to stick to one topic,
and it's something that
has been, uh, much on my mind,
because it speaks to how
civilized people should live.
betty says: torture!
what is going to be...
the future of opera?
opera?
you have a thought, betty?
i was just so excited
to hear the topic.
i'm sorry. please go on.
oh, no. really,
why don't you start us off?
everybody, this is,
uh, betty suarez.
she is a friend of matthew's.
please, betty. i'd be fascinated
to hear your opinion.
the future of opera.
go.
my experience with opera...
is not so vast.
so i guess my opinion...
is not so...
you know, fully...
you know, formed...
as... as some of you...
matt says:mode photo spread "opera" last november
gareth pugh
carmen
aida
the ring
rigoletto
opera is fashion.
meaning?
meaning that the opera
will thrive
as any art thrives--
uh, by evolving
and embracing new ideas
and, of course, by giving
its audience a grander,
more hopeful
version of themselves.
that is as succinct
and insightful
a piece of criticism
as i have ever heard.
do you mind if i use it
in my next column?
but what do you mean
when you say "fashion"?
well, i work at "mode."
i love "mode."
it's like my bible.
you know,
and in some respects,
what is more archaic
than couture dresses?
- like opera.
- exactly, and eventually,
these couture collections
have an enormous influence
on our modern style.
and opera can do
the same thing.
absolutely right.
i saw "don giovanni"
on the lawn last year...
here you go, councilman.
- ah. thank you for the takeout, ignacio.
- it was my honor.
- who knows? my cooking
may be eaten by royalty.
- well, i was thinking of leaving a little
for my cleaning lady tomorrow.
just as good.
uh, honey, could you come help
me in the kitchen with, uh...
- you know.
- oh, yeah. the "you know."
- that--that thing.
uh, good night.
- mm-hmm.
- excuse us.
- thanks again.
yeah. subtlety doesn't run
in this family's genes, so...
i guess according
to their plan,
this is when i'm supposed
to ask you out.
yeah.
yeah, that's the plan.
- well, good night.
- whoa, wait a minute.
you're gonna
disappoint them like that?
- my dad cooked you dinner.
- hilda, you're great.
and nothing
would make me happier
than to take you out
on a real date--
- one that you know about.
- that sounds good.
okay, guys. i asked her out,
and she said yes.
- what? oh, my god!
- what? what a surprise!
- we had no idea!
- oh, we're shocked.
ay, please.
miles, what can i say? we just
couldn't live without you.
well, listen,
i am so sorry about the way
our last meeting ended.
i just hate getting caught up
- in all these messy business details.
- and yet you do.
- i know. i'm so cute.
- so i guess we'll check in next week,
- start kicking around a concept?
- whatever. i am easy.
love to you both.
air kiss.
air kiss. au revoir.
so i see you put
your money together.
daniel, if we're
gonna be partners,
we need to be partners
all the way.
so i did what i had to do.
you know...
i know you think
i'm always looking for a way
to muscle u out,
but really, i'm not.
life is too short.
well, how about that.
daniel meade is
waxing philosophical.
just beginning to realize
what's most important...
because of molly.
she's just determined to
live life on her own terms,
even if it kills her.
oh, mrs. hartley.
hi. i was just looking
at your pictures.
- they're great.
- oh. mm. so, betty,
where did you go to college?
- um, queens college.
- oh, lovely.
and were you the first person
in your family to go?
yep.
yeah, i-i lived at home,
and i worked the whole time,
but i did it.
good for you.
that's wonderful.
you're ambitious.
i can see you're going places.
oh, wow. thank you.
yes. uh, matthew went to yale.
he speaks three languages.
uh, he spent a year in rome
on a fulbright.
- have you heard him play the piano?
- nope, not yet,
but i can wait to.
oh, well,
he plays beautifully.
he took lessons for years
at the turtle bay music school.
- do you know it?
- no. i haven't heard of it.
oh, it's a wonderful place.
all the kids study there.
so, uh, tell me, what exactly
do the two of you
have in common?
uh, w-well, loads.
uh-huh. loads.
betty, i have high hopes
for my son.
he's been given
every privilege,
and i expect him
to take advantage of that.
okay. uh, i'm not sure i
understand what you're saying.
what i'm saying is that,
uh, i hope you enjoyed
your meal tonight,
but i don't think that
we'll be seeing you again.
you know, if you're, uh, cold,
you could just say something.
we have, like,
17 fireplaces.
your mother just told me that
i'm not good enough for you
and we don't have a future.
i'm leaving.
- no, betty, please, please don't go. please.
- matt-- what if she's right?
- matt, what if it matters
that i didn't go to yale?
- it doesn't matter.
- this is too much for me.
- hey, hey, hey.
- i am not gonna come between
you and your mother.
- no, you won't. i'd like have you both in my life.
- what, and just keep us
apart all the time?
- now, betty, please listen.
look, i want this relationship
to have a future.
you have to trust me,
all right?
don't worry about her.
oh, matthew,
dessert is ready.
- come in after you say
good-bye to your friend.
- i'm not saying good-bye to her, mom.
- oh?
- i'm saying good-bye to you.
betty and i are leaving.
- oh, don't be ridiculous. just come--
- no, i don't know exactly what you said to her,
- but i can guess.
- matthew--
good night, mother.
i'm leaving with my girlfriend.
are you okay?
of course.
why wouldn't i be?
no reason. nothing.
i just don't want
our budget snacks
to set off another one
of your... episodes.
i swear, marc,
if you took a picture of me
on your cell phone,
i will kill you and eat you.
but i've arrived
at a better place,
- and daniel helped me get there.
- the boy blunder? how?
molly wants to live her life
till the day she dies.
and damn it, so do i!
but what about the cash?
what about the equity?
i can live without
the furs and the jewelry.
but to hell if i'm gonna
sacrifice everything.
i've worked too hard
to let it all slip away.
so... how are you
going to pay for it?
i will do
whatever i have to do.
maybe i'll take out
a second mortgage.
all i know for sure is,
as god is my witness,
i will never go without
champagne and caviar again.
now pass me a bellini, please.
and i know it's horrible,
- but i'm just so frustrated about it.
- because she won't do the treatment?
i get what she'saying.
i do. it's just...
i've done everything right,
and for the first time
in my adult life,
i am really in love,
and i don't want to lose it.
- and--and this treatment, it could work.
- but, daniel--
no, i know, i know
i'm not the one with cancer.
of course
it's her decision, but--
look, she's just trying to
give you
- the time she does have left.
- but i want more.
sometimes you can't get more.
sometimes you have to take
what you get.
oh, hold the door!
- hi, mrs. meade.
- hello, betty.
so did you wow victoria hartley
with your take on torture?
no, not quite.
she changed the topic.
oh, that old trick.
and then she told me that i was
completely wrong for her son.
ooh. she's really playing by
the rich bitch handbook.
i keep thinking there's
gotta be something i can do
- to make her like me.
- oh, please, betty.
- you're never going to win
that woman over.
- well, maybe that's true,
but i just
don't understand why.
well, grow up, because not
everybody's going to like you.
you've just got to
suck it up and embrace it.
- there's nothing i can do?
- hell, yes, there's something you can do.
you can throw it
right back at her.
when one of those
silk stocking hags
stares me down,
do you know what i do?
stare back?
you got that right.
hey.
hey, it's cold out.
what's going on?
you want to live life?
we're gonna live life.
put on your jacket.
we're going hiking.
- and tomorrow,
we're gonna go to the beach.
- but it's freezing.
i don't care.
look, all i know
is every free moment
of every free day i have
is gonna be spent with you.
you want to go traveling?
you want to stay home?
you want to go to the movies?
you want to ride around
on the friggin' subway all day?
it doesn't matter. all that
matters is, i love you, molly,
and i'm gonna treasure every
moment i have left with you.
you got a problem with that?
no problem.
good.
let's go play in the snow.
okay.
hey, where are you?
i'm here.
well, hurry up.
it's a beautiful day.
okay.
hi, mrs. hartley.
- waiting for my son?
- he's on his way down.
oh, that's right.
matthew's moving back in
to his apartment today.
i won't apologize for who i am
or what i think, betty.
well, neither will i.
what can i say?
my judgments are severe.
it's just the way
i look at the world.
well, i'm sorry for you.
but i might
be around for a while.
hey!
hey.
- ready to go?
- all set. want to get a cab?
no, let's walk.
it's a nice day.
so you play the piano?
oh, no.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入
www.tvsubtitles.net