Previously on "Ugly betty"...
-Hilda suarez, I love you. Will you marry me?
-Oh.
So you like someone.
Yeah.
-Are you my mother?
-Yes.
Tyler is not who you think he is.
-Well, who is he then?
-He's your brother.
I really, uh,
need to see you tonight.
I'm kind of busy right now.
Thanks for not ditching me tonight.
My name is betty suarez,
And I'm looking for
a new orthodontist.
I've been wearing braces
for over four years now.
Good-bye, braces.
Whoo!
-Morning!
-Morning.
Okay.
Hey!
Papi, betty and I were up all night
Talking about my wedding,
and there is really no way
That we can do it without
100 snow-white doves.
What do you need doves for?
City's full of pigeons.
-And they're free.
-Pigeons?!
Ugh! Why do you hate me?!
Betty, back me up.
I don't know if I said "
A hundred white doves."
Ay! Where is justin
when you need him?
Uh, hey, austin.
Um, just leaving another message.
Don't really know how you're
feeling about what happened...
Um, you know, the... kiss.
Maybe you st your
phone or something.
I don't really know. Probably not.
Um, anyway, you can call me back.
Um, uh, this is justin.
Justin! Papi doesn't
understand the doves.
There have to be a hundred,
and if they're not snow white,
Then they might as
well just be pigeons.
That's what I said.
Betty, before I forget,
This is your last check
for the orthodontist.
Papi, I'm an adult.
I can cover it myself.
Then I will take it.
What? Champagne waterfalls
are very expensive.
Please, I'm your father.
Let me do this.
And besides, it's my fault.
Everyone on my side of the family
Has the big, crazy chompers.
A.B., look this way.
I got you just a
little small something
To celebrate your
braces coming off.
Aww! How sweet!
Not so fast.
You can't have it until
those things are gone.
Okay, well, one more
thing to look forward to.
All right, family...
Say good-bye to the braces!
'cause you're never
gonna see them again!
Bye, braces!
Tyler? Interesting.
I'm totally on board.
Oh. Um...
Amanda spilled a wine cooler
on my shirt last night, so--
Oh, last night. So you slept over?
Boo-yay! I totally
got the stain out.
Thanks. Um...
Listen, listen,
I should probably go.
Okay.
So... will I see you later?
Yeah, if you want to.
Marc, nothing happened.
Honest to prada.
He was just jet-lagged
from his trip with claire
So he stayed over. That right there
Was the first time
we've even kissed.
It's actually kind of nice,
Getting to know a y before
I tickle his ginger. Sweet.
It really is.
Marc, I think this might be
the start of something real.
So does daniel know about
you and his half brother?
No, daniel doesn't know,
and he's never going to.
Really, never?
Secrets come out, mandy.
If you think this is real,
you should probably tell daniel
Before he hears about
it someplace else.
So the whole time I'm
on this date, right,
I keep staring at this guy's
funky lateral incisor.
But, I mean, I can't say anything
'cause you know how men are.
They're so sensitive.
Huh, what was that?
-Dr. Frankel?
-Yeah?
I'm really enjoying this story,
But we're gonna take
my braces off today,
-right?
-Of course. Absolutely! Of course.
Great.
So, anyway,
I'm sitting at the table,
And mr. Funkyity tooth is taking
forever with this menu, right?
Look, I have to be at work
soon because it's picture day,
And I'm really looking forward
to getting a new I.D... mm.
With my new smile.
And I don't want to
rush you or anything...
mm-hmm. Enough said. Absolutely.
You have had these on forever...
Forever. And you are
dying to get them off.
-We're not gonna waste another minute.
-Yep, okay.
-Are we ready?
-I'm so ready.
And...
-There's the fire alarm.
-Are you freaking kidding me?!
I'm so sorry. It's been
on the fritz all week.
Well, at least the sprinklers
didn't go off this time. What?
Bonjour!
I just got back. I brought
you some parisian chocolate.
Great. But I'm kind
of busy right now,
Getting ready for this shoot.
Oh, yes! The million dollar bra.
Everybody's talking about it.
You really pulled off
quite a coup there.
Ad sales are through the roof.
-Aren't you going to ask me about my trip?
-How s your trip?
Alexis and tyler really hit it off.
You know, she was
skeptical at first,
But then when she really let
herself get to know him...
I just... I wish you
had been there. Yeah--
A fun vacation with my half
brother who I don't like
And my mother who lied to
me about his very existence.
Daniel, can we please
just talk about this?
Why start now?
I'm late for my meeting. Excuse me.
I have three words for you--
Million dollar bra.
It's never been featured
on a cover before,
But the good people
at eve's seduction
Are allowing "Mode" To be the
very first, thanks to me.
Thank you, thank you.
Yes, yes. Daniel did
something right.
Hallelujah, it's a miracle.
So the bra launches its world
tour with a gala send-off
This afternoon at the guggenheim.
We will be shooting the
bra immediately after...
At the guggenhei also thanks to me.
If you turn to page
seven of your packets,
You'll see the bra's itinerary
for the day, or bra-tinerary.
Uh, we are working under
a very tight timeline,
-So you will have four hours to shoot the bra.
-Uh, daniel?
I'm sure you have this
all thought through,
And, uh, I might be a little slow,
But can you explain to me how
we're gonna shoot the bra
While it's on a plane?
What are you talking about?
Well, according to
your bra-tinerary,
You have us shooting the
bra in the afternoon,
But the new press release
from eve's seduction
Has the bra on its way to
cairo at the same time.
I'm sure it's just, uh,
been a little mix-up
And won't be a problem.
No, this is a huge problem.
I know the bra has a busy schedule,
But you promised me four
hours to do the shoot.
We... no, we didn't have
a written agreement,
We had a verbal one.
Look, just put someone
else on the phone.
-Hel-hello? -Dael.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
I sort of met someone.
Really?
Well...
Good for you... I guess.
There's more.
It's tyler.
Amanda...
How can you do this to me?
Well, we said we were casual.
I-I thought that's how this worked.
Yeah, but he's my half brother.
Don't you see how messed
up that is? Daniel--
Don't say anything.
?
Do you thinkaybe--oh.
Sorry, I-I was talking.
Hey, that's not so bad.
I had planned everything out.
I was supposed to
have my braces off,
I picked out a nice outfit.
Aww, why didn't you wear it?
And then the sprinklers went off
At my orthodontist's this morning.
-Ironically improving your look slightly.
-Thanks.
Hey, betty, ask me if,
in four years,
I've ever gotten tired
of making fun of you.
Go ahead, ask me. Ask me!
In four years, ve you ever got--
Nope!
Okay, betty, wait, come back.
Come on, we can fix this.
Look, watch.
First, we just gotta
get rid of the braces,
And then we'll fix that hair.
-Ah! Thank you, marc!
-Bup-bup-bup! We're not done yet.
Now we gotta fix that face!
Let's try this and this and this.
Voil?
Marc, this looks nothing like me.
You're welcome.
I am out of options.
Their head of publicity changed
the bra schedule last minute.
E really screwed me on this.
So go above her.
Betty, the only person
Higher up at eve's
seduction is eve herself,
And no one's ever seen her smile.
Everybody knows she's
a cast-iron bitch.
I mean, look at her.
Last time she smiled
Was when dick cheney shot
that guy in the face.
Hmm. All right. So don't
go above her. Go below her.
Eve's assistant alison is super nice,
and we're old pals.
She's probably online right now.
Look, I'm sorry I'm so stressed.
First, this whole thing with
the bra and then amanda.
-You know she broke up with me?
-She broke up with you?
Yeah. I thought it was
more casual than that.
No, we were.
It's just that she wanted
to start seeing tyler.
Tyler? Your brother?
That's intense.
-Why would she do something like that?
-I don't know.
Maybe she wanted something...
more than casual.
Hey, come on! I can do
something re than casual.
Okay. I'm just saying,
is that really what you want?
Hey, a-bomb!
B-Bomb! Got the birthday flowers.
You rock...
hard. You rock harder!
You're a rock star.
You're a rocket ship!
You are rock candy. Okay, uh,
can we just save all this rockin'
for later, ladies?Thanks.
Sorry. He's stressed.
Look, I just found out that
the bra has to go to Egypt.
That's really gonna
screw up our shoot.
Is there something you
can do to help? Ooh,
that might be tough.
Eve's in one of her moods today.
She does always pad the
bra's schedule though.
So tell you what. Why don't
we meet at the Guggenheim,
and see if we can try to convince her?
What do you say?
I'd say you rock! No, you rock!
-No, you rock!
-Okay, you both rock.
Sorry. Thank you.
We'll see you later. Bye-bye.
Betty, 1. Giving up, 0.
Uh, you've got a raisin
stuck in your... braces.
-It's kind of gross.
-Ew.
Hey, braces, the museum is
closed for a private party.
Your school's group is over there.
Ah, ha ha. No, I'm not with them.
-I'm actually with "Mode."
-I.D.
What's with all the security?
Eve's seduction hired us
to protect the bra, miss.
Can I see your press I.D.?
Yep.
This isn't you.
Oh.
Actually, it's a funny story.
See, it was picture
day at work today,
And this guy I know thought
it would be funny to--
Oh. Step to the side, ma'am.
I'm gonna have to ask
you to open your mouth.
Why? What do you think
you're gonna find?
I have braces, okay?
I'm an adult woman with braces!
It's a pain!
Do I wish that I was born
with perfect teeth? Yes.
But I wasn't. So if you'll excuse me,
I have a job to do.
A-bomb! Bomb!
Aah!
Ah!
Aah.
Do I wish
I was born with perfect teeth? Yes.
You've got a raisin
Stuck in your braces.
What happened?
You got your wish.
Dr. Frankel?
What are you doing here?
Well, you wished you were
born with perfect teeth,
And here you are.
You have perfect teeth.
You're welcome.
So what are you--
My guardian angel, a tooth fairy?
Eh, I don't do labels.
Wait a minute.
I don't need glasses
Wait, why don't I need glasses?
You got lasik.
You wanted perfect eyes to
match your perfect teeth.
-In this world, you're actually just a little bit vain.
-Really?
Mm-hmm. That doesn't
sound like me at all.
Hilda? Papi?
Are you guys...
-Who are you?
-Who e you?
-This is my house.
-Yeah, actually, it's not.
It's not? No.
Well, where's my family?
Baby, get the bat.
Oh!
My family lives here?
This is amazing.
And all of this happened
because I had perfect teeth?
Well, since your papi didn't
have to pay for your braces,
All that money went right
into the tech boom.
Rented out your old house
and voil? Casa suarez.
Oh, my god.
Is that my family?
Hey! Mija, there you are.
-We've been looking for you.
-Yeah.
Hi, guys.
Uh, hilda, you look so...
Beautiful? I know!
Well, I took your advice.
I'm wearing makeup.
-Isn't she a knockout?
-Oh! Anyway, betty,
I have been looking
everywhere for a wedding dress
That looks like the one that you
wore to prom. I went to prom?
I was prom queen?
Okay, ha ha, very funny.
Anyway, do you tnk I can
pull off a dress like that?
Oh, your opinion means
so much to me, you know?
You're my fashion guru!
Oh.
-Aah!
-Oh!
There you are. I'm so sorry.
-Where'd you go?
-I've been working double duty.
I'm showing anna paquin what
her life would've been like
If she didn't have that
giant gap in her teeth.
I mean, my family is loaded,
And hilda is happier
than I've ever seen her.
But why does she... look so...
-Different?
-Yeah.
It's the law of the universe.
There can only be one
really pretty sister.
I mean, think about it, right?
There's paris and nicky,
kim and khloe, jeff and beau...
So I'm the pretty sister? Mm-hmm.
You know you love it.
Don't pretend you don't.
You'd be surprised how something
As simple as perfect
teeth can change you...
And the people around you.
Good afternoon, "Mode" Magazine.
Please hold.
Oh, hi, betty.
-Marc... you have a baby?
-I'm so sorry.
Didier had a big trial today,
and our sitter canceled.
You look beautiful, by the way.
Are those earrings new?
They're great! And you're nice.
What are you doing at reception?
Oh, answering phones,
alphabetizing files.
But if you need me
to run any errands,
I can totally do that.
Rosalita will sleep
through anything.
She once slept through a
coup attempt in el salvador.
Oh. Oopsie-poopsie!
Somebody did a numero dos.
I just gotta change-sies,
But if you need anything,
seriously, just...
Ohh.
Ugh.
-I can't believe he brought that little goblin.
-Amanda?
This is a place of work... ish.
Okay, could marc's
desk be any gayer?
Not that I mind gay. I love gay.
I just usually prefer the loud,
swishy, stereotypical kind.
You're awfully quiet today.
Am I?
Yeah, usually you chime
in with some funny remark
About his lesbian jeans
or his jheri curl.
You mean... you and
I make fun of marc?
Only every monday
through friday, bestie.
Um, bestie, I don't think
you should be stealing
All that petty cash.
Um, it's not stealing when
you own half the company, b.
Mm-hmm. Yeppers.
Married to daniel.
Can you believe it?
I mean, at first it was
just casual, right?
And then he gets wind that
she's seeing other guys,
And then, of course,
daniel gets serious.
Ohh. Jealousy.
It can make a man marry you or...
Throw acid in your face.
Well, they seem happy.
Dr. Frankel?
Betty, these just came for you.
-They did? From who?
-Derek.
Derek who?
Derek jeter!
I'm dating derek jeter?!
Well, you were.
He's trying to win you back.
Why am I telling you this?
He can have me back!
I'll just put these in your office.
I'm a managing editor...
I'm rich...
And I'm dating derek jeter!
It's great to be betty suarez.
It seems like everyone
is doing great.
Daniel!
It's so good to see you.
Why? Have you got some
bad news to deliver?
Don't like what I'm wearing? Hmm?
Found some new way to humiliate me?
What? What are you talking about?
You may have everyone
else around here fooled,
But I know the real you.
Underneath that perfect smile,
You're ugly, betty.
Everything seemed so perfect.
Why does daniel hate me?
We've been through
so much together.
I was his assistant
for three years!
Oh, nope. You weren't.
Daniel's dad hired a plain jane
who wouldn't tempt his son,
And without your braces,
that wasn't you.
So bradford never hired me?
Well, then how'd I
end up at "Mode"?
I'm really nervous.
Are--are you
interviewing here, too?
Yes. I've always wanted
to work in fashion.
Oh. I like your poncho
Milan. Dolce & gabbana. Fall.
Marc, pull everything we
have on fabia cosmetics.
I want to thoroughly
humiliate daniel
At his first meeting
tomorrow morning.
Is that a bug in your teeth?
Oh, god. Oh, g-- ugh.
I think it's a poppy seed
from that bagel I ate.
You ate a bagel? Ugh.
My, what a beautiful,
clean smile you have.
Thank you.
Marc, you've just been
demoted to receptionist.
Pretty teeth, follow me.
So I was wilhelmina's assistant?
Mm-hmm.
How would that work?
I mean, we're completely different.
Well, maybe at first,
but you were a quick study.
No... awful...
No... should've been fired...
Hideous... and no.
Beth, do you understand
Why I can't even look
at you right now?
D-don't answer.
Betty, tell her.
Um...
There isn't much flow
from one look to another.
Betty, are you a
fashion person or not?
Tell her about the color!
Wilhelmina specifically
asked you for red.
What did you bring us?
No, not red, but burgundy,
Candy apple, scarlet, wine,
Crimson, blush, vermilion,
Puce, maroon.
Honestly, beth. Maroon?
Don't stop, betty.
The only true red in
this room is your face.
Betty, you are officially
my favorite person.
Oh, my god. I'm awful!
Beth can't help her red face.
She has rosacea.
Maybe I was just having a bad day?
Actually, that was a good day.
Yeah. You're kind of a beeyotch.
I've been trying to tell you.
Betty.
Mother meade. Look at you,
braving the sunlight
As if it won't burn your flesh.
Ahclever. I'm a vampire.
Well, excuse me if I
don't suck your blood
It's a little early to
consume that much booze.
Ha ha! Hah!
Everything is.
Claire and daniel hate me.
Wilhelmina and marc love me.
Oh, marc doesn't love you.
What? He couldn't have been nicer.
Well, to your face.
Honey, that's 'cause he's
terrified of you. Look.
It's like it's her life's mission
To make sure I never get promoted.
I hate her!
I hate her, her and her stupid,
beautiful eth.
He hates me.
Well, it's not like he
was that crazy about you
In your other life.
Well, what about my family?
They seemed happy.
Yeah, about that...
Betty. Hi.
Uh...
Betty, I need to talk to you.
Um, this is really hard for me,
But, uh...
You can't be my maid of honor.
I mean, it's my big day,
And I just want to be the
center of attention for once.
Do you hate me?
No.
No, of course not.
I mean, if this is what
you and bobby want.
Bobby? Who's bobby?
Talercio. Your fianc?
That guy I had a crush
on in high school?
Come on. Don't tease me.
I'm lucky I found a
guy like abundio.
Abundio? You're
marrying the meat man?
Isn't he, like, 70?
He's 61!
Well, how does justin
feel about this?
Justin? Who is justin?
Your...
Son.
What is with you today, betty?
Huh?
I mean, you're my sister,
and I look up to you,
But why do you always
have to make me feel bad?!
Hilda!
Hilda. Hilda!
Why doesn't she know about justin?
Well being the "Ugly sister"
Is a highly effective
method of birth control.
Mm-hmm.
Thanks to your perfect smile,
justin never existed.
Ooh. Spooky.
You really are a monster. What?
The million dollar bra shoot.
Oh, like you don't know.
Daniel, wait!
The bra shoot? That's today?
Yeah, it's today,
or it was until you sabotaged it.
No. No, I didn't sabotage it.
The head publicist changed
the bra's schedule on you.
How did you know that?
I didn't.
Look, daniel, I can fix this.
I know eve's assistant-- alison.
I can get her to help us.
Oh, just give it a rest.
How dumb do you think I am,
betty? I don't think
that you're dumb,
And I don'know what I did
to me you hate me, but...
I can assure you,
we are on the same team,
And the last thing I am is a liar.
Oh, yeah?
I can't believe I ever
slept with you, betty.
Frankly, I can't believe
you slept with him either.
Betty, darling, what are you up to?
Are you changing the plan on me?
Which--which plan?
Oh, sorry. We have so
many plans together.
The, uh, "Ruin the bra shoot/
humiliate daniel" Plan.
Oh.
Um, so I-I am sabotaging daniel.
No, we're sabotaging daniel.
Unless you're going rogue on me?
Betty, we're in this together.
So just stick with the plan
and by this time next week,
You and I will be
co-editors-in-chief of "Mode."
I don't believe that I'm in
cahoots with wilhelmina. Mm.
How could having perfect
teeth change me this much?
Well, let me break it
down for you, b-bomb.
All right, having
braces is hard, right?
People make fun of you,
and it hurts your feelings,
Which made you compassionate.
Pretty-teeth betty-
people fawned all over her,
And it went to her head.
What are you gonna do?
Betty?
Amanda!
Oh, hey, betty. Do you mind?
Yes, I mind!
You're in my office, and...
You're married!
And this is the last place
daniel would ever step foot,
Which is why you let ty-ty and I
have our private time in here.
Did you wanna saddle up?
It's a big desk. Mm.
Ew. Ew!
Hey, I never told derek jeter
about your side action,
So I expect you to keep your big,
sexy mouth shut!
Whoo! You eat lunch
on that desk? Ugh.
Ew. So amanda is
cheating on daniel...
Yeah, well--mm-hmm. In my office?
Well, daniel's not exactly
having a dry spell.
He's all over his assistant
right now in the copy room.
You wanna see? No! No, no, no,
no, no, no, no. I'm good.
, all right. So they're
both having affairs?
Wipe the judge-y off your face,
jeter cheater.
Betty, thank god.
I need $40,000...
Or I'm a dead man. My bookie says
if I don't cough up 40 large,
He'll break my legs. Bookie?!
You lost 40 grand gambling?
You know I've had
this mono on my back
Since we struck it rich.
-You gonna give me the cheddar or not?
-Papi!
It's not like I walk around
carrying thousands of...
Dollars in my purse.
There it is. Come to papi.
My god!
You're a good girl, mija.
Where would I be without you?
Well, adios, papi.
You have to stop doing that. Sorry.
Okay? Mm-hmm.
This is terrible.
Uh, I-I-it can't stay
this way. Mm-hmm.
It has to change. I have to-
I have to change it back. Okay.
-I'm gonna start with daniel.
-All right.
I'm gonna go to the
guggenheim... -mm-hmm.
I'm gonna talk to eve... -okay.
And I'm gonna get him the
-million dollar bra back.
-Oh, good, a change.
But maybe think about keeping
the hair. I love the hair.
So you see, if you
could just please find
A-a teeny, tiny,
teensy bit more time
For us to shoot the bra,
Then we all win.
We will all be happy.
All I heard was,
"Blah, blah, shrill.
Blah, blah, whine.
Blah, blah, beg."
And now I'm hungry
for mexican food.
Alison, get me some tacos!
Alison! Uh, I'm so sorry.
There is a little
problem with the bra.
It seems to be missing.
Okay, I am furious.
Alison, go punch yourself
in the neck. Officer!
Officer, what the hell is going on?
Officer!
Excuse me.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Wilhelmina?
Slacking off on the
elliptical, darling?
-The bra-- what are you doing?
-I'm protecting my interest.
The moment I heard you
speaking to daniel,
I knew you were gonna
stab me in the back.
First, I was hurt,
but then I realized,
Of course you'd double-cross me.
You're betty.
Help, security!
She's stealing the bra!
What?!
No, I'm not! I'm not! Ow!
You're a good girl, mija.
Jtin?
You sabotaged me!
I want my old life back.
Betty?
Hey, are you okay?
Daniel?
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey,
take it easy, take it easy.
Here you go.
I can see.
Uh... yeah.
No, no. You don't understand. I...
My braces! They're back!
I got my wish!
Okay. Maybe we should get you
to the hospital. No, I'm fine.
I'm fine. Where's the bra?
Is it still here?
Yeah, but they're about
to take it to the airport.
No, there's still time.
We have to find eve.
A-bomb!
No, no! No, no, no. No, hey.
No, it's a nickname.
It's okay, it's all right.
Come on. Jeez!
Come on, b-bomb.
Eve's right over here.
Thank you so much for this.
No problem.
Hey, weren't you supposed to
get your braces off today?
Yeah, change of plans.
Drag! I know how much
you hate those things.
Well, aside from not being
able to eat corn on the cob,
Which I love, it's not so bad.
Where's the bra?
It's supposed to be here.
Well, it's not.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, , no.
Not this time. Excuse me.
Excuse me. Sorry. Excuse me.
Wilhelmina.
Little extra cardio
wouldn't hurt, darling.
The bra. Give it to me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm not gonna let you
take it this time.
What the hell?!
Oh, my god.
I'm sorry. I t--I thought that--
That you were-- like before when--
I hit my head. I-I-I don't know.
I, like, maybe I have
a concussion or--
Ow!
No, no, no, no! Don't pull it.
I'm stuck.
What is going on here?
I'll tell you what's going on.
Betty is a breast man.
I am not a breast man.
My braces are stuck to the bra.
She ripped my shirt clean off!
I'm standing here with
nothing but a bustier on.
It's humiliating! No, it's genius.
You're bringing back
underwear as outerwear.
Yes, that's what I'm doing.
It's a celebration
of the brassiere.
Whoo!
Brava, brava. Thank you.
Hey, betty.
Ma'am, I'm gonna have to ask
you to step away from the bra.
Sir, what don't you understand?
My braces are stuck to the bra.
Well, that bra has to
be on a plane to cairo
Within the hour, whether
you're attached to it orot.
Look, you're not shipping my
junior features editor to cairo.
Look, there is one person
who can resolve this,
And it's eve. We have to find eve.
It's all about eve! Eve!
Eve! Don't go.
You gotta give us more
time to shoot the bra.
Yeah, we can charter a
plane to get it to cairo.
Look, if you could please just
look beyond this predicament
And--and--and look
into your heart...
Oh. Oh.
Uh, that was unexpected...
And a little painful.
Well, since you've cheered me up,
I will allow you to have
the bra for two hours.
Yes!
Not a minute longer.
Thank you. Yay! We did it! Ow, ow!
We just need to get your
braces off that thing.
-Is there an orthodontist here?
-Oh, yeah, that's likely.
Oh, me. That's me.
Excuse me. I got it.
Dr. Frankel?
Okay, here we go. Uh-oh.
What?
-Mm. It's more complicated than I thought.
-Oh, no.
I can't tell where the bra
ends and the braces begin.
Well, we're gonna have to just
cut the bra apart then. Ohh!
Oh, for god sake, cut betty apart.
That bra is worth
more than her life.
Well, the only other choice I
have is to remove your braces.
Now?
-Like, right now?
-Now.
In front of everybody?
Do it.
All right. Let's do it.
Okay.
I really need you to hold
your mouth right there.
They're gone? They're off.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Is something wrong?
No, it looks...
Betty, you look great.
Yes, yes, congratulations, betty.
Your smile will longer
induce seizures in children.
Now can we get this show
on the road, please?
Mm.
?Fa-fa-fashionista,
Hey, how do your teeth feel?
Weird. Fine. Naked.
Yeah. So I have to get home.
My family's planning something
for me to celebrate.
?Fa-fa-fashionista,
Amanda, hey.
Can we talk about us?
Oh, well, you were
pretty clear before.
Well... i'm sorry, okay?
I didn't have a right to say that.
You can date whoever you want.
That's what "Casual" Means, right?
That's...
Thank you.
-Hey.
So all of those
things going wrong--
That wasn't you, was it?
Part of your plot to
take over the company,
Making daniel look bad?
Daniel can do that all by himself.
No, marc, this shoot is an a-cup.
My plan for the meades--
Double-d.
Hey. Did I tell you
my brilliant idea?
Million dollar thong.
What's with the face?
You don't think it'd be comfortable?
I saw you hugging daniel.
Oh, cute. You're jealous.
Actually, daniel and I just
had a really great talk,
And he kind of gave
us his blessing. Wow.
So daniel meade gave
us his blessing.
How generous of him.
Okay, jealousy? Slightly less cute.
No, I am just saying that
the guy barely talks to me,
And now he thinks that I need
his permission to date you?
Yeah.
I think you guys still have
some issues to work out.
And you know what? So do I.
So why don't we take
a little time-out,
And we can all work on
our own stuff for now?
Tyler? I don't believe
we've officially met.
I'm wilhelmina slater.
Looks like y could use a drink.
Yeah, I could. But I don't drink.
Okay, ready?
Yes.
Surprise! Surprise!
Oh! Ahh!
Yay!
Yummy.
Aww.
Isn't that sweet?
So sweet.
Oh, can you get that, please? Yeah.
Thank you. Let's see.
Perfect. Okay, here.
Now you can ruin
your perfect teeth.
Sync by YYeTs.net