eason on "ugly betty"...
- is this a good idea?
- no.
- henry!
- charlie?
they denied my visa.
so what does that
- what does that mean?
it means i have to stay here...
for i don't know how long.
charlie,what are you doing here?
i'm pregnant.
it's my by. i have to
go to tucson with her.
dr. farkas has been dating
a girl named charlie.
maybe the baby isn't henry's!
you hate me!
the thing is,i don't hate you.
daniel,you're loaded.
?????
????
- oh,my god! the brakes.
- what? what? what? what?
wilhelmina,will you spend
the rest of your life with me?
you know i will.
my husband won't take my
calls. he won't see me.
i know if i could just get to
him,i could save my marriage.
relax,fish,a'ight? it's
all going down tomorrow
when they transfer us upstate.
get the damn gun! this is happening!
why would fey have
pictures of me in her safe?
fey sommers was your mother.
i love you,hilda,and i
want you to be my wife.
???????
oh
betty are you all right?
did you break another vase?
no senor grubstick
what`s breaking
is my haert
betty.
whore
darling
ican explain!
i can not take your lies anymory
i am having you baby
if i can`t have you
no one eles you
you will have to kill me to get to him
my pleasure
no wait don`t do ti
seeing you like this makes me
realize just haow mach i love
what
i love you too
ay.
no! no!
no
- aunt betty!
- oh,god.
sorry. it was just a bad
dream. what time is it?
8:15.
you fell asleep in front
of the tv again last night.
oh,god. i can't be late.
daniel's getting out
of the hospital today.
i gotta throw some laundry in.
- i gotta get breakfast started. is your mom coming down?
-  like she'd ever leave that room.
hey,why don't i just skip camp today
- and help you do the laundry?
- justin,it can't be that bad. it's arts and crafts.
they keep us locked in a
room,making us paint rocks
- and calling them paperweights. look,
- you're going. now you want some cereal?
shoot. i forgot to get the cereal...
which is okay because
we don't have any milk.
don't worry about it. we're
making macaroni necklaces today.
i'll just eat that.
when's grandpa coming home from mexico?
i miss him.
i know. i miss him,too.
he'll be home soon.
it's gotta be soon.
hey. where'd you go?
i couldn't listen to you snore anymore.
i took a shower.
what is the matter with you?
you're not supposed to
get your bandages wet,
and i do not snore.
i
- sometimes i sing through my nose.
oh. okay. mm-hmm.
you know what?
i'm actually feeling a
whole lot better today.
maybe******
oh no nono
you are not ready to go
back to your place. hilda.
does this hurt? ow.
you see? you're not ready to go back.
it's been three weeks. hmm.
you're gonna have to let
me out of here sometime.
ahh.
?????
????
except hotter.
what is the rush? we
got a great setup here.
betty brings us our meals.
we got tv. no one gets shot.
you see this gray hair?
this one is called "santos almost died."
i'm not willing to risk another one,
so just sit back.
relax.
watch tv.
morning,trendies.
this is "fashion buzz,"
and coming up in the hour,
we'll tell you why mauve is bad,
stripes are the fad
and naomi's gone mad.
but first,an exclusive
with "mode" director
and soon-to-be bride
of bradford meade,
wilhelmina slater.
clearly,grief becomes la slater.
she looked ah-mah-zing
as she gave us an update
on daniel and alexis meade's recovery
from that nasty car
accident three weeks ago.
bradford and i want the people to know
that we are planning on moving
forward with our wedding,
and i did ask alexis if she
would like us to move ahead
and told her
to flutter her eyelid once for yes...
oh.
and by god,that little eyelid fluttered.
that's our girl.
she is not your girl!
that is my family,do you hear me?
do you hear me?!
oh,no,she can't,
but everybody else in montauk can.
- yoga,where have you been?
- i went for a walk on the beach.
then i copped us some blueberries
from the farmers market.
ooh,fish,i got to give it to you.
hiding out in the hamptons
- sure do beat that crack house in the bronx.
- just don't get used to it.
mitsy sacks will be back
from barcelona in the fall,
and i don't think she'll take too kindly
- to having escaped convicts hiding out in her home.
-  just as long as we still hanging
for candy bergen's
end-of-the-summer barbecue
'cause everybody was talking about that
- at the clambake last night.
- we are fugitives. you're going to get us caught.
you the one everybody recognize.
folks just see me up in here,
they think i'm the maid or gayle king.
oh,shoot. i almost forgot.
found you a new seashell.
i don't want any more damn shells!
i want to see my children.
i want my husband back,
but that damn bitch won't
let him out her sight.
she's moved into my house,
changed his cell phone,his e-mail.
you gon' get yours,it's just-
you front page still,baby.
what if i wear a disguise?
mitsy throws a big
halloween party every year.
she has a closet full
of costumes upstairs.
you got a date on that party?
'cause i already got
uma's hayride that week.
oh,my god. mmm.
guessed who just showered
a mere 7 inches away
from mr. emilio estevez
at the gym this morning.
i am telling you-steam,a
little soap in your eyes...
st. elmo's still on fire.
mmm. what is that on
the corner of your mouth?
lip liner.
don't you lie to me,missy.
you've taken a lover,
and that lover has a creamy center.
just leave me alone.
mandy... you're binging...
and gaining weight by the minute.
stop staring at me!
i didn't stop when emilio
asked,and i won't stop now.
listen to me. i know you're stressed
about this whole birth
certificate thing. shh!
but you're starting to look
like two fat girls hugging.
just bite the bullet and
confront your parents.
what if it's true?
what if fey sommers is really my mother?
but at least you'll know the truth
and let the healing begin,
and by "healing," i
mean a 3-day f flush.
i haven'gained that much.
you can't even notice.
"mode" magazine,please hold.
morning,mark,betty.
i'm calling them. i'm calling them!
ew.
- good morning. - oh,betty,i'm so glad
you're here. big toe-please scratch.
okay.
oh,yeah,that's it.
oh,i'll never forget this.
this is not what i want
to be remembered for.
so when are they coming to
unhook you from this thing?
- actually,i don't think i'll be getting out
of here today. - what? but the doctor said-
you want to listen the doctor
or the guy who smashed into
a tree going 80 miles an hour?
- i am still in a lot of pain here,betty.
- well,i can see that.
you've taken the pain pill
every time they've offered it.
you know,daniel,you may
just want to pass on the pill
- and see how you're feeling. - yeah,that
whole feeling part-not really interested.
all right,i get it. so how's alexis?
there's no change.
mm. i was in with her all morning.
you know,i've been doing
a lot of internet research,
- and they say you really should talk to coma victims.
-  betty,i'm doing everything i can.
i know. i'm sorry.
????
you know wilhelmina-
jumping in with both
claws,running with it.
oh,that reminds me. here are my notes
on the features and the tahiti shoot.
make sure wilhelmina incorporates them.
????
after all,everything i do here
is in service of daniel's vision.
well,thank you very much,wilhelmina.
i will tell him you said that.
all right,sheila. the
victoria's secret shoot-
we have two double-page
spreads in november. go.
okay. the concept is "what is sexy?"
adriana and alessandra are booked,
and we've put a pin in
st. barths or coney island,
depending on the budget.
and who's shooting? peter?
i slept with peter. trust
me,he doesn't know what sexy is.
i was thinking warren.
he made kate moss look
like a man. get owen.
done. by the way...
i'm wearing the "very sexy"
push-up bra they sent over.
i've never felt hotter.
save the ass kissing
for the clients,sheila.
all right,features.
i'm moving the london
designers to the front.
tell health and fitness they
get six pages instead of eight,
and i'm still not happy
with european getaways.
congratulations,phillip. you've
managed to make paris boring.
get me a new draft
by the end of the day.
all right,people,gear up
for the natural disasters shoot today,
so sparkle and dazzle.
mm.
it's beautiful,isn't it?
mm. our best october yet.you've outdone
mm. and for what?
this magazine will never be mine.
claire owns "mode," and
she'll never give it up.
who cares? in a few weeks,
you'll be marrying old man liver spots
and all the rest of meade publications
will be yours. mm. if she
doesn't screw that up for me,too.
she's out there somewhere.
i just have to make sure
she does not make any
contact with bradford
before i get that ring on my finger. mm.
where are you,you gin-soaked hag?
come out,come out,wherever you are.
okay,the victoria's
secret stuff's good to go.
ooh. ooh. the leopard print baby doll.
hello,mrs. matt damon.
are you doing that "mrs.
matt damon" thing again?
i'd like to give him a "bourne ultimatum."
listen,do you have the test shots
for the natural disasters
makeover shoot today?
i want to show 'em to daniel.
right here. oh,amazing. tse
women have lost everything.
wilhelmina thinks a
mani-pedi and a new weave
is gonna change their lives. oh,and
who said fashion doesn't care?
still on for lunch? that was lunch. i
have to go. gotta meet my dad's lawyer.
gotta do some grocery shopping.
gotta get a sandwich to
the hospital for daniel
because they're serving
fish,and he hates it.
then i gotta be back here for the photo shoot
at 3:00. betty,you can't keep going at this pace.
i'm fine. no,you're not,look at you.
you're rushing around after
everybody else. what about you?
have you even called henry? it's
been three weeks. oh,christina,please.
look,i don't have time
to think about henry,
not with santos and daniel and alexis
and-and my dad still stuck in mexico.
i don't have time to worry
about little boyfriend problems,
which isn't even a problem
because he's not here.
he's in tucson with
his pregnant girlfriend.
end of story. but m-maybe
the baby's not his.
and maybe it is,
and the best thing that i
can do to take care of myself
is to not think about him at
all. betty,i just don't want you-
christina,enough! i cannot let
myself be distracted by henry.
i need to look straight ahead. (thu
oh,betty.
love hurts
±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
æ¬ãû ugly betty
µú2¼¾µú1¼¯
-=ææàãğü×öä»×é=-
·­òë£º¸öèëid
ğ£¶ô£º¸öèëid
ê±¼äöá£ºğ¡èı
ææàãğü×öä»×é
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- »¶ó­¼óèë
so this is where you grew up?
this is it
- the house of lies.
mother!
if that is her real name.
amanda?
wh-what are you doing out here
in the middle of the afternoon?
and overweight?
who's overweight? amanda!
hi,kitten. you didn't call.
what are you doing here?
i waed to talk to you both now,
while i've got my nerve.
i don't think you two have
been very honest with me.
what are you talking about?
we tell you everything.
actually,i think there's
one very big secret
you haven't told me about.
what secrets? we don't have
any secrets in this house. no.
yoo-hoo! did someone forget about us?
we were getting lonely.
uh,this is our
daughter a-a-amanda
and her friend marc,
and this is,um,bob and elaine klein.
they're our new,uh,internet friends.
it's a very funny story.
see,they came over to play tennis.
and wouldn't you know
it,the sprinklers went off?
that's right. that's right. it was...
they're just waiting
for their clothes to dry.
you know what?
we're,uh,we're gonna go wait.
for our clothes to dry.
now what's all this
crazy talk about secrets?
you know what? i
- i can't do this. never mind.
- amanda.
- i can't.
- you have to.
- i can't!
amanda found a birth certificate
that said that fey sommers
was her real mother.
ugh. this is taking forever.
i just have so much to do
today. you don't understand.
daniel cannot eat hospital fish.
okay,ms. suarez.
uh,it doesn't appear
to be a concussion...
see?
but i am a tad concerned
about your heart rate
and blood pressure.
really? he said a "tad."
a tad isn't serious,right?
could be nothing,could
be stress related.
now are you under lot of
pressure right now? yes.
no. no.
well,you might want to think
about slowing down a bit.
now leave that patch on
until the swelling's gone,
and i'll be back in a minute with a
prescription. okay. thank you very much,doctor.
well,i hope you take
his warning seriously
and maybe start to slow down just a little bit
- oh,no! it's 12:00! i'm late for my dad's lawyer.
will you stay for the prescription?
please,please,please,please,please.
and tell them i'll be there
on time for the photo shoot.
excuse me!
we're so sorry we never told you,honey.
fey never wanted you to know.
i can't believe this.
i'm adopted.
how?
well,when your father
worked for fey,you know,
handling her accounts,she
found out she was pregnant.
she wouldn't even tell
us who the father was.
honey,all fey ever wanted was a career.
she knew she could never
give you the love you needed.
and since we couldn't have kids on our
own... your father has lethargic sperm.
is that really an important
part of the story,rosemary?
so you've been lying
to me all these years?
i'm not here. just
looking for some more wine.
amanda,adopted or not,
- weoved you from the moment we held you in our arms.
-  you're still our little girl.
no,i'm not! i'm fey's and
some guy we don't even know.
i don't think i'll ever be able
to trust you two ever again!
it was really nice seeing you again.
your home is beautiful.
hey.
hey! you leave my sister alone.
you want a photo of a meade in trouble?
here i am,you son of a bitch!
mr. meade,this is i.c.u.
any change at all today?
her vitals are the same.
mr. meade,are you sure you
don't want to go in and see her?
it just seems like you want to.
you come this far every day,
and you look at her through the window.
i can't. no,i think,um,i
need my medication.
it's been four hours.
you know,you go through life
thinking you're one person,
and then boom,just like
that,the slate is wiped clean.
i mean,who am i?
- you are fey sommers' daughter.
- yeah,but what does that even mean?
she's just a woman who
walked by my desk for years,
and she never even looked
at me,and now she's gone.
maybe if we can find out
who your real father is...
how? he could be anybody.
true. your mother was
a hoochie in a bob.
mm.
if bradford is my father,
that makes daniel my brother...
who i slept with... a lot,
and that's the kind of
dirty that don't wash clean.
okay,first of all,he'd
be your half brother.
already a little better,right?
and second,i gotta say,kinda hot.
it's incest.
okay,before you get all
"flowers in the attic" on me,
let's first find out if
bradford really is your dad.
and how are we gonna do that?
invite him to father's day brunch
and see if he shows up?
no,sarcasma. three words-d.n.a.
dad,i'm so sorry.
i was only ten minutes
late to the lawyer's office,
but he still wouldn't see me.
so i made another appointment.
mija,relax. i'm fine here.
although it wouldn't
kill your cheap aunt
to turn on the air conditioning every
now and then! well,are you eating enough?
are you taking your medication? oh!
oh,i'm sorry. no peripheral vision.
stop worrying about me.
it just kills me that i'm so far away.
i know.
but you'll be home
soon,so just have faith.
te quiero.
s? i mean,hello>
is this betty suarez? yeah.
this is lisa lapera,justin's
camp counselor.
i just wanted to let you
know,your nephew just took off.
what do you mean,he just took off?
apparently,the indian dream
catchers we were making
were "amateurish" and
"culturally insensitive."
he threw a hissy fit and
said he was going home,
and i'm not sure,but i think
he stole a bottle of glitter.
and we need that back
or a check for $1.99.
justin wouldn't...
hello?
ugh.
this is not happening.
no!
damn,the hooker had her baby kidnapped,
now she has tetanus?
that's a pretty bad monday.
okay,december 15th is
the latest we can go
with the new wedding date.
otherwise people try to combine
your wedding gift with
your christmas gift,
and that is not gonna happen.
you sure you wanna wait till december?
i mean,didn't this teach us anything?
gotta live for today.
what are you trying to say?
let's elope.
elope? yeah.
oh. no,seriously,you,me,we'll
grab justin.
we'll go down to city hall this weekend.
besides,my dad would die if
he doesn't get to give me away.
i guess it would be pretty rough...
to miss you walking down the
aisle in your wedding dress.
you think it's all right
that i'm wearing white,right?
why don't you show me the dress?
no way! that is bad luck!
i just got shot. how much
worse can my luck get?
come on,mama.
oh... dad-ford!
i mean,bradford.
i mean,mr. meade!
i sufferrom severe cotton mouth.
would you mind licking this for me?
i beg your pardon?
lick this for me.
amanda,you don't have
to lick these. see?
thank you,betty. you're welcome.
hey,what's different about you?
did you ge your hair cut?
i'm wearing an eye patch.
you didn't always have that?
those are pink gerber daisies.
hey,look at that! they're for you.
i think they came a few weeks ago.
well,why didn't you give them
to me? you know what,betty?
i have had a lot on my
mind these last few weeks.
amanda! it might be hard to believe,
but pretty girls have problems,too.
thinking of you
all right, ladies of natural disasters,
and do say "ladies" and not "victims,"
because there isn't a victim among you.
you've all survived horrible tragedies
and now "mode" is going
to make you beautiful.
sheila,talk to me.
okay,just like on
the storyboards--
we're gonna show them
at their absolute worst--
ravaged by hurricanes, floods,fires...
sad,sad,sad.
and then we do the "afters."
happy,sexy,blown out. i love it.
we change their lives and,uh,
showcase the fall collections.
mm-hmm. just make sure the
skinny ones are up front.
(sheila) "famine," makeup. now.
bless your heart.
what disaster are you, honey? mudslide?
what?
no,i'm not a victim. i'm fine.
i just need some food. my
blood sugar's a little low.
uh-huh. looking good,"flood."
excuse me, are there any more bagels?
i don't see any more bagels. uh,no!
you can have mine.
no,no,no,no,no.
i'm not gonna take a bagel from
"famine." you need to eat,too.
give me sofi of th
it's just that there is nobody here
who cares about filling the inside.
they only care about fixing the outside!
what's stumpy up to now?
you know what? this concealer here,
this isn't gonna change the fact
that she doesn't have a house!
and--and this,
this eyeliner,
this isn't gonna bring back
the people that you loved!
these women have lost everything!
and there is not enough styling gel
in here to change that!
you know what? she's right.
we don't have enough styling gel.
oh,excuse me,mr. meade!
hi,i have some mail here for you.
ow!
oh,my god,a paper cut!
here,let me swab you.
no,thank you.
- ????
hit me again.
you sure? it's your third one.
i know my limit. this
time chili cheese fries.
betty?
daniel?
why aren't you in the hospital?
well,i had a few... dozen
calls about the photo shoot.
i thought you might need a friend.
fry?
i was thinking with the leopard,
we could add
this belt-- n!
i don't have the energy
to say "no" anymore.
what about this boa?
n!
what about this
brooch? we can--
why don't you just
stick the pin in my eye?
what is the matter with you people?
we might as well be
publishing "field & stream"
because apparently no one in this room
knows a thing about fashion!
(justin whispers) loose the belt.
is it just me,
or does anyone else see
the little fashion elf?
i'm sorry. i just think it's too busy.
like coco chanel always says,
"when accessorizing"...
"always take off..."
"the last thing you put on."
you've got the gift.
phone call!
i'm in the middle of a
run-through. take a message.
it's "schmaire schmeade."
(lowers voice) claire
meade? (lowers voice) yes.
(normal voice) everyone out!
(normal voice) go,go. get.
get out of here. go. go. go.
get out! ace the call.
what? how? i don't know. figure it out.
triangulate the signal.
hello,is this no one's most wanted?
oh,bite me,wilhelmina.
i wanna talk to you about bradford.
you mean my fianc?
you're not in love with him.
oh,claire, you're so wrong.
i'm madly in love with
him. as a matter of fact,
i'm staring at our wedding
invitations as we speak.
do you love him more than "mode"?
i know the magazine is what
you've wanted all along.
and i'm the only person
who can give it to you.
keep talking.
leave bradford,and i will
sign "mode" over to you.
"wilhelmina slater--
editor-in-chief."
are you salivating yet?
no.
meet me at the bow bridge in
central park tonight at 8:00.
i'll be dressed as a nun.
or a cat. i haven't decided yet.
have the documents ready,
and i will sign "mode" over to you.
8:00.
i couldn't do it.
i couldn't triangulate the signal.
i don't even know what triangulate
means! don't worry,marc.
i think all our problems
will be taken care of.
how'd you find me?
it's no secret
you turn to potatoes in times of need.
it helps.
look,daniel, i'm really sorry
if i screwed up the photo shoot.
i just--i think this
whole thing with henry--
it finally got to me.
and i shouldn't have let it.
after everything that's
happened to my family
and to you...
he's just a guy,right?
he's a guy you loved.
you know what? i have an idea.
go back the office.
there are some things you're
gonna need to get for tonight.
what's tonight?
we're going to a funeral.
sir?
i don't mean to disturb you.
may i speak to you privately?
it's about wilhelmina. what about her?
as you know,i'm privy to
many of her conversations,
both professional... and personal.
she has issues with you.
issues?
ear hair.
i didn't realize i had any.
perhaps others have tried to tell you,
but you couldn't hear
through all the ear hair.
she would never, in a million years,
bring this up.
so i thought,as someone
rooting for the relationship,
i might spare you
both the embarrassment.
may i clip you,sir?
never send a girl to do a woman's job.
mm.
ah.
don't you think this
is a little weird...
and illegal?
yeah, it's both those things.
it's also symbolic. henry's gone.
if you're gonna move on,
you have to put him to rest, right?
okay, i just hit something soft!
ah! oh,i'm sorry.
are you okay?  all
right, what are you gonna bury first?
um,well...
i could start with these.
this is from our first meal together.
sushi.
it was good... getting to know him.
the raw eel? not so much.
low sodium.
he was always looking out for me.
man,you brought a lot of stuff.
uh,we may need a bigger hole.
yo,how you doing in there?
okay,you ready?
damn.
you like it? i was
gonna take it in a bit,
maybe cut the top a little bit lower.
no,no,no,don't do anything.
don't touch it. it's beautiful.
just like you.
okay,so now you've seen the dress.
papi... i want something from you.
oh,come on,baby,you know
what the doctor said.
i need at least a month.
(laughs) no,not that.
i wanna hear your vows.
now?
i knew it.
i knew you didn't write them!
you had two months!
you are so not seeing
the honeymoon lingerieow.
give me my jeans.
reach into the back pocket. go ahead.
you feel stupid?
a little bit.
mm-hmm.
say your prayers,bitch.
bradford!
i knew i could count on you
working late on thursdays.
we don't have much time.
wilhelmina is in the park.
is she?
you ain't wilhelmina slater. no,i'm
not even sure what i'm doing here
or why i'm wearing this outfit.
please don't hurt me. (pants)
did you really think
i'd fall for your offer?
i knew you'd never take "mode"
away from your own children.
but that's all right.
i may not have "mode,"
but very soon i will
have everything else,
including your husband.
oh...
listen to me go on and on.
i'm so rude. sit down. you're the guest.
let me,uh, fix you a drink.
though you'll probably
have to down it quickly,
because the police will be
here in,um... three minutes.
i only need one.
and this is the crown he
gave me at the middle ages.
(snores) are you sleeping?
no.
(clears throat) that
was a silent prayer.
i was just...
so moved by the paper clips he gave you.
this is good-bye for him and you.
any final words?
okay,well...
here...
near the place where
it all came to an end,
lies the remnants of a relationship
that almost, but never quite was.
"it started good, really good.
"and then it got bad...
"mainly 'cause of me.
"i took her for granted,
"never realizing she
was everything i needed.
"she was always there...
right in front of me."
i hoped for so much.
i had a fantasy.
we were together.
we were building a life.
"it took me ten years...
"but i'm glad i finally
came to my senses...
before the most special
thing in my life..."
was gone...
for good.
* comfort is my solitude i embrace *
i loved you,henry.
"i love you,hilda."
* i will rise from my sorrow
* i wilmyrise froorrow *
how do you feel?
i don't know. uh,better,i guess.
maybe now i can start fresh.
what's that? are you in pain?
no,i
just--i...
i need a fresh start,too.
you okay?
not really.
there's something i didn't tell you.
the reason we were in the accident...
why my sister is in the coma...
i was high.
she was rushing me
to the rehab hospital.
it was my fault.
you know,i don't know if i'm ever...
gonna be able to get over the guilt.
but i can get over these.
good-bye,henry.
oh,it was horrible!
the next thing i know,
sister mary gang member
threw me to the ground
and took my wallet. marc,i
am in serious trouble.
you? i don't think i'll
ever be able to watch
"the sound of music" again!
claire's not going away easily.
and apparently she's got friends.
i need protection.
hi.
it's me...
daniel.
sorry i didn't come by... sooner.
i just didn't think i could
handle seeing you like this.
you were always the rock, right?
the strong one.
oh,my god!
i'm so sorry,alexis.
this should be me.
(strained voice) oh,i'm thirsty.
nurse! nurse!
alexis,can you hear me?
yeah,daniel, i can hear you.
alexis,i...
i can't believe this.
why do you keep calling me alexis?
what?
it's me.
alex.
hi.
so i heard there was
a little fashion elf
spreading the word of coco
chanel around "mode" today.
i'm sorry,aunt betty. i had to get away.
that's okay.
but as far as
tomorrow goes--
i know,back to camp.
actually,i think you were
meant for greater things
than macaroni necklaces,justin,
so i talked to daniel,
and it looks like we're gonna
need an intern around the office
for the next couple of
weeks before school starts.
oh,my god! oh,my god!
are you serious?
you deserve it.
thank you. thank you.
i can't believe you wrote this.
it is so beautiful.
what,did you think i
was gonna stand up there
in front of everybody and just wing it?
(giggles) kinda.
hey,tomorrow,let's open
up some of these presents.
let's see who's cheaper,
your family or my family.
look,babe...
we can't stay in here forever.
i think i gotta go.
no. no,no,no.
not yet,okay?
we just need one more day. shh.
just wait one more day.
it's gonna be okay.
oh.
hey,uh,i know you
probably don't want to,
but any chance you wanna come down
and help me and justin make dinner?
* together under
* lonesome silver stars
he's gone,betty.
s * theilence spoke for us
that's the first time
i've said that out loud.
* as i remember
* in a golden dream
oh,god,he's gone.
* there's a veil of tears between us *
yeah. he's gone.
* and many years
* may keep us apart
* but i remember
* in a golden dream
ææàãğü×öä»×é
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- »¶ó­¼óèë