Papi, I am so excited about
our Christmas dinner tonight.
I've been telling Matt all about
Your traditional homemade tamales
How do these look?
What is that supposed to be?
Potato latkes swimming in oil.
Apparently, grandpa wants me
to be a house by new year's.
Ugh, what's that smell, papi?
Oh! That's even worse.
Since when do you make
potato latkes?
Since I'm inviting someone
to join us tonight,
And I think she'd appreciate it
if we celebrated
Christmas and Hanukkah.
Someone?
She?
Hanukkah?
Well, there may be
a certain Jewish lady
I'd like to get to know better.
What?
After a long distance relationship,
It was nice to meet someone
in the neighborhood.
And she's excited to be
having dinner with a councilman.
Oh...  yeah. Archie's really busy, so...
I just called him. He's coming.
Oh, great.
Yay!
Now Archie and Matt can finally
get to know each other,
And then we can double-date.
Nope. Nope, I'm not gonna do
that thing that I always do,
Which is
get way ahead of myself
And start projecting into the future.
Could you project into this afternoon
And have him bring drinks?
Turns out,
Cooking Christmas and Hanukkah
dinner is quite a schlep.
I'd help, but I have model U.N.
Until 7:00. I'm Sweden.
That's great, mijo.
Come home when you can.
See if you can get us a discount
On a Volvo.
As Sweden,
you get a lot of that.
Oh, Papi, don't worry.
I promise I will start helping
you as soon as I get home.
Me, too.
No breakfast?
No. Actually, I'm feeling
kind of queasy today.
Oh, that's weird. Me, too.
Really?
I hope we're not
coming down with something.
All right, I'm off to work.
Love you all.
Have a good day.
Okay, bye.
Bobby!
Chipmunk!
Hey, hon, you know you're gonna
get over your crush on me
One day, right?
You're so funny. Bye.
See ya. Have a good day.
Bobby.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I came--
No! I know exactly what you're
doing here and I don't like it.
What happened between us--
That cannot happen again, okay?
I came to give Justin
a ride to school, okay?
He's got a bulky project.
He does not have
a bulky project.
Oh, thanks so much, Bobby.
Who knew that
Nobel prize winners and what
they wore could be so heavy?
Hey, Mr. Suarez.
Hey, Bobby. I was just about
to put up the manger.
Do you like our baby Jesus?
We've had him since someone
stole our original 14 years ago.
I had nothing
to do with that, I swear.
Can we go?
Jimmy Carter's cardigan
just slipped off the hanger.
Let me give you a hand with that.
Thank you.
It's official!
Jumpsuits are back... again!
Thank or curse
Former "Mode" evil queen
Wilhelmina Slater,
Who started the trend
after being spotted about town
In other news, Connor Owens,
Former "Mode" finance-wiz-
turned-caged-con man
Is behind bars for
stealing the Meade fortune.
Officials are searching
for the missing monies.
Let's hope enough of it
turns up to buy Willie a belt.
After all, Ms. Slater,
A waist is a terrible thing to waste.
What was she thinking?
I've seen actual blueberries
look less round.
I think
it's quite flattering.
Oh, Marc, she's gone.
You don't have to
defend her anymore.
Mom, leave him alone.
He's just working through
a little Stockholm syndrome.
She was
the Symbionese Liberation Army
To my Patty Hearst.
She even bought me a beret.
Speaking of accessories,
the ascot's really working.
You think so?
Trust me.
Mom, we really need to move
on a new creative director.
I don't like how Hartley's
dragging his heels
On that list of candidates I gave him.
He's considering a few other ideas
That are a little more...
"outside the box."
Don't worry about it.
My mom's letting her soulless
new boyfriend call the shots.
That seems like good, solid
business sense to me, hmm?
Look, Daniel.
It's Cal's money that's
keeping this company alive.
And if you'll recall,
Our money is gone
because of your friend.
God, I hope he rots in jail.
That traitor deserves
whatever he gets.
How on earth did you
manage to swing
Daily conjugal visits?
Well, having
a senator as a father
Certainly has its perks.
Willie, as fun as this is,
We didn't have you
turn me in for nothing.
I know you want to be
back at "Mode,"
So you do your part,
I'll do mine,
And we'll have you back there in no time.
Well, I hope it takes longer than that.
These past three weeks
have been heaven...
aside from my tailoring bill.
You have got to stop literally
ripping my clothes off.
I can't afford to be caught
sneaking out again
In one of your
ridiculous jumpsuits.
It's a miracle
I could pass it off as a trend.
You know,
some idiots will wear anything.
How long do we have to keep
hiding from her?
Well, until we're
less obviously happy.
Hmm, that could take awhile.
I know. I love our new thing--
No labels, no expectations,
just living in the moment.
Oh, by the way, will you bring
drinks to dinner tonight?
Something fancy. My dad's trying
to impress a new lady friend.
Some guys never stop
trying too hard.
You wanna see me break dance?
Not now.
But no expectations.
What are you thinking about?
You're glowing.
Nothing.
I guess you make me glow.
Mrs. Meade!
You'll be landing at
The Sioux Falls
regional airport at 2:35.
I'm sorry
I didn't book it sooner,
But those dopes
at the international terminal
Kept telling me
I was calling the wrong place.
Amanda, am I doing
the right thing,
Chasing after my lost son?
I mean, what if
He has a terrible life
because I gave him up?
What if he doesn't want to know me?
What--what if he hates me?
Mrs. Meade, you're putting way
too much pressure on my hand.
Look, you just have to
show up and see him.
And you'll know what to do next.
Thank you, Amanda.
But not looking like that.
You're going to South Dakota.
You have to blend in.
Less "money,"
and more "food stamp."
Come on. We're gonna
give you a make-under.
I've got the silver fox on the move.
Oh, the decorations
are so beautiful.
Yeah.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah. I don't know why
I'm so emotional these days.
Hi, welcome to
Macy's believe station.
For every letter mailed to Santa,
Macy's will donate $1--
Up to $1 million--
To the Make-A-Wish Foundation.
That is so nice!
That's great.
Now I'm gonna ask Santa
To make sure that one day every
child is happy and healthy.
Sure. And I always ask
for world peace.
And what did you ask Santa for?
Well, I can't tell you. Then I won't get it.
Your wife's very superstitious.
Oh, she's not--
I'm not his wife.
Wow! January Jones
for our March cover--
That's exciting!
Ugh! Enough "Sad Men."
Isn't she a little played out?
I love her.
I love her, too.
You know, Marc, it's okay.
You can totally disagree with
Daniel and he doesn't hit you
Or psychically shame you in any way.
It's confusing.
By the way,
your tie is really wide.
Yeah, it's, uh...it's an ascot.
We're playing.
You realize that's, uh,
kind of my bagel you're eating?
I'm sorry.
I've been feeling sick all
morning, and now I'm starving.
You can have it.
I'll go get my own.
Hi, honey.
Hello.
Uh, Daniel, Marc,
I would like you to meet
Denise Ludwig,
our new creative director.
Denise, this is Daniel meade,
our editor-in-chief.
Hey, it is great to meet you.
Are you ready to
kick this thing in the ass?
Uh, Denise here
was head of development
For White Line pictures.
This little lady is gonna bring
a touch of tinseltown magic.
And you sure as hell could use it.
I'm here to commercialize your message,
Just like I did for White Line.
I was the one that took them
from yawn-fest indie darlings
To back-to-back blockbuster
tent poles.
I get back-to-back tent poles
just thinking about it.
I'm kidding. You can't sue me.
Actually, you can try. I'd like to see that.
Cal, we need to talk
for a minute.
Uh, why don't I show you
the tanning bed?
Solid.
Okay.
What are you trying to pull?
My mother and I submitted
A list of top candidates
in the business.
You hire someone
not even in the business
Without discussing it with us?
Well, I'll discuss it with your mom
When she gets into bed tonight.
And with regard to
your problems with Denise--
My money, my choice.
Please.
You shouldn't be standing
in your condition.
No, I'm not, uh...
No breakfast?
No. Actually, I'm
feeling kind of queasy today.
Daniel uh, you do know
you're eating my bagel.
I've been feeling so sick
all day, and now I'm starving.
I love our new thing.
What are you thinking about?
You're glowing.
No labels, no expectations,
just living in the moment.
Pregnant.
Sync by ReHelen
Corrected by Lawman666
www.addic7ed.com
Excuse me.
Hi. Um...can you tell me
where the, uh...
Um, you know what? Never mind.
I probably don't need it.
It's all in my head.
How'd you know?
Darling, I know that look.
I didn't work 25 years
At the Barnard Health Services
for nothing.
Just make sure
You wait the full three minutes
for a plus or a minus sign.
And the saltines
and the ginger ale?
Sodas and crackers--
Aisle four and aisle five.
Thank you.
Hi. I need a Be-Shure
and a non-see-through bag.
I'm a little late.
Pay at the front.
Thanks. Oh, saltines
and ginger ale?
Crackers and sodas--
Aisle five and aisle four.
And, honey, relax.
Maybe you aren't.
I don't think so. This is
the one test I never fail.
Unbelievable.
So how do you want to take down
Miss Cecil B. Female?
Dig dirt? Blackmail?
Twitter backlash? How do you want
to play this?
You know what? I don't want
to play this at all.
Denise isn't the real problem,
Hartley is.
As soon as the FBI finds out
where Connor hid the money,
We'll buy him out, fire Denise.
No need for crazy schemes.
It's like I'm in a new land
Where the customs are so strange.
She's here.
Daniel.
Marc.
Willie, I--
I'm really not interested.
Okay.
Daniel, admit it. You need me.
You'll never get that money
from Connor unless I help you,
And I won't help you unless I'm reinstated
In my old position first.
Actually, Willie, I don't need you.
The FBI is locating the money for us.
The FBI?  Cute.
And your replacement started today.
All right, then.
I want every stick out.
Yes, ma'am.
You'll be better off without me.
Clearly I'm no longer
The trendsetting icon I used to be.
Nice jumpsuits, ladies.
Call me if you need me.
Mija! My help has arrived.
I'll be right down in a minute.
I gotta get in there.
Okay, hold on just one second.
Finishing up.
Betty, seriously.
Come on, already.
Coming!
I gotta pee.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Excuse me.
I need a bandage.
Okay, one second.
When did you get home?
I've been here.
What?
Why are you two still up here?
I need your help.
And that pot of tzimmes is not gonna make itself.
Just a minute. Papi, I gotta pee.
Oh, yeah, me, too.
You were just in here.
Papi.
Okay.
No, I gotta pee.
Hilda! So do I!
I am older!
That hurt!
Hilda, come on.
Seriously, how long does it
take you to pee?
Come on! Seriously.
I gotta get in there!
Okay. All right. All right.
Betty, I need to talk to you.
Not now.
Betty.
Oh, shoot.
Betty,
I need to talk to you.
It's important.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Betty, seriously,
I gotta talk to you.
Coming!
Coming.
Betty?
Betty, s--
I'm pregnant.
What? I'm pregnant.
What?
Girls, downstairs right now!
There you are.
Can you get the brisket
out of the oven, please?
So...
you got burned?
What? No. I didn't get...
yeah, I got burned.
Of course I was being careful.
Why? Weren't you being careful?
Yeah, well, not as careful
as I should have been. Ow!
Burned twice?
That's what happens when you
don't wear an oven mitt.
Hey.
This is the chair Willie got me
When I told her the one I had
was comfortable.
This mark here--
I was injecting her with botox
And I missed and hit a vein
in her forehead.
She ripped the needle
out of my hand,
Threatened to plunge it
into my eye
And said if it weren't
for my clogged pores,
My tiny brain would have
seeped out long ago.
Good riddance, huh?
Yeah.
Good riddance.
Still waiting on that order, Tyler.
Coming up.
All right.
You're not from around here.
Wh-what--what gave me away?
You have all your teeth.
Ah.  Yeah.
What can I get you?
Much as I'd love
to say scotch rocks,
I'll just go with
a cranberry and soda.
Ah, you, too, huh?
I used to pound pretty hard
in college myself.
You went to college.
I mean, you just seem so young.
Community college.
Oh.
A couple classes, you know.
Learned enough to realize
that a few more shots,
And it would all go south pretty fast.
It's genetic, I guess.
That's what I hear.
Can I get you some beer nuts?
That would be lovely.
So what do we do now?
I don't know.
You can cube cheese.
Ooh. I'll get that.
Oh, my God. I don't believe it.Are you gonna tell Matt?
Oh, my God. This is crazy. Are you gonna tell Archie?
I don't know!
Hilda, what am I gonna do?
I can't have a baby.
I know!
I mean, I've thought about it.
You know, maybe, someday,
but not now.
And my career, finally...
and Papi.
What are we gonna tell papi?
Nothing tonight. Okay, we don't
tell anybody anything tonight.
Let's just get through dinner.
But what if--
Papi is not gonna find out,
'Cause we're not gonna
say anything, Betty,
And we are
the only ones who know.
Hilda, Betty, this is Jean.
She works at the drugstore.
Hi.
What beautiful daughters
you have.
I'm surprised I've never seen
either of them
In the neighborhood before.
Are you well?
Yeah, thanks.
Yes, thank you for asking.
Are you positive?
Okay.
Where can I put my apple cake?
I'll take it.
I'll get that.
Hey. We both brought booze.
Just call us your sugar daddies!
Okay.
Phone call
from "Mode" magazine.
That's Daniel.
He can wait.
No, go. Go.
You have to make him believe I'm
the only route to that money.
Convince him you still love me,
Just like you convinced me
two minutes ago.
Go.
Yes.
Daniel, how sweet of you to call.
I don't believe it's gone,
you lying, son of a--
Oh, it's not gone. Not that
you're ever gonna see it again.
That money is mine.
You want to talk about mine and yours?
Let's talk about Molly.
She was mine
until you stole her from me.
And in a way, you stole Willie
from me, too.
Willie? Connor, what the hell
are you talking about?
I loved her. I wanted
to give her everything.
She chose you and your company
over me.
You're never getting
that money back, Daniel.
You've got enough
from me already.
You Marc St. James?
Oh. Uh, there must be a mistake.
This is supposed to go to Ms. Slater's.
She said she wanted you to have it.
Anyway... my niece made it,
And I thought it might be nice
to light alongside the tree.
Absolutely.
That is exactly the spirit
In which I whipped up these
multicultural holiday cocktails.
I present to you
mulled kosher wine.
Salud.
Oh. Ugh. This is terrible.
Is it okay if we have beer?
Yeah, that stuff is gross.
Okay, I got it. Who wants a beer? Matt? Betty?
Sure.
Oh, no, thank you.
Oh, yeah, we got it. Come on.
How could you turn down a beer?
I don't like beer.
I don't care. Passing on a drink
is a rookie mistake.
It's the first thing that makes
everyone think you're pregnant.
Well, I'm sorry. I've--I've
never hidden a pregnancy before.
Well, you need to get good
at it, and fast.
If somebody offers you a drink,
you take it,
You put your tongue in the top
and then you don't drink. Duh!
Oh, right. Duh. I don't know
why I didn't know that.
Girls, where are you?
Okay, here we are. Cerveza?
Here you go. Yum, beer.
But you don't like beer.
Sure, I do.
Oh, God. Here.
Let me help you with that.
I told you to act like
you wanted a drink,
Not like you were drunk.
Hilda, I'm sorry. I'm nervous.
Papi's date is the woman
I bought my pregnancy test from.
Wait. She's who I bought
my pregnancy test from today.
I could barely get home fast enough.
What? You took your test today, upstairs?
Yeah, I tried, but Papi knocked.
I had to stop halfway through.
Well, when you knocked,
I had to stop.
I freaked out. I dropped my test.
I dropped my test.
I had to sneak back in, pick it up off the floor.
I picked mine up off the floor.
Wait. Did we check the same test?
I don't know. I threw mine in the garbage.
I threw mine in the garbage!
Oh, here they come.
Where you going?
Um, I'm cold.
Oh, yeah, grabbing a sweater.
Scotch and soda, whiskey neat,
seven and seven.
Thanks.
Seems like a strange job
for you to take.
Temptation all around.
Well, if they're paying,
I'm working.
You know, here,
the post office, wherever.
Uh, my mom had to quit her job
a couple years ago, so...
I'm sorry. Is she all right?
Yeah. She's a fighter.
I'm sorry. Um, you're supposed
to be here on vacation,
Not listening to my troubles.
So what have you seen so far?
Nothing. I just got here.
Well, we got more
than Mount Rushmore.
We got the Badlands,
Crazy Horse Memorial
And a whole bunch of meth labs.
That sounds great.
Uh, no,
not--not--not the meth labs.
That was a joke.
So, um, if you want,
I can tell you some cool places
to check out.
I would like that very much.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're very kind.
Negative! One is negative!
Aah! Oh, thank God.
And positive.
Oh, God. I hope it's not me.
So you're saying you want it to be me.
No, I just mean that it's gonna be so much easier
For you to tell Archie
than for me to tell Matt.
Not... really.
What do you mean?
Hilda, what are you saying?
Exactly what you're thinking.
Oh, my God!
It's not Archie's?
Well...
whose would it be?
Well, that's what--
Oh, sorry. Sorry. It wasn't...
Oh, my God. Are you pregnant?
Pregnant?
Like pregnant pregnant?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I'm gonna leave you two alone.
I might not be.
See, uh, Hilda took
a test and I took a test,
And it got mixed up, and we
don't know whose is whose.
But one of us isn't pregnant.
One of us is.
We just don't know which.
Whoa.
I didn't mean for this
to happen. Things were so good--
Are so good--between us,
and this is not anything
That either one of us
should be thinking about.
Trust me. I know that.
I hope it's us.
What?
I kind of want it to be us.
I know. I know it... isn't
something that we planned,
And it's probably--
Okay, okay, definitely--
It definitely is not
the exact right time,
But a baby, with you...
how could that be bad?
Because. Just, uh, because.
Betty, listen. Look, I'm the guy
Who can never pick the right
thing for my life.
Well, maybe the right thing
finally picked me.
Look, Betty. Betty,
whatever problems we have,
We can work it out.
No, Matt. I don't want to work it out.
I don't want to have a baby
right now.
I mean,
I can't have a baby at all.
I-I can't be pregnant right now.
Okay. Okay. Well, maybe you're not.
I'll go pick us up another test.
How? Hilda and I have stalled dinner a hundred times.
There's no way my dad is letting you out of the house.
Don't worry. I'll be subtle.
Finally. Come. Sit.
You've been gone so long, your beer is warm.
I'll get more.
Yeah, we--we sure could use them.
Uh, Hilda, I think that's mine.
Is it?
Yeah, I'm sitting right there.
Who else's would it be?
Hey, anybody want a baby?
I got this for you. It's not
because I stole the last one.
Okay, I stole the last one.
All right. That was very thoughtful.
Uh, Jean, Archie,
this is, uh, Bobby.
Hey, Bobby. How are you?
Hey. How you doing?
Good.
Bobby?
It's Bobby!
Bobby in the house! Hey!
Yay! Happy Christmas!
Chipmunk--She's still got
a crush on me.
It's so cute. It's okay.
Oh, damn it, Marc. I just got
off the phone with the FBI.
They really think the money is gone,
But Connor admitted
he knows where it is.
He just won't tell me where.
This ascot is making my neck sweat.
We're experimenting. It's a process. Here.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I mean, if I don't figure
this out,
I'm gonna lose my own magazine
to my mother,
Her stupid boyfriend
and Malibu Barbie.
Technically, the brunette
was Skipper.
Okay, Marc.
Daniel, I think that it's time
To call Willie.
No. No, absolutely not.
Besides, she broke Connor's heart.
There's no way he's gonna
give her the money.
I'm not so sure. You see,
Once you've known Willie,
No matter how terrible she was to you,
You never really get over her.
She will make you do things
you swore you'd never do.
I've done it.
Connor will do it.
And you'll do it, too.
And I'll tell you why.
Because she's Willie,
And we're just men.
Wow! It's like you never saw
a wing before.
Well...
Look, it was nice meeting you,
But I'm getting out of here.
My shift is up, so...
I should be going, too.
Take care and, um, give my best
to your mother.
Sure.
She's lucky to have you.
Okay.
Ready?
Beautiful!
Okay, let's all go inside
and warm up.
Come on.
Bobby? You want to join us?
Oh, no. I think he's got other
things he's gotta do, right?
No, not really. Yeah.
All right, welcome.
Oh, thank you. Oh!
Um, I think you're in my spot.
Oh, I didn't know it was yours.
Hey. I thought you were
bringing beer.
They were out.
Well, you know how it is with
the holidays and alcoholics.
That's true.
All that matters is,
we can finally sit down
To a nice meal.
Jean, please light the menorah.
Matt, let me help you with that coat.
Oh, no, Papi.
No, no, no. It's fine. I got it.
I'm gonna say the prayer in English.
I want everybody to understand.
Dear God... let go, already!
Dear God.
Excuse me.
It wasn't me. I swear.
oh, thank God!
Oh, thank God!
Right?
Yeah.
I mean, I'd be lying if I didn't
say I was a little disappointed.
But it's all for the best.
I was getting ahead of myself.
It's not the right time.
Not at all. Oh, my God.
I have to tell Hilda.
Yeah, but it's not that bad.
I mean, uh, she's practically
engaged to Archie, right?
Betty? What's going on?
Whatever it is, I support you.
Look, I'm not mad.
All clear.
Oh, thank you, god.
I was gonna kill myself.
Sorry, mija.
It's fine, Papi. I'm relieved, too.
Good.
Me, too.
She said it first.
Look, let's just all go downstairs
And try to have a nice,
traditional Christmas/Hanukkah.
Papi, can you just wait
before you--
Whew! False alarm!
Hey! All right!
Back soon. Sweater.
But you're already wearing
a s-sweater.
No, no, no, no, no. Come on.
Let's all go in
and start this dinner. Please.
Okay. Good. I'm starving.
Glad you're here.
Thank you.
I've been there, pal.
Well, you'll never guess what
I'm getting you for Kwanzaa.
Ugh. Hold on. Call waiting.
Yello?
Amanda, I did it.
I saw him. I talked to him.
And now I'm done.
So he knows who you are?
No.
And he's never going to.
Holy smoke!
That lady just left me,
like, 2 grand.
Someone thinks you're cute.
Here we go.
Jean, I'm so sorry
about your menorah.
Oh, it's fine.
Between the Long Island nieces
And the Brooklyn nephews,
I have handmade menorahs
Coming out of my tuchus.
Ah, it would have been nice
to light it, though.
Well, we could improvise
with votive candles.
No offense
to the blessed saints,
But around here, we got those
coming out of our tuchus.
Where are the candles?
I'll go look.
Here goes nothing.
Daniel, Marc.
What took you so long?
Hilda.
You know, I never got
into all the saint stuff, Betty.
Well, it--it never made sense
to me.
They all looked so happy
suffering.
But...
now I get it.
What I did with Bobby...
what I did to Archie...
I'm a bad person.
I-I want to suffer. I deserve it.
I-I wish that someone
would peel my skin off
Or drag me behind a bunch of horses
Or make me swallow coals,
you know?
Are you absolutely sure
that it's not--
Yeah, he's been really busy
with the campaign.
These aren't about the baby,
by the way.
I've been lighting them all week.
I just--I needed
some sign, you know,
About whether or not
I should break up
with such a good guy.
Well, I got my sign.
I don't belong with Archie.
I just...I don't know if I'm gonna
have the guts to tell him.
Hilda.
Maybe you didn't make
the best choice...
but you are
a really good person.
And you don't deserve
to suffer.
Thanks.
But you know you still have
to tell Archie
That you don't want to be
with him, right?
Really? Couldn't you
just peel my skin off?
Can I come in?
I'm gonna
leave you two alone.
Hi.
What's with all the candles?
It's nothing.
It's not nothing, Hilda.
Your father invited me
here tonight, not you.
And every time I get near you,
you make some excuse
To run off into the kitchen
or rush upstairs, and, um,
Today when that woman thought
you were my wife?
You looked like
you'd seen a ghost.
I'm sorry. I--
No, it's--it's okay.
I love you, Hilda.
And I know you care for me,
But there's someone out there
Who's gonna be thrilled
to be mistaken for my wife.
And, um,
I deserve to find that person.
And you deserve to find
that person, too.
I hoped it could be me,
But... since it isn't,
It's... time
For me to say good-bye.
Happy New Year.
-woman
-man
- with 50% ownership.
- With equal veto power.
- Yes.
May I now, kiss the bride?
Not so fast. Can you really do this
without consulting your mother first?
Please. Focus on getting that money back.
Oh, I will. And I don't care if I have to
go to that filthy prison every day to do it.
Don't worry allright, I'm not gonna come around anymore,
I know that it makes you nervous. I don't like that.
Maybe a little.
- Bobby.
- What?
It's ok if you wanna drive Justin home now and
then, from school you know. Since it's so cold out.
Good!
***
Yeah.
That was a lovely dinner.
Such a nice family.
Thank you. We should do this again.
Maybe easter **.
I'd like that. Just don't tell my mother.
She'd kill me if she knew I was
dating someone who wasn't a Jewish.
I'm sorry I freaked out before.
Everything you said was so sweet. I wasn't really in
a place to hear it, but... I'm really glad you said it.
I meant it. I know. I know it's
not the right time, but...
***
- That's crazy right?
- No, that' not crazy.
Sometimes I imagine that too.
- And what do you see?
- It's silly.
And I'd much rather focus
on what I'm seeing right now.
That sounds good too.
- Merry Christmas Hanuka.
Sync by ReHelen
Corrected by Lawman666
www.addic7ed.com