You Will Be My Prot.
But That's Marc's Job.
And Now It's Yours.
Stuart,
What Are You Doing Here?
What's Wrong?
I Think He's Doing Drugs Again.
What?
I Was On That Trip With You
In Paris.
I Remember You Drooling
All Over His Mother.
Your Son's Grandparents
In France
Filed A Claim For Custody.
I Want To Stay With My Father.
I've Made A Decision.
Tonight We Are Welcoming Back,
As Editor-In-Chief Of "Mode,"
Daniel Meade.
Don't Forget, I Still Own
A Third Of This Company.
You Would Be Nothing
Without That Baby.
You Can't Push Me Aside.
Um, Is That Light
Really Necessary?
Sorry, Miss Suarez.
That's Okay. Believe Me.
No One Wants To Know
What Happened To Christina
More Than I Do.
About That--
Do You Have Any Idea
Where Mr. Meade Was Last Night?
Um... Do I Know
Where Daniel Was Last Night?
***
Hi, Dad.
Morning, Sweetheart.
Are We Gonna Do This
Every Morning?
Hey, I Miss You At Breakfast,
But I'm Sure
You're Having A Great Breakfast
In Your Own Apartment.
(Mouth Full) Mmm. It's Great.
I Can't Help It.
I Still Worry About You,
By Yourself In The Big City.
You Think You Have Enough Locks
On Your Door?
(Normal Voice) I Have Plenty.
And I Grew Up In The Big City,
Remember?
There's No Need To Be
So Protective Of--My Umbrella.
Why Would I Be Protective
Of Your Umbrella?
No, I Left My Umbrella
Outside My Apartment,
And Now It's Gone.
Amor, You're Too Trusting.
You Leave Your Umbrella
Outside Your Apartment,
People Will Steal It.
I'm Sure Somebody
Just Borrowed It.
My Neighbors Are Really Nice.
It Sounds A Lot Like
Your Bike In The Seventh Grade.
Okay, Those Guys Totally Said
That They Would Bring It Back,
And It's Fine If Someone
Borrowed My Umbrella,
'Cause I Don't Need It Today
Anyway.
You Look Different.
I'm Wet.
Big Improvement.
Betty.
Good Morning, Daniels.
What Is Popping, Shorty?
Super Tight.
I Am Outtie Five, 'Kay?
(Chuckles) Everyone At School
Listens To Hip-Hop,
So He's Sort Of
Been Studying Up.
Oh, Well,
He Is A Fast Learner.
Uh-Huh.
All Right, Daniel,
Your First Day Back At "Mode"--
Schedule...
Thank You.
Mail.
Oh, That's It?
Yep, The Rest Of It
Got Forwarded To Alexis,
But I'm On It. Don't Worry.
Oh, And I Also Thought
That I Would Go Do
A Dry Cleaning Run For You
Since You're Off
The Tracksuits. Yay!
Great. Oh. Uh, Can You Have
My Raincoat Dry-Cleaned
While You're At It?
(Coughs) Hello, Dusty.
Oh, And I Was Supposed
To Get My Mom Home Last Night,
But I Ended Up Leaving The Party
Early, So If Anyone Asks,
You Can Just Say,
Uh, We Were, Uh,
Here Late Packing Up
At "Player" Magazine.
But We Weren't At "Player."
Oh, I Know. I Just Thought
It Was The Simplest Explanation.
Well, Why Don't You Just Say
Where You Really Were?
Wouldn't That Be Simpler?
Because I Would...
Because It's Not A Big Deal.
(Claps Hands)
People! I Have
An Announcement To Make!
This Is Urgent!
I Have Important News!
Wilhelmina Slater
Is In The Hospital.
(Gasps)
It's Okay. She's Only There
Because Last Night
Her Surrogate, Christina,
Fell Down The Stairs
And Is Unconscious.
(Gasps) What?
Don't Worry.
The Baby And Wilhelmina
Are Fine.
Marc! What About Christina?
I'm Sure That She's--
You Know What? I Didn't Ask.
(Whispers) Christina...
(Normal Voice)
Hi. It's Betty.
Hey, Betty.
Are You All Right?
What Happened?
I Don't Remember.
It's--It's A Bit Fuzzy.
I Was Leaving The Party.
I'd Had An Awful Time.
And... I Was
At The Top Of The Stairs,
And...
And--And Then
Someone Pushed Me.
What?
(Large Cat Growls)
Mama...???
Rumors Are Swirling
Ever Since The Surrogate...
(Woman Screams)
Carrying Wilhelmina Slater
And Bradford Meade's
Latent Love Child
Fell Down The Stairs.
Or Was She Pushed?
With Meade In The Balance,
Everyone Wants To Know Who
Could Have Done Such A Thing--
The Millionaire Playboy,
The Tranny C.E.O.,
The Angry Matriarch
Acquitted Of Murder
Or Any One Or Wilhelmina's
Many Close Frenemies?
La Slater Lost No Time
In Trying To Help Authorities
Find The Culprit.
I Will Not Rest Until The Person
Who Threatened The Life
Of My Unborn Child...
(Whispers) And Others.
And Others
Is Brought To Justice.
So I'm Offering
A Reward Of $100,000
To Anyone With Information
Leading To The Apprehension
Of This Monster.
This Is A Huge Opportunity.
The More
They Talk About This,
The Less They Talk
About The Poor Sales
Of My First Issue Of "Mode."
(Turns Of Tv)
Still, Willie,Doesn't It Worry You A Little,
This Whole Situation?
Well,
Of Course I'm Worried, Marc,
But When Someone
Gives You Chintz,
You Can Do Two Things--
"A," Whine About The Fact
That It's An Upholstery Fabric
Or "B," Turn It Into
A Fabulous Bolero Jacket.
Okay, You're
A Diabolical Fashion Genius,
And I'm Delighted To Be
Your First Assistant Again,
But Your Baby...
And Others
Are In The Hospital.
I-I-I-I Know They're Okay,
But...
Marc, You're Right.
At The End Of The Day,
It's About My Child.
Now We'll Have To Make Sure
The Press Knows That.
We Need Speeches, Vigils,
Long Nights At The Hospital
With Our Scottish Rent-A-Womb.
We'll Have To Make Sure
They Don't Forget
The Real Victim Here.
The Baby.
Me.
You.
(Headset Beeps)
Hello. "Mode" Magazine.
You'll Have To Call Back.
(Beep)
Detective Averaimo. I'm Here
To Question People About--
I Did It.
Excuse Me?
And Now You Have To
Interrogate Me For,
Like, Hours And Hours,
And I Do Not Break Easy.
(Lowered Voice)
I Am Totally Easy.
Detective Averaimo,
Betty Suarez.
We're Gonna Set You Up
In The Conference Room.
(Normal Voice) Oh, But I'm
Guilty. Where Are You Going?
Just So You Know,
The Victim,
Christina Mckinney,
Is My Best Friend.
Don't Worry, Miss Suarez,
We're Taking This Case
Very Seriously.
The Attempted Murder Of A Woman
And Her Unborn Child...
Well, If There's Anything Else
That I Can Do For You,
Please Just Let Me Know.
Yeah, Well, You Can Start
By Answering A Few Questions.
Um, Is That Light
Really Necessary?
Sorry, Miss Suarez.
Do I Know...
Where Daniel Was
Last Night? Um...
You Know, After The Party.
I'm Not Really Sure.
You See, He Sort Of Asked Me
To Say He Was Working Late.
If Anyone, You Know, Asked.
He Asked You To Lie?
Uh... No, No. Uh, Not A Lie.
More Of A Small Untruth.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Excuse Me.
No.
I Think I Just Found
A Very Promising Lead.
He Said "Very Promising Lead,"
And Then He Circled
And Underlined Daniel's Name.
It's All My Fault.
Speaking Of Which,
I've Been Watching
A Lot Of Cop Shows Lately,
And That Mariska Hargitay
Wears Some Amazing Pantsuits.
I'm Just Trying
To Keep Things Upbeat.
Sweetheart,
I'm Sure If He Circled
And Underlined Daniel's Name,
The Detective Had
A Pretty Good Reason.
Dad, He Only Thinks
Daniel's Guilty
Because Of Something I Said.
It's Not Like Daniel Could Ever
Do Something Like That.
Well, If Daniel's Innocent,
Then He Has Nothing
To Worry About, Right?
Right.
You're Right.
I'm Worrying About Nothing.
I Better Get Going. Trains Take
Forever To Come After 9:00.
Okay.
Thank You
For The Italian Burgers.
All Right. Bye.
You're Welcome.
Let Us Know What Happens.
Okay.
(Lowered Voice)
Hi. Sorry I Missed Supper.
I'm Sure You Were Busy.
Hey. Listen. We Need To Talk
About Me And Coach, Okay?
You're The Only One Who Knows,
And I Know
You're Still Mad At Me.
Hilda, I'm Not Mad.
I Was Just Surprised Yesterday.
I Never Thought
You Were The Type Of Person
Who'd Do Something Like This.
Wait, Wait, Wait, Wait.
Wait A Minute.
I'm The Same Person. I'm Your
Sister. Have A Little Faith.
Tony's Marriage Isn't Working,
Okay? He Wants To Be With Me.
But Getting Out
Of A Situation Like That
Is A Little Bit Complicated,
So That's Why
We Were Wondering
If Maybe We Could
Just Borrow Your Apartment.
What? Are You Crazy?
No, Hilda.
I'm Not Gonna Let You
Turn My Apartment
Into Some Sort Of Sex Den.
Shh. It's Not About Sex.
It's About Love.
Fine.
Then Some Sort Of Love Den.
If It Was Just About That,
Then We Could Do It In His Car.
But That Is No Place
To Talk About Whether Or Not
We Have A Future Together.
Betty, I'm Trying To Figure This
Thing Out With Him, You Know?
And All We Need Is A Place
To Talk. Just Talk. I Promise.
I Love You.
Thank You, Mami.
Well, Before You Talk
To Daniel,
Could You
At Least Handcuff Me?
Daniel,
I Have To Tell You Something.
I Meant To Tell You Yesterday,
But I Thought
I Should Do It In Person.
You See, I Sort Of Might Have
Maybe Admitted To The Police
That You Asked Me To Lie
About Where You Were
The Night Of The Party.
Wait. Why Would You Do That?
I Don't Know!
I Am Not A Very Good Liar,
And I Didn't Think It Was That
Big Of A Deal, And Then He--
Mr. Meade,
You Got A Minute?
I Was Wondering About Something
I Noticed In Your Office.
Are These Your Sneakers?
Yeah. Uh, Those Are Actually--
They're Bapes.
They're... (Clears Throat)
One-Of-A-Kind.
Nigo Hand-Molded The Soles
For Me And Everything.
Fancy. Size 11, Huh?
Mm-Hmm.
I'm Afraid
You're Under Arrest.
What?
Wait. What?
The Tread Marks Here
Match The Size 11 Shoe Printswe Found In The Stairwell
Where Miss Mckinney Was Pushed.
Betty, Call My Lawyer.
*(Grunts)Um, Right. Okay, I Will.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
丑女贝蒂 第三季 第3集
-==破烂熊字幕组==-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
时间轴：没被咬死的卢斌
(Claire) $200,000 Bail--
That Almost Seems Cheap.
(Alexis) Here Comes The Press.
Come On, Guys.
Has Anyone
Talked To Daniel Jr.?
I Don't Want Him
To See His Father Like This.
I've Already Handled It.
I Told Him It's A Meade Thing.
See, Grandma Was
In Jail Before,
And Aunt Alexis
May Be In Jail Next.
Seriously, Mom.
We Have To Come Up With A Plan.
I Think Somebody's Framing
Daniel,
And I Wouldn't
Put It Past Wilhelmina.
(Betty) Let's Go.
(Claire) Thank You, Betty.
(Alexis) We Have Nothing
To Say At This Time. Thank You.
(Claire) Thank You.
What The...
(Camera Shutters Clicking)
Oh.
(Woman) Wilhelmina!
Surrogate!
(Man) Right Over Here.
(Woman) Surrogate,
Pull The Bandage Down.
You're Horrible.
Why, Because I Care About
The Welfare Of My Unborn Child?
(Loudly) That's Right.
I Care About The Welfare
Of My Poor, Unborn Child.
(Man) Good. One More Shot.
Because You Are
Using Me And The Baby
As Some Kind Of Prop
For A P.R. Stunt.
Ugh. This Pregnancy Has
Just Made You Hysterical.
Oh.
Believe Me. I Understand.
It's... (Whispers) Hormones.
(Normal Voice) You Just Need
A Drink Of Water. Nurse?
Nurse, My--My Surrogate
Needs Some Water.
She's--She's Suffered
So Much Already.
Please. Won't Anyone Help Me?
Can Someone Just Give Her
Some Water?
All Right!
(Gasps)
Daniel, Look.
I Know This Is My Fault,
And I Really Want
To Help You Get Out Of It,
But You Did Tell Me To Lie
About Where You Were Last Night.
I Know. It's Complicated.
More Complicated
Than Attempted Murder?
Look, You Just Gotta
Believe Me, Betty.
You Know Me.
I Didn't Push Christina.
But Beyond That,
The Less I Say, The Better.
I Promised Betty
We'd Keep It Clean In Here.
Oh, That's Too Bad.
I'm Feeling Dirty.
Coach, What Did I Just Say?
Mmm. Seriously, I'm Dirty.
Water's Out At Work.
Thank You Very Much,
New York City
Public School System.
(Sniffs) Yeah,
I Kind Of Need A Shower.
Okay, Well,
Now I Miss The Sexy Talk.
Do You Want
To Just Take A Shower Here?
Oh.
(Chuckles)
I'll Go Get Some Ice Cream,
And Then When I Come Back,
We Can Talk.
Talk?
Mm-Hmm. When I Say "Talk,"
I Actually Mean Talk.
Oh, Yeah. No. No.
I Know Exactly What You Mean.
(Laughs) Mm. I'll Be Back.
All Right.
All Clean, Sexy Ma--Aah!
Coach?
Papi. (Gasps) Tony.
Hilda.
Papi,
What Are You Doing Here?
I-I Was Worried About Betty.
I Came To Install Locks.
Oh, What'd You Get,
Schlage Locks?
No, Kwikset.
Oh, Yeah, Those Are Good.
You're Married?
Papi--Papi,
It's--It's Not What You Think.
I Think I Should Go.
I Don't Know Why Daniel
Won't Tell Me Where He Was,
But I Just Don't Think
That He's Capable
Of Doing Something Like This.
I Mean, It's My Fault
He's In This Situation.
I Have To Prove That He's
Innocent, And You Can Help Me.
Well, What Can I Do?
I Mean, I've Already
Talked To The Police.
I Know, But Maybe There's
Something That You Forgot
Or Something That
You Didn't Fully Explain
That Could Help Us Find
Who Really Pushed You.
I... Never Got Around
To Telling You
What Happened With Stuart.
What Happened With Stuart?
I S-Saw Him
On The Day Of The Party,
And... We Fought.
You Used Me. You Just Wanted
The Money To Buy Drugs.
Christina--
Just Get Your Hands Off Me!
I'm This Close
To Calling Immigration
And Having You Deported.
(Chuckles)
Oh, My God. Christina.
Everyone's So Fixated On Who
Wants Revenge On Wilhelmina,
Nobody's Talking About
Who Hates You.
I'm Sorry.
That Came Out Wrong.
What Did The Police Say
About Stuart?
I Haven't Exactly
Told Them About It.
(Gasps)
(Sighs) God, Betty.
This Has Just Been So Awful.
I Mean, Do You Think
That Stuart Could...
Really Have Done This To Me?
I Don't Know.
But You Can't Keep Something
Like This From The Police.
Christina, You Have
To Tell Them The Truth.
I Know.
??
Stuart. Hi.
What Are You Doing Here?
Well, I Heard Christina
Was In The Hospital.
I Had To Come
And See That She's Okay.
Yeah, Uh,
It's Just That, Um,
They Don't Really Want Anyone
In There Who Might Upset Her.
She Told You
About The Fight, Huh?
Nope.
Maybe. What Size Shoes
Do You Wear?
Why?
No Reason.
Size 14. The Kids At School
Used To Call Me "Big Foot."
It Was Humiliating.
Now Do You Want To Tell Me
Why You Need To Know That?
Well, The Person Who Pushed
Christina Down The Stairs
Wore A Size 11.
Do You Think I Did It?
It Breaks My Heart
That You Think I'm Even Capable
Of Hurting Christina.
I Love Her.
Well,
What Do You Expect, Stuart?
She Gave Up A Lot For You,
To Save Your Life,
And Now
You're Doing Drugs Again?
I'm In Pain.
The Treatment
That Christina Paid For--
It Didn't Work.
There's No Cure,
So I'm Gonna Die, Okay?
I'm Sorry. Uh...
I Had No Idea.
Are You Going To Tell Her?
After What
Christina's Done For Me,
To Tell Her
It Was All For Nothing,
How Am I Gonna Do That?
After All She's Done For You,
She Deserves To Know.
This Didn't Work In High School.
Why Would It Work Now?
What, Are You Stalking Me?
A Married Man, Hilda? I Thought
You Were Better Than This.
Said The Guy Who Had An Affair
With Our Mom.
No, That Was Totally Differe.
Oh, Right,
Because You're A Guy,
And You Got That Whole Latino
Macho Thing Happening.
Don't Make This About That.
This Is About You.
You'd Never Say
Anything Like This To Betty.
Maybe Because Betty Wouldn't
Do Something Like This.
Good Afternoon.
Hi. I'm Betty Suarez.
I'm Daniel Meade's Assistant.
I Need The Security Tapes
From Two Nights Ago.
You Want
The Security Tapes, Too?
Like, I Said,
I Work For Daniel Meade,
As In Meade Publications.
The Guy They Arrested
For Pushing That Pregnant Lady?
That's The One.
That's Crazy.
You Work For A Murderer.
Ah. Attempted Murderer,
And He Didn't Do It,
And You Work For Him, Too.
Wow.
I Work For A Murderer.
I Hadn't Considered That.
Right, So If You Give Me
The Tapes,
And We Can Prove He's Innocent,
Then We Won't
Work For A Murderer.
I Can't Do It.
The Morning After Your Boss
Tried To Kill
That Poor Pregnant Lady,
The Tapes Were Gone.
What? Well, Do You Know
Who Took 'Em?
I'll Tell You
What I Told The Police
And That Little Blonde Girl.
Okay.
I Have No Idea.
Wait.
What Little Blonde Girl?
So I Asked About The Tapes.
So What?
I Am Not Splitting Wilhelmina's
Reward Money With You.
Amanda, I Don't Care
About The Reward.
I Just Need To Help Daniel.
Look, You Know
He's Innocent, Too.
I Do.
Look, Don't Judge Me, Okay?
Not That You Ever
Really Could In... That.
But I Really, Really Need
That Reward Money.
I'm Having A Little Bit
Of A Cash Flow Problem,
And I May Or May Not Have
Maxed Out A Few Credit Cards.
How Many?
Like... (Mumbles) 15.
15?
(Normal Voice) Shh. I Like
Nice Things, Okay? So What?
Anyway, I'm Not Talking
To My Parents Now,
So I'm Kind Of On My Own
With This, Not That You'd Care.
No, Of Course I Care.
Look, Amanda, You Were There
The Night Christina Got Pushed,
So Why Don't You Just Tell Me
What You Remember?
Well, It Was Late.
That's When I Usually Trythe Credit Card Company's
Indian Call Centers.
They Are So Much Nicer.
Seriously, I Don't Know Why
You're Making Such A Big Deal
Out Of This, Rahul.
Is It A Crime To Purchase Things
You Can't Pay For? No.
Amanda,
Have You Seen The Mustard?
I Need It
For My Big, Fat Sandwich,
Which I'm Always,
Like, Eating Around You
And Making
A Total Mess Of Myself.
Y Know.
You Always Are, Right?
Mm-Hmm.
I Do Not Always Eat Sandwiches,
And I Wasn't Even There.
I'm Just Saying, It Really
Does Feel That Way Sometimes.
So Anyway,
I Was Back At My Desk...
Okay, If I Pay My Bill,
Then I Can't Pay My Rent,
And If I Can't Pay My Rent, Then
Where Will You Send My Bill?
See? This Is
Actually All For You.
(High-Pitched Scream)
(Gasps) Christina?
I Peered Around The Corner,
But It Wasn't A Woman.
Well, It Was Marc.
You Will Rue The Day,
Wilhelmina Slater,
That You Decided To Cross
Marc St. James.
I Know All Of Your Plans,
And I Will Make You Pay!
Actually, I Did Push Christina
The Other Night.
(Both) What?
Oh, It's Not What You Think.
God, You People
Jump To Conclusions.
And You... You'd Think Someone
With Your Skin Tone
Would Be A Little More Sensitive
To Prejudice.
Marc,
Don't Change The Subject.
You Just Said
You Pushed Christina,
And Amanda Said
She Saw You Yelling
At Wilhelmina That Night.
Oh. That.
Well,
That Really Wasn't Anything.
Then Why Are You Hiding It?
I'm Not Hiding It. I Just Don't
Want Anyone To Know About It.
Marc, That's The Same Thing.
Fine! Do You Want To Know
What I Was Doing? I'll Show You.
(Gasp) You Killed Wilhelmina,
And You Stuffed Her!
But You Put Her In Tahari?
Amanda,
It's A Wilhelmina Doll.
(Marc)
It's A Wilhelmina Mannequin.
She Had It Made
For Dress Fittings.
Now I'm Not Proud Of This,
And I Will Deny It If Asked,
But Sometimes
When I'm Angry At Her,
I Will Pull Out The Mannequin
Late At Night And... Yell At It.
You Will Rue The Day,
Wilhelmina Slater,
That You Decided To Cross
Marc St. James.
I Know All Of Your Plans,
And I Will Make You Pay.
You Slapped Her?
Hard Core.
Well, I Apologized Afterwards.
I Mean,
I Know She's Not Real,
But She Still Scares Me
A Little.
Marc, You Still Haven't
Explained
Exactly Why You Were Angry
At Wilhelmina.
Oh, I Don't Know.
Maybe Because I've Been Loyal
To Her For Years,
And Then In A Matter Of Days,
She Hires
This Little Mayan Fireplug
And Promotes Her Above Me?
Marc, That Again?
You May Think
That I Lick Willie's Boots
Because I Like It, And I Do
A Little--They're Fancy--
But There Is A Reason
Why I Put Myself Through It.
You're Not The Only One
Who Wants To Get Ahead
In The Magazine World.
I Have Dreams, Too.
Wow. You Never Mentioned That.
Anyway,
I Was A Little Worked Up
Yelling At The Wilhel-Mannequin,
So I Just Wanted To Go Home...
But Christina
Was Blocking My Way.
(Elevator Bell Dings)
Excuse Me.
(Claire) You.
You're Carrying That Thing...
For Her!
Aah!
So That's The Last Time
I Saw Christina, With Claire,
Who Seemed
Pretty Pissed Off At Her
Now That I Think About It.
Oh, My God. Claire.
She Had A Motive,
An Opportunity--
Not To Mention,
She Totally Murdered My Mom.
Kind Of.
(Betty)
All Right, Mrs. Meade,
If You Could Just Tell Us
What You Remember.
Just So You Know,
If I Had Done It,
I Would Never Let My Son
Take The Blame.
Oh, Something You Learned
In Prison?
There's Two Things
They Always Tell You--
Do Your Own Time
And Don't Trust The Popo.
Mm.
Okay. Uh, So What Exactly
Were You Doing
The Night Of The Launch Party?
Well, You Probably Remember Us
At The Party,
Exchanging
Our Usual Pleasantries.
You Can't Push Me Aside.
Don't You Ever Threaten
My Children, Wilhelmina.
You Have No Idea The Lengths
I Will Go To Protect Them.
You're Not Doing
A Very Good Job Of Explaining
How You're Innocent.
Yes, Well, Wilhelmina Has
A Way Of Getting Me Worked Up,
And That Night,
I Found Myself
Needing A Little Something
To Take The Edge Off.
All Right, You Slipped Up.
You Had A Drink. So What?
That's The Thing.
I Can't Have Just One Drink.
I Screwed Up, Betty.
Wilhelmina Slater.
More Like Wilhelmina Slut-Er.
Get It?
Oh, That's Okay.
I'm So Funny.
Oh! God.
Excuse Me.
Oh.
You.
You're Carrying That Thing
For Her!
Oh! Hold It--Oh. Ooh.
Oh, Mom.
Yeah, Right Here
On The Sofa.
Oh, No.
(Groans)
Mother,
Have You Been Drinking?
Maybe.
Well, T-The Last One
Sort Of Ended Up
All Over Me, Really.
Thank You, Christina.
Yeah.
Oh. Thank You.
My Mother Has Struggled
With This One For A Long Time,
But I Can't Really Blame Her.
It's Been A Stressful Week
For All Of Us.
I Was Sort Of Dealing With
My Own Problems That Night.
You Mean Wilhelmina?
Yeah. Wilhelmina?
Yeah.
Let Me Remind You
Of My Position At This Company
And Then All Of Yours
Before I Say,
This Doesn't Go Any Further
Than... This... Room.
(Gulps) Okay.
(Gulps) That's Great.
We Understand.
I Work Very Hard
To Look Poised...
But Sometimes Things
Slip Through The Cracks.
(Betty) Oh, My God.
What Did You Find?
(Alexis) Facial Hair.
(Amanda, Betty And Marc)
Facial Hair?
I'd Forgotten
To Take My Estrogen.
I Go To Great Lengths
To Maintain The Illusionthat I Was Born A Woman,
But I Wasn't.
I'll Be Honest. I Didn't Even
Notice Christina Leaving.
I Guess She Must Have Snuck Out
While I Was Helping My Mom.
The Rest Of The Night Was Spent
Trying To Hail A Taxi
And Keep My Mom
From Getting Sick
On My Brand-New Donna Karan.
Wow. I Never Knew
Alexis Went Through That
Or Claire Or You, Amanda,
With Your Credit Cards.
(Mouths Words)
I Mean, You'd Think There Was
An Easy Explanation
For These Things,
But There Just Isn't.
I Know, But After
Talking To Everyone,
It Really Does Seem
Like Daniel Did It.
And I'm Genuinely Surprised.
No, Daniel Is Innocent.
I Know He Is.
Maybe Wilhelmina
Could Help Us Prove It.
Prove What?
Prove That Daniel's Innocent.
(Whispers) Oh, I Didn't
Understand That Part.
Christina Was
Standing Right Here.
Okay, Guys. Go Ahead. Throw
The Mannequin Down The Stairs.
Hmm. I Don't Want
To Be Critical Here,
But We Can't Reenact
This Crime With That Mannequin.
It's Way Too Skinny.
So True.
We Need Something Heavy
That Can Double
As A Convincing Pregnant Woman.
Guys, Don't Be Ridiculous.
I'm Not Gonna Let You
Throw Me Down The Stairs.
Just Relax. You Won't Break
Anything Unless You Tense Up.
Marc, I Said Let Me Go! Aah!
Are You Guys Crazy?
You Could Have Killed Us.
Great. Can You Have My Raincoat
Dry-Cleaned While You're At It?
(Coughs) Hello, Dusty.
Oh, My God.
Daniel's Coat.
Dear, I Was Talking
To Barbara Walters' People
About Setting Up An Inter--
Well, I--
Everything All Right?
Emotional Stress Is
Not Good For The Baby.
(Voice Breaking)
Stuart Came To See Me.
His Treatment Didn't Work.
And He's Dying.
Well, I Suppose
That's The Danger
Of Experimental Treatments.
Can You Just Leave Me On My Own
For A Little While?
Please.
Oh... What Did I Do?
Daniel. Hi. I Was Just
Looking For Some Paperwork.
Nope. It's Not Here.
Hey, I'm Glad I Found You.
Look, I've Just Been Wanting
To Tell You How Much
Your Faith In Me Has Meant
During This Whole Ordeal.
Yeah. Of--Of Course.
Something Wrong?
No, Nothing's Wrong.
Why Would Anything Be Wrong?
I Don't Know,
Just Kind Of The Way
You Said, "Nothing's Wrong,"
It Kinda Like, You Know, Sounds
Like There Is Something Wrong.
Nope.
Oh, I Gotta Go.
Betty?
(Gasps)
Thank God You're Here.
I Don't Know What To Do.
Hilda's Having An Affair.
Coach Diaz--He's Married.
I Know.
Wait. What? You Know?
Dad! Enough With The Spanish.
I Think
Daniel Pushed Christina.
What?
I Found This In His Bag.
It's A Security Tape From "Mode"
The Night Christina Got Pushed.
He Stole It.
Do You Think He's Guilty?
I Don't Know. I Don't--
I Don't Know What To Think.
I Mean, I Spent The Entire Day
Trying To Prove
That He's Innocent,
And All I Found Out Was That
Everything Is More Complicated
Than I Thought.
Betty, This Is
Why I Worry About You.
I Know, Dad. I Know. You Think
I'm Naive. I'm Too Trusting.
Is It Really Naive
To Want To Believe In People?
I Mean, Look At Hilda.
Okay, So She Made A Mistake.
She's Still A Good Person.
And I Would Say
The Same Thing About Daniel
Right Before I Found This.
That's Not Being Naive, Mija.
That's Faith.
Have You Seen It?
No.
I Don't Want To Know
If I'm Wrong About Daniel.
What If You're Right?
Ew, Daniel.
This Is Dirty...
And Awkward.
But Why Would He Want
To Hide That From The Police?
It's Complicated.
It's Not That Complicated,
Daniel. I've Seen The Tape.
Oh, God. Not The--
Yes, And I Saw It
With My Dad.
Okay, So... The Woman
I Was With That Night,
That Was Holly,
The State Department Liaison
Who's Been Helping Me
With My Custody Problems?
And You're Sleeping With Her?
No, No. That--That Happened
After She Started Helping Me.
It Wasn't Like
She Started Helping Me
Because We Slept Together,
But If It Ever Got Out,
I Know That's
What It Would Look Like.
That's It? That's Why
You Couldn't Say Anything?
What, Are You Crazy?
Daniel, You Were Arrested
For Attempted Murder!
Yeah, Which I Didn't Commit.
Look, I Had To Believe
They Were Gonna Find
The Real Culprit Eventually.
Besides, If They Ever Found Out
Where I Really Was That Night,
Holly Could Have Lost Her Job,
I'd Lose Her Help
And I Could Lose Daniel Jr.
Forever.
He's My Son, Betty. I'm Not
Gonna Lose Him Now. I Won't.
Oh, My God.
Daniel, I Have Never Been
More Happy
To Find Out About
One Of Your Sleazy Affairs.
Oh! I Knew You Couldn't Have
Pushed Christina.
I Believed In You,
And I Was Right. Mm!
Thank You, Betty.
Um, I'm--I'm Sorry
To Do This Right Now.
I-I'm Late To Pick Up D.J.
Right. Okay. Yes.
You Should Go.
Would You Mind Giving That Coat
Back To Alexis?
What Do You Mean,
Give It Back?
She Borrowed It
A Couple Days Ago.
It Looks Better On Her Anyway.
Alexis?
I Know You Did It.
I Don't Know What
You're Talking About, Betty.
Daniel's Coat.
You Borrowed It.
It Had Dust Fsom The Bottom Of
The Steps Where Christina Fell.
So I Got His Coat Dusty.
So What?
It Doesn't Mean Anything.
What About Your Feet?
Excuse M
There Are A Lot Of Things
You Can Change About Yourself,
But Your Shoe Size
Isn't One Of Them.
Men's Size 11,
Just Like Daniel's,
Same As The Ones
The Police Found
At The Bottom Of The Stairs.
You Pushed Christina, Alexis.
What Do You Want?
What You Did To Christina
Was Horrible,
But Then You Stole Daniel's
Shoes And You Wore His Coat?
You Framed Your Own Brother,
Alexis.
I-I Didn't Mean For That
To Happen. I Swear.
Yeah, Well,
That's What It Looks Like.
The Night Of The Party,
Things Were Bad With Wilhelmina.
I Know We've Had
Our Differences, Wilhelmina,
But We're Going To Have To Find
A Way To Work Together.
Oh, Spare Me, Alexis.
You Stabbed Me In The Back.
So Let Me Give You Fair Warning,
My Freakishly Tall Girlfriend,
You Will Never Be Rid Of Me
Thanks To This Baby.
I Know All Your Secrets,
And When I Get My Chance,
You'll Never See It Coming.
(Alexis) I Was So Pissed Off
That I Broke A Heel.
Oh!
Brand-New Sergio Rossis, Too.
I Knew He Was My Size,
So I Went To See
If Daniel Might Have
A Pair Of Shoes That Fit Me.
Then I Saw The Facial Hair.
And Right After That...
I Know It's Not Right,
But At That Moment,
I Didn't See Christina.
I Saw Someone Else.
(Electricity Crackles)
You'll Never Be Rid Of Me.
She Was Right.
As Long As Christina
Was Carrying Her Baby,
I Would Never Be Rid Of Her.
My Mother Passed Out.
So I Followed Christina
Out Into The Hallway.
And I Can't Explain It...
But When I Saw Christina
Then...
All I Could Think Of
Was Wilhelmina
And Everything
She's Put Our Family Through.
I Didn't Think. I Just...
I Ran To Her Afterward.
I Made Sure
She Was Still Alive...
And Called 9-1-1.
I Can't Justify What I Did.
And Daniel--I Never,
Ever Wanted That To Happen.
It Was Insane.
I Just Kept Telling Myself,
"He's Innocent. It'll Go Away."
Oh, God, Betty.
If I Could Take It Back,
I Would,
But I Can't.
What Do I Do?
Well...
No One Else Knows Yet.
And I Haven't Told Danielbecause I Know
You're A Good Person, Alexis.
But Right Now, You're The Only
Person Who Can Prove That.
(Woman) * You Wanna Bend
* Oh, But If You Do
* It All Comes Back
* Just Breathe
* Breathe
* We Tend To Forget
We're All The Same *
* We All Have Joy,
We All Have Pain *
* Oh, But If We Would Remember
* Yeah
* How Beautiful It Would Be
* If We Breathe
* Breathe
* Believe
* We Tend To Forget
We're All The Same *
* We All Have Joy,We All Have Pain *
???
* Breathe
So Her Lawyers
Are Negotiating
The Terms Of Her Surrender.
Betty, You Think You Know
Your Own Sister By Now...
I Know.
People Can Surprise You.
Miss Meade...
If You're Ready.
Dear?
Mom, There's One More Thing
I Have To Tell You.
Could--Could You Give Us
Another Moment, Please?
Thank You.
When I Was Clearing Out
My Office,
I Accidentally Opened Up
A Piece Of Daniel's Mail.
Well, Darling, Given What
We're Dealing With Here,
I Think Daniel's Going To
Overlook That One.
No. No, He Won't.
It Was A Paternity Test.
I Don't Understand.
* Breathe
(Lowered Voice) Daniel
Isn't Daniel Jr.'S Father.
I Am.
* Breathe
破烂熊字幕组作品
-==http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
欢 迎 加 入