Oh, hey, Betty.
Could you grab me my loofah?
What is that? I got it for Halston.
He's supposed to come anytime I ring it,
but he's kind of a bad doggy.
Not like you, Betty.
You're a good girl! No. No, don't do that.
Look,
Amanda I'm really glad that you're getting so comfortable living here these past couple of weeks
really, I am, but I think it's time you and I
Have a talk about something that really has been bothering me.
Is this about that $60 that you left out for anyone to take in your bottom drawer?
It's time to let that go, Betty.
Amanda, you have this tendency to treat me like I'm your assistant.
What? give me an example.
Well, for instance, you rang a bell to summon me.
You're constantly asking me to take your calls,
-Write down your messages  -oh, that reminds me.
What time's my massage tomorrow?
Oh, 6:30. amanda! oh.
No. look, I am an assistant all day long at work.
I don't want to come home and be an assistant here, too.
But you like your job.
Yes, I do.t is a wonderful stepping stone.
However,
I don't think doing menial tasks for
You is gonna help me get ahead in my career.
Hey, Betty,
Is it possible you're taking your career frustration out on me?
I don't think of you as an assistant. I really don't.
I think of you as a roommate, and sometimes a maid.
Would you grab me a coffee while you're up? that's not my job.
Good morning, Betty. could I get a cup of coffee?
Sure. that's my job.
Oh, Betty.
Nick pepper. what are you doing here?
Oh, you know, just visiting the old haunts.
I bet you've all been wondering what I've been doing since I left "mode.
you left "mode"?
Yeah, like two months ago, when alexis left?
Oh, right.
-We really missed you. -Anyway, crazy story.
I get one job interview, and the next thing you know,
I am deputy culture editor of the "new york review."
-Boo-yah! -What?
You're an editor? I know. can you believe it?
No. no.
Ah, isn't life funny?
No, but seriously, how are you guys? things going good?
Oh, yeah, marc got engaged, but then he got dumped.
It was sad. mandy.
Hold that thought, you guys. my assistant is texting me.
You have your own assistant? oh, yeah.
Hey, nick, just out of curiosity, how did you manage to get that job?
I mean, you weren't an assistant here for very long, and no offense,
But you weren't really that good at your job either.
Yeah, but I also graduated from y.e.t.i.
Last year.
Y.e.t.i.? young editors' training initiative.
It started a couple of years ago, uber-selective.
Nearly everyone from my class has gone on to become an editor.
So what, there's, like,
This magical school where assistants
Go to get turned into editors overnight?
One doesn't become a ninja overnight, Betty.
The hard part is getting in. you need a sponsor.
You gotta present a whole magazine concept to a bunch of judges.
But once you get in-- if u get in--boom.
I got my brass ring, and I am running with it, baby.
Talk to me. nick pepper, deputy culture editor.
Oh! daniel, great news.
You get to be my sponsor for y.e.t.i.
the young editors' training initiative.
Great. uh, what does a sponsor do?
Just write a letter about how great I am.
Try and keep it under a page if you can.
Thanks, daniel. this means so much to me.
Um, okay.
Oh, gross. look who's here.
Wilhelmina, good morning.
Look who's here.
How are you?
Very well, thank you.
And look at you, with your hair all up and everything.
Aren't you coltish?
-Molly was just dropping me off. -I've gotta run.
We're doing a big thanksgiving thing at school today.
I have a native american from the poospatuck tribe coming to speak.
Mm, the life you lead.
Well, it's always good to see you. likewise.
We'll have to do brunch. really?
I'd rather gouge my eyes out.
I will shoot you in the heart before I'll let you brunch with her?
I mean, she's a mousy schoolteacher.
And he is ambitis, he's shrewd, he's competitive, he's hot, he's...
He's me.
He's the me-a-mina.
Well, why can't he see we'd make the perfect couple together?
Maybe you need to spend more time with him, you know, one-on-one.
Well, I do have that advertisers' meeting in florida.
Maybe I could invite him. he could see me in action.
Maybe he can see you in your underwear as well.
Marc.
It's not about the sex.
I can see a future with him.
And he could, too, with, me.
If he'd just get to know me, he'd see that we're the same.
Okay, but if that doesn't work, you could always wah-wah.
'cause you've still got it, lady.
Well, it's always good to have a plan "b."
Or a plan 34-c. uh-huh.
Here at y.e.t.i.,
we see people as more than just assistants.
We see you as the future leaders of the publishing industry.
Gosh, I feel like I'm dreaming.
This is exactly the opportunity that I've been looking for.
So here are your guidelines for your presentation.
You have to create a cover,
A table of contents and a letter from the editor for
An original magazine concept that best describes you.
Oh, this application is for next year. I'm looking for this year.
The deadline for this year is just too tight.
Oh. well, I can't wait another year.
This is my future. I need to start my future, pilar.
My boss works under deadlines all the time.
I've done it before. I can do it.
I hope y're right. you are adorable.
Thank you.
Oh, and so how tight is my deadline?
Like a month, a couple weeks?
You have 48 hours.
To create a magazine?
Good luck.
Y.E.T.I.
Dad, please, you made the posole.
You don't have to clean up, too.
Mija, you just stay right there and keep working.
We want you to get into this y.e.t.i.
I don't know how they expect you to come up with a magazine in two days.
Well, luckily I know exactly what a fashion magazine is supposed to look like.
You're doing a fashion magazine?
What? well, stop looking at me. dad.
Sweetheart,
I thought the assignment was to do a magazine that expresses who you are.
It is.
It is, and--and I have a million ideas that I want to do,
But they're all too big, and I don't have time, so I'm being practical.
I have the resources at "mode" to do a fashion magazine.
It just has to get me in. oh, I guess that makes sense.
You get your foot in the door,
And then you're on your way to doing your not-fashion magazine.
okay, mom.We have to go.
Randy's coming over to watch "little shop of horrors."
The high school doing the play tomorrow,
And randy thinks that he can see the play without seeing the movie.
I know.
Crazy, right?
Okay, please through out the garbage, and we'll meet you downstairs.
Betty needs to get back to work.
You, too. all right. god.
Hey, so justin's spending a lot of time with randy, huh?
Yeah. it's been great.
You know, they hang out all the time you know, ever since santos died,
Justin really hasn't had any male presence in his life.
Hello? I'm right here.
You know what I mean. bye. mwah.
Love you. love you.
Betty, you're getting in. I know it.
>lo siento aqu?
Well, I hope you're right.
Papi, this could be the fast track to everything I ever wanted.
Fashion.
Connor, hi.
Hi. listen, are you familiar with doral resort wear?
As in the largest resort wear label in the country?
That's the one.
Well, they are interested in exclusive back cover  spots through 2012.
That's huge.
Well, we just have to persuade them to jump ship from "elle,"
And they can only meet tomorrow.
So, uh, will you join me for the meeting?
I'm supposed to speak at molly's school in the morning.
Can we schedule it for the afternoon? oh, I forgot to tell you.
Doral's corporate offices are in key largo, florida.
Uh, so you and I are going on a little trip.
Right. okay, betty, which one of these vests do you want for your cover?
Um, I like the spotted one.
Really?
Well, I don't know. the... the blue one?
Or I mean, does it even need a vest?
Maybe a blazer or a bolero.
Well, betty, now you're just saying words at me.
I just--i can't wrap my head around this letter from the editor.
Betty, how hard can it be? daniel does it. what do I do?
What don't you do?
Thank you. christina, would you sign this out?
I'm not really feeling the red tie today.
What is all this?
Oh, uh, we're working on my magazine for y.e.t.i.
So you're doing a fashion magazine?
Mm-hmm. why?
Great. yeah, so... carry on.
Christina, am I on the wrong track? no. no, no, no, no, no.
Right now. come on. concentrate, missy.
Which of these vests do you want for the cover?
That one?
Yes! that's my girl. all right!
It's easy.
So what do you think so far? I like it.
You know, the guy who plays the dentist is really good for high school.
You're as good as him. you could totally play that part.
You think so? mm-hmm.
Randy.
Hey, man, what's up? what's up, man?
What are you doing here? just watching the show.
Oh, the one about the singing plant? yeah.
It's pretty lame, dude. skip the rest. let's hang out. are you insane?
They haven't even done "suddenly seymour" yet. wait.
You guys are watching the show together?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, man. well, have fun.
See ya. well, some people enjoy a musical, thank you very much.
Come on. let's go back inside.
Okay. betty, this is it. I think we've got it-- the winning look.
Christina... yes!
It's great.
Oh, I think my cover is gonna be amazing.
God, that took a really long time.
I guess choosing this stuff doesn't really come natural to anybody.
Okay, write this down.
I need the elie tahari, mm, this dusty rose dior,
Whatever this fabulous thing is, and, oh,
You know what would be gorge with this?
Those amethyst drop earrings by pippa small. ooh.
Mm. we're signing all of this out. thank you. for what?
Marc's y.e.t.i. presentation.
What? marc, wait! marc!
You're applying to y.e.t.i.? I didn't know that.
Well, you know me. I like to keep a low profile.
I'm applying to y.e.t.i., too.
Really? you're my competition?
What's your magazine? what's your vision?
Um... betty's doing a fashion magazine.
Really? oh, my god. brilliant.
I'm as good as in. betty, you know fashion means clothing, right?
Betty's magazine is gonna kick your magazine's ass.
Oh, really? what's it called, "clashing patterns digest"?
Okay, okay. all right. no need to be so snarky.
We could both get in.
Actually, that's where you're wrong, betty.
Y.e.t.i. never takes two people from the same magazine.
Really?
Yep. so when it's this... against this...
In the fashion world, I think you know who the winner is.
Good luck.
Oh, there's my baby boy.
I thought we talked about that.
Oh, right.
There's my big strong man.
How was the play?
You know, you'd think I'd be tired of seeing "little shop," after, like,
14 times, but you'd be wrong.
And how about Randy?
Um, he liked it... I think.
He had to go home right after.
Mm. do you think Randy would like to go with you to a broadway show?
"In the Heights,"
Winner of the 2008 tony for best musical? mm-hmm.
Third row orchestra? mom, I'm goin' blind.
All right, all right. don't go blind. just have fun.
Randy's gonna flip.
Mwah. thank you.
All right. I love you. love you.
Justin, slow down.
Mija, what a surprise.
Mm. papi, I need a pan of your capirotada and a spoon.
Two spoons. I need one going at all times.
Uh-oh. two spoons. never a good sign.
Did you finish your presentation?
No, I quit.
I can't do a fashion magazine.
Told you so!
Not helping!
And now I have to wait another year to apply to Y.E.T.I.
I was just kidding myself. It wasn't me.
Sweetheart, that's the problem.
Wasn't the assignment to do a magazine that shows who you are?
-Yeah.
-Well, do that. -Dad, there isn't any time.
Of course there is.
When you are passionate, you can do anything.
Remember when your mother was in the hospital the first time?
You wanted her to know everything you guys were doing, so you made...
A magazine for her. remember?  oh!
Oh, you saved "the betty review"? oh!
I save everything you girls do. oh!
Look at this--articles,
Pictures of all the things that are important to you.
Look at my hair! I looked so good.
And as I remember,
You were able to make this whole magazine in one afternoon
because it mattered to you. oh.
So why don't you just give them this?
This? you're not helping.
No, wait. that does help. that does help.
Hilda, thank you. papi, thank you.
Okay, I'm going back to work now.
Work? there's nobody at work.
-Doesn't matter. -What about the capirotada?
I'll eat it later.
Morning, daniel.
Got your phone sheet, your schedule and your coffee.
Might have had a few cups myself.
Uh, is that the same outfit you were wearing yesterday? good eye.
Good eye. yeah.
I stayed up all night working on my Y.E.T.I.
Application, but I finished,
And I was wondering if you could maybe take a look at it,
you know, like a dry run sort of thing?
it would mean a lot to me,'cause your opinion matters.
uh, sure. but I haven't even sat down yet.
Right, right, right, right, right.
Well, you know, settle in, take your time,
But just not too much time 'cause my presentation's at 2:00.
-Man, I had a lot of coffee. -You okay?
Borderline, on the edge-- the good side of the edge--
So don't you worry about me.
Hey, did you finish my letter of recommendation?
Uh, no, not just yet.
-You forgot?  -No, I didn't forget. just...
You know, if you're anxious about it, maybe you should write the letter,
And that way, I could sign it.
You can write whatever you want, make yourself sound great.
Daniel, have you got a second?
Uh, yeah, sure. thanks, Betty.
So Wilhelmina and I are about to head off to Florida.
Oh, right, the doral account.
Good luck with that. you'll definitely need it.
thanks. yeah.
Anyway, uh, I'm in a world of trouble with Molly.
I promised her I'd talk to her class today about the magazine business.
Now feel free to say no to this, but...
You want me to talk to Molly's class?
I know she'd really appreciate it, and I know you think she's great.
No, I don't.
-What? -no, uh, I like her,
but I don't like her like you like her
Uh, I'd love to talk to her class.
Great. all right. I'll get you the details.
Thanks for going for me, mate.
Yeah.
Daniel, are you going out of the office?
Uh, when do you think we can do the dry run of my presentation?
Oh, I'm not gonna be gone long, hour, tops.
You got something in your hair.
Oh. I was looking for that.
If I get called out there and I don't make it back...
I want you to know, you have been an excellent teammate, Sherman.
Red rover, red rover, send daniel right over.
Okay. okay, everyone.
Everyone, quietly, quietly get in line for potty break and juice.
Go with miss Haskell, quietly in line.
Great call with the red rover.
I knew I was in trouble when I asked them who wanted
To be an editor when they grow up, and little Emmy said...
"um, I want to be a dancer/monkey/ chinese person."
So you're good with kids.
Yeah, well, it's definitely something I've been thinking about lately,
You know, starting a family.
-Oh, come on. what?   -No. nothing.
You are just not the Daniel Meade that you read about in the tabloids.
Well, I'm just full of surprises. mm.
So what's next? um, finger painting?
macaroni art?
Hey, if you got the time, I got the pasta.
I guess that's that.
I've been an aistant to the editor-in-chief at
"mode" magazine for two years now, and I love my job there.
But as we all know,
The goal of a fashion magazine is to create
And sell an image that women will want to become.
I have imagined a magazine that celebrates what women already are...
A magazine for the young woman looking to
Be inspired beyond celebrities and clothing.
Sounds like my daughter.
Well, then your daughter might be interested in reading...
"b magazine," a lifestyle magazine for young women.
This magazine says that it's okay to get involved, to use your mind,
Be thoughtful, be confident, be yourself.
"b magazine."
Nice, miss suarez.
Let's hear your letter from the editor.
Okay, okay, okay.
So how did it go?
I think I nailed it.
Yay! she nailed it! yes! my daughter!
Shh, shh, dad. she's my daughter. this is my daughter.
Dad, dad, shh.
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Andre, heather, emily,
Sven-- would you mind setting up the powerpoint screen in there, please?
Thank you so much. you're the best.
Marc.
You brought a team.
Oh, just some of the interns from "mode"
Helping out with the heavy lifting. no big whoop.
"a-list" magazine-- for all things fashion, fabulous and famous.
See that? all fluff.
-You showed 'em you were smart.  -A celebrity magazine?
I mean, hasn't that been done?
Well, instead of just exploiting the celebrity culture,
I'm commenting on it, ruminating on america's obsession with fame.
Why can't we get enough?
-That sounds kind of smart.  -I know.
Actually, david sedaris wrote a really great feature for us about--well,
You know what? why don't you just take a look?
-You can keep that.  -Wait. you did an entire magazine?
Marc, sorry we're late.
There they are.
Suares, you're familiar with the super chic,
Iconic stylings of fashion house badgley mischka.
Meet mark badgley and james mischka.
Marc's y.e.t.i. sponsors. uh!
We read your magazine. it's so sharp.
-It's right on the money.  -Where has wilhelmina been hiding you?
Oh, mark, james.
-Marc st. james?  -Yes.
-francesca.  -james!
I didn't know you were a judge for this.
-You're gonna love our friend marc.  -Come in.
Yes. we're eager to see your presentation.
Thank you.
There's my favorite girl.
Hey,are you applying to y.e.t.i. again?
I don't know.
Daniel, I've applied for 49 years in a row.
Maybe if you finally gave me that letter of recommendation...
Oh, come on, betty. don't be such a nag.
Hey, would you mind grabbing me a cup of coffee?
That's my job.
Don't run now.
Wouldn't want you to hurt yourself...
Because you're gonna be my assistant until your dying day.
You're my betty.
Betty.
Sorry I'm late. I lost track of time.
I'm ready to help you with your y.e.t.i. thing.
Oh. excuse me.
"you missed it"?
Betty, why are you texting me?
"can't talk to you right now!!!"
Hmm. all capitals, one, two, three exclamation points.
Okay, I get it. you're mad at me.
Look, I feel terrible.
Is there something I can do, someone I can talk to for you?
"too late." happy face?
-That's supposed to be an unhappy face.  -Ha! I got you to talk.
You can't go back now.
I'm shutting my phone off. listen to me.
Betty, I am sorry.
Whatever, daniel.
Recommendation letter, dry run-- none of it would have helped.
I'm not getting into y.e.t.i.
Daniel meade's office. how can I help you?
Yes, this is betty.
What?
Wait. I got in? I got into y.e.t.i.?
That's amazing!
Yes!
All right!
That's so great! should I come down there?
You were brilliant. ah.
You got that guy to lock in the premium rate for the
Next five years and make him think that it was his idea.
I thought I was pushing it.
Well, sometimes people want to be pushed a little.
You were magnificent.
Well, we certainly do make for a well-oiled machine
Yes, we do. so shall we go out and celebrate?
Yes. absolutely.
Although the restaurant we passed on the way in
Had a sign in front that says, uh, "we've got crabs."
Hmm. okay, what do you suggest?
Well, believe it or not, this hotel is the best place in town.
Maybe we could, um, order room service, a bottle of wine?
Sounds great.
Yes, it does...
Doesn't it?
Okay,
So you are never gonna guess where we are
Going tomorrow night-- "in the heights" on broadway.
Okay. you're speechless.
I was, too, but hello! four tonys, two tickets.
Um, I can't go. I'm busy.
Well, you're gonna have to cancel whatever you're doing,
Because you don't even understand how great these seats are.
-Look, justin, I don't--  -What?
I don't think we should hang out anymore.
Why? is there something wrong?
Dude, stop following me around.
It's pathetic. get a life.
See you in dance class.
Oh, man, what a loser.
Hi, marc.
Marc, isn't in right now, but if you leave your name and number,
He'll never speak toou again
you odious sea cow, betty. beep.
Okay.
Obviously you got your y.e.t.i. news.
Look, I know you must be disappointed
but for whatever it's worth,
I really liked your presentation.
It was really good.
Only about a thousand times better than yours.
Okay, well, I don't know about that.
Look, maybe the judges just saw how much I wanted it, you know,
How much I want to be an editor.
Mm-hmm. you're right, because I don't want to be an editor.
I didn't go to f.i.t.
Or spend a summer abroad studying menswear in milan
Or spend the last four years of my life slaving for the
Best creative director in the industry,
Who doesn't even know and wouldn't even care that I applied to y.e.t.i.
Okay, well, clearly you wanted it.
Look, maybe they just liked my concept better or, you know,
Who knows why they would pick me. i-- yeah, okay.
What? nothing. forget it.
No. what, marc?
You really think that what you did in two days
Is better than what I spent three months working on?
Y-y-you're really gonna make me say it?
Say what?
You helped them meet their quota.
What are you talking about?
I mean, they picked you, betty suarez of queens, becausyou're latina.
You're the token ethnic girl.
Wha-- what? n-- they picked me...
That doesn't even...
Wow, marc.
You have said a lot of really ugly things to me in the past,
But that is by far and away the ugliest.
Well, I'm sorry, betty.
It may be ugly, but it's the truth.
Surprise! surprise! you're in the y.e.t.i.
Guys, guys, guys, guys, no.
No, no. it's not really a good time right now. what?
Bui brought the capirotada. yeah!
Yay, betty! she did it. ow!
God!
Guys, I don't feel like celebrating right now.
Why? what--what-- what's wrong, mija?
Marc told me that the only reason y.e.t.i.
Accepted me is because I'm latina.
What? sounds like sour grapes to me.
Yeah. yeah, well, I called, and they didn't exactly deny it.
Who cares why you got in? you got in.
I care. look, you gotta take every advantage you get in this life.
When I have to go to the butcher shop, I put on my tightest tank top,
And thank you to the pointer sisters right here,
Abundio the meat man--
Is that fair? no. so what?
who cares? I don't care. thank you
I can never show my face in that butcher shop again.
Please. betty, it doesn't matter.
When your mom and I came to this country,
We wanted to start a better life.
oh, here goes the young immigrant story.
All over the city, I looked for woras a chef, but nobody would hire me.
One guy told me flat out,
"puerto ricans don't touch the food.
You can wash the dishes."
I said, "i'm not puerto rican. I'm a maxican.
Know what he said to me? "even worse."
papi, look, i-- all I'm saying is,
If being mexican helped this time, then good. take it.
No, papi.
I wanted to be accepted because I earned it.
You did.
So, wil... yes?
Tell me, no mann your life,
or are men just disposable to you?
Well, yes, there's been men, but, uh... what?
Well, it sounds awful, but they've all been such terrible disappointments.
Well£¬I've seeyou in action,
and you are a very formidable woman.
I'm sure they find it hard to keep up.
So molly--um, she teaches children how to color?
Yeah, she's great.
Molly--she's, um, very free-spirited, very forthright.
You always know exactly what she's thinking.
Yes, yes, yes.
I met her. she's a peach.
But a schoolteacher doesn't seem like a
Natural fit for a powerful business mind as yourself.
Well, I guess at first,
It was the differences that were challenging and exciting.
It was an aphrodisiac-- opposites being drawn together.
And, uh, now?
And now...
We're engaged.
Let's, uh, have some more wine, shall we?
Justin, easy on the door. leave me alone.
Excuse me.
Lose the attitude or you're not going to "in the heights" tomorrow.
I'm not going anyway.
Justin, what happened? why are you so upset?
Randy doesn't want to be friends anymore. why not?
I don't know, mom. I don't know.
But I'm not going to the stupid show.
Justin, I'm sure that randy did not mom.
Please stop. I don't want to talk about it.
"dear, daniel, thanks for coming to our class.
You are old."
Hello.
Oh, hey. uh, it's daniel. um...
Just got your thank-you notes.
Just calling to, um, thank you for those.
You're thanking me for thank-you notes?
It's kind of weird. I'm sorry.
Um, i-i didn't mean to bother you.
You're not bothering me.
It's nice to talk to a grown-up.
Connor's still in florida, so I'm working late tonight.
By the way, the macaroni earrings you made are surprisingly wearable.
Why is it that I'm stonkered and you're fine?
Well, I guess I can hold my liquor better than you.
You know, wil, I disagree with everybody at the office.
I think you're great.
Oh, that reminds me of boarding school.
We used to play spin the bottle.
That sounds like a dangerous game.
Well, no, it's harmless.
Of course never wanted the bottle to land on me.
I was, uh, always afraid of just what might happen.
You are very hard to resist.
Well, then stop resisting.
No.
Stop.
Wilhelmina, I'm engaged.
You need to stop what you're doing and accept that.
Here. you're in.
What?
You were right.
Your presentation was better. so I dropped out, and you're in.
Betty, are you crazy?
I have been discriminated against my whole life.
If I was given an advantage like you, I would take it and run with it.
Marc, you're a gay man in the fashion industry.
You have plenty of advantages.
That gets me nothing.
Madonna--tickets, backstage passes.
Thanks, bitch.
Okay, but outside the fashion world, it's a different story.
Look, marc, at the end of the day, you deserved it more.
-And I could just... apply next year. -I-I...
Marc, just--please, before I change my mind.
Okay.
I'm sorry for the things that I said yesterday.
I hope you don't think I'm a racist.
Just so you know,
Some of the hottest guys I've ever dated have been Latino.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
You know, you might feel better if you just tell me what happened.
I don't know.
I'm on your side.
Well, one minute Randy's my best friend,
and... now he-- he hates me.
That's not possible.
No, it is...
Because... I don't fit in with his friends.
Well, then that's their problem, because you're perfect.
Yeah, okay.
No.
Sweetie, listen to me.
You are perfect.
But you're gonna meet a lot of stupid people in your life,
And they're just not gonna get you.
Screw 'em.
All that matters is that you never, for a second, change who you are.
I know.
Promise?
Yeah.
Mom?
Yeah?
Did you get rid of the theater tickets yet?
No. Do you want to go?
I mean,
Just because Randy's an idiot doesn't
Mean we have to waste perfectly good tickets.
Yeah, man.
I would love to see "in the heights."
Are you kidding me? oh, my baby boy.
Sorry. sorry. I know you don't like that.
It's okay. you know, I love you, mom.
Oh... I love you, baby.
So how was the trip with Connor? was there nudity?
-Did you get a look... down under? -It was a complete bust.
For some reason, he's completed devoted to that...
Molly.
Ugh. devotion.
Does he see that she doesn't use eyeliner?
So what's the plan? what do we do now?
Nothing. there is no plan.
I'm not gonna beg.
If he wants to marry that do-gooding gremlin, that's his choice.
I'm sorry, willie.
Sorry for what?
Oh, and, uh, marc, I heard you got into the Y.E.T.I program.
I trust that's not going to interfere with your job here.
Oh, of course not.
Good.
I can't think of anyone more deserving.
Congratulations.
Betty, can you come in here a moment?
Betty...
I know how important Y.E.T.I. was to you,
and I dropped the ball.
It's fine. no, it's not.
And now I'm hearing you dropped out so marc could get in?
Y.E.T.I. won't take two people from the same magazine.
Yeah, that's why I made a couple calls.
I just thought, you know,
They should know you worked at "player" this year, too.
Just don't drop out this time.
Did you get me accepted?
All you had to do was say I worked at "player"?
Yeah. now you and marc are from different magazines.
I'm sure this didn't hurt either.
I'm sorry it took me so long to write your recommendation.
Daniel, this is six pages.
That's short. you should have seen the first draft.
Well...
I don't--i don't even know what to say.
Uh, sorry about before?
Look, I know you're going places, just--you gotta do me a favor.
Try not to get there too fast.
I'd be lying if I didn't say I wish you
Were my assistant for the next 20 years.
But don't worry.
I know in 20 years, I'll probably be your assistant.
Daniel told me we both got in.
Pretty cool, right? did you see the schedule of speakers?
Anna Wintour and Tina Brown in the same week. ah!
This is just the first step, you know?
We're gonna be huge.
-Betty, phone. -Marc, where is my moisturizer?
Coming, willie.
Daniel Meade's office.
Oh, thank you for calling back. I wanted to confirm...