Ugly Betty Season 3 Episode 17
Made by Nazel
Here you go
Hey guys, good morning!
Wow Betty, who died?
I didn't wanna look too cheerful
Everyone's so depressed at work
This is a financial crisis
And Daniel's girlfriend is sick ..
Did I overdo it?
No, No! All black is ..
Aunt Betty, you look.. Almost fashionable
Justin, are you crying?
No, I'm just proud
You do listen ..
You know I still don't understand how that guy Connor
Could steal all that money from the company
And nobody even noticed?
That's terrible
I know papi, and the worst part is
I think he's gonna get away with it
He's totally disappeared
Why, why does he do that?
I don't know, I guess some people are just greedy
You don't wash mushrooms, you wipe them!
He's not talking to you
He's talking to that stupid TV chef on Kitchen Rumble
This Frankie Barata guy really makes me mad
Then why do you keep watching him?
Because, I keep thinking somebody's gonna beat this guy
I mean, I mean ..
If the judges like your dish better
You could walk away with thousands of dollars
But if they like mine ..
All you're gonna get are my leftovers
Hey spit on your leftovers
Eww
I keep calling him and telling him I should be on that show
I can cook better than him
Papi, you can cook better than everyone
Oh by the way, I'm not gonna make it to dinner tonight
I have plans with my new friend Matt
Mmmmmmm
We've been hearing a lot about this new friend Matt
Say, you're blushing
Stop! What, it's just a couple of dates and ..
I don't know, I think there's something there
Ok I gotta go, bye!
- Love you ..
- Bye
Do I look serious enough for a company in ruin?
Yes! Don’t touch your outfit you look perfect
So close and yet so far
Daniel Meade's office
Did you get the gift I sent?
This is Matt by the way just in case you're wondering
Hi Matt, I know who it is
Umm, no I don't see a gift,
Oh even better, then I'll be on the phone when you get it
I love the looks on a person's face when they get a present
You can't see my face through the phone silly
I'll imagine it
Oh, hold on one second
Good morning Daniel,
how are you, can I get you something?
Coffee, cream, a couple of billion dollars
Or a company that doesn't go bankrupt
Just joking, sort of
Have you spoken to Molly?
She needs time alone, to figure out her treatment
Whether she wants to go through all that again
And you don't wanna be there with her?
She made it pretty clear that she wants to be left alone
So I have to respect her wishes
Oh .. thank you .. Ohh
Someone has an admirer?
Let me just put this away
Sorry
Don't apologize
You should take happiness when you can find it
- You deserve it
- Thank you
I just got your jellybeans
Yay! So what does your face look like?
My face is .. Smiling
Was that a smile on your face?
No Willi, it was a sneer I promise
Good
What are you ..
Are those gladiator sandals?
Are we in ancient Rome?
Will you be wrestling a lion?
Take those off
- Burn these ..
- You are fired
Willi, as much as I love watching fired employees
Scamper off sad and barefoot
Are you okay?
What mood do you think I should be in Marc?
The company's on the brink of collapse
Connor ran off with all the money
Yeah Hey Willi, he did break your heart a little bit, right?
Don't be ridiculous, Connor Owens is a thief
Nothing more than that to me
Just another disappointing useless male
Has it occurred to you that my mood of late
Might have something to do with a newborn baby
Who never seems to stop crying?
Speaking of darling baby William
The nanny called, she can't come this week
Apparently, her own child has come down with chickenpox
Her own child? Who does this woman think she is?
Get Christina to babysit
And here's a list of things I need you to pick up for the baby at Estella
Agh .. I did not sign up for this baby business
Cashmere diapers, is she kidding?
Aw .. I love shopping at baby stores
You do?
I like to sit in a tiny furniture and pretend I'm a scary giant
The children cry, it is so much fun
Hey do you wanna go with me tomorrow?
Yeah, wait .. Mode magazine, this is Amanda
How may I direct your call?
You! How many times have I told you not to call here?
Leave me alone you psycho!
What was that?
It was my mother, she's been reading about the company in the news
And she's concerned about my job
Mandy, it's been a year
Would it be so horrible if you reconnected with your parents?
They lied to me my entire life about being adopted
Now you know me I'm not the one to hold a grudge
But I will never speak to my parents as long as I may live
- What?
- Nothing, it's just really pretty when you're dramatic
The bad news is our insurance doesn't cover us for a loss of this magnitude
Oh ..
So what's the good news?
There is no good news
Oh good god!
Do you even know how the good news/bad news setup works
If you're looking for good news, why don't you ask your boyfriend Connor
Well you stole his fiancee no wonder he wanted to steal from us
You were dating him, how could you not know what he was doing?
Oh so it's my fault now?
Stop! Bickering isn't going to solve anything
Yes, stop bickering Daniel
Thousands of people are going to lose their jobs if we don't fix this
Well easier said than done Claire, what's your bright idea
How about a federal bailout?
Oh of course, Daniel and I will just march down to Washington
And beg the government to save our magazine
You don't have to march anywhere
They're already here
Federal government sends panel to New York City to consider print media bailout
Mum, this is genius
You may wanna rethink your wardrobe Wilhelmina
We're gonna have a little trouble convincing them we need money wearing mink
It's not mink darling, it's chinchilla
Whatever it is, you look like a rich bitch
Matt, you didn't have to come all the way to Queens just to see me home
Well considering how I left my wallet at work and made you pay for dinner
I could use your brownie points
Oh sorry, don't mind me
So you must be Betty's new friend Matt
I'm her sister
Betty you didn't tell me you have a sister
- What?
- Yes I did
I'm kidding, she talks about you all the time
I have a terrible sense of humor
It grows on you, or it doesn't
- It's nice to meet you Hilda
- You too
Thanks again for dinner
Wait a minute, why was he thanking you for dinner?
He didn't pay?
Well sometimes he forgets his wallet
Sometimes? As in more than once?
Oh no no no, Betty, I do not like this man
He's just absent-minded, but he's so sweet
He sent me jellybeans at work today
Jellybeans? What kind of a cheap present is that?
Hilda! Stop
Okay maybe he's not perfect but..
The more time I spend with him, the more I like him and ..
I don't know, just all this craziness at work is really giving me perspective
I have a wonderful job and a great family and ..
A guy that I like, can't I just enjoy this moment, please?
Mum, Mum! I found this with the mail
Honey, what is it?
It's from the landlord
This document shall serve a termination of your rental agreement
Please be advised you have until the end of the month to vacate the premises
Oh my god! We're being evicted
I hate doing this to you Ignacio
Then don't, we've been living in this house for 25 years
Mr. Di Lena, this is our home
I mean there's gotta be something we can work out right?
The truth is I'm having some money problems
I'm gonna have to sell to my idiot nephew
Sao, couldn't we rent from him?
He's turning it into a recording studio cause that's a good investment
A recording studio? But I have my business here too
My salon, what am I supposed to do?
I wish I could help, but unless you can match my nephew's offer
buy the house yourselves
Yes! Yes, we'll buy the house
We should've taken the limo
Right and have our picture taking getting out
That will help us get the bailout money
But a bus, really Daniel?
Oh god, this is the lowest moment of my life
Straight tote across town, come on it's gonna be fun
- One please
- Metro cards or quarters only
Do you think I carry quarters?
I don't know whether to laugh or cry
Can you break a 50?
Thank you!
Ok, the loan officer said that we do qualify for an FHA loan
So what does that mean?
It means we only have to put down 5% before the end of the month
15 thousand dollars
Betty, I don't have that much money saved up
Yeah but if we combine all of our savings
This is my responsibility, I'm not taking money from my children
Dad stop, stop being so stubborn
This is our house and we wanna stay
Why don't we just ask Daniel for the money?
Justin! Daniel has his own money problems
And I would never ever ask him for something like that
Oh! But Marc and Amanda still owe me the security deposit on my apartment
That's a start
I could offer more sodas at my salon
Smear some yoghurt on an old lady's mug and call it a facial
Yeah! See? Come on papi it's our house, our memories
We should at least try, right?
Come on!
Alright
Excuse me sir, you're in my personal space
So if you're fond of your thumbs I suggest you take one large step backwards
Thank you very much
I thought you were gonna dress down so it looks like we need money
This is what I wear to the gym
For god's sake, hold on to the pole
No way, I don't know who touched that thing
You're such a baby
We better get that bailout
Agh why would anyone want to have a baby
They're so expensive
I know right?
I need food, I need diapers, think of yourself first
Hey thanks for coming with me today
If I never see another baby as long as I live it'll be too soon
You guys shop at Estella, best baby store ever
Oh I know, it's like my favorite place in all of New York City
And Chelo here just loves her little organic cut and onesies
Wait, Chelo? What kind of baby name is that?
So creative, really special
I'm Timothy by the way
Marc, and we're not together, she's just my hag
So I'm guessing you have a baby?
No he doesn't
No, not on me, my little angel's at home
Oh with your partner?
No, nope, single .. Single and ready to mingle
Me too yeah, single parent
You know what, we should get together for a play date sometime
Definitely, I'll call you
Play date
That was rude, he didn't even introduce himself to me
Cute and rude! I'm in love
Oh just the people I was looking for
I need to talk to you about money situation
Gorgeous! That will be 200 dollars
What?
Hey, if you have a Kirsten Dunst and this is Madison Avenue, this is what you pay
Not the same Madison Avenue
Yes, yes, this is Ignacio Suarez
And I'm trying to find someone who can help me
No, I will not hold,
So my family is trying to buy our house
And since you guys are subletting my apartment
I thought it was only fair that you pay the security deposit
75 dollars, 50 dollars
Come one we're trying to buy our house
Money makes the world go round, the world go round, the world go round
Money makes the world go round, of this I can be sure
On being poor
Anyway, my family really needs this money
Oh that is just so you Betty
All fluky and sweet
So you can give me the security deposit money?
Not a chance in hell
Ta
We stand before you today
Humbled by an economic crisis
That threatens the entire publishing industry
Meade Publications is an American company
Founded by an American family
And today we're asking for your help
We understand your plight Mr. Meade
But your flagship publication is a fashion magazine
Why should the government care about something so frivolous?
Frivolous? Oh my dear congressman
Fashion is art, it enriches people's lives
Not to mention it is a vital part of our New York economy
The industry imploys thousands of people
Photographers, construction workers, engineers, vendors
Many of whom we rode the bus with just this morning
Yeah you've mentioned that several times
Well I must concede, your proposal raises some interesting points
We will reconvene on Thursday and talk numbers
Thank you Mr. Chairman
So if you add up all of our savings
We're still 9644 dollars short, how?
What about the security deposit from Marc and Amanda?
Ugh, no luck
You big day at the salon?
Am I the only one who made money today?
My one man show on the street totally killed
Justin, you skipped school and pan handled?
I made like 250 bucks
Oh! Good boy
What about you papi?
Don't worry, I'm gonna get us that money
Papi, how are you gonna get 10,000 dollars by the end of the month?
Ok, here it is
Come on, everybody, quick
We have a winner
A man, from Queens New York called us 162 times in a single day
He says my food is terrible
Well I got news for you Ignacio Surez
I'll be coming to your kitchen to make your dish
And with 10,000 dollars on the line
It better be good
Because Ignacio Suarez, I challenge you to a Kitchen Rumble
I told you, I told you I'll get us the money
That is so cool, how do they do that?
Oh .. hey!
The camera adds 10, you'll thank me later
And you! Betty's new friend Matt
Why does everyone keep calling me that?
Wow, that really doesn't move does it?
Can we off this thing?
Justin why don't you go help grandpa
So what happens if your dad doesn't win?
Matt, don't say that too loud, you'll make my dad nervous
But if you lose the house, where will all of you live?
Don't worry about it, my dad's gonna take care of it
Oh my god look it's Frankie Barata
Which one of you is Ignacio Suarez?
I am!
Come here you persistant old bird!
You're really gonna be on this show huh?
So what you'd do with the money if you win?
Fat chance but what, do some travel, new car?
Actually, we're trying to buy our own home
Ah that's great man, the American dream, good for you
Frankie, we're rolling so whenever you're ready
In 5, 4, 3, 2 ..
I'm Frankie Berata and I'm coming to you from Queens New York
Where Ignacio Suarez and I are going head to head
For bragging rights to New York's best chicken molé
If Ignacio wins he gets 10,000 dollars
But if I win, all he gets are my leftovers
Let the kitchen rumble begin
Well it was pretty clear that the committee responded to me
So when we go back let me do all the talking
Hello Daniel
- Yeah?
- I'm trying to antagonize you but it's no fun if you're not here
Where are you
Sorry, just a little distracted
You know, I couldn't imagine this would ever happen
Connor Wiping us out like that
Yeah well I guess you really never know anyone
Yeah but you were in love with him, that's gotta be hard
We're not here to chat about Connor
This is a business lunch
Save the pillow talk for your girlfriend
Actually Molly and I are ..
Trouble in paradise?
Can we not talk about her right now?
Oh sure, it's okay for you to ask me about my personal life
But you can't be in the hot seat?
She's sick Wilhelmina, she's dying
Well, now you made me feel awkward
Waiter, we're gonna need some wine, lots of it
Now, it looks like Ignacio is making a traditional molé poblano
While Frankie seems to be experimenting with a molé of peanuts
Or in espanol, cacahuetes
Pace yourself papi, you still have 10 minutes
Ignacio grinding cherry paste
And can this be right, I don't believe it!
Frankie putting bread crumbs in his pot
I can't watch I'm too nervous
What's you grinding over there Ignacio?
Frankie getting in Ignacio's head now
Not bread crumbs Frankie
Ooh listen to that trash talk
Papi! What's wrong?
Are you okay, is it your heart?
No it's my back
Throw it out I can't move
Stop the clock, time out, TO
Sorry guys, there's no time out
If you can't stand the heat, get out of the kitchen
Fine, then we'll need to make a substitution
A substitution in the middle of cooking
A Kitchen Rumble first
I'll allow it
Good, good, ok who's the best at chopping?
No no no don't look at me
- I just did my nails
- Me too
- What? No
- Yes
No papi I don't even know how to cook at all
I'll tell you exactly what to do
Mi hija, it's for the house
8 Minus 9 and counting
Okay, I'll do it, what do I do?
Just turn the molé and turn the chicken
Turn the molé, and turn the chicken
Smart move, they turned to the sturdy girl to step in
I can hear you, you know
Now remember ladies and gentlemen
The judges have no idea which dish belongs to which chef
That's our molé
I know, and they love it, look at their smile
We're so gonna win this
It looks like the judges have made their decision
In the battle of chicken molé, there can only be one winner
That winner ladies and gentlemen is ..
Frankie Barata
What?
Oh wow! Thank you, thank you
This was so unexpected
I can't believe we lost
Come on guys! It's not a total loss
You get to eat my leftovers
Well it's not your fault you lost Betty
Those shows are rigged
It's actually sinking in
We're gonna lose our house
Look, you know what maybe I can help you guys out
No, Daniel, no, I cannot ask you to do that
Especially with all the money problems going on here
Chop chop Daniel, we can't keep the government waiting
We have millions to collect
You know your family's important to me
We're not done talking about this
Alright, I'll be fine, just go to your meeting
Save the company
And so after extensively reviewing our finances
We have decided to ask for a subsdidy of 75 million dollars
We feel the government must step in to protect the print media industry
Uhmm, well speaking of print media
I was wondering if either of you caught this morning's post
You look pretty smiley here for people on the verge of bankruptcy
Oh no no no, no we were commiserating
We were only laughing because the waiter had just tripped
This is a 400 dollars bottle of wine
Well to be fair congressman, it was the only drink offered on the menu
You expect the hard working American tax payer
To hand over millions of dollars
While you two paint the town red?
Congressman, I assure you, we were not using company funds
We were spending our own money
Shame on you! Shame I say
Do you know when that hot gay dad asked me on a play date
I didn't actually think he meant play date
You're fine! You just borrow Wilhelmina's baby
Slap on a fanny pack and voila, you're a dad
So what do you even do with a baby?
I don't know, lie to it
Pretend it's yours, never tell it it was adopted
Mandy, is that phone call from your mum still bothering you?
That woman robbed me of the chance to ever know my real mother
I mean I was conntected to Fey Summers for years and never even knew
- Downer
- I know right?
Hey Christina, we need to sign out Wilhelmina's baby
He's not a pea coat, you can't just sign him out whenever you want
What are you two up to?
What are you up to?
- What?
She's fine Christina
Wilhelmina feels that I need to bond more with her little bundle of joy and sticky
Oh, well if that's what Wilhelmina wants
Please be careful with him
No piercings, no tattoos
I was sure I could beat him
Papi, you were robbed
Frankie Barata doesn't deserve to eat your leftovers
- It's gonna be okay
- It's not okay
I promised your mother I would look after you guys
And now you, Betty and even Justin are raising money for the house
It's my responsibility
This was my chance
Oh my god! Oh my god!
What are you doing here?
Look, the answer to our prayers
Ten thousand dollars!
Daniel
Timothy right on time
Let me just put my fanny pack on and we'll head to the playground
Where's Chelo?
Sorry, my Chelo is back at home with the nanny
Somebody woke up from her nap with a little fever
That's great!
I mean not for Chelo, poor Chelo
But it just so happens that Amanda here is my nanny
So, why don't we leave the babies with the nannies
And we'll get some coffee
Bye bye honey
Marc! Marc
Is she okay? She seems a little confused
Oh, her English isn't so good
I'll see you later Amanda, thank you so much goodbye
I know this fabulous little cafe around the corner, have you been?
Marc, Marc
First of all, thank you
You're welcome
But it just doesn't seem right
With everything at the company up in the air
We cannot take your money
Okay, what are you talking about
The check, for ten thousand dollars
What check for ten thousand dollars
Alright, I know that you're trying to be all anonymous
That's why you made the signature so hard to read
But, I knew that you were worried about my family and ..
We didn't get the bailout Betty
I just blew our last shot at saving the company
What? No but I thought ..
Meade is done Betty ..
And I'm sorry, but I didn't write you that check
Here, take it
What happened, where is Marc?
I thought Wilhelmina wanted him to bond with the baby
He just needed it to hook up with this guy
- What?
- Oh yeah, babies are THE hot accessory in the gay world
Small dogs, totally 5 minutes ago
Well he likes you
Well I did carry him for 9 months
Kinda hard not to feel connected
You have to be careful with some things,
Remind myself that I'm not his mother
What do you mean?
Well, you're adopted, you should know more than anyone
Your real mother's not just the one who gave birth to you
It's the one who raises you and tuck you in at night
And yells at you when you miss your curfew
uhoh, you wanna help me change the diaper?
No
No notes, no explanation, just 10,000 dollars
Doesn't that seem so weird?
Yes, really weird
I mean what would you do?
If I get a check like that?
I don't know, cash it?
Dance for joy?
I can't dance by the way, please don't ever ask me
It's just .. Maybe I'm overthinking it
Oh thank you
Thank goodness I've brought my wallet today
I know it's a miracle
uhoh, it's work
Can you just hold on one second?
Hello?
So without the government's help
The company has no money to move forward
As of tomorrow, Meade publications goes dark
I can't believe this is happening
I told you not to flaunt your wealth
Oh please, I suppose you've started making bathtub gin to economize?
When you start ordering your botox from Mexico we'll talk
They were right
The bailout committee
We don't deserve that money
What are you babbling about?
Well do we really expect some unemployed auto worker to save us?
It's not fair
So what, we throw in the towel?
No, we clean up our own mess
It's our name on this building, it's our responsibility
What do you propose?
I'm gonna start liquidating my personal assets
The house in Amagansett, the town house, stocks, art
Everything I've got
I should be able to raise enough to keep the company afloat
Keep everyone on payroll at least for a few months
You do realize that if the company doesn't turn around
You will lose everything
I know
Daniel, I don't have the same kind of resources you do
But I'll contribute as much as I can
I have a son now and it's his company too
Your father would be proud you've taken this off
You are very very brave son
Yeah
Thanks mum
Sorry about that
You're ready to go?
Matt what is this?
Is it some kind of a joke?
It's not a joke
So this is you
And you weren't gonna tell me
You were just gonna let me believe that some stranger gave it to me?
You weren't supposed to find out
Betty listen, the last thing I wanted was for you to feel ..
I don't understand, how did you even find this much money?
Well, well my family is sort of, really wealthy
Okay, and you weren't gonna tell me that either
Well, it never came up in a conversation
Betty, please don't be angry
Look, it's not that much money
Yes, it is
No, not when you get billions of dollars laying around
I'm sorry, did you just say billions?
Well,you know it does go up and down you know with the markets
The dollar has been pretty ..
Matt!
Betty, I want you to have this money
Look, I know you're trying to help ..
No no,look, you don't even have to pay it back
Matt, you can't just give me this
It's too much
No, no it's not, it's not
Look we throw money like this at charity all the time
I'm not your charity
No, Betty
Hilda, would you please give it up
We're not taking Matt's money
You don't even like Matt
What? You are crazy, I love Matt
Matt wants to give us 10,000 dollars
In fact, if you don't marry him
I'm gonna scoop him up myself
- Mum
- What, I'm just kidding
I am not kidding
Do you smell that?
It smells like papi's molé
That's because it is papi's molé
You all remember Mr. Barata
What is he doing here?
Yeah
Your dad was just giving me a cooking lesson
You know I couldn't say this on TV
But he really skewed me with his molé
- So then why didn't he win?
- Yeah!
Don't be upset
I gotta win 3 outta 4 contests just to make my show's budget
So it was fixed!
We really needed that money
Look, I'm really sorry, I know
And that's why I came by to offer your dad
A job at my restaurant
I'm excited to have his molé, on my menu
And I told Mr. Barata that I would love to go work for him
Papi, you just gave this guy your molé recipe?
Gave? This guy don't give anything
He took me for 10,000 dollars
It is quite a secret recipe
And it's worth every penny
- I'll see you monday Ignacio
- You bet
Thanks a lot
Do you think we should've asked for more?
So how was your date?
Oh it was terrible
Just talked about his stupid baby the whole time
Chelo this, Chelo that
Hello! Let's talk about me
But hey listen
I'm sorry I left you stranded with the Wiliminini
No, the baby time was good for me
Kinda got me thinking
You wanna have a baby
Oh my god! You want me to be the father
Ew! No, gross!
Okay it's not that gross!
You were saying?
I guess .. I just realized that I spent so long being mad at my parents
That I kinda forgot that they were my parents
I mean they've always been there for me
They must really miss me
And to be honest I kinda miss them too
So I heard you're gonna finance the company with your own money
That's pretty brave
That's what everyone's telling me
Though, I've never felt like a bigger coward
In my entire life
I Just .. Let her walk away
Molly?
She told me she was sick
Told me not to get involved
To let her go
And the messed up part was ..
I felt relieved
Why?
Because, I was scared ..
To see her get worse
But ..
But?
I love her
Well then you should be with her
Yeah
Go find her .. Go
Now
Hey mum, it's me
Molly!
Daniel?
What are you doing here?
I thought about it
I decided I'm not letting you go
Daniel, we've talked about this
You don't know how hard this is gonna be
I can't put you through it
And I can't let you do this alone
I know you're scared
Molly, I am too
But I need you
I need you in my life
- Hi
- Hey
Thanks for meeting me
Matt, I'm sorry that I got so upset yesterday
No, don't, I'm the one who should be apologizing
You are not my charity
And I will never try to buy your house again
It's a deal
I don't have to buy anything if you don't want to
No dinners, no jellybeans, no nothing
Alright, alright, let's not go crazy
It's just ..
When you gave us that check
It's like one minute you're Matt
Who forgets his wallet and then ..
Betty, I'm still the same person
I know, I just feel like I don't know that much about you
Well, here's something else you might not know
I'm glad that you're not still mad at me
Cause, I'm kinda really into you
- Betty hurry up
- Where's the popcorn?
Made by Nazel
www.tvsubtitles.net