Previously on Nip/Tuck...
You guys are
screwing each other.
You really don't give
a shit about me.
I tried.
Stop it, please...
No, I won't stop...
not until we're together again.
I am pregnant.
It's Sean's sperm.
- And this is?
- Ramona... my fiancee.
I'm gonna work for her
father in his carpet business.
Matt doesn't want either
of you in his life anymore.
The whole therapy thing
is bullshit.
You're right.
We should just end it,
end us.
- Ok. You ok there, dad?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Ok.
So, Mr. and Mrs. Krieger,
tell me what you don't
like about yourself?
I see you're both
booked for the consult.
We want our tattoos removed.
This strikes me
as a very big decision.
Yes.
Well,
it first occurred to me
when I was watching
this documentary
on the TV
about Buchenwald.
And suddenly,
I was overwhelmed.
And I thought,
well,
we have lived
such a great life.
We've survived so much
since then. So, I...
I want to erase
this obsession
with terrible things
from the past.
You can see, she...
she's a remarkable woman.
That's not what
you said in the car, dad.
Allie, please.
Shh.
How can I keep
my mouth shut
when holocaust deniers
are more vocal than ever?
When so many survivors
have passed,
why would you want
to erase one single reminder?
My daughter is upset,
and I understand.
She has
a different perspective.
And you, Walter?
Are you sure
this is what you want?
At the end of the day,
I want what Edith wants.
She is my inspiration.
This will be a chance,
a second chance,
for some joy.
And I can give it to her?
Yes. Take...
take it off.
You need to be
aware that, uh,
the work on the elderly
is not as simple.
The skin is much thinner,
healing takes longer,
and infection is
always a possibility.
Doctor,
after what we've
been through, please.
This is bupkis.
Yeah.
Nip/Subs Team
presents
Season 7 - Episode 8
"Edith and Walter Krieger"
Original VO: honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Original VO corrected by chamallow35
Corrections & Resynchro VO :
Sean
God. These new corporate taxes
are killing our bottom line.
For every set
of implants we do,
it's like Uncle Sam
gets one titty for himself.
Still, it's a pretty good net,
all things considered.
I guess you're right...
For those tax returns
over the years.
Well, I should get going.
You can get all that stuff
to the accountant, all right?
You're not staying?
I got dinner coming.
No.
I'd love to, but, uh...
Maybe some other time.
Hey.
Uh, can I come in?
Hey, Matty. You brought
enough for 3, right?
- Yeah, of course.
- Ok.
Yeah.
Is this some kind of setup?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Wow.
Smells good.
Yeah. Ramona's been
cooking all day.
Ok. I guess I'm staying
for a bite.
Good.
I'll get some plates.
So, your fiancee
cooked all of this?
Yeah. She was just trying
to support me. And...
after we heard what happened
at the shrink's office, you know...
Uh, she actually
wanted me
to bring you
both this.
What is it?
It's in Spanish.
I don't know what...
Let's see.
It says, uh,...
"please join us in celebrating
the marriage of our daughter
Ramona Perez and
Matt McNamara. Casual attire,"
then something about parking
instructions. I don't know.
I, uh, started
learning Spanish.
I want Jenna
to be bilingual,
especially since half her family
is gonna be speaking it soon.
So, you're inviting us
to your wedding now?
Yeah.
I thought you didn't want us
in your life anymore.
Ramona has made me see just
how important family is.
I was on the can all
night after those tamales.
I know. I even had mine
for breakfast.
- She's mine.
- Oh, you think so?
Yup.
Good morning.
How can we
help you, miss?
I know you like 'em
young, Ava,
but shouldn't you at least wait
for his testicles to descend?
His name is Rafael.
He's my adopted son.
As I recall, you left
your last son on the floor
to decompose while you
dashed off to gay Paris.
After I left, I, uh,
I rented
a small pension in...
Le Quartier Latin
where I...
wept for days.
Weeks passed before
I received a letter from Baltimore.
Adrian's death had been
determined to be a suicide,
which it was.
I was cleared
of all wrongdoing.
So, naturally, you jumped
on the next plane back to Miami
to give your son
a proper burial.
I used my grief as fuel
...to move on.
Adrian was covered
in maggots.
Stop!
Please.
Have a little decency.
I don't think you should be
lecturing us on decency.
Look. Whatever
you're here for,
there's no procedure
we could do
that Dr. Moore
couldn't do just as well.
Barrett's dead.
Series of strokes.
I am not the monster
you think I am.
All my life, I've tried
to turn tragedy
into something
meaningful.
I started a foundation with
the money Barrett left me
that subsidizes
corrective surgery for
third-world children.
Leishmaniasis.
It looks like leprosy.
Black fever, Jericho buttons,
it's the same thing.
It's endemic in areas
around the Amazon.
Amphotericin b, I think, is
the recommended treatment.
Side effects are horrible,
often lethal
in a child his age.
Would he survive?
My brave little Rafael?
He's free of
the parasite, but...
has you can see,
it's left its mark.
So, why bring him to us?
Because
you're the best,
and I want what's best
for my son.
You'd do the same
for Matt, wouldn't you?
You know, why don't you
leave your contact information
at the desk, and we'll
send you a list of referrals?
And please don't ever
talk about Matt again.
Rafael's only crime was
being born into poverty.
And now
he's scarred for life.
I'm trying to give him
a second chance.
Perhaps you think that
Beverly Hills matrons
who come to you for
face-lifts are more...
deserving.
We're not doing it.
Don't get carried away.
She's evil.
But that baby is
just a sick child.
And it is intriguing from
a medical point of view.
Look. I know you and I
try to mend fences
and all that bullshit.
I get it, ok?
But I don't give a shit
if Ava comes in here
with baby Jesus himself.
We're not helping her.
All right.
This procedure will only
take about 20 minutes,
as soon as our anesthesiologist
gets off the phone.
Where are my tunes?
Ok, I'm sorry.
That was my gynecologist.
I just got my CVS results.
My baby is perfect.
Oh, Mazel Tov.
How far along are you,
darling?
I am 12 weeks, just
past my first trimester.
Can we dial down
the estrogen, please
and get
my music cranking?
The machine's
on the fritz.
Dr. Troy, could I sing
a song for my wife?
It will relax her.
Fine by me.
I didn't think you weren't coming
into town for a few days.
- You look great, Julia.
- Thank you, Christian.
You haven't changed a bit.
- Thanks.
So, where are
Connor and Annie?
Uh, they're at the hotel.
I thought it best that
I came to see you first.
Oh, you gotta see
my new apartment.
There's plenty of room.
You guys could stay there.
It's probably easier
than a hotel.
I'm getting married
again, Sean.
Congrats.
Good for you.
Is it 2 brides?
2 grooms?
Woman?
Beast?
His name's Edmund,
and, um,
he lives in Knightsbridge,
in England.
And he has
an estate somewhere
that's been in the family
for, like, 400 years.
Uh, what about our kids?
I want them
to come with me.
Yeah, well, London is a
10-hour flight from L.A., so...
Yeah, I know.
And, um,
well, I need
your permission.
You know, it's hard
enough finding time
to fly across the country
to see them.
Now I'm supposed
to fly across the Atlantic?
They need their father.
Ok?
They need
a stable family.
Well, I'm not giving up
my rights to my children
just so you can play
house 6,000 miles away.
It's bullshit,
is what it is.
I can't take a week off
from work
every time I want to see
my kids. It's not realistic.
And what about
the time difference?
If I don't call them by noon
L.A. time, they'll be in bed.
Can I get a 400?
You know, whether
we're married or not,
we still have to do
what's best for the kids.
And she's not
remembering that.
You know, I think that you're the one
who's forgetting what this is about.
You're really losing her.
- Julia?
What are you saying?
Look, I know how you
feel about the kids.
But what you're really
pissed off about is, she's going.
She's going for good this time.
And you still love her.
So, tell me
about this guy.
Ed?
Well, he's a little older
than I am.
He's very intellectual.
He reads a lot.
He's, um,
I don't know.
He's charming.
Rich?
I hope.
I don't want you flitting off
to London with some kind of
saggy-balled bookworm
from Barnes & Noble.
Well, let's just say
he works very hard,
and his balls are
far from saggy.
- Good.
- Ok?
Ok.
- How pissed is Sean?
- You are stealing his kids.
I know.
Uh, we all have
to move on with our lives.
You're getting no arguments from me.
Trust me. Not on that one.
You look great.
Thank you.
So do you.
Thanks.
How are you doing?
In all honesty, this whole
Sean thing's got me a little...
You do know that he dragged
me to couple therapy.
Then you know he's always
gone through these dark phases.
You know he did
when we were married.
He gets through it.
This time feels different.
You look great.
I'll be right back.
You want to know
what's weird?
Every time I see you,
I get a hard-on.
After all these years...
Does it have to be you...
[incompréhensible]
...when I can put it
in my pants?
Christian, stop.
You're moving very,
very far away.
Oh, Christian.
Coming.
I'd fire my receptionist
if she gave out
personal information.
But then again,
I'm very persuasive.
Sorry. I, uh,
I should have called, but...
You would have said no.
- I still could say no.
To a woman with a baby
who needs your help?
No, Sean.
You're not that man.
You want a drink?
No, thanks,
but feel free.
I know you had
a hard day.
You two should see
a professional.
And by "you two,"
I assume you mean...
Your...
other half.
Notice I didn't say
"better."
Well,
we're fine.
You're either in denial,
or you're very selective
about the reality
you accept.
He's beautiful.
Yeah.
He will be.
But his spirit is
sheer radiance.
So, we'll keep looking for
a doctor who will help me...
so that his
appearance can...
match the soul
that's inside.
I know you want to.
There are so many children
who could use your help.
It's your choice,
you know?
You don't need
his approval.
It just feels that way.
Oh, look at you.
I would need all of
his medical information...
doctors' records,
blood workups...
I can try to find them.
I've been moving
around so much.
No, just give me
the name of the hospital
where they gave him
the amphotericin b,
and I will get
in touch with them.
Ava...
Why don't you tell me
how you got this baby?
I, uh, I told you.
I should have
known better
than to be taken in
by you.
Get out.
They had one caretaker
for 50 babies... one.
They let them cry
themselves to sleep.
After weeks of doing nothing
but crying and screaming
and wanting
to be held...
They learned to stop,
to need nothing.
Mothering a suicide didn't make me
a prime candidate for adoption.
My...
past, it seems, hangs
around my neck like a noose.
I brought a small bag.
Seen me with it before, so
no one bothered to check it...
empty going in,
and...
with this beautiful...
if damaged...
Little boy coming out.
Was it illegal?
Yes.
But you tell me.
Was it immoral?
Should I have
left him there?
Scarred?
Malnourished?
Virtually unadoptable?
So he could
grow up alone
and outcast for
the rest of his life?
Like me?
You're incapable
of telling the truth.
Get out.
Maybe I was wrong
about you, Sean.
Whatever it is
that keeps you so...
locked up and judgmental
and unhappy...
Maybe it's got nothing at
all to do with Christian.
Oh. Doctor,
I'm so glad to see you.
We had to take a bus,
because my daughter
didn't answer her phone.
How you doing, Walter?
This one gets a tattoo...
...and that one gets no tattoo
Get me a wheelchair.
He woke up this morning.
His arm was swollen
like a balloon.
I'm sure it's just
a staph infection.
Walter, you're gonna
come with me, all right?
You're gonna get up with me.
We're gonna get into the chair.
The little children.
We're gonna hook you up to
an IV, get you into a bed.
You should be fit as
a fiddle in a couple of days.
So, this is
our finest Berber,
perfect for high-traffic areas
such as your living room.
Um, here.
There you go.
Take your shoes off.
Run your toes through it.
Ooh, I love it, Tony.
How is it with dog pee-pee?
Don't start with
that again, Anita, ok?
Because I'm pretty happy
with the linoleum.
Yeah, but you said that when
your mom came to live with us
that we were gonna be
getting new carpeting.
I know that, but I don't know why
you always have to criticize...
Hello, Matt.
What are you doing here?
You look good, Matt.
Where have you been
the past 6 years?
I tried looking for you.
I always want that things to
turn out differently than they did.
I'm getting married
in 3 days.
I know.
That's why I came.
I, uh,
I have a gift for you.
That's a lot of money, Ava.
It's the least
I can do after
all the horrible things
I've done in the past.
You deserve a fresh start.
Is everything
all right, Matthew?
Yeah, honey.
Hi. Um...
Hi.
Uh, this is Ava Moore,
an old friend
of the family.
And she just came by,
actually,
to give us
a wedding gift.
Ava, this is
my fiancee Ramona.
And who is this
precious little thing?
Uh, that's
my daughter Jenna.
Hello, sweetheart.
She's just perfect.
Well, I think the three of
you make a wonderful family.
I'm so happy for you.
Well, thank you.
I have, um,
business
back in Los Angeles.
Yeah. Traffic gets
pretty bad around here.
You might want get
on the road early.
I hope your wedding is
everything you dream it will be.
Bye, sweetheart.
You good?
Same shit,
different day.
You ok?
You a little hung over from your
bachelorette party with Julia?
Very hung over.
- Did you sleep with her?
- No.
But it wasn't for
lack of trying.
Christian, stop.
No!
I don't want this.
I used to get butterflies
whenever you walked into a room,
or if you called the house
to talk to Sean and I picked up.
I thought about you
when I was making love
to other men,
even Sean.
And I thought
for one second...
that I felt
that way tonight.
But I don't.
I still love you.
But that...
thing that we had,
that...
electricity...
that's gone...
Forever.
That's kind of
a kick in the nuts, huh?
Well, one you deserved.
How could you do that?
How could you do that to me?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I spill my heart out to you.
I tell you that I'm still
in love with her,
and you try to screw her
in the bathroom of some bar?
Hey. You know what, buddy boy?
Like it or not, there's 3 of us. Ok?
I'm not saying
it's a good thing,
but I love her, too.
That's your justification?
I'm sorry if this is
hard for you to hear.
If you want to hit me
or you want to quit
or do whatever it is
that you like to do,
you just go for it, ok?
But I'm not gonna apologize
for what I did last night.
You're right.
We both need to have
our own way with this.
I'll be around at 9:00
to pick up the kids.
If I'm gonna consider this,
I think you should stay a bit.
Seems the least
you could do.
Tell me a little bit
about this new guy.
Oh, come on.
I won't bite.
Cheers.
So,
how did you meet this guy?
At a mutual friend's
dinner party.
How did he propose?
- We were in bed.
- In bed?
What,
in the throes of passion?
Julia,
I don't think you thought
this through very well.
Sean,
Edmund and I have been talking
about marriage for a few months.
Now, I know that it's gonna
be difficult for the kids
being in a new country,
but...
he loves them.
And they need him, too,
you know?
They need a father who
they can see every day.
And you know what?
I can't do it
alone anymore.
Julia...
I'll move to New York,
and we can all be
together again.
We were
a happy family once.
Just say the word, and
we can have it all back again.
I still love you.
I've always loved you.
I never stopped.
Julia, just stay
with me tonight.
And I'll show you
how good we can be...
Oh, my God.
You and Christian...
you are unbelievable.
You've never changed.
Sean, you're both
trying the same trick...
professing your love
to me like 2 teenagers.
I've grown up.
I've moved on.
It's time that you did, too.
I'll pick up the kids at 9:00.
Walter,
when you were delirious,
you were talking in German.
And you kept saying
this one thing
over and over.
You said,
"what did we do
to the children?"
What were you talking about?
Edith, I... I wouldn't
have known what it was.
I was delirious, Edith.
No, no.
There was something...
in your voice.
There's something different.
When you kept talking
about the children, you said,
"what did... we,"
like you were
one of them.
Walter, please. Tell me
I'm afraid for nothing.
Tell me you don't know
what I'm talking about.
I didn't sleep all night.
Walter, what did you do?
I was...
I was just a tattooist, Edith.
I was not the exterminator.
- Is everything all right here?
- No.
Is not all right.
- What are you talking about?
I... I gave
the prisoners the tattoos.
Only the strong ones.
It meant that
they could go to work.
Without a tattoo,
they would be killed.
When the war was over, and...
I escaped to California.
And I promised God
to give me a second chance.
If he would give me
a second chance,
I would live like a Jew.
As a penance, I... I lived with
the people that I harmed.
You see here?
I gave myself...
I gave myself a tattoo.
And I was your penance?
Edith,
why I was given this gift,
I do not know,
but I was.
- God gave me you.
- God is a joke!
Edith,
does it count for nothing?
What I have become?
How long I have
been a good man?
You always talk
about forgiveness.
Forgiveness, Edith.
Hi.
I came to return this.
Ramona's not
comfortable taking it.
And neither am I.
Such reverse snobbery.
It would have been
easier just to...
stick it in the mill,
I would think.
Yeah, well, I like to drive
around sometimes at night.
It clears my head.
Clarity's overrated.
Ramona wouldn't object to you
just having one drink, would she?
Well, maybe just one.
Good.
Ramona trusts you...
A good precedent to
begin one's married life.
Skol.
You've grown older...
even more handsome.
Love agrees with you.
Ramona is
very down to earth...
And nice.
Good.
You, um, you deserve
someone nice.
You weren't very
nice at all.
Just incredibly...
What?
Beautiful.
You still are.
Thank you.
I, uh...
I needed that.
You always did know
exactly what to say.
Sometimes in the dark,
when I'm with her,
I think about you.
I fantasize what my life
would have been like
if I'd come away with you...
If we'd been together.
Listen to me, Matt.
You found something
nice, stable.
So have I...
Beautiful baby boy.
Forget this happened.
Forget you saw me again.
For your sake
and Ramona's, just...
put me out
of your mind.
You can't go.
I won't let you.
I have no choice.
My baby needs help.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Yeah.
We don't need any carpet.
That's very funny,
actually. Um,
no. I wanted to talk to you
guys about something...
a wedding gift.
I'd like you to do
that surgery on Ava's baby.
Did she come to you?
I knew we couldn't
trust that bitch.
She's not a bitch, man.
Her kid's really messed up.
Did you sleep with her?
Matty, Matty, Matty.
She's like a drug to you,
as bad as meth.
The second you're around her,
you start making bad decisions.
Yeah, she seemed so
different, though, you know?
Like being a real mom
softened her or something.
I'm sure she was all
puppy dogs and rainbows
until she casually asked you
to talk to us about the surgery.
Well...
that was my idea.
- No.
That was her idea.
Matt,
you've got a shot at the real
thing here with Ramona...
true happiness
with a great girl.
Ava is just gonna toss you
aside the second
she's done with you.
I'm such an asshole, and
she sucked me right in.
You're not an asshole.
Come on, now.
What you need to do...
is, uh, go home
and get some sleep.
You're getting
married tomorrow.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thanks, guys.
I, uh,
I'm so glad to have you
back in my life.
And I just want
to keep you there.
There are your prescriptions,
pain pills, and antibiotics.
Why should
he get painkillers?
He didn't give
his victims any painkillers.
Allison.
You remember Leena Gold
from Temple?
Yes.
She works with the
Simon Wiesenthal center.
Oh, my God.
Allison,
what have you done?
I decided to call
the OSL in Washington.
Is that part of
the Justice Department?
Yes. And if the evidence
warrants it,
Mr. Krieger,
or whatever his name is,
will hopefully be deported
to stand trial for his crimes.
Mom, I'll take you home,
and then Leena
will stay here with him
and wait for them to come.
I'm not going anywhere.
Fine.
Stay with your Nazi.
He's my husband.
You are not the only
one he has to answer to.
Allison,
Mein Kind,
how are you ever going
to live with yourself?
Come, Allison.
Come, dear.
Where does it come from,
this capacity to forgive?
How do you do it?
How do you not?
Hey!
Hey.
It's quite a party, huh?
Hey, Matty.
You look great.
So...
are you ready for this?
You know what? For the first
time in my life, yeah.
This feels right.
There you are,
Matthew!
Hi.
Uh, Celia, this is my dad
Sean McNamara.
- Oh, hello!
- Hello.
You have
a wonderful home.
Oh, thank you,
Dr. McNamara.
Welcome.
- Come.
- Ok. Uh...
- Hello, hello.
- Hey, Sean.
Where are the kids?
Annie is helping
Ramona to get ready, and...
Connor is playing
with her nephews.
Oh, good.
It's easier to do this
when they're not around.
What is this?
Sean...
Thank you.
Thank you, Sean.
This means so much to me.
Ok. Now we finally got that
out of our systems,
can we please have
some fun around here?
- Uh, yes.
- Let's have some fun.
Ok. Can I suggest
one final...
3-way?
- Oh, come on.
- Oh, no.
I mean this kind of 3-way.
There you go, buddy.
Our son's getting married.
Maybe we did something right
along the way or something like that.
- I'll drink to that.
- Or something.
I know.
Hard to believe.
Sean.
Nip/Subs Team
Seriessub.com