I like my ring, and it came...
from Mike's heart which
is really good...
And I don't think
you really have one.
I do have one.
And...and it belongs to you....
Mike, I just need
you to back up...
All the way to... taking
my ring back?
I love you, Mrs. McNamara.
The key for s'mores is getting
the perfect proportion...
between the chocolate bar to a...
...graham cracker....
- Look at that.
- Nice.
You marry a woman
you don't even know,
who tries to kill you.
I don't need a lecture.
Well, tell us what you don't
like about yourself, Mrs. Pierce.
Well, I guess the fact
that I'm not perfect.
Well, who is?
Barbie.
Is Barbie a friend of yours?
Well, I've worshiped her since
I was a little girl....
- You mean the doll.
- Uh, she's more than a doll.
Barbie and Ken are the
synthetic embodiment...
of the ideal post-modern couple.
Not to mention they've
been together for 50 years,
never aging,
just changing outfits.
Of course, he doesn't
have a penis, and she...
doesn't have anything.
Because they've made the ultimate
monogamous commitment.
A sex-free relationship.
Well, this is all
very interesting,
but, uh... why
exactly are you here?
Show them, Skip.
Skip had his nipples removed,...
one less erogenous zone
for him to think about.
And now, we'd like
you to remove mine.
Look, we're not crazy, ok?
We both very successful realtors.
Even in this market, we sold
more houses last year than...
any other team in
west Los Angeles....
- Honey, let me explain.
- Alright.
My nipples are hard
all the time...
- All the time.
- All the time...
- It's like... it's like...
- It doesn't stop...
big gumdrops on my...
It's embarrassing.
I mean I would like
to know what it's like...
to have someone
look me in the eye...
- ...for once.
- She has a beautiful mind....
- Thank you.
- You too, honey.
So, how did you two meet?
Oh. Well... uh,...
we met at the national doll
collectors convention...
in San Diego 5 years ago.
We've both been obsessed
with Barbie and Ken...
- Obsessed...
- ...since we were little kids, and...
...we just want to take one more step
to becoming more like them.
- That's all.
- It's evolution.
So, what if the two
of you split up?
How would you explain these
modifications to your new partners?
We've both had tons
of sexual relationsips...
Tons.
And they always ended up
being about...
ownership and exclusivity,...
not about love.
Eliminating sex allows us
to really relate.
We get to see each other outside
of our own selfish demands.
Think about it.
If Barbie and Ken had
been able to have sex,...
do you really think their marriage
would have lasted 50 years?
Nip/Subs Team
presents
Season 6 - Episode 8
"Lola Wlodkowski"
Original VO: Ladyhawk
Corrections & Resynchro VO : Sean
Excuse me. Can you tell me where
I might find a Dr. McNamara?
I have a package for him.
You found him. Just put it right
here on the desk, please.
Sign here, please.
Thank you, Doctor.
You're welcome.
Aren't you gonna open it?
Okay.
Ok, what uh...
Uh...what is this?
Hold on a second.
What are you doing?
Helping you with your package.
Hey, Sean, your 2 o'clock...
Mrs. Cox, please...
We can still fit you in.
Thank you. I think
I've seen enough.
Did you want to finish?
Finish what?
Who are you?
Where did you come from?
Boy, you are grumpy.
No wonder Dr. Troy wanted
me to cheer you up.
Did you have anything
to do with this?
Is she still here? I didn't get
a chance to see her in person,
but the agency
told me she was a 10.
What the hell are you doing,
calling a stripper to the office?
A stripper? Sean, I
wouldn't do that to you.
She's a hooker...
- You bought me a prostitute?
- Of course I did....
What the hell's wrong with you?
You've been wallowing in misery
ever since Julia took the kids to New York.
I was just trying to
make you feel better.
Cheap sex is not what
I need right now.
In fact, I'm not interested in
any kind of sex right now.
I'm thinking about
taking a break....
- A break from sex.
- What's' wrong with that?
Well, nothing, if you
want to be a priest...
or just wallow in your mid-life
self-pitying crisis bullshit.
- It is not 'self-pity, it's self-preservation, ok?
- Alright.
The last time I jumped into bed
with someone after Julia,
I wound up with Teddy.
And after that, with some...
drug addict stabbing
me in the leg.
Which is why I thought
I should pick this time.
Alright?
You know...
maybe Tracy...
had a point.
More often than not,
sex ruins relationships.
And that's what messed up
me and Julia his time.
That's what's complicated almost
every relationship I've ever had.
I appreciate your concern
for me.
Next time put it in a card.
Thank you
Oh, I ate too much.
Oh, thanks for the surprise
tonight, sweetie...
- Ok? I'll call you later.
- Wait. Honestly.
Have I gained weight since we
started dating?
Sweetheart, you look fantastic.
Trust me,... Gotta go.
I am a little freaked
out about this.
I mean, just answer me honestly.
Do I need to start
smoking again?
Kimber
Christian
- Yes.
- This is my friend Lola.
Hey.
So, uh... you two go
wait in my office.
I'll be in in a second.
She's got a problem. Ok?
Not you.
Sometimes I feel
that's how I look.
So,...
you're uh...
Lola...
- Wolad...
- Wlodkowski.
Wlodkowski....
- What are you grinning at?
- I'm just...
I'm just real happy for you.
Is that so bad?
Happy for what?
You know...
He's a bit of an idiot, but he is
a very good surgeon....
- Ok.
- We're friends. Lola is not gay.
Me? No. Please.
I am a card-carrying hetero.
Although... Liz would
be the first girl
I'd call if I was so inclined.
Yeah, we met at
Adam and Eve's.
I've been going there
since I was a kid.
The nudist camp?
Lizzie.
Who knew?
I was looking for something to
help me love myself again...
after my divorce.
Sure....
- So, how can we help you?
- She needs her moles removed.
I noticed them at the pool,
and she came over to me...
all on her high horse,
gonna tell me that...
Yeah, well, she was staring,
which we do not we do.
But it's common
with the nubees.
They get all distracted
by genitals...
and... all the bare flesh.
In any case, I told
her that you would...
removed them with no
scar and that...
you would have give her
a significant discount...
because she has no insurance.
Of course.
You know that any...
friend of Lizzie's
is a friend of ours.
In fact, because you're such a
good friend, we'll just...
throw in some free lipo....
- You mean to make me skinny?
- Um hmm.
You know...
I just figured, you know, you're
walking around nude all the time.
Maybe you just want to streamline
your silhouette a little bit...
- Oh, my God.
- I didn't mean any...
No, I am not insulted,
Liz, not insulted.
He is just a victim of
his self-loathing, really.
Thanks, Doctor. But um...
I'll pass on the lipo.
I'm fine with the way I am...
You know, maybe you should come
up to Adam and Eve sometime.
People discover all sorts of
things about themselves.
It's hard to keep the secrets
when you're naked.
Alright, I have no problem
getting naked.
Oh, well, social nudity is
something else.
It requires dropping facades
and pretentions.
You've never had a really
big woman, have you, Doc?
Do I make you nervous?
Nervous?
No. I...
Not a bit.
You're quite a lotta gal, Lola.
Not too much gal for you?
Now, some men just aren't
ready for me...
and I am not just
talking about the pounds.
Hey, you two...
Is it time to get a room?
Uh... no.
But I think it's time we took a
look at those moles.
Mrs. Pierce...
Before we get started, I'd like you
to look over these consent forms.
It's to remind you that
this is an elective surgery...
and you're aware of the risks.
Skip already told me what to
expect. I'm not concerned.
I'm excited, actually.
Now, are you planning
to have kids?
Because if you're
hoping to breastfeed...
Oh, I can't have children.
Ken and Barbie never did, so...
Of course.
If you would open your robe?
And you promise there
won't be scarring?
Ah, yeah.
Um, that's why I want to
put you under anesthesia
Z-plasties will stop any
keloids from forming.
Stop trying to impress me
with the details, Dr. Sexy....
I just want to know
I get my body back.
If you want to get
your body back,...
try 20 minutes on the
treadmill every day.
Those gerbil wheels?
Please.
I get enough exercise
in the bedroom,
thank you very much.
You don't glow like
this if you're not...
having great sex
five times a week.
Believe you me...
- That tickles.
- Sorry.
That's ok.
I've always been sensitive.
Well, dermal nerve networks
and concentrations...
of tissue around the
ducts along with...
minute hair follicles in
the areola itself, all contribute...
to the area's hypersensitivity.
Which is a fancy
way of saying...
your nipples... Our...
nipples were designed
for pleasure.
Well, you've never
worn a bra before.
They have seen their
share of pleasure...
over the years.
It'll be a relief
to have them gone.
So you're not really interested
in sex anymore?
Let me tell you something.
When you don't have
to worry about it anymore...
you realize how much
more there is to life.
I thought being nudist wasn't
about having sex all the time.
It's not. I'm talking about
my life outside the fold.
Really?
So between that and
doing life...
you basically never have
your clothes on.
Well...
It is how God made us.
Some are better than others, huh?
Sorry to be blunt, Lola.
You're not my type.
You go for the more shallow,
superficial dates.
You poor man.
You have no idea what you're
missing, do you?
Don't you worry about
what you'll be missing?
- Sex wise?
- Yeah.
I mean, it's not like it's
a big mystery anymore.
Two people kiss...
tongues touch...
hands rub the same parts...
Maybe they pinch and grab...
Maybe they smack an
ass cheek or two...
Someone gets hard,
someone gets wet,
you trade some fluids...
then it's all about
the in and the out,
and the up and the down...
Someone screams, 'Oh, baby, yes'
or 'Oh, God, please' and then...
Poof.
It's done.
Yeah, you put it like that,
I guess I see your point.
Trust me.
I'm celebate...
and I've never been happier.
That was the best orgasm
I've ever had.
Liz is going to put you into
uh... twilight.
That sounds delightful.
Yeah. And no scars, I promise.
I'm good at that.
You're good at a lot of things.
I'd put you in the top
6 or 7 percentile.
Just say it.
I'm a scumbag, pussy-crazed dog,
and I should be shot.
Get over yourself.
I'm not your priest.
This woman is a force of nature,
you know that? I mean...
she don't take no
for an answer.
Yeah. Well, as usual...
you got it wrong.
I am delighted.
What? That I had sex
with a fat chick?
No, because you
couldn't get to her.
You're right.
You know what? You could take a
page out of her book.
She and living proof that
beauty is not everything.
You know
what I'm saying?
I mean, it's how you
feel on the inside....
- Right?
- Wait.
You do something shitty and then
you rub my face in it?
And because
I don't fall apart,...
you give me a lecture on
what's wrong with me?
You're an idiot,
you know that.
Send these to Pathology.
You're right,
I was out of line.
Yeah, well save it for
someone who cares...
the other idiot, Kimber.
She actually believes
that the two of you are gonna...
walk into the monogamous...
Ken and Barbie sunset together.
God bless her.
Oh my God... seriously?
I'm... I'm gonna wet myself.
Look at this.
Fiber...
Hoodia...
Appetite suppressants...
Oh, yeah, here.
This and my favorite one...
This sucks the fats
out of the food...
and then leaks it
out of your colon.
I have been killing
myself to stay a size 0...
while you're off discovering
your inner chubby chaser.
She wasn't... all that fat.
Oh honey, I saw her. You needed
MapQuest to find her vagina.
But what you don't understand
is... this is great.
Like, I'm happy. I can
finally just... relax.
We... Now I know......
we're still gonna be having
sex when we're old and fat...
Where you going?
I'm gonna go raid your
freezer because...
I swear I saw some Cherry Garcia
in there and I've never had it.
Come on, baby...
Dive into your diva.
Timber -- here comes Kimber.
Left...
Are you watching?
Wait...hold...hang...
hang on, stop.
It...I'm sorry, it hurts me.
Alright, I'll get two spoons and
fudge sauce, I'll be right back.
Stay right here,
I'll be right back.
- I promise.
- Take your time.
Found it.
Wow, this is really good.
Here.
I've got you a spoon.
Come on.
Let's get fat.
You two seem very happy together.
Of course. He's my
fantasy come true.
Wouldn't you be?
Honey, I'm home.
Darling.
Let me get that for you.
You had a hard day,
Come in and relax.
What's that smell?
I made your favorite --
roast chicken.
Leg or breast tonight, honey?...
- How about both?
- Oh, you're so silly....
- Are you okay?
- Huh? Oh, fine.
Just tired.
I understand, let's go to bed....
- 'Night.
Oh, your hand...
- It's so soft.
- It's my new lotion.
Honey, what if we push the
beds together tonight?
We've never done that before.
Something wrong, Sean?
I was talking with Christian
at the office today...
and he mentioned something
to me about blowjobs.
And well...
it sounded like fun.
You mean putting your
penis in my mouth?...
- Isn't that sex?
- Not from what I understand.
I thought we should try it.
Okay, as long as it's not sex.
I guess you should pull
down your pants first....
What?
No wonder we've never
done this before...
Look.
Are you okay?
Fine.
I hope he's happy.
She's a perfect doll now....
- Have you seen my patient?
- Ah, yeah.
I saw way too much.
She said her stomach
was grumbling.
Oh, Jesus...
You'll blind someone.
Do you have a pannini press?
'cause I would kill for a
grilled ham and cheese.
This is not your personal feeding trough,
and it's not Adam and Eve either. Here.
Put this on, until
I find you a tent.
Well I'm...sorry. I just...I'm so
used to being in the buff...
Yeah, well we don't need to see
your flabby flesh around here.
Oh, I guess you thought
you were dreaming when...
we humped like bunnies
in your exam room?
Bunnies? I remember
riding an elephant.
And then I got stuck
in an overgrown bush.
Why would I give a shit
what you think?
You're just a shallow asshole
whose in denial of the fact that...
some day you're gonna wake up
and be fat, sagging and ugly.
I am an asshole, and
maybe one day...
I will wake up fat,
saggy and ugly.
But right now, I am
embracing beauty.
And beauty is happiness,
beauty is power...
beauty is confidence.
And don't tell me
you don't agree.
It's time to go back
to the watering hole,
hungry hippo.
You... are checking out.
Yeah?...
- You got a sec?
- Yeah. Actually, I was just...
thinking about coming
over to apologize.
Um... I was...
was harsh, and... and you didn't
deserve it, and...
I had a... a really
fun time with you.
Ok, enough.
I liked you better
when you were honest.
Do you like being
called a hippo?
It was interesting...
Bracing.
And then uh...
it made me see something.
I screwed up.
Why?
Well, half the battle with
self-acceptance is...
acting as if you feel it
even when you don't.
And I have become a
really good actress.
I have all the right words,
and the right moves and...
it works most of the time...
but... every now and then, I
want to crawl away and hide.
Like...
when I... get a bad
crush on a guy...
and... I know I'm never
gonna be in the running.
That's when I do something
bold and defiant.
Like walking around
the office naked?
Yeah.
Look, I am not stupid
And I'm not blind.
I'm just a gorgeous, sexy woman
who's trapped in a fat body.
And I was raised to
think that it's...
a sin to love myself...
any other way but the way I am.
Please, you're not
gonna turn into some...
self-hating person now, are you?
I want to know what it feels
like... not to pretend...
I don't care about
what people think.
I am tired of...
working so hard
at this self-acceptance.
So, be honest with me.
What will it take?
Lipo or... a tummy tuck?
Both.
I didn't think you'd
be out of bed so soon.
Oh, look. I've never been
able to do this before.
No more gumdrops.
Smooth.
Just like Barbie now.
Want to have a seat on the bed?
I'll check those stitches.
You did such great work.
I can't wait for Skip to see them.
He's going to love them.
Yeah.
What's wrong? I didn't pull
a stitch or anything, did... ?
No, no, no. The surgery's fine.
It's just...
What?
I spent my whole career
trying to make...
women's breasts look
more attractive... youthful...
so their husbands or boyfriends
will notice them again.
And here you are with this
perfect, natural set, and...
you're happy because I've
completely desexualized you.
It's okay if you
do not understand.
Most people don't.
Well, I think I do
understand...
- And... I think it is very sad.
- What are you talking about?
I had a moment
where I imagined...
what it would be like
to give up sex...
to have that kind of
relationship when...
you don't touch each
other, and it...
It what?
It isn't natural.
You're not just denying
the act of sex...
You're denying
intimacy, passion...
Skip and I are intimate.
We just...
choose not to be
physical about it.
But how can you choose to give up
that feeling you get when your skin...
makes contact with someone else's
and that charge just...
runs through your whole body,...
like every nerve inside
you just caught fire.
I mean, the way
you described it...
hands grabbing, smacking...
That's about passion, fire.
And you're not trying
to catch your breath.
You are trying to
inhale someone else's.
And it's complicated...
it's messy...
But I say every minute of the
pleasure is worth...
the pain it might bring later
because nothing on this Earth...
can make two people
feel that good.
Lizzie, would you
give me a break.
Lola, came to me and
asked me for lipo.
You reduced a strong, proud woman
into a self-loathing wallflower.
No, I did not. All I did was
help her open open eyes.
You didn't help
her out, Christian.
You broke her will....
- I did not.
- And why?
All because you're
not man enough...
to admit that you had a mind
boggling orgasm with a fat girl.
And you discovered someone
who has beauty...
on the inside and it
scared you, and why?
Because you, underneath
that shell...
that handsome shell, is nothing.
And the only thing you can do
to make yourself feel better,...
is pull people down into
your own personal little hell...
- Ok, feel better?
- Yeah, I feel better...
And you know what?
Even better yet.
I'm not doing the surgery.
- Hi, Liz.
- Hey, Jack...
- Liz.
- Hi Javier...
- Liz...
- Hi...Hi, Kyle.
Lizzie is throwing another fit.
We need to find
another replacement....
What's going on?
Nothing. It's gonna be fine.
Don't you worry.
Lola?
Hey, guys.
What are you doing here?
Saving your beautiful ass.
Take that gown off because...
we're taking you out of here.
What the hell are you doing here?
You can't come in here.
Get the hell out of here.
Alright, you put the scalpel down
and nobody gets hurt.
You're kidnapping her?
Plastic surgery steals
a person's humanity.
Look, fellas, I...I just want
to shed a few pounds.
We won't let you do this.
We love you exactly
the way you are.
Hey, if you want to keep ignoring
the world we live in, be my guest.
That's the difference
between us, doctor.
We don't live in your world.
We live someplace happier.
I'm sorry.
Are you sure they never make any
mistakes on these biopsies?
Look, it's not a death sentence.
We can...
remove the tumor,
get rid of all the...
tissue surrounding it so that
the melanoma cells are gone.
We can... do chemo,
follow up by radiation.
We?
You can beat this.
I did.
Chemo...
Well, that could be the
best diet ever, right?
I'll be a thin girl yet.
My mother would be so proud.
Beautiful on the outside...
scarred and cancerous
on the inside.
Lola, you're beautiful.
You will always be beautiful,
cancer or no cancer.
You're pathetic.
I didn't know you were gonna
be home so soon...
You weren't supposed
to see that.
Yeah, well I did...
I can clean up after myself.
No, that's fine. It'll stop
me from strangling you.
I just wanted to try
some of the things...
that I've always
been afraid to eat.
Don't tell me that's
the first time...
you shoved your fingers
down your throat.
No, it's not, but
it's the first time
I've had pepperoni pizza...
Listen, just explain
something to me.
Is this little experiment
over or not? Ok?
Because I don't do fat, and I don't do
whatever the hell it was in there
when you were
throwing up, alright?
which night I come
home. Understand?
You know, when I was in
there, I was thinking...
that...
I truly hate myself.
And... it's the reason why
I always go back to you,
Christian, is because you
hate me the best...
and, for some reason,
it just feels right.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Go to brush your
teeth. Get some mints.
I have.
Look at me.
Turn around and look at me.
Why are you with me, Christian?
You think I'm stupid.
You think I am a slut.
You think I'm pathetic.
It's so clear to me now.
You hate yourself like I do.
And that's why you always
come back to me...
because you think I am
all you deserve.
You were wrong about
the stupid part.
That was pretty smart.
Now go get dressed.
I need some dinner.
So we'll put that on the books
and see you next week.
And, again, thank you
for understanding...
about that silly
little office prank.
Yes. Well, now that I've
met you, I can see...
you're not the type to
engage in that sort of thing.
Bye.
Dr. McNamara.
I need to talk to you.
Skip.
Uh... I'm very busy right now.
- If you'd ike to make an appointment...
- Tracy told me what happened.
Let's step into my office.
I'm not upset.
In fact, I'm...
I couldn't be more relieved.
I wanted to thank you...
- Thank me.
- Yeah.
It was bound to happen to
one of us, sooner or later,...
and I'm glad it finally did
because...
it...it helped me to finally
deal with who I really am.
You mean you don't want to pretend
that you're a doll anymore?
No. No, no, I still see
myself as a model of Ken.
No, I meant that I can...
finally admit that I'm gay.
Joe,
would you like
to meet the doctor?
Nice to meet you, sir.
Joe's been a
"Don't ask, don't tell"...
member on the army since '97.
And... an avid doll
enthusiast like myself.
Skip and I have known
each other for years...
only we could never
admit how we really felt.
Now that we're together...
we're gonna explore
the new postmodern...
version of a real relationship.
One that makes sense for us.
You mean...
- between Ken and G.I. Joe?
- See? I told you he'd get it.
Don't tell me you're here to
have your nipples removed.
No, no, no.
Calf implants...
"Anatomically correct"
is our motto.
Wow.
- Nice pad.
- Do you like it?
You really live the life, huh?...
- Do you want something to drink?
- I would love a drink.
Hey. Hi, Sean.
That's Kimber.
Looks like you're having fun.
Oh, yeah. Someone back there
is getting a little hungry.
Hey, Sean.
Tracy, what are you doing here?
I love your Malibu beach house.
It could use some color,
but it's really quite lovely.
I'm sorry about Skip.
No, you're not.
Neither am I.
I just can't believe I couldn't
see who he was really was...
even with all the pink
cardigans and perfect hair.
Kimmy, won't all that
sugar make me fat?
Oh, God, no. This
is for Christian.
But I'm gonna get you
some ice cubes.
- But I don't have any nipples.
- Well, you have a lot to learn.
The body has thousands of
sensitive spots...
and we're just gonna have
to work to find yours.
Strawberries.
Come on, ladies, ladies.
Come on.
Gabfest is over.
Sean... how's it hanging, baby?
You're beautiful, ladies.
Ready to get back to business?
Keep those strawberries chilled.
What's Tracy doing here?
I'm sorry, buddy, but
two Barbies are...
better than one. You
know what I'm saying?...
Don't I know you
from somewhere?
I'm the delivery
girl from last week.
I love hookers.
Right?
You can pay 'em to be
whoever you want 'em to be.
Have fun.
Ladies.
Ha ha ha.
Who do you want to be, Sean?
You know...
Tonight I think you should
just be yourself.
Maybe it's you who wants to
be somebody else.
I've 'done it
that way too before...
- Ok.
- Good.
So, who do you want to be?
I don't know.
Someone else.
Nip/Subs Team
Seriessub.com