Previously on Nip/Tuck...
You know how they say when you find your Bliss
is when the Money starts rolling in?
Mine is so amazing, man.
It takes us beyond our petty egos,
beyond language and unifies us.
Either pay your share
of the rent by sundown
or you can sleep on the beach
with all the other freaks.
Daddy, my stomach!
It hurts so much.
It's an intestinal condition,
resulting from the consumption of hair.
what?!
Annie, how did this happen?
I just pull it out. That's all.
Dixie, is that you?
Oh, you look fantastic as a brunette.
No, I'm Teddy.
Teddy Row.
I need you to stay still
Mrs. Reinhold.
- We eloped 2 days ago.
- Is this a joke?
Just spit it out.
You don't like her? I don't care.
I just hope you didn't put
any of your stuff in her name.
Maybe it's better you weren't there.
"Make sure she can't touch your money"
would have been a lousy toast.
I am doubling my life insurance policy.
Making Connor and Annie sole
beneficiaries.
what if Annie stayed with us
For a couple of months?
Connor can come out too.
I have worked too hard
to leave my family with nothing.
You're up early.
It's almost 11:00.
Do we have any coffee?
mm-hmm.
I saved you some of the paper.
It's the "help wanted" section.
About time you got a real job.
- What's this?
- It's $850.
Or as you and Christian
like to call it: rent.
I have a real job.
That's 2 months in a row
I've made now.
Oh, wait a second.
Did I hear you say you're paying the rent
without another threat of homelessness?
Give me a look at this stuff.
Smell likes real money.
Looks like real money.
of course it's real.
And Here. Here's a little extra.
Why don't you get some real
coffee around here from now on? This stuff sucks.
where'd you get all this money?
where do you think?
From practicing my craft.
Craft?
You mean miming?
that's right.
I heard about you!
The mime robbing people.
You don't scare me!
Let me get this straight:
People actually pay
to see you perform?
Yeah. Mimes are back,
Christian in a big way.
Thanks to you two,
all the greats are being rediscovered:
Marcel Marceau,
Shields et Yarnell.
I'm just carrying on the tradition.
well, you must be pretty good
if you're getting paid like this.
I am.
I make enough to pay my rent
and support my child.
Please let me see her on saturday.
I was going to take her to the Pier.
Forget it dead beat dad.
You know, you are 5 months
behind on your child support.
I'm working my fingers to the
bone to pay for her childcare.
No. I'm sorry, I pay for everything.
So, you consider
this your last visit
until you pay up.
Here.
I'll pick her up at 9:00 A.M.
You make sure she's ready.
Am I clear?
where did you get this cash?
- we should come see you perform.
- That's a good idea.
You just Stand on the venice
boardwalk, right?
- You don't have to do that.
- We're proud of you, Matt.
I mean it seems like you finally
found something you really like doing.
And you're making money,
which I'm very impressed with.
Even if you are a clown.
Mimes aren't clowns.
I'm an artist.
we just want to show
our support.
You know, we can come down,
all get lunch together
and make a day of it.
Look, I don't want you to.
Ok?
Look, you guys have never supported me.
Not once.
I don't need you to start now.
I mean, really man.
Isn't the money enough?
Nip/Subs Team
presents
Season 6 - Episode 4
"Jenny Juggs"
Original VO: www.addic7ed.com
Original VO: honeybunny
Correction & Resynchro VO : Sean
They've expired. It's a waste.
We don't need this much lidocaine, all right.
We should just cut back
until things pick up.
We just cut back on
the epinephrine and the atropine.
I don't want to risk not having
what we need in case of an emergency.
What about the Pre-filled
syringes--
Outdated. All of it, ok?
It's money just thrown away.
I mean, maybe with the rent
going up on the malibu house,
we should just do surgeries there,
we'd save a bundle.
you know,
I should just tell you:
Teddy's place sold.
And we made an offer
on a really great place we saw,
Santa Monica adjacent.
well, that's great.
I mean, I'm fine.
I'll be fine. You know.
I'm not gonna let rent get in
the way of you moving on with your life.
I think it's great.
whoo. I gotta go.
so, when's Connor's flight get in?
uh, 11:10.
I can't wait for Teddy to meet
the little guy.
You know, she's really excited about
becoming a part of this whole new family.
I guess that doesn't include me
because she doesn't give a
shit about getting to know me.
you just have to give it a little time.
You guys got off to a rocky start.
You didn't like her from the beginning.
You know...
Teddy is planning a little family
brunch to welcome Connor to L.A.
- Why don't you come?
- you know, maybe later.
She Should--she should get to know
the kids first.
one more.
Bad day, doc?
Bad year.
Don't mean to make it any worse.
But, uh, you need to close out your tab.
It's been a couple of months now.
Boss has been on me about it.
when's the boss gonna get
some new talent around here?
I mean, these old whores are
getting tired.
couple of new girls on a
break right now.
One of 'em is kinda skinny.
But the other one...
Right up your alley.
A huge talent.
Juggernaut talent, truthfully.
what's her name?
Jenny.
Jenny Juggs.
Well, why don't you run along
And tell Jenny Juggs
to brush her teeth and
meet me in the V.I.P. Room?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll pay the tab before I go.
Are those real?
ahh. No touching.
No touching. No, no.
You like my boobies?
Yeah.
You do don't you.
'cause you're a very nasty
little boy.
Just a little feel?
I mean, I gotta see if
those babies are real, huh? Huh?
did you hear me?
This is not the goddamn farmers market,
you pervert,
You can't go squeezing the melons.
Get the hell off me!
This is bullshit. Freak.
I'm not paying for this.
I'm not a hooker,
I'm a performer.
you got some delusions of
Grandma sister!
I'm sorry.
I'm very Sorry. Ok?
This is my first day.
I'm a little defensive.
Ok?
I'll be nice, ok?
I'm sorry.
I'll let you touch 'em.
You want to touch 'em?
you know what, sweetcheeks?
I'm over it.
But my name's Dr. Christian Troy.
I'm a plastic Surgeon.
You should call me, all right?
So I can do something with
these gravity bags.
They must be killing your back.
I deserved that.
Ok.
I totally deserved that.
Just stay.
Don't get me fired.
And I'll let you touch 'em.
And you'll like it a lot
You want to do that?
Yeah. Put your face right
in the middle of them.
How do you like them gravity
bags, shitface?!
Are you going to eat those
eggs or make a sculpture of them?
I don't eat unborn chickens.
This is an unfertilized globule
of albumen and protein.
It comes out of the same opening
that a chicken poops out of.
Once the mother hen lays it,
she promptly runs away
with great relief:
this egg is never going
to be a chicken.
It is never going to feel pain.
And it is never going
to have a soul.
Now eat.
I'm not hungry.
Perhaps mademoiselle McNamara
would enjoy her eggs more
if there was a hunk of hair
mixed in.
Hello!
Anybody home?
Aww.
This must be Connor.
He's a little shy with
new people.
Maybe he just senses evil.
Annie, for god sake!
She been giving you a hard time?
She's a 13 year old.
It's her job.
I wish I had your patience.
Well, you were never a Teenage girl.
Lucky me.
Connor, this is Teddy.
Hey.
You're so handsome.
Just like your dad.
Wow.
You sure have a way with him.
Annie, you want to drop the
attitude for 5 minutes
and try to be a part
of this family?
she's not my family.
She's right.
I am the monster
Who dared have her sit
and eat some eggs.
Anytime I exert
any authority over her,
she thinks I'm trying
to take the place of her mom.
You know, I was thinking...
Maybe we could just start over.
You know, get to know each other
in a new environment where there
aren't so many memories.
Go some place together.
You mean like a family
vacation?
Sounds like fun.
You know, Connor's
never been to Disneyland.
Disneyland blows.
Disney World's twice as good.
Only half as many people
get hurt each year.
I'm with Annie on this one.
Disneyland does blow.
I was thinking more
along the lines of something
kind of... adventurous.
Like a camping trip.
camping?
Like in the outdoors?
Yeah.
Like in the outdoors.
Well, that sounds great.
It'd be something new,
wouldn't it?
I think it's a fantastic idea.
Shake things up a bit,
Give us all a chance to connect
in a new way.
Honey, give her a chance, ok?
For me.
Sounds to me you like you had
it coming.
when I go to a strip club,
I'm paying to objectify women.
That's the whole goddamn point.
It's the only place this side of Bangkok,
where a man can actually act like a man.
I'm not letting Jenny Juggs
ruin our last man oasis.
Still, you probably shouldn't
have said what you said.
I should have said
something much worse.
The only reason she's working there is so she can
get rid of her angry feminist agenda bullshit.
She's a tit terrorist.
She's Valerie solanas with beach balls.
Valerie who?
Famous man-hater who shot
Warhol.
I don't understand.
She punched you in the face with her breasts?
Yes! She punched me in the
face with her breasts.
And I'm not...
It's not funny.
I'm not the only one,
there are other victims.
You can come and take a look.
I'm serious.
It's not... Come here, I'll show you.
You think you're
so scary don't ya?
Those things must weigh
50 pounds.
Glaring at us women,
smiling...
she's talking to a pumpkin.
I said stop Smiling!
You want my tricks and treats?
Well, I'm here to tell you
I am no man's trick.
And that is the only treat
that you deserve.
A lesson in how to
treat women.
- You see? Those are deadly weapons.
- what are you going to do?
I'm gonna have her arrested
for assault and battery.
She needs to be taught a lesson.
She needs to learn that
crime doesn't pay.
You see,
this is a great app.
You can alter photographs,
I look kind of sad here.
So I swipe it.
And I'm smiling.
That's cool.
I need to see Dr. Troy
right away.
Do you have an appointment?
No. But I need to talk to him
today as soon as possible.
ok. Well, why don't you just
take a seat.
And what's your name?
Jennifer Juggs. Ok?
And I'm not leaving
until I see him.
All right, well, she's gonna call
the doctor. You go take a seat.
I just have his voicemail--
Dr. Troy, I just barely
made bail
after spending the whole night
in a freakin' cell!
I just lost
my freakin' job too!
ok--all right. Take a seat or
I'll call security.
you obviously don't know who
you're talking to.
clearly a person with poor
people skills.
People skills?
Want to see some people skills?
Are you the world's most
self-destructive woman or what?
I know, ok?
I know. I know.
I have rage issues.
But that's why I'm here.
I'll pay for your phone,
Dr. Troy.
I just need some help.
Damn right you need some help.
Dr. Epstein is just down
the hallway.
He's a very well respected shrink.
He deals with...
you know...
body image issues.
It's so much bigger than that.
What color are my eyes?
I don't know.
They're blue!
And they're really pretty!
But no one's ever gonna know that.
All they know is my juggs
is gigantic.
If you ask anyone
in my 10th grade class,
what they remember
about Jenny Jarvis...
First, they'll laugh uncomfortably.
And then they'll say:
"her humungous tits."
And that's it.
'cause that's who I am.
And that's all I'll ever be.
I need you to give me
a breast reduction.
Why would you work at
a strip club, huh?
It's the one place where people actually
pay to look at your breasts.
It's a little counter-intuitive,
don't you think?
what else am I gonna do?
You gonna hire me to be
you receptionist?
sweetheart after what you've
done to my t-2 and my telephone,
I don't think I'm the right guy
to be asking.
I know that I seem a little
bitter and angry.
I need you to believe me that
I have really tried
to embrace myself.
I've tried to do some
standup comedy
and some performance art.
Is that what you call
those videos?
Comedy and performance art?
You are a sick, angry person.
You need to be taught a lesson.
I thought you were a doctor,
and I thought
that you would want to heal me
instead of trying to punish me.
Ok.
Can I get a little help?
I've got mess kits,
4 sleeping bags,
coleman lamp, and other
odds and ends.
Annie doesn't want to go.
I'll bring all this stuff back.
Is it bugs?
Her allergies?
well, I told her about
the camper,
that she'd have her own bed.
I made it sound like the 4 seasons.
Sean, you're a great dad.
But you don't ask a 13 year old
to go on a trip,
you tell her.
I know. I know.
It's just that I don't see
her very often.
So, yeah. I indulge her more
than I should.
Annie's never gonna respect you
if she knows she can manipulate you.
You know, kids need limits.
Do you want to be
her father or her mark?
Why don't you do this:
How about you and Christian,
you go see Matt's mime thingy.
And I will talk to her.
That could backfire.
She hasn't been able to accept you.
I mean, us.
We really should have had some
kind of ceremony.
I could have invited Annie and Connor
and made them a part of it.
You terrible, horrible,
horrible man you.
Thinking of yourself for once.
It'll be ok.
I promise I'll talk to her.
I love you, Mrs. Mcnamara.
Do you know that?
You want to walk back again?
Maybe he was on a break.
You kidding me.
Go past all these freaks again?
The whole place smells
like patchouli.
Hey, excuse me.
- You normally work down here?
- Every day, bro.
Is there a section where
we might find a mime?
A mime?
A mime, you know, they do
the whole "I'm in a box" thing.
He's got dark hair.
His name is Matt.
Yeah, there's no mimes on
this boardwalk man.
At least not anymore.
I mean, there used
to be a bunch, man.
- But now, like--
- Now what?
Well, ever since that one started
doing all those Robberies, man,
they all just Sort of like,
disappeared, you know.
What robberies?
Some dude dressed as a mime
has been jacking people at gun point.
Happened like 5 times, so
the cops started rounding up
all the mime's on the boardwalk
for questioning recently.
Now, they're all gone.
Since when?
A week.
Which is great for me, man,
because more business!
Hey, how much do you make in a day?
On a good weekend like, uh,
I don't know...
Like 40, 50 bucks man, easily.
40, 50 bucks.
Yeah.
That's it?
Dude, that's tax free, man.
How much did Matt give you
for the rent?
Almost 900 bucks.
Annie?
I'd like to talk to you.
Hey, there.
I just wanted
to let you know that I Understand
what you're going through.
You know, feeling betrayed,
self conscious,
certain that no one likes you.
I didn't say you could come in.
I wasn't aware that I needed permission
to enter and exit in my own home.
- Fine. I'll go back to my mom's.
- Will you?
See you're mom is just
as worried about you as we are.
That's why she sent you here.
We all agree that you need help.
you're so full of it.
I don't believe anything you say.
"Distrustful of others."
I forgot that one. I'm going to have
to add it to the list.
what list?
The symptoms list on
the admissions form.
Annie,
you're not alone,
there are thousands Of girls just like you.
Hair eaters,
skin cutters,
self starving manic
depressives.
They've all managed to get help
at places
like discovery ranch.
No, really. Just google
"mentally disturbed teenage girls"
You'll see.
There are More resident centers
than motel 6s.
We'll find the right one for you.
my dad will never--
You daddy is not always going
to be around to protect you.
And you're not always going to
be daddy's little girl.
Here's a Big secret, Annie:
He's a man Just like
every other man.
You can't count on him.
In fact, he's already pretty
fed up with you.
For god's sake he had to pull
a pound of hair out of your stomach.
But it's up to you.
Wait!
What do I have to do?
what do you think?
Any of these bozos look familiar
to you, Mrs. Park?
Hmmm.
I don't know,
they all look the same to me.
Number 5 is 6'5".
You don't remember if the mime
who held you up is 6'5"?
- It happened very fast.
- And he didn't say a word?
All he did was that mime shit.
Ok, gentleman, here's
the drill:
You're each going to step
forward one at a time
pretend your holding a gun to
somebody's face.
Number 1, you're first.
No, that's not him.
Your turn number 2.
That look like little Joe on
Bonanza.
Number 3.
All right, all right, all right
guys. Come on.
Let's just keep this simple.
Number 4, it's your turn.
No. That's not him either.
And it's not the bald one.
My mime had hair.
- you sure he wasn't wearing a wig?
- No. No. None of these guys are right.
Round up some more mimes
and give me a call.
All right, fellas you can go home.
This is bullshit!
I can't believe you guys
are accusing me of this. I'm your son.
which is why we know this kind of thing
isn't out of character for you!
You've gone from a little shit
to a piece of shit, Matt.
you know what?
I don't need to listen to this.
You sit!
I found this in your bedroom.
You're going through my stuff now?
What is this? Malibu or Moscow?
Where'd you get the money, Matt?
- From miming!
- Bullshit!
You get 20 bucks for walking
against the wind?!
Yeah. Sometimes.
I'm good. I told you.
- Or is that so hard for you to believe?
- We went down to venice and you weren't there.
That's because I moved over
to the promenade.
There are more Europeans there. Where
the hell do you think I get all the 20s from?
It's like 2 bucks to them.
Put yourself in our shoes.
There's over $3,000 here.
From miming?!
You guys really think I did it.
My own fathers.
That's--
That's just great. Hold on.
"Albert chavies. Detective.
Pacific division."
- What is this?
- He's the cop investigating the mime crimes.
He gave me his card after the
line up yesterday.
- You were in a line up?
- Yeah.
And the eye witness cleared me
as a suspect.
You can call him if you want to.
Oh, and congratulations by the way.
You both are getting what you wanted:
I'm moving out.
All right, buddy. Here we go.
Now the trick here is to hold it
just far enough away till it
gets a little brown.
But you don't want it
to catch on fire.
The key to the 'smores
is getting the perfect
proportion
between the, uh, chocolate bar
to Graham cracker.
Think that's brown enough?
Me too.
I think we're ready.
Ok.
Ooh.
- Here you go.
- Oh, look at that.
Look how good that looks!
Come here sit down.
I think yours is ready.
Goody!
You know why they call it
a 'smore, don't you?
It's because the 'smore you eat
the 'smore you want.
Maybe they should call 'em
barf bags.
well?
At least it keeps the bugs
away.
All right.
My turn.
Ooh, let the professional
handle this one.
Don't shortchange me on the
gooey stuff. Ok?
I won't.
There you go.
Look at that. Look at that.
Nice.
I'm gonna get some water.
can you fill the canteen for
me, please?
I think she's
warming up to me.
what are you doing out of bed?
You just had a huge surgery.
Didn't somebody bring you
a bedpan?
she forgets to empty it.
well, that will not do.
I apologize.
Get back into bed.
Could somebody come in here
and clean out ms. Juggs' bedpan, please?
Ms. Juggs is dead.
I have to get
a new stage name.
Jenny Joy.
No need for all that anger.
Now, we managed to
take out more than I anticipated.
You down to a "C".
From a "G" to a "C"
if you can believe that.
I'm a little disoriented.
I just feel like something is
missing.
uh-huh.
Drainage is looking good.
Linda's gonna show you how
to do that once you get home.
I gotta tell ya:
In all the years that
I've done this, I've never seen,
let alone removed,
so much fat and tissue
at one time.
I should have called the
Shelter.
We could have fed the
homeless for weeks.
What?
They look like 2 mosquito
bites.
Sweetheart.
A "c" is a nice handful.
And you know what they say:
Anything more than a handful
is too hard to handle.
Don't talk about my breasts
as if they're your playthings.
And don't ever call me
Sweetheart!
Are you in pain? Hmm?
You need to get a handle
on that.
Look, you just grab this little guy here
and you press the button.
Press the button!
Look at you, Mr. Ain't-I-cool.
Feeling like a bigshot
'cause you took away my mojo.
Just cool your jets, all right? I'll get
somebody in here to clean out your bed pan.
No need for that.
can't do this to me.
I'm in recovery.
It's torture!
Don't call amnesty international.
I'm pressing full charges against her.
I'm pressing full charges against you,
you sexually harassing dickweed!
If I ever see you again,
I'll cut off you arms and legs as well!
Not before I cut your head off
and shit down your neck!
I guess just because you take
a person's weapons away doesn't
mean you take away their anger.
Hey baby.
Hey.
So, the kids are passed out.
I think nature does something
for insomnia.
This was a great idea of yours.
One big happy family.
Mm-hmm.
This was a very good idea.
So this is where all that
singing's coming from?
Scared me.
Sorry.
Couldn't sleep
and I heard the opera.
So I figured why not come see
who my cultured neighbor is.
Teddy McNamara.
Nice to meet you.
My husband and I are with the
kids over at number 14.
Just up the road.
I'm Jerry.
I'm sorry about the music.
I really thought I was
the only one out here.
Oh, gosh. No worries.
I can't sleep
in those campers anyway.
They're so cramped.
My husband, he's got
the heat up full blast.
Kids are sawing logs.
What about you?
You here with a wife or girlfriend?
Me?
No, no.
I can't convince her
to get the waders on.
- Fly fisherman?
- Yeah.
Any luck today?
Not much. but I think that's
about to change.
I hope so.
- Would you like some wine?
- Sure.
I have some time.
In that case, you're really
going to enjoy the show.
The show?
What show?
So where are we going?
Just a few more steps.
Here we are.
Where?
Just wait a second,
it's about to begin.
Dad. Dad.
Connor's sick
and I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
My head...
- You feel it too?
- Can you just open a window?
I tried but
they're all locked.
It's called the perseid
meteor shower
named after the
Perseus constellation.
Oh.
Happens every year
about this time.
But tonight is a very rare event.
Connor, hey.
Come here, Bud.
Come here.
We're gonna get out of here.
It's so transcending.
This is the best part.
You can feel it.
It's like being
one with the cosmos.
Like gods.
Yes. Well, thank you
for bringing me out here.
I need to go.
Ok. Come on. Let's go.
Come on, buddy.
Help! Help!
I hate the one's that scream.
Are you ok?
It feels worse.
Help! Somebody help!
Sean!
- You ok?
- I don't understand what happened.
keep your brother awake.
Sean!
Sean! Sean!
My wife must have taken
the keys when she went for a walk.
I'll get one of my guys to swing by
and find her when she gets back from her walk.
You know you're just lucky
I heard you screaming.
Never get any cell reception out here.
Yeah. Lucky.
You're that mime bandit,
right?
Don't worry. They don't pay me
enough to put up a fight.
It's kinda cool, actually.
Get me on the 6:00 news.
Maybe they send one of
those hot ass reporters down
and interview me.
You want silver too?
can you mime dead?
Oh, shit.
Who is it?
Christian?
what?
You forget your invisible box?
What?
Help me.
Jesus.
Nip/Subs Team
Seriessub.com