Previously;
They've been feeding you your son's
blood so you'll like it and want more.
Angelus is in his nature.
The beast will re-emerge.
Wesley's taking the baby away,
for good.
Hello, son. Your name is Steven
Franklin Thomas, and I'm your father.
- Give us the kid.
- Anyone tries to take him, he dies.
You look into the Quor-toth,
the darkest of the dark worlds.
Daniel!
There are no portals to Quor-toth.
Punching through requires dark magics.
The kind of power
it takes centuries to build.
There's almost always some
cosmic price to using primordial powers.
- What are you fleeing from?
- The Destroyer.
It's coming after you, Angel.
Hi, Dad.
Wait!
No!
Interesting.
My God.
It's you.
Connor.
Angel!
Look, will you just stop for a--?
- Can't we just talk about this?
- No.
Wait!
Okay, everybody just calm down.
Angel, if Peter Pan here
doesn't stop--
No!
Connor!
You're gonna fry out here, man.
Come on.
We'll go.
- Anybody get the bus number?
- 17. I'll see where it ends up.
- Let me check online. It'll be faster.
- That was it, Angel.
No, it isn't.
I'm gonna find him.
The fight you just had. It was
the vision I warned you about.
- You never mentioned Connor.
- Because I only saw you.
Angel, we sure this was Connor?
Just because he said "Hi, Dad"?
It was him.
- He was just in diapers, now he's a teen?
- Tell me we don't live in a soap opera.
I'm less worried about how he
grew up than why he came back.
He came back because he could.
He found a way to escape that place.
That's a possibility.
Here's another: You sure he said
"Hi, Dad" and not "You're dead"?
He's angry and afraid.
As soon as we talk-- Fred?
The 17 ends up at Union Station.
I'll go underground.
Somebody hit the streets.
- You got it, man.
- We will not fail, man.
Let's split up.
You guys start at the end of the line,
work your way--
Okay, that can't be good.
The dimensional rift from Quor-toth
must still be open.
Let's close it up before anything
else slithers or slides out of there.
Amen to that.
Princess, perhaps your newfound
powers can seal it shut.
Can't hurt to try.
I command you, close!
Okay, I got nothing.
- We do know somebody who might--
- No.
I already went to Wes'.
Can't do that again.
Well, I might know a guy
who knows another guy.
Is it dangerous?
It's not dangerous, it's just awkward.
This guy's all hands.
I mean, all hands. Like, 50 of them.
Anybody fluent in sign language?
We can't all leave when we have
a cosmic crack hanging over us.
Then I will stay...
...and guard the hotel.
I'm with him. You two hit the streets.
Lorne?
Already gone.
You went to Wesley's for me.
He's the one who told you
how to save me.
Yeah. He made it clear.
That's a door none of us
is ever gonna be knocking on again.
I would've called, but I figured
you'd tell me to go to hell...
...so I thought I'd just take a shot
and drop by.
- Invite me in?
- No.
Okay.
Not what I expected. You know,
bunch of flowers, some get-well cards.
Maybe a couple of those balloons
with the smiley faces on them.
I guess when she slit your throat
she nicked your sense of humor.
Not at all.
I find you being here extremely funny.
- How's that?
- Because you're going to offer me a job.
It's a shame, really, what happened.
You dedicate your life to a cause,
and the very people you try to help...
...turn their backs on you.
Yes, tragic.
Now get the hell out.
A man with your talents, a scholar,
a man of intellect....
Inside knowledge
of Angel Investigations.
Did I mention Wolfram and Hart
has the finest library of...
...mystical, occult and supernatural
reference material in the world?
Full medical, dental, 4O1(k) package.
- Not interested.
- Hey, it was worth a shot.
Anyway, here's something to help pass
the time in the unemployment line.
- Dante's Divine Comedy.
- It's just part one, "The Inferno."
It's not a first edition. More like the
1500s. But it's in the original Tuscan.
- Have you read it?
- Several times.
Then you know it's a guided tour
of the nine levels of hell.
Yes. Descending concentric rings
based on the severity of the sin.
You know...
...I always forget. At the very
bottom of hell, in the ninth circle...
...the devil's frozen in ice, right?
He's got three heads, three mouths...
...and those mouths are reserved
for the worst sinners.
Now, I can't remember,
who is in the center mouth?
What was his name?
The one person in all of human history
deemed the greatest sinner....
Who is it?
Judas Iscariot.
Right.
The worst spot in hell is reserved
for those who betray.
So don't pretend you're too good
to work for us.
- Did you find him?
- No,
We just missed him,
He's leaving a trail,
What? Did he hurt somebody?
No. I mean gawkers, folks not used
to seeing a kid in animal skins...
...riding on top a bus. Well, not south
of Santa Monica Boulevard anyway.
- Two more Robin Hood reports.
- Hear that? He's headed downtown.
- Where are you?
- Just east of Union.
- He won't head all the way into town.
- No?
He'll head for someplace
less populated.
- You want us to come get you?
- No. Just keep following the trail.
The minute it goes cold, let me know.
And if it doesn't go cold?
I mean, if we find him first?
He's my son.
He's my son, and he's alive.
He's gonna stay alive.
- Anything else we can do for you?
- Yeah.
Make the sun go down.
Come on, Tyke.
Look, this stuff is good.
Why are you being such a jerk?
I need it right now.
Tyke, come on.
Don't be such a jerk. Come on.
Brand new, never opened.
They've gotta be worth half a gram.
- They suck.
- They rock.
Look, it's like every hit from the '80s.
Plus, this girl is hot.
Get out of here, Sunny.
You're embarrassing yourself.
They're worth at least
a quarter. Please.
All right, okay.
Bye! Bye! Bye!
You jerk!
- Ow!
- You know what?
- That you get to work off.
- Let me go!
- No!
- Walk away.
An entire suit made of chammies.
That's different.
"What are you wearing to the Oscars?"
"My chammy suit."
What's all this?
Things I killed.
Aren't you all scary.
Chammies and teeth.
Wanna know what else is scary?
Me.
Just get rid of him.
No!
Don't!
Are you crazy? The police are probably
on their way. We gotta go.
So he won't forget me.
Isn't your neck stiff?
You've been standing
like that all day.
Pylean warriors are trained
for such endurance.
I once happened upon
a herd of Burrbeasts.
As you know, an engorged Burrbeast
will couple with anything that moves.
I was forced to stand
perfectly still...
...for 11 days and nights.
So you were never...?
No.
That honor was yours, princess.
I don't know.
Angel does all that...
...ninja-statue-don't-move-a-muscle-
or-you're-dead stuff too.
Me? I wouldn't last 10 minutes.
Of course, heels? Not helping.
Yes, I'm sure Angel has regaled you
with his many exploits.
He's tried, all right.
But I get so bored with all that
"days of yore" crap.
I mean, they're nothing like
your thrilling tales of adventure.
Not that you need adventurous
tales to impress me.
I'm impressed by you just being you.
But the way you constantly
speak of Angel....
Is because these last weeks
have been so hard for him.
He needs me.
And you do too.
I should be watching for creatures
from the other dimension.
You're the only creature from another
dimension I'm interested in.
I was worried that your affection
for the Groosalugg had waned.
Some shopkeepers saw Connor jump off
the bus right up the road from here.
He was here. I can smell him.
Cops say it was a drug thing gone
wrong. Some guy got killed.
It wasn't our boy.
They I.D.'d a local as the shooter.
- So he was here, but not part of--?
- He was part of it. Lot of mayhem.
Including a guy's ear
sliced off as a trophy.
Ew....
He was raised
in a hell dimension, okay?
So how do you want to play this?
It'll be dark soon.
You two head back to the hotel.
- Shouldn't we all keep looking?
- I'll have a better chance alone.
I don't want to scare him.
He's all alone in a strange world.
So that was really cool today.
So where'd you learn to fight all
badass like that?
In Quor-toth.
Quor-toth.... Mexico, right?
Sorry.
Lots of folks squat here.
Most are cool, but...
...if a fat guy asks you to play
"Teddy Bear in the Hole"...
...just tell him to get lost.
So, what did you do for kicks
in Quor-toth?
- Kicks?
- You know, like, fun.
Parties, movies, the mall?
- How'd you spend your time?
- I hunt.
Big surprise.
Home sweet home.
This is....
This is home.
Tonight it is.
You're welcome to crash here too.
Don't think it's your size.
People squat here, and they leave stuff.
So...
...how you feel about losing the whole
dead-animal thing?
I mean...
...not that I'm against
eating a cheeseburger.
We have all the food groups.
Meat...
...chocolate.
- So you were really going to kill Tyke.
- He was hurting you.
- Well, it's good you didn't.
- Why?
Because it's wrong.
I mean...
...I know Tyke's a bastard, but...
...cops are even worse.
I love these.
Have you ever had one?
Well, then get on down here, cowboy.
Isn't it the best?
I know this.
A tool for eating.
Um.... No.
That isn't for food.
It's for this.
I get it from Tyke.
It's medicine.
You're sick?
No, it's not that kind of medicine.
It helps me sometimes when I'm...
...sad.
You're sad?
No.
Connor's new to this world,
alone, probably scared,
- He looked scared kicking my ass.
- We should've gone with Angel.
Especially now that we know
what Connor's capable of.
Food, cash...
...place to crash....
I've had worse days.
How about you?
So, what's your deal?
Why did you come to L.A.?
To find my father.
Really?
I came here to get away from mine.
Parents should have to take a test
before they can have kids.
And if they're drunks or idiots...
...or evil, they should
just be sterilized.
If they're evil,
they should be killed.
You don't say much,
but I like what you say.
I'll be right back.
Sunny?
Sunny.
Connor.
- She put any of this crap in you?
- No.
Okay.
Sorry, I'm just....
We'll take care of this, okay?
Together.
Too late.
Connor.
I'm sorry about....
Was she your friend?
Connor, just talk to me.
You must be feeling like you just traded
one hell dimension for another...
...but if you just let me....
What are you doing?
- What is that?
- Give it back.
Why? Who are you tracking?
You're going after the guy
who gave her the junk.
- His medicine killed her.
- And you're gonna do what about it?
- Punish.
- You mean kill.
Slow down.
Listen to me.
No!
You will listen.
I'm not gonna let you walk out that
door and get in any more trouble.
Hear me?
Fine.
I'm sorry.
- You just don't understand this world.
- I understand.
Sunny was nice.
Now she's dead.
- Connor--
- Stop calling me that!
My name is Steven.
- And then what?
- And then nothing.
Standing, talking....
Boom! Knocked on our butts.
- You think something else came out?
- Hello? Face down, knocked out?
I found a picture of that beast
Connor killed.
And it says that these things
usually have a mate.
Lorne should have been back
with that expert hours ago.
Well, he said it was complicated.
There's that other expert.
You know someone else who can--?
I don't think Angel's
going to go for that.
Yes, we must always consider Angel.
Angel is our leader.
We must obey his wishes.
We're supposed to sit here with a fissure
from a hell dimension in the lobby...
...when we know someone
who can help us?
- I don't think so. I'm calling him.
- Fred. No, you're not.
- Lorne.
- Sorry it took so long, kids.
Mistress Myrna is a very difficult
woman to find.
You see what I mean?
It's been like this all day.
One of the nasty side effects
of specializing in dimensional magic.
What I wouldn't do for a lasso
and some Krazy Glue.
Steven.
Okay.
It's a good name.
Not Irish, but....
I know we haven't gotten off
to a great start, but if we can just...
...take a minute...
...that'd be good. Please, just....
Don't run away from me, all right?
I lost you once already.
There's just....
There's just so much I want to know.
There's so much I need to know.
You been okay?
I mean, what was it like there?
Do you have any friends?
Okay, I mean, not friends.
It's not like you were at summer camp.
You were stuck...
...in a hell dimension.
Connor, I'm so sorry.
I tried to come after you.
I would've done anything. I just--
- I couldn't find a way in.
- I found a way out.
Yeah.
You did. You sure did.
I should have tried harder.
I shouldn't have quit.
But you're back.
And that's what's important, you know?
You came back to me.
I want to know everything, son.
I want to know everything.
Everything about you.
What your life's been like.
You must have a million questions.
No.
- No?
- My father told me everything.
Your father?
Holtz isn't your father--
You don't get to say that name.
You don't even get to think it.
I know everything.
He told me all about you.
That you're a...
...thing that...
...kills and drinks blood.
- You're a vampire.
- What do you know about vampires?
Decapitation, stake in the heart...
...daylight, fire. I forget anything?
You have a second face.
A face for killing.
Show it to me.
I want to see it.
Show me the face you used
to kill my father's family.
Show me! Come on, show me!
It looks like this, son.
That's what you are.
It's part of what I am.
A part I hope you'll be able
to accept one day.
- You'd have to kill me first.
- Well, that's a plan.
But I got a better one.
- Chammy man.
- No, no, no. Don't.
Where's Sunny?
Would that be the dead girl
in the bathroom?
- Who are you?
- I'm his father.
- No, you're not.
- Will you let me handle this?
Let's find a way to work this out.
Talk through it.
Which is a thing that we do here.
There's no need for violence.
I'm sorry, did you say "no need for
violence"? You may want to speak up.
You see, I don't hear so good anymore!
Sunny's dead in the can. OD.
I begged her to get help.
- One down, one to go.
- We can make this right.
You can give me a new ear?
- Well, maybe you can wear a hat.
- Maybe I could blow your head off.
That's my coat. And whatever's not in
Sunny's body better be in the pockets.
- Son, give him the coat.
- You killed her.
Tyke!
Cops, man. They're looking for you.
They're everywhere.
I hope this pentagram wasn't some
dark attempt to close the fissure.
No, that was a dark attempt
to open one.
Different one. Long story.
So you think you can close it then?
Sure. That's not the worry.
You have worry?
How did it open? There are no portals
to Quor-toth, and for good reason.
It's not a place anyone should ever go.
If there aren't any portals,
what is it?
A tear in reality. Big cosmic no-no.
Something punched its way through.
Something I really don't want to meet.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Here you go.
Just the way you asked.
Should we leave
or get behind something?
No, it's pretty routine. Just sometimes
I get a little schmutz in my eye.
It's closed.
Did anything
else come through it?
Not sure, and not sticking around
to find out. Bye.
Dead body in the river,
another one in the bathroom.
It just does not bode
well for you, does it?
You see, son, violence
just always ends up badly!
Hey!
- Connor, we've gotta get out--
- I've gotta get out of here!
Don't.
Use me.
I'm bigger.
I'll make a better shield.
L.A.P.D. ! Drop your weapons!
Out that window!
Go! Out the window!
Stay down! Stay down!
Go!
- Do you need to stop?
- I'm okay.
Get behind here.
Maybe I do need a second.
What you did....
You hurt?
You know, if you want,
you can come back to the hotel.
No pressure or anything.
- No....
- But if you need a place to stay....
- I have to go.
- You're not alone.
You know that, right?
Yeah. I know.
- Hello, son.
- Hi, Dad.