Previously on Angel:
- All those years she spent in that cave.
- She trades one for another.
The visions aren't from The Powers.
A young man's been unfairly imprisoned,
and you're gonna save him.
I do this, and you stop sending
Cordy the killer visions.
- It's just business.
- Don't come at me through Cordy again.
You play that card a second time,
I'll kill you.
- Just trust me.
- I do.
- Don't stiffen up.
- Yeah, you either.
Good defense is about
moving the line of attack.
When the bad guy comes at you, step off
the line like this, creating a new one.
Every time you do, your opponent
will be forced to adjust.
- Move the line, then what?
- Just keep moving the line.
You'll be able to keep an attacker
busy until.... You know.
What? Until he dies of old age,
or until you swoop in to save me?
I didn't ask you to train me so I could
stave. I already know how to stave.
- I need to learn to fight.
- You don't think that I would.
- Would what?
- Save you.
Menfolk not always around
to protect the womenfolk, you know?
Besides, what if you were the guy
I had to fight? It could happen.
Okay.
When you put an adversary down,
make sure he doesn't get up again.
Force the other guy to counter,
and he'll open himself up.
- We'll go half-speed--
- I got it.
Three years of cheer squad, I only ever
had to be shown a move once.
Handling a lethal weapon is a little
different than shaking a pompon.
Ready! Okay!
Go team.
- How long has he been here?
- 20 minutes.
You should have pulled me
out of the meeting. The family?
On their way.
Lilah. I was just keeping
Billy company.
Thanks, Gavin.
I'll take it from here.
Your family has been worried sick.
Where have you been?
- I went for a walk.
- A walk. For three days?
- He was feeling cooped up.
- Why don't you go close an escrow.
You're not supposed to be out
on your own. Remember last time?
You don't wanna end up in that
awful place again, do you?
Of course he doesn't.
No one wants that.
Congressman.
- I trust you've stayed out of trouble.
- No trouble.
Let's go home.
This is the second time you've returned
our nephew safely to us. Thank you.
Our pleasure.
"Our pleasure," in the sense
that he had nothing to do with it.
Nice boy.
He's great. Had his own private
room in hell. Family connections.
Oh, by the way, get out.
- I wasn't finished.
- No. You really were.
You go sniffing around one of my clients
again, I think we'll have a problem.
You think?
Who told you you could think?
Why don't you try listening instead
of flapping that fat mouth of yours?
You weren't captain of the debate team,
were you? At least Lindsey knew--
It's inspiring to see you like this.
Training with Angel, taking
responsibility. I'm proud of you.
Never hurts to be prepared.
We should all be battle-ready.
Dead! So very, very dead.
Just how dead are you?
I'm tired of being the dead one.
I was thinking I'd enter into a similar
training arrangement with Fred.
If you think she can help
you fight, why not?
I'm kidding.
Wesley, if you want
to get to know Fred better...
...maybe the next time you have her
over for dinner...
...you won't ask the rest of us
to come along.
I mean....
Was I that obvious?
Yeah! Yes!
I don't think anybody else noticed.
She's a rather
extraordinary young woman.
Still, the last thing any of us should
be doing is coupling with each other.
Office romances,
even under normal circumstances--
We don't live
in normal circumstances.
What are the odds of any of us
finding someone...
...who can deal with the stuff
that we have to deal with?
- I don't know, maybe we are meant--
- For each other?
Actually, I was gonna say, to be alone.
But what the heck.
Wesley, if you like her, tell her.
Just go right up to her and...
...hack her into little pieces.
Easy. Okay. Up.
Convenience store.
Man attacking a woman.
- His wife. It's his wife.
- How many stores on the West Side?
Even if you just include Santa Monica,
Beverly Hills and Malibu...
...the combined population is 130,000,
spread over 30 square miles--
- A lot.
- I was getting there.
- Two teams. Gunn, you and I--
- No, it's too late.
You can't save her.
This murder happened a week ago.
Why would they show this to me now?
- What's this?
- Everything you saw in your vision.
Police reports,
husband's written confession...
...captures from the store's cameras
and, I caution you...
...the medical examiner's
crime-scene photos. Cordelia....
You shouldn't be looking at that.
Tell that to The Powers.
They ran the THX version in my head.
- How did you get this stuff?
- The old-fashioned way. I bought it.
- The police sold you this stuff?
- Not exactly. Someone who has access.
Usually they sell to the tabloids
when the victims are high-profile.
- Charlene Baird.
- The victim.
She and the perpetrator were married for
30 years. No previous domestic violence.
- Why'd he do it?
- He says she wouldn't listen to him.
- He was trying to make her stop talking.
- Well, it worked.
This guy confessed. Crime solved.
Why are The Powers airing reruns?
- I don't know.
- I do.
11:24, 20 minutes before
the crime occurred, look who's there.
- Oh, boy.
- What?
What?
Okay, kind of cute.
So who is he?
You're sure this is him?
This is the guy?
You pull someone from a hell dimension,
you tend to remember their face.
Yeah, that's him.
Well, then.
Now we know why The Powers made me
experience that woman's death.
She died because of me.
- No.
- Yes.
Angel, if he's somehow responsible,
then so am I.
You didn't break him out and put him
back on the streets. I did.
- For me. You did it to save me.
- And I'd do it again.
- Angel....
- Hey.
Whatever's happening now,
you're not responsible for this...
...and neither am I.
But I know who is.
Dramatic entrance. Except for
the part where you can't enter.
- You're a little jumpy, Lilah.
- Long day at the office.
And you know your boy's on the loose.
You know what he's doing.
It's been brought to my attention.
- God, are you--?
- I'm fine. You should see the other guy.
I plan to.
- Billy never touched me.
- I know, he has some power that makes--
Billy never touched me, and
you can't touch him. Nobody can.
Billy, as in Blim, as in
Congressman Nathan Blim's nephew.
That family's the closest thing
this country has to royalty.
They own half the eastern seaboard.
The law won't go near them.
- I'm not the law.
- This isn't some beast you can just--
- Why are you protecting him?
- I'm sorry. This deep concern...
...coming from the only man I know...
...who definitely wants to kill me
is a bit much on a day like this.
- Your hands are shaking.
- Stay away from my client.
- This is it. The Blim estate.
- Not very welcoming, is it?
I don't suppose it'd do much good
to ring the bell either.
How about we sneak in dressed
as security guards or something?
Well, it's a possibility.
Or we could--
So you wanna go next?
- I guess we wait here.
- Yeah.
Why doesn't it surprise me that
I can walk in without an invitation?
As far as I'm concerned,
you have a standing invitation.
You're not a right guy.
You're not quite human either, are you?
Not quite. More than you.
You like to hurt women.
That make you feel like a man?
I've never hurt a woman in my life.
I just like to watch.
- Not anymore.
- Oh?
- You're going back.
- Really?
- I don't think so.
- L.A. Police Department!
Hands where we can
see them. Turn around. Slowly.
- You're looking for me.
- William Blim?
That's right. I'm the one that
called you. Did you find the body?
- We're taking you in for questioning.
- Oh, yes. I should think you would.
Sanchez, read him his rights.
Will those be necessary? I won't
give you trouble. I'll come quietly.
- Who are you?
- He's nobody.
You have the right
to remain silent....
- I told you to take Pico.
- Relax, Sanchez. We'll get there.
Did you just tell me to relax?
You think you can talk to me like that?
I'd talk to you with my finger,
but I like both hands on the wheel.
- Pull over.
- What?
- Pull over!
- What's your problem?
I'll tell you what my problem is,
I got a woman here that don't listen.
My contact at the morgue confirms it,
a body was discovered earlier tonight.
A young woman was reported missing
three days ago. Someone phoned in.
- Billy.
- Makes no sense. Even if he did it...
...he didn't do it. Why confess?
What does it get him?
Gets him out.
Out of his $12 million compound
and into a cell at Men's Central.
- Yes, but for how long?
- An impenetrable cube of hellfire...
...in a demon dimension
couldn't do much, so...
...my guess, regular bars,
not really a problem.
She's right. All he'll need
to get out is his lawyer.
- What're you doing?
- Get there before Lilah does.
- And then what?
- I'll take him out of the cell.
Wait. You can't barge into a police
precinct and go all Terminator,
- I'll be okay.
- It's dangerous. He's dangerous.
- What if he lays his whammy on you?
- He won't be conscious.
He's not there.
I just heard it on the police scanner.
The patrol car never made it back.
There's been an accident.
There was an altercation. One
of the officers attacked his partner.
She was forced to shoot him.
The female's been taken to the hospital.
Maybe she can tell us what Billy did
to her partner before he snapped.
Wouldn't be a bad idea if one of us was
standing by at the hospital.
Maybe start a conversation
with the staff or one of her buddies?
- Maybe.
- I'm on it.
The blood in that car,
some of it is his.
Not human.
He came through here.
And recently. It's still wet.
I'll take a sample and see
what sort of creature Billy is.
- I can't wait for that.
- I understand.
- I can find him.
- Be careful.
What you doing?
I'm gonna go run an errand.
A normal, everyday errand.
Cordelia.
I don't think you should do this.
How can I not?
Fred, you're here. Good.
I was hoping you would assist me.
I managed to lift
a sample of Billy's blood.
Maybe we can identify his demon lineage
and figure out how his power works.
Would you hand me the...
...glass slides?
Thank you.
- Cordelia Chase? Come to gloat?
- I can do that anywhere.
Are you gonna invite me in?
Oh, wait. I'm not a vampire.
Please, come on in.
I want you to tell me about Billy.
Everything you didn't tell Angel.
Help me stop him.
What makes you think
I'm gonna do that?
Well, there's your face,
for starters.
- I accept the risks of my job.
- Why were you crying five minutes ago?
There's not a thing about badly
reapplied mascara I don't know.
I'm not Lindsey McDonald. I don't
switch sides whenever it gets tough.
And since when is this your job?
I thought Angel was the dark revenger.
Angel feels responsible for this guy
because he brought him back from hell.
I feel responsible
because he did it to save me.
You, who are actually
responsible for the entire thing...
...feel nothing at all,
because you are a vicious bitch.
- So you know me.
- Please. I was you. With better shoes.
- These are Baracci.
- Fall collection?
- Next spring.
- He's widened the heel.
- And rounded the toe.
- Won't work with pink.
- Pink is out this spring.
- Billy Blim makes people crazy.
Not all people. Just men.
He brings out a primordial misogyny
in them. Turns them into killers.
Then why didn't he do it to Angel?
- Angel's seen him?
- Yes. Right before he escaped.
- What's so witty?
- Billy's touch works differently...
...on different men.
Some lose their mind in an instant.
Others can take hours.
Gee, I sure hope Angel
isn't starting to feel testy.
- You better hope it.
- I know. I've seen his dark side.
You really haven't.
I have to find Billy.
And I'm gonna help you, why?
You know that guy you hired
to hack into my visions?
What he did to me,
you know what it felt like?
I was cut, torn up, my face
disfigured and burning with pain...
...not knowing if it would end
or just get worse till I died.
- So you think I owe you--?
- It's not the pain.
It's the helplessness.
The certainty that there is nothing
you can do to stop it.
That your life can be thrown away
in an instant by someone else.
He doesn't care.
He'll beat you down...
...because he doesn't
even think of you as alive.
No woman should ever
have to go through that.
And no woman strong enough
to wear the mantle of "vicious bitch"...
...would ever put up with it.
Where is Billy going?
He seemed like a level-headed guy.
Always polite.
"Yes, sir. " "Thank you, sir. "
To lose it like that....
I didn't see it coming.
Hacking 14 years, I understand
why he did it. There's a point, right?
How many times you feel like
taking a fist to a customer?
- One of your drivers snapped?
- Yeah, he beat the hell out of a fare.
- A woman?
- That surprise you?
Probably sitting in the back telling
him how to drive. You know the type.
Yeah. Probably had it coming to her.
I'm just saying....
Get out of here. You're gonna tell me
what this driver's last stop was...
...right before he beat up
that woman. "I'm just saying. "
- Dylan, your cousin's here.
- Which one? There's a zillion.
- I think he said his name's Billy.
- Billy? Not possible. Billy's....
Hi, Dylan.
Billy.
I didn't know
you were having a party.
We agreed that you weren't gonna come
here anymore after that last thing.
Somebody should talk to them
about appropriate public behavior.
Do you want to, or should I?
This was taken from the print I made of
Billy's blood. Tell me what you think.
Looks to me as if some of the red
blood cells are supercharged.
Those would probably
be from Billy's demon lineage.
So however Billy's putting the mojo
on people, the power's in his blood.
Which means it could also be in his
sweat, his saliva or even his touch.
Speaking of saliva,
where is Cordelia?
What do you mean,
"speaking of saliva"?
It's a simple question.
Where is Cordelia?
- I think she went out.
- Out?
- Did she happen to mention where?
- She said an errand.
When you say you "think she went out"
you mean you know she went out...
...because you spoke to her.
- Well, I suppose that--
- Suppose?
- I did. Yes, I did.
- That's better.
Lie to me again...
...and we're going to have a problem.
- Where are you going?
- I was gonna call Cordelia...
- ...find out where she is for you.
- That's not necessary.
- It's not?
- No.
Sit down, Fred.
- It'll just--
- Sit down.
There's something
we need to discuss.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
Cordelia left. Really, I am.
We're past that.
I put it behind me.
However, we will have to make
some changes around here.
- Change can be good, I guess.
- No more of these provocative outfits.
Provocative?
Maybe Mommy and Daddy never
explained to you that men, grown men...
...are wired a certain way.
You can't come in here, day after day,
waving it in my face like this.
- What?
- You're practically daring me to take it.
Is that what you want?
- Stop it.
- Oh, are we standing now?
- This is making me uncomfortable.
- You're uncomfortable? That's rich.
What do you think it's like for me
with you smelling the way you do?
- Wesley, please.
- You think you can taunt a man?
You brush up close,
bat your eyes...
...and when our backs are turned,
you laugh at us.
- I'd never--
- Humiliate us.
You think you can do anything
you please because you bleed?
No.
I'll show you blood.
What do you tell a woman
who has two black eyes?
Nothing you haven't already
told her twice.
No sense of humor.
- I'm looking for Billy Blim.
- You a friend of his?
Friend? To be honest,
I'm looking to kill the bastard.
Come on in.
- Is he here?
- No. He came and went.
And everybody's okay? I was expecting
blood, carnage, bad things.
You gotta know the rules around Billy.
Everybody in the family does.
Never leave him alone with your girl
and don't let him touch you.
- He wants money, leave it on a table.
- Is that why he was here?
Said he needed fun money.
I just wanted to get rid of him.
Can you explain something to me?
How come you invited me in after I
told you I wanted to kill your cousin?
You're Angel, right?
- Billy mention me?
- No. There was a chick here. Cute.
She said a melodramatic guy named
Angel would eventually show up.
- Cordelia. Thinks I'm melodramatic?
- You did say you'd kill my cousin.
That's not melodrama--
She was here?
- Melodrama is exaggerated--
- This is real. Where'd you send her?
Santa Monica. The family plane is there.
Billy said he wants to fly someplace.
He didn't say where.
Hopefully far away.
Fred?
Fred.
I know what you're doing.
What you're up to.
Luring me.
Forcing me to find you.
It's such a dog-and-pony show.
You beguile me
with your girlish ways.
I pursue you.
But you never give over, do you?
No, you just keep
laughing and running.
Well, guess what, my love,
I'm not some downy-faced schoolboy.
I'm a man.
You can't come out into the open,
can you?
No, you hide.
You deceive.
It's nothing new.
It goes all the way back to Eve.
You and the serpent,
plotting behind our backs.
"Here, honey, eat this.
It's just an apple."
That's the problem with your sex.
You're all weak and you're all dirty,
and you won't be satisfied...
...until you've brought every one
of us down into the muck with you!
Why do you make me do this?
Billy.
Yes? Do I know you?
Not exactly.
I thought we should meet.
I'm the woman Wolfram and Hart
tortured to get you out of your cell.
Oh, I see.
And you're here to whine.
Poor, helpless, battered woman...
...needs to vent her feelings
about the injustice of it all.
No, ass-wipe.
I'm here to send you back.
I'm still here.
I don't run away like a girl.
I see things through.
You think I hate you because
you're a woman. I don't.
- And I was feeling special.
- I don't hate women.
Sure, you're all whores, who sell
yourselves for money or prestige...
...but men are just as bad.
Maybe even worse.
They're willing to throw away
careers, families, lives...
...for what's under your skirt.
I'm wearing pants.
So you can dress and talk like a man....
Does that make you feel superior?
I'm feeling superior because I have
an arrow pointed at your jugular.
And the irony of using a phallic-shaped
weapon.... Not lost on me.
You don't have the nerve to do it.
Wrong again.
- I can't let you do it, Cordelia.
- You saved me again. I knew you would.
- You know what he is.
- Which is why I'll waste him myself.
Angel. He can't hurt me.
No, I won't hurt her.
I won't hurt her at all.
In here.
- What happened to Wesley?
- Somehow he got infected.
I figure it happened while he was working
with Billy's blood from that handprint.
That finger-painty-looking handprint
downstairs is Billy's blood?
Wes turned into a psycho killer
because of that bloody handprint...
...that I picked up and looked at?
When you put it that way,
it worries me.
I better get out of here.
Lock the door behind me.
Or maybe we'll go to plan B.
Oh, God.
You said you'd go to plan B,
but what's plan B?
Plan B.... Plan B....
Charles?
Plan B is the one where, if you don't
stop whining, I bash in your--
Oh, God.
Cordy, get out of here.
- No.
- Cordelia.
- I can't.
- Get out!
- You can fight this.
- Don't fight it, feel it.
You can, can't you? All that rage
and hatred bubbling to the surface.
I've never done this to a vampire.
Should be entertaining.
Please, go.
I can't.
I have this problem.
This is happening to you
because of me. Because of me.
So I can't leave you, Angel. I won't.
You think that's your problem?
That's not your problem.
You know what your real problem is?
Guys like him!
'Cause you got no power over me.
You're scaring me.
Take this and knock me out.
Knock me out!
- You want me to hit you?
- Yes!
- I can't.
- You might want to.
Hit me!
- Charles, please.
- "Charles, please." Fine.
Give it back to me so I can
smash your stupid head with it.
- What?
- Give me the damn chair leg!
You're gonna pay for that.
Would you like to hear
my theory, Fred?
It's about how stupid you are.
I believe that after five years
of living in a cave...
...you'll instinctively retreat
to small, dark places...
...rather than run outside,
where you'd be safe.
Let's finish this.
I'm sorry, Wesley.
You're sorry?
You were right about me
liking dark places to hide in.
But you forgot
I also like to build things.
I don't get it.
I don't get it either.
I mean, you're a man...
...so why didn't
Billy's touch affect you?
Maybe because I'm not human.
Oh, right. And a vampire can never
be turned into a monster.
Well, that thing that Billy
brought out in others?
That hatred and anger....
That's something I lost a long time ago.
Even when you were evil?
I never hated my victims.
I never killed out of anger.
It was always about the pain
and the pleasure.
Huh.
I guess you could say your demon-ness
makes you less petty than humans.
Almost noble.
I mean, in a twisted, dark
and really disturbing kind of way.
- Thanks.
- Uh-huh.
It's weird.
What is?
I'm getting used to being
creeped out...
...and comforted at the same time.
I get that.
Wesley?
Wesley, it's me, Fred.
Does that hurt?
Sorry.
I left a bunch of messages.
Yes. I meant to call you back.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Wesley, you gotta come back to work.
- How can I?
- What do you mean?
How can you not? You're the boss.
We need you.
You took a few days off.
That's good. We all did.
- But now it's time to come back.
- Fred.
- I tried to kill you.
- That wasn't you.
How can you know that? Something
inside me was forced to the surface.
- Something primal.
- Do you wanna kill me?
God, no.
It wasn't something in you, Wesley.
It was something
that was done to you.
I don't know what kind of man
I am anymore.
Well, I do.
You're a good man.
Will I see you back at the office?
Yeah.
Good.