Ah! The Great Pact of Nottingham.
All drawn up and ready for signature?
Safe in your quarters?
Good, good.
And you've told
nobody about your work?
The scribe is mute, my Lord.
Mute? Are we sure?
Oh, look! Look!
The Black Knights. On their
way to the castle to sign the pact!
Now we're sure.
Is this what you're looking for?
Your blood money. Betray your
friends for a few measly pennies.
Traitor! Look, I'm sorry, all right?
I'm really sorry...
Really... I never wanted...
HORSES APPROACH
Is that who I think it was?
The Black Knights, heading for
Nottingham. What are they up to?
I'm going in.
What about Allan? Forget him.
He's dead to us.
Meet back at the camp in one hour.
Well, you can't just decide
to go like this and go!
Without planning... without us!
Yes, I can! It's the Black Knights!
Why does he do this? Why does he
always, always do this?
What are these in aid of, Sir Guy?
A bit of colour for you.
I was wondering if you would
accompany me to the celebrations
today.
What are we celebrating? The King's
birthday.
What are we really celebrating?
Does it matter?
It's the signing
of an important document.
Something tells me it is a
document which I won't approve of.
Well, Marian, you should approve,
because this document brings
me closer to real power.
And that, in turn, benefits you.
COULD benefit you...
in time.
Meanwhile, there's a
pretty dress in it for you.
Am I so easily won?
You must be the least
easily won woman in England.
Well, if that's my reputation,
then perhaps nobody will mind
if I do not attend...
Choose a dress. Guy...
What are you doing here?
Just dropping in on you.
So, the Black Knights
are assembling.
Did you hear Gisborne? They're
signing an important document.
Who died? The Sheriff's scribe.
Fell from the battlements.
Outlived his usefulness. What?
Dead scribes, Black Knights...
Something tells me we have to find
this document.
Not being funny... your guards.
Useless!
You need smarter people on your team.
And that's you, is it?
Well...
Hood found you out?
Maybe.
Don't insult me.
All right. I need your help.
I've lost everything cos I
helped you, so you owe me.
I owe you nothing.
I paid you.
Take me on, Guy, come on.
You won't regret it.
Go and get one of my
servants to give you some food.
Ah, nice. Where you off to, then?
Get yourself cleaned up.
Come and find me at the castle.
This is it. The scribe's room.
...Better get a move on. Down at
the front gate again on guard...
Robin. This isn't the time...
Will that work?
Trust me, I've done this before.
With which girl's hairpin?
LOCK CLICKS
"The Great Pact of Nottingham.
"We, the undersigned, by the
affixing of our seals of office
and nobility,
"hereby undertake to remove
King Richard from the throne.
"By his lasting absence, he
demonstrates his scant regard for
the welfare of his subjects."
This is outrageous!
"We further undertake to replace the
said Richard with his brother, John,
Prince of the realm."
The Sheriff is making the Black
Knights sign their allegiance.
This is a traitors' charter.
Looks like the Sheriff
has made some new friends.
Buckingham, Spencer...
Winchester?
Surely not.
He's an old friend of my father.
DOOR SLAMS
When the Pact is signed, there
can be no going back for our friends.
And enjoy this party.
Nobody here.
Look at this.
The colour,
the detail, the tone texture.
This man was a true artist.
I'm sorry I killed him, though.
A clue...
No.
Door.
Go, go...
I cannot believe Winchester would
willingly be involved
in this revolt.
Winchester controls the south coast.
The Sheriff wants to intercept the
King's landing. But Winchester?!
I've known him since we were boys.
The Sheriff must have got to him.
Good. Good? If the Sheriff
can get to him, then so can I.
Edward, I'll be back.
And when I get back, I
will get you out of this place.
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
What should I do?
Be meek and obedient, my child.
Until I know more.
Jailer, confession's over.
Why have we stopped?
Oh. Move it!
My Lord Winchester, I'm a friend.
I know you are coming to Nottingham
to sign the Sheriff's pact. I don't
know what you're talking about.
My name is Robin Hood.
We haven't got time for games.
Robin! Forgive me, I... have to
be careful.
We have a mutual friend.
Sir Edward, the former Sheriff
of Nottingham. Edward, how is he?
In the Sheriff's dungeons.
Good God. What can we do?
First, we need to kill this pact.
Spencer and Buckingham
are signing under duress, too.
Lf, at the moment of signing, you
were to refuse,
the Black Knights would lose
faith and the Sheriff's pact
would be history.
That's dangerous. The Sheriff would
turn his men on me. That's where I
come in, you need support.
Forgive me. I am a peace-loving man.
I want only stability and
the Sheriff is offering me that...
What they don't know...
is that I've already sent a
messenger to the King.
Roger of Stoke. By now, the King
will already know about this plot.
When he returns to England, the
first thing he will do is crush
the Black Knights.
If you love peace, do anything,
but do not sign the Sheriff's pact.
Ahhh... Count me in.
Right, lads, work to do.
We're going to the castle. Why?
Why? To save England,
Marian and her father.
They're hosting a celebration
for the King's birthday. Except
it's really a celebration
for the Black Knights
signing the pact.
Will, you need to find us a way
of getting into this party.
I've already done it. How?
The castle announced
this party weeks ago.
Put out a call
for entertainers and players.
And it gave me an idea.
It's a recurve bow!
Djaq? It's a flute.
What does this do? Much, don't!
Sorry!
This is for you.
Will, you're a genius!
And a magician. That's brilliant.
You crafty craftsman!
What about me? Ah.
These are for you.
Bells? What do they do?
Oh, they're just bells.
Thanks.
FANFARE PLAYS
Delighted...
to welcome Harold of Winchester...
to join our celebrations
for the King's birthday.
Thank you, Marian.
We sign in one hour. Marvellous.
I was ungrateful earlier.
I'm sorry. I was over-bearing.
Can I have word
in private with you first?
I'd like to talk to your
predecessor, if I may.
Yes, well, Sir Edward is,
how shall I put it, indisposed.
In what way? He's in the dungeons.
No, really? He's loyal to the King.
And also, a right royal
pain in the derriere.
I'd still like to talk to him,
if you have no objections.
Yes, well, it can be arranged.
Gisborne will show you to
your quarters.
Keep an eye on him.
This way, my Lord.
My Lord?
This way. Ah... yes.
Reason for visit?
Security check.
No knives, no weapons in the castle.
We're the band, the minstrels.
Will. Allan! Much.
I'm Sir Guy's man.
Can you let me pass? In you go.
What's he doing here?
He's being "Sir Guy's Man".
Unbelievable.
Did you see what he was wearing?!
Whose is this?
I said, whose is this?
It's mine.
A bit's come off, sorry...
That's all right. I'm good with wood.
Er, bells, mate.
You know what to do. I'm off
to see Winchester. Wait here.
Oh! Cake.
What?
Had to put something on, didn't I?
I suppose you want me to introduce
you to the Sheriff now, do you?
Yeah. Wait through there.
Go in there and get yourselves ready.
Er... Of course,
we'll go in there and... tune up.
We can't possibly go in there.
Allan. Why not?
We, er, never share dressing rooms.
You're already dressed.
It's the principle. We're artists.
He's the drummer.
My men are safely in the castle. I
heard you could walk through walls.
Your meeting will take place in the
War Room. I'll be there. It will be
strictly Black Knights only.
Then I shall be a Black Knight.
Confident.
Determined. My men will be
waiting outside the War Room.
When you've said your piece,
I'll cover for you and you run.
My men will secure your safe exit.
Thank you. What about you?
Well, I can walk through walls.
Remember?
Good luck. You too.
And thank you.
Tell me something. What do you know
about a messenger sent by Robin Hood
to the King, telling of our plans?
Roger of Stoke?
Don't worry about him.
He got lost en route. Well done.
If I may be allowed
to speak to Sir Edward in private?
Edward.
Harry! My old friend.
What has happened to you?
Sit down.
I've had a visit
from a friend of yours.
Robin. Excellent. He advised me not
to back the wrong horse.
But then, I look where
you've ended up... Harry?
I could back you, Edward. And end
up stuck in a cell with vermin.
Or I could back the Sheriff and
just get richer and more powerful.
Rats or riches?
It's a tough choice.
Harry.
You cannot sign the pact.
Oh, I will sign the pact.
You are mad if you think
you can trust the Sheriff.
Trust? Oh, no,
I don't trust anyone.
You taught me that,
when you stole the woman I loved.
Jailer?
Kate?!
She chose me, Harold.
I didn't steal her.
I was just thinking of her.
I thought I saw her outside
just now. A young woman,
the very image of Kate...
She's your daughter!
Of course! She's her mother's
double.
Well done, Edward.
We wouldn't want her inheriting
your looks, now, would we?
Oh, oh, oh...
I've just had an idea.
If I couldn't have the mother...
What's her name, hmmm?
Your little precious pea? No!
No? That's not her name, now is it?
No! Harry, she's got nothing
to do with this. Please!
I don't think he likes me any more.
Please!
Harry... you wanted a word?
What was the word?
Sussex. Sussex?
Sussex.
I want it. Sussex?
I hold the key to the success of
your plan. It's come to my attention
that Buckingham and Spencer are
nervous. They'll do as they're told.
Not if they see me falter.
Not if they think you don't have
access to where King Richard
is most likely to land.
I have therefore decided that my
price for helping you is Sussex.
Oh...
and some of Surrey.
Harry...
Very good, very good.
Almost had me there.
No, I'm serious.
If you want this pact signed,
it will cost you Sussex. And some of
Surrey. Surrey...
And the girl. What girl?
Er... Marian. No! Shut up.
You still gain Warwick, Lincoln
and Cambridge.
And... some of Surrey.
Oh, and I have something to
offer you. A little bonus.
A little... sweetener. Still, if
you're not playing...
You get Sussex.
I keep Surrey.
Oh, you drive a hard bargain.
It's a deal. Marian stays.
Not negotiable, sorry.
Personal thing. I won't bore you
with the details.
The girl and Sussex
and then you sign?
Pleasure doing business with you.
My Lord...
Harry? Hmm?
What was the sweetener? Later.
You'll like it.
You cannot give him Marian!
I have lost Sussex!
SUSSEX!
And all you can do
is bleat about a girl!
I want a hanging!
What? Find me somebody to hang.
I want to see somebody twitch.
My Lord, this man said you
were going to see him. Not now!
You'll do. For what? Hang him. What?!
No, this man works for me. So?
So, he was my spy in Hood's camp.
Was? Hood found him out.
Served his purpose then, hasn't he?
He might still prove useful. You're
not listening to me, Gisborne!
Find that lady leper friend and take
her to see Lord Winchester.
Then bring him before me with a
hood over his head!
Hang on a minute. I'm on your team
now!
And I can help, honest. Guy!
Lah... di-dah di-dah.
Guy?
Hang on, let me say something here,
right? Guy! Come on, you can't be
serious.
Just take him away. What?
Guy, what are you doing?
Psst! I'm not hungry.
Robin, thank heavens... Shhhh. I
haven't got much time.
The Sheriff is about to have his
meeting. And Winchester is going to
refuse to sign.
There'll be absolute chaos.
And in that chaos, I intend to come
down and get you out.
What? Winchester is going to sign.
He's a traitor. A traitor?
And he wants Marian.
Marian? What for?
Revenge. Against me. What?
He thinks I took his woman.
So he's going to take my daughter.
Robin?
Then I have no choice.
What? What are you going to do?
God speed, Edward.
Guy, at least do me the courtesy of
knocking... Get your possessions.
You're leaving.
What? Now! Why? Winchester's made a
deal with the Sheriff, you've become
part of a negotiation.
Pardon? Winchester wants you.
Tell him he can't have me.
The Sheriff has agreed.
I cannot protect you.
Listen to me. You have to run. Now.
I can't! My father... I will take
care of your father.
I cannot leave him. Why do you
always resist? I'm attempting
to help you.
I know, I can see
that and I'm grateful.
If the Sheriff knew I was doing
this, my life would be in danger.
Why do you work for him?
I have nobody. So you choose him?
So I choose power. He is my
route to position, standing.
He is mad, you know that.
No. He's single-minded.
He does not allow... distractions
to divert him from his course.
Distractions? Like a little
humanity?
Humanity is weakness.
You don't believe that.
You must leave this place.
This money will secure your passage.
I have instructed a man on
the west gate to let you out.
Marian.
Good luck.
Go! Now!
Excellent.
Taking the lady to see her new lord?
My Lord...
As my lieutenant, Gisborne, you
sit at the right hand of the father.
You will share in the fruits
of OUR labour.
You will be a god amongst men.
As long as I can trust you.
Take Lady Marian to Winchester.
This? Oh, well...
Tunisian, actually.
Yeah, we tour all over the place,
London, Lincoln, er... Hull.
Right, come on.
We're in the middle of something
here. We have to go warn Marian.
Now, come on! Marian?
Guy? Marian...
I'm sorry.
Sheriff's instructions.
What? Get off me. Guy!
Get off me, get off me! Guy!
KNOCK AT DOOR
Enter.
Ah, the icing on my cake!
Daddy's little girl.
I will not be treated like this.
You're quite right.
These handcuffs and leg irons, could
they be made a little tighter?
How dare you?! Oh, gag her for God's
sake. She's pretty till she talks.
To business. Come on!
She's not here. What's the problem?
I wanted to talk to her before...
Before what? What do we have
to warn her about?
Robin! Much...
"My dearest Marian.
"I fear we may not meet again...
"in this life.
"For the things I did wrong...
"for the things I am about to do...
"but mostly for the life,
"for the love we could not have...
"I am truly sorry."
I want you to give
this note to Marian.
What for?
There's been a change of plan.
I want you to wait here for her.
Aren't we supposed to help you and
Winchester escape? Yes, after
the showdown.
I'll deal with Winchester.
Use the distraction to go and
release Sir Edward.
Then take him and Marian to the
forest. I will meet you there.
How are you and
Winchester going to escape?
If the castle guards find you...
Just do as I say.
Please.
I want you to give me your word.
Good.
And thank you, my friends.
I have a message for you,
from King Richard.
I don't like this.
I hate it. It doesn't make sense.
If Marian's in danger,
we should be looking for her.
Robin's up to something.
No, you cannot
open people's private letters!
John?
Read it.
Read it for me.
"My dearest Marian.
"I fear we may not meet again...
"in this life." What?
"We're both to be betrayed
by Winchester..."
"I cannot allow it. All the Black
Knights will be gathered together.
"Winchester, Durham, Rotherham and
the rest of the Sheriff's
traitorous gang.
"I may never have the chance again.
"I cannot allow this opportunity
to pass.
"I must kill them.
"I only hope you remember me well.
"Forgive the brutality
of what I'm going to do.
"If England is to live...
"they must die.
"And so, I fear, must I.
"Go to the woods, to fight again.
"Go with my lads.
"I will see you in heaven."
Let the walls enclose us.
"Goodbye, my love."
My friends, we are
a brotherhood of steel.
And our time has come.
As a sign of my unbending fastness
to the cause,
I, Vaizey, Sheriff of this shire,
do add my name to
the Great Pact of Nottingham.
And I do make my mark.
Next to add his name,
the Lord Winchester.
As a sign of my unbending fastness
to the cause,
I, Harold, Lord of Winchester,
do add my name to this
Great Pact of Nottingham.
And I do make my mark.
Traitors! Robin Hood!
Winchester, the death of every
man in this room is on your head.
Sheriff, Gisborne, say your prayers.
Hood. Forgive me...
Guards!
Thank you, my Lord Winchester.
A very good little sweetener indeed.
My pleasure.
Gisborne, don't hang your boy.
I've got a better idea.
Cake on the terrace, gentlemen.
If he dies, I die.
Halt! Been looking for you.
Us? How come?
The Sheriff wants musicians outside.
They've caught Robin Hood.
Behold the outlaw!
The... invincible...
and legendary Robin Hood.
And his friend, Allan A Dale.
How fitting, then, that these
two renegades,
these enemies of the law,
which makes them enemies of good
King Richard himself,
should provide us with entertainment
on this, the day of the
King's birthday.
Thank you, legendary Robin Hood.
Now, the game is very simple.
Fight or fry!
And of course,
the winner gets his freedom.
Cake!
Enjoy!
Poke him, poke him!
You don't have to do this, Allan.
Don't give them the satisfaction.
Even if you do kill me, they won't
let you go. Come on, poke him!
You know, if you had listened,
you might have understood.
You should have given
me a second chance, Robin.
How did you get to be so low?
That was always your problem, Robin.
So high and mighty.
So much better than everyone else.
No, just better than you.
Careful!
Ah! Well, it looks like our little
Robin red-breast is about to
become fried chicken!
Oh, I like this! Yes, it's very good!
Music! I'll give him music.
Outlaws! Get them!
Robin! Stop him!
John, thanks.
Traitor! Oi!
I let you in, but I'm
not letting you out.
Told you I was good with wood.
Time to disappear.
What's he doing?
Oh, no...
This way!
Guards!
Well, you said it would be
entertaining, but that
was really something!
And once again, gentlemen,
it was a pleasure doing
business with you. Bring the girl.
Marian...
I'm surprised you gave in
to his demands. I had to get
his signature!
But now...
I have his signature.
I'll send a squad of men. No.
No, we do this one quietly.
Bring your boy.
Home!
Here they come.
Get your hands off me.
Spirit! Just like your mother.
Will, you take out
the two outriders.
Much, John, Djaq,
you cover me while I rescue Marian.
What are they doing?
They're stopping!
Why have we stopped?
It's you! Yes, me.
Did you really think that I would
just smile and let you have Sussex?
A clue. No.
Hmmm?
Marian.
A little sweetener for you.
A little bonus.
You're safe now, Marian. Thank you.
Sweet. Very sweet.
What?
I'm trying to think of the good bit.
Even on a bad day, there's
always something good.
That's what my mother used to say.
But today, Winchester's betrayed us,
the pact has been signed.
Allan is Gisborne's man.
Marian's galloped off.
I mean, help me out here,
cos I'm struggling!
Much, shut up.
Robin's alive.
That's a good thing.
That's a very good thing. Because
for a minute there, that was
looking... Shut up, Much!
And if I may say so...
Much, shut up!
We can't just eat in silence!
Shut up, Much!
We have to go back and get
that pact.
It's proof of the Sheriff's treason.
Raaaghhh! It's empty!
We are gathered here to witness
my marvellous bird cage.
Robin! Get me down!
The Sheriff's selling Beatrice
to the Earl of Durham.
We're here to escort the
prisoner to the Earl.
Looking for me, Sheriff? Guards!
Where's the pact? I don't have it.
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk
jorrami - Shanghai, China