TREETON MINE
Out of the way. Get out of my way!
Son, you're too late. Your uncle's dead.
They're all dead!
Here, Father.
Gisborne's coming.
Tell him.
Go on, tell him!
Father, tell him his mine's a death trap.
You're not working down there no more.
We'll not go down there again.
You'll do as I say.
My brother' s dead.
And your behavior suggests
that you'd care to join him.
We're on strike.
Till it's shored up properly you'll not get a miner
down that death pit of yours.
You'd rather die here?
Yes.
I'd rather my soul roamed free up here
than get trapped down there again.
Stay!
They claim they would rather die
than go back down.
You're giving them choices.
Very good, Gisborne.
Well!
Enjoy the strike.
It'll make you feel... much better.
Goodbye.
They're all sacked!
- Really?
- Although we need the mine working...
Really?
Forward planning, Gisborne.
It's all under control.
There will be fresh workers arriving
who will do as they're told!
By tomorrow morning, this mine...
will be working.
Unlike you lot.
Bury this man's body with the others.
His family will pay for the grave.
If they will not work,
they will not be fed
until I see fit.
Anyone giving them assistance will hang.
You are all sacked. Go home.
Resynchro by ScarHand
Adapted by
ScarHand
Episode 5
"TURK FLU"
SHERWOOD FOREST
I knew you'd be like this.
If you're so bothered about
the archery competition...
I'm not!
If you're so bothered...
we could always have a little competition here.
I don't want to be in the archery competition.
Even if there is a silver arrow for the winner.
Just as well.
Because by the time we've done a little hunting
and had ourselves a decent feast,
there 'll be no time to go to Nottingham
and get ourselves hanged.
Father, I will avenge thee. Gisborne will pay.
Food parcels?
You can't give to us.
Gisborne's forbidden it.
He has spies everywhere.
Nothing like a tragedy to
bring out the do-gooders.
Where is your leader?
Where is Robin Hood?
Or are you alone?
Does Robin Hood think himself too important
to do his own mischief now?
A man of few words? No matter.
I'm sure I will hear your voice
when you plead for your life.
Not even an "Ouch".
"Ouch" costs nothing.
Surely you could utter an "ouch".
The trap worked.
We caught one. A cart.
Let's go. Let's go!
Heap! Rubbish heap!
And you! Rubbish heap.
Here. It's all I have of value.
Take it!
Pretty! Not very appetizing.
Livestock?
Take one.
And let me on my way.
They'll work for you.
They understand simple commands.
New men for the Sheriff's mine.
Slaves?
KNIGHTON HALL
Sir Guy.
She is home?
Yes.
Come through.
Father?
Are you hurt?
I caught it on a splinter on the door.
Let me see.
No, no, no, it's nothing.
What does Gisborne want?
I don't know. Come on.
Come down.
Marian.
To what do we owe the honor, Sir Guy?
Today I am attending...
I'm sure you would expect,
as you yourself may also have the intention...
But I thought, even so, that would not
necessarily make my question redundant.
Attending...?
The Sheriff's fair.
So what's your answer?
Forgive me, Sir Guy.
I do not yet understand the question.
I am inviting you to the fair
as my personal guest.
I fear I wouldn't be good company.
I'm tired.
You're ashamed of your hair.
But I thought of that. I have a gift for you.
It's a shawl...
You can...
I didn't sleep well. That is all.
You're declining my invitation?
Marian is delicate. She has wounded...
Wounded?
Pride.
Wounded pride.
My hair. As you guessed.
Thank you.
So you will come?
Good!
It should be an interesting day.
The Sheriff is convinced
that he'll lure Robin Hood.
He's put up a silver arrow as a prize.
Silver?
Yeah, but it won't work.
Hood is delegating his crimes to lackeys now.
I confronted one this morning.
An outlaw?
Or a disguised villager.
I'll find him.
He is marked, I inflicted a wound to his arm.
I was being kind. I should have killed him.
Well, I'll send a coach for you then.
Good day.
My Lady.
Sir Guy.
I think you owe me an explanation, young lady.
It was you, wasn't it?
There are people starving. People whose menfolk
have died at the mine. Should we do nothing?
What? You think you're Robin Hood now?
Is that it? You're in competition with Robin?
This is no competition.
I've been helping people far longer than him.
How much longer?
Three years.
I do not know you at all, do I?
I never thought I'd see this again.
Outrageous.
Disgrace.
Trading people.
Would you like some more wine?
I'm not being funny but...
you brought him here for a picnic?
We need him. He's our way into the mine.
There is no way into the mine.
We're going to stop this.
This is a gift.
We're going to close the mine once and for all.
We will stop this human trafficking.
I thought you were gonna slit me throat.
Or worse.
We don't do throat-slitting.
It's too messy.
Now you've eaten I'd like to feed
your prisoners.
Not meat.
It makes them spirited, you see.
Oh, and keep your distance.
Don't let them breathe near you.
Disease!
Some of our soldiers dropped dead
after getting too close.
Dropped dead?
Aye, one minute stood there
strong as you, the next...
brains dripping from their nostrils.
Water.
That'll do 'em.
They had some scraps earlier.
There used to be a decent living
to be made from selling folk.
Then the Pope goes and bans trading Christians.
Thank heavens King Richard likes
his wars abroad.
Will?
They need water.
Yeah, I'm on it.
Look, you seriously don't believe...
No!
Well, give them water.
Can't you see they're suffering enough?
I notice you're not doing it.
Listen, there is no disease.
It's ignorance and superstition and...
You are a genius!
John!
Have a drink with our friend.
What?
There 's something I need to find
in the forest. I need some time.
If he loses consciousness, then so be it.
No consciousness.
Could have been worse. If you'd not ordered
the slaves, we'd have had to close the mine.
"Slaves?" I prefer "out-workers."
This... mourning, it is tiresome.
Isn't it? Outlaw it.
Au moins, personne ne regrettera
nos nouveaux mineurs  quand ils rentreront.
Les femmes !
Comment arrivent-elles à faire un son si aigüe,
que vous voudriez vous percer vous-même les tympans ?
Ne vous marriez jamais, Gisbourne.
Les femmes! Gardez-les à distance. Pensez...
Pensez à un lépreux.
Juste après le départ à la guerre de Robin,
vous souvenez-vous que j’étais malade ?
Sarah la cuisinière me veillait.
Elle était toujours si gaie, et un jour, elle n’est plus venue.
Mon médecin m’a dit que sa fille était
très malade,
et l’a été très longtemps.
Quand tu dormais, j’allais voir Sarah
et donnais mes médicaments à sa fille.
Très noble, mais si tu te fais prendre...
Sarah était bouleversée
et je me suis occupée d’elle.
Et c’est là que j’ai décidé...
...que je pouvais aussi faire la guerre.
Je pouvais faire la guerre à la pauvreté.
Sir Edward, ma Dame ?
Sir Guy attend.
Nous devons nous débarrasser des gardes de la mine.
L’un de vous doit aller dans la cage
comme prisonnier.
Nous avons besoin d’un homme dedans pour
répendre la rumeur de la fièvre Turque.
Un volontaire !
Oui, Much.
Merci.
Allan.
Et alors, je dois manger ça ?
Non ! Seulement mâcher.
Il n’y a rien à craindre.
Quand les gardes croiront qu’un prisonnier
est malade, ils se sauveront !
Seulement les plus stupides y croiront.
Je veux dire...
La Fièvre Turque ?!
Les gens craignent l’inconnu.
Je n’ai pas eu peur.
Non !
Will, tu l’as prouvé toi-même.
Même si tu avais des doutes,
les hommes du shérif...
Ils vont foncer dans le panneau.
Ça ne marchera jamais !
J’ai une autre idée.
Au lieu de faire confiance
à la stupidité des hommes du shérif...
Pourquoi...
- Laisse !
- C’est à moi.
Volé !
Tu parles Anglais !
Tu ne vas pas aimer ça, Robin,
mais je crois que c’est Marianne
dans la voiture de Gisbourne.
Elle doit aller à Nottingham.
La fête du shérif.
VILLAGE DE TREETON
- Pourquoi ai-je fait ça ?
Pourquoi lui ai-je dit de défier Gisbourne ?
J’aurai du me taire.
Je lui ai dit de se battre pour lui-même.
Mais qu’ai-je fait ?
Gisbourne et le shérif se sont dirigés
vers moi et je n’ai rien fait.
Toi et moi, on va s’en sortir.
Ne t’inquiète-pas,
je ne vais rien faire de stupide.
Pourquoi ferai-je quelque chose
de stupide ?
Il y a juste une chose que je dois faire.
A plus tard.
Islama ?
Islama.
Je connais une façon simple et efficace
de te rendre ta liberté.
Et bien moins dangereuse que d’aller
à une mine fortement gardée.
Ouvrir la cage :
c’est simple et efficace.
Non...
C’est malin.
Renonce à ton Dieu. Alors,
on ne pourra plus t’acheter ni te vendre.
Renoncer à mon Dieu ?
Et clamer ta foi dans le Dieu Chrétien.
Mais tout est bien,
car les Dieux savent tout.
Donc ton Dieu saura que tu feints.
Pourquoi feindre d’être Chrétien ?
Vous tuez mon peuple au nom du Christianisme !
Les Chrétiens ne peuvent pas être vendus.
Le shérif ne t’achètera pas.
Tu peux être libre,
et nous pourrons rentrer manger.
Puisque c’est si facile...
Fait-le.
Renie ton Dieu.
Moi ?
Tu ne crois pas
qu’il peut lire dans ton cœur ?
Bien sûr que si.
Il le peut.
Je pourrai le renier, comme ça.
Je ne crois pas en Dieu.
Non, vraiment pas.
Voilà !
Aller ! Aide-moi à attacher Brooker.
J’y crois... de toute évidence.
Où est le marchant ?
Bien sûr, il doit être chez lui
Avec un gobelet de bon vin rouge.
Je regardais votre archer,
quel est son nom ?
Michael le Rouge.
Michael le Rouge !
Oui !
Seigneur,
Si vous préférez rentrer à Nottingham,
Je serai ravi de rester et...
Quoi ? Vous laissez la responsabilité
de la mine ? Désolé.
Rappelez-moi combien de minerai de fer
avez-vous remonté aujourd’hui ?
Vous ! Vous ne pouvez pas
aller faire quelques manœuvres ?
Rien de plus drôle à faire, aujourd’hui !
Gauche ! Gauche ! Gauche !
Nous renvoyons Brooker.
Quand le shérif et Gisbourne retournent à
Nottingham, Allan fait son truc...
...là, nous attaquons.
Voilà ce qu’on va faire.
Tu vends tes prisonniers au shérif,
comme prévu.
Allan sera juste derrière toi,
déguisé en prisonnier.
Si tu nous donnes, sache-le, nous pourrions
revoir notre position sur les égorgements.
Au feu ! Il y a le feu !
Punition de Dieu !
C’est de ma faute !
Je suis désolé, Seigneur !
J’ai vraiment la foi ! Vraiment !
Much, vas-tu te taire ?
Comment as-tu allumé ce feu ?
Laissez-nous partir !
Nous essayons de vous aider.
Vous nous avez volés pour nous revendre.
Vous ne valez pas mieux que lui.
S’il te plait, laisse-moi t’expliquer.
Si vous ne voulez pas nous aider,
alors vous pourrez partir. Tu as ma parole.
Quel est ton nom ?
Djaq.
Nous vous aiderons à fuir.
Mais si vous partez maintenant,
le shérif aura encore besoin de mineurs.
D’autres prisonniers arriveront dans un mois,
des gens comme vous.
Nous allons détruire la mine,
mais nous avons besoin de vous.
Comment nous aideras-tu à fuir ?
Le shérif vous achètera,
et nous vous donnerons cet argent.
Et nous vous mènerons à des gens
qui vous feront passer au port.
Vous avez fait de nous des ennemis.
Et maintenant, vous jouez au protecteur ?
Et demandez notre aide ?
Laisse-les décider ! Si vous voulez tenter
votre chance, alors allez-y.
Que disent-ils ?
Il dit que si vous ne nous laissez
pas partir, il vous tuera.
Ce n’est pas ce qu’il a dit.
Il a dit "nou sa lei".
Ça veut dire « prier ».
C’est ce que tu veux faire ?
Te laver et prier ?
Prier ? Nou sa lei ?
Ensuite nous aiderez-vous ?
S’il vous plait.
Gauche ! Gauche ! Et demi-tour !
Aller, regard droit !
Robin dit que nous devons...
Vous m’espionnez !
Non ! Robin, il... Nous devons garder...
Souviens-toi. Si ça tourne mal,
Tu mourras !
Ce retard...?
J’ai contourné la forêt.
Je ne voulais pas croiser les hors-la-loi.
Ai-je demandé un itinéraire ?
Non ! Le mois prochain, vous serez à l’heure,
Compris ?
Je serai à l’heure le mois prochain,
mon Seigneur.
Les chaînes !
J’aime ça, c’est bien.
Tu n’espères pas le prix fort pour celui-là ?
Il n’a pas de muscles.
Il a de l’esprit.
De l’esprit ?
J’ai vu plus d’esprit dans du fromage.
Qui es-tu ?
Je suis Rowan, fils de Dunne,
Et je vais tuer Gisbourne.
Si tu fais ça maintenant,
la mine restera ouverte.
Tu saboteras notre plan,
et mettras en danger un de mes hommes.
Si un seul meurt pendant le mois...
Je le retiendrai sur ta prochaine note.
Payez cet homme, Gisbourne.
Bien. Alors, au travail.
Le fer, le fer !
Je ne peux pas le laisser partir.
Si la mort du shérif ou de Gisbourne avait aidé Nottingham,
je les aurai tués il y a des mois.
Ils méritent de mourir.
Ne préfèrerais-tu pas de les voir
perdre tout ce à quoi ils tiennent ?
Comme quoi ?
La mine.
Le minerai est leur force, leur pouvoir.
Dedans !
Donnez-moi un autre travail, s’il vous plait !
Je travaillerai deux fois plus.
Tu n’es pas prisonnier de guerre,
tu es Anglais !
Je suis un déserteur.
Il y en avait plein comme nous avec...
C’est le Fièvre Turque.
Ça a anéanti tout le monde sauf moi.
La fièvre Turque ?
Nous, les Anglais n’y avons pas
de résistance.
Ecume aux lèvres, convulsions, pourriture.
On l’attrape en étant aussi proche que toi.
En quelques minutes,
ce liquide noir suinte du nez.
Allez travailler.
VILLE DE NOTTINGHAM
Je ne sais pas ce qui est pire,
Les veuves éplorées,
ou les paysans en parade.
Voyez-vous celui avec qui
vous vous êtes battu ?
Petit et blessé.
Bien que sa blessure soit
sous sa manche gauche.
Peut-être dois-je ordonner
de relever les manches ?
Peut-être devriez-vous vous rappeler
qui donne les ordres.
- Marianne.
- Mon Seigneur.
Les lepreux, Gisbourne. Les lepreux.
Lord save me! Save me!
Kill him, quick!
No! His blood will poison the air.
If you're gonna kill someone, kill me, please.
I can feel it starting in me!
Don't let me suffer.
What's that?
What's wrong with him? Quick!
Let's get out of here!
John! Keep him conscious.
What is this stuff? Tastes weird.
You'll be fine as long as you don't...
swallow it.
I said, don't swallow it!
You'll be fine.
Lay fires!
Around those beams and inside!
Let me light them.
I'll burn the place to t'ground.
I don't think so. We'll do that.
No! Let Rowan.
For his father.
Thanks to the rogue element amongst you,
I have been forced
to introduce new security measures.
The guilty object to security
because the guilty have something to hide.
I expect your full co-operation.
No man shall wear a sleeve on his left arm.
Oh, and, er...
do have a lovely fair. Thank you.
That one... Ooh, no.
Can I not keep the money?
You are a despicable, heartless, soulless
slave-trader, lucky to escape with your life.
That's a no.
Now go.
Go?
I'll see that you suffer!
You're letting him free?
He'll run straight to the Sheriff of Nottingham
and he and Gisborne will get on their horses...
Oh, I get it.
Get what?
They come here, you go to your fair.
Much as it saddens me to drag
Gisborne away from his wooing.
Gisborne's wooing?
Yes. Marian!
Remember the road I told you of?
- When you get to the Abbey...
- Mention your name.
Salaam alaikum, Djaq.
Alaikum Salaam.
God speed, Robin.
Much!
What's going on with the pilot fire?
I'll do it.
Primitive!
Well, I think we deserve
an outing to Nottingham
for such a smooth and successful operation. In fact,
apart from Allan's ingestion of a certain plant root...
Which will do what to me exactly?
...I'd say today has gone without a...
John!
Step forward Ford, son of Ford.
No sign of Robin Hood.
He's a coward.
Your Michael the Red better be a winner.
I don't want to have to give
this silver arrow away.
But surely if my man wins then...
the silver arrow will be mine.
If Robin Hood turns up and wins,
I will hang him and keep the arrow.
If he doesn't, and your man wins, he will return it.
I see...
Or I will hold you responsible.
When are we gonna burn the mine?
The Sheriff will be coming.
We can't until we've rescued John.
I'm going down there.
What?
To get stuck down there with him?
To help him!
We broke up the ladders for firewood.
If we can't pull him out...
He could be bleeding to death.
Maybe he just can't breathe.
So he suffocates, will that suit you better?
I'll go down there.
You need someone smaller.
You couldn't lift him.
I'll help him lift himself.
He could be bleeding.
Or suffocating, I heard.
My father was a physician.
Oh, great!
My father was a blacksmith.
It doesn't mean I can make a horseshoe.
No Djaq, wait. Please!
If there is something you can do.
I can stop the blood. Bring him round.
Then do it.
I need silver.
Look over there.
There must be some along with the iron ore.
Silver?
He wants paying now?
Traces of silver.
Not coins.
And water, quickly.
Do as he says.
Sorry, Lord, I will fast for a day and a night,
just please let us get him out.
Silver and this - acid.
Together make a liquid, stop the bleeding.
You don't need to understand.
Fine.
Save Gisborne's mine.
Save his wealth.
I'm going to go and tear his heart.
Let's see him woo a dead woman.
Not quite the bullseye. They say the peel of
an apple can predict who a woman will marry.
How?
The curl of the peel represents
the first letter of his name.
Our next archer is Michael the Red.
Ah. This will impress you.
I cut myself.
Your arm?
No, my hand.
Look.
I must have got some on my sleeve.
I think he wants us to follow him.
The mine's...!
Robin Hood.
Robin Hood, mm...
Fire!
Robin Hood, mine, fire.
Soldiers! Soldiers!
It's witchcraft.
Because we don't know what it is?
We made him trust us,
so we have to trust him.
Just drop the second line down.
Lower me down.
We should have gone after Brooker.
He'll have told the Sheriff by now.
Three days and three nights.
Not a morsel will cross my lips.
Just get us out of here.
Come on, big man.
Wake up...
Please!
Wake up!
There you go. Here, smell this.
It will help you...
Put this on.
Around your foot.
Pull!
Master, the Sheriff. What do we do?
Come on, John!
They're getting closer.
Come on, almost there! Pull, John, pull!
Get John into cover. I'll take care of this.
Into the trees. Go! Run!
Where are your guards,
on their refreshment break?
Get it out!
Get the fire out!
Does anyone smell burning?
Forget the outlaws! Save the mine!
Never forget the outlaws!
- Where are the others?
- Gone.
Hey, Rowan will be sorry he missed the blaze.
Him? He's gone to take revenge on his enemy.
Why? Gisborne's here.
His woman! To tear his heart
ut by killing his woman.
Gisborne hasn't got a...
Marian!
Nothing tempts pennies from the poor
like their hope of silver.
- Name.
- Rowan, son of Dunne.
Rowan, son of Dunne.
You'd not sooner keep your penny, son?
No, thanks. A penny well spent.
The next contestant will be...
This place is done for. You
should have expected him.
It was obvious this was a target.
With respect, my Lord, he was supposed to be
in Nottingham trying to win the silver arrow.
Over there.
He's following Marian, quick!
My Lady!
It'll be quick. I'm a good shot.
Your father died at the mine, didn't he?
How do you know?
It's difficult to explain.
But I know he must have loved you very much.
Everybody knew how dangerous it was
to go down that mine.
I told him not to.
He wanted to feed you. And your family.
Your lover knew it wasn't safe!
Your father must have known too.
I'm going to kill you. Make him suffer.
Make him understand loss.
At the cost of your own life?
It's what Gisborne deserves.
Your mother will lose
the man of her house twice.
What about her suffering?
I can't do nothing.
Just stand and do nothing.
Well, if you want to hurt the Sheriff,
win his silver arrow.
You say you are a good shot. Win it.
Use the silver, melt it down into coins.
You could feed your family for months.
Compensate all the miners ' widows.
Or would you rather shoot
an unarmed woman?
Marian?
Better late than never, I suppose.
Make sure this one wins the silver arrow.
Robin!
Help me.
Will then next contestant please take his mark!
The next contestant is Rowan, son of Dunne.
Bravo!
- Robin Hood!
- Seize him!
That arrow will feed the miners
for a whole winter.
Come on, let's go.
Him... Rowan.
No food or drink for one day and night
and then he'll be fine.
Oh, just as well seeing there 's
so little venison left...
You're fasting too, aren't you?
You made a promise...
...to God!
You don't know it was Him who got us out.
We might have got out of there anyway.
And if it had been Him,
there would have been a sign.
And there was no sign.
So I am gonna to build a fire, cook some food,
and there 's nothing any of you can do about it.
Champion of the Sheriff's Fair, and winner
of the silver arrow, Rowan, son of Dunne.
Ho! A sign!
Which means I have to fast.
Except God wants me to eat.
Oh! Quite a lot...
Djaq! Come and join us.
For good?
Well, I was thinking just for dinner, but...
And I was thinking for good.
Perhaps I should have let
your big friend here die, huh?
Then there would have been a vacancy.
It wouldn't be safe for you to join us.
For us or for him?
For her.
I guessed as much.
What's your name? Your real name.
Safiyya.
- Safiyya...
- But I prefer you to call me Djaq.
Djaq!
Well, your expertise did
help to save Little John's life.
For which we will be eternally indebted.
Anyone have a problem with
a woman joining the gang?
Er... Can you, er...
I'm a rubbish cook!
Well, looks like we're cooking dinner then.
If the fire thing was Djaq and not
a sign then...
does that mean I can eat or...