LOCKSLEY VILLAGE
Come on, pay up your taxes.
Guards, take this to the Sheriff.
Taxes, we do not like.
Well done, lads!
Hello, there.
We're winning.
Sorry, my Lord.
Come on, we are really winning.
And there's one more prize.
If we really wanna
beat the Sheriff...
NOTTINGHAM CASTLE
How do we know there
even is a Strong Room?
- A wild guess.
- How do you think?
A little bird told him.
A little Marian bird. Mmmm.
This is it.
Djaq.
This?
It's just a door.
No handle, no lock.
Robin!
I do not like this.
Will?
- Will, what's this?
- Much, don't touch that!
Why do I do it?!
- Right, let's check it out...
- Wait !
Look, look, look!
Turn it! Turn it! Turn it!
What is this?
The Sheriff's war chest.
And that, is our poor chest, lads!
We're not equipped for this.
Robin! Dogs!
I know. But we'll be back.
DEEP IN THE HEART OF ENGLAND
LIVES A LEGEND
ROBIN HOOD
Subtitles by The SubWood Team
Resynched and adapted
by ScarHand
EPISODE 2
BOOBY AND THE BEAST
Am I to drown
in everybody else's incompetence,
whilst Robin Hood steals everything
that is rightfully mine?!
A clue : no!
Do something about it, Gisborne!
My Lord, we now know
the Strong Room works.
It stopped Hood dead in his tracks.
Not dead enough!
Stealing our money from me
on the way here is one thing.
Stealing it from right under
my very nose is another!
The Black Knights are coming,
expecting their share out, Gisborne!
At this rate, there'll be
nothing left to share!
I want Hood caught, Gisborne.
I want him dead!
Meanwhile, how's your German?
- German?
- Pat, woman, pat! Don't rub.
- Ah, this guest you're expecting?
- Yes.
Count Friedrich of Bavaria
is one of the richest aristocrats
in Europe, by all accounts.
And stupid too. So...
You and he should get on.
He also has a weakness for gambling.
- Your alterations to the Great Hall?
- Yes.
We will extend the count
every courtesy, Gisborne.
I've taken my bath six
months early for a reason.
And then we shall
take the inbred booby
for every penny he's got.
LOCKSLEY MANOR
The Sheriff wanted me to thank
you all for your hard work,
building his new Strong Room.
Slave labour, more like.
Where's our money?
You'll get what's coming to you.
Now...
How did Robin Hood
find out about the Strong Room?
Somebody... must have told him.
Loose talk costs lives.
Good. Very good.
This world is full of idiots,
waiting to be parted
from their money.
But, as you know...
...the house always wins.
Now, I've had this table
put here in the middle,
because dice is the
count's favourite game,
and this is the first thing
I want him to see when he arrives.
Good. Carry on.
Ah! Lady Marian,
there you are.
Now, our guest
is due to arrive shortly,
and I'd like you to
be a friend to him.
I'd like you to make
him feel that his every desire
is yours to obey.
Every desire?
Show him a good time.
- What do you think, Gisborne?
- Good idea.
No, I won't!
Yes, you will, missy.
How's your father, so to speak?
Frail.
House arrest doesn't help.
But very much alive.
What if he sees my heart isn't in it?
Well, then pretend.
Deception comes
easily enough to you.
Now, when the count arrives,
I want you to smile for him,
and buy yourself a gown that...
how shall I say?
Stimulates the imagination.
The cheaper the better, I think.
Fetch.
Stand further off.
You make me feel
as if I am under arrest.
Trinkets for the lovely lady?
You call this fresh?!
You can't expect
people to eat this muck!
Hey! Stop it!
What are you doing?!
- They have you well guarded.
- Why did I choose this?
I can hardly breathe in there. Shhh.
What happened?
They're expecting a guest
today, a rich German count,
and they're making me fawn over him, making me dress up...
A German?
Do you thing the Sheriff and Prince
John looking for allies abroad?
He's not an ally, he's a gambler.
The Sheriff has set up
gaming tables in the castle.
He's planning to fill his new
Strong Room with the count's money.
You see?
Another good reason to rob him.
Robin, please,
do not go down there, it's dangerous.
You know me.
I like a challenge.
You don't have to do this!
Yes, I do.
Without me, you wouldn't even
know there was a Strong Room.
- "England needs me?"
- Yes.
England needs me.
England needs us.
And I need you.
Guard?
We need to break
into the Strong Room,
and Stephen was the first person
I thought of.
- Is he a friend of your father's?
- A teacher. A legend in his day.
He doesn't work anymore
but he used to be famous.
He worked in the Orient.
They were his apprentices
Gisborne's lot killed this morning.
Will?
Still passionate? Angry?
- A lot to be angry about.
- True. And your skills?
You're using them, not wasting them?
- I'm with Robin Hood.
- Good.
That is not a waste.
Do not touch that, please.
I have seen this
type of work before.
It is Persian, no?
It was my wife's.
The men who died had
families, wives and children.
I want them to be taken care of.
They will be. You have my word.
If there is any information
you can give us...
- anything that they told you...
- Look, I'm not being funny...
We've seen this death trap
in action, right?
And now we're gonna take
advice from a blind man?
When a man loses his sight,
he finds compensation
in the senses that remain.
I do not intend
on joining your mission.
But I might be of assistance
in planning it.
Yes, but what can you possibly know
about the Sheriff's Strong Room?
A great deal.
I designed it.
NOTTINGHAM TOWN
Marian.
Who'd have thought?
Ah! Count Friedrich!
Welcome to Nottingham.
Tell me, are all the
roads in England so bad?
I feel like I've been
beaten like an egg.
Your safety was my first concern.
I organised the route
so as to avoid the forest.
We couldn't have your
fortune or your good self
falling into outlaws' hands.
Myself and my men are a match
for any rustic ruffian, I assure you.
Had I known what awaited me here,
I would have employed winged horses.
Lady Marian has made it
her personal responsibility
to make sure your stay
is as comfortable as possible.
Really?
I'm very happy to
make your acquaintance.
Oh, come, come,
acquaintances are for
old ladies and priests.
We will dispense
with such formalities.
I am already your friend,
and always your servant.
Do be careful there!
Take the chest to my rooms.
It's a few shillings
for the gaming tables.
Tell me, do you play, Lady Marian?
Such pursuits are not
entirely to my tastes.
Then we must find pursuits
that excite you more!
Tell me, do you ride?
Come on, come on.
Leaving so soon?
I got your message.
What have you got for me?
Robin wants to have
another go at your Strong Room.
Obviously. And?
Well, that's it.
It'll be the next few days though,
- so you'd better be ready.
- Don't waste my time.
I don't pay for obvious.
You'll have to do better than that.
Like what?
Who told Robin Hood
about the Strong Room?
I don't know.
I don't. Honest.
It's early days in our relationship.
But come to me again with nothing,
and I will be very disappointed.
- Understand?
- Yeah. Got it.
Don't make me wait too long.
The designs were not meant
for the Sheriff.
They were a commission.
- By whom?
- A Persian general.
I did not complete the work,
but I kept the plans with me always.
Then, not long ago, my apprentice
sold them to the Sheriff.
His family was starving,
I can't blame him.
He died for it.
No expense has been
spared for your gambling pleasure.
Food, drink, company.
We aim to please in every respect,
isn't that right, Marian?
Is this your idea of sport?
You do not like the skittles,
my lady?
But it is a charming game.
A child's game, surely?
Do men really waste their money
playing this?
No waste if the prize
is worth having.
Come, let me show you.
Gently caress the ball...
Danke schön. Thank you.
Forgive me, Count Friedrich,
my aim was a little wide.
This is the door,
the only entrance or exit.
There's no windows.
The room itself is
20 feet long by 20 feet wide.
Both walls are
honeycombed with blow holes,
each loaded with arrows,
primed to strike a specific spot.
You step on the wrong stone and...
- Which stones?
- My great innovation.
It changes.
Well, that's not possible. Is it?
A weighted wheel beneath
the floor rotates regularly.
Each turn defines a new route,
changing the order
of the sprung stones.
So, any stone can trigger a trap
at any time?
I did not say it would be easy.
This, I do not like.
Come, Lady Marian,
bring me some luck.
- Where've you been?
- An errand.
He's quite taken with her.
Encourage him.
He'll lose quicker.
Marian just needs a little coaxing.
It's her way.
She says no when she means yes.
Really?
Then I shall relish the challenge.
Lady Marian, I cannot roll
unless you help me.
- No, thank you.
- No, no, Lady Marian, I insist.
- Lady Marian wins!
- You see?! I win!
Perhaps you will excuse me.
I have a headache.
Oh, how terrible for you.
If I may, I find that gentle rubbing
of the temples is most effective.
You are very kind,
but I think I will go and lie down.
As hard as it is,
we must let you go.
Thank you
for your understanding, Count.
Quite the beauty.
I must confess, when I first
came to this country,
I thought I would not like it.
But now,
I like it very much!
You'll be up against time.
Opening the door turns an hourglass
set beside the base of the plinth.
When the sand runs through,
a final fail-safe is triggered.
I shouldn't ask, but what, exactly?
There is a vault
behind the back wall,
containing a vat of molten lead.
It is kept at a constant heat
by the fires of the kitchen.
When the hourglass is empty,
the vat is turned.
The liquid
flows into a series of gutters.
- The pipes in the walls.
- Burning liquid sprays out,
covering the entire room.
Anyone inside
would not stand a chance.
And yet...
the coins remain intact, because
they're harder than the soft lead!
Well, all I'm hearing is arrows,
lead and certain death.
Encouraging!
How long before the hourglass
runs through?
A slow count of eight score and ten.
In a count of 170,
you've got to get to
the money and get it out?
Nice of you to join us, Allan.
Well...
I still think you're mad.
But if you want some more help...
We are mad!
We should stick to robbing
merchants in the forest!
That, we are good at.
Then we will work
until we get better at this!
We'll meet near the old barn, near Clun.
What for?
To practise.
We are going to build
this Strong Room over there.
Good!
- Excuse me, can I pass?
- Orders.
No-one passes, not even you.
Sheriff's private room.
Lady Marian?
Oh, no!  Let me pass,
just this once. Please.
Well, what's in it for me?
Nice gown, very fetching.
A bit of a new look for you.
- How dare you?!
- I'm just being friendly.
How about a little kiss?
How about a little smack?!
Excuse me!
- You are an impressive fighter.
- Yes, I know.
And you are also very
impressive in many ways.
Please.
- Are you not glad I came after you?
- I made no invitation.
You feign a headache and retire.
I follow.
This is the way that
trysts are made all over the world.
Well, this one is all over,
all right?
As of now.
- Gisborne !
- I mustn't be found here.
Quickly.
Come, quick!
There should be a guard
on that door at all times.
- I'll look into it immediately, my Lord.
- Wait.
First things, first.
Tomorrow's meeting. Come here.
There.
I have outlined the division
of the money in my Strong Room.
You will be in charge of making sure
our friends, the Black Knights, get their share.
You wish to strengthen our forces in the south?
- The share is generous.
- Strategy, Gisborne.
The King is most likely
to land there on his return.
Besides...
there will be plenty of funds in the war
chest, after our German booby loses tonight.
We'll make sure he loses big.
- What if the count surprises us and wins?
- Wins?
That buffoon?
"Oh, I feel like I've been
beaten as an egg."
Mincey oaf.
But you have made
provision just in case?
You know me too well, Gisborne.
Of course.
All eventualities
have been considered.
Dice that only roll one way.
In our favour.
Make sure Marian is with us tonight.
What does he think?
That I will not be suspicious of
an invitation from a sheriff in...
Where are we?!
That I will not do my homework
and find out who he is?
Does he think that his reputation
has not spread to Europe?
And you... you are in on this plan.
Do you think this is not the
first time I have been offered a girl...
- to take my eyes from the table !?
- Let go of me!
Do you people think
that I am a complete idiot?
Yes, until now. Which is
exactly what you wanted, isn't it?
- What do you mean?
- Oh, come on.
The way you fight.
You're no booby.
I don't think a booby
does homework on his hosts.
It suits you to have
people think you're an idiot.
It helps sometimes.
People play less cautiously,
but I am no cheat.
And for what it's worth,
I am no lackey of the Sheriff.
So, we are both players.
And what will you do?
Do? Leave.
If the Sheriff is loading the dice,
I cannot win.
I will be struck
by a sudden illness.
Don't leave. Help me.
Help you?
You heard the Sheriff.
He's using the money
to plot against the King.
I have friends who would like
to relieve him of his money
before he distributes it.
- And that will have to be tonight.
- This is a dangerous game.
But you're a player.
The hourglass turns now! One...
- Arrow!...
- Two, three, four, five...
- John, no!...
- six, seven...
I am stone!
- Not there John, no.
- Well, where?
- There!
- Hang on, stone? I thought he was pit?
- No, I'm pit!
- Stop! Please! Shut up!
Lives depend on this.
The wives and families of the dead.
Not to mention
what will happen to England
if the Sheriff
starts to give out that money.
If we are going to defeat
the Strong Room,
then we have to work as a team,
and that means discipline.
What do you think you're doing?
- You stay in the castle.
- Believe me, I would rather stay here.
I am merely doing as I am instructed.
The lady Marian
is to ride out with me.
No, no, no, no.
Well, if I do not ride,
I might be out of sorts,
and if I'm out of sorts,
I might decide not to
play the tables at all tonight.
Very well.
I will provide you with an escort.
Guards!
The forest
is a very dangerous place.
Sheriff, we are both
men of the world, ja?
Perhaps alone with nature, out in the
forest amongst the trees and flowers,
Lady Marian might
not play so hard to get.
No guards.
Don't be late back.
There is a way, you know.
A way to what?
There is a way to do all the things
you need to do and still find love.
You're a troubled soul.
Be patient.
You will prevail.
And you can tell all that
by just feeling my face?
No. Your friend Much
was telling me earlier.
Now I'm better acquainted
with your Sheriff,
I begin to understand why you have
such admiration for this outlaw.
- It's not just me.
- I didn't mean just you.
I think I would like to
take to the woods
and fight injustice
like your Robin Hood.
What do you think?
Why does a potential freedom fighter
waste his life gambling?
I am a count.
My life has been managed
since the day that I was born.
Tradition, etiquette...
It's all so safe.
I crave danger.
You wouldn't understand.
Don't be so sure.
Are you sure you know
how to find these friends of yours?
I'm hoping they're gonna find us.
They already have!
Who's your new friend?
Count Friedrich Berthold
Otto von Wittelsberg,
from the German Duchy of Bavaria.
And your friend.
- This is the Sheriff's guest?
- Yes
And you trust him enough
to bring him here to meet me?
- He wants to help us.
- Oh.
It seems we have a
common desire, Robin Hood.
I mean, we both wish to see
the Sheriff broken and humiliated.
- Marian and I were discussing...
- First name terms!
- Jealous?
- Of him?
Marian has a proposition for you.
If you want to rob the Strong Room,
you have to do it tonight.
Not possible.
We're not ready.
Well, then don't bother at all.
The Sheriff will divide the
money between the Black Knights
and they're coming tomorrow.
After that the Strong Room
will be empty.
I don't like that look.
- That look means trouble.
- Robin, it's certain death.
Well,
if that money is going to be
used to finance weapons and men
to kill the King, then...
then we are dead already.
- Kiss me.
- What?
Otherwise what will they think
we've been doing all this time?
We have a budding
romance after all.
So it would seem.
Maybe one more,
to make it really convincing?
Careful.
- Remember the skittles?
- Ah, ja.
He's succeeded where you failed,
Gisborne.
So, come on...
money to be made.
You. Stop.
I want the count's goblet filled at
all times tonight. You understand?
Go on.
Put it here.
You know what to do.
There.
The money you lose
tonight goes into that.
It connects directly to
the Strong Room below.
- Now, once it's in there...
- Ja, ja, I know.
Our outlaw friends
will steal it back for me.
It seems unfair. No gambler
likes to lose, even on purpose.
Well, if you win,
the Sheriff will never let
you leave Nottingham alive.
I was running towards the
Great Hall and I tripped and I fell,
and I think I've hurt my ankle!
Look!
Men are so obvious.
- Now, play as long as you can.
- Ja.
Take your time, and then,
when we get the
signal, start losing.
Oh, I didn't recognise you!
- What?
- Nothing.
- You wanna dress like a girl more often.
- Oh, I do, do I?
It's just a thought.
Count Friedrich.
Ah! Fortune awaits, good luck!
Lady Marian is my good
luck charm this evening.
You know, Gisborne,
I have a new-found
respect for Marian.
Are we to endure
this ritual at every turn?
Let him lose in his own way.
And if he doesn't,
we'll switch the dice!
I won!
Throw.
Count Friedrich wins!
The count wins!
Again! I win!
No dogs this time.
Where's the arrow?
I don't know.
Go on, Will.
Poison.
That wasn't there before.
They've changed the sequence.
- Well, then we can't go on!
- Tonight is our only chance.
It the sequence has changed,
our practising is for nothing!
If we do not try,
then all the money in there
will be given to the Black Knights.
And England will be lost!
Yes, and if we're dead,
then that's MY England lost!
We go.
All right.
But if we die,
don't come running to me.
Go on, Will.
John?
Ready?
Djaq? Tell Marian we're in.
Allan, John, keep watch.
Much?
Do not take your eyes off
that hourglass. Bow.
They're in.
Better start losing.
If that's the way he loses,
you may have to use your contingency
plan sooner than expected.
We're about even. It's early yet.
Don't think about that.
Marian.
We have to start losing.
- I am doing my best.
- Time is running out.
Oh, brilliant.
Go on!
Watch out!
Sheriff,
let us make things interesting.
Everything I have,
against the entire contents
of your Strong Room.
As we say in Bavaria,
"Das letzte Hemd hat keine Taschen."
"You cannot take it with you."
Sheriff, what do you say?
It's only money.
I agree.
It's such a momentous game.
Might I suggest...
...a change of dice?
As you wish.
Ja.
I see.
Ja...
You see?
It's easy once you know how.
Excellent!
For luck.
The house wins!
Hang on...
what's this?
Master, please get out,
there's no time!
Oh, Sheriff.
It's another trick.
It's an illusion.
An image
thrown onto a sheet of glass.
The money is not here.
Lady Marian,
you have brought me
nothing but bad luck.
Your attentions
are no longer welcome.
Auf Weidersehen!
Well done, Marian.
It wasn't so hard, was it?
No... It wasn't.
Excellent. The war chest
has doubled in one night.
Master, get out of there.
What are you doing?
Just leave it!
We've come this far!
- Come on. What's he doing?!
- Wait!
The money is here.
The bags, quickly!
Come on, Much. Give it...
All right, all right!
Marian.
My men have the coach ready.
Your friends?
If they have succeeded,
we will know soon.
And if they haven't?
The hourglass!
Why do we leave everything...
to the last... second?!
Well...
I find it's more fun that way.
No...
Come on, go!
The Strong Room...
Guards!
Help! You men, quickly!
The Sheriff is under attack!
Look at YOU!
You must be careful.
If I can see the friendship
between you, so may others.
Don't worry,
I crave the danger.
If you're ever in Bavaria,
I remain, my lady,
your servant, your booby...
and your friend.
You're funny.
- You are beautiful.
- You're leaving.
My war chest,
and the booby's money...
But they can't have done! No! No!
No! No!
No!
Count Friedrich will take
you as far as the coast.
I can't thank you enough
for your help, Stephen.
Yes, you can.
The families of the
men that died.
We'll look after them.
You will prevail.
Now, you're sure about your route?
You stick to the smaller roads.
The Sheriff will have
the main ones covered.
Another bumpy ride.
This country...
By the time I get home,
I will be perfectly scrambled.
This is your money.
And thank you.
England is forever in your debt.
Take it. Keep it.
What?
England's debt is to Lady Marian.
Not me.
Spend it wisely, Robin Hood.
About Marian...
One gamble I would have
given anything to win.
You are a lucky man, Robin Hood.
Farewell.
Right...
Work to do.
I'm not being funny but...
the poor have it easy.
I don't think so, Allan.
This is what we do, lads.
We've turned war chest
into poor chest.
Well, come on. We have four
more villages before sun down.
I've been thinking.
We've never been to Germany.
If things don't work out here, then...
maybe the count would
have us over there.
Much, Count of Schleswig-Holstein!
What's so funny?
I could be Count of Schleshy...
whatever.
It's hard to be count of a place
you can't pronounce!
No, not necessarily.
Nah. Sovereign of Sherwood, mate.
That's you.
Well, that's us, lads.
Sovereigns of Sherwood.
NEXT TIME
- It's Gisborne.
- Now!
He's creating a new armour.
- We need to take his toys away.
- Get them!
I want 5000 suits of armour.
I'm afraid I can't let you keep
these diamonds, Gisborne.
And I can't let you take them.
When there are people
who know our little secret,
those people have to die.
I need your permission
to leave the castle.
Hit him!
A man wearing this
would be invincible.