SHERWOOD FOREST
Robin Hood!
This way!
Come on!
Take cover.
Robin, the Sheriff's in range.
It's the perfect shot. One arrow,
it's the end of the reign of terror.
For your crimes against the
people of Nottingham, Sheriff.
You're rubbish, Daniel. It's my turn
with the bow.
- I'm Robin!
- You're always Robin!
I get this boring piece of tree.
Hey!
Mark, get up.
Now!
You see?
I told you I could do it!
Nothing can penetrate it.
- Excellent work.
- What else did you expect?
Unfortunately...
this secret cannot leave the forest.
Get them!
DEEP IN HE HEART OF ENGLAND
LIVES A LEGEND
ROBIN HOOD
Subtitles by
The SubWood Team
Resynched and adapted by
ScarHand & Kiry
EPISODE 3
CHILDHOOD
Go round, go round!
Mark, come on!
Come on out.
You can trust me.
I'm Lord of Locksley.
Lord of Locksley...
- Let go of me!
- It's all right.
Hang on, I know you.
You're Marian's
stableboy at Knighton Hall!
How do you know that?
What happened?
I know Gisborne's up to something,
cause I've been tracking him.
- I don't trust you.
- All right.
- Tell me your name.
- Daniel.
- Daniel, do you know who I am?
- No.
I'm Robin Hood.
So what were you doing up there?
Nothing! Playing.
- Playing Robin Hood.
- What, playing a loser?
We didn't see anything, sir.
If you didn't see anything?
Why would you say
you didn't see anything?
We won't say a thing, sir.
You can be sure of that.
Wait!
We can use them.
Send them to the mine.
And send word to the Sheriff.
Success...finally.
Gisborne's got my friends.
He's got my friends!
I can help you with your friends,
but I need you to tell me what you saw.
A man. They shot him,
but he didn't die.
The arrows bounced off.
And then Sir Guy
killed him with a knife.
And now he's going to kill my friends.
The arrows bounced off what?
Armour. He was
wearing armour - funny armour.
Let's see about your friends,
shall we? Come on.
- Thank you.
- I thought you said "chicken"?
This is a pretty
small chicken, Much.
Yeah. Again.
And have you seen in the trees?
No squirrels lately!
It's not squirrel.
And what happened
to the vegetables,
All you eat is bread and meat.
We are surrounded by
edible berries and leaves.
- Where's the fruit, the salad?
- Salad?!
Men eating leaves?
There's only one use
for leaves around here.
And you wouldn't want to
be eating them afterwards!
Up!
We need to go. This is Daniel.
His friends are in danger.
And if I'm not much
mistaken, so are we.
- What's up?
- It's Gisborne.
He's creating
a new armour.
We need to take his toys away,
so arm yourselves.
Little John!
Will! Allan A Dale!
And you must be
Djaq, the Saracen. Wow!
Sorry. Who are you?
That...
- That's Much.
- Oh, yes! The servant.
Very funny.
- What?
- Nothing.
It's just...
I thought you'd be... taller.
I'm quite tall.
But you know, like a giant.
Men tend to lie about their size.
You ready? Give me that.
You won't be needing it.
Come on. Let's go.
They've gone.
It's Mark's.
See the M?
- That's good.
- We play outlaws.
I'm Robin Hood.
Well, I hope you're better at playing
Robin Hood than I am.
No.
I let go of his hand. Gisborne's
lot were coming, and I just ran.
- Then you did the right thing.
- Really?
If you hadn't run, you would have
been caught too. What good is that?
Listen...sometimes,
in the heat of battle,
there isn't time
to watch your gang's back.
Wagon tracks.
They've gone to
Locksley, all right?
Come on. Let's go.
Let's see it, then. The magic metal.
Is this it?
- Indeed.
- Very thin.
Thin... yes.
But that is its beauty. With this
on, a soldier can dance in battle.
- Yes. How does it work?
- That is my secret,
and I am the only man west of
Jerusalem who knows how to make it.
Ooh, lah-de-dah!
O ye of little faith.
Come, I will show
you a little of my art.
Stinks like a Turk's trousers.
To the artist, it is a beautiful smell.
Here, my special ingredient.
This, to me, is more
precious than diamonds.
- I hope so. More expensive than diamonds.
- Watch!
Don't cough. Inbreathe, inhale!
- Enjoy.
- Enjoy?!
Water for the Sheriff.
Believe me, in time,
you will grow used to it.
You will get used
to it, my friend.
Start production. I want
5000 suits of armour.
My lord, that is a very great
undertaking.
- Yes. Your fee is very generous.
- The King of France would pay double.
You are indeed an artist.
Double?
An inconvenience. But think of the gain.
An army of indestructible warriors.
Put this safely in my room.
Gisborne...
have you started a family,
- without telling me?
- My lord...
Children.
I caught them snooping around
in the woods, my lord.
Tell me they didn't see you
testing the armour in the forest.
Why didn't you kill them?
My lord, I decided we could use them in
the mines. We need extra labour so...
You see,
just when I thought I could let you out
by yourself, to flap your little wings,
you go and show compassion!
When there are people who know
our little secret,
those people have to die.
- It's the back door plan!
- Come on. We move.
Every time!
Round here.
Wait.
I don't like waiting.
Especially behind a cow.
- It's not good for my constitution.
- Much! Shhh.
- Hood? !
- It's Locksley, to you.
No.
Locksley's mine now.
This Locksley will never be yours!
Still sore?
Face facts, Hood!  you lost, I won!
Will... I need Allan and Djaq now! Go!
You want hearts and minds.
But you'll never have them.
No matter how many people you kill.
No matter how many
children you terrify.
No matter how much armour you put on.
You overestimate me, Hood.
You know that sometimes at night, I get
one of your servants to rub my feet.
I don't care if she has a heart
or a mind!
Right. Step over there,
cover your eyes. I'll be back.
Ok?
Ah...rescued by outlaws.
Quelle surprise!
We fight. Take this.
Defend me from above.
Well, this should be fun.
Come on! Where's
Mark? You've left Mark!
He's all right. We need you. Now.
- You lot, stay here.
- In. Go in.
I'm afraid I can't let you
keep these diamonds, Gisborne.
And I can't let you take them.
The Black Knights would be VERY
disappointed.
Then it's a stalemate.
- Shall we toss a coin for it?
- Not stalemate. Checkmate!
I'll see you!
Ah! Son of a camel!
Hood!
In the heat of the battle, there is
time to watch your gang's back.
Thanks, Dan. Go! Go!
This way!
This is for the poor!
Got you!
Come on! Get in. Get in.
- Is everyone all right?
- No, wait.
Where's Daniel?
Gisborne! Robin Hood just knocked
one of my men out with a wooden box.
Now, you tell me it was not the
box with the black diamonds in it!
Five men and a boy!
Hostage!
Daniel!
Robin Hood'll be back.
He'll rescue me.
We're counting on it.
People of Locksley!
Let Robin Hood know this.
We want our box and its
contents back by morning.
Or his little friend...
will be punished.
His little friend will die.
Robin, we get the boy... now.
No. We stop and we think, John.
You've got to give
him what he wants.
Robin, take a look at this metal.
It is Damascus steel,
or something like it.
A man wearing this
would be invincible.
Western weapons would
be useless against this.
We can't let the
Sheriff make this stuff.
That's why I took the stones.
- We cannot give them back, Robin.
- I know.
- But we can't let the boy die.
- What do we do?
Thank you.
My guard has gone for bread.
We have two minutes.
I heard about the boy.
What do you want?
The Sheriff and Gisborne are
developing a new armour.
It'll make him and the Black Knights
invincible. We have to stop them.
- We can't risk the boy.
- I know.
But if the Sheriff defeats the king
then how many more lives will be lost?
My guard! I will get the boy out
tonight.
- How? You're under house arrest.
- I will find a way.
That's the whole point
to me being here.
Here, take this.
So, if Marian succeeds,
we don't have to do any of this?
But if she doesn't, we need a plan.
Right...
we need to trade Daniel and
the black diamonds in open space.
And that's here. So when
the Sheriff has the diamonds
and we have Daniel back safely,
then we can strike.
We can't just nick them back, though.
He'll have the place surrounded,
won't he?
May as well just walk in, hands in
the air, saying, "Shoot me."
- We could destroy them.
- We'll have to.
We need something that burns quickly.
- Pitch.
-  What about straw?
Straw is fast,
but it's not hot enough.
Pitch.
- Wood?
- Wood's hot, but it's not quick enough.
Pitch. Fast-burning and hot.
Pitch! Good thinking, Mark.
I could make a new box. Choose
the right wood. Something thin.
Could line it with pitch.
We'd carry the black diamonds
in that to the Sheriff,
and you could shoot it, Robin.
A flaming arrow.
And the rocks will explode.
Good idea, Will. We'll test it
in the morning.
Much... Is this rat?
- It's chicken.
- I can't see any feathers.
No? We haven't seen any squirrels!
Right.
I don't suppose anyone round here
has actually noticed,
but I have to do everything
you all have to do, AND...
keep this larder stocked.
So if anyone else would care of
run themselves, ragged in the forest,
trying to catch us some massive animal,
then you can be the servants!
My lord.
My lord, I beg a favour of you.
I have prepared a pass for you to sign.
And I need your permission
to leave the castle.
- Why?
- You so decreed it.
No, no.
I mean, why do
you need to leave?
To visit Guy.
Gisborne?
Well...he's had a bad day.
I don't advise it.
He should have killed...
some little boys.
And now it's a mess.
Well, then, perhaps now is a good
time for me, to offer him an apology.
At this hour?
And in your finest silks.
I hope to make
my peace with him.
Please.
Well... missy.
If it were me...
...I would slap your fickle face.
Both of them.
This is a pass for the castle gate.
But underneath is an order to send
Daniel back to the castle,
so the Sheriff can
question him tonight.
Gisborne won't release him to us.
But he will release him to...
a castle guard.
I'll do it.
Are you aware of the risk?
- If Guy catches you...
- Don't worry.
- He'll be putty in my hands.
- You're a brave man.
Well...
I'll go ahead.
I told the Sheriff I'd call on Gisborne,
so I must show my face there.
Good luck.
Forgive me.
Marian, it's late.
Why so urgent?
I wish to speak to you...
about a personal matter.
I'll send for you.
Yeah. What is it?
There is bad blood between us.
You overestimate yourself
I had feelings for you.
I made no bones about that.
But now...
I feel nothing.
And I have larger
concerns... ambitions.
Is there no hope of a reconciliation?
I know you are a man
capable of compassion.
I offer...
I offer friendship.
Guy...
- What?
- I don't know.
Marian, what is this all about?
- It's about friendship, that's all.
- No.
This isn't about friendship.
You want your freedom back.
That's what this is all about.
And I can't give that to you.
You and your father, you've made
your own bed.
Sorry, master. There's a messenger
from the Sheriff.
I should go.
That looked friendly.
- You were spying on me?!
- I was not spying on you!
- I was making sure you were safe.
- I was safe.
Shouldn't you be making sure
Allan is safe?
I've played my part.
Marian...
This is the Sheriff's official seal.
Who gave you this?
Listen, mate...
the fact you're standing there, holding
that, means I've stopped Robin, right?
I don't know where it's from.
You know, I start asking too many
questions, they're gonna blow my cover.
- You did well to bring this to me.
- Yeah!
I know. I think I'll
have a bit more wine.
So... your plan's failed.
What will Robin do?
Well, if this doesn't work,
it's a straightforward swap.
Diamonds for boy. Robin wouldn't risk
the boy's life, not for anything.
How very noble of him.
But there must be some trick.
What's it worth?
Pitch,
in a box containing the diamonds.
Boy runs free. Robin fires
a flaming arrow and...
...bye-bye, diamonds.
- What will you tell Hood?
- Oh, that's easy.
I'll just say I was tumbled.
You recognised me, we had a fight,
which obviously I nearly won.
I left you for near dead, fleeing the
manor, dispatching guards as I go.
Good idea. Mm.
- What was that for? !
- Believability.
Allan?
- Quick. Let's go. Gisborne rumbled me.
- How did you get out?
We had a scrap. I knocked him out.
Unbelievable.
Luckily, his guards didn't hear us,
but...
- we should scarper before he comes to.
- Right. Come on.
Robin...
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, it's not your fault, is it?
We'll tell the others and Marian.
It's Mark's pitch plan. Come on!
Right...
Let's go.
Guards, take your positions.
You, over there, move it! Move it!
Here, boy. See that?
If Robin Hood doesn't show up,
these people here are going
to watch you swing.
Sit.
Well... I can see the sun,
no sign of your saviour.
- He'll come.
- Well, let's hope so.
For your sake!
Hood!
Oh, Robin Hoo-oo-ood!
Stay where you are, Hood.
My smith will meet you in the
middle. Check the merchandise.
If it's all right, you get
the key to the boy.
No, Sheriff! You can make the exchange.
Otherwise your archers there will kill me.
And if they do fire upon me,
my men will kill you.
Out of the way! Clear!
Go to your houses. Move!
Oh, lah-de-dah!
Right, let's get on with it.
Allan, Djaq, take the archers
on the left. You two, with me.
Stop!
You cannot release the child
to an outlaw.
Somebody find me a box and put this
woman inside it!
Release him to me.
I'll see that he gets home safely.
Locksley, this makes no difference
to you. You have my word.
- I accept these terms.
- Good for you.
Go on, then.
Now...
...the black diamonds. Not yet!
Allow me to check
the merchandise first.
Oh, so sorry.
You are, after all,
as Lady Marian pointed out...
...a murderous outlaw.
- The Sheriff's guessed our plan.
- Unbelievable.
Something wrong, Hood?
Gisborne! All yours.
That's the armour!
Enjoy!
Robin!
- Stay back! My sword!
- Master!
Look at that!
- What now, Locksley?
- Run!
Master!
- Robin!
- Don't touch him. Stay with the archers.
No, John! Wait!
Locksley will
always be mine.
What's he doing?
Is that the best you can do?
What now?
Playing outlaws with the
children?! Goodbye, Hood!
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yes!
Tell your men to withdraw, Sheriff!
Another exchange,
the black diamonds for Gisborne.
And your other bag.
Well,
- How long can you hold your breath?
- My lord, please!
You... You seem to have overestimated
Gisborne's importance to me.
Make sure he's safe.
Not even you would let him die.
I have everything I could want.
- Sheriff!
- Not again...
- Let him live!
- Who?
Guy!
- Marian, what are you doing?
- I am asking you to reconsider.
You are helping Hood!
Quite the opposite. I'm reminding you
that Sir Guy is your most loyal servant.
- My lord, please!
- Let him die.
He is noble, and a good man.
He must be worth more to you
than a sack of rocks.
I will have those rocks.
Then I will kill this man.
Without him...
- are the rocks really any use?
- Eh...no. No, they are not.
I'm the only man west of Jerusalem
who can make them work their magic.
- My lord!
- Shut up!
My lord, I will
get you more rocks.
You'll be punished for this, Marian.
Be in no doubt.
You'll be punished.
Get out.
Burn these.
You saved my life. I'm grateful.
I could not watch you die
and do nothing.
- You saved Robin, too.
- That was incidental.
Was it?
Marian, I've been assuming that
since Hood became an outlaw...
that you've had nothing further to do
with him. Was I wrong to assume that?
- No.
- Because if you were,
associating with an outlaw...
the punishment would be more severe
than house arrest. The punishment...
- would be death.
- Would you prefer me to have let you die?
Gisborne. Stay there!
Wait, wait!
I cannot work in this environment.
My dear friend, we could make an
arrangement to increase your fee.
In France, they know
how to treat an artist.
- What were you thinking?
- Guy is your faithful servant.
I was preventing you
from making a mistake.
You do not prevent me
from making a mistake!
- You must be punished!
- Well, I am ready for your punishment.
Yes...but is your father?
- You leave him out of this!
- Oh, I will leave him all right alone,
to rot in a dungeon.
Until you learn
to behave yourself!
No.
- A toast.
- Just hang on.
Djaq, Will...
Good work, lads.
You are now, honorary members
of our gang.
You are our eyes and ears
in the villages.
And any time you need us...
...you can call on us.
- Any time you need us, call on us.
- That's a deal.
We are Robin Hoods!
NEXT TIME
The pestilence has come to Nottingham.
- She's gonna die!
- No. That's not what she's got.
- Dad!
- Set up those barricades.
Let me through! This has got nothing
to do with me.
Don't do this!
Someone's impersonating me.
- You poison people.
- He's going to kill the Sheriff.
- Don't I know you?
- You knew my dad, Dan.
Will...