Previously on The O.C.:
- You're gonna get through this, Coop.
- I shot someone, Sum.
- Are we okay?
- Why wouldn't we be?
Since that night,
we haven't talked about it.
What are you doing back in Newport?
Caleb dies... suddenly you show up.
We'll collect on Caleb's will, and we'll
go back to being a normal, happy family.
No matter how hard
I worked, or how hard I tried...
It was never enough.
Hi, I'm Charlotte Morgan.
I'm not going back to my husband
and my boys until I know...
...that I'll never let them down.
You should be
coming home any day now, right?
- Morning, Dad.
- Hey, just in time for breakfast.
- Who wants cereal?
- We have cereal?
Yeah, I found some
tucked away in a cabinet.
- Cereal doesn't go bad, does it?
- Oh, no, but milk does.
- How about some hummus?
- For breakfast?
Sure, with a side of... Of sesame beef.
Breakfast of champions.
- As much as I love botulism, I'll pass.
- I'm gonna stick with coffee.
We gotta eat together.
It's a special day. You're both seniors.
It's just registration.
It's a coming-of-age moment.
We love coming-of-age moments.
At my bar mitzvah,
he was frothing at the mouth.
I was excited then, I'm excited now.
I'm proud of you both. So's your mom,
even though she's not here to tell you.
Or prevent us from living
in this cesspool.
Boy, she kept this place in tiptop shape
without so much as picking up a sponge.
- How does she do that?
- Her presence kept us neat, Ryan.
It's that Protestant evil eye.
It's a powerful thing.
She is a woman of many talents.
We could have dinner tonight, right?
- Sure, just the three of us.
- Yeah, Ryan'll even clean up.
He will.
I'll pick up the steaks.
Boy, you've got some nerve
showing up here.
Look, I apologize
for our little misunderstanding.
Oh, so I misunderstood. You didn't try
to frame Ryan for the shooting.
Sandy, I did what any parent
would do.
- I was trying to keep my family afloat.
- By using my kid as a raft.
You can lecture me later.
Right now, we need to put
our differences behind us.
We have bigger problems.
What's happened now?
I got a call from
the school this morning.
Apparently, the parents are protesting.
They want Ryan and Marissa out.
I should've seen that coming.
I'll talk to them.
No, you don't get it. They have
a petition. They filed a motion.
- See you, Dad.
- Have a good day.
Sandy, unless we can put a stop to this,
Ryan and Marissa are getting expelled.
And we'll take pancakes,
with extra butter.
Thanks.
Wow, it's the last time we'll ever order
pancakes before registration.
- And that's a sad thing to you?
- Yeah, it is sad.
Everything we do this year is for the last
time. It's like a farewell tour.
After the summer we've had,
that doesn't sound so terrible.
- lf we make it through this year.
- lf we get through graduation.
- With no major traumas.
- Then I'll be happy.
No, you guys, that's unacceptable.
Look, I know that our summer sucked.
- To say the least.
- But we made it through it.
No one is in juvie or in a jump suit.
I think Marissa would've
worn one well.
I do. It's the right cut on you.
Point is, the four of us are together,
and it's our senior year.
So it's our last time
to make everything all-time.
She makes a point.
Becoming quite
the motivational speaker.
Okay, Sum, you win.
It'll be the best year ever.
Thank you. High-five.
Best year ever.
- Jimmy couldn't make it?
- He's working.
A business associate
from Hawaii showed up.
Just as well. One Montague,
one Capulet. That should be plenty.
Sandy, Julie, come on in.
You have to understand...
...no student at Harbor has ever been
involved in a shooting.
And I know, as principal,
you have to do something, but...
If you could please avoid expulsion.
There is a petition circling
amongst the parents.
Almost 1000 signatures.
It's hard to ignore that kind of outcry.
Dr. Kim, you know my daughter, right?
Tall, pretty, wears Chanel?
Not exactly what you call gangster.
Look, the bottom line is
Marissa and Ryan are good kids.
- They deserve to graduate with friends.
- lf it were up to me, they would.
But it is up to you.
You're the principal.
The board thought it would be
a good idea to bring in someone new.
A specialist in school safety.
Oh, you mean like a hall monitor?
Flattering. But actually
more like dean of discipline.
Jack Hess, nice to meet you.
Sandy Cohen. Julie Cooper-Nichol.
- I'm very anxious to talk about Marissa.
- And Ryan.
Thanks, but I don't really think
that'll be necessary.
I read their files, talked to the officers.
I know what I'm dealing with.
Well, you never really know
until you talk to the kid.
I was a PD in the juvenile system
for years, and l...
I've seen my fair share of kids
in trouble.
So have I, Mr. Cohen.
Got a master's in education, taught
six years in boarding schools back east.
- I like to think I know what I'm doing.
- I hope so.
These kids very much
want to go to college.
If you kick them out,
they've got no shot.
Well, frankly, I'm not here
to make everyone happy.
I'll let you know my answer
by this evening.
Jimmy.
Another Scotch on the rocks
for my friend.
Friend. That's a... That's a good sign.
You know I like you, Jimmy.
Even though you test my patience.
- Here you go, sir.
- Thank you.
Soon. You will have the money soon.
I think you said that two months ago.
Well, the will's gonna be read
any day now.
- You gotta... You gotta believe me.
- I believed you before...
...when you said you were gonna
sell me a boat...
...but you pissed away my deposit
on some crazy stock venture.
Do we have to...?
Do we have to relive this?
Point is, I'm nice.
But I'm not as nice as I look.
I got a lot of friends who'd be more than
happy to take care of this for me.
All I gotta do is pick up
the phone.
You're gonna have your money.
I promise.
Coop, you need a wheelbarrow for
that binder. That thing's a monster.
It's everything I need
for Kickoff Carnival.
Waivers, invoices, vendor contracts.
That is so boring, it hurts.
So you won't be joining us
for Social Committee this year?
Let me think about it. No.
Sum, it's our last year. What happened
to "living every moment"?
You know how I feel
about school-sponsored events.
Love to go to them, hate to plan them.
I prefer not to look behind the curtain.
You see, if I join clubs, I'll have to
hang out with girls like that.
- Taylor Townsend?
- Okay, guys?
I spent the whole summer
working on your Kickoff Carnival...
...so I have tons of great ideas.
I mean, I didn't even have a vacation.
But you know
someone has to do it, right?
Coop, she's totally stealing
your meeting.
Yeah, well, she's been fighting me for
Social Chair since, like, freshman year.
God. Nothing I hate more than perky
blonds who wanna take over the world.
- Come on.
- You'll be in charge of booths.
- And Meredith, I'm gonna put...
- Taylor?
Hey. I think you're at
Marissa's podium.
Marissa.
I'm sorry, I just went ahead
and guessed...
...that you weren't gonna be
making it today.
Well, here I am.
Well, I just assumed with everything
you've been through this summer...
You know, with the:
Right. Well, I'm fine, thanks.
You are so strong.
Listen, sweetie, if it gets to be
too much, just holler.
I can totally take over...
...since I pretty much did the whole
thing myself last year.
Yeah, that's great, but do you wanna
take your stuff off the podium now?
Absolutely.
I'll just be gone in a jiff.
Okay. Let's go.
Bye.
Oh, that bitch is going down.
You sure you don't need
a HAZMAT suit?
Oh, my God, look at this.
- Chicken from the Fourth of July.
- Those things fossilized yet?
Yeah. What are you doing?
Making a Seth Cohen starter pack
for Mom, rehab edition.
I got their new Klosterman...
...got Craig Thompson's Blankets
and I got Mötley Crüe's Dirt.
It will help
put Mom's indiscretions in perspective.
Very thoughtful.
That's pretty much everything.
You wanna give me a hand here?
- How are things with you and Marissa?
- They're fine.
Fine?
- They're fine?
- Yeah, why wouldn't they be fine?
I don't know, she shot your brother.
Throw the average couple for a loop.
We've been living
and breathing it all summer.
Now it's over,
we just wanna put it behind us.
You've talked about it, right?
I mean, hashed it out?
We don't need to.
Dude, Summer and I fought
over a comic book for a year.
Yeah, what's your point?
If I've learned anything
from being with Summer...
...it's that every issue in a relationship
snowballs. Even the small things.
You gotta deal with it,
or eventually it'll come between you.
Skipping town?
Yeah, checking out tomorrow.
You?
Yeah. Almost all packed.
Oh, I just can't wait to get back
to my family, my... My house, my bed.
Still, I know you were...
...worried about going too soon.
Well, I can't say that l... I feel really
ready, but I'm guessing that's normal.
Absolutely.
Going home
is the trickiest part of recovery.
The last time I went straight home,
I relapsed almost immediately.
I mean, after being here in this bubble,
it can be a shock to your system.
So this time I am planning
on making a pit stop.
Well, that seems like a good idea.
My father has a cottage
at Lake Arrowhead.
Totally remote and empty, which
makes it the perfect halfway house.
Well, it makes sense.
If there's one thing we've learned here,
it's to do things in steps.
You know, it...
There's a lot of extra room.
I mean, I know you wanna get home, but
if you're having any second thoughts...
Well, just think about it.
Thanks.
- Can I help you, sir?
- So have you heard anything?
About Marissa?
Is there another crisis
we're dealing with?
Of course not.
School hasn't called yet.
So how was your drink with that client?
Did you sell him a fleet of yachts?
It was... It was fine.
Look, I know you're worried
about Marissa, but you never know.
She could catch a break.
Marissa catch a break?
- That'd be a first.
- I don't know.
Cooper family's been on
a bit of a lucky streak recently.
My husband died in a pool.
Our daughter's about to be expelled.
What do you define as lucky?
You and I got back together.
And thank God.
Because it's the only thing
keeping me sane.
Whenever you're ready.
I... l...
- I left my wallet in the car.
- Jimmy.
Can't we just put it on Cal's tab?
Yeah, why not? We've charged
a summer's worth of drinks to him.
Julie Cooper-Nichol.
It's the dean.
Oh, I understand, dean.
And this decision is final?
Is there any way
I can get you to reconsider?
There'll be an opportunity for appeal?
I'm sorry to hear that.
I just want you to know I...
I think you're making a huge mistake.
Steaks ready?
Grilling is an art form, Ryan.
It can't be rushed.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, you want yours rare, Dad?
Sure.
- What's wrong?
- I got some bad news.
I had a meeting at the school today.
They're concerned about bringing you
and Marissa back after what happened.
- I'm getting kicked out.
- No, you're not.
But Marissa is.
"Dirt: The Mötley Crüe Story."
Well, that ought to put things
in perspective.
Our son has a very strange take
on self-help.
How are the boys? I miss them.
They're great.
They miss you like crazy.
I'm guessing they'll be
seeing you soon.
I'm taking that suitcase
as a good sign.
- I am leaving.
- Oh, honey, that's great news.
Your timing couldn't be better.
We cleaned up the house. It was...
It was a pit.
Sandy, I'm not coming home.
I'm going to Lake Arrowhead
with a friend.
- A friend?
- Her name is Charlotte.
She has a lot of experience
with these things...
...the dangers of relapse.
Honey, if you're thinking about relapse,
why check out at all?
I'm not saying that. It's just that...
- You don't want to come home.
- No.
Yes.
I want to come home. Of course I do.
I just need to know that when I do...
...that I'm home for good.
That this is all behind me.
Is there a timetable for this?
Oh, Sandy, I don't know.
Well, when you do, call me.
- Coop?
- Hey.
- How you doing?
- Oh, I've been better.
We thought
you could use some breakfast.
We got bagels and a support group.
Yes. Captain Oats
is a really good listener.
Princess Sparkle stands there
and looks cute.
- You guys didn't have to do that.
- And we're getting you back in.
You shouldn't suffer for this.
It should be me.
Well, you didn't shoot somebody.
I did.
I don't care what it takes,
we're getting you back in.
- Hey.
I'm checking online.
There's decent schools in the area.
- Marissa won't be going to any of them.
- What?
I was brainstorming during
Cardio Barre...
...which is where I do all my best
thinking and I came up with a solution.
- Well, I'm all ears.
- Money.
- Excuse me?
- We give Harbor a fat donation.
Remind them they're kicking out
Caleb Nichol's stepdaughter.
Except that Caleb's
not around anymore.
But his money is, or at least it will be...
...when they get around to untangling
his 79 Swiss bank accounts.
I don't know, Jules.
I don't... I don't think it's gonna work.
Then it's a write-off. I mean...
Look, I admit it's a long shot,
but we've gotta at least try.
Honey, this is our daughter
we're talking about.
You're right.
So you write the check.
I'm dry until the will comes through.
Well, how...? How much you thinking?
Like, 2000? Or three?
Wake up, Jimmy.
The Siegfrieds donated a pool
and a field house.
Their son only smoked pot.
Marissa shot someone.
We've gotta at least give them
100 grand.
What happened to Marissa Cooper
is a tragedy.
But let it be a lesson to all of us.
One minute you're on top,
the next you're on the streets.
With that in mind, I would like to take
a moment of silence...
...to remember Marissa Cooper, and
the great work she did as Social Chair.
That felt really good.
Okay, so it is with a heavy heart...
...that I assume Marissa's post
as Social Chair.
Summer Roberts.
I was just wondering
if anyone else has a chance to try out?
What, are you saying
that you want to be Social Chair?
Maybe.
Okay. Have you ever done
this kind of work before?
Please. No, but l...
Have you ever done
any extracurricular activities at all?
And shopping doesn't count.
Okay, maybe I'm not, like,
super qualified, but neither are you.
Who do you think has been running
this committee these past few years?
- Marissa Cooper.
- Marissa Cooper has been busy.
Skipping school. Experimenting
with her sexual orientation.
And I was here, picking up the slack.
Doing all of the work
while she got all the credit.
Do you have any idea
what it's like...
...to have all of the responsibility
and none of the power?
Do you?
Okay, then.
Let's get back to work, people.
We have a carnival to throw.
Charlotte, it's so charming.
Thanks.
God, I haven't been here in years.
We stopped coming when Dad bought
a house on the Vineyard.
I always loved it.
Well, that wasn't too important
to dear old Dad.
You know how that is.
But you're here now.
Yeah.
Dad is also a security freak,
so he locks this place up like Fort Knox.
There we go.
So this is it.
The kitchen is right over there,
where I will be teaching you to cook...
...whether you like it or not.
It's beautiful.
Thinking about Sandy?
Can't help it.
I feel like I've let him down yet again.
You're doing this for him.
I don't think he sees it that way.
Well, then show him.
Invite him up for dinner.
- You wouldn't mind?
- Of course not.
You've been talking so much about your
perfect husband, I'd love to meet him.
- Ryan.
- Dr. Kim, hey, I need to talk to you.
Ryan, the board had an exhaustive
debate about you and Marissa...
...and they came to what I think
is a fair decision.
They might change their minds
if they knew what happened.
They do know what happened.
The board has reached its decision.
Look, who can I talk to?
How can I change this?
You'd have to talk to the new dean.
It's his department.
Great, so if Marissa and I
could just talk to him, tell him our story.
Please?
Hey, you hungry?
Thought we could get a bite to eat.
I'm too sick to eat.
- Sick?
- Yes, of senior year sucking.
But it hasn't even started yet.
So?
It's already terrible.
Marissa got the axe...
...and now I have to watch as Überbitch
feeds on her remains.
You mean that Taylor girl?
I thought I could compete
with Psycho Barbie for Social Chair.
- You wanted to be Social Chair?
- No, it's just all I could do to help.
To try to keep Marissa's legacy...
...from falling into the grubby paws of
Taylor Townsend.
- Okay, well, then you should.
- I can't.
She's Taylor Townsend.
She's like the Karl Rove of our school.
So you can take Karl Rove...
You know who Karl Rove is?
Yeah. My stepmom sometimes
naps in front of CNN.
I hear things as I'm dragging her
off to bed.
I know you don't think
of yourself as active...
No. Two hobbies: shopping
and sunbathing.
- but you have Marissa as a resource.
Now, you combine that with
your natural God-given rage...
...you have everything you need
to topple that tyrant Taylor Townsend.
You're right. You know what?
We need to go to Marissa's.
- Pretty sure I said I was hungry.
- Come on.
Jimmy.
You proved me wrong.
Figured you'd be tossing back
tequila shooters in Oaxaca by now.
I don't have the money.
- You're kidding, right?
- No.
I haven't even gotten
to the unbelievable part yet.
l... I need to ask you for a loan.
I'm sorry.
You want to borrow money?
A hundred thousand dollars.
It's for my kid. She's...
- She's had some bad luck.
- Runs in the family, I guess.
Look, the best way for you
to get your money is to give me more.
- So why don't you sell the boat.
- Well, if it were mine...
The bank owns it now. Look...
l... I'm... I'm in a real pinch here.
Once the money comes in,
I pay you back.
Julie and I, we... We...
We live happily ever after, okay?
Trust me, l... l...
I got a plan.
- You really think this is gonna work?
- Yeah, well, we gotta at least try, right?
You must be Ryan and Marissa.
It's good to finally meet Harbor's
most notorious couple. Please, come in.
Have a seat.
So we just... We wanted to tell you
our version of what happened.
This doesn't really concern you, Ryan.
As far as I know, you're still enrolled
at Harbor, despite my best efforts.
So I say we focus on Marissa.
So, Miss Cooper...
...tell me why I'm wrong about you.
- I...
- Because that's what this is about, right?
- I've got you all wrong.
- I don't know.
I just know I've never been involved
in anything like this before.
Really? Well, l...
I gotta disagree with you.
What are you talking about?
You know, I'm new to Newport.
I moved here a few weeks ago
from the East Coast.
So far, it's not bad.
The weather's great.
And you know what else
I like about it here?
People here talk. They love to talk.
Especially about you.
You can't buy into the gossip
in this town.
All right, so...
Yeah, you tell me, then.
Shoplifting, alcohol abuse,
an overdose in Tijuana.
And please stop me
if any of this is just gossip.
Those things have nothing to do
with what happened with Trey.
You know what, I did those things.
- But, I mean, the shooting was different.
- Marissa, it's never different.
A troubled kid gets ahold of a gun,
the ending is always the same.
- I'm not troubled.
- You almost killed another kid.
I don't even hear a hint
of remorse in your voice.
Because I don't have any.
I'm proud of what I did,
and I'd do it again.
So, you know what,
maybe the next time...
...you're out on the town talking with
people you should tell them I said that.
I hope she gets a good, long look
on her way out.
She's never setting foot
in this school again.
All the California fire codes
are in here. I think.
- Wanna test me?
- No.
Come on, I have to catch Taylor
breaking a rule...
...or I have no shot
at taking back this carnival.
Well, you're not gonna
out-Taylor Taylor.
I mean, fire codes and regulations,
that's her bread and butter.
Well, what do you suggest?
I suggest you find something
you're good at that she's not.
Hey, dude, you wanna play?
More in the mood for stewing,
I got it.
You should go talk to him.
Go talk to him.
- You okay?
- Not really.
Look, I know this thing with the dean
has you a little pissed off.
- Or a lot.
- It was all I could do...
...to keep from kicking that guy's ass.
- I know how it feels.
Actually, I don't.
But you don't do that anymore.
Sometimes it seems like
the best way to handle things.
- I don't like where this is headed.
- Yeah, well...
Okay, well, listen. I mean, even if
you can't get Marissa back into school...
...all right, at least she's not going
to jail. It's not the end of the world.
Voilà. One hundred thousand dollars.
Oh, thanks, but I don't think
we're gonna need it.
We don't?
Marissa had a meeting
with the dean yesterday.
Apparently she showed him a side
of herself usually reserved for me.
Oh, it was that bad, huh?
I don't think any amount of money
is getting her back in that school.
Oh, I'm sorry.
At least we found out now.
Saved us some money.
- Actually, I could use this.
- What?
Well, you know, the landscaper,
the pool guy, the gardener.
None of them have been paid
since Caleb died.
I'm afraid one of them's gonna kill me
in my sleep.
Okay, next I've got your stations
set up right here.
Summer, you showed up.
And you brought a little friend.
- Seth Cohen, is it?
- Present.
So as I was saying...
We had some ideas,
so we came to help.
Oh, well, that's sweet,
but we've got it under control.
Well, all right. Gotta go.
- So as I was saying...
- Hey, Ash.
What would you think
about getting a chocolate fountain?
Awesome. Didn't Britney
have one at her wedding?
You know what? She did.
And Seth and I here
rented one for tonight.
- Sorry, that's not really our carnival.
- Well, it should be.
- Yeah, really.
- What else?
Well, I was thinking, for food...
...how about, like, mini-burgers,
mini-dim sum...
...maybe, like, mini-soups
in little shot glasses?
How cute is that?
- Because mini is the new super size.
- So true.
We should also maybe
cancel Shenanigans.
What?
The Harbor Comedy Troupe's gotten
way too political lately.
Ever since Tina Wu left,
they are so not funny.
And why are we raffling off
a gas-guzzling SUV...
...from Taylor's dad's dealership,
when we could give away a hybrid?
- Air quality is so important.
- I know. We breathe it.
All right, you guys,
so who is onboard with my carnival?
I'm sorry.
Hey, you must be Sandy Cohen.
Bit of a legend back at Suriak.
Thanks, Charlotte.
Nice to meet you too.
Kirsten's just up in the kitchen.
- You left her unsupervised?
- Consider it therapy.
Boy, everything seems to be
therapy nowadays.
Cooking, holing yourself up
in the woods.
This place will be great for Kirsten.
What would be great for Kirsten
is for her to be with her kids.
Look, Sandy, I know you don't know me.
And I know this all seems a little weird.
But I've been around this track
a few times.
I'm not proud of that,
but I've learned a few things.
And I know that the reason
Kirsten was in rehab...
...is because she spent her life
trying to be the perfect daughter.
So now if she tries to be the perfect
mother and the perfect wife...
She may never come home.
- I'm so glad you're here.
- I am too.
Okay, who wants dinner?
- Hey.
Why aren't you at the carnival?
Because I was hoping I could
get you to go with me.
Seth and Summer are there.
It'll be fun.
Or really depressing.
Look, about that. It's not over yet.
I'm gonna talk to Sandy.
Maybe get him a copy
of our testimonies.
Ryan...
If you're innocent of all charges...
...they'll have to admit
you shouldn't be punished, right?
No. No, it's over.
I don't get it.
Why don't you wanna fight this?
Because I can't keep doing this, okay?
Look, I appreciate
everything you've done to help me...
...but maybe you've done enough.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- I don't need you to help me.
I don't need you to protect me.
- I don't now, and I didn't then.
- Wha...?
Oh, what,
so this whole thing is my fault?
What happened was between
me and Trey.
You didn't need to get
in the middle of it.
So I was supposed to watch you die?
I did what I did, and I'm prepared
to face the consequences.
Yeah, well, there are consequences
for me too. He was my brother.
Right.
And now, because of me, he's gone.
No, that's not what I mean.
Ryan...
And the winner of the Toyota
Highlander Hybrid is Jillian Flynn.
- I won! I won!
- All right, all right.
Hey, Summer.
Totally awesome carnival.
- We love the mini-burgers.
- And high-five for taking down Taylor.
Thanks, guys.
Bye, have fun.
Hey, why the sad face?
This is your Rudy moment.
I know, I just... I can't enjoy it.
Not without Coop.
- No?
- No.
We're never gonna go back...
...to the way things were, are we?
- I don't know.
You worked too hard on this
to miss out on it.
- I know, but, Cohen...
- Come on.
One mournful ride on the Tilt-A-Whirl
is the least we can do.
- I thought you'd be at the carnival.
- Didn't really work out.
I guess Marissa's expulsion
hasn't been easy on you too.
No, I just wish there was something
I could do, you know.
So you wanna fix this?
The universal male instinct.
Happens to the best of us.
So I'm supposed to sit here
and do nothing?
No, you need to go back.
But just listen.
- Just listen.
- Trust me.
Works better than you think.
Could we...? Could we get another bottle
of Dom Perignon?
Okay, Daddy Warbucks.
What's the occasion?
Can't I take you out
to a nice little dinner?
Sure, it's just that I thought
we agreed that tonight...
...was Taco Bell
and Dancing with the Stars.
Well, I brought you here
because I wanted to tell you...
...that I am never
leaving this family again.
I lost you once, Julie, and l...
I'm never gonna let that happen again.
James.
And with that in mind...
My old ring.
Will you marry me, Julie?
Again?
Of course.
Want some company?
Sure.
Sorry about before.
I know.
You know...
...I was always worried
that I'd screw things up for myself here.
Get in trouble.
Ruin the chance the Cohens gave me.
- And now I screwed things up for you.
- Ryan.
I'm not gonna let
getting kicked out of Harbor ruin my life.
I'm not even gonna let it
ruin my year.
Look, I know that we're not
in school together anymore...
...but at least we still have
this last year in Newport together.
I'm listening.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
How you feeling?
My stomach is far too Jewish for that
ride, but I'm almost done spinning.
Summer. Hi.
I just wanted to thank you
for all your little touches on the carnival.
It's just... It's really sad that Marissa
Cooper couldn't be here to see this.
It must be hard having
your friend ostracized from school.
Okay, Taylor. Number one...
...Marissa was not ostra... Whatever.
- Ostracized.
Number two, she happens to be
on her way now.
- Marissa's coming here?
- Oh, I'm not done yet.
And number three...
Do we have a number three?
Oh, yeah, we do.
Number three, this is the best carnival
this school has ever seen.
And not just because
I canceled Shenanigans.
- Yeah.
Come on, Cohen.
I didn't know Marissa was coming.
- Me neither. Coop!
- Hey.
You came.
I couldn't miss your first
Kickoff Carnival.
- Not bad, huh?
- I couldn't have done it better myself.
So can I interest you
in the Ferris wheel?
- What were you saying?
- Now we go to the carnival.
Charlotte?
Charlotte, what's wrong?
- I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
- No, no, I was up. What's the matter?
I haven't...
I haven't been totally honest with you.
There's something I need to tell you.
I haven't yet, but I might.
It's okay.
What am I gonna do when you're gone?
I can't do this without you.
I saw you with Sandy,
and I know how much you miss him...
...and you're gonna leave soon,
and what am I gonna do?
I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me you're ready.
We're in this together.
Thank you.
Let's go to bed.
You'll feel better in the morning.
I'll be right behind you.
Okay, I'm nauseous again.
Ryan, I'm feeling queasy.
Will you leave them alone?
They're having a moment.
I just want to warn you
in case that dim sum resurfaces...
...you're kind of in the line of fire.
- You're getting good at this, aren't you?
- Yeah, third year's a charm.
Look, I know the last three years
haven't exactly been perfect...
...and I know this year's gonna be
even tougher...
...but we just gotta find our moments,
you know?
Well, I think we're having one now.
Excuse me, Miss Cooper,
what do you think you're doing?
- Taylor Townsend.
- She is Karl Rove.
We're not on school property.
She's my guest.
This doesn't involve you, Ryan.
I want you out of here.
- It's fine, okay? I'm leaving.
- No, you're not going anywhere.
She worked on this carnival
every year.
Thanks for the trip down memory lane,
but that is not my problem.
Now, get out of here.
- Get your hands off her.
- Another word, you're out of school.
- Get off of me!
- Hey, don't touch her!
Ryan!
- Oh, my God.
- That's not good.
Well, this is my lucky day.
Here I thought I was gonna have to work
to throw you out of this school...
...but you did it yourself.
Get out of here.
Either of you ever set foot
near this school again...
...I call the police.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group