Previously on The O. C:
My mom and I are getting kicked out.
I had to move into Summer's.
This woman is the princess
of Orange County.
I will find a way to use her.
Welcome to Newport Union.
I'm Casey.
- Nice to meet you, I'm...
- Johnny.
Everyone calls me Chili.
That's gonna be a problem,
because I love you.
Marissa.
- What's wrong? What did you do to her?
- Nothing. I'm fine.
- This is my...
- Boyfriend, I'm guessing. Hey.
She's Taylor Townsend.
She's like the Karl Rove of our school.
- Taylor Townsend.
Taylor Townsend.
- Don't touch her!
- Ryan!
Either of you ever set foot
near this school again...
...I call the police.
- Where's all the cereal?
- Oh, I guess we're out.
- There's no bagels?
- I thought we'd try something new.
Mom, listen to me. I understand that
this whole cooking-with-Kirsten thing...
...is helping you keep focused...
...but you cannot preempt
a man's regularly scheduled breakfast.
- It is a sacred routine.
- Sit.
You are having...
...eggs Benedict Gruyère
avec pâtes du fruit.
Something smells...
...fancy.
- Have a seat, there's plenty.
- No thanks. I'll just grab a bagel to go.
Good luck with that.
Hello?
Oh, Dr. Kim, thanks so much
for getting back to me.
Dr. Kim as in Principal Dr. Kim?
Oh, she's probably confirming our
reservation for the college fair tonight.
You know, you're gonna be exposed
to a lot of new things in college.
Yeah, horny coeds and alcohol poisoning.
I just don't think they're gonna have
French fusion on the menu.
- They don't want me there, do they?
- No, Harbor's only hosting.
And it's a public event.
There is no reason why you can't attend.
So you boys meet us here,
we'll head over together.
Sounds good to me.
- Hey, man, give me a ride to school.
- We'll hit the drive-through on the way.
- What's going on?
- Harbor's dean of discipline...
...is making it his personal crusade
to ruin Ryan's future.
He's attached a note to his transcript...
...detailing his pathologically
violent behavior.
Ryan certainly needs to work on his
self-control, but he's not pathological.
Considering everything
he's been through?
No one'll get a chance to consider it.
A letter like that is a red flag to colleges.
And unless it's rescinded...
...no way a reputable school
is gonna wanna touch a kid like Ryan.
What color do I want?
Come on.
Just go that...
Okay, you're, like, twice my height.
We can probably figure this out.
Why don't you just...
Like that. Right.
- Solved.
- I'm sorry.
You must be sick of me
being in your way.
Oh, are you kidding?
I date Cohen, okay?
My patience is infinite.
Having you in my space
makes me miss you less at school.
Well, I miss you guys too.
You know, we should all
do something tonight.
You know, I told Cohen
I'd go with him to that...
What is it called?
That college circus thing?
- Why don't you come with us?
- To Harbor? I think I'll pass.
It's not like you're on
the most wanted list.
- Have you checked the dean's office?
- Very funny.
Look, I'm not really thinking
big picture right now anyway.
I mean, college isn't even on my radar.
You're a senior in high school.
How could it not be?
Let's see, maybe because I'm homeless,
going to public school and totally broke.
And yet things could be worse.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi, sweetie.
Just checking on you.
How's everything going at Summer's?
Fine, but I'm kind of worried
I'm wearing out my welcome.
Then I have some good news.
Kirsten's turned me on to a promising
lead on some beachside property.
So if you could just hang on
a little bit longer.
- Sure, I guess.
- Great.
- Is everything okay, Mom?
- Oh, I'm fine, honey.
Okay, I mean, I've been better...
...but I have a plan,
and you have nothing to worry about.
We'll have lunch at the club
this week, okay? I'll call you.
Okay, bye.
Hey, don't stress out, okay?
You can stay here as long as you want.
Thanks.
Excuse us, ma'am.
No problem.
Hey.
Look at her. All coy and texty.
I bet it's the dean, all like:
"Come over to my creepy apartment.
I'll give you a lesson in discipline."
Be afraid, Cohen.
Be very, very afraid.
If she isn't stopped, who knows
how far she'll take her agenda.
Well, she hijacked Social Chair. It's
not like world domination is inevitable.
Yeah, well, school domination is.
She's got Dean Hess in her back pocket,
front, who knows where else.
Look, I know Us Weekly is your bible...
...and believe me, I love a good scandal
as much as the next guy...
...but nothing is going on between
the dean and Taylor Townsend.
I saw what I saw, okay?
In a dark hallway,
in the middle of a rage blackout.
Isn't it possible you saw
what you wanted?
What...? No, no one chooses to witness
something that repellent.
I'd like to give her a side kick.
- Where are you going?
- Recon.
You sure this is a good idea?
Of course. I want you here.
Does anyone else?
Well, there's only one way to find out.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
Hey.
- Is this Ryan?
- Yep.
Yeah, I see why
you didn't break up with him.
Chiseled jaw, deep, soulful eyes.
He's pretty.
You get struck by lightning,
I'll take care of your woman.
- I'm worried.
- You should be.
- Good to see you again.
- Good to see you.
Sorry about the other day.
I lost my cool.
You see your girl talking to some guy
you don't know...
...it could happen to anyone.
- So you guys wanna sit with us?
- Sure. Thanks.
Cool.
So you blowing off school today?
No, actually, I'm doing
a homeschool thing for a while.
I thought that was for, like, Christians.
And for people who punch
the dean at their school.
- You did that?
- Yeah.
I wish I could homeschool.
I can't wait to get out of here.
Though Newport
beats the hell out of Brea.
You're from Brea?
Where'd you go to school?
- Arovista.
- Chino Hills.
Come on, Marissa.
Let's get frozen yogurt.
- Okay. Ryan, you want anything?
- I'm good.
- Dennis, you like frozen yogurt.
- Okay, yeah, I love frozen yogurt.
- Come on, you can hold our tray for us.
- Okay.
Trust me, the faster they become
friends, the better off you are.
We used to kick your ass
at football.
- I know, I used to play safety.
- Quarterback.
Really? What year?
Okay, at first I thought it was cute...
...you following me,
obsessing over me...
...but the Single White Female thing
is so mid-90s.
- And it never ends well for the ugly one.
- Could you be more full of yourself?
I have better things to do
than follow your ass around.
Okay, I know it must be hard going from
prom queen to the invisible woman...
...but what are you trying to prove?
That you're not just pathetic,
you're also crazy?
Oh, you want crazy?
Oh, I will show you crazy.
Okay, you might wanna rethink
threatening me.
If you haven't noticed,
I'm close with Dean Hess.
Oh, no, I've noticed.
Well, you know, Dean Hess,
he isn't exactly discreet.
- Okay, what does that mean?
- Never mind.
I've been trying to erase this image
from my brain, like, all day.
Unfortunately, I think it's gonna take
serious therapy.
- What image?
- Nothing. l...
Dean Hess could get in,
like, a lot of trouble.
I think it's, like,
sexual harassment or something.
What is?
Kissing.
Ms. Applebaum, yeah.
The volleyball coach with the toned arms
and the legs for miles.
I saw them behind the gym bleachers
this morning.
- Okay, you're totally lying.
- I wish.
The look on Ms. Applebaum's face is,
like, permanently burned into my retinas.
God. Pure carnal satisfaction.
Yeah.
Sorry. I guess I gotta go.
You have a super day.
I was going this way.
- So, what do you think?
- Aren't condos for old people?
These units were conceived
for professionals.
- Single, divorced executive types.
- How much are we talking?
Since I know the developer,
10 percent gets you in...
...the rest you can finance.
- Ten percent?
Julie, it's a really good investment.
If you need help with
the down payment...
I'm not destitute, Kirsten,
I'm discerning.
So should I make a call,
set up a walk-through?
Why not?
Wonder who that is.
- Hi.
I thought you might
wanna join me for a bite.
Oh, it's good of you to stop by.
- Sorry, I didn't realize you had company.
- No. Charlotte, this is Julie.
- Julie, this is Charlotte.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
We met at Suriak.
- Oh, are you a doctor?
- Patient.
I have an appointment
I have to be getting to...
...so call me when you hear
from your friend.
On my cell.
My hotel is terrible about messages.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
Okay, clearly I have got to learn
how to call ahead.
I'm sorry. I hope I didn't
scare your friend away.
Oh, it would take a lot more
than that to scare Julie.
She was married to my dad.
That would explain
the size of the rock on her finger.
Well, he didn't leave her much else.
"Newport Point Condominiums."
It's not the Taj Mahal,
but it'll be a good place...
...for her and her daughter.
Can I get you some salad?
We have plenty left.
Yeah, that'd be great.
I'm starving. Thanks.
So your dad left her with nothing?
She must be feeling
really vulnerable now.
I'm glad you came by.
Come on, Coop. Ryan's going.
Yeah, and I'm sure he'll have
a great time with you and Seth.
Look, it's not because it's Harbor.
And it's not because it's college.
- I just have a lot of homework.
- Yeah, sure, homework.
What, you want me to focus
on my future?
Well, guess what? Tomorrow I have
a trig exam that I'm totally gonna fail.
Okay. Sure.
I'll just tell everyone you said hi.
- Okay.
- Okay. Enjoy.
- I'll be fine.
- Later.
Ivy League. Big Ten. Pac-10.
College fairs are like shopping.
It's all about brand recognition.
You know Princeton was originally called
the College of New Jersey?
How hard would it be
to get into that school?
Well, why don't you ask them?
Why not, indeed?
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, fine.
Just a little weird being back here.
I feel like a fugitive.
You have as much right to be here
as anyone.
- So where do you wanna start?
- I really don't know.
I hear Berkeley's an excellent choice.
Very pretty girls too.
Oh, and there's the UC sign.
- Sounds good?
- Sure.
So all these schools
are in the Northeast.
- Yeah, so?
- So?
Just a little something
I like to call winter.
God, your bony ass can't even take it
when Newport drops to 70.
- Oh, my God, wait.
- What?
Busted.
Now do you believe me?
That is a couple fight.
Or Dean Hess told Taylor her chances
are better at Cornell than Dartmouth.
You still don't believe me?
No, I'm just saying, look...
...an on-campus argument in front of
the students, faculty and parents...
...is not proof of a relationship.
- Okay, I'm gonna go get you proof.
- What?
- What are you interested in studying?
- I'm not totally sure.
Ryan's strong in math and physics.
And he's shown a real aptitude
for building and drafting.
- Architecture? Got a great program.
- Maybe, yeah.
- It's good to see you.
- Great.
I'll be right back.
That looks good.
What is Atwood doing here?
He's not to set foot on this campus.
I cleared it with Principal Kim.
You can keep him from enrolling here,
but not from a public event.
I'm calling security.
Unless you have a court-ordered injunction
against my son, keep your hands off him.
Fine, he can stay.
But it's a waste of time.
None of these schools
will even admit him.
Because of the letter
you attached to his file.
Maybe he'll think
about assaulting his next victim.
He made a mistake,
and he should pay for it.
But should the price really be his future?
You're killing his one shot.
No.
He did that all by himself.
Morning, buddy.
Got up early, put on a pot of regular.
Ryan?
Oh, no.
Oh, man.
Ryan, you're here.
Where else would I be?
Well, after last night, I thought
you might have gone Greyhound...
...but clearly my concern
was unfounded because you're fine.
Sure. I mean, no one in my family
even got through high school.
Two years ago the thought of college
never even crossed my mind.
- It was never where I was headed.
- Yeah, okay.
Where are you headed right now?
A field trip with your tutor?
I canceled. If anyone asks,
I'm at the library.
Good. That's a good idea.
You take a day, clear your head
with independent study.
My head is clear.
The tutor's not coming back.
- I'm done with school.
- You're dropping out?
- And then what?
- I don't know yet. Okay.
Well, that's a smart move.
Have you told my parents?
Have you told Mariss...?
That's fine.
High school's... It's overrated.
I'm sure you'll do fine.
Ryan, you can't just drop out of school.
It's only gonna make things worse.
I gotta get to class, okay?
Please, let's just talk after. Bye.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, great.
- My boyfriend's quitting school.
- Why?
He doesn't think he can
get into college, so he's giving up.
Seems like a smart kid,
I'm sure he'll be all right.
This time, I'm not so sure.
- His family is kind of screwed up.
- Whose isn't?
Okay, true,
but Ryan's is really screwed up.
He's got a chance to be different,
if he'd take it.
- Have you told him that?
- I don't think he'll listen to me.
In fact, I don't know who he'll listen to.
What is that thing?
- Miss Morgan?
- No.
Julie Cooper-Nichol.
Oh, right. Kirsten Cohen's referral.
The door was open,
so I thought I'd take a peek.
Gave me a chance to really visualize
myself in the place.
- I'll take it.
- Beg your pardon?
I brought the down payment with me.
I'm assuming cash is okay.
- Miss Cooper...
- Cooper-Nichol.
I think we have a misunderstanding.
You see, when we spoke this morning...
...I was under the impression
that this unit wasn't right for you.
- I beg your pardon?
- This is a four-bedroom.
The one that we talked about
is a two-bedroom in the garden.
Garden?
Realtor speak for "basement," right?
- Hello.
- You must be Miss Morgan.
- Yes. Hi.
- Hi.
Julie, right?
Hi. What are you doing here?
I might ask the same thing.
I'm doing business in the area, and I
heard this condo might be a perfect pad.
- But looks like you beat me to it.
- Actually, your timing is perfect.
Sorry, I'm looking for something
with a better view.
Charlotte, the place is all yours.
Well, follow me, Miss Morgan.
We'll start with the master.
Hey, where you been?
I've been looking for you all day.
I've been avoiding you.
Just because I don't buy into
your whole...
...Taylor and the dean
forbidden-Iove delusion?
Can we table that. We have
a bigger problem to worry about.
Ryan quitting school?
I know, Marissa told me.
- We should do something.
- Why do you think I'm writing this letter?
A petition? That's a good idea.
No, it's not a petition, dumb-ass.
I'm begging for Taylor's forgiveness.
You had me, and then you...
I think you lost me.
Okay, if Taylor thinks that Dean Hess
is sorry, maybe they'll get back together.
And then we can expose them
and use that to get Ryan back in school.
No, no, l... I understand.
Can...? Can I call you right back?
Thanks.
- What's going on?
- That was Ryan's tutor.
- Calling for her final paycheck.
- What?
Ryan told her that he would
no longer be needing her...
...since he won't be
finishing high school.
- Where's Ryan now?
- Seth said he was at the library.
One kid dropping out of school,
the other lying.
And I thought today
was gonna be boring.
Hey, man.
- Hey, Johnny.
- Marissa said they had the best burgers.
- Figured I should check it out for myself.
- They are. Come on in.
So she told you what's going on.
Might have mentioned it.
Well, no offense,
but you barely know me.
Which is why I'm not here
to talk you into anything.
I mean, I'm not going to college.
Figured I'd do all right
in a few surf competitions...
...maybe hook up with some sponsors,
turn that into a career, you know?
It's a simple plan, but...
Better than what I got.
Thought I'd get a job,
figure things out after I make money.
- What kind of job?
- Did construction last summer.
Hours were long, but I liked the work.
My uncle has this
commercial fishing operation.
He's always looking for new guys.
I mean, it's brutal,
but you can't beat the pay.
- Think he'd give me a shot?
- lf you want, I'll take you down there.
He could be off
joining the Foreign Legion...
...joining a cult.
Ryan could be...
He could be taking place
in a mass marriage...
...drinking Kool-Aid
from brand-new sneakers.
- So many sick things.
- I'm gonna try his cell again.
- Hey.
- Ryan.
Dude, where were you?
- We were about to sound an AMBER Alert.
- I'm sorry.
I know you've had a rough 24 hours...
...and I am a firm believer
that every man deserves his space.
- You can't go off like that.
- Won't happen again.
Lucky for you I was able to do
damage control with your tutor.
She's agreed to come to make up
for what you missed.
Oh, I appreciate that, but...
What's this?
It's a guardian release form.
I got a job.
On a boat.
You mean a cruise ship?
You don't really seem like the type.
This is a joke, right?
These boats go out for weeks at a time.
- You're not of age.
- That's why I need your signature.
You wanna throw away your future
to work on a fishing boat?
My future's already trashed.
I tried it your way. It didn't work.
- You have to keep trying.
- No, I don't.
I have been trying...
...and I appreciate everything
you've done for me, I really do...
...but I need to make my own decisions.
And I'm asking you to let me go.
- Sandy.
- Dad.
Come up here and help George
on the deck.
Check the icemaker.
Put the Freon in there.
We lose any in the next haul,
it's coming out of your paychecks.
- Mr. Harper?
- Yeah.
Ryan Atwood, from yesterday.
- Yeah, Johnny's friend, right?
- Yeah.
Hold this.
Look, kid, we don't need
part-timers right now.
Check back next summer.
Give me a kneel, somebody.
About that, I got the... I got
the signature. I can... I can do full-time.
You know,
this isn't putting bait on hooks.
It's hard work.
You mess up out there,
you don't get fired, you get hurt.
I worked construction, I can handle it.
I'd appreciate the chance.
Yeah, that's because
you don't know better.
All right, we got a spot open on
the Gale. We're prepping her now.
- Great, how long's she gonna be out?
- Depends on the action.
My guess, about three weeks.
She shoves off tomorrow at sunset.
- You got a problem with that?
- No, sir.
- Just got some loose ends to tie up.
- Yeah, don't we all.
All right, don't be late.
Hey.
Oh, hey. How was surfing?
Pretty calm.
Had time to do some soul-searching.
- You gonna talk to him?
- I'm sticking with our plan.
Your plan. Sandy, he's leaving
on a boat tomorrow.
- This is the wrong time to be stubborn.
- Honey, I'm stubborn all the time.
We can't force Ryan
to make the right choice.
But we can stop him
from making a horrible mistake.
From permanently knocking
his life off course.
Yeah, it's a course we set for him.
Would you let Seth do this?
- We kind of did.
- No. No, that was different.
It was summer, he didn't miss school and
it was Seth, we knew he'd come back.
You know, in Ryan's position,
at his age...
...I can't say I wouldn't do
the same thing.
I left home at 17.
To start your life,
not throw it away.
Ryan doesn't want this.
He'll come around.
But we gotta let him
get there on his own.
And what if he doesn't?
- Hey.
- Oh, hi, sweetie.
Have you seen Ryan?
He hasn't returned my calls.
- Oh, he should be home soon.
- This thing has really gotten to him.
I think the best thing we can do
is support him, no matter what.
You wanna throw him
a going-away dinner?
- Well, that's not a bad idea.
- Wait, where's he going?
"You are like a warm breeze
blowing down Van Nuys Boulevard.
From Encino to Reseda,
there is nothing as beautiful as you.
Your eyes are as blue
as a smogless day..."
- What the hell is that?
- Well, I lifted it...
...from the season finale
of The Valley.
When Manuel was busting
a move on April and she found out...
...Jake was sleeping with her mom.
- Riveting stuff.
Yeah. Will you proof it for me?
We have to act fast. Ryan's
a yellow slicker and a beard away...
...from becoming
the Gorton's fisherman.
- Not getting the reference.
- He got a job on a boat, leaves tomorrow.
Wait, what? Wait, are you serious?
Your dad's just, like, letting him go?
Pulling the old Sandy Cohen
Jedi mind-meld on him.
- Trying to break his will by agreeing.
- Like he did with you?
Which you fell for because
you're spineless and weak.
Yes, exactly, but this is Ryan.
So if Taylor's gonna fall for your plan,
we need a language she'll understand.
Are you trying to say
that you believe me?
No, not exactly. There's no other
options. Do you have her phone number?
We're not gonna call her.
She's not a moron, she's evil.
We're not gonna call her,
we're going to text her.
- What is that?
- Or, should I say, Dean Hess is.
- You got the bedazzled one? Pink too?
- Yeah.
We can't text her an apology.
We're texting her an apology?
An invitation.
I got a room at the Mermaid Motel.
The place where Ryan may have
conceived Theresa's baby...
...and where Marissa's mom
and Luke got it on?
Newport's very own den of sin.
- But I like it.
- We can even...
I mean, if we have some free time...
Whatever.
Hope you don't mind.
I'm early for your party.
My what?
Well, Sandy and Kirsten wanna
have a send-off party for you.
Since, apparently, you're leaving.
- I was gonna tell you.
- It slipped your mind?
No.
I was waiting for the right time...
...since I thought
you might not understand.
Understand what?
- That you're becoming a fisherman?
- It's not about the job.
- I need to make a change.
- A change.
No, not from us.
Right. You taking off for weeks at a time
won't change us at all.
It's not forever, it's...
- It's just until...
- Until when?
The dean lets you back into Harbor?
Because that may never happen.
- I need you to understand.
- Consider it understood.
- You sure about this Julie Cooper?
- Definitely.
She's got all the right connections
and nothing left to lose.
I hope so. You better be right.
I know what I'm doing, babe.
Damn it.
- Hi.
- What the hell are you doing here?
I hope you don't mind.
I got your address from the realtor.
Are you stalking me?
No, but I can see
why you would think that.
- Can I come in?
- You really don't want to. And no.
Okay, well, l...
I have some good news.
- I got the condo.
- Oh, well, I'm happy for you.
- Adios.
- I put it in your name.
- Say what now?
- I bought it for you.
You bought me a condo?
Kirsten filled me in on your situation.
- It moved me.
- It moved me too.
Right into this fleabag hellhole.
Nonetheless, a long time ago I learned
there is no such thing as a free lunch.
- Or condo.
- Julie, I don't want anything from you.
I swear. Except the use
of the spare room when I'm in town...
...which should only be
a couple weeks a year.
Other than that, it's all yours.
You're serious?
I know what it's like
to fall on hard times.
No one else has to know about our
arrangement. This can just be our secret.
You realize, Ryan,
of all our harebrained schemes...
...of which there are many,
quitting school for a life at sea...
...that may be number one.
I can't say the idea has gotten
an enthusiastic response.
Except from your dad,
who's throwing me a dinner.
- He's calling your bluff.
- I'm not bluffing.
- Didn't say it was working.
- I think he's hoping to...
...give me enough rope to hang myself.
- You've fashioned said rope...
...into a perfect little sailor's knot.
- Well, it's the best option I got.
If Harbor let you back in,
would that change your mind?
- Never gonna happen.
- Never say never.
- I may have a plan in motion.
- I feel a lot better.
Let's just get this over with.
We got all dressed up,
and you decided to come to this thing.
- You might as well make the best of it.
- How?
I don't know,
but at the same time tomorrow...
...Atwood is gonna be netting sea bass
with rank fishermen in wool sweaters.
Yeah, well, this could be
the last time I see him for a while.
Where he doesn't smell
like pickled herring.
All right. I'll try.
Honey, this homemade pad thai,
it's delicious.
Keep this up,
we'll save a bundle on takeout.
Oh, thank you. I hope everybody likes it.
I used tofu instead of shrimp.
It's fine by me. I think I've kind of
gone off of seafood for a while.
I for one, I love the tofu.
Tofuna. Tofurky.
To-bagel with cream to-cheese.
- Too much.
- It was a valiant effort.
So tell us about the captain.
Well, he's pretty much
what you'd expect.
Oh, what's that? Eye patch, peg leg?
Parrot on his shoulder?
I love parrots. I think they're cute.
You know, "Polly want a cracker?"
Yeah. Sorry.
Actually, the captain's Johnny's uncle.
That's how I met him.
Johnny got you the job?
Unbelievable.
You know what? I think I'm just ruining
everyone's dinner, so I'm gonna go.
- No, no, no.
- No, no, no. Sit down.
You're not ruining anything.
Well, maybe a little.
But it's completely understandable.
Well, I'm glad something around here is.
Summer, can I have the keys?
- Thanks for dinner, Sandy. Kirsten.
- Excuse me.
Summer, your purse is buzzing.
Taylor took the bait.
Marissa. Hey, wait,
can we talk about this?
What's there to talk about?
You've already made your decision.
- I don't wanna leave like this.
- Then don't leave.
All right. Well, then I guess
we don't have a choice.
- Need any help?
- I'm good, thanks.
At this point I'm pretty good
at packing light.
Are you sure you wanna
go through with this?
You've beaten
the Sandy Cohen mind-meld.
I was hoping if we gave you space...
...you'd realize this isn't the answer
to your problem.
Maybe my problem
doesn't have an answer.
Sure it does. If you keep
out of trouble until you graduate...
...you'll land at a community college.
Yeah, post a couple of semesters
of good work...
...you transfer to a four-year school.
If you come from my family,
it's not so easy.
We're your family now.
I may not be an Atwood anymore,
but I'm not a Cohen either.
I don't know what I am.
So you're gonna figure it out lost at sea?
Lost at sea, lost on land.
What's the difference, right?
Well, kid, we can't force you to stay.
But this is your home now.
And the door is always open.
Thank you. I'm gonna head out.
See you in a couple weeks.
Marissa, what's going on?
Hey, I wanted to talk about
that job you got Ryan.
- I'm glad I could help.
- How, by ruining his life?
I'm gonna go out
into the ocean far away.
I'm a little confused.
I mean, Ryan needed a job, I got him
one. I thought I was helping him out.
I know. I shouldn't be blaming you.
It was his decision,
it's just now he's leaving.
I take it it wasn't a happy sendoff.
We got in a fight.
Well, at least you got to be
honest with him.
Tell him how you felt.
Actually, I didn't.
- And I don't even know where he is.
- I do.
Home sweet home.
Wow, gift horse, mouth,
far be it for me to do any looking.
I don't know what to say.
Thank you?
Don't say anything. It makes me
feel great to be able to help.
Though the place needs furniture.
I can cover that.
I have a little money stashed away.
I bet pawning that ring
brought in a small fortune.
- How about a little champagne?
- Aren't you just out of rehab?
All right, for you. I'll have water.
I will open this, I'll meet you out there.
If you can find some glasses.
My pleasure.
She's in.
- Any extra ones?
- All right.
I will. We will.
- All right, have a great trip.
- How you doing?
- Get all this below deck.
All right. Let's go.
- Is everything onboard?
- No.
Ryan?
Marissa, what are you doing here?
I couldn't let you leave
without telling you how I really felt.
Okay.
You see, I couldn't figure out why
I was so mad at you...
...and then I realized it's because
you're doing what my dad did.
He left and ran away on a boat,
and now you are too...
...so I guess that makes you
just as much of a coward as he is.
And you know what, running away
never really helped him at all.
What if this is the bed
that Julie and Luke had sex in?
- A boy can dream.
- Will you quit peeping out the window?
You don't peep out of windows.
You peep into them.
You'd know.
Taylor. She's coming.
Hey, skank.
You were expecting someone taller,
blonder, with a pageboy haircut?
Welcome to the Terrordome, Townsend.
- You're busted.
- For what, exactly?
A little extracurricular activity
with Dean Hess.
Yeah, I saw you two
making out at the dance.
So what if we did?
She'd make a hell of a poker player.
- Unless you want this little thingamajig...
- Indiscretion.
...to go public...
- What up?
...we have a few demands, don't we?
- Yeah.
Starting with lifting the ban
of Ryan Atwood from Harbor.
You can go ahead
and tell anyone you want.
No one's gonna believe you.
She's like a block of ice.
You willing to bet your squeaky
little reputation on that, Taylor Trash?
Because I've got a huge mouth
and an even bigger Buddy List.
See this right here? Sidekick.
Walkie-talkie of the 21 st century.
- Who should we radio first?
- How about my dad?
Yeah, ten-four, good buddy.
So, what's it gonna be?
You can either tell Seth's dad
the perverted truth and save your ass...
...or you can roll the dice.
Over and out.
- Sandy, come on in.
- Thanks for meeting me on a Sunday.
I take it from the surreptitious nature
of your phone call...
...you have something serious
to discuss.
Surreptitious. Good word.
No wonder they made you dean.
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
Do you classify a surreptitious
student-teacher relationship as serious?
If you're here to make an accusation,
Sandy, then please feel free.
It's just the two of us, we can talk.
Man-to-man.
Why talk when a picture's worth
a thousand words.
Or a hefty lawsuit.
Sorry, I'm not following.
Technology's a bitch, dean.
I have a hard time keeping up with it.
This little puppy's a phone,
it surfs the web...
...and, unfortunately for you,
it transmits photos.
Hard to send a picture of something
that never happened.
So you're saying you didn't get too close
to a coed at the school dance?
And these photos I have are fakes?
She's an aggressive girl.
She had a schoolgirl crush...
...and at the dance,
she forced herself on me.
And it was just a kiss.
I don't think the board
will see this as just a kiss.
Plus, it's not what the girl is saying.
- You talked to her?
- Yep.
She told me everything.
She doesn't want this to get out.
And I assume you don't either, because
this could be a real career killer...
...and you seem to be an ambitious guy.
- What do you want, Sandy?
- You kicked Ryan out of this school.
I want you to let him back in
with a clean slate.
I suggest you get yourself
one of these...
...get on craigslist and find yourself
another position on the East Coast.
Sound good to you?
I didn't know her.
- Mocha?
- Yeah, thanks.
- Skimmed? Regular?
- Regular.
I got into my car when
the cell phone went...
- Coop, are you okay?
- Ryan left.
- He's gone?
- Wait, what?
We just pulled off a life-changing scam.
Are you telling me we're too late?
- What are you talking about?
- Well, it doesn't matter now.
Well, this sucks.
Hey, it's the return of
the not-so-ancient mariner.
Ryan.
Look...
...I don't know what my future is...
...but I know it's with you.
Here.
Not on some boat
in the middle of the ocean.
I love that.
Hey, I got good news for you.
Well, I have good news,
and I have some bad news.
- Yeah, what's the good news?
- Good news is, you're back at Harbor.
- Really?
- My dad bluffed the dean and he caved.
- And the bad news?
- Well, you're back at Harbor, so...
And...?
Oh, you know what,
don't worry about it.
My getting kicked out
was backed up by the community.
With you, it was just the dean.
Besides, public school isn't that bad.
This is good news.
- I think so.
- Yeah, she's right.
You know, we gotta take our victories
as they come.
I have to say, Ryan Atwood, fisherman,
I think that's a good cheer for you.
- Yeah, you like that?
- I came up with some other jobs for you.
But I should warn you,
they're pretty wacky.
- Okay. All right.
- Okay?
Ryan Atwood, bullfighter.
Big hat, like, tight pants
and a little red coat.
- But I don't speak Spanish.
- Neither do bulls.
- Ryan Atwood, bounty hunter.
- Yeah.
Then you could have, like, a crossbow
and steel-toed boots. You like those.
What do you think of
Ryan Atwood, coward?
- That may have been harsh.
- You think so?
- It got your attention.
- Ryan Atwood, fluffer.
- Fluffer?
- Fluff what?
- Let's not ask that.
- I'm gonna explain it later.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group