Previously on The O.C.:
- Neil.
- Julie.
What a nice surprise.
Marissa's a real
chip off the old block.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Brains, beauty.
That surgeon...
...convinced the guy Johnny would make
a full recovery. He's back on the team.
- Thank you.
- She deserves to be happy.
I'm taking Kaitlin
to go look at new ponies.
Whatever no longer fits,
we'll just send it to your sister.
Thank God Kaitlin's going to boarding
school. This is no place for a child.
It's just not right for a little girl
to love a hairless pony.
- Why do you keep touching your face?
- Last night, before I went to bed...
...I had the sensation of a pimple
about to surface.
This morning,
skin's as clear as a smogless sky.
And that's a problem because...?
- Ryan, don't you see?
- Not so much.
Things are going way too well
around here.
What?
Marissa got back into Harbor.
You guys seem to have resolved
your surf-tastic love triangle.
My girlfriend got a near perfect score
on her SATs. We've never been happier.
Senior year is supposed to be
the best year.
No, you should know better.
Every time things are going too well,
doom comes a-knocking.
- Doom?
- A-knocking.
Or a-ringing.
Right on time. Don't answer it.
It's probably a flaming bag of crap.
Or FedEx.
Yeah?
So I show up at my house
to surprise my mom...
...and this Persian dude
answers the door.
- I'm sorry?
- I figured he was the new butler.
But then I saw his shoes. Prada.
I thought maybe he's my new stepdad.
And I was about to, like, hug him...
...and then his wife shows up.
No matter how rich the guy is,
my mother would never join a harem.
- I don't...
- So I was like, " Persian dude...
...what are you doing at my house,
and where is my mother?"
He was like, "Who's your mother?"
So I told him...
...and he tells me that my mother moved
and the mail is being forwarded here.
- I think you may have...
- Are you gonna invite me in or what?
Jeez, Ryan. I see Newport
hasn't improved your manners at all.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Kaitlin Cooper?
Weird neighbor kid. Hi.
- You've... You've grown...
- Boobs?
No, I...
Oh, it's a-knocking.
Kaitlin Cooper? Must be
two years since she's been back.
She mention why she's home
in the middle of a semester?
We never really got past
where home was.
Oh, Julie wants us to wait
until she gets here before we tell Kaitlin...
Her family's a prime candidate
for Pimp My Double-Wide?
Hey, guys, good morning.
You ready to go?
Third day of the Pride and Prejudice
mini-series in English.
Summer, the show you're about to see...
...has the makings of a classic
Jane Austen novel.
You've got sisters, lies and bosoms.
- Kaitlin's back.
- Mini Cooper?
- Mini Coop not so mini.
- Kaitlin?
- Where's my baby?
- She's getting herself together.
The kid's a little confused.
Don't know what I'm gonna tell her.
I wanted to protect her from everything
that's gone on around here.
Shootings, funerals, public school.
Well, just explain it to her.
She'll understand.
You might've. You're your
father's daughter. Kaitlin's me.
- She's not gonna want our life.
- She came home.
She wants her family
more than anything.
Mom?
Oh, baby.
Mom.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
Do you even look at my calendar?
It's mid-winter break.
I knew that.
I just... I figured...
Isn't it Fashion Week?
I thought you'd be in Paris
with Alexandra like last year.
Front row at Chanel.
I saw the photo on Wirelmage.
I thought that you'd be happy
to see me.
Well, I am. Of course.
Hey, we're so happy to see you.
So that guy at Caleb's said you moved.
I think we're gonna be late
for school, guys.
- Can I talk to you about the launch party?
- I love discussing a party.
I'm gonna be late for school too.
- Let's do something later and catch up.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Okay, so, what's going on?
Okay, do you remember that e-mail
I sent you about Caleb?
There were some
financial complications afterwards.
Oh, my God.
- We live in a trailer.
- Well, yes.
But not "live" live.
We're more like refugees.
We're only a half a mile
from the beach, and, well...
...it's Tiffany Blue.
Oh, honey, this is so temporary.
Once Kirsten's and my business is...
...up and running everything's
gonna be like it was.
So let's go inside.
And then you pull it open like this...
...and voilà, it's a bed.
That's versatile.
Oh, honey.
I'm sorry. I know this isn't
what you're used to.
But think of it as a life experience.
It's the kind of place
Britney Spears is from.
Mom, it's okay. Really.
I mean, it's like a slumber party.
The three of us, here.
You still have this puppy
Marissa gave you.
Though you didn't care
until you found out he was a purse...
...you could put
your pretend credit cards in.
Yeah, it was that summer in Tahoe.
The whole family together.
I guess it's sentimental.
Let's get our nails done.
I wanna hear everything you've
been up to in Montecito.
I'm supposed to help Kirsten
with our launch, but she'll understand.
You got a message?
Somebody from school?
A boy?
My little girl's growing up.
I'm gonna call Kirsten.
Hey, it's me.
I can 't believe
you just took off like that.
Don 't think that just because
you left town I'm gonna...
It's just the Kaitlin I know
is obsessed with her hairless pony.
I feel like I missed
this whole part of her life.
Puberty?
- And it's all my fault.
- What are you talking about?
Well, I mean, it's not like
I ever tried to keep in touch.
In fact, we were never really close.
It was always her and Mom
versus me and Dad.
She's home now. You can fix that.
You talking about Kaitlin's
transformation from...
...horsey tweener to
lanky-limbed jailbait?
Cohen, one more pervy word
about Coop's not-so-mini Coop...
...and I may have to staple
your tongue to your collar.
- There you are! Hi!
- Hey, Taylor.
Thanks so much for everything
at that meeting last week.
Oh, of course.
You were Ionely at that school.
You had no friends. No one to talk to.
Kind of like Charlton Heston
in Planet of the Apes.
I think that was Mark Wahlberg.
Actually, I had a couple good friends.
But not like our group here.
Right?
- I should get to class.
- Me too.
The poor thing.
It must be really hard for her,
re-adjusting.
Kind of like coming back from Nam.
Thankfully, she has us.
Hey, you all right?
Taylor can be a little Taylor.
No, she just made me realize I haven't
talked to Johnny since I got here.
I mean, I've left him messages.
The tour starts soon.
I hope he hasn't left yet.
No, I don't think he'd do that.
Why don't you try,
what's his name, Bizzaro Seth?
Chili? Right, I could.
- Thanks.
- No problem. All right, see you at lunch.
Dude, will you please
just call her back?
This sacrificing-your-happiness-for-hers
thing clearly is not working.
No, it wasn't a sacrifice, all right?
I just thought my life would be
simpler without her.
Yeah, it's real simpler.
You're miserable.
Dude, will you please
just take my phone and call her?
It's like I summoned her. Marissa.
Hey, Chili, have you seen Johnny?
As a matter of fact,
Harper is right next to me.
Thanks. Hey, Marissa.
Hey, I called you a few times.
Did you get my messages?
Yeah, sorry, I've just been really busy.
- Of course. Packing and stuff.
- Yeah. Packing.
My sister's in town. I'd love
for you to meet her before you leave.
Oh, yeah, I don't know.
Maybe if I have time.
You're not gonna leave
without saying goodbye?
The diner, 4:30. Please?
I'll see you there.
- Veronica. What are you doing here?
- Hello, Kirsten.
I hear you and Julie
are starting a new dating service.
I want you to set me up
with the delicious Dr. Neil Roberts.
The father of Marissa's best friend?
The girl you called Miss Columbine
at last week's board meeting?
- Do you really think he'd go out with you?
- Of course not.
lf, however, I could talk to him,
say, over a candlelit dinner...
...I'm sure I could
convince him that I was...
...just a concerned parent
looking out for her daughter.
- That's where you come in.
- And why would I help you?
Marissa's back at Harbor.
But her involvement
in after-school activities...
Senior Day, prom, graduation.
- is yet to be determined.
And I carry a lot of weight
with the Parents' Association.
You might say
I am the Parents' Association.
You're gonna hold a 17-year-old girl
hostage for a date?
A good man is hard to find, Kirsten.
I'm free tomorrow, if you're wondering.
You'll have the contracts by Friday.
Yeah. Oh, it's great, Sid.
I'll talk to you then.
Well, this is a wonderful surprise.
I wish it was.
Sandy, I have a problem.
Veronica Townsend came by
to see me this morning.
She wants me to set her up
with Neil Roberts.
Good luck.
She threatened to make Marissa's life
a living hell at Harbor if I don't.
- And she can do it.
- We can't give in to threats like that.
We don't negotiate with the Newpsies.
I know. But Marissa's
been through a lot.
All Neil has to do is take her
out for dinner tomorrow.
What do you want me to do?
You've got the dating service.
- Neil isn't a client.
- And I'm not an employee.
No, but you are Sandy Cohen,
professional persuader.
You guys play golf together,
and you're guys.
And I'm calling in a wifely favor.
Just call?
Shopping was such a good idea.
Yeah. Even if it was at a thrift store.
Hey, vintage is very in right now.
So who are we meeting again?
My friend Johnny from Newport Union.
I guess he's going away
on this surfing trip, and...
- I just don't wanna lose touch, you know?
- Do I know about losing touch?
Kaitlin...
Mom, in her own deranged way,
was just trying to protect you.
And I was...
I don't know, but it won't happen again.
Yeah, I know, it's just,
I'm not a little kid anymore, you know.
I know. There they are.
Which one's Johnny?
Perfect Bone Structure or Carrot Top?
Yeah, you're definitely not a kid.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- So, Kaitlin, this is Chili and Johnny.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- Hey, Marissa.
- Hi. Thanks for coming.
So when do you leave?
- Next week.
- April.
Right, he leaves
next week for training.
Tour starts in April.
Dude, did I lock my car?
I think I forgot to lock...
Been a lot of thefts in the area lately.
He's got...
...a bunch of cassette tapes in there.
Can you excuse me?
Much coffee, small bladder.
What's going on?
Marissa, do I have to spell it out for you?
Okay, I guess I do.
Look, he knew that you weren't gonna go
back to Harbor while he was there, so...
He told me that he was leaving?
Oh, my God.
- Johnny.
- Hey.
So how long have you been in love
with my sister?
- We're just friends.
- Good.
Because I'm sure, as you know,
she's not available.
Unlike, say, me.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Hi, this the Cohen house?
- It is. Can I help you?
I'm looking for someone.
I had the wrong address.
Persian guy said I could find her here.
- Kaitlin Cooper?
- You a friend of hers?
I need to get ahold of her.
Is she here or not?
Look, man. I haven't seen Kaitlin
since she was 11 and rode a pony.
All right.
Well, if she shows up, call me?
It's important.
Hey, Ryan. What's up?
- Your sister around?
- No, she went out.
Can I help you?
Maybe.
There was this guy showed up
at the house last night looking for you.
- Justin?
- You know him?
He's from Montecito,
and he goes to Cate.
I met him at a mixer.
Is he your boyfriend?
I barely even spoke to the guy.
Then he kept on calling me.
Coming by my school.
I finally told my dorm mother,
and it got him in trouble.
And now he's like, " You're messing up
my chances in Princeton."
I can't believe that he showed up here. I
mean, I'd already changed my cell phone.
- All right. I'll take care of it.
- And you won't tell Marissa?
We're just starting
to get to know each other again.
And I don't want her to think
I'm some stalker magnet.
And I don't want her to worry.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- So, Chili...
- Told you?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he was never one to keep a secret.
Well, what you did was pretty amazing.
- I just wanted to thank you.
- Yeah. I'm a real martyr.
So, what are you gonna do now?
- Since you're not going on tour.
- I hadn't really thought about it.
Well, you could always apply to college
for next January.
- No, I don't think so.
- I could help you.
Listen, Marissa...
...it's not your problem anymore.
You're back where you belong.
You know, my life...
...maybe it's not
to tour the world to surf...
...but I don't need you saving me.
- You did this incredible thing for me...
- Is that what you think?
I needed you to leave.
So I'm back at Harbor.
But what are you saying? That you
don't ever want to see me again?
Yeah, I guess that's what I'm saying.
Right now, I just need you
out of my life.
Okay.
- Hello?
- Neil. Hey, it's Sandy.
- I hope I'm not interrupting.
- Not at all, Sandy. How can I help you?
Well, there's a bit of a situation
with Marissa.
Anything I can do?
Marissa and her mom mean a lot to me.
Well, this is awkward.
You know Veronica Townsend?
Do I know Veronica Townsend? Sandy,
I know every former A-cup in this town.
What would you think
about having dinner with her tonight?
- You mean a date?
- Look, I know she is a bitch-on-wheels.
She wants to go out with you.
She's willing to make Marissa 's life at
Harbor difficult if it doesn 't go through.
Sandy, that's preposterous.
Wouldn't ask if I didn't think
she'd follow through.
Look, it's one dinner.
Crowded restaurant, meet there.
- Kirsten and I will pick up the tab.
- How horrible can it be?
Trust me, it'll be horrible. I owe you.
Thanks.
- Good, you're here.
- Where's Kaitlin? She came with you?
I didn't think that was a good idea.
The best thing for you to do...
...is get in your car, go back where
you came from, put this behind you.
I'm not going anywhere without the
1500 bucks she stole from my brother.
- She says she barely knows you.
- We've been going out for like a month.
And I wanted her to meet
my brother Sam.
He's a Gamma Tau at UCSB. They were
having a party, so I brought her.
Then she ditched me, ran off with
the door money, and left town.
Three guys saw her
stuff it in a gym bag and take off.
I'm supposed to take the word of drunk
frat brothers over a 14-year-old girl?
Fourteen? She told me she was 16.
Like I said,
put this behind you.
I'm trying to help her.
All right, it's not my money,
and now it's out of my hands.
I had three messages
from Taylor this morning.
I told you.
She has abused-puppy syndrome.
If you show her the tiniest bit of
affection, she'll follow you for life.
I know, but she's kind of
our responsibility now.
- Oh, my God! Huge news!
- Oh, my God!
- Who let you in?
- I speak fluent housekeeper.
Guess what?
My mom's getting set up with your dad.
- Oh, my God.
- lf they get married, we could be sisters.
I'm gonna take a spin around
and see which room I might want.
- Okay? I'll be right back.
- Okay.
She is so going back to the pound.
No, no, no. The football players
are the real pussycats.
It's the female tennis players
that will kill you in your sleep.
You know, in Russia, rumor has it
that Sharapova's rep is former KGB.
I had no idea being a sports
agent was so dangerous.
Mom, this place is way too expensive.
Oh, but honey, it's your homecoming.
It's a special occasion.
- Mom?
- You know where we should go?
- Here. You just said so.
- The Crab Cooker.
We haven't been there in years.
It'll be so fun.
But... Okay.
- Hey.
Oh, I'm almost ready.
Take your time.
The movie doesn't start for a while.
You all right?
- I'm trying to find my stupid jacket.
- I'll help you.
It's brown with things on it.
And stupid?
I got in a fight with Johnny.
He lied about the surf tour.
He was never going.
You knew, didn't you?
Yeah, and I should've told you,
but the guy did a good thing.
He did it to get rid of me.
And, I mean, even though
he's not going now...
...he still says
he doesn't ever wanna see me again.
But he's in an awkward position.
You gotta respect that. Give him time.
I know.
- Okay, you got your sister back here...
- Yeah.
- I guess I do have a great boyfriend.
- You have a great boyfriend too.
And I'm just getting to know my sister.
So life could be worse.
- Hey!
- Hey.
That's awesome.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey.
You seem pensive. Scoot down.
So Kaitlin is up to something.
- Dude, I told you. Doom.
- I know.
- Hit me with it. What is it?
- All right.
So this guy showed up looking for her.
I asked her about it.
She said he'd been stalking her.
When you gave
the "get out of town" speech...
He said she stole money
from some frat party.
And then I found this bag he described
in the trailer.
She's Jimmy Cooper's daughter.
Theft is in her blood.
I wanna give her a chance
to explain, but...
Hey, guys. Good morning.
Hey. I love how people
just come in now.
No more of that useless back and forth
to the front door.
So we're gonna go get pancakes.
You guys wanna come?
Actually, Marissa, I'm gonna need
to borrow you for a second.
We have to work
on Summer's birthday present.
- Her birthday's not for eight months.
- What to get the girl that has everything?
We need to plan early.
So I went to see Justin yesterday.
Oh, my God, thank you so much.
- He said you stole some money.
- What money? I don't know what you're...
I found the bag in your stuff.
Okay, so I took it.
- But it was for a good reason.
- Please.
Justin's brother Sam
is dating my friend Megan.
He seemed like the perfect guy, right?
Until she told him she was pregnant.
Okay, then what happened?
So she asked him for some money
to, you know, take care of it...
...and he said it wasn't his problem,
so I took it.
Do you wanna call Megan
and ask how her abortion went?
Whatever happened,
you need to tell Marissa, okay?
You know I can't tell her.
You know how she is.
Seth, whichever action figure you choose,
Summer will be equally thrilled.
Can we go?
You know, I lost my appetite.
Can you guys just drop me off
on the way?
Yeah, sure.
Is everything okay?
Morning, sweetheart.
Late night last night?
Actually, I wanted to tell you,
I went on a date.
- With Veronica Townsend?
- How'd you know?
Word gets around when Orange County's
Cruella nabs her next puppy.
I am sorry I didn't tell you.
I thought it would just be one dinner.
What do you mean "you thought"?
One dinner, I get.
One dinner is a man on the rebound
with a severe lapse of judgment.
All right. That's enough.
She happens to be
a misunderstood woman.
Dad, she is an evil bitch.
Her daughter was picking out paint chips
for her new room, which is your study.
I am taking Veronica
to the party at the Cohens' tonight...
...and I expect you
to at least be polite to her.
Fine.
Gus, I'm sorry.
My mom said
I can't open the door for you again.
Even if you actually have candy.
It's Johnny.
- Hi.
- Is Marissa here?
How come nobody ever comes
knocking on this door for me?
Sorry. I just...
I said some stuff to her yesterday.
I wanted to apologize.
I'm afraid she's not here.
- Okay.
- But...
...my mom's having a launch party
tonight for her new company.
It's at the Cohens'. She'll be there.
- Maybe you should stop by.
- I don't think that's such a good idea.
Come on. I'm inviting you.
So at least there's one person there
that's not totally lame.
Maybe I'll stop by.
To apologize to Marissa.
- So tell me.
- That obvious?
You barely touched your short stack.
I can tell something's up.
It's Kaitlin.
There's this guy looking for her.
Says she stole money from his brother.
Oh, she stole from another kid? No way.
She admitted it.
But she says she took it because
the brother got her friend pregnant...
...and needed it.
I can't believe it.
It doesn't make any sense. Why would
he come after her if her story's true?
- So you think she's lying?
- I don't know. You need to talk to her.
And accuse her of being a thief?
After everything we've put her through,
that'll build her trust.
I don't think the guy's going away
without his money.
All right, well,
I'll talk to her after the party.
Until then,
we'll just have to keep an eye on her.
Check the propane? Thank you.
- How's it going?
- Great.
I've done maybe 12,
and I've got about 100 to go.
Well, make that 102.
I've added Neil Roberts
and Veronica Townsend to the guest list.
You've gotta be kidding me.
- Did Sandy...?
- What? Tell me they were dating?
No. I had to find that out myself
last night at the yacht club.
It's just...
- What is it?
- Well, for the past few weeks...
...Neil and I have gotten quite close.
And sure, the man is a real catch...
Wealthy doctor,
estate with pool and tennis court.
- but I was just grateful
that he's been so kind to Marissa...
...and then last night
I saw him with Veronica, and it hit me:
I think I have feelings for him.
Romantic feelings.
Now he's with that witch
who tried to harpoon Marissa...
...and they're coming
to our launch party.
I'll be okay, Kiki.
I'm like the Gulf region.
At this point, what's one more hurricane?
I'm telling you, it'd work.
We're not starting a rumor
my dad has genital warts.
Hey, Seth, how about
lending your mom a hand downstairs?
Actually, we're kind of busy right now.
We're trying to figure out how to break
up my dad and some skanked-out ho.
- Veronica Townsend.
- Everyone knows.
You got nothing to worry about.
It's a long story.
- Last night's date, one-time thing.
- He's bringing her to the party tonight.
He's going on a second date with her?
Sandy, there you are.
I have to talk to you about
Veronica Townsend and you-know-who.
- Now we have a quorum.
- What happened?
There are factors of which I was not
aware when I had you set them up.
- Wait, you set them up?
- She wanted a date with Summer's dad.
She threatened to make
Marissa's life hell.
- Neil agreed as a favor.
- Look, Neil's a smart guy.
If he wants to go on a second date,
maybe he sees something we don't.
- What the hockey?
- No, no, no.
Okay, okay, fine. But we have to make
sure that she's the one who ends it.
If Neil pulls away,
she might take it out on Marissa.
- Genital warts. It's the answer.
- Seth!
You've got a dinner to set up. You two
work on a plan. I'll keep thinking.
We can do this.
Okay, we've gotta make Veronica
Townsend not wanna date your dad.
So tell me the most shameful thing
you know about your father.
I'm just not sure which is
harder to believe:
That she stole money
or she paid for another girl's abortion.
Either way, that girl's not my sister.
I'll get it.
- Hey. You brought friends.
- This is the guy who knows where she is?
No one's getting anything.
Get out of here.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- And which are you?
The stalker, or his brother
who got a 14-year-old girl pregnant?
What is she talking about?
Has anyone seen the cocktail napkins?
- Give me my money back, bitch!
- Kaitlin!
Kaitlin, Kaitlin, go to the pool house.
Get out of here or we'll call the cops.
I've been trying to do Kaitlin a favor.
She won't help herself.
Wanna call the cops, go ahead.
- I'll call them.
- No, no, it's fine.
Marissa, just go talk to her, please.
Maybe we can settle this.
Give them a second, all right?
Kaitlin, these guys are...
Kaitlin?
Looks like she already
planned her getaway.
- Going somewhere?
- Like anyone would notice.
- I think those boys you stole from would.
- I told you not to tell her.
I knew she was gonna act
like a self-righteous princess.
- You're blaming me?
- Hey...
...why don't you just talk to each other?
- You should let me help you.
- Now I'm supposed to believe you care?
- I do care.
- Yeah.
That's why I spent the last two
Christmases with complete strangers.
Strangers who don't
even have a nice tree.
And I want to make that up to you.
But you have to start being more honest.
I have to start being honest?
Look around, Marissa.
You and Mom have been
living a giant lie.
Hey, I just found out about the trailer.
Mom said she was renovating a condo.
And you believed her?
My friend Hadley's dad
owns this property.
And when he heard
about his new tenant...
...he called her right away.
He couldn't believe it.
"Julie Cooper-Nichol?
Isn't that Kaitlin's mom?
Why would she
be living in a trailer park?"
- I can't believe you knew.
- My whole school knew.
So why did you steal the money?
- Because I wanted to come back home.
- What, to find out...
...if the rumors were true?
- No.
To make sure
that you and Mom were okay.
I'm sorry.
But we really were
just trying to spare you.
From what? Being a part of this family?
Come here.
If you stick around long enough,
you might find out what that's really like.
Ryan?
I only wanted enough
for the car to get down here.
- I'm sorry for the lies.
- I'll tell the cabbie he's not needed.
Well...
...I guess, unfortunately,
you have to go to Mom's party.
Only if I can borrow something to wear.
I'll drink to that.
Where is she?
Don't worry. Taylor will be here.
I can't believe I told you
about my dad.
Well, it does kind of
make me see him in a new light.
Hi, everybody. Welcome.
- Thanks for coming. I'm Kirsten Cohen.
- And I'm Julie Cooper-Nichol.
Thank you. Well, tonight we launch...
...Newport's first
exclusive dating service, NewMatch.
Because, well, whether you're gay,
straight, single...
...divorced, nearly divorced...
...in a world of wealth and luxury...
...the only thing really worth pursuing
is a soul mate.
So drink up, enjoy and flirt.
If I didn't already have the perfect
woman, I would sign up.
Will you two excuse me?
Don't worry.
The plan is in motion.
Taylor, you're here. Great.
- Oh, it's good to see you too, Seth.
- Yeah, so...
Now, don't make a pass at me.
I don't want you coming between sisters.
Come here.
Listen, how serious is your mom
about Dr. Roberts?
Well, let's put it this way.
When my mom decides
she wants something, she gets it.
Like when she wanted my dad,
she got him.
And when she wanted all of his money...
...and the house in the divorce,
she got that.
Now she wants Dr. Neil Roberts.
Well, there's something
I think you should know about him.
Here it is. Most of it, anyway.
Thanks.
So where's Kaitlin?
With her sister. Why?
Why do I get the feeling
this isn't just about the money?
I just thought Kaitlin
might come by with you.
To apologize or something.
Least she could do is apologize.
So she didn't say anything to you
about me at all?
- Like?
- I don't know.
You're in love with her.
Maybe I thought I was, but...
- But what?
- Just be careful of that girl, man.
She's amazing.
Thanks.
You know, I used to always lie awake,
so jealous...
...that you, Mom and Dad
were at one of these things.
A Newport party.
- Yeah, well, you're finally here.
- Yeah.
Well, what I had in mind
was way cooler than this.
Well, how did it go?
Watch and see.
We should go somewhere
more private and have a drink.
- Well, that sounds like a good idea.
- Hi, I'm sorry.
Mom, can I talk to you for a second?
Dr. Roberts and I are trying to
have a private conversation.
- This is just gonna take a second, though.
- It's okay. Go ahead.
What? Who told you that?
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, Neil...
...we'll have to do that drink another
time. Taylor's not feeling well.
- I'll just talk to you later.
- All right.
Oh, my God, that is amazing.
All you told her was
he voted for John Kerry?
Yes, that is exactly what I said.
You told her he had genital warts?
- That Kerry thing wasn't gonna work.
- Come on.
- Neil.
- Hey, Sandy.
- You're all alone.
- Yes, yes.
Veronica's daughter wasn't feeling well.
- Well, you just dodged a Newpsie bullet.
- Well, you're probably right.
I think I've been out of the dating pool
so long, I was momentarily blind.
Well, I think it's time
for me to be getting home.
I think there's someone here
who wouldn't mind your company.
Hey, Kaitlin.
- You leaving?
- I wish I could.
- Party that good?
- It just got a little bit more interesting.
I'm gonna find Marissa. Excuse me.
Hey there.
- Where's Veronica?
- She left.
Alone?
Really?
You two seemed to be
getting along so well.
Actually, I was hoping you might
have dinner with me sometime.
Neil, I would love to.
Ryan.
- Oh, sorry.
- Walked into that.
No, what are you doing here?
I'm not staying. I just...
I wanted to apologize.
For yesterday.
I don't know why I said those things.
They're not even true.
I guess, I just...
I missed you.
Apology accepted.
I missed you too.
Look, I know we both
have our own lives now.
Just don't be a stranger, okay?
Speaking of strangers,
have you seen my sister?
Yeah, she's out front.
Seemed a little bored.
Yeah. You think maybe
you could drive her home?
Sure.
Take her for ice cream or something.
Of course, I didn't mean to hit you.
I just find it interesting
how your hand collided with my face.
- Summer.
- Taylor, I thought you left.
Oh, I did.
I told my mom I had to come back.
I am so bummed that it
didn't work out between our parents.
But if you don't mind, I would still
really like to think of you as my sister.
- Yeah, me too.
- Really?
- Okay, that's great.
- That makes this all worthwhile.
Okay, so I gotta go,
but I'll see you tomorrow in school, sis.
- Okay.
- Okay. Bye.
Bye.
You want another black eye?
- Hey.
- How did it go?
- Good, I guess.
- Was he okay about the money?
- I don't think it was money he was after.
They were seeing each other.
What? You're kidding.
He's, like, our age.
And she lied about hers.
Well, that's not that big
of a surprise, I guess.
I kind of feel sorry for the guy.
I mean, you were, what,
a year older than Kaitlin when I met you?
I know what it's like
to fall for a Cooper girl.
Yeah. I guess you do.
- Where is she now?
- Well, Johnny took her home...
...so hopefully, by now,
she's safe in bed.
Thanks for getting me out of there.
No problem.
You know how people say
that you can't go home again?
I'm never sure if that means
that the place has changed or you have.
- Well, what do you think?
- I think this place is the same as I left it.
And you?
Pull over.
- No, we're gonna stop...
- I don't want ice cream.
Just stop the car.
I feel like a swim.
- Now?
- Yeah.
So? You scared?
- No, but...
- Come on.
- Kaitlin!
- Last one in!
Kaitlin, wait.
Come on.
It's freezing!
- Come in.
- Kaitlin!
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group