I understand the pressure that you're under, I do.
Daddy, Daddy.
I know how patient you have been with my handling of Jarod, but,
No more excuses. I…
wasn't finished.
What?
I thought you came here to kill me.
Better to find the story.
Who are you?
My name is Igor.
- Let me go, Frankenstein.
- I'm going to...
Beautiful, beautiful.
People think spontaneous combustion is a myth.
I don't. I wouldn't be caught dead because of combustion in my pocket. Hey, look at this.
Focus.
There must be an connection between ''ring a bell''
and the Frankenstein movie.
Do you remember any of the dialogue?
Something like:
''Who are you?''
''My name is Igor.''
Hey, Son of Frankenstein!
Basil Rathbone goes back to his dad's castle and meets lgor, Bela Lugosi.
And they bring the monster back to life.
It's not a Jesus James Whale's movie, but,
it's definitely get a chatter.
Oh, you are a lonely man, aren't you?
Look.
It's an angel with the broken wing.
Perhaps Jarod perceives himself as a fallen angel?
Or he simply forgot to put the caution fragile tags on the box?
Hey look!
Igor knows the secret.
What's secret?
The Center throw a rock in you head one.
I am calling Bjorn to getting ... Broots, why don't you watch Son of Frankenstein again,
and see if Basil is a wonder boy.
We have half of our sweapers out there looking for him.
We are gonna find him.
And when we do, we'll have a little spontaneous combustion of my own in mind.
That's him! Get him!
I'll get him out!
Mark, get in!
There are pretenders among us.
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours, he's already demonstrating more talent than any of our others.
How many people died because what I thought up?
Since I broke up, I spent every moment searching for my past.
He is a pretender.
A genius who can become anyone that he wants to be.
- The Center wants him alive.
- Preferably.
He defends the weak and abused.
Life is a gift.
THE PRETENDER
Season 2
Episode 8
FX
-=伊甸园论坛http://www.ydy.com=-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=YTET PRESENTS=-
DICTATION: 笨笨/葱葱
You are a doctor?
I am today.
End, cut!
Beautiful work, Jarod.
That is what I get paid for.
Jarod.
They said that you are the hottest new special ... in town
that I realised that matter literally!
Brynne McLain.
Thank you for comming.
I just never doubt I get invited to alive at your resume.
It's a clever idea, really sense.
Although I've been wondering why a special effects coordinator will actually do that fire stunt himself.
No one pulls the stunter design unless I try to first myself.
- Noble.
- Smart, considering the accident on the Blaster Beer set last week.
I figured the FX coordinator was a little smart
that's exactly what you mean.
Producing a Super Sunday can pay a new beer,
can make a break of an agency.
The accident put it on jeopardy.
Which is what I have wanted you to see for yourself
how my effects ... Say!
Bit better. With commercial time in three million per thirty,
I need Pavarotti.
Twitch, and I'll be watching grey matter of the walls.
- What?
- And how is lgor?
He'd better not snore.
Oh, sounds the noisy makes keep you up,
So sharp toe nails.
It's all funny, Jarod.
- Will you tell me what it means?
- Ask lgor.
Right. ''He knows the secret.''
Can we do the kwit dance another time?
Sure, if you tell the secret of who I am.
You know I cann't help you with that one.
Well, then I cann't help you with this one.
But I have a god's feeling.
You figure it all out.
What're you looking at?
And now we've got Marianne Bosha live on the scene.
Friendship and Fire. As tragedy striked at the filming of Blaster beer commercial.
Stuntman Dave Dugger was hospitalized
with severe burns and head trauma.
who attending to drive this Cadillac through out an exploding billboard.
Although a small explosion was planned
witnesses describe the one occured as massive.
Well, our thoughts and prayers,
at secure ...
as well as Blaster brewery,
that make us blaster beers
all with Dave Dugger and Dugger family.
We all wish Dave Dugger's recovery.
In meantime, we want an internal investigation.
to make sure we get to the bottom of what caused this tragic accident.
Adding irony a pain,
this stunt was maximized by Dugger's long time FX coordinator,
and childhood friend Mickey Clausen.
Dave and me have done some of the stunts a hundren times.
I ... I ... don't know what went wrong.
Dave is my best friend.
Excuse me.
Dave Dugger's hospitalized in the intense care unit of Queen of Hope hospital.
His prognosis remains uncertain.
''Tragedy on Blaster Beer Set''
We thought it's a lot of times expensive in this campaign, Jarod.
Blaster brewery spend millions to launch this new beer.
That's why I hire Jarod, Mr. Connelly. He will make your beer blast through America's TV on Super Sunday.
I like ...
Let me show you what we have in mind.
- You remember Ray Slater. He's my assistant.
- I was Mickey Clausen's assistant.
we redesigned the stunt, so that the Blast trajectory blows over the car,
it'll be safer, yet larger blast.
It'll be a shot to die for.
Hey, Jarod, you have to show your brainstorm to the director.
- lan? Ian?
- Yes.
lan Tottenham, this is Jarod Lugosi, a new special effects coordinator.
Hello, Jaord.
We've all seen explosions,
but we need the audience to feel the explosion,
touch it, taste it,
cry for it.
Excuse me.
Cry for it?
He's pump us and then secure,
But he want a clear directing might .. glu spot.
Sounds revealing.
So you are up to speed on the campaign concept?
Well, I've never actually seen any of the commercials.
Show him spots.
The campaign concept involves around two young guys.
Sean and Joey.
- Who finds tickets to the big game
- In a case of Blaster beer.
- So now they are driving across America...
- In Blastermobile.
- to make a time for gig-off.
- the gig get them lost.
In our first spot, they winded in Louisiana.
and an old Cajun guy tells them to go west.
- so they blast off...
- And they end up here
Wow, check it out, dude!
Polar bears, penguins,
Santa Clause.
Dude, I don't think this is California!
No, man. This is Cream Day.
Let's punk!
Aren't they big talking frogs!
So who are these talking frogs?
Last year's big commercial?
This year will be all Sean and Joey
who in the last spot finally make it to California
- But they ...
- use too much Blaster power
and they end up overshooting in San Diego
when they are crashing a billboard on a beach in Tijuana.
Isn't that great?
So let me get this straight.
There are people out there who will buy your beers
based upon two guys who are not only two ... to read a map.
but simple-minded enough to drive through an exploding billboard?
That's our target market.
Jarod, we've got three days to finish this spot make it on your date.
Can you make a scene?
Like Pavarotti.
I need some remote control to do whatever it does but I can't find it.
I'm sure it's whereabout its line with the clues he's given us.
Come on, lgor, do something.
Catch on fire, ring a bell...
Help me!
Syd, give me your cell phone.
Audio-sense triggering mechanism.
Just like spontaneous combustion that blew up that crate in my office.
Jarod is annoying, but he is clever.
..., Brootsie.
It'll take my fingers off.
Give it to me.
My name is lgor.
''Ring a bell'', lgor knows the secret.
Igor knows the secret.
Igor knows the...Igor knows the secret.
That's it?
Another dead end.
You look just like her
You look just like her.
Just like whom?
Your mother.
lgor knows the secret about your mother.
Cancle clever. Jarod is just annoying.
Broots, I want you to search the man from DSAs, anything else you can think of.
Sydney, check your files. Any reference to lgor,
a name, anagram or acronym, whatever.
Ok, Jarod, you got my attention.
You think we're going to need stuntman for the shoe gag?
Not if we caught the socks with ...
We can put rubbers mat on the shoes.
- That toys came pretty sample?
- It's a model kit.
Didn't build models when you were a kid?
I built the Empire State building once.
And I carved the design of what later became the AMC Pacer out of a bar of soap.
It wasn't my best work.
How long have you been on the program?
Your ... chip.
I've been sober five years and unchanged.
That's great.
Dave Dugger sponsored me on the program.
He was the stuntman that was burned.
Dave is the reason I'm sober today.
And you know, he is the reason I'm alive.
Sounds like a good friend to have.
So what I think it is?
She was built before the fire.
That's what happened when you go to have in the potassium chlorate.
Is that what Brynne's investigation concluded?
They know Mickey Clausen screwed up. Case closed.
I just find it hard to understand how he can screw up so badly.
I mean every effects coordinator knows how reactive PC is.
At show base,
you want to keep good rep,
you get to produce the flash and fx.
So you think Mickey put his best friend in harms way to,
enhance his reputation?
As much as I hate to say.
That's exactly I will say.
Halitosis.
Excuse me?
The creature from death breath.
Now that is destined to become a classical among special effects ...
Do I know you?
I am Jarod Lugosi.
I was wondering if I might pick your brain for a minute.
Yeah, this is the first.
Guy who replaces me on the job comes to ask me for some point.
I always learn from the best.
Those are your folks?
Those are Dave Dugger's parents.
You and Dave are really close, ah?
Yeah, like brothers. His folks practically raised me.
But my days in Dugger's family are over.
Because of the accident?
I must have miscalculated the amount of the oxidizer.
What's that you think happened?
Well, cars don't blow up by themselves.
Were you able to detect anything when you watch the dailies?
I cannot watch them.
Here.
I want you to take them.
I can't see on tape what I see in my nightmares.
I just wish it were me in that car.
Have you seen Dave or his parents since the accident?
I can't face him. I can't face his folks.
Not after this.
If you don't go to the hospital,
they will never know how you feel.
Don't lose the people that you love.
Guy, may you have a good ride. Let's go!
How this happened?
Get him out of it.
Help me, help me!
Oh, no!
How this happen? Get him out...
There wasn't one explosion.
There were two.
You look just like her. lgor knows the secret. My name is Igor. My name...my name is Igor.
- What's wrong with the Igor, Broots?
- I don't know. I don't know what it is.
Forget lgor. What do you mean you didn't find anything?
I searched the main frame, checked all the DSA logs.
Just no acronyms, no anagrams, nothing on Igor.
And I went through my files but I find anything pertaining to anyone but that name.
Igor knows the secret. Figure it out. I've got to get feeling.
Shut that thing up or I swear to God I'll shoot it.
It's out of function. That is automatic.
Don't, Miss Parker.
... got to get feeling.
Got feeling.
Wait, wait, what are you doing?
How to get feeling?
Hi.
I am so sorry. I never meant...
Mickey.
Now the gag would look something like this.
That's it's. I've seen bigger rubber burns.
Those snikers were supposed to step in rock of fuel.
Maybe we should use some our rubber...
Just make it big.
But not too big. We got millions of dollars invested in Joey and Sean.
You should ... on some ... stunt..
That's supposed to be cold supplement and petrol.
Okay, first of all, lan, it's not called petrol. Maybe in your country they are called petrol. But over here in America, we call it gas!
- And second of all, have you been snipping son ...
- Okay, people.
He is right. The gasoline is way too volatile.
Safety doesn't sell beer. Flash does.
I got a day and half left on the shoot. Jarod, work with me here.
I have an idea, Jarod.
Napalm.
Napalm?
Where did you get it?
I made it.
You make your own napalm?
Mickey told me how.
With right balance, you can create massive explosion under control burn.
It's perfect for the shoe gag.
You might have a future in this business.
The tape from inside lgor is a security record of sublevel twenty-seven.
So that's what it looked like before it burned.
April 12, 1970.
The day before your mother died.
Mom!
Mr. Fenigor?
Mr. Fenigor? Fen…
lgor!
Can you recognize him?
Too damn dark.
Did you find out where they're keeping Timmy?
He's in room 155.
I've got to get Jarod and Timmy out of here tonight.
I have got a feeling something's going to happen.
can't escape ... special camera records us now.
I can't have to warn people finding out about these.
I'll take care of it.
The children's lives depend on us.
Who the hell is Timmy?
Somebody Mr. lgor was trying to help my mother rescue.
One was Jarod.
Syd, do you remember Timmy?
I want more co-operation next time.
Who is that?
When can I go home, Dr. Raines?
In good time, Timmy.
He's crying, Sydney.
He's scared.
- I want to talk to him.
- No, Jarod.
Come on.
It was one of Raines' project.
And if this was going on on in SL twenty-seven...
Timmy must have been...
one of Raines' experiments.
Broots
Run in Fenigor. I need to know who he is.
And Sydney, you go through your files again into searching for anything on Timmy.
We're going to find room 155.
What? You mean SL twenty-seven?
Again?
My mother wasn't afraid to go down there. Are you?
Oh, Yeah!
That's Raines' secrets in sublevel.
If he finds out we have been down there, He'll have us killed.
Then make sure he doesn't find out.
With the smoke, it's fire.
You shut up?
I've been sober 5 years and unchanged.
There is actually nothing on Fenigor.
And the only sound of Timmy's stay in the Center
is a simple discharge ...
signed by then Dr. Raines,
dated April 14, 1970.
The day after my mother was killed. How coincidental!
Hey, look!
''Lindbergh Baby Kidnapped''
- Jes
How long has the Center been doing this stuff down here?
Are you going to browse or you are going to help us find ...?
- Sydney, what else do Timmy's records reveal?
- Very little.
No last name, no forwarding addresses.
Common for a routine discharge.
Well, if it was so common then why was my mother so intending to rescue him?
Like the creature said: ''lgor knows the secret.''
The secret as to what got my mother killed maybe even who murdered her.
Easy, Parker.
One stopped at the time.
The information you are talking about could get us all killed.
Miss Parker.
What the hell...?
What is that?
It's a neuro-electric chair.
For a kid? I think I'm going to hurl!
I remember rumours about clandestine experiments involving brain-waves manipulation.
No wonder my mother was trying to save Timmy,
save all the children. This is unbelievable.
Hey, guys
Let's get out of here.
This place was trashed in a fire, we'll never know for sure what's happened to Timmy.
Maybe, maybe not.
What are you thinking, Einstein?
Let's bring in Angelo.
Maybe he can empath what happened down here.
What are you doing?
You cannot sell off your business.
This is your life's work.
Tell that to Dave Dugger and his parents.
Mickey, they are just trying to ... what happened.
Hollywood just ... what happened.
There is no stuntman in this town would work with me again.
I cannot believe that.
Everybody in town knows how wonderful you are at your job.
You are only as good as your last project.
It is over, Jarod.
- Alright, I'll buy it all.
- Excuse me.
I'll buy everything.
Mr. Formaldéhyde.
The lipstick camera you used to trail the cyclops
The bust that you created all these wonderful grotesque figures.
This one is not for sale, alright?
This is Dave Dugger.
We made this bust when our first gig together here.
This is the face I'll always remember.
I do not know what I'm going to do, Jarod.
I just...
What am I going to do?
What's the matter with him? I've never seen him ...!
He is on empath perhaps he is confronting
some negative associations as what he has for SL twenty-seven.
It could have meant both.
Maybe this was not a good idea.
Well if he can tell us something, it is a good idea.
Get him in here.
Come on, let's go, Angelo!
Angelo, Angelo, tell me what happened here?
- Angelo is frightened.
- What happened here, Angelo? Tell me about...
- Miss Parker, please.
- Tell me about Timmy.
Timmy...Timmy
No more Timmy.
- Angelo. Angelo.
- No more Timmy.
Come back, Angelo.
No more Timmy.
- Yeah.
- Ray, It is Jarod.
You're working late.
(I do a little arrangement.)
I have got some good news.
I just came to the hospital, Dave Dugger regains consciousness and he's asking for you.
Ray, are you there?
Yeah.
It's ... that's great news, Jarod.
I'm on my way.
- Is he ok?
- Angelo.
Can you hear me?
Angelo, can you speak?
I am sorry, Angelo.
Please, talk to me.
What you know may help me discover who killed my mother.
Angelo.
Look, I know how much this information means to you.
But down here will you hit a dead end.
Dead end is not our option, Sydney.
Somewhere in this hell hole are the answers about Timmy and Igor,
and the truth about what happened to my mother.
And it's time to take a look in the Raines' private deal and safe files.
Hey, Dave.
Are you awake?
Of course.
Hard to talk.
How are you doing?
(I am not likely to go to dance.)
I am sorry.
Don't get on soft on me, Ray.
Now that have drawn Mickey left me…
I need my real friends to be strong.
You are the only real friend that I have left.
What's up, buddy?
Your hands are shaking.
I started to drink again, Dave.
Why?
It is the guilt.
About what?
The ... I did to you.
I don't understand.
Mickey didn't do this to you.
He was looking out for you.
But Brynne, she would take no for answer.
One day she talked to me about the explosions
and I told her about my napalm and gave her a little demonstration.
When the explosion happened, I know she's stolen some and put it on the radiator.
I confronted her about it, and she threatened to off me if I talked.
With my background, nobody's going to believe me?
My career, my family
my life would have been oversewd.
I sold you and Mickey out to save myself.
I am sorry, Dave. I am so sorry.
It's ok, Ray.
The first step towards forgiveness,
is telling the truth.
Hello, Brynne?
It is Jarod.
I made an explosive break-through,
and I would like you the first see it.
Would you come to the set, before two o'clock tomorrow?
Wonderful.
Jarod.
You should know I make it apart to never get intimate with any of the man I work with.
Like it's for us. The job ends today.
But we still work here.
I get to tell you I put so much napalm on that billboard.
When this Cadillac hits it,
it's going to explode like Baghdad during the Gulf War.
Watch.
Hey, Brynne, why don't we take Cadillac for a little spin before we turn...?
Okay.
Thank you sir.
(Your belt.)
Do you have something special in mind?
Actually I thought of driving you into that billboard.
- What?
- Don't worry.
I've set it up to be very bit safe as you set up for Dave Dugger.
I even spill Ray's homemade napalm all over the radiator.
Just like you did to Dave.
I am out of here.
Oh, there is no point of struggling.
You know how strong ... glu is.
You created the commercial for it.
Are you insane?
People thought I was when I set myself on fire.
But I did remember to put on the suit and cover myself with Zel-jell.
So I should be just fine.
I am sure Dave Dugger would take the same precautions.
But how was he supposed to know that you re-did another explosion for inside of his car?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Well, maybe a little 3rd degree burn will help your memory.
Jarod.
Oh, come on, Brynne.
You will be a shot to die for, remember?
Jarod, please!
Why would you put napalm on the radiator?
The bigger the explosion the better the commercial?
You tell me something.
What demographic says that the beer sales are more important than that man's life.
The commercial had been ... lost in account.
What about what Mickey Clausen lost?
What about Dave Dugger?
They lost everything. The only thing you could have lost was just a job.
Just a job?
I work my ... to get what I am.
It is a boys' club.
Through glass ceilings I am not about to lose it all because a funky special effects guy was too soft to do the job we paid him for.
You know something, Brynne?
I don't think your ...agency is going to be giving your ... officer after all this.
Look on the bright side,
maybe you have a career ahead of you.
In stunt work.
Jarod, Jarod.
Jarod.
No, Jarod.
- Did the camera record all that, Mickey?
- We got we want.
That's rep.
I found Timmy.
In Raines archives.
Run them.
Mrs Parker, what are you doing here?
I came by to visit Timmy.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Well, Dr Raines, my husband thinks it's important my visit with hold the children.
Wait here.
Hi.
Timmy, my name is Catherine. How are you doing?
I miss my mum and dad..
I know you do, honey.
Come on, Timmy!
That's it?
Well, there is another one dated on the following day.
No, no. Timmy.
You ... to come in here.!
My god.
What have you done to that little boy?
It was an experiment!
My husband was ... for this!
You don't know your husband as well as you think you do.
I advise you remain quiet about this.
You know what's best for you.
Timmy!
Raines, what you can do with Timmy now?
There is no Timmy any more.
From now on, he is being called…
Angelo.
Is Timmy Angelo?
What, what Raines do to him?
Somehow his emotions,
his ability to relate to the physical world,
were driven invert.
And gave Angelo his unique gift.
But took away his life.
Were you involved in this?
If I had known about this,
I would have done everything in my power to stop it.
And then you were dead.
Just like my mother.
So you actually sold your effects stuff?
Yeah, I know, I know. I don't suppose you will be willing to sell it back.
For the right price.
Then charge him double.
It's ... think he did this to me.
Thanks a lot, Jarod.
Hi, Mickey.
Mickey.
Timmy is gone.
White choose the ... variation,
to answer the blacks, ... in defence.
Very good, Jarod.
Who are you, Mr. lgor?
Sydney, when do I get to meet that boy?
He is gone.
What do you mean ''gone''?
I received a copy of paperwork today.
Dr. Raines released him.
Did he do something wrong?
He wasn't special.
You were special, Timmy.
What?
How are you coming with my ..feeling?
You need to ask?
Why the game, with the creature, why not just tell me?
Sometimes the destination isn't as important as the journey.
Well, where on your journey,
did you find that... ?
In one of your mother's safe deposit boxes.
Like her wedding ring and medical file.
Oh, you will be surprised what one could find in there.
Jarod.
You know the dance, Miss Parker.
You help me with one of my secrets,
I help you with one of yours.
We weren't able to find anything about lgor or Fenigor.
I don't know if he was my mother's ... or betrayer.
Keep searching.
lgor, he holds the secrets to both our pasts.
What makes you so sure?
Call it,
you got feeling.
''FX''
End
Dictation: 笨笨/葱葱
-==YTET PRESENTS==-
伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径