then brought back by bigger idiots.
One...
two...
Professor, my fry-fro is all frizzy.
Well, that's all.
Also,
I'm covered with severe burns.
So? What of it?
Why is... those things?
You mean you don't remember?
Nope, nothing.
It's like when I passed out in college.
Except no one drew magic marker penises
on my forehead.
I suppose it's for the best,
considering the unbearable horrors
you've endured.
Let's never speak of it again.
It all began a few days ago.
We were interstellar fugitives,
on the run from the law.
Fire all weapons
and open a hailing frequency
for my victory yodel.
And so,
as you and Leela kissed good-bye
in a tender display
of tonguesmanship,
we plunged into a massive wormhole,
never to be seen again!
Yeah, we're back.
Sweet coincidence of Port-Au-Prince!
- We're back at Earth!
- Of course!
That was the Panama wormhole,
Earth's central channel
for shipping.
How humorous.
Yes! It's sort
of a comedy central channel.
And we're on it now!
I get it!
We've lost power
to the forward gameboy!
Mario not responding!
Brace for emergency landing!
Roger that!
Activate safety spheres!
Also, mine has air-conditioning.
Yet thanks
to my trusty safety sphere,
I "surblibed"
with only "tribial" brain "dablage."
- And the others?
- Right here behind this horror cloth.
Are they dead?
Much worse.
Move over, God!
Prepare for rebirth!
Wrong switch.
Come on, stem cells,
work your astounding
scientific nonsense!
Fetal stem cells?
Aren't those controversial?
In your time, yes.
But nowadays, shut up!
Besides, these are adult stem cells,
harvested from perfectly
healthy adults
whom I killed for their stem cells.
Hermes Conrad!
I'm dripping with placenta!
Good thing it's casual Friday.
Amy Wong!
Baby soft!
Indeed!
Dr. Zoidberg!
Hermes, my friend!
Let me cut off your umbilical cord.
And the rest!
We're back in business!
Over my dead body.
Never mind.
Bender! Are the stem cells working?
I'm dyin'.
- I need mouth-to-ass resuscitation.
- I'm on it!
It's not working!
I die happy,
knowing you fell for that.
His power supply is shot!
He's flatlining!
Only one thing can keep him alive.
Possibly this thing!
I've never felt so energetic!
That's because the doomsday device
I shoved all up
in you puts out 50 gigawatts!
That's ten times your recommended...
Who are you, my warranty?
That's a good...
For God sakes, Bender!
Keep dancing!
Keep whooping it up!
You must burn off the doomsday energy
as fast as its produced,
or it will build to critical levels!
You don't mean...?
But I do.
If you stop partying
for a single second,
you'll explode
and kill everyone here
in a fireball of melted gears
and splatter bowels!
Sounds like a party, baby!
Speaking of splattered bowels,
can I cook you
a romantic dinner tonight, Leela?
Where's Leela?
Is she okay?
Why hasn't she acknowledged
my dinner offer?
Something's wrong!
She's not responding to my poking stick!
Poke harder, damn it!
I'm poking as hard as I can!
I'm sorry, Fry,
but I'm afraid Leela is in...
An irreversible coma!
My soul mate is gone!
Why should I go on living?
Because the pain slowly fades,
but the love is forever.
But what if I forget
the sweet sound of her voice,
or the moist touch of her eyeball
on my lips?
Are you still hung up
on what's her name? Move on already!
- Maybe you're right.
- Maybe I'm always right!
"Build-a-bot workshop"?
It's time to start living again!
At least it's something
to distract me from Leela.
Now that I like, for some reason.
I like jelly beans!
- Do you?
- I sure do, honey.
Come, now, Fry!
You can't live out
this sick fantasy!
Not without our help.
These security tapes record everything
at planet express,
including the ship,
shower and urinals.
And yet, it still hasn't stopped
the elusive bathroom burglar.
Maybe he's just trying
to feed his family.
Computer, analyze tapes
and extract personality profile of one
Turanga Leela.
Analyzing.
Checking my ebay bid.
Damn it!
Analyses complete.
I was nuzzling that!
Attributes transfer.
Shoe size 12, etcetera.
Brace for emergency landing!
What?
We survived the crash?
Party people in the house say...
This is wonderful!
The last thing I remember,
I was dying in an explosion.
Yet here I am in the flesh,
more alive than ever!
Alive?
- You better tell her, Fry.
- Tell me what?
Anyway, my work is done.
I'm gonna hit the showers.
Nibbler, come give mama a hug!
What the...
Bad Nibbler! Bad Nibbler!
What you doing, pooper-doodle?
It's me, Leela!
Am I really just a robot?
I mean, I have Leela's memories,
her opinion of gazelles,
majestic, her emotions...
confused and hurt.
I swear,
I didn't know this would happen.
The only thing I truly know is,
I love you.
Her. Wait.
Help me out here.
- No, spank you.
- I said do it!
The truth is, Fry,
I still have feelings for you.
But are they really my feelings?
Am I just an automaton?
Or can a machine
of sufficient complexity
legitimately achieve consciousness?
I agree.
I need some time to figure this out.
Until then...
friends?
Listen up, disco dummies!
You just flunked out of Bender's
College of Party Knowledge!
Do the back dance,
do the back dance.
Good news, everyone.
I'm going to make one final attempt
to awaken Leela.
After all, there's always hope.
- Really?
- No, don't get your hopes up.
Frankly, she's just a brainless mound
of scabs and pus.
I didn't need to hear that.
No, and you don't need to see this.
Wake up! Wake up!
Well, that's it.
I'm afraid traditional medicine
has failed.
I refuse to give up!
Wake up, Leela!
I...
love...
- you!
- Fry, stop.
She's gone.
Dr. Zoidberg,
can you note the time
and declare the patient legally dead?
Can I!
That's my specialty!
As you all know,
Leela's living will states that,
in the event of coma,
her body is to be fed
to the wild cyclophage,
a highly endangered creature
that eats only cyclopses.
Yup, that's what
her donor card says.
Good-bye, my love.
The beast approacheth!
To the beat, y'all!
I'm dancin' a jig
with my feet, y'all!
Bender, cut it out!
People are trying to have emotions!
You think I want to party?
I'm sick of partying!
More partying!
- Quiet, Bender!
- Cut it out!
Shut the hell up!
Bender, stop shutting the hell up!
Oh, right.
Leela's back,
as if I care.
All right, Leela!
Thanks.
It's so nice to wake up and see...
How is this possible?
And can you believe
she wore a tank-top to my funeral?
We've got to get out of here!
No, you shut up.
All aboard the party ship.
There's no room for two captains
in this chair!
There would be
if you'd taken a spin class
instead of lounging around
in a coma.
This is crazy.
It's like I'm looking at
an exact robot duplicate of myself.
That is what you're looking at.
How could you do this, Fry?
Coma... sad...
I have to go.
This is just too freaky.
Please don't get upset, Leela.
She's nothing like you.
I have to go.
This is just too freaky.
I need cheering up, Bender.
I don't know.
You want to go out and party tonight?
I hate partying.
If only I didn't have so much crunk
in my badunkadunk.
Why does everything I date run away?
I love Leela.
Always and forever.
And if I loved robot Leela, too,
that's only 'cause she had so much
of real Leela in her.
I thought she loved me, too.
- But obviously, I was wrong, as usual.
- Wrong again.
You were right.
Leela? Leela Leela?
I've been thinking, fry.
If I lost you,
I don't think I could stand it,
either.
I'd probably build
a copy of you, too.
As long as robo Leela's not a jealous
type like me, things will work...
I'll kill you, you slut-clops!
He's mine!
Back off, missy!
Somebody do something!
Here, take this.
A gun? Do-do I really need to...?
Shoot her!
She's the robot!
No. Shoot her!
She's the human!
But how do I know who's the human
and who's the robot?
- We just told you!
- Yeah, you idiot!
Okay, fine.
If you're gonna be like that,
I'm not shooting anyone.
Right between the lungs.
Man, that was close.
I'm a robot, too!
That explains this growth
on your drive shaft.
- But how is this possible?
- Who knows?
I do.
Allow me to explain
what really happened
the day the ship crashed.
I'll protect you, Leela.
My love is stronger than
the vast majority of explosions.
Fry did, in fact, save Leela,
though at a terrible cost
to himself.
I tossed him into the stem cells,
but he just bubbled away,
like phlegm on a hot sidewalk.
Leela was so distraught,
she went all blade runner
and built a duplicate.
Then uploaded Fry's personality
from the urinal surveillance tapes.
I sure love Leela.
Alas, in recreating
Fry's adorable jelly belly,
she had overstuffed him
with copper wadding.
The inevitable static discharge
electrocuted Leela,
and destroyed both
of their short-term memories.
So that's why I'm so amazed
by these things I already knew.
What to do?
I hung up Leela
with the other bone-bags
and went to procure the final ingredient
for my stem cell brew.
Professor, my fry fro is all frizzy.
My God,
I can't believe I'll never see
that particular Fry again.
Where's my shoes?
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize I was already here.
Wait.
What's with all the Leelas?
Trust me, don't ask.
Okay, dork.
I'm gonna hit the urinal,
maybe talk about myself a little bit...
Hang on.
It's time to sort things out.
The truth is,
I love fry.
- That fry.
- And I love Leela.
Any Leela.
We're robots, and we're in love.
Let's ditch these meat jackets.
Hasta la vista, Wiener.
We'll be back.
For our stuff.
Why did their voices change?
That's the one thing
we'll never truly understand.
This is a bit awkward.
Or is it?
I'm not sure...
I lost track
around the second robot.
You know how I feel.
I waited for you for a thousand years.
I can wait a little longer.
What a load of mush!
I've had it!
He's gonna blow!
Party, Bender!
Party for your life!
No chance, high pants.
I'd rather die
and kill all of you than party
for one more millisecond!
The cyclops eater!
Hold on, mack!
It ain't like that!
Geez, what does it take to kill me?
Bender, you blew out
your excess capacity.
You're cured!
Sweet mercy!
My hellish nightmare is over!
I never have to party again!
Well, that's that, then.
We're back, everyone!
Par-tay!