.:: 605 ::.
The Duh-Vinci Code
=:= Bite My Shiny Metal Ass Team =:=
Silence, puny audience!
And welcome to...
Who Dares To Be A Millionaire?
Tremble
before Morbo's mighty likeability,
as I chit-chat
with our first contestant,
Philip J. Fry.
Give him hell, Morbo!
Prepare for pleasantries!
So, Fry, what do you do
for a living?
Me?
- Can I phone a friend?
- Chit-chat achieved!
Are you ready to play?
I didn't come to play.
I came to win.
Now let's play.
For one dollar...
Is it...
B, nail, final answer!
Sweet dodo of Lesotho!
Don't you ever stop to think
before you speak?
I never stop to think about it.
Leave Fry alone.
His intelligence is just a little...
differenty.
You a big dummy!
I'm beginning to think
you guys don't think I'm very smart.
You can barely remember
your own name, Einstein.
Einstein is a hard name to remember.
Smeesh, Professor.
Don't have a shmaneurysm.
Fry's your distant relative.
Not distant enough.
I'll be a monkey's uncle
if I'm this monkey's nephew.
But you're my only family.
Who will hug me
if I achieve something?
Perhaps I've been too harsh.
Come, lad, take my hand
and I'll explain
why I find you so repugnant.
All my life,
I've been inspired by great minds...
Euclid,
Copernicus, Braino...
And my personal role model,
Leonardo da Vinci.
What turned them to stone?
Da Vinci was history's greatest artist
and inventor.
Voilà!
He invented flying machines,
war engines, submarines...
- Nibbler died in the wall.
- That's not Nibbler.
That's my most precious possession.
Leonardo's beard!
I paid a fortune for it
at an auction of historic body parts.
I suppose
if I have an Achilles' heel,
it's because I bought it
at that same auction.
Indeed so.
Most indeededly.
Careful with that, you fool!
But possibly yes.
What is it?
It's da Vinci's
fabled lost invention.
Even the scholars
who wrote of this device
had no idea what it was for.
And now, at last, neither do I!
- Maybe we can figure it out.
- We?
Well, I may not have brain smarts,
but at least I have street smarts.
I was in the hospital two weeks.
- No one visited me.
- Quiet, you!
I'm trying to deduce the function
of da Vinci's lost invention.
Not even a card.
He might have hidden a clue
in one of his other works.
Ergo, I sent Bender out
for a copy of The Last Supper.
I'm back!
Everybody at Kinko's was an idiot,
so I just brought the original.
Jesus Christ...
and his 12 Apostles.
That's odd.
This hand here doesn't belong
to anybody.
And it's pointing a knife
at James the Lesser.
That's the great thing
about that hand.
And what about
these funky table legs?
It's like they're from some other,
funkier painting.
Maybe da Vinci painted
over something else.
It's called a pentimento.
That's true, Dr. Zoidberg.
How did you know that?
My doctorate is in art history.
Let's see
what's under The Last Supper.
Wait a second! I'm not big-boned.
I'm just fat.
My God! Look!
My God! I'm looking!
My God! Saint James was a robot!
My God! Da Vinci left
his legs unpainted as a clue.
My God! This is
the greatest mystery of all time.
We must fly to Rome
and exhume the body of Saint James.
Didn't we used to be
a delivery company?
To the ship.
Leela,
wanna join the mile-deep club?
Sure, why not?
No time!
I've found a clue that could unlock
all the secrets of history.
- Look at these Roman numerals.
- Roman numerals?
- I've got it! We're in Rome.
- Don't be stupid.
It's a long-lost mathematical code.
I'll need to consult
these ancient writings.
Some preposterous hogwash...
About the Fibonacci sequence...
The markings indicate
how many paces we need to take.
One...
Okay, we're there.
Brothers and sisters, let us pry.
It's true!
Saint James really was a robot.
I bet he's up
in Robot Heaven right now.
So he won't miss his eyes.
My God!
Robot Saint James is a zombie.
Nay, I am not Saint James.
Enough of your lies, Saint James.
We saw you in The Last Supper.
The great man Leonardo
built me as an artist's model.
When I took repose in this coffin,
I carefully tossed
the real Saint James
in yonder heap.
I'm sure you have many questions.
Come, there is a chamber
where I used to speak
with Pope John the Patient.
I told him
I'd be back in five minutes.
He'll make a nice heap.
I am Animatronio,
guardian of da Vinci's great secret.
He left my legs visible
in the painting as a clue,
then dispatched me hither
to await his shadow society
of intellectuals.
Hi, Animatronio.
You personally knew da Vinci?
Was he nice?
How did his hair smell?
And on a personal note,
what is the function of this device?
Halt! You know not the function
of the Machina Magnifica?
Then thou art not members
of the shadow society!
- The what, now?
- Not one more word shall I breathe.
Not even about the great fountain
where thou mayest find the...
Wait...
Thou didst not know about the fountain,
didst thou?
Curses!
I must be punished.
Quick, we must find out what he knows,
before he flays himself to death.
- Where is the great fountain?
- What makes it so great?
Why does a robot need a codpiece?
Fie, thou fen-suckled bumbailey!
Thou willst never pry information
from these mechanical lips!
Just tell us, already.
Okay,
the fountain thou seekest is...
And so dies our hope
of solving this mystery.
Come on, gang.
Let's go home.
Wait! Let's not give up so easily.
Animatronio mentioned a fountain.
That's a statue of Neptune,
god of water.
The number of points on his trident
is three, or "trey."
The "U" in his name
is written like "V."
Trey... V...
Trey...
Trevi!
It's the Trevi Fountain!
There can be no question!
- But Professor...?
- There can be no question!
It hasn't changed
in a thousand years.
Okay, everyone, into the fountain.
What are you, senile?
I'm not jumping in there.
Look... coins.
I got 48 cents.
There's one more nickel,
and it's a big one!
Quickly, into the sewer hole.
Why?
What's this dump?
It's the Pantheon!
This place is 3,000 years old.
What could possibly be left
to discover?
Maybe something about ourselves.
Wait! What's under that blanket?
Da Vinci's Vitruvian Man!
It's truly a masterpiece.
Note how the perspective lines
draw the eye right to his dong.
Say, what's this?
Anyone hear something?
It's a coin slot.
Bender, insert that giant nickel.
Sure.
Hush, Bender!
What's your game, Vitruvian Man?
I withdraw the question,
Vitruvian Man.
Da Vinci's lost workshop.
At the risk of sounding stupid,
do these things actually work?
Of course not, stupid!
That flying machine's
as aerodynamic as a sofa!
How could it possibly
get off the ground?
In a way thou shalt ne'er discover!
Hi, Animatronio.
I feign death and stalk thee,
that I might preserve
the greatest of Leonardo's secrets.
All right, buddy,
we want secrets.
And they better be ancient!
Porco metallico!
Ne'er shall I reveal
how these wondrous machines
fit together!
They fit together?
I said no such thing.
And then I died!
You're right, Professor.
This thing doesn't fly.
Don't sit in there, you idiot!
That's dangerous!
No wonder this contraption
isn't aerodynamic!
It's not an aircraft,
it's a spacecraft!
Basta! As I live,
thou shan't discover
the great secret!
Bye, Animatronio!
Why would Leonardo's machine
have brought us here?
I don't know, let's ask this guy.
I am Leonardo.
Welcome to planet Vinci.
That's what I was gonna say!
You're alive? Here?
You've learned my great secret.
I was but a visitor to Earth.
In truth,
I am what you call "a space alien."
It's an honor to meet you, Leonardo.
And might I say,
you were great in Titanic.
The Beach...
That's Leonardo DiCaprio,
you blockhead!
Looks like eating rocks
wasn't as dumb as you said.
So what do people do for fun here?
Do you enjoy partying all night,
with plenty of ale and lusty women?
- I sure do!
- Not us.
We spend our leisure time
in the mathematics museum.
Planet Vinci
is basically
a single colossal university.
- How's your football team?
- Learned.
I'm going to check out
that math lecture.
All this knowledge
is giving me a raging "brainer."
Would you like to hear
the lecture, too, Fry?
No. It would just go in one ear
and our some other hole.
Come. Sit down.
Now, that I can do.
I have a terrible secret to confess,
Mr. DiCaprio.
I'm not very smart.
I appreciate your candor.
I don't even know
what language you're speaking.
I, too, have a confession.
You see, here on planet Vinci,
I am the stupidest person.
What?
Who'd possibly think you're stupid?
I'm Leonardo!
I don't know the mass
of the Higgs boson.
I have to draw in pencil,
'cause I don't know how to use
rendering software.
Stupid Biff!
- Thinks he's so smart.
- He looks stronger than you, too.
I went to Earth
because I could no longer stand
the ridicule.
But being surrounded
by even stupider people
was equally infuriating.
I can see myself
in your shiny button.
Inventing is what makes me happy.
Or did, until I misplaced the plans
for my masterpiece.
You mean these?
The Machina Magnifica!
Infinite joy!
Fry, my friend,
you have given my life meaning again!
That calculus lecture was harder
than I expected.
We had to answer every question
in the form of an opera.
I have a lot of homework for tomorrow,
if I don't want to be...
embarrassed.
Thank you. Thank you.
And if you like that,
you'll love our main event.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Leonardo DiCaprio!
I mean da Vinci!
For centuries, you've ridiculed me.
Especially you, Biff.
Nice hat!
But, at long last,
this invention will show you.
'Twill show you all!
Behold,
my unstoppable doomsday machine!
And I helped! Wait...
You told me it was
an unstoppable ice cream machine.
Ice cream is just a byproduct
of the machine.
Its primary purpose
is to exterminate
everyone who ever
made me feel inferior!
I'm so scared!
Bring it on, dum-dum!
Oh, yeah?
Let's see how hard you're laughing
when my doomsday machine
chops off your face!
Leonardo, stop!
I want in on this!
Are you crazy, Professor?
I hate these nerds!
Just 'cause I'm stupider than them,
they think they're smarter than me.
Kill them all...
starting with the math teacher!
I knew this final invention
would be a humdinger.
We three idiots
will finally have our revenge.
I don't think so.
You two make me ashamed
to call myself an idiot.
There's always going
to be someone smarter than you,
so the only way to be happy
is to make the most of what you've got.
But you've got nothing.
Oh, no?
I've got one single nail,
and another nail to nail it in with,
and I'm gonna stop this infernal
ice cream machine once and for all.
Some doomsday machine!
It barely killed anyone!
Well, take this!
Poor Leonardo da Vinci.
He sure was stupid.
Fry, I admire what you did today
and I'm deeply sorry
for insulting your intellect...
Your tiny, tiny intellect.
There I go again, you dope.
I mean, dummy.
It's okay.
I may not be clever,
but I have a good heart.
That's what my mom used to say.
She was a wise woman.
Also that I'm not much to look at.
A wise woman indeed.