What you see.
The Library.
Open your eyes again.
Where are you now?
My living room, Dr Moon.
When you close your eyes...
I go to the Library.
Go to the Library now.
- Are you back there?
- Yes.
The same part?
No, it's always different.
The Library goes on for ever.
How you do move around?
By wishing.
- What's wrong?
- Something's here!
Someone's got in!
No-one's supposed to get in!
She's never mentioned anyone.
She's always been alone.
Someone's in my library.
No! No, please! That's not allowed!
Listen to me.
The Library is in your mind.
I know it's in my mind.
But something's got inside!
Oh! Hello!
Sorry to burst in on you like this.
OK if we stop here for a bit?
Doctor Who - 4x08
"Silence In The Library"
Transcript by evarin
www.transcripts.subtitle.me.uk
Subtitles by LauCass
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~
Books! People never
really stop loving books.
51st century.
By now you've got holovids,
direct to brain downloads, fiction mist,
but you need the smell.
The smell of books, Donna. Deep breath.
The Library.
So big it doesn't need a name.
Just a great big "the."
It's like a city.
It's a world. Literally a world.
The core of the planet
is the index computer,
biggest hard drive ever.
And up here,
every book ever written.
Whole continents of
Jeffrey Archer, Bridget Jones,
Monty Python's Big Red Book.
Brand new editions,
specially printed.
We're near the equator, so...
this must be Biographies!
I love biographies.
Yeah, very you.
Always a death at the end.
You need a good death.
Without death, there'd only be comedies.
Dying gives us size. Oi!
- Spoilers!
- What?
These books are from your future.
Don't read ahead,
spoil all the surprises.
Like peeking at the end.
Isn't travelling with you
one big spoiler?
I try to keep you away
from major plot developments.
Which, to be honest,
I seem to be very bad at,
cos... you know what?
This is the biggest
library in the universe.
So where is everyone?
It's silent.
The Library?
The planet.
The whole planet.
Maybe it's a Sunday.
No, I never land on Sundays.
Sundays are boring. Well...
Maybe everyone's really,
really quiet.
Yeah, maybe.
But they'd still show up
on the system.
Doctor, why are we here?
Really, why?
Oh, you know, just passing.
No, seriously.
It was all, "Let's hit the beach,"
then suddenly we're in a library.
- Why?
- Now, that's interesting.
- What?
- Scanning for life forms.
If I do a scan looking for
your basic humanoids, you know,
your book readers, few limbs and
a face, apart from us, I get nothing.
Zippo, nada, see?
Nobody home. But if I widen
the parameters to any kind of life...
A million million.
Gives up after that.
But there's nothing here.
There's no-one.
And not a sound.
A million million life forms,
and silence in the Library.
But there's no-one here.
There's just books.
I mean, it's not the books, is it?
I mean, it can't be
the books, can it?
I mean, books can't be alive?
Welcome!
- That came from in there.
- Yeah!
I am Courtesy Node 710/aqua.
Please enjoy the Library and
respect the personal access codes
of all your fellow readers
regardless of species or hygiene taboo.
That face, it looks real.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
But a statue with a real face, though!
- It's a hologram, isn't it?
- No, but really, it's fine.
Additional, There follows a brief
message from the head librarian
for your urgent attention.
It has been edited for tone and content
by a Felman Lux Automated
Decency Filter.
Message follows.
"Run.
"For God's sake, run.
"Nowhere is safe.
"The Library has sealed itself,
we can't... Oh, they're here.
"Arg. Slarg. Snick."
Message ends.
Please switch off your mobile comm
units for the comfort of other readers.
So that's why we're here.
Any other messages, same date stamp?
One additional message.
This message carries a Felman
Lux coherency warning of...
- Yeah, yeah, fine, just play it.
-  5, 0, 11...
Message follows.
"Count the shadows.
"For God's sake, remember...
"if you want to live,
count the shadows."
Message ends.
Donna...
Yeah?
Stay out of the shadows.
Why, what's in the shadows?
So...
We weren't just
in the neighbourhood.
Yeah, I kind of, sort of lied a bit.
I got a message
on the psychic paper.
What do you think, cry for help?
Cry for help, with a kiss?
Oh, we've all done that.
- Who's it from?
- No idea.
- So why did we come here, why did you?
- Donna.
- What's happening?
- Run!
- What, is it locked?
- Jammed! The wood's warped!
Sonic it, use the thingy!
- I can't, it's wood!
- What, it doesn't do wood?!
If I can vibrate the molecules,
fry the bindings,
- I can shatterline the interface.
- Oh, get out of the way!
Oh! Hello!
Sorry to burst in on you like this.
OK if we stop here for a bit?
What is it?
Security camera.
Switched itself off.
They were in my library.
How can they be in my library?
Who were they?
What's that? What's that noise?
What noise?
Nice door skills, Donna.
Well, you know, boyfriends, sometimes
you need the element of surprise.
What was that ?
What was after us?
I mean, did we just run away
from a power cut?
Possibly.
Are we safe here?
Course we're safe.
There's a little shop.
Gotcha!
No, stop it!
No, no!
Ooh, I'm sorry.
I really am, I'm sorry,
I'm so sorry. It's alive.
You said it was a security camera.
It is.
It's an alive one.
Can you hear me?
Are you all right?
- Others are coming.
- Who's coming?
Who are the others?
The Library is breached.
- Others are coming.
- What others?
Others?
What does it mean, "others"?
Excuse me,
what does it mean, "others"?
That's barely more than a speak
your weight machine, it can't help you.
So why's it got a face?
This flesh aspect was donated
by Mark Chambers
on the occasion of his death.
It's a real face?
It has been actualised
individually for you
from the many facial aspects
saved to our extensive flesh banks.
Please enjoy.
It chose me a dead face
it thought I'd like?
That statue's got a real
dead person's face on it!
It's the 51st century.
That's basically
like donating a park bench.
It's donating a face!
No, wait, no!
- Oi! Hands!
- The shadow, look.
What about it?
Count the shadows.
One. There,
I counted it, one shadow.
Yeah...
But what's casting it?
Oh! I'm thick!
Look at me, I'm old and thick!
Head's too full of stuff,
I need a bigger head!
Power must be going.
This place runs on fission cells.
They'll outburn the sun.
- Then why's it dark?
- It's not dark.
That shadow.
It's gone.
We need to get back to the TARDIS.
Why?
Because that shadow hasn't gone.
It's moved.
Reminder,
the Library has been breached,
others are coming.
Reminder,
the Library has been breached,
others are coming.
Reminder,
the Library has been breached...
Hello, sweetie.
- Get out.
- Doctor?
All of you, turn around,
get back in your rocket and fly away.
Tell your grandchildren
you came here and lived,
they won't believe you.
Pop your helmets, everyone.
We've got breathers.
How do you know they're not androids?
Cos I've dated androids.
- They're rubbish.
- Who is this?
You said we were the only expedition,
I paid for exclusives.
I lied, I'm always lying.
Bound to be others.
Miss Evangelista,
I want to see the contracts.
You came through the north door?
Much damage?
Please, just leave. I'm asking you
seriously and properly, just lea...
Did you say expedition?
My expedition, I funded it.
Oh, you're not, are you?
Tell me you're not archaeologists.
Got a problem with archaeologists?
I'm a time traveller.
I point and laugh at archaeologists.
Professor River Song, archaeologist.
River Song? Lovely name.
As you're leaving, you need
to set up a quarantine beacon.
Code-wall the planet,
the whole planet. Nobody comes here,
not ever again. No-one living thing.
Not here, not ever. Stop right there!
What's your name?
Anita.
Anita, stay out of the shadows.
Not a foot, not a finger in the shadows
till you're safely back in your ship.
Stay in the light.
Find a nice, bright spot and just stand.
If you understand me,
look very, very scared.
No, bit more scared than that.
OK, do for now.
You, who are you?
- Dave.
- OK, Dave...
Oh, well Other Dave,
because that's Proper Dave
the pilot, he was the first Dave,
so when we...
Other Dave, the way you came,
does it look the same as before?
Yeah. Oh, it's a bit darker.
How much darker?
Oh, I could see where we came through
just a moment ago. I can't now.
Seal the door. Find another way out.
We're not looking for a way out.
Miss Evangelista?
I'm Mr Lux's personal... everything.
You need to sign these contracts
agreeing that your experiences
inside the Library are...
the intellectual property of
the Felman Lux Corporation.
- Right, give it here.
- Yeah, lovely. Thanks.
My family built this library.
I have rights.
You have a mouth that won't stop.
You think there's danger here?
Something came to this library
and killed everything in it,
killed a whole world.
- Danger? Could be.
- That was 100 years ago.
The Library's been silent for 100 years.
Whatever came here is long dead.
Bet your life?
Always.
What do you doing?
He said seal the door.
Torch! You're taking orders from him?
Spooky, isn't it?
Almost every species in the universe
has an irrational fear of the dark.
But they're wrong.
Cos it's not irrational.
It's Vashta Nerada.
What's Vashta Nerada?
It's what's in the dark.
It's what's always in the dark.
- Lights! You got lights?
- What for?
Form a circle, safe area,
big as you can, lights pointing out.
- Do as he says.
- You're not listening to this man?!
Apparently, I am. Unpack the lights.
Other Dave, make sure the door's secure,
then help Anita.
Mr Lux, put your helmet
back on, block the visor.
Proper Dave, I want you
to access the library database,
see what you can find about what
happened a hundred years ago.
Pretty Boy, you're with me.
Step into my office.
Professor Song,
why am I the only one wearing my helmet?
I don't fancy you.
Probably, I can help you.
Pretty Boy, with me, I said.
- Oh, I'm Pretty Boy?
- Yes.
Ooh, that came out a bit quick!
Pretty?!
Don't let your shadows cross!
Seriously. Don't even let them touch.
- Any of them could be infected.
- How can a shadow be infected?
'Scuse me, can I help?
- No, we're fine.
- I could just...
you know, hold things.
No, really, we're OK.
éOK.
Couldn't she help?
Trust me, I just spent 4 days on
a ship with that woman. She's...
Couldn't tell the difference between
the escape pod and the bathroom.
We had to go back for her.
Twice.
- Thanks.
- For what?
The usual. For coming when I call.
That was you?
You're doing a good job,
like you don't know me.
I'm assuming there's a reason.
- A fairly good one, actually.
- OK, shall we do diaries, then?
Where are we this time?
Going by your face,
I'd say it's early days for you, yeah?
So, erm...
Crash of the Byzantium...
have we done that yet?
Obviously ringing no bells.
Right, Picnic at Asgard.
Have we done Asgard yet?
Obviously not.
Blimey, very early days, then. Hoo!
Life with a time traveller
never knew it could be such hard work.
Look at you!
- You're young.
- I'm really not, you know.
No, but you are.
Your eyes.
You're younger
than I've ever seen you.
You've seen me before, then?
Doctor...
Please tell me you know who I am?
Who are you?
Sorry, that was me. Trying to get
through into the security protocols,
I seem to have set something off.
- What is that, is that an alarm?
- Doctor.
- Doctor, that sounds like...
- It is.
It's a phone!
Dad!
In a minute.
I'm trying to call up the data core,
it's not responding. Just that noise.
- But it's a phone!
- Let me try something.
Dad! The phone,
aren't you going to answer it?
It's not ringing, sweetie.
OK, doesn't like that,
let's try something else.
'OK, here it comes.'
Hello?
Hello. Are you in my television?
Well, no, I'm...
I'm sort of in space.
I was trying to call up
the data core of a triple-grid
security processor.
Would you like to speak to my dad?
Your dad or your mum,
that would be lovely.
I know you! You were in my library.
YOUR library?
The Library's never been
on the television before.
What have you done?
Ah, I... just rerouted the interface...
What happened. Who was that?
Keep working on those lights,
we need those lights!
You heard him, people,
let there be light.
Sorry. Youre not allowed to see
inside the book, its against the rules.
What rules?
Your rules.
What's that?
- I didnt do that, did you do that?
- Not me.
What's CAL?
You all right?
What's that? What's happening?
I don't know.
Oh, thanks for... you know...
offering to help with the lights.
They don't want me.
They think I'm stupid cos I'm pretty.
Course they don't, nobody thinks that.
No, they're right though.
I'm a moron, me.
My dad said I have the IQ of plankton.
And I was pleased.
See, thats funny.
No, I really was pleased.
- Is that funny?
- No, no.
What's causing that?
Is it the little girl?
But who is the little girl?
What's she got to do with this place?
How does the data core work?
What's the principle? What's CAL?
Ask Mr Lux.
CAL, what is it?
Sorry. You didn't sign your
Personal Experience contracts.
Mr Lux, right now,
you're in more danger than you've
ever been in your whole life.
And you're protecting a patent?
I'm protecting my family's pride.
Well, funny thing, Mr Lux. I don't
want to see everyone in this room dead
because some idiot thinks
his pride is more important.
Then why don't you sign his contract?
I didn't either.
I'm getting worse than you.
Ok, ok, ok.
Let's start at the beginning.
What happened here?
On the actual day, a hundred years ago,
what physically happened?
There was a message
from the library. Just one.
The lights are going out.
Then the computer sealed the planet and
there was nothing for a hundred years.
It's taken 3 generations of my family
to decode the seals and get back in.
Excuse me...
Not, just now.
There was one other thing
in the last message...
That's confidential.
I trust this man.
With my life, with everything.
- You've only just met him.
- No, he's only just met me.
This might be important actually...
In a moment!
This is a data extract
that came with the message.
4022 saved. No survivors.
4022, that's the exact number of people
who were in the Library
when the planet was sealed.
But how can 4022 people have
been saved if there were no survivors?
That's what were here to find out.
And so far, what we havent
found, are any bodies.
Everybody, careful. Stay in the light.
Keep saying. I don't see the point!
- Who screamed?
- Miss Evangelista.
Where is she?
Miss Evangelista,
please state your current...
Please state your current...
position.
It's her.
It's Miss Evangelista.
We heard her scream a few seconds ago.
What could do that to a
person in a few seconds?
- It took less than a few seconds.
- What did?
Hello?
Erm, I'm sorry everyone
this isn't going to be pleasant.
She's ghosting.
She's what?
Hello, excuse me?
I'm sorry, hello, excuse me?
That's. That's her.
That's Miss Evangelista!
I don't want to sound horrible,
but couldn't we just. You know?
This is her last moment... no, we cant.
A little respect, thank you.
Sorry, where am I? Excuse me?
But that's Miss Evangelista.
It's a Data Ghost,
she'll be gone in a moment.
Miss Evangelista,
you're fine, just relax.
We'll be with you presently.
What's a Data Ghost?
There's a neural relay
in the communicator.
Let's you send thought mails.
That's it there, those green lights.
Sometimes it can hold an impression
of a living consciousness
for a short time after death.
Like an after image.
My grandfather lasted a day.
Kept talking about his shoelaces.
She's in there!
I can't see, I can't... Where am I?
She's just brain waves now.
The pattern won't hold for long.
She's conscious! She's thinking.
I can't see, I can't...
I don't know what I'm thinking.
She's a footprint on the beach.
And the tides coming in.
Where is that woman?
The nice woman... is she there?
What woman?
She means... I think she means me.
Is she there? The nice woman?
Yes, she's here, hang on.
Go ahead. She can hear you.
Hello? Are you there?
Help her.
- She's dead.
- Yeah. Help her.
Hello? Is that the nice woman?
Yeah. Hello.
Yeah, I'm I'm... I'm here.
You OK?
What I said before...
about being stupid...
don't tell the others,
they'll only laugh.
Course I won't.
Course I won't tell them.
Don't tell the others,
they'll only laugh.
I won't tell them. I said I won't.
Don't tell the others,
they'll only laugh.
I'm not going to tell them.
Don't tell the others...
She's looping now.
The patterns degrading.
I can't think, I... don't know, I...
I...
Ice cream.
- Doe's anybody mind if I.
-  Ice cream.
Ice cream.
Was...
That was horrible.
That was the most horrible
thing I've ever seen.
No. It's just a freak of technology.
But whatever did this to her,
whatever killed her...
I'd like a word with that.
I'll introduce you.
- I'm going to need a packed lunch.
- Hang on.
- What's in that book?
- Spoilers.
Who are you?
- Professor River Song, University of...
- To me.
- Who are you to me?
- Again... spoilers.
Chicken, and a bit of salad.
Knock yourself out.
Right, you lot.
Let's all meet the Vashta Nerada!
Darling, Dr Moon is going now.
But hed like a word with
you alone, is that all right?
- Yes, of course, Dr Moon.
- Thank you.
Now,
listen.
This is important.
There's the realworld, and
there's the world of nightmares.
That's right, Isn't there?
You understand?
Yes, I know, Dr Moon.
What I want you to remember is this...
and I know its hard.
The real world is a lie,
and your nightmares are real.
The Library is real.
There are people trapped in
there, people who need to be saved.
The shadows are moving again.
Those people are depending on you.
Only you can save them.
Only you.
You travel with him, don't you?
The Doctor, you travel with him.
What of it?
Proper Dave, could you move over a bit?
Why?
Just over there by the water cooler.
Thanks.
You know him, don't you?
Oh, God, do I know that man.
We go way back, that man and me.
Just not this far back.
I'm sorry, what?
He hasn't met me yet.
I sent him a message but
it went wrong, it arrived too early.
This is the Doctor in the
days before he knew me.
And he looks at me,
and he looks right through me.
And it shouldn't kill me, but it does.
What are you talking about?
Are you just talking rubbish?
Do you know him or don't you?
- Donna, quiet, I'm working!
- Sorry!
Donna? You're Donna? Donna Noble?
Yeah, why?
I do know the Doctor.
But in the future.
His personal future.
So why don't you know me?
Where am I in the future?
OK! We've got a live one.
That's not darkness down those
tunnels, this is not a shadow.
It's a swarm.
A man-eating swarm.
The piranhas of the air,
the Vashta Nerada.
Literally the shadows
that melt the flesh.
Most planets have them,
but usually in small clusters.
I've never seen an infestation
on this scale, or this aggressive.
What d'you mean, most planets?
Not Earth?
Mmmm, Earth, and a billion other worlds.
Where there's meat,
there's Vashta Nerada.
You can see them sometimes, if you look.
The dust in sunbeams.
If they were on Earth, we'd know.
Nah, normally they live on road kill.
But sometimes people go missing.
Not everyone comes back out of the dark.
Every shadow?
No. But any shadow.
So what do we do?
Daleks: aim for the eyestalk.
Sontarans: back of the neck.
Vashta Nerada: Run! Just run.
Run where?
This is an index point.
There must be an exit teleport.
Don't look at me, I haven't
memorised the schematics!
Doctor,
little shop! They always make you
go through it on the way out
so they can sell you stuff.
You're right! Brilliant!
That's why I like the little shop!
OK, let's move it.
Actually, Proper Dave, could you
stay where you are for a moment?
Why?
I'm sorry. I am so, so sorry.
But you've got two shadows.
It's how they hunt, they latch on
to a food source and keep it fresh.
- What do I do?
- You stay absolutely still.
Like there's a wasp in the room,
a million wasps.
- We're not leaving you, Dave.
- Of course not.
Where's your helmet?
Don't point, tell me.
On the floor, by my bag.
Don't cross his shadow!
Thanks.
Now, the rest of you,
helmets back on and sealed up.
- We'll need everything we've got.
- We haven't any helmets.
- Yeah, we're safe anyway.
- How are we safe?
That was a clever lie to shut you up.
Professor, anything
I can do with the suit?
What good are suits? Miss Evanglista
was wearing one, there was nothing left.
We can increase the mesh-density
dial it up 400%. Make it a tougher meal.
OK.
- 800%! Pass it on.
- Gotcha!
- What's that?
- It's a screwdriver.
- It's sonic.
- Yeah, I know. Snap!
With me, come on!
Are we shopping?
Is it a good time to shop?
No talking, just moving!
Stand up in the middle!
Its a teleport, stand in the middle.
Can't send the others,
TARDIS won't recognise them.
- What you doing?
- You don't have suit, not safe!
You don't have a suit, you're
in just as much danger as I am...
Donna! Let me explain.
- Oh, that's how you do it!
- Doctor!
Where did it go?
It's just gone. I looked round,
one shadow. See.
Does that mean we can leave?
I don't know why we're still here.
We can leave him, can't we?
- I mean, no offence.
- Shut up, Mr Lux.
Did you feel anything?
Like an energy transfer?
No, no, but, look, it's gone.
Stop there, stop moving.
They're never just gone.
And they never give up.
Well, this ones benign.
Hey, who turned out the lights?
No-one, they're fine.
No, seriously, turn them back on!
They are on.
I can't see a ruddy thing.
Dave, turn round.
What's going on? Why can't I see?
Is the power gone, are we safe here?
Dave, I want you to stay still,
absolutely still.
Dave, Dave? Dave,
can you hear me, are you all right?
Talk to me, Dave.
I'm fine, I'm OK, I'm... fine.
I want you to stay still,
absolutely still.
I'm fine, I'm OK, I'm... fine.
I can't. Why can't I? I...
I can't. Why can't I?
I...
He's gone. He's ghosting.
Then why is he still standing?
Who turned out the lights?
Doctor, don't!
Dave, can you hear me?
Who turned out the lights?
- Who turned out the lights?
- Scuse me!
Back from it, get back, right back!
- Doesn't move very fast does it?
- It's a swarm in a suit.
But it's learning.
What do we do? Where do we go?
See that wall behind you?
DUCK!
Squareness gun!
Everybody out. Go, go, go!
Move it, move, move!
- You said not every shadow.
- But any shadow!
Who turned out the lights?
Run!
Sweetie, dinner's ready.
Donna Noble has been saved.
Sweetie?
Trying to boost the power.
Light doesn't stop them,
but it slows them down.
So, what's the plan? Do we have a plan?
Your screwdriver...
- Looks exactly like mine.
- Yeah. You gave it to me.
I don't give my screwdriver to anyone.
I'm not anyone.
- Who are you?
- What's the plan?
I teleported Donna back to the TARDIS.
If we don't get back in five hours,
emergency program one activates.
Take her home.
- We need to get a shift on.
- She's not there.
I should've received a signal,
console signals me if
there's a teleport breach.
Maybe the co-ordinates slipped.
The equipment here's aged.
Donna Noble.
There's a Donna Noble in this library,
do you have the software to locate her?
Donna Noble has left the Library.
- Donna Noble has been saved.
- Donna!
Donna Noble has left the Library.
Donna Noble has been saved.
How can it be Donna?
How's that possible?
Donna Noble has left the Library.
- Donna Noble has been saved.
- Oh, Donna!
Donna Noble...
- Who turned out the lights?
- Doctor!
Donna Noble has been saved.
Who turned out the lights?
Donna Noble has left the Library.
Doctor, we've got to go, now!
Who turned out the lights?
Donna Noble has left the Library.
- Donna Noble has been saved.
- Who turned out the lights?
Donna Noble has left the Library.
- Donna Noble has been saved.
- Who turned out the lights?
Donna Noble has left the Library.
- Donna Noble has been saved.
- Who turned out the lights?
Donna Noble has left the Library.
- Doctor, what are we going to do?
- Who turned out the lights?
Donna Noble has left the Library.
Donna Noble has been saved.
I'd trust that man to the end of
the universe. Actually, we've been.
Who are you?
And then you forgot.
You just killed someone I like
and it's not a safe place to stand.
Planet's going to crack like an egg.
Daddy, no, Daddy!
- I hate you sometimes!
- I know!
Don't play games with me.
We need to stop this,
we've got to save CAL.
What is it, what is CAL?
- Spoilers.
No, don't tell, you mustn't tell!
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~