Ancient Rome.
Well, not to them, obviously.
To all intents and purposes,
right now, this is Brand New Rome.
Oh, my God, it's...
It's so Roman!
This is fantastic.
I'm here,
in Rome,
Donna Noble, in Rome.
This isjust weird.
- I mean, everyone here's dead
- Well,
don't tell THEM that.
Hold on a minute,
that sign over there's in English.
Are you having me on, are we in Epcot?
No,no no, it's TARDIS
translation circuits,
it looks like English
Speech as well,
- you're talking Latin right now
- Seriously?
- Ijust said 'seriously'in Latin.
- Yeah.
What if I said something in actual Latin?
Like, 'Veni, vidi, vici'? My dad said
that coming back from the football.
Ifl said, 'Veni, vidi, vici' to that
lot, what would it sound like?
I'm not sure.You do think of
difficult questions.
I'm gonna try it.
Afternoon, sweetheart,
what can I get you, my love?
Erm... Veni, vidi, vici.
Ah? Sorry?
Me-no-speak-Celtic.
No-can-do, missy.
Yeah.
- How's he mean, Celtic?
- Welsh
You sound Welsh.
There we are, learnt something, hm?
Don't our clothes look a bit odd?
Naaah. Ancient Rome, anything goes.
It's like Soho, but bigger.
- Have you been here before, then?
- Mm.
Ages ago.
And that fire had nothing to do with me.
Well... a bit. But I haven't got
the chance to look around properly.
The Colosseum. The Pantheon.
The Circus Maximus...
You'd expect them to be looming by now.
Where is everything?
Try this one.
I'm not expert,
but there's SEVEN hills of Rome,
aren't there?
How come they've only got one?
Here we go again!
Wait a minute...
One mountain.
With smoke.
- Which makes this...
- Pompeii.
We're in Pompeii
And it's volcano day.
Doctor Who 4x02 Fires of Pompeii
Transcript : Evarin
Subtitles by www.doctorwho.scifi-guide.net
English subs: luxbella, Sanju
I beg audience with the High
Priestess ofthe Sibylline.
The High Priestess cannot be seen.
- What would you tell her, sister?
- It has come.
As foretold in the prophecy.
The box.
The blue box.
You're kidding.
- You're not telling me the TARDIS has gone?
- OK.
Where is it, then?
You told me not to tell you.
-0i. Don't get clever in Latin.
Hold on.
'Scuse me, 'scuse me,
there was a box, big blue box,
big blue wooden box,
over there,
where is it gonne?
- I sold it, didn't I?
- But...
- It wasn't yours to sell!
- It was on my patch, weren't it?
I got 15 sesterce for it, lovely jubbly.
- Who did you sell it to?
- Old Caecilius. Look,
if you want to argue, why don't
you take it out with him?
He's on Foss Street,
big villa, can't miss it.
Thanks.
What did he buy a big
blue wooden box for?
Modern art!
Out ofthe way, thafs it.
Oh, Rhombus, I'm a little bit peckish,
get me some ants in honey, good lad.
Ooh, maybe a dormouse?
What d'you think?
You call it modern art.
I call it a blooming great waste of space.
But we're going up in the world, my love.
Lucius Dextrus himself is coming here.
This afternoon.
What with that, and our Evelina
about to be elevated...
Oh, don't go on about it, Dad!
If we'd moved to Rome, as I said,
she could have been a Vestal Virgin.
- Someone mention Vestal Virgins?
- Quintus, don't be so rude.
You apologise to the household gods!
- Get off.
- Apologise, right now!
The gods are always watching.
Positions!
There, now you've made the Heavens angry.
Just say sorry.
I tell you, Caecilius,
that boy will come to no good.
Sorry, household gods.
So where were you last night?
Down the thermopolium, I bet?
Cavorting with Etruscans and Christians and all sorts.
How's your head, sunshine?
How's your head?
All right, Dad, give us a break!
You want to smarten yourself up,
Quintus.
Before Lucius Dextrus gets here.
Look at your sister,
she's giving us... status.
Oh, yeah,
cos it's all about Evelina.
She has the gift.
Be proud of your sister, for once.
- Have you been consuming?
- Not this morning.
Well, come on, sweetheart.
Practise!
Oh, it's hot today,
the hypocaust is on full blast.
The Mountain God must be happy.
Breathe deeply.
Remember what the Sisterhood said.
- It hurts.
- Oh, my love, is it too hot?
Sometimes, in the smoke...
- I see the most terrible things.
- Like what?
A face.
A face of stone.
It'll make sense.
One day.
Sister Spurrina promised.
The veil will be parted,
and you'll be a seer.
Who are you?
Ah, I've got it!
Foss Street, this way!
No, but I found this big sort
of amphitheatre thing,
we could gather
everyone together there,
then we could ring a big bell...
- They got bells yet?
- What d'you want a bell for?
To warn everyone.
Start the evacuation.
What time does Vesuvius erupt?
It's 79AD, 23rd of August,
which makes Volcano Day... tomorrow.
Plenty of time
to get everyone out, easy.
Yeah,
except we're not going to.
But that's what you do,
Doctor, you save people!
Not this time.
Pompeii is a fixed point in history.
What happens, happens.
There is no stopping it.
- Says who?
- Says me.
What, and you're in charge?
TARDIS, Time Lord, yeah!
Donna, Human, no!
I don't need your permission!
I'm telling myself!
You stand here announcing the end,
they'll just think you're a mad old soothsayer!
Now, come on. TARDIS. We are getting out of here.
I might just have something
to say about that, spaceman!
Oh, I bet you will!
The tall one.
He calls us mad.
Then he is a stranger to Pompeii.
Soon, he will learn.
We have found it, Sister Spurrina.
In the Thirteenth Book
of the Sibylline Oracles.
The blue box.
A temple made of wood.
And yet, the Sibyl foretold that the box
would appear at the time of storms
and fire and betrayal.
Sisters!
Reverend Mother, you should sleep.
The Sibylline Oracles are wrong.
But we have venerated her
words for generations.
This is a new age.
Heed my words.
I predict a future
of prosperity and might.
An endless Empire of Pompeii,
reaching out from this city
to topple Rome itself,
and encompass the whole wide world.
If the disciples of the blue box
defy this prophecy,
their blood will run across
the Temple floor.
The gods approve.
Positions!
There you go.
Thank you, kind sir.
I'm afraid business is closed for the day.
I'm expecting a visitor.
That's me.
I'm a visitor. Hello.
- Who are you?
- I am...
Spartacus.
And so am I.
Mr and Mrs Spartacus?
- 0h, no, we're not married.
- We're not together.
0h, brother and sister?
Yes, ofcourse!
You look very much alike.
- Really?
I'm sorry,
but I'm not open for trading.
- And that trade would be...?
- Marble.
Lobus Caecilius.
Mining,
polishing and design thereof.
- If you want marble, I'm your man.
- That's good, cos...
I'm the marble inspector.
By the gods of Commerce,
an inspection!
I'm sorry, sir.
I do apologise for my son.
This is my good wife, Metella.
- I confess, we're not prepared...
- Don't worry.
I'm sure you've nothing to hide.
Although, frankly, THAT object...
- looks rather like wood to me.
- I told you to get rid of it.
I only bought it today!
Ah, well... Caveat emptor.
Oh, you're Celtic. There's lovely.
I'm sure it's fine, but I might have to take
it off your hands, for a proper inspection.
While we're here,
would you recommend a holiday, Spartacus?
Don't know what you mean, Spartacus.
Well, this lovely family.
Mother and father and son.
Don't you think
they should get out of town?
- Why should we do that?
- Well, the volcano, for start.
- What?
- The volcano.
- The WHAT-ano?
- That great big volcano right on your doorstep...
Oh, Spartacus, for shame, we haven't
even greeted the household gods yet.
They don't know what it is.
Vesuvius is just a mountain to them,
the top hasn't blown off yet.
The Romans haven't even got a word for volcano.
Not until tomorrow.
Oh, great, they can learn a new word.
- As they die.
- Donna, stop it.
Whatever sort of kids
you've been flying round with,
don't tell me to shut up.
That boy, how old is he? Sixteen?
- And tomorrow, he burns to death.
- And that's my fault?
Right now, yes.
Announcing Lucius Petrus Dextrus,
Chief Augur of the City Government.
Lucius. My pleasure, as always.
Quintus, stand up!
A rare and great honour, sir,
for you to come to my house...
The birds are flying north,
and the wind is in the west.
Quite. Absolutely.
That's good, is it?
- Only the grain of wheat knows where it will grow.
- There now, Metella.
- Have you ever heard SUCH wisdom?
- Never.
It's an honour.
Pardon me, sir, I have guests,
this is Spartacus and... Spartacus.
A name is but a cloud upon a summer wind.
But the wind is felt most keenly in the dark.
But what is the dark,
- other than an omen ofthe sun?
- I concede that every sun must set...
- And yet the son of the father must also rise.
- Damn.
Very clever, sir.
Evidently, a man of learning.
Oh, yes. But don't mind me, don't want to disturb the status quo.
He's Celtic.
- We'll be off in a minute.
- I'm not going.
It's ready, sir.
- You've got to.
- Well, I'm not.
The moment of revelation.
And here it is!
Exactly as you've specified.
- It pleases you, sir?
- As the rain pleases the soil.
Oh, now that's... different.
Who designed that, then?
My Lord Lucius was very specific.
- Where did you get the pattern?
- On the rain and mist and wind.
- But that looks like a circuit.
- Made of stone.
D'you mean you just dreamt that thing up?
That is my job.
As City Augur.
What's that, then, like the mayor?
Oh! You must excuse my friend.
She's from Barcelona.
But this is an age of superstition,
of OFFICIAL superstition.
The Augur is paid by the city
to tell the future.
"The wind will blow from the west",
that's their Ten O'Clock News.
They're laughing at us.
Those two use words like tricksters,
they're mocking us.
No, no, no.
I meant no offence.
I'm sorry, my daughter's
been consuming the vapours.
By the gods, mother,
what have you been doing?
- Not now, Quintus.
- But she's sick, just look at her!
I gather I have a rival
in this household.
Another with the gift.
Oh, she's been promised to
the Sibylline Sisterhood.
They say she has remarkable visions.
The prophecies of women
are limited and dull,
only the menfolk have the capacity
for true perception.
I'll tell you where the wind's blowing right now, mate.
The Mountain God marks your words.
I'd be careful, if I were you.
- Consuming the vapours, you said?
- They give me strength.
- It doesn't look like it to me.
- Is that your opinion...
- as a doctor?
- I beg your pardon?
Doctor, that's your name.
- How did you know that?
- And YOU...
You call yourself Noble.
Now then, Evelina, don't be rude.
No, no, no, no, let her talk.
You both come from so far away.
The female soothsayer is inclined
to invent all sorts of vagaries.
0h, not this time, Lucius.
No, I reckon
you've been out-soothsayed.
Is that so...
- man from Gallifrey?
- What?
The strangest of images...
Your home is lost in fire, is it not?
Doctor, what are they doing?
- And you, daughter of... London.
- How does he know that?
This is the gift of Pompeii.
Every single oracle tells the truth.
- That's impossible.
- Doctor...
she is returning.
Who is? Who's she?
And you, daughter of London...
there is something on your back.
What's that mean?
Even the word 'doctor' is false.
Your real name is hidden.
It burns in the stars, in the Cascade of Medusa herself.
You are a Lord, sir.
A Lord of Time.
Evelina!
She didn't mean to be rude,
she's ever such a good girl.
But when the gods speak through her...
- What's wrong with her arm?
- An irritation of the skin.
She never complains, bless her.
We bathe it in olive oil every night.
What is it?
Evelina said you'd come from far away.
Please, have you ever seen anything like it?
It's stone.
- Different sort of hypocaust.
- Oh, yes.
We're very advanced in Pompeii.
In Rome, they're still using
the old wood-burning furnaces.
But we've got hot springs, leading from Vesuvius itself.
- Who thought of that?
- The soothsayers.
After the great earthquake,
17 years ago.
An awful lot of damage.
But we rebuilt.
Didn't you think of moving away?
No, then again, San Francisco...
That's a little restaurant in...
Naples, isn't it?
- What's that noise?
- Don't know.
Happens all the time.
They say the gods of the Underworld
are stirring.
But after the earthquake,
let me guess...
- is that when the soothsayers started making sense?
- Oh, yes, very much so.
I mean, they'd always been,
shall we say, imprecise?
But then the soothsayers, the augurs,
the haruspex, all of them,
they saw the truth,
again and again.
It's quite amazing.
They predict crops and rainfall with absolute precision.
Have they said anything about tomorrow?
No.
Why, should they?
Why d'you ask?
No, no, no reason.
Just asking.
But the soothsayers,
they all consume the vapours, yeah?
That's how they see.
Ipso facto...
Look you. ..
- They're all consuming this.
- Dust?
Tiny particles of rock.
They're breathing in Vesuvius.
Quintus, me old son.
This Lucius Petrus Dextrus,
where does he live?
It's nothing to do with me.
Let me try again.
This Lucius Petrus Dextrus...
Where does he live?
Don't tell my dad.
Only if you don't tell mine.
Pass me that torch.
The liar!
He told my father
it was the only one.
Well, plenty of marble
merchants in this town.
Tell them all the same,
get all the components from different places,
so no-one can see what it is.
- Which is what?
- The future.
Doctor, we are building the future.
As dictated by the gods.
You're not supposed to laugh.
Thanks for that.
What d'you think?
The Goddess Venus.
That's sacrilege.
Nice to see you laugh, though.
What d'you do in old Pompeii,
then, girls of your age?
You got... mates?
D'you go hanging about round the shops?
TK Maximus?
I am promised to
the Sisterhood for life.
- D'you get any choice in that?
- It's not my decision.
The Sisters chose for me.
I have the gift of sight.
Then...
- What can you see happening tomorrow?
- Is tomorrow special?
You tell me.
What do you see?
The sun will rise. The sun will set.
Nothing special at all.
Look,
don't tell the Doctor
I said anything cos he'll kill me,
but I've got a prophecy too.
Evelina, I'm sorry,
but you've got to hear me out.
- Sisters!
- Evelina, can you hear me?
Listen...
There is only one prophecy.
But everything I'm about to say to you is true. I swear.
just listen to me.
Tomorrow,
that mountain is gonna explode.
Evelina, please listen.
The air is gonna fill with ash and rocks,
tons and tons of it,
and this whole town is gonna get buried.
That's not true.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
- But everyone's going to die.
- A new prophecy!
Impossible.
There is only one.
Even if you don't believe me, tell your family to get out of town.
Just for one day, just for tomorrow.
But you've got to get out.
- You've got to leave Pompeii!
- This is false prophecy.
The noblewoman.
She spoke of a new prophecy,
the fall of Pompeii.
Pompeii will last forever.
- Then what must we do?
- The False Prophet must die.
Sacrifice her!
Put this one... there.
This one...
there.
Er, keep that one upside down,
what have you got?
- Enlighten me.
- What, the soothsayer doesn't know?
A seed may float on the breeze
in any direction.
Yeah, I knew you would say that.
- But it's an energy converter.
- An energy converter of what?
I don't know.
Isn't that brilliant? I love not knowing. Keeps me on my toes.
It must be awful being a prophet,
waking up every morning,
"Is it raining? Yes, I said so."
Takes all the fun out of life.
But who designed this, Lucius, hm?
- Who gave you these instructions?
- I think you've babbled enough.
Lucius, tell me, honestly,
I'm on your side.
- I can help.
- You insult the gods.
There can be only one sentence.
At arms!
Oh, morituri te salutant.
Celtic prayers won't help you now.
But, sir, he made me do it.
- Mr Dextrus, please, don't.
- Come on now, Quintus.
Dignity in death.
I respect your victory, Lucius.
Shake on it?
Come on.
Dying man's wish?
- But he's...
- Show me.
The work of the gods.
He's stone!
Armless enough, though.
Whoops! Quintus!
- Run!
- The carvings!
Run!
My carvings!
The work is unbroken.
Oh, Lord of the Mountain,
I beseech you!
This man...
would prevent the rise of Pompeii.
Lord, I beg of you, show yourself.
Show yourself!
No sign of them.
Nice little bit of allons-y.
I think we're all right.
But his arm, Doctor.
Is that happening to Evelina?
What was that?
The mountain?
No, it's closer.
- Footsteps...
- It can't be.
- Footsteps underground.
- What is it?
What IS it?
What is it?
What's that noise?
Doesn't sound like Vesuvius!
Caecilius, all of you! Get out!
- Doctor! What is it?
- I think we're being followed.
Just get out!
The gods are with us.
Water! We need water!
Quintus, all of you, get water!
Donna!
Blest are we to see the gods.
Talk to me, that's all I want!
Talk to me, just tell me you are.
Don't hurt these people!
I'm the Doctor,
just tell me who you are.
Doctor!
What was it?
Carapace of stone,
held together by internal magma,
not too difficult to stop.
But I reckon that's just the foot soldier.
Doctor, or whatever your name is,
you bring bad luck on this house.
I thought your son was brilliant,
aren't you going to thank him?
Still...
If there ARE aliens at work in Pompeii,
it's a good thing we stayed.
Donna!
Donna?
You have got to be kidding me.
The False Prophet
will surrender both her blood
- and her breath.
- I'll surrender you in a minute.
Don't you dare!
- You will be silent.
- Listen, sister.
You might have eyes
on the back of your hands,
but they'll be in the back of your head
when I've finished with you!
LET me GO!
This prattling voice will cease forever!
Oh, that'll be the day.
No man is allowed
to enter the Temple of Sibyl.
Well, that's all right, just us girls.
Do you know, I met the Sibyl once,
hell of a woman.
Blimey, she could dance the Tarantella!
Nice teeth.
Truth be told, I think
she had a bit of a thing for me.
I said it would never last,
she said, "I know".
Well, she would.
- You OK there?
- Oh, never better.
- I like the toga.
- Thank you.
- And the ropes?
- Yeah, not so much.
What magic is this?
Let me tell you about the Sibyl,
the founder of this religion.
She would be ashamed of you.
All her wisdom and insight gone sour.
Is that how you spread the word?
On the blade of a knife?
Yes, a knife that now welcomes you.
Show me this man!
High Priestess,
the stranger would defile us.
Let me see.
This one is different.
He carries starlight in his wake.
Oh, very perceptive.
Where do these words of wisdom come from?
- The gods whisper to me.
- They've done far more than that.
Might I beg audience?
Look upon the High Priestess?
Oh, my God.
- What's happened to YOU?
- The heavens have blessed me.
If I might...
- Does it hurt?
- It is necessary.
- Who told you that?
- The voices.
Is that what's gonna happen to Evelina?
Is this what's gonna happen to all of you?
The blessings are manifold.
- They're stone.
- Exactly.
The people of Pompeii are turning to stone BEFORE the volcano erupts.
- But why?
- This word, this image in your mind.
This... volcano...
What is that?
More to the point,
why don't you know about it?
- Who are you?
- High Priestess ofthe Sibylline.
No, no, no, no, no,
I'm talking to the creature inside you.
The thing seeding itself
into a human body,
in the dust, in the lungs,
taking over the flesh and turning it into...
- What?
- Your knowledge...
is impossible.
Oh, but you can read my mind,
you know it's not.
I demand you tell me who you are!
We... are... awakening.
The voice of the gods!
Words of wisdom, words of power.
Words of wisdom, words of power...
Name yourself! Planet of origin.
Galactic coordinates.
Designation according to the ratification of the Shadow Proclamation.
We...
... are... rising.
Tell... me... your name!
Pyrovile.
Pyrovile, Pyrovile, Pyrovile...
- What's a Pyrovile?
- That, growing inside HER.
- She's the halfway stage.
- And that turns into...
That thing in the villa was an adult Pyrovile.
And the breath of a Pyrovile will incinerate YOU, Doctor.
I warn you, I'm armed!
Donna, get that grille open.
- What for?
- Just...
What are the Pyrovile doing here?
We fell from the heavens.
We fell so far and so fast,
we were rendered into dust.
Right, creatures of stone,
shattered on impact.
When was that, 17 years ago?
We have slept beneath
for thousands of years.
OK, so 17 years ago woke you up,
and now you're using human bodies
to reconstitute yourselves,
- but why the psychic powers?
- We opened their minds and found such gifts.
OK, so you force yourself inside a human brain,
use the latent psychic talent to bond,
I get that.
But seeing the future, that is way beyond psychic,
you can see through time.
Where does the gift of prophecy come from?
Got it!
- Now get down!
- What, down there?
Yes, down there.
Why can't they predict a volcano?
Why is it being hidden?
Sisters, I see into his mind.
The weapon is harmless!
Yeah, but it's gotta sting.
Get down there!
You fought her off with a water pistol.
I bloody love you!
This way!
- Where are we going now?
- Into the volcano.
- No way.
- Yes way.
Appian way.
The stranger would threaten our great endeavour.
The time has come.
The prophecy must ADVANCE!
The prophecy must advance.
Thy will be done.
- Summon the Cult of Vulcan.
- Yes, sir.
We must go to the mountain.
Vesuvius awaits.
Sunrise, my love.
A new day.
Even the longest night must end.
The mountain's worse than ever.
We killed a messenger of the gods
in our own house.
Sweetheart, can you see?
Tell us.
What's going to happen?
Just leave her alone.
- I can see...
- What is it?
A choice.
Someone must make a choice.
The most terrible choice.
But if it's aliens setting off the volcano,
doesn't that make it all right,
for you to stop it?
Still part of history.
But I'm history to you.
You saved me, in 2008, you saved us all. Why's that different?
Some things are fixed, some things are in flux.
- Pompeii is fixed.
- How do you know which is which?
Because that's how I see the universe.
Every waking second,
I can see what is, what was,
what could be, what must not.
That's the burden of the Time Lord, Donna.
And I'm the only one left.
- How many people died?
- Stop it.
Doctor, how many people died?
20,000.
Is that what you can see, Doctor?
All 20,000?
And you think that's all right, do you?
They know we're here.
Come on!
Almighty Vesuvius,
accept these offerings, in Vulcan's design,
and show unto us, I beseech you, the gods of the Underworld.
It's the heart of Vesuvius.
We're right inside the mountain.
There's tons of them.
What's that thing?
Oh, hurry up and think of something,
Rocky fall's on its way.
That's how they arrived.
Or what's left of it. Escape pod?
Prison ship?
Gene bank?
But why do they need a volcano?
Maybe...
it erupts, and they launch themselves back into space or something.
Oh, it's worse than that.
How could it be worse?
Doctor, it's getting closer.
Heathens!
Defile us!
They would desecrate your temple, My Lord gods!
Come on.
- We can't go in!
- Well, we can't go back.
Crush them!
Burn them!
There is nowhere to run, Doctor, and daughter of London.
Now then, Lucius, My Lords Pyrovillian,
don't get yourselves in a lava.
- In a lava?
- No?
No. No. But if I might beg the wisdom of the gods,
before we perish,
once this new race of creatures is complete,
then what?
My masters will follow the example of Rome itself.
An almighty empire, bestriding the whole of civilisation.
But if you've crashed,
and you've got all this technology,
why don't you just go home?
The Heaven of Pyrovillia is gone.
What do you mean, "gone"?
Where's it gone?
It was taken.
Pyrovillia is lost.
But there is heat enough in this world for a new species to rise.
Yeah, I should warn you, it's 70% water out there.
Water can boil.
And everything will burn, Doctor.
Then the whole planet is at stake.
Thank you.
That's all I needed to know.
Donna!
You have them, My Lords!
Could we be any more trapped?
Little bit hot.
See? The energy converter takes the lava,
uses the power to create a fusion matrix,
which welds Pyrovile to human.
It's complete, they can convert millions.
Can't you change it?
With these controls?
Course I can, but don't you see?
That's why the soothsayers can't see the volcano.
There IS no volcano.
Vesuvius is never going to erupt.
The Pyrovile are stealing all its power,
they'll use it to take over the world.
But... you can change it back?
I can invert the system, set off the volcano, and blow them up, yes.
But that's the choice, Donna.
It's Pompeii or the world.
Oh, my God.
If Pompeii is destroyed then it's notjust history.
It's me.
I make it happen.
But the Pyrovile are rocks, maybe they can't be blown up.
Vesuvius explodes with the force of 24 nuclear bombs.
Nothing can survive it.
Certainly not us.
Never mind us.
Push this lever and it's over.
20,000 people.
Nooooooo!
A new prophecy.
The future is changing.
The sky is FALLING!
Death. Only death!
It WAS an escape pod.
Out! Out, everybody out!
Quickly!
You lied to us!
And yet, this was meant to be.
Don't!
Don't go to the beach!
Don't go to the beach, go to the hills!
Listen to me!
Don't go to the beach, it's not SAFE!
Listen to me...!
Come here.
Give him to me!
Come on.
Yeah! God save us, Doctor!
No!
Don't say you can't!
DOCTOR!
You can't just LEAVE them!
Don't you think I've done enough?
History's back in place.
Everyone dies.
You've got to go back.
Doctor, I'm telling you, take this thing BACK!
It's not fair.
No, it's not.
But your own planet.
It burned.
That's just it. Don't you see, Donna?
Can't you understand? If I could go back and save them then I would,
but I can't.
I can never go back, I can't.
I just can't, I can't.
Just someone.
Please.
Not the whole town.
Just save someone.
Come with me.
It's never forgotten, Caecilius.
Oh, time will pass, men will move on, and stories will fade.
But one day,
Pompeii will be found, again.
In thousands of years.
And everyone will remember you.
What about you, Evelina?
Can you see anything?
The visions have gone.
The explosion was so powerful
it cracked open a rift in time.
Just for a second. That's what
gave you the gift of prophecy.
It echoed back into the Pyrovillian alternative.
But not any more.
You're free.
But tell me,
who are you, Doctor?
With your words, and your temple containing such size within?
Oh, I was never here.
Don't tell anyone.
The great god Vulcan must be enraged!
It's so volcanic.
It's like some sort of...
volcano.
All those people.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You were right.
Sometimes I need someone.
Welcome aboard.
Yeah.
Metella, my love,
have you seen that clasp?
The beetle one.
- The Egyptians do love a scarab.
- Here we are, I was giving it a polish.
Now calm down.
If I get that contract, for the marble granaries of Alexandria,
we'll be rich, you'll see...
Hold on there, Evelina.
You are not going out wearing that!
Don't start, Dad,
it's what all the girls in Rome are wearing.
I'll see you later.
Are you seeing that boy again?
Oh, look at Quintus.
My son, the doctor.
Mum, I've told you,
I'm not a doctor, not yet.
I'm just a student ofthe physical sciences.
Well, that's a doctor to me.
Give thanks to the household gods before you go.
There's a good boy.
Come here, let me fix it.
You've got that folded all wrong...
Thank you, household gods.
Thank you for everything.
Now then, Doctor Noble, Mrs Noble, come with me.
Oh, no, no, we're not married.
- So not married.
- Never.
Here at Ood Operations, we like to think ofthe Ood as our trusted friends...
Your unwanted guests.
- Because at heart, what is an Ood...
- I'm on YOUR side!
... but a reflection of us?
It's a revolution.
- If your Ood is happy...
- The circle must be broken.
What is it? What is the circle?
Then you'll be happy, too.
Shoot!
Doctor, Donna, friends!