- I said, no.
- A sapphire waterfall!
It's a waterfall, made of sapphires!
This enormous jewel,
size of a glacier,
reaches the Cliffs of Oblivion, then
shatters into sapphires at the edge,
they fall 100,000 feet
into a crystal ravine.
- I bet you say that to all the girls.
- Oh, come on, they're boarding now.
It's no fun on my own.
Four hours, that's all it takes.
No, that's four hours there and four
hours back, that's like a school trip.
- I'd rather go sunbathing!
- You be careful.
That's X-tonic sunlight.
Oh, I'm safe. It says in the brochure,
this glass is 15-feet thick.
All right, I give up.
Back for dinner, we'll try that
antigravity restaurant. With bibs.
That's a date.
Well, not a date.
Oh, you know what I mean.
Oh, get off!
- See you later.
- Oy!
- And you be careful, all right?
- Naaah.
Taking a big space truck
with bunch of strangers across
diamond planet called Midnight?
What could possibly go wrong?
Doctor Who - 4x10
"Midnight"
Transcript by evarin
www.transcripts.subtitle.me.uk
Subtitles by LauCass
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~
Complimentary juicepack
and complimentary...
Just the headphones, please.
There you go.
That's the headphones
for Channels 1 to 36,
modem link for 3D vidgames,
complimentary earplugs,
complimentary slippers,
complimentary juicepack,
and complimentary peanuts.
I must warn you some
products may contain nuts.
That'll be the peanuts.
- Enjoy your trip.
- Oh, I can't wait! Allons-y!
- I'm sorry?
- It's French, for let's go!
Fascinating.
- Headphones for channels 1-36...
- No thank you! Not for us!
- Earplugs, please.
- There you go.
They call it a sapphire waterfall,
but it's no such thing,
sapphire's an aluminium oxide,
but the glacier is just a compound
silica with iron pigmentation!
- Have you got that pillow for my neck?
- Yes, sir.
And the pills?
Yes, all measured
out for you, there you go.
Hobbes!
Professor Winfold Hobbes!
- I'm the Doctor, hello!
- It's my 14th time!
Oh! My first.
And I'm Dee Dee, Dee Dee Blasco.
Don't bother the man!
Where's my water bottle?
Complimentary slippers,
complimentary juicepack,
and complimentary peanuts,
I must warn you some
products may contain nuts.
Don't be silly, come and sit with us.
Look! We get slippers!
- Jethro! Do what your mother says.
- I'm sitting here.
Oh, he's ashamed of us.
But he doesn't mind us paying, does he?
Don't you two start. Should I save
the juicepack or have it now?
Look, it's peach and clementine!
Ladies and gentlemen
and variations thereupon,
welcome on board the Crusader 50,
if you would fasten your seatbelts,
we'll be leaving any moment.
Doors!
Shields down!
I'm afraid the view is shielded
until we reach the Waterfall Palace.
Also, a reminder, Midnight has no air,
so please don't touch
the exterior door seals.
Fire exit at the rear,
and should we need to use it...
you first.
Now I will hand you
over to Driver Joe...
Driver Joe at the wheel!
There's been a diamondfall
at the Winter Witch Canyon,
so we'll be taking a slight detour,
as you'll see on the map.
The journey covers 500
kliks to the Multifaceted Coast,
duration is estimated at four hours.
Thank you for travelling with us,
and as they used to say
in the olden days, wagons roll!
For your entertainment,
we have the Music Channel
playing retrovids of Earth Classics.
# "Do It Do It Again" #
by Raffaella Carra
Also, the latest artistic
installation from Ludovic Klein.
Plus, for the youngsters,
a rare treat :
the Animation Archives.
Four hours of funtime!
Enjoy!
Well, that's a mercy!
I do apologise, ladies and gentlemen
and variations thereupon.
We seem to have had a failure
of the Entertainment System...
Aw...
- But what do we do?!
- We've got four hours of this!
Four hours of just sitting here!
Tell you what! We'll have to talk
to each other instead!
98 KLIKS LATER...
So Biff said, "I'm going swimming".
Oh, I was all ready,
trunks and everything! Nose plug!
He had this little nose plug,
you should've seen him.
I went marching up to the lifeguard,
and he was a Shamboni,
you know, those big foreheads?
Great big forehead!
And I said, where's the pool?
And he said, "The pool is abstract!"
It wasn't a real pool!
- It was a concept!
- And you wore a nose plug!
I was like this!
Mmm... where's the pool?
150 KLIKS LATER...
I'm just a second-year student,
but I wrote a paper on
the Lost Moon of Poosh,
Professor Hobbes read it, liked it,
took me on as a researcher.
Just for the holidays. Well...
I say researcher, most of the time
he's got me fetching and carrying.
- But it's all good experience!
- And did they ever find it?
- Find what?
- The Lost Moon of Poosh!
No! Not yet!
Well, maybe that'll be your great
discovery, one day. Here's to Poosh!
Poosh!
209 KLIKS LATER...
No, no, I'm with this
friend of mine,
Donna, she stayed behind
in the Leisure Palace. You?
No, it's just me.
Oh, I've done plenty of that.
Travelling on my own.
I love it.
- Do what you want! Go anywhere!
- I'm still getting used to it.
I've... found myself single,
rather recently. Not by choice.
- What happened?
- Oh, the usual.
She needed her own
space, as they say.
A different galaxy, in fact.
I reckon that's enough space, don't you?
Yeah.
I had a friend who went
to a different universe.
Oh, what's this, chicken or beef?
I think it's both.
251 KLIKS LATER...
So this is Midnight, d'you see?
Bombarded by the sun!
X-tonic rays, raw Galvanic Radiation...
Dee Dee, next slide!
It's my pet project.
Actually, I'm the first person
to research this.
Because you see...
..the history is fascinating,
because there is no history.
There's no life in this entire system,
there couldn't be.
Before the Leisure Palace
Company moved in,
no-one had come here in all eternity.
No living thing...
But how d'you know?
I mean, if no-one can go outside...
Oh, his imagination! Here we go!
- He's got a point, though.
- Exactly!
We look upon this world through glass.
Safe inside our metal box.
Even the Leisure Palace
was lowered down from orbit.
And here we are now,
crossing Midnight...
but never touching it.
We've stopped.
Have we stopped?
Are we there?
We can't be, it's too soon.
They don't stop,
Crusader vehicles never stop.
If you could just return to your seats,
it's just a small delay.
- Maybe just a pit stop.
- What's going on?
There's no pit to stop in, I've been
on this expedition 14 times,
they never stop.
Evidently, we have stopped,
so there's no point in denying it.
- We've broken down!
- Thanks, Jethro.
- In the middle of nowhere!
- That's enough, stop it!
Ladies and gentlemen
and variations thereupon,
we're just experiencing a short...
delay, the driver needs
to stabilise the engine feeds.
Perfectly routine, so if you could
just stay in your seats...
- No, I'm sorry sir...
- There you go,
- engine expert Two ticks!
- Sorry, sir, if you could sit down!
- You're not supposed...
- If you could return...
Company insurance,
let's get an assessment...
So, what's the problem, Driver Joe?
We're stabilising the engine feeds,
won't take long.
Um, no, cos that's the engine feed,
that light there, and it's fine,
and it's a micropetrol engine,
so stabilising doesn't make sense?
Soory, I'm a doctor. I'm very clever.
So what's wrong?
We just stopped, look, all systems fine
and everything's working,
but we're not moving.
You're right.
No faults. And who are you?
Claude, I'm the mechanic. Trainee.
Nice to meet you.
I've sent a distress signal. They should
dispatch a rescue truck, top speed.
- How long till they get here?
- About an hour.
Well, since we're waiting...
shall we take a look outside?
Lift the screens a bit?
It's 100% X-tonic out there,
we'd be vaporised.
No, those windows are Finitoglass,
give you a couple of minutes. Go on!
Live a little!
That is beautiful...
Look at all those diamonds!
Poisoned by the sun.
No-one can ever touch them.
Joe, you said we took a detour?
- Just 40 kliks to the west.
- Is that a recognised path?
No, it's a new one, the computer
worked it out, on automatic.
So we're the first?
This piece of ground.
No-one's ever been here before.
Not in the whole of recorded history.
Did you just...?
- No, sorry. Nothing.
- What did you see?
Just there. That ridge.
Like... a shadow. Just for a second.
What sort of shadow?
X-tonic rising!
Shields down.
Look, there he is, look, there!
- Where ?
What was it?
Like, just, something...
shifting, something sort of... dark.
Like it was... running.
Running which way?
Towards us.
Doctor, back to your seat
and not a word, rescue's on its way.
If you could close the door,
thank you.
What did they say? Did they tell you?
What is it, what's wrong?
Oh, just stabilising,
happens all the time.
I don't need this.
I'm on a schedule.
This is completely unnecessary!
Back to your seats, thank you.
Excuse me, Doctor,
but they're micropetrol
engines, aren't they?
- Now, don't bother the man.
- My father was a mechanic.
Micropetrol doesn't stabilise,
what does 'stabilise' mean?
Well. Bit of flim-flam.
Don't worry, they're sorting it out.
- So it's not the engines?
- Just a little pause, that's all.
How much air have we got?
Professor, it's fine.
- What did he say?
- Nothing!
- Are we running out of air?
- I was just speculating...
- Right miss? Are we running out of air?
- Is that the Captain said?
If you could remain calm...
- How much air have we got?
- Mum, stop it.
- Everything's under control.
- Doesn't look like it!
He said it.
Fine, the air is on a circular filter...
- He started it!
- Everyone...
QUIET!
Thank you.
Now, if you'd care to listen
to my good friend Dee Dee...
Oh!
Um...
It's just that...
Well, the air's on a circular filter so,
we could stay breathing for ten years.
There you go!
And I've spoken to the Captain,
I can guarantee you, everything's fine.
What was that?
It must be the metal.
We're cooling down,
- it's just settling...
- Rocks. Could be rocks falling.
What I want to know is,
how long do we have to sit here.
- What is that?
- Someone's out there!
- Don't be ridiculous!
- Like I said, it could be rocks.
We're in the open.
Nothing could fall against the sides.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Is there something out there?
Well? Anyone?
What the hell is making that noise?
I'm sorry, but the light
out there is X-tonic,
that means it would destroy
any living thing, in a split-second.
It is impossible for
someone to be outside.
What the hell is that, then?!
Sir! You really should
get back to your seat.
Hello?
It's moving...
It's trying the door.
There is no 'it',
there's nothing out there. Can't be.
That's the entrance. Can it get in?
No, that door's on 200
weight of hydraulics.
- Stop it. Don't encourage them.
- What do you think it is?
- Biff, don't...
- Mr Cane, better not...
It's cast iron, that door...
Three times! Did you hear that,
it did it three times?!
- It answered!
- It did it three times!
All right, everyone, calm down.
No, but it answered, don't tell me
that thing's not alive, it answered him!
I really must insist,
you get back to your seats...
No! Don't just stand there
telling us the rules!
You're the hostess,
you're supposed to do something!
What the hell's making that noise?
She said she'd get me. Stop it,
make it stop, somebody make it stop!
Don't stand there looking at me, not
my fault, he started it with stories.
- Calm down!
- He made it worse.
- Why couldn't you leave it alone?
- Stop staring at me!
- Just tell me what it is.
- Calm down!
It's coming for me,
it's coming for me,
it's coming for me...
It's coming for me!
It's coming for me.
Get out of there!
OK?
Arms. Legs. Neck.
Head. Nose. I'm fine...
Everyone else?
How are we?
Everyone all right?
Earthquake, must be...
But that's impossible,
the ground is fixed, it's solid.
Got torches, everyone take a torch,
they're in the back of the seats.
Oh, Jethro, sweetheart, come here...
Never mind me, what about her?
- What happened to the seats?
- Who did that?
They've been ripped up.
It's all right, it's all right,
it's all right, it's over.
We're still alive...
Look, the wall's still intact.
D'you see?
- Joe, Claude?
- We're safe.
Driver Joe, can you hear me?
I'm not getting any response,
the intercom must be down.
What happened? What was that?
Is it the driver?
Have we lost the driver?
- The cabin's gone.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- It can't be gone, how can it be gone?
- Well, you saw it!
There was nothing there,
like it was ripped away.
What are you doing?
That's bit of light, thank you.
Molto bene!
- You know what you're doing?
- Cabin's gone, leave that wall alone.
The cabin can't be gone!
No, it's safe, any rupture
would automatically seal itself...
But something sliced it off.
- You're right. The cabin's gone.
- But if it gets separated...
It loses integrity.
I'm sorry. They've been reduced to dust.
The driver and the mechanic.
But they sent a distress signal.
Help is on its way.
They saved our lives!
We're gonna get out of here, I promise.
We're still alive,
and they're gonna find us.
Doctor. Look at her.
Right, yes, sorry...
Have we got a medical kit?
Why won't she turn around?
- What's her name?
- Silvestry. Mrs Sky Silvestry.
Sky?
Can you hear me?
Are you all right?
Can you move, Sky?
Just look at me.
That noise, from outside...
- it's stopped.
- Well, thank God for that.
But what if it's
not outside any more?
- What if it's inside?
- Inside? Where?
It was heading for her.
Sky...
it's all right, Sky.
I just want you to turn around,
face me.
Sky?
- Are you all right?
- Are you hurt?
- You don't have to talk.
- I'm trying to help.
- My name's the Doctor.
- OK, can you stop?
- I'd like you to stop.
- Why's she doing that?
- She's gone mad.
- Stop it. I said stop it!
- I Don't think she can.
- Stop it, this isn't funny.
- Sh, sh, all of you.
- My name's Jethro!
- Jethro, leave it, shut up!
- Why are you repeating?
- What is that, learning?
- Copying?
- Absorbing?
- The square root of pi is...
- 1.77245385090551602729816748...
- 3341. Wow!
- That's impossible.
- She couldn't repeat all that.
- She...
"Tell her to stop!"
"She's driving me mad."
"Make her STOP!"
"Stop her staring at me, shut her up..."
"Telling you, whatever your name is."
"Stop it..."
"What's wrong with her eyes?"
"Six, six, six."
- That's the back-up system.
- Well!
That's a bit better.
- What about rescue, how long's?
- About 60 minutes, that's all.
Then I suggest we all calm down.
This panic isn't helping.
That poor woman is evidently
in a state of self-induced hysteria,
- we should leave her alone.
- Doctor...
I know.
Doctor, now step back,
I think you should leave her...
Alone.
What's she doing?
How can she do that?
She's talking with you...
and with me!
Oh, my God!
Biff, what's she doing?
She's repeating...
- At exactly the same time.
- That's impossible.
-There's not even a delay.
- Ohh man, that is weird.
I think you should all be very,
very quiet, have you got that?
- How's she doing it?
- Mrs Cane, please, be quiet.
But how can she do that?
She's got my voice, she's got my words!
Sweetheart, be quiet, just...
hush now. Hush.
- She's doing it to me!
- Just stop it, all of you.
Stop it. Please.
Now then, Sky. Are you Sky?
Is Sky still in there?
Mrs Silvestry?
You know exactly what I'm going to say,
how are you doing that?
Roast beef!
Bananas!
The Medusa Cascade.
Bang!
Rose Tyler, Martha Jones,
Donna Noble, TARDIS!
Shamble bobble dibble dooble.
Oh, Doctor, you're so handsome.
Yes, I am, thank you.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G,
H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O...
First she repeats. Then she catches up.
What's the next stage?
Next stage of what?
But that's not her, is it?
That's not Mrs Silvestry any more.
I don't think so, no.
I think...
the more we talk,
the more she learns.
Now, I'm all for education,
but in this case...
maybe not. Let's just... move back.
Come on. Come with me.
Everyone, get back,
all of you, as far as you can.
Doctor, make her stop.
Val, come on,
come to the back, stop looking at her,
come on, Jethro, you too,
everyone, come on...
50 minutes. That's all we need.
50 minutes till
the rescue arrives. And...
she's not exactly strong, look at her,
all she's got is our voices.
I can't look at her.
It's those eyes.
We must not look at goblin men.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It's a poem. Christina Rossetti.
We must not look at goblin men.
We must not buy their fruits.
Who knows upon what soil they fed.
Their hungry, thirsty roots?
I don't think that's helping.
She's not a goblin, or a monster,
she's just a very sick woman.
- Maybe that's why it went for her.
- There is no 'it!'
Think about it. That knocking,
went all the way round the bus.
Till it found her.
And she was the most scared,
out of all of us.
Maybe that's what it needed.
- That's how it got in.
- For the last time!
Nothing can live
on the surface of Midnight.
Professor, I'm glad you've got
a definition of life in the universe,
but perhaps the universe
has got ideas of its own, mm?
Now trust me. I've got previous!
I think there might well be some...
consciousness inside Mrs Silvestry,
but maybe SHE's still in there.
- It's our job to help her.
- You can help her, I'm not going near.
No, I've got to stay back.
If she's copying us,
maybe the final stage is becoming us.
I don't want her becoming me,
or things could get a lot worse.
- Oh, like you're so special.
- As it happens, yes, I am.
So that's decided.
We stay back. And we wait.
When the rescue ship comes,
we can get her to hospital.
We should throw her out.
I beg your pardon?
- Can we do that?
- Don't be ridiculous.
That thing, whatever it is,
killed the driver, and the mechanic,
and I don't think she's finished yet.
- She can't even move!
- Look, look at her eyes!
She killed Joe,
and she killed Claude, and we're next.
She's still doing it. Just stop it!
Stop talking!! STOP IT!!!
- Biff, don't, sweetheart!
- She won't stop!
We can't throw her out though,
we can't even open the doors.
No-one is getting thrown out!
Yes, we can.
Cos there's an air pressure seal.
Like when you opened cabin door,
you weren't pulled out,
you had a couple of sec,
cos it takes the pressure-wall
about six seconds to collapse.
Well, six seconds exactly.
That's enough time to throw someone out.
- Thanks, Dee Dee, just what we needed.
- Would it kill her? Outside?
I don't know, but she's got a body now,
it would kill the physical form.
No-one is killing anyone!
I wouldn't risk the cabin door twice.
But we've got that one.
All we need to do is grab hold
of her and throw her out.
Now, listen! For all we know,
that's a brand new lifeform over there.
And if it's come inside to discover us,
than what's it found?
This little bunch of humans,
what d'you amount to?
A murder? Cos this is where you decide.
You decide who you are.
Could you actually murder her?
Any of you?
Really?
Or are you better than that?
I'd do it.
- So would I.
- And me.
- I think we should.
- What?!
- I want her out.
- You can't say that!
I'm sorry, but you said it yourself,
Doctor, she is growing in strength.
- That's not what I said!
- I want to go home.
I'm sorry. I want to be safe.
You'll be safe,
the rescue truck is on its way.
What happens then, Doctor?
If it takes that thing back to
the Leisure Palace,
if that thing reaches civilisation,
what if it spreads?
When we get back to the base,
I'll be there to contain it.
- You haven't done much so far!
- You'r standing with the rest of us!
She's dangerous.
It's my job to see this vessel is safe.
We should get rid of her.
Now hang on, I think, perhaps,
we're all going a little bit too far.
- At last! Thank you.
- Two people are dead!
Don't make it a third!
Jethro, what d'you say?
- I'm not killing anyone.
- Thank you.
- He's just a boy!
- What, I don't get a vote?
There isn't a vote,
it's not happening! Ever.
If you try to throw her out that door,
you'll have to get past me first.
- OK.
- Fine by me.
Oh, now you're being stupid.
Just think about it!
Could you take someone
and throw them out of that door?
Calling me a coward?
- Who put you in charge?
- I'm sorry, but...
you're a Doctor of what, exactly?
He wasn't even booked in.
Rest of you, tickets in advance.
He just turned up, out of the blue.
Where from?
I'm just... travelling,
- I'm a traveller..
- Like an immigrant?
Who were you talking to?
Before you got on board, who was that?
Just Donna, my friend.
- What were you saying her?
- Hasn't told us his name.
Thing is, Doctor,
you've been loving this.
Oh, Jethro, not you.
No, but ever since all the trouble
started, you've been loving it.
It has to be said,
you do seem to have a certain...glee.
All right, I'm interested,
yes, I can't help it,
cos whatever's inside her,
it's brand new,
- and that's fascinating.
- What, you wanted this to happen?
No!
You were talking to her,
on your own, before the trouble,
right at the front, you were
talking to that Sky woman,
- the two of you together, I saw you.
- We all did!
- You went in the cabin!
- What you said to her?
- I was talking!
- Saying what?
You called us humans
like you're not one of us.
- He did! That's what he said!
- And the wiring,
he went into that panel
and opened up the wiring.
That was after.
- But how did you know what to do?
- Because I'm clever.
I see. Well.
That makes things clear.
And what are we, then? Idiots?
That's not what I meant.
If you're clever what are we?
You've looked down on us
from the moment we walked in.
Even if he goes,
he's practically volunteered.
Oh come on,
just listen to yourself, please!
D'you mean...?
We throw him out as well?
If we have to.
Look, just...
Right, sorry, yes, hold on, just...
I know, you're scared,
and so am I, look at me, I am.
But we have all got to calm down
and cool off and think.
Perhaps you could tell us your name.
- What does it matter?
- Then tell us.
- John Smith.
- Your real name.
He's lying, look at his face.
His eyes are the same as hers.
- Tell us?!
- He's been lying to us,
right from the start.
No-one's called John Smith!
Now listen to me right now!
You need me, all of you, if we're going
to get out of this, then you need me.
So you keep saying!
You've repeated yourself more than her.
If anyone's in charge, it should be
the Professor, he's the expert!
Stop, just look...
- You keep out of this, Jethro.
- Look at her!
She's stopped...
When did she...?
No, she hasn't, she's still doing it.
She looks the same to me...
No, she's stopped!
Look, I'm talking, and she's not!
What about me? Is she?
Look! Look at that!
She's not doing me, she's let me go!
Mrs Silvestry?
Nor me! Nothing!
Sky?
What are you doing?
She's still doing him!
Doctor. It's you.
She's only copying you.
Why me? Why are you doing this?
She won't leave him alone!
D'you see? I said so, she's with him.
- They're together!
- How d'you explain it, Doctor?
- If you're so clever.
- I don't know.
Sky, stop it.
I said stop it. Just stop it!
Look at the two of them...
Mrs Silvestry. I'm trying to understand.
You've captured my speech, what for?
What d'you need?
You need my voice in particular.
The cleverest voice in the room.
Why? Cos I'm the only
one who can help?
Oh, I'd love that to be true.
But your eyes.
They're saying something else.
Listen to me.
Whatever you want, if it's life,
or form, or consciousness,
or voice, you don't have to steal it.
You can find it
without hurting anyone.
And I'll help you.
That's a promise.
So.
What d'you think?
- Do we have a deal?
- Hold on, did she...?
- She spoke first.
She can't have.
- She did!
- She spoke first!
Oh, look at that, I'm ahead of you.
Did you see? She spoke
before he did! Definitely!
He's copying her.
Doctor? What's happening?
- I think it's moved.
- I think it's letting me go.
What do you mean?
Letting you go from what?
But he's repeating now,
he's the one doing it! It's him!
They're separating.
Mrs Silvestry?
Is that you?
Yes, yes, it's me.
Yes, yes, it's me...
I'm coming back, listen.
- I'm coming back...
- It's me!
Listen. It's me!
Like it's passed into the Doctor.
It's transferred. Whatever it is,
it's gone inside him.
No, that's not what happened.
But look at her!
Look at me, I can move...
- Look at me...
- I can feel again...
- I'm coming back to life.
- I can move...
I can feel again.
- And look at him.
- I'm coming back to life.
- He can't move.
- And look at him, he can't move.
- Help me.
- Professor?
- Get me away from him.
- Please.
Oh, thank you.
They've completely separated.
It's in him, d'you see?
I said it was him all the time.
She's free! She's been saved!
- Oh, it was so cold.
- I couldn't breathe.
- I'm sorry.
I must've scared you, so much.
No, no, it's all right,
I've got you, ooh, there you are,
my love, it's gone,
everything's all right now.
I wouldn't touch her.
But it's gone, she's clean,
it passed into him.
That's not what happened.
Thank you for your opinion, Dee,
but clearly, Mrs Silvestry
has been released.
- No.
- Just leave her alone!
She's safe, isn't she?
- Jethro? It's let her go, hasn't it?
- I think so, yeah.
Looks like it. Professor?
I'd say, from observation...
the Doctor can't move,
and when she was possessed,
she couldn't move, so...
Well, there we are then!
Now the only problem
we've got is this Doctor.
- It's inside his head.
- It killed the driver.
- And the mechanic.
And now it wants us.
- And now it wants us.
- I said so!
- He's waited so long.
- In the dark.
- And the cold.
- And the diamonds.
- Until you came.
Bodies so hot.
- With blood.
- And pain.
Someone make him stop.
- But she's saying it!
- And you can shut up!
It's not him, it's her,
he's just repeating!
But that's what the
thing does, it repeats!
- Let her talk.
- What do you know?
Fat lot of good you've been!
Just let her explain.
I think...
I mean, from what I've seen...
it repeats, then it synchronises,
then it goes on to the next stage
that's exactly what
the Doctor said would...
- What, and you're on his side?
- No!
- The voice is the thing!
- And she's the voice!
She stole it! Look at her!
It's not possessing him,
it's draining him!
She's got his voice...
That's not true,
I saw it pass into him,
- I saw it with my own eyes!
- So did I!
- You didn't!
- It went from her, to him.
You saw it, didn't you?
- I don't know.
- Don't be stupid, Jethro,
of course you did!
- I suppose he was right next to her.
- Everyone saw it!
But you're just making it up!
I know what I saw,
and I saw her stealing his voice.
She's as bad as him,
someone shut her up.
I think you should be quiet, Dee.
- I'm only saying...
- And that's an order!
You're making a fool of yourself!
Pretending you're an expert
in mechanics and hydraulics,
when I can tell you, you are
nothing more than average, at best!
Now shut up!
- That's how he does it.
- He makes you fight.
- Creeps into your head.
- And whispers.
- Listen.
- Just listen.
- That's him.
- Inside.
- Get him out of my head!
- Yeah, we should throw him out!
Don't just talk about it!
Don't be so useless!
- Do something!
- I will! You watch me!
I'm gonna throw him out!
- Yes!
- Throw him out!
- Get rid of him!
- Now!
- Don't!
- It'll be you next!
I don't think we should do this.
It was your idea!
Professor, help me.
I can't...
- I'm not...
- What sort of a man are you? Come on!
Throw him out!
Just do it, throw him out!
- Professor, help me.
- Get him out!
Grab hold of him...
Not like that!! Are you stupid?!!
- Cast him out!
- Into the sun!
- And the night!
Come on.
Don't just stand there!
- Do something say!!
- Get him out!
- Do it!
- Do it now!
- Faster!
Just do it!
- That's the way!
- You can do it!
- Molto bene!
Get him out!
- Allons-y!
That's his voice.
- The starlight waits!
- She's taken his voice.
- The emptiness!
- Get him out!
The Midnight sky!
It's her.
She's taken his voice!
One, two, three, four, five, six.
It's gone, it's gone...
It's gone, it's gone, it's gone...
It's gone.
It's gone...
It's gone, it's gone, it's gone...
I said it was her.
20 MINUTES LATER...
Repeat, Crusader 50, rescue vehicle
coming alongside in three minutes,
door-seals set to automatic.
Prepare for boarding,
repeat, prepare for boarding.
The Hostess...
what was her name?
I don't know.
What d'you think it was?
No idea.
D'you think it's still out there?
Well, you'd better tell 'em.
- This lot.
- Yeah.
They can build a Leisure
Palace somewhere else.
Let this planet keep on turning.
Round an X-tonic star.
In silence.
Can't imagine you, without a voice.
Molto bene.
Molto bene!
No, don't do that.
Don't.
Found a body, sir.
The Doctor is dead.
How could anything...
be worse than this?
What happened, what did they find?
Oh, my God. The stars are going out.
- Who are you?
- I was like you.
- Turn around... show me your back.
- I've been pulled across
from a different universe because
every single universe is in danger.
There's something on your back.
- What am I supposed to do?!
- Powering up...
None of this... was meant to happen.
You're going to die.
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~