You're gonna love this.
One, two, three.
It's lovely!
You want to buy Shukina?
Or Peshwami? Most beautiful
Peshwami in all of Shan Shen.
Er, no, thanks.
Tell your fortune, lady?
The future predicted.
- Your life foretold.
- Oh, no, thanks.
Don't you want to know
if you're going to be happy?
I'm happy right now, thanks.
You've got red hair.
The reading's free for red hair.
All right, then.
Oh, you're fascinating!
No, but you're good.
I can see... a man.
The most remarkable man.
How did you meet him?
You're supposed to tell me.
I see the future.
Tell me the past.
When did your lives cross?
It's sort of complicated.
I ended up in his spaceship
on my wedding day.
- Long story.
- But what led you to that meeting?
All sorts of things,
but my job, I suppose.
It was on Earth,
this planet called Earth. Miles away.
But I had this job, as a temp,
I was a secretary,
in a place called HC Clements.
HC Clements, can I help you?
Sorry.
It's the incense.
Just breathe deep.
This job of yours.
What choices led you there?
There was a choice.
Six months before.
Cos the agency offered me
this contract with HC Clements.
There was this other job,
my mum knew this man...
Jival, he's called, Jival Chowdry.
He runs that little photocopy
business and he needs a secretary.
I've got a job!
As a temp! This is permanent!
It's 20,000 a year, Donna.
HC Clements is in the City,
it's nice, it's posh, so stop it!
Your life could have
gone one way or the other.
- What made you decide?
- I just did.
But when was the moment?
When did you choose?
It won't take long, just turn right,
we'll pop in and see Mr Chowdry,
so Suzette can introduce you.
I'm going left,
if you don't like it, get out and walk!
If you turn right, you'll have a career.
Not just filling-in.
You think I'm so useless.
Oh, I know why you want
a job with HC Clements, lady.
Cos you think you'll meet a man
with lots of money and your
whole life will change.
Well, let me tell you, sweetheart,
City executives don't need temps.
Except for practice.
Yeah, well, they haven't met me!
You turned left.
What if you'd turned right?
What then?
- Let go of my hands.
- What if it changes?
What if you go right?
What if you could still go right?
Stop it!
What's that?!
What's on my back?
What is it?
Make the choice again, Donna Noble,
and change your mind. Turn right!
I'm turning.
Turn right.
Turn right!
Turn RIGHT!
Let me tell you, sweetheart,
City executives don't need temps.
Except for practice.
Yeah.
Suppose you're right.
Turn right, and never meet that man.
Turn right and change the world!
Doctor Who - 4x11
"Turn Left"
Transcript by evarin
www.transcripts.subtitle.me.uk
Subtitles by LauCass
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~
# We wish you a merry Christmas
We wish you a merry Christmas #
and a happy New Year... #
Get out of the way!
Here we are! Feed at the trough!
Mooky says, let's go to the Boardwalk,
- it's 2 for the price of 1.
- Christmas Eve? It'll be heaving!
Well, exactly! Get in and grab 'em!
That's the second round of drinks
you've bought, it was my turn.
I can afford it. Promotion!
You are talking to Jival Chowdry's
Personal Assistant, I'll have you know.
Capital P, capital A,
£23,000 per annum, merci beaucoup!
- Here's to Mr Chowdry!
- Mr Chowdry!
She gets all the luck.
What's wrong? What is it?
Sorry?
Someone spill a drink on me?
No.
Why d'you keep looking
at my shoulder, what's wrong?
I don't know.
Oh, don't tell me you're
getting all spooky again.
It was bad enough when you saw the ghost
of Earl Mountbatten at the Boat Show.
What're you looking at?
- What is it?
- It's like...
It's like there's something I can't see.
No, shut up all of you!
Come and see.
Just look at the sky!
It's a star! It's a Christmas star!
Come on, then.
What the hell is that?!
Ken Livingston, that's what!
- Spending our money on decorations!
- How much did that cost?!
Don't be so stupid,
it's flying, it's really flying!
That's not a star,
that's a web.
It's heading east,
the middle of the city.
Alice, there's a great big
web star thing shooting at people
and you're looking at ME!
There's something on your back!
Donna! Where you going?!
You'll get yourself killed! Donna!!
Fire!
Everyone stay back!
The Thames has been closed.
Return to your homes.
Keep away from the river,
and that's an order.
Trap 1 to Greyhound 15,
what is your report? Over.
From the evidence I'd say
he managed to stop a creature,
some sort of red spider.
Blew up the base underneath the barrier,
flooded the whole thing. Over.
And where is he now? Over.
We've found a body, sir. Over.
- Is it him? Over.
- I think so.
Just didn't make it out in time.
The Doctor is dead.
It must have happened
too fast for him to regenerate.
Escort the ambulance back to unit base.
What happened, what did they find?
Did they find someone?
I don't know.
Bloke called the Doctor or something.
Where is he?
They took him away. He's dead.
I'm sorry. Did you know him?
I mean, they didn't say his name.
It could be any doctor.
I came so far.
It could be anyone.
- What's your name?
- Donna.
- And you?
- Oh, I was just...
passing by, I shouldn't even be here.
This is wrong. This is wrong.
This is so wrong.
- Sorry, what was it, Donna what?
- Why d'you keep looking at my back?
- I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
You keep looking behind me,
you're doing it now.
What is it, what's there?
Has someone put something on my back?
You can't sack me!
I'm your Personal Assistant!
You don't have to make a scene,
just come downstairs, and we can talk.
Oh, I'll make a scene,
right in front of a tribunal.
And the first thing I'll say is
"wandering hands"!
You know what it's been like
for the past few months,
ever since that Christmas thing.
Half my contracts were on
the other side of the river,
and the Thames is still closed off.
Look, I can't deliver,
I'm losing a fortune.
Well, sack one of this lot!
Sack Cliff! He just sits there,
I don't know what he does all day.
Sorry, Cliff.
Actually, I'm not sorry,
what DO you do all day?
What the hell?!
Like an earthquake.
That's weird.
Funny sort of clouds...
Who typed this?
I'm your PA, did you get
someone else to type this?
Beatrice!
It sounds impossible,
but the entire hospital has vanished.
The Royal Hope no longer exists.
It's not been destroyed,
there's no wreckage,
it's simply gone.
Reports from bystanders say that
the rain lifted up around the hospital.
Hole punch, having that.
Stapler, mine.
Toy cactus,
you can have that, Beatrice, catch!
Cliff, I'd leave you my mousemat,
but I'm worried you'd cut yourself.
All right, Donna, have some respect.
There's 2,000 people in that hospital.
And it's vanished!
I'll show you vanishing.
Thanks for nothing!
Oh, and you know when that
money went missing from the kitty?
Anne Marie. That's all I'm saying.
Anne Marie!
Oh, don't tell me,
the hospital's back!
Well, isn't that wizard?!
To confirm. The Royal Hope Hospital
was returned to its original position.
But with only one survivor.
The only person left alive,
is medical student Oliver Morgenstern.
And there were these creatures.
Like rhinos.
Talking rhinos in black leather...
Rhinos?
Rhinos, could be aliens.
We couldn't breathe,
we were running out of air.
A colleague of mine gave
me the last oxygen tank. Martha.
Martha Jones.
And she died.
Least you've got a hole punch.
And a raffle ticket.
Yeah, well, they can keep the raffle,
I wouldn't take a penny off that man.
Honestly, you two!
There's aliens on the news!
They took that hospital
all the way to the moon,
and you're banging on
about raffle tickets!
Don't be daft, Gramps,
it wasn't the moon, it couldn't be.
I am telling you, it is getting worse,
these past few years.
It's like all of a sudden,
they suddenly know all about us
and there's keen eyes up there
and they're watching us,
and they're not friendly.
This stapler says Bea.
Can't believe how well you're taking
me getting sacked.
Thought you'd hit the roof.
I'm just tired, Donna.
What with your father and everything.
To be honest, I've given up on you.
This further report just in
from Oliver Morgenstern.
There was this woman
who took control.
Said she knew what to do, said she
could stop the MRI or something.
Sarah Jane, her name was.
Sarah Jane Smith.
Sarah Jane Smith was
a freelance investigative journalist,
formerly of Metropolitan Magazine.
Her body was recovered from
the hospital late this afternoon...
- What's for tea?
- I've got nothing in.
I'll get chips.
Last of my wages.
Fish and chips, yeah?
Along with his teenage friends
Maria Jackson and Clyde Langer.
It is feared that they also perished.
Blimey, you all right?!
- What was that, fireworks, or...?
- I dunno. I was just...
walking along. That's weird!
You're the one...
Christmas Eve, I met you, in town.
- Donna, isn't it?
- What was your name?
How're you doing?
You're looking good.
What you been up to?
- You're doing it again.
- What?
Looking behind me.
People keep on doing that.
- Looking at my back.
- What sort of people?
People in the street.
Strangers.
I just catch them, sometimes.
Staring at me.
Like they're looking at something.
And then I get home and
I look and there's nothing there.
- See? Look, now I'M doing it!
- What are you doing for Christmas?
What am I what?!
Next Christmas. Any plans?
I dunno, that's ages away!
Nothing much, I suppose. Why?
Just, I think you should get out,
you and your family. Don't stay
in London. Just leave the city.
What for?
Nice hotel. Christmas break?
Can't afford it.
Well, now,
you've got that raffle ticket.
- How d'you know about that?
- First prize.
Luxury weekend break.
Use it, Donna Noble.
Why won't you tell me your name?
I think you
should leave me alone.
# Merry Xmas Everybody #
by Slade
Cor blimey! That's what I call posh!
I said you were lucky!
Didn't I always say, my lucky star?
For God's sake, don't tell them
that we won it in a raffle. Be classy!
- Dad, take those things off.
- No, I shan't, it's Christmas!
I'll have that one, thank you,
it's got my liniment in it.
I reckon we deserve this.
It's been a hell of a year.
Your Dad would've loved this.
Yeah.
He would've.
Oy! Gramps!
Get that, that'll be breakfast!
We've got croissants!
Why can't you get it? Lady Muck!
It's Christmas Day,
I never get up before ten.
Only madam there
was up with the dawn chorus.
Like when she was six years old!
I'm not wasting a second in this place!
- How was the sofa?
- Oh, yeah, not so good, really.
You know we could've paid
for a second room.
Oi!
- Merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Dad.
All right! All right, my darlin'!
Grub's up! Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas, sir.
Have you seen this?
Nice early breakfast,
then we'll go for a walk.
People always say that at Christmas,
"Oh, we all went for a walk"
I've always wanted to do that.
So, walk first, presents later, yeah?
Donna, come and see.
Tienes algo en tu espalda.
- What?
- Look at the telly.
Tienes algo en tu espalda.
What does it mean?
Don't know what you're saying.
- Donna, look at the TV!
- Tienes algo en tu espalda!
For God's sake, Donna,
don't just stand there, come and look!
This footage is live and genuine.
The object is falling on Central London.
I repeat, this is not a hoax.
A replica of the Titanic
is falling out of the sky and
it's heading for Buckingham Palace.
We're getting this footage from
the Guinnevere range of satellites.
Is that... a film or something?
The Royal Air Force
has declared an emerg...
It's gone dead.
All of them.
No, but the Titanic?!
Oh, don't be daft!
Is that like a sequel?
Oh...
Oh, God rest their souls.
I was supposed to be out there,
selling papers.
I should've been there.
We all should.
We'd be dead.
That's everyone.
Every single person we know.
The whole city.
Can't be.
But it is. It's gone.
London's gone.
If you hadn't won that raffle...
Leeds?! I'm not moving to Leeds!
I'm afraid it's Leeds,
or you can wait in the hostel
for another three months.
All I want is a washing machine.
What about Glasgow,
I heard there was jobs going in Glasgow.
You can't pick and choose!
All of Southern England's
flooded with radiation,
7 million people in need of relocation,
and now France has closed its borders,
so it's Leeds or nothing. Next!
The Daniels Family,
billetted at number 15.
Mr & Mrs Obego, billetted at number 31.
Miss Coltrane, you're in number 8.
The Noble family,
billetted at number 29...
That's us! Come on. Off we go.
All right?
Used to be a nice little family,
number 29.
They missed one mortgage
payment, just one,
they got booted out, all for you lot.
Don't get all chippy
with me, Vera Duckworth.
Pop your clogs on and go
and feed t'whippets.
Sweetheart, come on.
You're not gonna make the
world any better by shouting at it.
I can try.
What happens, do we get keys?
- I don't know, do I?
- Who do we ask, the soldiers?
Hey-ey! Is a big house!
Room for all! Welcome! In you come.
- I thought this was OUR house.
- Is many people's house! Is wonderful!
In! In! In!
We've been here
for eight weeks already.
I had a nice little paper shop
in Shepherd's Bush. All gone now.
So, upstairs, we have the
Merchandani family, seven of them,
good family, good kids.
Except that one, be careful of him.
That's a joking! Where's that smile?
Rocco Colosanto,
I'm here with my wife, and her sister,
her husband, their kids,
and their daughter's kids.
We've got the front room.
My mother, she's got the back room.
She's old, you forgive.
And this, this is you,
this is your palace!
- What d'you mean, this is us?
- You live here!
- We living in the kitchen?!
- You got camp beds!
You got the cooker, you keep warm,
you got the fridge, you keep cool!
- Is good!
- What about the bathroom?
- Nobody lives in the bathroom!
- No, I mean, is there a rota?
Is pot luck! Is fun!
I go wake Mamma,
she likes new people.
Mamma! Is people! Nice people!
Ah, well...
We'll settle in, won't we? Make do.
Bit of wartime spirit, eh?
But there isn't a war.
There's no fight,
There's just...
this.
Well, America, they'll save us.
It was on the news.
They're gonna send Great Britain
50 billion quid in financial aid!
God bless America!
America is in crisis with
over 60 million reported dead.
Sixty million people have dissolved
into fat. And the fat is walking.
People's fat has come to life
and is walking through the streets.
And there are spaceships.
There are reports of spaceships
over every major US city.
The fat is flying...
Aliens.
Yeah.
...into the air.
Mary McGinty, d'you remember her?
Who was she?
Worked in the newsagent on a Sunday.
Little woman, black hair.
Never really spoke to her.
She'll be dead.
Every day, I think of someone else.
All dead.
Maybe she went away for Christmas.
Maybe.
I'll go out tomorrow,
I'll walk into town.
There's got to be work.
Everyone needs secretaries.
Soon as I'm earning,
we'll get a proper place.
Just you wait, Mum.
What if it never gets better?
Course it will.
Even the bees are disappearing.
You don't see bumble bees any more.
They'll sort us out,
the Emergency Government.
- They'll do something.
- What if they don't?
Then...
we'll complain.
Who's gonna listen to us?
Refugees.
We haven't even got a vote.
We're just no-one, Donna.
We don't exist.
# ..And I spent all my
money on whisky and beer.. #
I am going to kill that man!
Now, listen, Mussolini!
I am telling you, for the last time,
to button it!
If I hear one more sea shanty...
Always loved a sing-song.
# ..I'm just a poor boy,
nobody loves me
# He's just a poor boy
from a poor family
# Spare him his life
from this monstrosity
# Easy come, easy go
# Will you let me go...? #
You stay here!
Everyone, stay!
Hey! Firing at the car, is not so good!
You crazy or what?!
It's this ATMOS thing, it won't stop,
it's like gas, it's toxic.
Well, switch it off!
I have done! It's still going!
It's all the cars,
every single ATMOS car!
They've gone mad...
You... lady, turn round.
- Turn around!
- Are you crazy, boy?
Now!
- Put that down!
- Turn round!
Do what he says!
Show me your back! Turn around!
Show me your back!
Sorry.
I thought I saw...
Call yourself a soldier?!
Pointing guns at innocent women!
You're a disgrace!
In my day, we'd have
had you court-martialled!
Donna, where are you going?
It's not safe at night!
Donna! Donna!
Hello.
Hi.
It's the ATMOS devices.
We're lucky, it's not so bad here,
Britain hasn't got that much petrol.
But all over Europe...
China, South Africa...
They're getting choked by gas.
Can't anyone stop it?
Yeah, they're trying right now.
This little band of fighters,
on board the Sontaran ship.
Any second now.
And that was...?
That was the Torchwood team.
Gwen Cooper,
Ianto Jones, they gave their lives.
And Captain Jack Harkness has
transported to the Sontaran homeworld.
There's no-one left.
You're always wearing
the same clothes.
Why won't you tell me your name?
None of this was meant to happen.
There was a man.
This wonderful man.
And he stopped it.
The Titanic, the Adipose, the ATMOS,
he stopped them all from happening.
That... Doctor?
- You knew him.
- Did I?
When?
I think you dream about him sometimes.
It's a man in a suit.
Tall, thin man. Great hair.
Some really great hair.
Who are you?
I was like you. I used to be you.
Cos you travelled with him, Donna,
you travelled with the Doctor
in a different world.
I never met him. And he's dead.
He died underneath the Thames
on Christmas Eve.
But you were meant to be there.
He needed someone to stop him,
and that was you. You made him leave.
You saved his life.
Doctor! You can stop now!
Stop it! I don't know what you're
talking about, leave me alone!
Something's coming, Donna.
Something worse.
The whole world is stinking.
How could anything be worse than this?
Trust me. We need the Doctor
more than ever. I've...
I've been pulled across
from a different universe,
because every single
universe is in danger.
It's coming, Donna.
It's coming from across the stars,
and nothing can stop it.
What is?
The darkness.
Well, what d'you keep telling me for?
What am I supposed to do?!
I'm nothing special.
I mean... I'm not...
I'm nothing special. I'm a temp!
I'm not even that! I'm nothing.
Donna Noble, you're the most important
woman in the whole of creation.
Oh, don't.
Just... don't.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
I need you to come with me.
Yeah, well,
blonde hair might work on the men,
but you ain't shifting me, lady!
That's more like it.
- I've got plenty more.
- You'll come with me.
Only when you want to.
You'll have a long wait, then.
Not really, just 3 weeks.
Tell me, does your grandfather
still own that telescope?
He never lets go of it.
Three weeks' time.
But you've got to be certain.
Cos when you come with me,
Donna... I'm sorry,
so sorry, but...
you're going to die.
And you! I'll gonna
miss you most of all!
All flame-haired and fiery!
Oh, but why d'you have to go?
It's the new law!
England for the English, et cetera.
They can't send us home,
the oceans are closed,
they build labour camps!
I know, but labour doing what?
There aren't any jobs.
Sewing, digging, is good!
Now, stop it
before I kiss you too much...
Wilfred!
My capitano!
It'll be quiet with him gone.
Still, we'll have more room.
Labour camps.
That's what they called them last time.
What d'you mean?
It's happening again.
What is?
'Scuse me!
'Scuse me, where
are you taking them?
Where are you going?
Where are you going?!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
I asked about jobs.
With the army.
They said I wasn't qualified.
You were right. You said I should
have worked harder at school.
Suppose I've always
been a disappointment.
Yeah.
You know we'd get a bit of cash
if we sold this thing.
Don't you dare.
I always imagined, your old age...
I'd have put a bit of money by.
Make you comfy.
Never did.
I'm just useless.
You're supposed to say,
"No, you're not."
Ah, it must be the alignment...
What's wrong?
Well, I dunno, I mean it can't be
the lens cos I was looking at Orion,
the constellation of Orion.
You take a look.
Now, tell me, what can you see?
- Where?
- Well, up there, in the sky!
Well, I can't see anything.
It's just black.
Well, I mean it's working.
The telescope is working.
Well...
- maybe it's the clouds.
- There's no clouds.
- Well, there must be!
- There's not!
It was there, an entire constellation.
Look!
Look there.
They're going out.
Oh, my God!
Donna, the stars are going out.
I'm ready.
Loadstone testing now at 15.4,
repeat 15.4.
- Ma'am.
- I've told you, don't salute.
Well, if you're not going
to tell us your name...
What, you don't know either?
I've crossed too many different
realities. Trust me, the wrong word
in the wrong place can change
an entire causal nexus.
She talks like that. A lot.
And you must be... Miss Noble.
Donna.
Captain Erisa Magambo.
Thank you for this.
- I don't even know what I'm doing.
- Is it awake?
Seems to be quiet, today.
Ticking over.
Like it's waiting.
D'you want to see it?
What's a "police box"?
They salvaged it from underneath
the Thames. Just go inside.
- What for?
- Just go in.
No way!
What d'you think?
Can I have a coffee?
Time And Relative Dimension in Space.
This room used to shine with light.
I think it's dying.
It's still trying to help.
And... it belonged to the Doctor?
He was a Time Lord. Last of his kind.
But if he was so special,
what was he doing with me?
He thought you were brilliant.
- Don't be stupid.
- But you are.
It just took the Doctor to show you
that, simply by being with him.
He did the same to me,
to everyone he touches.
Were you and him...?
- D'you want to see it?
- No.
Go on, then.
We don't know how the TARDIS works,
but we've managed to scrape off
the surface technology,
enough to show you the creature.
It's a creature?
Just stand here.
Out of the circle, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Can't you stay with me?
Ready?
And... activate.
- Open your eyes, Donna.
- Is it there?
Open your eyes. Look at it.
- I can't.
- It's part of you, Donna. Look.
It's OK, it's OK, it's OK, calm down!
Donna, Donna, Donna! OK.
What is it?
We don't know.
Oh... thanks!
It feeds off time.
By changing time, by making
someone's life take a different turn,
like, er, meetings never made,
children never born,
a life never loved.
- But with you it's...
- I never did anything important.
Yes, you did. One day, that thing
made you turn right, instead of left.
- When was that?
- You wouldn't remember.
It was the most ordinary day
in the world. But by turning right,
you never met the Doctor. And the whole
world just changed around you.
Can you get rid of it?
No, I can't even touch it.
Seems to be in a state of flux.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Sort of thing the Doctor would say.
You liar!
You told me I was special.
But it's not me,
it's this thing, I'm just a host!
No, there's more than that...
The readings are strange.
It's like reality is just
bending around you.
Because of this thing!
No, no, we're getting
separate readings from you.
And they've always been there,
since the day you were born.
This is not relevant to the mission.
I thought it was just
the Doctor we needed,
but it's the both of you.
The Doctor and Donna Noble. Together.
To stop the stars from going out.
Why?
What can I do?
Turn it off!
Please.
- Captain.
- Power down.
It's still there, though.
What can I do...
to get rid of it?
You're going to travel in time!
The TARDIS has tracked down the moment
of intervention, Monday the 25th,
10:01 in the morning.
Your car was on Little Sutton, leading
to Ealing Road, but you turned right,
heading for Griffin's Parade.
You need to turn left.
You've got to go back,
turn left. Got that, Donna?
At 10:01, make yourself turn left,
heading for the Chiswick High Road.
Keep the jacket on at all times it's
insulation against temporal feedback.
This will correspond to
local time wherever you land.
This is to combat dehydration.
This is where we leave you.
Don't want to see that thing on my back.
No, the mirrors are just incidental.
They bounce chronon
energy back into the centre,
which we control
and decide the destination.
It's a time machine.
If you could...
Powering up!
- How d'you know it's gonna work?
- Hmm?
Oh, we... we don't.
We're... we're just guessing.
Brilliant!
Just remember,
when you get to the junction,
change the car's direction
by one minute past ten.
- How do I do that?
- It's up to you.
Well... I'll just have to...
run up to myself and...
have a good argument.
- I'd like to see that.
- Activate lodestone.
Good luck.
- I'm ready!
- One minute past ten.
Cos I understand now!
You said I was gonna die, but...
you mean this whole world,
it's gonna blink out of existence...
but that's not dying,
cos a better world takes its place.
The Doctor's world!
And I'm still alive!
That's right, isn't it?
I don't die. If I change things,
I don't die. That's...
that's right, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
But I can't die!
I've got a future!
With the Doctor, you told me!
Activate!
But...
Hold on... But this is...
I'm not...
This is Sutton Court!
I'm half a mile away!
I'M HALF A MILE AWAY!
Four minutes.
Oh, my God!
Jival Chowdry,
he runs that little photocopy
business in Merchant Street
and he needs a secretary.
I've got a job!
HC Clements is in the city.
It's nice, it's posh,
so stop it!
It won't take long,
just turn right.
I'm going left, if you don't like it,
get out and walk!
You think I'm so useless.
Oh, I know why you want
a job with HC Clements, lady.
Cos you think you'll meet a man.
I'm not gonna get there.
You're gonna die.
City executives don't need
temps, except for practice.
Yeah.
Suppose you're right.
Please.
Can you hear that?
- Oh, no! Go back!
- Oi! Get a move on!
- The traffic's stopping.
- Something must've happened.
Tell him this.
Two words.
Well, that decides it.
I'm not sitting in a traffic jam.
I'm going left! I'm going left!
Left... left... left...
Left...
Left... left...
What the hell is that?!
You were so strong.
What are you?
What will you be?
Everything all right?
Oh, God...!
What was that for?!
I don't know!
Can't remember.
It's slipping away.
You know, like when you think
of a dream, and it sort of goes.
Just got lucky, this thing.
It's one of the Trickster's Brigade.
Changes a life in tiny little ways.
Most times, the universe just
compensates around it, but with you...
great big parallel world!
Hold on, you said
parallel worlds are sealed off.
They are.
But you had one created around you.
Funny thing is...
seems to be happening a lot. To you.
How d'you mean?
Well, the Library. Then this.
Just goes with the job, I suppose.
Sometimes I think there's way
too much coincidence around you, Donna.
I met you once. Then I met
your grandfather. Then I met you again.
In the whole wide universe,
I met you for a second time.
It's like something's
binding us together.
Don't be so daft.
I'm nothing special.
Yes, you are, you're brilliant.
He thought you were brilliant.
SHE said that.
Who did?
That woman.
I can't remember...
She never existed, now.
No, but she said...
The stars...
She said the stars are going out.
- Yeah, but that world's gone.
- No, but she said it was all worlds.
Every world.
She said the darkness is coming.
- Even here.
- Who was she?
- I don't know.
- What did she look like?
She was...
blonde.
What was her name?
- I don't know.
- Donna, what was her name?
But she told me...
to warn you.
She said... two words.
What two words? What were they?
What did she say?
"Bad Wolf."
What does it mean?
Doctor, what is it?
What's Bad Wolf?
It's the end of the universe.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are at war.
- It can't be.
- There's nothing I can do.
- Oh, my God!
- What is it, who are they?
What are we going to do?
It's impossible.
It can't be!
I'm sorry, we're dead.
Doctor, come back!
It's only just beginning.
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~