Hikers aren't supposed to let
their dogs off the leash back here.
But I'm pretty sure the dog was running free
when he found the... what he found.
- What's the condition of the body?
- No idea.
- Can't get close enough to examine it.
- Why not?
- The dog's definitely not on his leash at this time.
- [Dog Growling]
- Oh.
- Put down the bone.
[Booth]
How the hell are we gonna get to the body?
- Buddy, drop it.
- You don't see that every day.
Sent for animal control.
Take another hour though.
Drop it now! I'm so sorry.
He's never done anything like this.
You ever have a dog, Bones?
- I always wanted a pig.
- A pig?
Very smart, and despite the popular
misconception, very clean.
I prefer my pig with a little mint,
a little honey glaze...
Not funny. In some cultures,
dogs can guard corpses...
sometimes to the point of starvation,
so shoot it.
I'm not shooting him for just
doing what comes naturally.
As far as he's concerned,
you know, finder's keepers.
That dog is compromising the integrity
of my remains, so wing it... him.
[Booth]
There's another way, Bones.
Dogs love me.
Nice doggy.
Good pooch.
Ah! Nice doggy.
- [Barking]
- Oh! Hey, we're just gonna wait for animal control.
- I'll do it. [Whistles]
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah. A pinecone's really gonna work.
- Buddy! Buddy!
- Okay.
- Come back here!
I need everybody to clear the area.
Set up a perimeter.
Clear the area!
Let's set up a perimeter.
- And tell animal control I'll need that bone back.
- Right.
First thing I'll do
when they get here.
[Brennan]
Victim was female, late teens.
Blonde. Cause of death looks like
blunt trauma to the back of the skull.
- She was buried facedown.
- What's that, some satanic hoo-ha?
My Uncle Preston wants to be buried
standing up without a casket.
Pupal casings and insect remains suggest
she was buried out there seven to 10 years ago.
Placement of wrists and ankles
suggest she was bound.
Residue on the medial malleolus
might tell us what restraints were used.
- Look at that.
- Wear to her right lateral
epicondyle and rotator cuff.
Also, repetitive motion damage
to the lower lumbar vertebrae.
- What's that mean?
- Golf?
Hi, Angela.
You look great today.
Thanks, Hodgie.
This is my " boho, rocker, artist...
midweek,
take-a-deep-breath-and-pout" look.
Hodgie?
Uh, I did a facial reconstruction...
extrapolating skin tone
from hair color.
For the record, I hate
the guy who killed this girl...
and I hope to hell
he burns in all eternity.
- That our victim?
- I found flecks of black enamel paint in the wound.
- Shape suggests a tire iron.
- Tire iron.
[Screams]
Tire iron.
Hands and feet bound, buried facedown.
Epps.
Hello?
New team member in the room.
Howard Epps,
a serial killer on death row.
- Killed at least three.
- We found two of'em last year.
Thejudge stayed his execution
to try him on the new charges.
You saved his life. Ironic.
The time frame fits.
This girl would've been killed...
about six months before
Epps went to prison.
- Run her through the database, get an I.D.
- Why don't you just ask him?
Because last time Bones saw Epps,
it got violent.
- You'll be there to protect her.
- She's not the one who needs protecting.
Bones broke his wrist.
He touched me with his creepy
serial killer hands.
Better not take Dr. Brennan.
[Door Buzzing]
Agent Booth.
What took you so long?
And where's Dr. Brennan?
Who's this?
Oh! That's right.
You're chained.
[Chuckles]
How about removing these shackles?
The name, Howie.
The name.
You know...
those hack doctors
at the prison infirmary...
did a miserable job
setting my wrist.
It aches all the time, and I don't have
a full range of movement.
And let me tell you, when you're stuck
in a prison cell for 23 hours a day...
there's really only one thing
you can do to pass the time.
And I need my wrist.
Well, I'm sure Dr. Brennan
would be happy to re-break it for you.
- What's that?
- What, these?
These are crime scene photos,
the ones you like.
Tell you what.
You, uh...
You tell me the girl's name,
I'll, uh, let you take a look.
Everything you need to win the game
is right there in front of you.
Game?
[Scoffs]
You're bored, huh?
Are you playing us?
When Dr. Brennan figures it out,
come and see me again.
But bring your lady scientist.
Otherwise, I don't say a word.
Next time you see
either one of us...
they'll be giving you
a lethal injection.
- Classic game theory.
Throwing down of the gauntlet.
- What?
Conflict of interest arises
followed by a series of moves...
- from which divergent strategies can be discerned.
- What did he say?
- Epps is playing us.
- Yes. That's exactly what I said.
Zero sum, obviously. After a few moves,
we'll know Epps's order of preference.
- What did he say?
- We'll find out what Epps wants.
Look, I already know what he wants.
I told you.
- He wants Bones sitting across the table from him.
- Three rational players.
- Me, Booth and Epps.
What about the nondeliberative agent?
- What did she say?
In a game, there tends to be
one "N" rational players...
and a nonconscious,
nondeliberative agent.
What did Epps talk about before he said all
the information you needed was in front of you?
Mom, Bones, blondes, his wrist
being set badly after Bones broke it.
And, um, you know, he...
he made the point that
he really needed his wrist.
Chronic masturbation.
The game may be all about
self-gratification.
The phrase he used was
"right in front of us."
- Yes.
- The blonde is right in front of us.
And she has a wrist.
Well, two, in fact.
- If you had a pet pig, what would you name him?
- Jasper.
- Oh.
- This wrist looks completely normal.
Here.
The right hamate bone.
Hamate?
The whole coloration is off.
It's slightly greasy compared
to the surrounding bone.
It's about an eighth of an inch bigger
than the same bone on the other side.
This hamate bone does not belong
with these remains.
It belongs with a second body.
There's another victim
out there somewhere.
Round one goes to Howard Epps.
- Why?
- Because he gets what he wants.
Me in the room with him.
- Who's that?
- Oh, that is, uh, Caroline Epps.
- Howard's sister?
- Uh, no.
- Howard's wife.
- Well, he didn't have a wife last year.
Well, they got married
about four months ago.
Heads up, Bones. It's our turn
to visit the psychotic murderous maniac...
Bastard.
Hi, Mrs. Epps.
I'm Special Agent Seeley Booth.
- This is Dr. Brennan.
- Oh, Agent Booth.
Howard's told me you both
saved his life last year.
- It was our pleasure.
- What? I was disappointed.
Extending Howard's life
has given him time...
to come to grips with what he's done...
to ask God for forgiveness.
Then we did the right thing
by having his execution stayed.
- Are you on some kind of medication?
- Bones.
Dr. Brennan, I'm not one of those crazy women
who falls in love with death row killers.
Obviously,
that's exactly what you are.
If the prison ever gives you a hard time
in coming to see your husband, give me a call.
- I might be able to help.
- Thank you, Agent Booth.
- Are you serious? She's crazy.
- Chop-chop. Let's go.
- Thank you. Nice to see you.
- Nice to meet you both.
- Why were you nice to her?
- Because we might need her.
Ah. Dr. Brennan.
You came.
I got your message.
We're analyzing the wrist bone right now.
We just met your wife.
- She seems very nice.
- Caroline's a hairdresser.
[Door Buzzing]
I'm glad you came.
I hope you come back
after you analyze the bone.
Caroline's the best
I could do in here.
Yeah, not your usual type, Howie.
I mean, not young, not blonde.
- Not dead.
- Bones, could you please shut up?
- Excuse me?
- Is this why you duct-tape their mouths?
Because that I understand.
That's the lamest attempt
at bonding I have ever seen.
[Sniffing]
You smell that?
What?
My stinky effort to bond?
Antiseptic.
My mother smelled like that.
Obsessed with germs.
She washed her hands with ammonia.
Mine too.
My one regret...
I didn't make her my first victim.
- Put her under a little stone cross years ago.
- Okay.
- "Okay" what?
- [Door Opens]
Don't be mad at me, Bones.
My telling you to shut up was a ploy.
- Now he thinks you're an idiot.
- Game theory, Bones, okay?
For two players to gain
advantage over the one...
they must be distinct
from each other.
- Where'd you get that?
- From me. I suggested that you be the smart one.
Which, you know, left me making
a ploy that was supposed to be lame.
- Don't enjoy this.
- What?
The only reason I am playing his game is
to discover the identity of this young woman.
Well, we've made
no progress on that.
Check the junior golf leagues.
Given the amount of wear
to her shoulder, elbow and spine...
she must've started golfing
at an early age.
I found minute traces of gypsum
and selenium on the mystery wrist bone.
Also, phenolphthalein,
which is a kind oflaxative.
Laxatives show up in bones?
No, not even after years of ingestion.
The laxative is on the surface of the bone.
l-I have no explanation.
We have scoured every inch of her,
X-rayed her, run her through an M.R.I.
- What clue are we missing?
- The laxative is the one thing that makes no sense.
Last time, it was masturbation.
Did he reference bowel movements?
He mentioned his mother
was a germophobe...
scrubbing his hands
with ammonia...
- Ammonia.
- Ammonia. Oh! Why didn't you say so?
Ammonia?
Booth thinks we should get together
and buy Brennan a pet.
- What kind of a pet?
- A pig.
And I don't think he means a guinea pig.
A real pig.
Like a Mulefoot, Saddleback,
or pot belly.
You wanna expose a piece of
crucial evidence to ammonia gas? No.
Besides being a laxative,
phenolphthalein is a sensitive pH indicator.
Colorless unless
it's exposed to ammonia.
The second you expose this bone, it's useless.
Epps wants you to destroy evidence.
Why would he want us
to destroy evidence he planted?
Why would he plant
evidence at all?
It might be a win-win
scenario for him.
lfhis endgame is to disorient
Dr. Brennan, he can do that...
by ruining evidence
that he himself planted.
Fine.
You can perform the experiment.
So, glasses.
- [Saroyan] What is that?
- Not sure.
A Freemason symbol?
Hey, this explains
the "buried facedown" thing.
Oh, it's all starting
to come together.
These crossed hammers prove that Epps is
working for the top level of the Illuminati.
That's the cartographic symbol
for a mine.
Oh.
Epps is telling us that the second victim's
in a mine? What kind of mine?
One that contains
gypsum and selenium.
[Brennan]
In prison, Epps mentioned a stone cross.
That's what we should
be looking for inside.
Okay. This is the only
abandoned gypsum mine...
within Epps's known killing ground
to also contain selenium.
Six entrances, hundreds of shafts,
and half of it's flooded.
All right. You just follow my lead and
watch yourself in there, okay? Thank you.
I don't think Epps would
make it that hard for us.
Yeah, well, Epps said he wished
he'd buried his mother under a stone cross.
I bet that is a hint.
Okay, people, listen up!
- I'm calling in a "splunking" team.
- Spelunking.
Spelunking team with imaging capabilities
to look for a stone cross.
Until they get here,
let's focus on the ventilation shafts...
Hold on...
to the west of the main shafts...
What? Oh.
Never mind.
Can we get some light
down this shaft, please?
- It's the cross, Booth.
- That is, uh, definitely a cross.
- Will you help me move these?
- Move what?
- The rocks.
- [Grunts]
Bones! Oh!
Oh!
[Sighs]
Well, it's definitely human, but...
- What?
- Well, Cam can be more precise...
but I don't think
this is more than a week old.
Epps has been in prison
for seven years...
which means he has an accomplice
killing people...
on the outside.
God, I wonder
how many more there are.
This is where
the hamate bone was taken.
The victim is female, mid-teens.
Extensive contusions
around the ankles.
Yes, and bone damage too.
Hip displacement,
elongation of the spine.
[Screams]
- He hung her upside down.
- I agree.
And while she was still alive too.
Is that part of Epps's M. O?
- No.
- So his accomplice threw in some flair of his own.
Nine years ago,
Epps killed someone and buries her.
He goes to jail seven years ago.
Last week,
his accomplice kills another girl...
and swapped wrist bones with
the girl Epps buried nine years ago.
[Brennan]
How do they communicate?
Inmates are allowed phone calls,
visitors, letters.
- But those are all monitored.
- He has a wife.
Look at this. It's a burn.
Cigarette, probably.
And there's this.
It was jammed in her shoe.
What? She wasn't wearing it?
The, uh, mine victim's dental work...
identifies her as Sarah Koskoff,
Bethesda, Maryland.
Disappeared three weeks ago.
- Sixteen years old.
- Sarah Koskoff.
She fits Epps's victim profile perfectly.
[Phone Ringing]
- Brennan.
- [Booth] Yeah, Bones, it's me.
Listen, I talked to
Sarah Koskoff's parents.
They said her dream was to own her own beauty
shop. She worked for a hair salon in the city.
- Don't tell me.
- Yep. "M" Salon, Cleveland Park.
- Owned by Caroline Mapother.
- Now known as Caroline Epps.
You know, you remember when I was
nice to her and you weren't? This is why.
Thank you.
Hi.
- Is-Is Howard okay?
- Howard's fine, Mrs. Epps.
You don't have
to worry about anything.
I couldn't help but notice
the "Help Wanted" sign in the window.
Did you recently lose
one of your employees?
It's, uh, hard to keep help
that doesn't steal from you.
Sarah Koskoff steal from you?
No. Why?
What did she do?
She died.
You know, I'm afraid
I'm gonna have to ask you...
but when was the last time
you saw her?
Uh, three weeks ago.
She just stopped coming to work.
She... She died?
Did you ever, uh, talk
to Howard about her?
- Uh, I don't know. Maybe.
- Howard ever see a picture of Sarah?
l-I don't like this.
What's going on?
She was found buried facedown
in an abandoned mine.
Back of her head bashed in,
wrists, ankles tied.
Your husband's M.O.
Poor Sarah.
But Howard...
Howard has been in prison
for the last seven years.
How could he kill anyone?
He has an accomplice.
- You think it's me?
- You love your husband.
I love the good in Howard.
I reject the evil.
We're going to have a child together.
I've petitioned the court
to let Howard donate.
Yeah.
[Clears Throat]
I have a search warrant here
for your home and your shop.
You don't need a search warrant.
You can look anywhere you want,
because you won't find anything.
[Booth] Sarah Koskoff was hung
upside down before she was killed.
That suggests the torture route.
And I was hoping it was in
the basement of a beauty salon.
But, uh, my agents,
they didn't find anything.
- What's that?
- Religious medal.
- Sarah had it in her possession.
- Saint Agnes.
Patron saint of young women...
especially those
who remain pure.
How do you know all that?
I'm Catholic, Bones.
- "S.A.H.S."
- Yeah, St. Agnes High School.
Except I think Sarah Koskoff
went to public school. Oh, God.
What?
What does that mean?
It means I have to go talk to a nun.
We have no student at St. Agnes
named Sarah Koskoff.
Maybe she's a friend
of one of your girls.
As soon as you called me last night...
we implemented a telephone tree
asking precisely that question.
- No response.
- Do the names Howard Epps...
Caroline Epps, Caroline Mapother
mean anything to you?
May I have the keyboard?
Yes, Sister. Yeah, of course. Here.
[Chuckles]
I need to enter a password.
Oh, yeah.
I'll be right over here.
I'm Catholic.
l-I go to mass every Sunday.
Well, almost every Sunday.
I'm very trustworthy.
Nobody by any of those names.
I feel that I have been very patient...
in regard
to not asking what this is about.
Oh, yeah.
Murder victim.
Ayoung girl was found
with this religious medal.
Helen Majors.
Helen Majors?
Who's that?
This golden medal...
is given to the Holy Spirit Award winner
every year.
I presented this medal
to Helen Majors myself.
May we please see Helen Majors?
Talk to her?
Helen left school three days ago.
No one has seen her since.
Three days ago,
Helen had that medal.
Yesterday, we found it with
Sarah Koskoff's dead body.
It's possible Helen is still alive.
- We have Caroline Epps under surveillance.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
- I hate this.
- All right.
- Booth.
- I don't want to find that girl's
remains in some mine, Booth.
Reiner Hatin?
Address.
7408 Haskell Street, Cleveland Park.
Uh, 22705 to Control.
I'm en route to possible
H.R.T. incident at 7408 Haskell Street.
- Requesting backup.
- [Man On Radio] Affirmative, 22705.
- 7408 Haskell.
- What?
Epps's prison letters log
show in the last year...
he wrote six letters to a man by the name
of Reiner Hatin at that address.
Caroline Epps might not be
Epps's accomplice after all.
- What are you doing?
- Where's the siren on this thing?
- Don't touch...
- [Siren Wailing]
- Okay, Bones, I'm going in.
You're gonna wait outside.
- Booth...
No, I don't wanna hear it. When backup arrives,
tell 'em there's a federal agent inside.
- Which one is it?
- [Clears Throat]
- [Sirens Wailing]
- Great. A vacant lot.
I tried to tell you.
[Door Buzzing]
Did you hear?
I'm gonna be a father.
The judge granted our petition
for artificial insemination.
When I make my donation to the baby bank,
I'm gonna be thinking about you.
- Who's Reiner Hatin?
- Oh, Reiner.
[Speaking German]
The letters were addressed
to a vacant lot.
I must've written the address down wrong.
I'm slightly dyslexic, you know.
Hey, come here. You know,
I really enjoyed playing your game.
Now, you know what?
There is a girl out there...
hanging upside down
with duct tape over her mouth!
Booth, let him go.
Let him go!
For all your faults, Mr. Epps...
you were never interested
in letting your victims suffer.
You didn't torture them.
You're not that kind of man.
She's an innocent child.
She's a young woman...
and there's no such thing
as an innocent woman.
Look within yourself.
You know I'm right.
You know, I'm just guessing here,
you understand, but I think you'll find that...
Helen Majors has less
than 24 hours to live.
Better get going.
Sorry.
[Laughing]
- What are you asking me for?
- You said you've dealt with
manipulative men before.
Sweetie, this is a psycho killer...
not some loser who wants you
to cosign a loan for his Jet Ski.
Epps is pushing me around, Ange.
He's in control. I hate that.
You know...
Epps is acting
kind of like a boyfriend.
[Chuckles]
What?
Well, you obviously fascinate him.
He can't have you,
and he can't kill you.
- So he wants to make you hate yourself.
- God, Ange.
What kind of boyfriends
have you had?
Let's keep the focus
on you and Epps, okay?
Okay.
Epps knows that you'll
never forgive yourself...
if you don't find Helen Majors
before she's murdered.
Not only is Helen being tortured,
but her family must be in agony.
You see?
This is what he's doing.
He's putting pictures
in your mind.
He's messing with
your objectivity.
There's nothing
I can do about that.
You have to step back, okay?
Let the rest of us deal with the families.
You find Helen. That'll keep Epps
from getting a Jet Ski outta you.
Bones. Caroline Epps...
not an accomplice.
- She was at work when
Helen Majors was kidnapped.
- [Speaking German]
- Yeah, whatever.
- It means " old friend with
similar tastes" in German.
Oh, no. Epps telling us
the name of his accomplice?
- That's too easy.
- Well, if it's too easy, then why can't we find him?
You know what?
He talked about impregnating Caroline.
What is with Caroline Epps? I mean,
why have a child with a monster like him?
What is she gonna tell the child when it
grows up? "Hi. Your daddy's a monster."
Look. Time out.
You gotta detach from this, all right?
- We let Epps get under our skin,
it's exactly what he wants.
- Zack was right.
Epps is trying to break us. Not only
did we save his life, but he is still killing.
I found traces of ethylene oxide...
and high levels of an antibacterial agent
on Sarah's ankles.
Also, polymer residue found in
Polygenex latex glove liners...
used by people who handle
toxic substances.
- Airport screeners, cops...
- Wait. Prison guards?
Lauren Hathaway was a nationally ranked
junior golfer in 1997.
Yeah, it's Booth.
I need to know if Howard Epps...
ever had a prison guard
by the name of Reiner Hatin.
She disappeared on May 9...
after leaving the Southampton Country Club
in Raleigh, North Carolina.
Check and see if
any guard changed his name.
"Reiner" is German for "pure."
Epps has a thing about that.
Translate the name and see if that comes back
in any form. Then get back to me.
- This the victim from the park?
- Her father is in your office.
- What?
- Why didn't you say that?
- You were on the phone.
- Booth.
I can't do this one.
Maybe Angela can help.
All right.
I'll take care of it.
My wife died five years
after Lauren disappeared.
I think because
she just gave up hope.
Part of me is glad
she's not here today for this.
We're sorry for your loss, Mr. Hathaway.
For both your losses.
When Lauren disappeared, the police
originally suspected her golf coach.
Yes. He'd had an affair with
one of his students the year before.
Ironically, his alibi was that
he was with another student.
- Does the name Reiner Hatin
mean anything to you?
- No.
Do you recognize this man?
No.
I'm not helping, am I?
That photograph is current.
Here are some drawings that show...
what he might've looked like
10 years ago.
Mmm.
Yes. That one.
He was a greenskeeper at the club.
He helped us load the car one day.
I remember because he told Lauren she looked
just like his mother when she was young.
It was an odd thing to say.
I told the police about it when she
disappeared. Why didn't they arrest him?
Caroline Epps.
She knows something.
- She just won't talk to me.
- Why?
- I'm a man last time I checked.
- But she'll talk to a woman?
- That's my thinking.
- Fine. I'll do it.
Oh, no. You can't sarcasm it out of her.
You have to connect.
- You don't wanna send Brennan?
- No. Angela.
Angela's an artist,
an expert in 3-D reconstruction.
- Well, unlike you and Bones, Angela is, uh...
- What?
She's better with the living
than she is the dead.
- Fine. I'll go tell her
what she's just volunteered for.
- Thank you.
Thanks for coming.
I've told your people everything I know.
I don't see the point of this.
I know this is disturbing.
lfind it very upsetting...
and I'm not married
to the man who did it.
I love Howard,
Miss Montenegro.
I believe you.
No one's ever said that to me.
I think you'd have to love him very much
to be willing to overlook what he's done.
Done in the past.
The thing is, we're not so sure
that it was in the past.
For Howard,
it's obvious what he likes.
- Blonde girls.
- Not me, you mean.
Men can't hide what they like.
For Howard, it's this.
Men can change
what they look at.
Does Howard ever just look at you as though
you just feel his eyes adoring you?
He...
He asks for magazines, DVDs.
He's... He's very specific.
He likes blonde girls.
[Chuckles]
Always the blonde girls.
M-Maybe if I...
if I dyed my hair...
I'm sorry.
I have to ask you something.
Have you ever delivered
any messages for Howard?
- Don't you miss them?
- I'm sorry?
I wrote the message
"Don't you miss them?"...
on a... on a... on a piece of paper
and slipped it into a mailbox.
Whose mailbox?
Um, a man named Henry Gerber
who Howard knew from prison.
Howard calls Henry "The Mad German."
When did you deliver the message?
F... Five days ago.
Thank you.
Can... Can...
Will you sit with me
just a moment longer?
I'm... I have to make a phone call.
You understand?
But after that,
I'll sit with you as long as you like.
- F.B.I. Hands in the air. That's it.
- [Woman Moaning On TV]
Now move over there slowly.
Ah! Keep your hands where I can see 'em.
- I can't do both.
- Booth.
Easy.
[Moaning On TVContinues]
- Where's Henry Gerber?
- I'm Henry Gerber.
There is no way a man in a wheelchair
could have killed Sarah Koskoff...
or swapped hamate bones
with Lauren Hathaway.
All right, Epps got us again, huh?
Gerber's paralyzed from the waist down...
because Epps knifed him
just before he was paroled.
So, what? His message
"Don't you miss them?" meant what, his legs?
Epps is good.
Not morally, of course.
But it's a classic feint-and-parry misdirect
delivered via his wife.
He gets off on screwing
with people's lives.
- Where are we on Reiner Hatin?
- Nowhere.
I had some thoughts. Perhaps the point
isn't that German is a different language...
but that it's actually
a different language.
- Great. Thanks, Zack, for being so helpful.
- Go on.
More broadly speaking, I mean, like
an anagram or an inner or secret language.
These are phrases I found in English.
Perhaps in German...
No, the whole German thing was a ruse.
If it's anywhere, it's here.
"Rant Herein I."
You know, like inner schizophrenic voices.
"A re Inner Hit" could mean...
I don't really do
the poetry thing.
"Neither Rain." No.
"Neither rain nor sleet nor dead of night."
- The postal service motto.
- Hey, the guy's all about sending messages.
Mail to an empty lot.
Messages dropped in mail slots.
Postal workers wear
Polygenex gloves.
Who received the letters
Epps sent to that empty lot?
[Man] Letters with an invalid address and
no return address go to the dead letter office.
- Who has access?
- Uh, sorting staff and the
mail carrier for that route.
Stream us a route which includes
7408 Haskell Street, Cleveland Park, right?
Yes. But there is no
7408 Haskell Street.
Got it.
Hey, that's Caroline Epps's beauty salon.
That's St. Agnes High School.
The killer picked his victims
from a postal route.
- Tell us the name of the mail carrier.
- I can do better than that.
All I ask is that when this goes to the press,
nobody uses the word "disgruntled."
I'm so sorry.
He's never done anything like this.
- Booth.
- Yeah, I got him.
- What?
- That's the guy who found the first body.
Found it because he knew
where it was buried. Let's go.
- [Barking]
- Oh!
Whoa.
Oh, great. Him again.
I'll need a pinecone.
Listen, dog, I will shoot you in the head
if you don't cut it out right now!
[Whines]
Oh.
- Oh.
- God.
I hate the serial killer
wall of death.
This is Sarah Koskoff.
- Helen Majors.
- They were so young, so innocent.
And Lauren Hathaway.
Southampton Country Club.
That's where Epps and his accomplice met.
- Lappin maintained the golf carts.
- [Cell Phone Dialing]
He's winning, Bones. All right?
We're this close to saving Helen Majors's life.
- We're running out of time.
- [Hodgins On Phone] Yeah?
Hodgins, it's me. Is there anything you can
tell us about where Sarah Koskoff was held...
before her body was
dumped in the gypsum mine?
The only substance I can't explain
is ethylene oxide.
What about the ethylene oxide
plus the antibacterial agents?
It could be a lot of things.
I'll set up a statistical model,
give you four or five scenarios.
There is no time.
A girl's life is at stake here.
Just give me
your best guess right now.
I can't just guess!
I have a process!
What if I guess and the girl dies?
- No. No way!
- All right. Just simmer down, Hodgins.
We're all just trying to do our best
in this situation right now.
- Jack.
- Hodgins, are you still there?
Hey.
Pretend it's me asking, okay?
Look, we're just exchanging theories here
at work like always.
Two substances, right?
Put them in the same place at the same time.
- Either they mean something or they don't.
- Hodgins, you there, buddy?
- Yeah. Just give me a second, please.
- We don't have a second.
Booth, do you think you could just
stop talking, please?
Okay. All right.
Uh, antibacterial agents.
And, uh, he...
He's a postal worker.
- Okay.
- Uh...
What else, Jack?
- Anthrax.
- Anthrax?
After the anthrax attacks in 2001,
the post office shut down several sorting centers.
Okay.
All right.
Tell me.
Uh, they used ethylene oxide
and this antibacterial agent to...
That's how they cleaned 'em.
Not all of'em reopened.
So it's possible Sarah was kept
at an abandoned sorting center?
Yes.
Yes, it is.
I knew you'd come through for me, buddy.
Good work.
Whew.
All right.
- Here.
- I didn't even have to ask.
Yeah, well,
just be careful, all right?
Don't shoot me.
Don't shoot Helen Majors.
- Otherwise...
- [Chains Rattling]
[Sobbing Quietly]
Please?
- [Booth] Helen?
- Please... Please help me.
All right. Okay.
Take it easy. I got you.
I got you. I got you, all right?
Where is he?
He just left.
I don't know where he went.
Bones, stay here with her.
Stay right there.
Don't leave me.
Please don't leave me.
[Grunting]
[Gunshot]
[Groaning]
Is he dead?
Yeah, he's dead.
[Groans]
God!
I had to shoot him.
Yeah.
I'm glad you did.