[Gunshot]
# [Alternative Rock]
# [Ends]
Mr. Addy,
your dissertation is entitled...
"Analysis of Bone Trauma."
When viewed in cross section,
the pressure and force...
exerted by the weapon can be assessed.
Obtaining the cross section
will compromise the original bone.
My technique preserves
bone surface morphology...
through the use
of polyvinyl replication.
A transparent positive is made
by covering the impression...
with an aqueous solution
of synthetic polymer.
Hey, Bones. Come on. We got a body.
Went up like a Roman candle.
- Hey, Zack. How's it going?
- So far, they don't like me.
- Shocker. Let's go.
- [Brennan] I'm in the middle of something.
You know, real-life murder and mutilation
versus academic claptrap, no contest.
- Sorry. No offense.
- This committee can carry on
without you, Dr. Brennan.
- Zack, just answer the questions.
- [Booth] Yeah.
[Booth]
Okay, come on.
Next question?
How do you expect anyone
to take you seriously...
as a working forensic anthropologist...
when you look the way you do?
What?
- [Brennan] Male, middle-aged.
- What was with Zack back there?
Defending his dissertation.
Last step before he gets his doctorate.
I think these are what's left
of his intestines.
- Is he gonna make it?
- No. He's very dead. [Chuckles]
- I mean Zack.
- Ah, 50-50.
- He's a stoolie.
- Zack?
Our victim.
No, he's a rat, a snitch.
- What makes you say that?
- His guts got spilled.
- You know, spill your guts.
- Very literal.
Hung up there like a scarecrow on a rooftop of
a hotel used to house witnesses. It's a warning.
There's something jammed
down his trachea.
[Zack] I rectified their erroneous assumptions
concerning polyvinyl replication.
You corrected them?
- Only when they were wrong.
- [Chuckles]
Are the remains
ready for X-ray?
Yes. Maybe we'll get lucky and I.D.
the poor bastard that way.
Oh, wejust got lucky.
"My name is Garrett Delaney."
There's something metallic here.
This is gonna turn out to be some
freaky, weird ritualistic thing, isn't it?
Oh, man, I hope so.
Christopher Columbus.
- Where's Dr. Brennan?
- Her brother came for a visit.
Dad called you?
You're sure it was him?
He said, " You and your sister
are in danger," and he hung up.
I spend half my time with a sniper-trained
F.B.I. agent. I feel safe.
Tempe, I know someone
is watching me.
- What's your evidence?
- I can feel it on the back of my neck.
You spend some time in jail,
you develop a sixth sense.
- Maybe you should stay with me for a few days.
- Tempe, I have work.
- I have Amy and the girls.
- What about your sixth sense?
- Hey!
- What?
You can't not believe
in something one second...
- and then use it against me in the next.
- It's a long drive.
You could start fresh tomorrow.
And I've got...
cold beer in the fridge.
Don't drink the Moroccan beer.
Tastes like ear wax. How you doing, Russell?
- Okay, Booth. You? Good?
- Yeah. Good.
I still make him nervous, don't I?
Come on. Let's go.
Why do I always feel
like you're abducting me?
[Booth] Yeah. It turns out our corpse
is a former F.B.I. agent.
Garrett Delaney, he left the F.B.I.
about 15 years ago.
He's now head of security of
some big K Street lobbyist.
So why'd he end up
a human torch?
That's what we're here
to find out.
His place is much better than yours.
Ten times better.
I told you he left public service.
He makes, uh, more money than I.
So that's all your dad said, huh?
- Is you're in danger?
- Yes.
- And Russ's sixth sense agrees.
- What are you doing?
I've been practicing some
of the black ops stuff you taught me.
Let me show you.
Every F.B.I. agent in the country
is looking for my father.
Maybe he's trying
to scare us off.
Six months without a break
in the case, he ain't gonna be nervous.
- Now let me show you.
- My dad's a career criminal.
Just because he says that Russ
is in danger doesn't mean it's the truth.
Let me show you how it's done, okay?
[Kicks Door]
Oh. He might've
gotten it right this time.
[Brennan]
Russ.
These are all pictures of Russ.
Me at work, me and Amy.
This was the day before yesterday.
Dad was right.
Somebody's watching.
- This is worse than watching.
- What do you mean?
- This is hunting.
- Hunting?
As in kill. You see these?
Right here. These are ranges. He's picking out
a spot from which to shoot at you.
- So what do I do now?
- The hunter's dead. The hunt is over, right?
- Anyone else know you're here?
- Only Amy.
Great. Call Amy and tell her
if anyone calls looking for you...
she doesn't know where you're at.
You should stay with me until we find out
why Delaney intended to kill you.
- How are you gonna do that?
- By figuring out who killed him.
[Angela] This is the paper that was
pulled from Delaney's throat.
It was dated, signed, and initialed
at the bottom ofboth sides of the page.
February 1978.
It looks like a cop's notebook.
- That makes sense except...
- [Typing]
"I will not put an innocent man in prison
just because he is a political threat.
Marvin Beckett hasn't
broken any law."
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Marvin Beckett?
Back in the '60s, Marvin
Beckett was a civil rights activist.
He made his bones protesting...
African American overrepresentation
in the Vietnam War.
- In '78, he was sent to prison for life.
- Why?
He killed an F.B.I. agent
named Gus Harper.
- Wait. Augustus Harper?
- Yeah. You know the case?
"A ugust Harp."
Look. Augustus Harper.
Oh, wow.
This means Delaney's murder
has something to do...
with Marvin Beckett
going to prison.
Oh, when you're good,
you are very, very good.
1970s, Ohio.
There is a task force made up
of F.B.I., state police, and local cops.
It goes bad. Starts taking a cut from the same
bank robbers they're supposed to be catching.
Then they conspire to plan a stack
of stolen money on Marvin Beckett.
Well, then this young agent,
right, Harper, okay?
He decides he can't live with that
and decides to blow the whistle.
- I can read.
- The same guy who's gonna blow
the whistle on them...
for framing Marvin Beckett
then gets murdered by Marvin Beckett?
Come on. Talk about
killing two birds with one stone.
- Who else knows about this?
- Us and you. That's it.
- Let's keep it that way.
- Hey, I've seen this movie.
- I get killed on the way home.
- Then don't go home.
[Chuckles]
You serious?
Thirty years ago, I was married
to Gus Harper for exactly eight months.
I'm not sure I can help you.
What about the contents of the note?
What do you people want?
The truth.
The last time the F.B.I.
came to talk to me...
they told me to keep
my mouth shut...
or you won't get
your husband's death benefits.
Your husband is a good man.
And he tried to do the right thing.
And he ended up dead.
I can't let that stand.
The F.B.I. murdered Gus.
Then they had
a state funeral for him...
complete with
the grieving widow as a centerpiece.
Is this your husband's handwriting?
Yes. He was compiling evidence.
- And there was more?
- There was a diary...
a dozen audiotapes, field notes.
- And where did Gus keep it?
- Safety-deposit box.
Can you tell us where
that safety-deposit box was?
Ohio First Savings and Loan in Dayton.
Excuse me one moment.
My parents robbed
that exact bank...
just days after
Gus Harper was killed.
They were looking
for that evidence.
That has to be why Delaney
was stalking Russ.
Go home. I have a few more questions
for Barbara Harper, okay?
You go home and you be
with your brother, all right?
Okay.
- You think it's Delaney?
- [Zack] Definitely.
I hope to keep working here
when I receive my doctorate.
We'd all like that.
What did she mean when she said, " How do
you expect anyone to take you seriously?"
It's a comment on...
your deportment.
Dr. Brennan doesn't
care about deportment.
That's true.
But if you work here, you won't be
Brennan's grad student anymore.
You'll be a full-blown
forensic anthropologist.
Cam will be your boss.
In your opinion, does
deportment matter to Cam?
Let's just say that Cam's not
the kind of woman you catch...
with crusties
in the corner ofher eye.
Haley's six, and Emma's eight.
Tempe?
I'm sorry.
Preoccupied.
Tempe, if I play my cards right...
these little girls are gonna be your nieces
in the next couple months.
The least you can do
is memorize their names.
- They're cute.
- Haley has lung trouble.
They're trying to figure it out.
You ever deal with an H.M. O?
- If it's money, Russ, I can help.
- No, forget it.
If I'm gonna become these little girls' daddy,
I gotta man up for the job.
- [Knocking]
- That's not rational.
I'm a good mechanic.
I'll take care of my own.
Gus Harper's service history.
Okay?
Graduated top half of his class
in Quantico.
He was assigned to theJoint State-Federal
Bank Robbery Task Force. Right there.
- The victim.
- Back when he was Special Agent
Delaney supervising Gus Harper.
- The guy that was hunting me?
- That's right.
Okay, here's a list of the bank robbers
with their F.B.I. code names.
[Brennan]
Dad's code name was Columbus.
Yeah. Lewis, Clark...
Magellan, Cook, Columbus.
All named after explorers.
That's Mom and Dad.
- Every one of these people are deceased.
- Except for Dad.
Delaney was killed to send
a message to the F.B.I.
This Columbus coin was found
in the victim's mouth.
Columbus shot a man
in the head...
hung him from a pole...
gutted him,
and set him on fire.
And Columbus is our father.
[Russ]
Dad had it under control.
- I mean, for 15 years everything was fine until...
- Until what?
Dad left you a message.
He said, "Stop looking." You didn't.
So this is my fault?
Well, consequences
aren't the same as fault.
My parole officer
is very philosophical.
Well, all we have is a voice tape
of Dad saying, "Back off"...
and a little silver dolphin
that I found at Mom's grave.
That's as far as
the investigation has gone.
- According to Booth.
- What? Booth and I are partners.
Tempe, he's F.B.I.
You aren't.
You're the daughter of a career criminal
and the sister of a loser on parole.
What?
I wouldn't let anyone else
call you a loser, Russ.
What makes you think
you're allowed?
I love you too.
What you're asking is the kind
of thing that destroys careers.
From the time I was a little girl,
I dreamed of putting bad men in jail.
Put that back. Which is why I became
an Assistant United States Attorney.
- You don't have to help me.
- Of course I have to help you!
Marvin Beckett is still a hero
to a lot of African Americans.
Some of us never believed
he killed this F.B.I. boy.
Now you buy me breakfast, tell me you
found a way to clear his name...
release him out of wrongful incarceration
after 30 years?
I cannot walk away,
which you already know!
- Maybe you should have some more coffee.
- Of course I want more coffee.
- We have to come up with our plan of attack.
- I was thinking Judge Moran...
We should exhume Gus Harper.
See if your genius scientist partner...
can ascertain whether he died in the manner
the F.B.I. said he died 30 years ago.
- Moran's got a long...
- No. We want Kemper.
- "Hang 'em High" Kemper?
- I'm ruining my career,
I'm doing it my way, understand?
Now, take a doughnut hole.
I'm offering.
Thanks.
This was lodged in Garrett
Delaney's sinus cavity.
.22 caliber.
These dimples indicate that the bullet
ricocheted around inside the cranium.
Are you worried
about your doctorate?
No. Dr. Grayson touched me
with an open hand on the shoulder.
You mean inappropriately?
No. I read a book
on body language.
Apparently in our culture, when an older male
lays an open hand on a younger male...
it conveys approval.
But if he bumps younger male
with a closed fist, it conveys doubt.
Dr. Grayson went like this,
not like this.
Like this.
Not like this.
Dr. Grayson is elderly and arthritic.
Perhaps he simply needed help
getting to his feet like this.
Dr. Brennan, visitors in your office.
Tempe, this is a friend of Dad's.
Father Coulter is Toby Coulter,
train trestle guy.
Oh, yeah.
I remember that story.
When Dad and his friend accidentally
blew up a train trestle.
Come on. How do you accidentally
blow up a train trestle?
Well, we were hired by a farmer
to dynamite the ice offhis stock pond.
We get this competition going
who's gonna slide the dynamite...
farther across the ice
before it blows.
You know it's a federal offense
to blow up a train trestle, Father.
I mean, even if it is accidental.
Father Toby Coulter,
meet my partner, Seeley Booth.
- Careful. He's F.B.I.
- Ooh. Well, I'm innocent.
It was Max's toss that brought
the trestle down.
Max Keenan's best friend
grows up to be a priest.
I'm sure your people have
that fact on file somewhere.
Tempe, Father Coulter
has a message from Dad.
It's a private message.
Come to my office.
She's just gonna tell Agent Booth anyway.
Might as well let him listen.
"Back off."
That's the message.
- He said you'd understand.
- [Booth] Where'd you see him?
- In confession.
- We're not Catholic.
Oh, the sanctity of the confessional
is extended to all.
Um, did he ever call you
on your cell phone, Father?
Two days ago.
- Can I see your phone?
- You want to trace the call?
Yeah.
So, uh, Max Keenan,
he come to you for absolution?
Well, I'm sure you know
the requirements for confession.
Contrition and intent
not to repeat the sin.
And Max doesn't have either.
And as a priest, I failed him.
I never was able to get him
to walk the straight and narrow.
Is there anything else
you can tell us?
Well, he was angry.
He felt his hand had been forced.
Where can we reach you, Father?
Father Coulter's staying
at St. Augustine Seminary...
for the next few days
before heading back to Ohio.
Here, Father.
Your father loves you.
Is that part of Dad's message?
That's a personal observation.
[Booth]
Delaney's murder, the threats on Russ's life...
this is all happening now
because of a little metal dolphin...
we found on your mother's grave.
F.B.I. field unit in Denver traced it
to a local artist in Mead, Colorado.
Who identified Dad as the buyer.
But Delaney left the F.B.I.
15 years ago.
- And somebody told him about your dad.
- And didn't tell you?
- They're part of the conspiracy.
- You must be annoyed.
You know what? I am.
And I don't like finding out...
there's a dirty F.B.I. agent
in this building.
Here's what I think happened.
Delaney goes to your father.
He asks him to hand over
the evidence.
He doesn't do it,
he kills you or Russ.
Dad calls Russ to warn him.
And then kills Delaney.
Guts him, burns him,
leaves a calling card.
Don't mess with
Max Keenan's kids.
Am I supposed to like that?
No, Bones. I'll take a stand-up crook over
a crooked cop any day of the week.
Booth, I got us a meet
with thejudge. Let's go.
And you better get back to your lab
in case we're successful.
- I just find it best to do what she says.
- Okay.
You want to exhume the young F.B.I. agent
that Marvin Beckett murdered?
That's correct, Your Honor.
- That is a big, noisy mess in the making.
- [Door Opens]
The F.B.I. has credible evidence that the homicide
case against Marvin Beckett was manufactured.
Assistant United States Attorney Dan Burridge
arguing against this writ, Judge Kemper.
- On behalf of...
- The F.B.I.
- I thought you were F.B. I?
- I am, Your Honor.
I told you.
A big, noisy mess.
All right. Let's hear your argument,
Mr. Burridge.
This is a precipitant exhumation
in a highly inflammatory case.
The evidence to which Miss Julian
alludes has not been authenticated.
It has been authenticated
by theJeffersonian Institution.
The F.B.I. would like to do their own
in-house analysis before proceeding.
Of course they would. They're the ones
who did the framing 30 years ago.
- I take exception to that.
- Why? You weren't even born 30 years ago.
- Judge...
- Not like me and Judge Kemper...
who got to see firsthand
what Marvin Beckett was really like.
Miss Julian, did you bring this to me
because I knew Marvin Beckett personally?
Did you? I wasn't aware
of that, Your Honor.
Were you aware of that,
Agent Booth?
We'd like to do this slowly
and carefully, Judge. That's all.
And we want to exhume Gus Harper
so we can make sure...
he was murdered in exactly
the way the damn F.B. I...
said he was murdered, Your Honor.
[Saroyan] As mandated by the writ
of exhumation byJudge Theodore Kemper...
of the D.C. Federal Judicial District...
I, Dr. Camille Saroyan,
will be performing an autopsy...
of Special Agent
Augustus Donald Harper...
under the auspices
of theJeffersonian Institution.
Date of death:
June 25, 1978.
Date of internment:
July 2, 1978.
Date of exhumation:
that would be today.
Also present at the post-exhumation
autopsy is Dr. Temperance Brennan.
The original autopsy in 1978
found that Agent Harper...
was killed when he was shot
three times at close range...
by a.38 Colt Detective
Special revolver.
Two shots to the chest,
one piercing the heart.
The other, the left lung.
The third,
a shot to the frontal bone.
- What?
- That bullet hole in the head, that's from a.38.
- Just like the coroner said.
- I can already tell these two holes...
are from something a whole lot bigger
than a snub-nosed revolver.
Something more like a rifle
that a sniper would use.
Zack, you'd better get a full set of X-rays
before Dr. Saroyan reopens.
We're gonna conduct this one
like the whole world is watching.
- Hey, Russ.
- Okay, I'm here. What's up?
You know, you're an idiot, Russ.
I like you,
but you're a real idiot.
- What'd I do?
- I got a call from your parole officer today.
Why?
Why? Because you crossed
state lines without informing him.
I just told him you were aiding
in an F.B.I. investigation.
Thanks.
You're slipping, aren't ya?
Look, I want to marry Amy
and raise her kids.
One of them is sick.
That costs money.
I'm a felon on parole.
I work part-time as a mechanic.
You tell me what job am I gonna get that lets me
be the man I need to be to raise a family?
You got this sick little girl
depending on you. I get that.
But you go back inside and you cross
that line, you're not helping anyone out.
- [Gunshot]
- [Woman Screams]
Everybody down!
[People Shouting, Gasping]
[Woman On TV] Civil rights activist
and convicted murderer Marvin Beckett...
was released today
when a second autopsy...
on his alleged victim,
F.B.I. Agent Gus Harper...
revealed inconsistencies with details
of Mr. Beckett's trial back in 1979.
[Coulter]
What kind of inconsistencies?
You have your confidences
to keep, Father. I have mine.
Well, it's over, right?
I mean, now that it's out,
there's no reason to kill Russ.
You know, the men behind this,
they don't care about Marvin Beckett.
- They care about being exposed.
- Lucky you were together.
- Why were you together?
- Oh, you know, a man's gotta eat.
To think that some people still refuse
to believe in guardian angels.
Booth!
- Who's that?
- [Booth] Deputy Director Kirby.
My boss's boss's boss.
- You're what's known as a real
pain in the ass, Agent Booth.
- Yes, sir.
I just had my testicles
handed to me...
by the attorney general of
the United States of America.
He wanted to know why
this Marvin Beckett issue...
wasn't done slowly and carefully
with greater forethought and tact.
- You know what I told him?
- No, sir.
I told him I did not know.
Sir, I had to do it the way
I did it because the F.B. I...
Not your decision, Booth.
You're suspended without pay.
Gun, I.D., security card, please.
Sir, I'm entitled to the reading
of the charges against me.
The charges against you...
are that I was pissed upon
from a very great height!
You're out of here in 10 minutes.
Can they do that? Just kick you out
without any warning?
The two guys standing behind me
with the guns seemed to think so.
As you can see, Harper's ribs and sternum
were practically obliterated...
by the two shots
to his torso.
Zack, Booth got fired.
- Suspended, not fired.
- Suspended's F.B.I. speak for fired.
Do you know what hurts the most?
They took the car. I got no wheels.
The bullets themselves
were removed from the body.
- But Hodgins found some very small fragments.
- Copper, lead, polymer.
I mean,
this is a conspiracy, baby.
Guys, what we're dealing with here is that Booth
won't be working with us anymore.
Well, I got my own gun. It's just, God,
why did they have to take the company car?
I assume that the only way
Booth can get his car back...
would be to solve the case
on his own and that we'd help.
Oh, no. No, no.
I can't let you guys do that.
Anyone who wants to help Booth,
raise their hands.
All right, I reverse engineered to find the
most likely design of the bullets.
After the bullet spread, lead pellets
were released like buckshot.
Wait a second. That's a homemade round
invented back in the '70s.
- We're talking a military-issue
M-40 A-1 sniper rifle.
- Nice.
Dude, what you call being a conspiracy theorist,
I call being well-informed.
Wait. Gus Harper was murdered
by a military sniper?
- Who makes his own rounds.
- Maybe we could compare it
to the bullet that grazed Russ.
I'm a civilian.
We don't have access to that round.
Maybe Caroline can help us.
[Booth]
You still have a job?
Not for long.
I'm on performance review.
None of the F.B.I. members of the Bank Robbery
Task Force had sniper training in the '70s.
I need to know who else
was on that task force. Local...
- Booth! Booth! I got it figured out.
- State cops, A.T.F.
And if any of'em had sniper training.
Once you find out, you keep your head down.
Task force, sniper training,
'70s, duck. Got it.
- I figured out a way to solve
the case and get your job back.
- Wow. That'd be great.
We need my father to give us the rest of the
evidence he stole from that safety-deposit box.
- Great.
- I'll drive.
Dr. Saroyan, when I get my doctorate,
I'd like to work here.
Zack, you are
an excellent scientist.
But an important part of thejob
is appearing as an expert witness in court.
- Ooh.
- "Ooh," what?
Jurors have to take you seriously.
And frankly...
you look like a weekend fill-in
at a college radio station.
Truth hurts, dude. Learn from it and grow.
[Chuckles]
You weren't able to find Max by tracing him
through the cell phone call he made to me?
Call came over the Internet.
It was untraceable.
Well, Max always
did things his way.
Guess your being a priest didn't
have much of an affect on him.
Son, I spent my whole life
trying to turn Max's life toJesus.
He knows exactly one Bible verse.
Numbers 35: 19.
"The revenger of blood himself
shall slay the murderer.
When he meeteth him,
he shall slay him."
- What's that mean?
- That's the law of the jungle.
Father Coulter, if my father
makes contact with you again...
please tell him
he needs to trust me.
His way got my mother murdered
and almost got Russ killed.
- It's time he tried my way.
- He won't contact me again.
- Well, how do you know?
- Ask him.
He put me under surveillance.
If a parish priest can figure out
the F.B.I. is watching him...
so can an experienced
fugitive like your father.
I need a makeover.
[Sighs] Zack, I am a big believer
in people being themselves.
You're actually
kind of cute.
Yes. I've been told that many times.
Usually followed by the word "but."
In this case,
"But no one takes you seriously."
I need help, Angela.
So, what do I do first?
Lose the floppy hair.
[Groans]
- Why are you mad at me?
- [Sighs] I need a gun.
No, you don't. You got me.
I'm your gun. You want equipment?
Here. Have these. All right? New division of labor.
I shoot 'em, you cuff'em.
Why didn't you tell me
you had Father Coulter under surveillance?
It is my job to find your dad
and put him in prison.
- And you don't think I'll help.
- He's your father.
I really don't think I should
have to ask you to help.
He abandoned me, Booth. And that's
the best thing you can say about him.
Your father lives by a certain code.
And part of that code is defending
his family by whatever means necessary.
You mean killing people
and setting their corpses on fire?
- "Any means necessary" sort of covers that.
- You respect him?
I'm just saying in his world,
he's a very honorable man.
That's ridiculous.
There's only one world. It's this one.
Would that be the one world where you're mad
at me for trying to catch your father?
- Or the other world where you
actually want him caught?
- Neither.
- You have to pick one.
- Either. Both.
Dr. Brennan, Agent Booth...
I thought you'd like to meet the reason
we're all losing our jobs and getting shot at.
This is Mr. Marvin Beckett.
- I wanted to thank you personally.
- You're welcome, Mr. Beckett.
Thirty years ago, crooked agents put me
in jail for something I did not do.
I did not kill the young F.B.I. agent.
I did not steal the money.
And I thank you for proving it
to the world.
That's why I'm here to tell you
to your face, to assure you...
I did not do those things.
You freed an innocent man.
And in return,
I must warn you...
the people that did this to me
aren't just a bunch of corrupt cops.
They serve masters
of much greater influence.
You're looking to bring
their world down around their ears.
They will strike at you.
Watch yourselves.
Here's your list of snipers
from the decade of disco.
This time I'm advising you.
Duck.
- Anyone you know?
- Yeah.
The A.T.F. rep on the task force
was a marine sniper, Robert Kirby.
F.B.I. Deputy Director
Robert Kirby?
That just suspended you?
Call your brother,
tell him to get out of the house.
- Tell him to get out now.
- Why? What's going on?
Seconds after Caroline got this list,
Kirby knew about it.
He's not answering.
I don't understand, Booth.
It's not us that Kirby is afraid of.
It's your father.
The only way to strike at him
is to go through you or Russ.
- Kirby was the one that took a shot at Russ.
- No answer.
- Russ?
- Hello?
- All right, just stay back.
- Russ?
- There's no sign of a break-in.
I'll check the back. Russ?
- Russ?
Oh, my God.
- Booth?
- What?
- Russ.
- Just take it easy, all right?
We don't know that for sure.
That's too much blood. Nobody could
survive that... that much blood loss.
Nobody.
All right. Okay.
It's all right.
Oh, my God.
It's against the law
us not calling in a murder.
It wasn't a murder.
It was a bloodstain.
That much blood,
it's mur... it's murder.
We call it in, the next thing
is we find ourselves under arrest.
That had to be Russ's blood.
You got a sample, right?
We'll check the D.N.A. at the lab.
Until then, who's the one who always says,
"Don't jump to conclusions"? Right?
Yeah, you're right.
Thanks.
I wish you wouldn't keep letting
me hug you when I get scared.
Hey, when I get scared,
I'll hug you.
We'll call it even.
- Results?
- The blood's not Russ's.
- Even you can't do a D.N.A. test that fast.
- Didn't have to.
Both Brennan and her brother
are "O" type blood, as was the mother.
The blood sample
you brought me was "AB."
- Therefore...
- Okay, let's go tell Bones.
I just saw her.
She's on her way to see the priest.
- Why?
- He said he had something for her.
She can't be going places without me.
Not when it's open season on Brennans.
- [Cell Phone Rings]
- Bones?
[Caroline]
Not even close, chéri. We need to talk.
Well, first, I want to tell you
that your brother...
is, uh, with his father.
You mean... with God?
No, his earthly father...
your father.
- Are you certain?
- Saw it with my own eyes.
Oh, thank God.
Which I use only
as a figure of speech.
Well, you have
to start somewhere.
You know, you're...
you're very much like him.
I'm... I'm nothing
like my father.
Black and white. The two of you,
you always saw the world in black and white.
Your mother wasn't like that.
Either is Russell.
All right, go.
I was clearing out my desk
when my phone rings.
And it's this F.B.I.
agent named Carlson.
Yeah. He heads up
a surveillance unit.
He tells me you and Booth are wasting
my time with this damn priest.
I tell him, " You better mind
your mushy mouth."
I gotta find Bones,
keep her from getting killed.
Father Coulter
is 90 years old...
confined to bed with Alzheimer's in a
convalescent home out there at the seminary.
Which does not much sound like
the priest you told me about.
Your father,
he talked about, uh...
when you were four
and your brother was nine.
And... And he hid behind this door
and he jumped out at you.
- You know what? Just give me the keys to your car.
- My car?
Boo! He hollers, "Boo!"
And you... you had this doll.
- Had this string in the back for talking.
- Chatty Cathy.
Wham! You took that doll.
And you wound up. And you hit your brother
so hard you knocked him flat as a pancake.
I said to your mother, " No one will ever
jump out at that girl again."
And your mother said,
"Just like you, Max.
She's just like you."
Hair color, plastic surgery...
colored contact lenses,
chin and cheek implants...
15 years older.
Still, I should have seen it.
- [Tires Screech]
- [Horn Honks]
- [Line Ringing]
- Come on, Bones. Pick up. Pick up!
- This is Dr. Temperance Brennan. Leave a message.
- Damn it.
Russ knew it was you all along?
Yeah.
You talk to Russ,
but not to me?
You know, to tell you the truth...
you do better without me
and Russ does worse.
- Take this.
- I'm not religious.
No. We're gonna play
this your way. Please.
This is Gus Harper's journal.
There's a key there
that's to a safety-deposit box.
In that safety-deposit box
is all the evidence.
Why didn't you give it
to them back in 1978?
Because your mother took
one look at it and said...
"If you turn this over to them,
they will kill us and our kids."
They got Mom anyway.
- There's not a day that goes by
that my heart is not broken.
- [Vehicle Approaching]
Dad, come on!
I gotta go.
Wait. I can't let you go.
Oh, I love you too.
No. I mean, I can't let you go.
- I'm sorry.
- [Moans]
I must be getting old.
I let you get the drop on me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I just can't let you get away.
I'm sorry. Listen to me.
If you find somebody that you can trust,
you hang on to him. Remember that.
- Dad, let's go!
- I'm proud of you. I love you.
Dad, get in.
You take care of her.
- F.B.I. Stop or I'll shoot.
- Booth.
Booth. Booth.
Oh.
Right. Did he really have to hit the car?
I wasn't gonna chase him.
You okay?
# [Indie Rock]
# [Continues]
# [Ends]
- What's this?
- Zack's doctorate.
I'd like to recommend him
for a job.
I can't put him in front of a jury.
I'm sorry.
I'll put in a good word in Pure Research.
That way, he can come visit once in a while.
- Visit?
- Dr. Saroyan, Dr. Brennan, Dr. Hodgins...
I'd like to present your colleague.
Dr. Zachary Uriah Addy.
[Chuckles]
Look at you.
- All grown up.
- [Saroyan] Wow.
Very impressive.
I can learn how to be effective
in front of juries.
Zack can learn anything.
All right, he's hired.
Who am I to break up this team?
- Lunch is on me, Dr. Addy.
Anywhere you want to go.
- The diner.
- Anywhere, I said.
- I like the diner.
Hey, do me a favor, Uriah.
Need a little time to adjust
to your fascist haircut.
Let's go.
Congratulations, Dr. Addy.
Thank you, Dr. Brennan.
[Angela]
Zack, congratulations.
- [Hodgins] Congratulations.
- Hear, hear!
[Hodgins]
It's about time, man. Congratulations.
[Saroyan]
You should be proud of yourself.
What happened?
Well, the attorney general took one look at
the, uh, evidence your father provided.
And, you know,
he reinstated me.
I'm glad.
Listen. We, uh, found
another burned body.
Same place, same setup.
- Kirby?
- I'm pretty sure.
It was Kirby's blood in your apartment.
Dad's still trying to warn people.
Leave me and Russ alone.
Uh, Russ, he's safe with your father.
They're warning people
to stay away from you.
You know what? I'm sorry that
you had to go through it again.
Watching your family drive off,
you know, leaving you behind.
- I'm sorry.
- My father is... is...
He's your dad.
And he loves you.
You know, I'm just...
I'm just one of those people
who doesn't get to be in a family.
That's...
Listen, Bones. Hey, there's more
than one kind of family.
- Well, Zack got the job, right?
- Come in and congratulate him.
Nah. He's your squints.
Not my squints.
No. Booth, we are all
of us your squints.
Do me a favor and pat Zack
on the shoulder with an open hand.
What? Why?
Does that mean something?
[Chuckles]
What's that mean?