[Brennan]
I'm supposed to be on vacation.
You know,
spending time with Sully.
[Booth]
Oh, that's a good lesson for Sully then, huh?
Next time he actually takes you away
on vacation, you should go away.
- You know, leave town.
- Uh-uh! You had a vacation and never left town.
It wasn't a vacation.
It was a suspension.
- Plus compulsory therapy.
- Hey, dude, don't knock therapy, okay?
Dr. Wyatt has helped me realize that there
are certain pressures that build up on the job...
and I need creative ways...
- We do everything together.
- of dealing with them.
What exactly do you have to contend with
on the job that I don't?
[Laughs]
You, Bones. You don't have to contend with you.
So we got a trunk. Looks like
it's been wrapped with chains.
Battered up pretty good. Most likely came
through the sluiceways upstream in Maryland.
- Is it locked?
- Not anymore, it isn't.
- Is there a body in there?
- Sort of.
[Siren Approaching]
Beats the hell out of me what
the deal is with this one.
The head looks flat,
as if the skull's been totally pulverized.
- Maybe she got run over by a steamroller.
- [Booth] What are you saying?
She was killed
by Wile E. Coyote?
Okay. I want the whole "kip and canoodle"
transported to theJeffersonian.
Kit and caboodle.
- [Brennan] Whatever.
- Why don't we just wrap this up fast...
- so we can get you back on your vacation?
- Thank you. I'd appreciate that.
- You have got to be kidding.
- What's with the tone?
- You want me to take this face
and build a skull for it?
- Can you do it?
- No.
- You're always taking skulls and putting on faces.
- Can't you simply reverse the process?
- No.
- Why not?
- Because I am a human being.
She's missing every bone in her body?
- Her skeleton was removed.
- Oh. All right.
Leaving the third circle of hell.
But before I go, I think she's Asian.
Don't base that on skin tone.
She was boiled...
which is why we can only
get partial fingerprints.
I'm not going off skin tone.
I'm going off her hair.
I have an idea for the face... if you can remove
the head from the rest of the skin sack.
Please, God,
I am not out of earshot yet.
The victim was boiled. Then a number
of incisions were made from the top of the skull...
around her right ear
and down her right side.
Then from her left foot, along the outside
of the body to her left hip.
- Someone with medical training?
- Definitely not.
An untrained hand
but a very sharp instrument.
- Boiled?
- The entire skeletal structure removed.
Then the skin was sewn back
around the organs.
It doesn't fit any kind of ritual killing
I've ever heard or read about.
[Saroyan] The organs are damaged due
to the clumsy cutting, but everything's there.
- Except the brain and the eyes.
- Oh, God.
It must have been difficult to remove all those
smaller bones, like the phalanges.
Well, it's all gone.
I didn't even find one bone.
The algae in the trunk is cyanobacteria
called Microcystis aeruginosa.
The size of the... scum colony
indicates eight days submersion.
Dr. Brennan?
Have I offended you in some way?
Dr. Saroyan said no bones,
so you know what that means?
I'm back on vacation.
No bones, no Bones.
That...
I was the second "bones."
That's very witty.
[Zack] Essentially, all we have to do
is refill the empty head.
Like a balloon.
- Which is literally what we did.
- Oh, no. You did not.
Put a bladder inside the head
and inflate it very slowly.
[Air Hissing]
[Saroyan]
This is...
It's absolutely...
- Brilliant?
- Useless.
You need the exact shape
of a skull to get a likeness. Notjust a...
This is...
Turn that off.
Oh, my God.
You guys are perverse.
Dr. Brennan was right.
Bone people should only do bone things.
[Air Hissing]
Hello?
Hey! Dr. Brennan!
- Agent Sullivan, I presume.
- [Chuckling]
So, what do you think?
- I think you're very dirty.
- Ooh.
- You got something.
- Oh. Oh.
Uh, come on aboard.
Here.
So I didn't think I'd see you
for a couple days.
Well, I know it's strange,
but I'd actually...
rather spend time
with you than work.
Well, I'm flattered.
So, um, you renting it?
Well, uh, I'm thinking
about buying her.
Wow. Can you afford it?
Well, if I liquidate everything
and borrow heavily, not at all.
[Chuckles]
So you'd... you'd live on it?
Her. You know, live on her.
But before I commit, I want to
spend the night on her with you.
- Oh, what would that prove?
- Call it sexual feng shui.
[Chuckles]
I don't think that's a real thing.
If it doesn't work for us,
I don't want this boat...
Wow. Apparently, you do
think it's a real thing.
I can't find anything on how to estimate
the height of a body without bones.
Does the skin stretch or
contract without a skeleton?
Boiled leather immersed in water would
tend to stretch, then contract as it dries.
Maybe the principle applies.
- [Saroyan] I'm finding bruising on the torso.
- [Device Buzzing]
I'll subject the tissue to reflectant
spectroscopy to get a rough idea...
of when the blows were sustained
and whether they were fatal.
Dr. Saroyan, the face debacle
taught me a lesson.
I'm strictly a bone guy
like Dr. Brennan.
Which is exactly why
I called for you, bone boy.
- A patella?
- Yes.
X-rays showed it lodged
in the fatty tissue of the leg.
A bone...
something we can work with.
It's just a kneecap, Zack.
Don't get too excited.
To you, it's just a kneecap.
To Dr. Brennan...
- it's the best part of a human being.
- Good to know.
[Brennan Chuckling, Moaning]
Hey.
[Chuckling, Moaning Continue]
Ahoy, the boat?
- [Sully] Booth?
- Yeah. I need Bones.
Permission to come aboard
or what?
Hey, man.
Uh, is this important?
- Yeah. We got a bone.
- Tell me about it.
It's from the boneless girl.
What kind of bone?
- [Brennan] Here and here.
- Frontal spurring.
- Mm-hmm. What's that mean?
- Zack?
A lot of time spent on the knees.
Oh, she's either a nun or a prostitute.
No. The tendon attachments on the inside
of the patella also suggest squatting...
which is not nunlike behavior.
- You didn't need to interrupt
my vacation for this, you know.
- Well, you know...
you said to call if a bone showed up...
and this is a bone.
The density of secondary
osteon structures...
suggests the victim was in her early 20s
at the time of her death.
See? Zack is capable.
You don't need me.
- An interesting shape.
- [Zack] Square rather than triangular.
Classic nail-patella syndrome.
It's a genetic defect,
also known as Fong's Disease.
Fong's Disease, right.
What's that?
Angela said the victim's hair
suggested Asian.
Our victim may have grown up
in a non-industrialized rural environment.
Well, early 20s, Asian, rural area...
I'll... I'll check with immigration.
Zack will do an osteological
profile on the bones...
see if we can focus geographically,
while I get back on vacation.
Wow. Dr. Brennan
really likes that boat.
[Beeping]
[Booth]
I thought you said you couldn't make a face.
Well, did you hear about Zack and Hodgins
and the balloon in the head?
- Huh. Was it as bad as it sounds?
- Yes.
The least I could do
is try to give her a face, poor woman.
So, a boat, hmm?
Oh, Sully? Yeah.
Last month, he wanted
to live in a tree house.
Mmm. He's like me.
Yeah. I don't see that.
Well, he's not really made for all this murder
and corpses and empty eye sockets crap.
He's a romantic.
- Unlike me?
- No. You're a romantic of a narrow kind.
You live to catch bad guys.
Sully lives wide.
- [Computer Beeping]
- Hey, I got a hit off
the Homeland Security database.
[Booth] "Li Ling Fan."
Yeah. She's here on a fiancée visa
from mainland China.
Yeah, well, the fingerprints...
It's a match. Print this up for me.
- Yeah, this is the victim.
- Okay. I'll go visit her fiancé tomorrow.
You know, I...
I live wide too.
[Scoffs]
Far and wide, right?
There's nothing wider
than Seeley Booth.
Okay, then. My bad.
Ling Fan is dead?
Are you certain?
When was the last time
you saw your wife, Mr. Harper?
- Fan wasn't my wife.
- Well, [Chuckles]
she immigrated here
on a, um, fiancée visa...
and you're listed
as the, uh, fiancé.
We called it off.
Mutual thing.
Well, you see, I...
I don't believe that.
I mean, a poor girl
from China travels...
thousands of miles
away from her family...
to be with the man
that she loves.
Not like she has
many options.
- So, uh, when was the last time you saw her?
- About a month ago.
- How did she die?
- Yeah, we're still, uh...
- we're still looking into that.
- Foul play, right?
I mean, the F.B.I. wouldn't be asking
so many questions if it was an accident.
So you, uh...
you get off on all this, uh...
- [Dings]
- Asian stuff, huh?
Martial arts and weapons?
I've dedicated my life to it.
She had some bruising, your fiancée.
I don't know anything about that.
These, uh, weapons here... here...
- Are they, uh, genuine?
- Knock-offs.
- I can't afford the real thing.
- Really?
Since when does a fence
worry about affording things?
Details like a criminal record... they tend to,
uh, come up during a murder investigation.
- Murder?
- Homicide.
See, I've, uh,
dedicated my life to it.
Hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey!
[Brennan]
I've been on Arab dhows about this size...
but I don't think
I could handle one all by myself.
This is a lot more high tech
than a dhow.
Why... Why didn't you ask me
to go out with you?
I'm a good sailor.
Well, you know, I've gotta be able
to handle her by myself.
I'd much rather have a crew...
you, in fact...
but what if you got conked on the head
and ran off with a pirate?
[Chuckles]
- Ahoy, the boat.
- Aw, Booth.
Don't tell me.
You found another bone.
Well, I got this, uh,
Chinese book that needs translating.
Maybe you, uh, got somebody
at theJeffersonian we could talk to?
No! I'm on vacation.
Well, he'll just keep showing up.
Might as well pitch in
and get the case solved.
It's a ledger for buying
and selling weapons.
[Booth]
Illegal weapons.
Mmm.
One entry refers to this.
It's a jian...
a double-edged sword.
A degu... This fellow's
not Chinese, correct?
- How can you tell?
- His characters are labored, overly formal.
Professor ShiJon Chen is a highly respected
cultural anthropologist...
- who specializes in...
- Yeah, he's one of you. I get it.
You definitely didn't
get all the weapons.
Including this...
a Qing Chuang.
A flying horse...
a very rare, ornate dagger.
So what do you think,
Jon Chen?
Obviously he has a fetishistic
slant towards all things Asian.
A mail-order bride would've been a thing
to him, like these weapons.
What about the ritualistic removal of the bones?
Could it be minghun?
- No. Definitely not.
- What's that, huh?
It's an ancient belief in rural China
that if a young, unmarried male dies...
his family should rebury
his bones with the bones of a woman.
- A bride for the afterlife.
- Like a "buriage" or a "marrial." [Laughs]
- A "deading"?
- [Laughing]
But I've never heard of anyone
committing murder to get these bones.
Well, then we should pursue
this avenue of investigation.
If you come across a minghun...
in which the origin of the bride's bones
is unclear, you let us know.
Of course.
All right, Sully, look.
I want you to look into buying...
one of those ancient Chinese
weapons... leaping donkey?
- Flying horse?
- Yeah, whatever. See if Harper surfaces...
long enough to, uh...
to make the sale.
Homeland Security says the fiancée visa
was expedited by a lawyer...
on retainer to a smaller bride agency
here in town called The Perfect Wife.
- Oh, that sounds archaic.
- Oh, you know, in therapy I learned...
that, uh, superlatives like "perfect"
are, uh, meaningless.
Not in science. A perfect number is a number
whose divisors add up to itself...
as in one plus two
plus three equals six.
You know, in therapy I learned
that definitive statements...
are by their
very nature wrong.
Isn't the statement,
"definitive statements...
are by their very nature wrong,"
definitive, and thus, wrong?
- You hate psychology.
- Well, you haven't said anything
to change my mind.
You know, this is exactly why, okay, sometimes
I do things like shoot up an ice cream truck.
Oh, it's a good thing you had therapy.
You know, we talked
about you in therapy.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
What did you say?
Well, you know,
since it was, uh, my therapy...
I don't have to share
the details.
Sorry.
So you specialize
in bringing brides over...
from Russia, Romania,
China and Thailand?
I've had over 500 marriages
since I opened shop.
I match the happy couple using an empirical
system of reciprocal attributes.
You can't match humans empirically...
because the variables number
in the tens of thousands.
I never recommend a match with less than
200 points of compatible commonality.
Tens of thousands
is way more than 200.
This is great.
Were Drew Harper and Miss Fan...
- Miss Li.
- In Chinese nomenclature, the last name's first.
- And the first name is last.
- Great. Were they a good match?
Sadly, I'm sorry to say,
in the end, no.
They decided not to marry.
What happened
to Miss Li after that?
On a fiancée visa,
the couple has 90 days to marry.
And if they don't, the bride is required
to return to her country of origin.
So if Ling Fan is missing, it's probably
because she went back home.
- Miss Fan is...
- [Clears Throat]
Li Ling Fan is dead, Miss Burrows.
- She was beaten.
- Drew Harper may have killed her.
Did that possibility show up
in your 200 points?
[Exhales]
Um, this is my background check
on Drew Harper.
You'll find that my screening process exceeds
the minimum set by the Marriage Broker Act.
Thank you, Miss Burrows.
You... You can leave.
[Whistles] Well, Harper provided
a completely false background.
- Is that possible?
- Oh, career criminal, fence?
I mean, yeah. He could bring himself a whole
identity based on false documents.
This is definitely
not a match made in heaven.
I've been worming my way into observing
the ceremony firsthand for two months...
- through the groom's family.
- That'd be the dead groom.
Yes. Overtures are always made
by the groom's family.
Now, I hear they will pay
$25,000 for a bride.
- That would be the dead bride.
- Booth, you're being very judgmental.
I apologize.
I just think it's a little...
Apparently, they found a bride.
Well, who is she... or was she?
You know, because she's dead.
- My sources don't know anything about the bride.
- Who got the $25,000?
- Most likely the bride's family.
- "Most likely"?
My understanding is that
before the minghun...
the bones are spread
throughout the family members...
and then brought together
for the reburial ceremony.
- That's correct.
- If you could get me a sample of one of the bones...
we could check the D.N.A.,
see if it's Li Ling Fan.
- Do you know where any of these
bones are, Professor Shi?
- [Sighs]
I might know where maybe
one bone is being kept.
If you could get me to a place
where I could just look at the bone...
your subjects
will never know I was there.
All right. But you'll have to pretend
to be... my girlfriend.
[Snickering]
- And her brother.
- [Chuckles] Yeah, right.
[Speaking Chinese]
- What did she say?
- Just hospitality stuff.
[Chinese]
I don't need to speak Chinese to get that.
She don't think Bones is good for you.
- You just made that up.
- Nail on the head.
- Ha.
- [Chinese]
[Chinese]
- [Chuckles]
- She said your face has character.
Yeah. Well, all the older ladies,
they... they like me.
[Whispering]
Bones, what are you doing? Bones? Bones?
- [Woman Speaking Chinese]
- These are traditional storage pots.
Please, Dr. Brennan, whatever you find,
you promised not to disturb it!
No. I promised not
to disrupt your study. Ooh!
Whoa, what is this?
Is that human?
It's an ilium...
part of the hip bone.
Ah. What am I supposed
to do with this?
- Dr. Brennan, quickly, put it back!
- [Woman Continues In Chinese]
[Chinese]
[Sighs]
Did Bones just speak Chinese?
[Exhales]
Definitely human.
- No sign of any cut marks.
- Well, is it Li Ling Fan?
- No. It's male.
- So, you got a part of the groom
instead of a piece of the bride?
- Bones stole it.
- Not stole. Swapped.
From an old Chinese lady's mantle.
I brought a bunch of chimpanzee bones
and pulled the old, uh, "switchamacallit."
- Switcheroo.
- Whatchamacallit.
- Two different things.
- These anomalies...
Whoever this was, died of cancer.
I'll get Zack to find the details,
but this is definitely not Li Ling Fan.
- Maybe it's the groom.
- [Saroyan] Makes sense.
Especially if this
is a "dead people bone marriage" thing.
- [Knocking]
- Uh, Temperance?
Hey, uh, you got a sec?
Excuse me.
[Brennan]
You bought the boat.
Finalized this morning.
Wait. Sailboats have keys?
Um, no. Not... Not really.
These are the keys to the marina.
But, you know, it's symbolic.
Congratulations.
[Chuckles]
So I'm gonna
tell you something.
And I want you to think about it
a while before you answer.
- Okay.
- Well, you say okay...
but it takes you microseconds
to think things through.
So this time, I... I'd appreciate it
if you, uh, just took a breath...
because it's... it's big.
Well...
what is it?
I'm headed south in the boat
to the Caribbean.
- When?
- When this case is done.
- You quit the F.B. I?
- No. No, not yet.
I'll take a couple of months to get used to
the boat, you know, really check it out.
And then I'll start running charters,
probably for the Turks and Caicos, which is...
You're... You're really
talking a lot.
I know. And I haven't
even gotten to the main part.
Which is, uh...
I really, really
want you to come with me.
You do?
I do.
Look, take a sabbatical.
There's more to life than...
than corpses and murderers.
You know, we do this job
for too long, we get warped.
I can feel it happening already.
Maybe you can too.
Let... Let's run away together.
Well, you know, think about it.
Want a hug? Okay, no.
That's... That's, uh, a lot to process.
So just, you know, I don't know.
You know, let me know when you
think that maybe that...
Okay.
- [Beeping]
- [Typing]
Stage 3 sarcoma,
M1 metastasis.
Like Brennan said, cancer.
Yes. Most likely it spread from
prostate or testicular cancer.
So it's definitely a guy.
If this is the groom, then he's Chinese,
and according to Dr. Shi...
most likely related in some way
to the old lady who kept him in a pot.
Which should be enough to identify him
through hospital records.
None of Harper's weapons show any sign
of being used to dissect a human being.
No protein residue,
even under A.L.S.
Is there any way to tell what kind of blade
was used on the skin?
Only that it was sharp
and straight edged.
But I did find evidence of
toxicity damage to the kidney.
Wait. The victim was poisoned?
I thought she was beaten to death.
Well, the bruising could've
been a result of Fong's Disease.
Toxicology identified the toxin
as a root called lei gong teng.
In small doses,
it's an anti-inflammatory.
In large, it has another name.
Loosely translates
as "walk seven steps and die."
I'll have Booth check out
Chinese herbalists.
- You want me to bring you up to date?
- No.
- [Beeping]
- I want you to tell me what to do.
About what?
- Sully wants me to run off with him.
- Go.
- For a year.
He wants to run a charter boat
around the Caribbean.
- Go.
- He says I should take a sabbatical.
Go. What is the downside?
He's a great guy.
- This is a great idea.
- I'll miss you guys.
Oh, we'll meet you in Barbados.
Look, you have been working
every day since I met you.
It's time to let another part of yourself
out into the sun...
- with a bare-chested man and a tropical breeze.
- [Chuckles]
William Chang...
single, age 27.
Died two years ago
of metastasizing prostate cancer.
Great nephew of Mei Zhang.
- He looks nice.
- Booth will want to talk to his parents...
try to find out where they got
the female bones, in case it's Li Ling Fan.
Listen to me, Brennan. Go.
There'll still be murder
and mayhem when you get back.
They're going to know this information
came from me. You've ruined my study.
They won't know for sure
it was you.
Their son's bones are spread
all over the city.
They let me in on something
very precious to them, and now this.
I broke the first rule
of anthropology...
minimize your effect on the study.
Do you really believe that your study is more
important than catching a murderer?
You used to be dedicated
to a much larger, timeless truth.
Now you're just a tool for those
who have smaller concerns.
[Door Opens]
- [Exhales]
- [Door Closes]
So you buried your son
William three years ago?
My condolences.
We have come into possession
of one of his bones.
You have no idea
how this happened?
Maybe you're planning
on reburying your son...
with the bones of a younger woman...
to provide him loving company
in the afterlife?
Well, you see, we need to know
who this woman is, because it's possible...
that she's a murder victim.
You wouldn't want that,
would you?
[Sighs] Okay. Well, you give me no choice
but to get an order of exhumation.
- Sully bought that boat.
- Yeah?
Next thing you know, he'll be shipwrecked
on some island talking to a volleyball.
He's leaving
for the Caribbean.
- [Machinery Running]
- [Dirt Spilling]
Really?
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry, Bones.
I know that the two of you
were kind ofhitting it off...
He wants me to go with him.
Oh.
Oh. Yeah, yeah.
He says I should
take a year off... a sabbatical.
- He says it'll be fun.
- Yeah, it would be.
But you just said he'd be
shipwrecked with a volleyball.
No, he's got you.
He doesn't need the volleyball.
You think I should go?
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, you know,
it's, uh, one year out of your life, huh?
I mean, a person's
gotta live wide.
And this is kind of narrow.
- [Wood Crunching]
- Oh. The coffin already?
Can't be.
We're only two feet down.
Oh, easy. Careful.
Is this fake money?
There's no body
in this coffin.
- There was a body in here. It was removed.
- Yeah.
- What's with the fake money?
- Chinese tradition.
Send a loved one off to the afterlife
well funded, at least symbolically.
How long ago
was the body removed?
This little darling
is Phaenicia sericata...
also known as the common
green bottle fly.
Now William Chang was buried
in January, three years ago.
Since the green bottle fly is only active
in the summer months...
I contend he was dug up
lastJuly or August...
which allowed maggots
to be laid in the casket to feast on...
- Okay, yeah, I got it.
- Oh, I can be a lot more specific.
No, no. You know, dug up last summer
and distributed to the family.
Specific enough
for the F.B.I.
He would've
decomposed quickly.
Buried in a pine box,
improperly sealed...
buried only two feet
below the surface.
- The Changs should sue their mortuary.
- Because of the shallow burial?
Yeah, and the decomp seepage
into the fake money is au naturel.
- What does that mean?
- The body was not embalmed.
None of this is helping us solve the mystery
of what happened to Li Ling Fan.
The funeral home was in on it.
They wanted the body
to decompose as quickly as possible.
Full-service mortuary. They perform funerals
and weddings for dead people.
Mortuary records show that we buried
William Chang in a lead-lined casket.
- And if you found another casket...
- Pine box. It was a pine box.
- It is obvious that Mr. Chang
was dug up and reburied.
- Who embalmed William Chang?
The records show that my
grandson and I had that honor.
- You're lying.
- William Chang was never embalmed.
But you yourself said there was nothing
but fake money in the casket.
- So how can you tell?
- We can tell from the residue
left in the empty casket.
[Speaking Chinese]
I'm sorry, but we cannot help you.
Wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Mr. Han, please, just sit down. Please? Just...
Here's what I think, okay?
I think that you have...
some old Chinese
traditions alive...
which are illegal
in this country.
- The minghun reburial ceremony.
- [Booth] Well, I'm not concerned about...
- What I care about is if the bride was murdered.
- Murdered?
Our understanding is that
Mr. Chang's family paid $25,000 for her bones.
And people have killed
for much less.
So, uh, what part of that
25 grand came to you?
- Did the Changs admit to paying that money?
- No.
We found a cash withdrawal
that they can't explain.
But you are not even certain
that William Chang's minghun bride...
- is this murdered woman?
- No, sir.
We can't know for sure it isn't her
without looking at the bones.
If the bride were not this murdered woman,
would you allow the ceremony to proceed?
- Grandfather!
- [Chinese]
What ceremony?
- # [Traditional Chinese]
- [Man Chanting In Chinese]
[Brennan]
We're... We're very sorry to disturb you.
F.B.I. I need
to see the coffin. Sorry.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Take a look, Bones.
- Take a look.
- Okay.
[Brennan] Indications of cancer.
I believe this is William Chang.
Here's the chimpanzee ilium
that I left.
What about the girl?
[Brennan]
There's lots of score marks on the bones...
congruent with flesh being removed
from the skeleton with blades.
I believe this is Li Ling Fan.
[Booth]
Where is everybody?
I guess we really
broke up the party, huh?
Positive I.D. on both sets of remains.
William Chang and Li Ling Fan.
- Wow. They kinda go together.
- [Saroyan] Because they're deceased?
Yeah. But more than that.
They're exactly the same level ofhotness.
Which is zero
because they're skeletons.
The cuts left on the skeletal structure
by the removal of soft tissue...
match the implements the F.B.I.
confiscated from the mortuary.
She was ill, and he was ill.
It's really too bad they never actually met.
The mortician's lawyer
advised him to clam up.
[Saroyan] The Changs now say the $25,000
was used to pay off a family debt.
You ever think that their
spirits actually did meet...
and are working to get their bones together
here on the physical plane?
You mean like we're possessed
and doing their bidding?
[Sighs]
You know what you people lack?
Whimsy.
It's a genuine handicap.
There are four morticians working at that
mortuary and a half a dozen assistants.
Any one of them could've removed the bones
and sank the skin in the river.
[Zack] Personally, I would've cremated
the remaining skins and organs.
No crematorium
at that mortuary.
I am gonna draw them
a wedding picture.
Okay. Well, you do that.
We should find out who poisoned the victim
and arrest him for murder.
Probably the, uh, bouncing,
flying mail-order husband.
Does that count as whimsy?
Well, you're handicapped, Zack.
Someone really needs to throw
a telethon for you.
How did Sully find Harper so quickly?
He didn't say.
You know, Sully's a nice guy.
You sound condescending.
I'm just trying
to be nice, okay?
I'm complimenting the fact that
you got a good one this time.
Thereby implying I'm incapable
of making my own judgments.
The physicist
who couldn't tie his shoes?
Oh, the former professor who was jealous
of your own success. Should I stop?
- Yes.
- Oh, the guy that you found on the Internet...
and ended up being some
kinda recruiter for a cult.
Oh, and this is my favorite...
the guy who cut off his own brother's head...
because he thought
he was possessed by a witch.
You made your point.
Look, I'm just saying a guy who wants to take
you away from all of this on a sailboat...
- that's a step up.
- Condescending.
[Chattering In Chinese]
- That's our guy.
- [Brennan] Okay. So when do we take him off?
Down. We take him down when Sully
puts his cap in his back pocket.
Now. Freeze!
- [Groans]
- Freeze! Harper!
Geez, I told you he was fast.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Great. Fine. Sully, you chase him.
I'll head him off. Okay?
Okay, okay, okay.
[Grunts]
- Have you thought about my offer?
- Yes.
- What do you think?
- This is not the time to discuss it.
- [Sully] The guy must be on meth.
- [Brennan] Martial arts.
F.B. I! Freeze right there!
I said freeze!
Freeze! Damn it!
What is he, on wires?
[Groans]
- [Groans]
- He ain't bouncing around anymore now, is he?
See that?
- I did not kill Ling Fan.
- Then why did you keep running away, huh?
- I'm a criminal. You're police.
- [Sully] Ling Fan didn't really know anyone.
- That makes you a good suspect.
- Sell her bones for $25,000.
- Make up for the loss.
- What loss?
You paid $25,000
to The Perfect Wife Agency to bring her over.
Probably another eight grand
for the round-trip ticket.
- That's a lot of knife sales.
- [Harper] You people got it completely wrong.
Chick doesn't work out,
you get a full refund or a swap.
I took the money-back guarantee.
- Really?
- Oops.
I didn't lose a cent. It's the mail-order agency
that's out all that dough.
- What was wrong with her?
- What?
Why did you send
Ling Fan back?
Chick was defective, man.
I'm a very active person.
She moved slow, like an old lady.
- You meet the flying horse?
- Yeah.
That is a very good item.
Maybe you still want to buy it?
I'm gonna need bail money.