I'm Wayne Malloy.
My family and I are travelers.
Our kind has been living in
this country for 150 years.
We're not listed in the phonebook,
we don't have social security numbers.
We live off the grid.
Some call us gypsies,
others call us thieves,
most though, don't even
know we exist.
I've got three kids,
a boy, a girl,
and, uh...
My wife Dahlia is just out of jail,
on parole.
We took her home
to the traveler camp.
The family gave her
a warm welcome.
I, on the other hand,
got a different type of welcome.
I am the new boss.
He is the old boss.
Get over it.
Sometimes, it takes a beating to make
you realize it's time to move on.
So where are we gonna go?
Life's a river, kid.
You gotta go where it takes you.
So, with a loan from the family bank,
I packed up the RV and went out
in search of something better.
- Shit!
- It wasn't
that long before the family
tried to stop us.
You're in the wrong lane, asshole!
Mick, look out!
Shit! Stop!
Unfortunately,
they stopped someone else instead,
and then they ran.
She's breathing.
Knowing that we couldn't
go back to our old home,
we decided to visit
their new home
edenfalls,
as The Riches.
Now, who buys a house
on the internet?
Come and meet our new neighbors.
Doug, meet Hugh Panetta,
biggest asshole
east of the mississippi.
You flatter me, Jim.
Dougy was looking for work
as a lawyer,
and you've got a lunch
interview today.
A good lawyer
makes you believe the truth.
A great lawyer makes you believe
the lie.
You're a sick mother, Doug,
and I like that in a liar.
I've taken many things in my life,
but I'm on my way to taking something
I never thought possible.
The American dream.
We're gonna steal it.
Will the past ever catch up with us?
I don't know.
Doug, I know you're there.
Don't you hang up on me, Doug.
But I'll be damned if I go down
without a fight.
Dad, do we really have to do this?
Why can't just crank the blue plate
special like we always do?
The blue plate special has its flaws.
Dad's right, honey.
Phony chits and
phony slangs
only get you so far.
- Come on, cupcake. Get out of the car.
- I am not going.
- Yes, you are, Cal.
- I'm not-- I don't want--
I don't want a damn number.
- Get out.
- No one's gonna own you, honey.
Come here. Let me see.
Dad, I don't want
to be a number, either.
Nobody is going to be a number.
Sammy, take the shoes off.
Come on.
But I like the shoes.
We're not a family of shoe-wearers.
We are a family
of missionaries.
Missionaries.
We've been spreading
the good word, ma'am.
Here's our paperwork.
What country are these
birth certificates from?
Indonesia.
The wife and I are U.S. citizens,
the kids were all born
in Pare-Pare in indonesia.
- Pare-pare.
- That's right,
Pare-Pare born and bred.
But you're a priest?
Oh, yes, ma'am.
A catholic priest?
Yes, ma'am.
Spreading the good word,
spreading the good seed.
So good.
And what's your name, hon?
Her name is Delilah.
She was bitten by a monkey
when she was eight
so her english is not so good.
Pad thai*!
[*gibberish]
Quit scratching honey.
He got bitten by a tsetse fly
at the airport.
Big ol' son of a bitch.
So, now, we're back on U.S. soil,
we wanted to get the kids
all socially secured,
you know, with cards.
God bless you.
~SeriesSub.com~
present
Transcript:
swsub.com
Synchro:
Jarick
Hutch
Season 1 - Episode 03
Operation Education
Problems with the newlyweds.
That guy Pete,
he e-mailed again and said
he wants to reschedule the golf trip.
Good. Reschedule.
Tell him the mono is
really kicking in,
and it's contagious as hell.
Don't come around.
Didn't like you anyway. Weasel.
Do you have to call them newlyweds?
They're newlyweds.
So how do we use these cards?
We use them
to enroll you kids in school.
Would you stop scaring 'em.
I'm serious.
So am I.
Dad, come on. School?
Who wants to learn a bunch
of buffer bullshit?
School is the cornerstone
of buffer society.
That's where you meet
a lot of buffer friends and
learn really important things.
Wayne, it will kill their tiny minds.
No, I went to school till seventh grade.
It didn't kill my mind.
You're half-breed.
I'm just saying.
Come on.
It will be real fun, won't it?
When was the last time you were
in an educational facility?
Fifty minutes outside
Georgia rippin' off that school.
Yeah.
Wasn't that great?
Dad, it sucked.
What else do we really need to know?
You taught us everything.
We're smart, we're crafty,
we're self-taught,
we're autody...
namic.
Auto...
Shit. What is that again?
The word is autodidacts, and if
you don't know, you're not self-taught.
- I know history.
- Really,
All of it?
Who's Sulla?
The guy from Star Wars.
He was the first dictator of Rome.
Freak.
I read a book on Joan of Arc.
Look, this is not an education, kids.
I do not want my children
in no buffer facility.
Stop being scared of school.
Nothing to be scared of.
Knowledge is power.
That's the end of it.
On a lighter note...
Honey, you're my best friend.
What do you think, red or blue?
I have no opinion.
I'm scared of school.
Obviously red.
I'm gonna tell my mom.
Yeah? You little bitch.
You tell your ma who
you've been talking to.
I haven't talked to Cal in a week.
Look, incoming calls from Cal.
Okay, so I talked to him,
but I don't know where they are.
Don't sass me.
I will beat you with a switch.
See?
Now you make me get all violent.
Screw you, Dale.
Shit, Wayne.
Shit, Wayne!
Not bad for a half-breed.
Not bad.
And...
Sex and a gold card, too.
Because you're worth it.
They're legit.
Wait, we have to pay at
the end of every month?
That's the idea here.
It's FEO.
For Energetic Orgasms?
For Emergencies Only.
Shit, Wayne.
I've been running hot plastic since
I was eight years old.
You can't just screw me give me
a gold card, and tell me it's FEO.
New life,
new horizons,
new challenges.
You know,
just 'cause you grew up a buffer
it don't give you the right
to call me ignorant, you know?
I never called you ignorant.
You said I was scared of school.
I ain't scared of anything.
What does Panco do anyway?
Real estate investment something.
Cal got me a bunch of stuff.
Did you even glance at it?
Yeah, I glanced at it.
Well, that is really girly.
It doesn't feel right.
Hold on.
Better, huh?
Thank you.
Wish you were coming with me.
I bet.
Who else gonna put rocks
in your briefcase?
You and me.
I know.
You'll be fine, though.
You're the best conman in the world.
The world is a big place.
You're the best conman
who gets in my pants.
Sorry, I called you a half-breed.
This is crazy.
Hi, welcome to Panco
Thank you for calling Panco.
Please hold.
Welcome to Panco.
Are you a Panco person?
Hi. Welcome to Panco.
Thank you for calling Panco.
Please hold.
You must be a Panco person.
I am on mondays, wednesdays,
and fridays.
Can I be tuesdays and thursdays?
Thank you for calling Panco.
Please hold.
I'm Doug Rich.
Mr. Rich.
Mr. Panetta has been expecting you.
Excellent.
Hi, Doug Rich.
You're late.
Meet your new team.
Panco team, meet your
new legal chief.
I hope you don't mind an impromptu.
I wanna get folks together,
and just kind of dive in.
No. Impromptu?
Very good.
Love to dive in.
Great.
All right.
The floor is yours.
Do you--
where would you like me to start?
I don't know.
How about the present, future,
vis-a-vis the Doug Rich way.
Present, future, Doug Rich way.
Good morning.
What is the Doug Rich way?
What is
Doug Rich way?
Anybody?
Okay. Now, that would be too easy.
Is it about the present?
Yeah, sure is, right now.
Is it about the future?
It's written in the stars.
It's about...
It's about problems.
It's about, "what's the problem?
"where's the problem?
There's the problem.
"catch the problem. Look, it's getting
away. Stomp it with your foot."
It's about people
solving the problems.
Panco people,
people of Panco.
Peter Piper picked
a peck of Panco people.
And it was good
on the first day.
And these are the people, you--
we are the people that
will win each and every case.
What case?
Exactly.
What cases?
We're a real estate company.
Panco real estate company.
That is what we are.
What have I got in my briefcase?
What does he mean?
A hundred bucks
to anyone--
no, hell, a thousand bucks
of Hugh's money.
Anyone, have a guess,
what's in the briefcase?
What's your name?
Kimmie, a thousand bucks.
The Beaufort-Simpson file?
The Beaufort-Simpson file.
A file I will be getting to know.
No, it isn't in the briefcase.
Good guess. Anyone else?
A thousand bucks.
Pink slips.
No, thank you.
Not today.
Well, I'll show you.
I'll get the thousand bucks.
A rock.
Is that a rock?
When people ask me,
"what is the Doug Rich way?"
I say, "it's this."
This is it.
This is the Doug Rich way.
This is
what I am about,
what we will be about.
The whole team.
So you want us
to be rocks?
What's your name?
Tony, you got yourself a raise.
Check with Hugh.
Yes, we will be rocks,
all of us. I am a rock.
What are you, Kimmie?
A rock?
Yes, you are.
We will be rocks.
You and you and you
and you, all of us, rocks.
Rock-solid, rock sure,
rock and roll, baby.
This is us.
Now,
and if we all...
All as rocks, if we stick together,
we become...
A mountain.
A mountain, yes.
Together, we will be
a mountain.
A Panco mountain.
All right.
All right, Doug.
There's Robert E. Lee.
It's a public school.
It's mixed,
which, in my opinion,
is a good thing. I mean...
Who wants to be with
Whitey mcwhitey all the time?
Also, it's cheap.
That's good.
Excuse me, is that a camel?
Jim and his shitty alpacas.
And then, there's the jesuits.
And, of course,
you've famous old Rosemere.
Is that a school?
The Rosemere academy.
1,500 a month, 18 a year.
It's a symbol of everything
that's wrong with the universe.
Eighteen what?
Thousand dollars, hon.
18,000 a year to send
a kid to school?
Get out.
That's not including books.
Sugar?
Sure,
I would love some sugar.
And to think of all the kids
that are starving in Africa.
So you send your daughter
to public school?
Hell, no.
Rosemere.
We're all hypocrites.
Come on in here.
And this, this here is Greg.
Greg's a great guy,
great accountant, too.
And, here we are,
a little snacky.
This is Diana.
Lynn, Kimmie, Jen.
Great speech.
You're a real Panco person.
Kimmie is terrific.
Yeah, so are Lynn and Jen.
Great girls.
Ladies. Ladies.
Come here. Come on.
Aubrey's a five star paralegal.
Wants to be a lawyer, too.
What year are you on,
year two at the night school?
Third year, actually.
Third year, yeah.
I'm not sure I want her to graduate.
Then she'll be a lawyer. I'll lose her.
She's the hardest worker I've got.
Let's see now.
And...
Yeah. Sit down, Tony.
Como esta tu esposa hoy?
My husband?
Your husband?
What about your wife?
What the hell?
- Muy bien.
- Thank you.
Wife's in chemo,
he hadn't missed a spill.
He's a god damn Saint
and a great janitor.
Hey, there, Stu.
What's goin' on?
You know.
Yeah, Stu's okay.
He's pretty good.
Sit down, Greg.
You'll be moving into
Stewart's offices today.
- Stewart's moving office?
- No,
No more offices for Stewart.
Somebody comes, somebody goes.
Somebody dies, somebody lives.
I'm a hunter, Doug.
In hunting,
you eat what you kill, you kill
what you eat. Comprende?
So when are you planning to tell him?
I'm not planning
on tellin' him anything.
Get rid of him by lunch.
I got I I got it.
Don't pick it up.
I got it.
Don't touch it. I said don't touch--
give me my phone.
Give me my phone.
Can I have my phone, please?
Have you been talking to her?
Cal, look at me.
Did you tell her where we are?
Yeah, Di, I gave her the address
'cause I'm that dumb.
Don't be a dick, Cal.
Rule number eight:
don't rat on your family,
even when you think
your dad has lost his mind.
We're gonna be gone in a week.
What do you care?
Maybe not, huh?
Maybe we'll graduate high school
and become lawyers or dentists
or successful americans or shit, Cal.
Maybe dad has a plan, Cal.
Did you ever think of that?
Maybe dad has a-- when was
the last time dad had a plan, Di?
When?
Do you really think dad has a plan?
Do you?
He stole the money,
ma lost the money,
and now we're here
in a dead guy's house.
He got a job, Cal.
He got a job.
That's great.
It is, Di, but when was the last time
he held one down for more than two days?
We're gonna get caught, Di.
- Hello.
- Hi ya.
Well, Nina was kind enough
to make an appointment for us
today at Rosemere school.
Yeah, well, couldn't you give me
a little bit more notice?
I mean, this is just
a little bit inconvenient.
- Hello?
- I know.
I didn't ask her to, she just did it.
Don't get mad at me.
You want school.
Yeah, okay.
Well, I'll see you at noon.
- See you at noon.
David's good, Doug's better.
Well, I hear we're gonna
be workin' together... Doug.
You know, I've been beggin' Hugh
for some support around here.
I hope you're ready for me
to work you to death.
Beaufort-Simpson.
Yeah. You read up on the deal, right?
You know, we got
a conference call at three.
Why don't you just jump in
and take the call yourself.
Give them the old Panco punch.
Absolutely. Better still,
you could take the call.
I'll watch the master at work.
Chicken, huh?
Wise owl.
So who are you replacing, Doug?
- You mean, the--
- No, you know, what I mean.
Hugh's a freak. Space is limited.
If you're in, who's out?
I got a hundred bucks on that picarelli.
The guy's a heck of a whiner.
You guys bet on
who's getting canned?
I know, it's a local entertainment
around here.
I got 500 bucks says it's you.
That's not even funny.
I got 12 mouths to feed.
What you mean,
all these kids are yours?
Of course, they're mine.
Adopted
from every corner of the world.
This one's got a heart of gold.
Her name's,
Chi Ho.
You wanna get started on this?
All this.
Right.
This is a school ?
This is a private school, honey.
It's an academy.
I gotta get this done fast.
I got a conference call at 3:00.
Shit, look,
he snuck them on.
Sammy, Sammy,
do secret squirrel, okay ?
Di, what's your name ?
- My name's Delilah Rich from Tampa.
- Hobbies ?
Fencing, skiing,
racquetball, and sex.
Ow, chess.
Cut the sass.
Have you kids even thought
about who you are ?
I'm a rich jerk-off.
I think we know who we are
but the question is,
do we really wanna go to a school
that rips us off for 18 grand a year?
18 grand a year,
is that a joke ?
Why are you
so scared of school ?
My mom was scared of school,
and look what happened to her.
- What happened to her ?
- She drowned in a creek
cause she couldn't read
the goddamn danger sign.
"We know what we are,
but not what we may be."
William Shakespeare.
I don't know what that means,
but y'all take notes.
Bonjour.
Asseyez-vous.
Répétez.
Je veux.
Tu veux.
Il veut.
Très bien.
Excellent class.
Maintenant, le verbe "avoir".
And chess, too?
Well, I'm no pro or anything,
but I do play the computer.
Our daughter
is very gifted.
You mean highly gifted ?
We mean perversely gifted.
That's what
we got here, Jane.
So what can I do for you
nice people today ?
Jane, we are in the scouting process
at the moment, being new to Edenfalls,
and our kids' education is,
of course, paramount.
And we're looking for
the topmost educational environment
for our three dangerously
gifted children,
- And Rosemere...
- Yeah, Rosemere's it.
I see. You're
interested in Rosemere.
- We are, Jane.
- And I assume you are aware
that we have
an extensive waiting list.
We are, Jane.
The extensive
waiting list, of course.
We are
people of means.
Excuse me ?
We got money.
No, I know what
"means" means, Mrs. Rich.
Look, you should feel free to apply,
and I'll be sure and let you know
if we have
any openings next fall.
- Next fall ?
- That's when our year begins.
Our school is
currently full, Mrs. Rich.
You can make room
for three little kids.
Now, that really wouldn't be fair
to our current parents,
would it, Mrs. Rich?
I mean, they thought ahead.
They made our deadlines.
They got their applications in on time.
Now, I'm delighted to hear
that your children's education is,
in fact,
"paramount" to you.
From where I'm sitting,
it doesn't really look that way.
I think what you're looking for is
a delightful public school in the area.
Robert E. Lee.
Yeah ? Well,
I shit on Robert E. Lee.
Baby, don't you listen to that bitch.
We can go anywhere we want.
Public school, private school ?
What do you care ?
You've never even been
to a school.
She can take her 18 grand
and shove it up her ass.
They don't just
give it to you, Wayne.
This american dream,
they don't just give it to you
with a big old ribbon
and a bow.
If we want it,
we gotta take it.
We got to do whatever it takes
to get it and to hold on to it
till they rip it out
of our cold, dead hands.
They're ain't nobody gonna tell me
I don't care about my kids.
There's nobody gonna say
"they ain't good enough".
They're not gonna
let us in.
Yeah, they will.
Come on, Sam !
This is it. Jane Fedley.
1158 old hickory.
It's quite a nice house.
It's not as nice as ours.
Cal, you first.
- We need to do this quick.
- All right, kids. Dig in.
Thanks, mom.
Di, come on.
Do it.
Whoa, this one reeks.
Cal, do y'all wanna go
to private school or not ?
- No.
- Well, you are.
They are?
Take the bags, quick.
Thank you, ma'am.
May I have another ?
- Hurry up, will you ?
- Don't you have a meeting ?
Okay, if you get caught,
call me. I'm a lawyer.
Did I teach you anything ?
Oh, my God. Cal, come here.
Check out this bird.
Gotta go, gotta go.
Are you deaf ?
What part of "hold my calls"
don't you understand ?
- I'm sorry.
- Get it?
So what happened?
I put the money in,
and it wouldn't come out.
Couldn't pull the trigger ?
You didn't seem to have a problem
pulling the trigger last night.
- What happened ?
- That was firing a gun.
Doug, listen.
I'm an easy-going guy.
I got three rules
here at Panco :
don't litter,
flush the john...
And make the new guy
fire the old guy.
Can you live with that ?
- Aubrey !
- That-a-boy.
Conference call in a half an hour,
all right ?
And get him on the phone first
and don't screw up.
Pronto !
Sit down.
What do you think of this ?
Excuse me ?
Would you like to have a go at this ?
I mean, would you like
to take a stab at this?
- At the candy bar ?
- No, this, this. Not this, this.
Beaufort-Simpson, right ?
I am not
a lawyer, Mr. Rich.
Yes, but you're an expert.
You know your field.
You must know this
like the back of your hand.
Oh, so you want me
to mark it up.
I want you to mark it up, that's it.
Just to mark it up.
- I'm a paralegal.
- Good.
That should help.
I don't wanna
get blamed, and
- I really, really need this job.
- You will not get blamed.
You're doing this for me.
I just want your opinion.
You want my opinion ?
I'm a just man. I am a fair man.
I am a woman-loving, colorblind,
and powerful man.
And I want your opinion.
And I wanna give you
this candy bar as well...
for the job.
Are you gonna fire him ?
The man's got 12 children.
Can I tell you a secret ?
Those aren't his children.
He cut the photos
out of a catalog.
No, shit.
How are you doing, baby ?
Well, she just sat down for a snack.
So, say we got us 20, 30 minutes easy.
Okay. Well, you keep
your eye on her. Bye-bye.
Okay, my account name
is Jane Fedley.
She must really like Cosmo.
Jones.
Yeah, J-O-N...
That big ol' computer must have
a big ol' mistake inside it
because that is
my mother's maiden name.
Sure. My birthday ?
September 18, 1961.
- Yeah. My social is 433-35-66-22.
- Gotta go. Gotta go.
Y'all want the blood
of my first-born too ?
Just give me one moment.
- Would you shut that bird up ?
- Mom, I am trying, okay ?
God damn it.
I'm so sorry.
My in-laws are in town.
Well,
I've lost my cell phone.
And I just wondered if you could suspend
my service for a couple of days
just to see if
it shows up.
Well, thank you so much.
I love them shoes.
Baby, come here.
Now, you gotta make
a choice.
What do you mean ?
Right now.
For the con.
See, when you rope
that Fedley woman,
you can be a girl,
but then, see,
you gotta stay a girl.
Or you can be a boy.
It might be easier.
I gotta make a choice?
Not for me, not ever.
I love you,
just like you are.
But, yeah, you gotta
make a choice.
For them.
You wanna go
to that school, right ?
I swear to God, that this bird,
if it says it one more time,
I'm gonna cook him.
Of all things that we had to steal,
we had to steal a goddamn parrot ?
- It's not funny.
- Gotta go. Gotta go.
- You hold him.
- Did you find something good for him ?
- Let me see.
- It's a prep school called Burton.
It's about an hour away.
- It's pretty fancy.
- That is good.
- Do you think he can do this ?
- Oh, sure.
Kid's a Malloy.
He can do it.
Okay, show me
that bike. Come on.
Operation Education.
Here we go.
Gotta go.
Hi, there.
Is everything all right ?
Dear. Gotten yourself a flat
there, haven't you ?
My mom's gonna
kill me for this.
Ah, so your mom's not here
and she doesn't know
where you are, does she ?
No, I snuck off
to the library to study.
You snuck off to study ?
Yes, ma'am.
You know what,
I have my phone here.
Why don't we give her a call ?
You have her number, right ?
- That's odd.
- What ?
Don't seem to have
any service here.
I need to call my mom.
Okay, sweetheart.
It's all right.
You know what ?
I live right around the corner.
Why don't we walk over there and
we can call your mother from my house.
- Will that be okay ?
- Thank you.
So you're a Burton kid ?
Oh, yeah...
But not yet. My brother and sister
and I are supposed to start next week.
- Well, Burton is an excellent school.
- It's all right.
It was actually
our second choice.
- Really ? What was your first choice ?
- Rosemere.
Mom said that
was the kind of place
where a kid like me could really
spread his wings in.
Intellectually,
of course.
What's
your favorite subject, Sam ?
French, ma'am.
Être ou ne pas être.
Voilà la question.
You read Shakespeare
in french?
Just the soliloquies.
This is actually
where I live.
He threatened me, okay ?
He said I had to do it.
I had no choice.
- He said...
- Who ? Who is it ?
Dale.
It's Dale, okay ?
You don't have
to marry him.
- By rule, you can say no.
- I can't say no.
He forced me, Cal.
I'm...
I think I might be
pregnant with his baby.
I'm splittin' tonight,
got some bucks.
Take the hound, see where it leads me.
You know what I mean ?
No. No,
don't do that.
Well, what do you suggest ?
Come live with us,
okay ?
I'll take care
of the baby.
You can...
you can go to school
here, I don't know.
- Since when do you go to school ?
- Since today.
So how do I find you ?
I'll pick you up.
8:00 tonight.
You remember
that place you got...
sick off those fish sticks ?
I don't remember the name.
Off route 19 ?
I'll see you then.
Bye.
- What ?
- You left the window open.
Where is the bird ?
Oh, shit.
Birdie ?
Bird ? Bird ?
Come here, birdie.
Come on.
You know I like you.
Come on,
you little shithead.
Come here, bird.
Who's gotta go now, huh ?
Come on, bird.
- God damn it.
- Is this what you're looking for ?
Gotta go.
Great. Yeah, Could you just bring
him down for me ?
How about you come up?
Oh my God!
- Want some?
- No, thanks.
I'm working on a triptych.
So what's... it about?
Your trip thing?
Isolation.
Don't worry, madam.
We'll find you the little "oiseau".
- My mom is here.
- Oh, sweetheart,
I was worrying sick about you.
This is the nice woman who let me
use her cell-phone.
- Jane!
- Yes, yes... Hello, hello.
- You two know each other?
- Well, Miss Fedley...
Ms.Fedley is the head
of Rosemere,baby.
Wait... You...
Well, thank you, Jane.
Thank you so much.
- I think we should be going now.
- Of course.
Mom, my books.
Books, books...
We can't leave her.
Her bird.
"Le petit chou" is missing.
- "Le" what?
- It's french, it's... means cabbage.
We gotta help her find him.
Well sweetheart, you know,
Ms. Fedley is an adult,
- I'm sure she can manage.
- She did something nice for me.
Why can't we do something nice for her?
- Thanks guys.
- Thanks
You didn't say a word.
Next time chime in.
That's what you're here for, isn't it?
Let's talk about Panco, Stu.
Hey, you know what?
Let's talk about your lack of
participation on that conference call.
No, forget about that.
Tell me about Beaufort Simpson.
Are we winning or loosing?
I couldn't tell on my conference call.
Okay, let's play again.
I'm gonna read a paragraphe
on the Beaufort-Simpson file,
and you tell me what it means, okay ?
Here we go.
"The provision of law, R.C.19,
"which prohibitsa court from
enjoining "the yada-yada-yada-yada,
violates the separation-of-powers
doctrine
and is therefore unconstitutional.
What the hell does that mean?
What kind of lawyer are you?
No, just imagine
I know nothing about the law.
Okay, just imagine I just come
straight out the far-west.
I'm a kid from the swamps,
and I'm here and, whoa.
Just help me out here.
"Eminent Domain"
Now what's that? I saw it in a film.
- "Eminent Domain"?
- Yeah, is it important?
Jesus Christ! Where did
you go to school man?
You have to be
the worst lawyer in the world.
I am... I am
And you...
You are the best
liar in the world.
Your family?
Cut out of a magazine.
- That is brillant.
- You know what?
I am tired of this shit.
Get out of my office.
No, you get out of your office.
You're fired.
I'm sorry.
Not that sorry.
He doesn't know.
The new guy doesn't know anything.
He doesn't even know
about Eminent Domain.
Welcome to Panco, Doug.
- I hope your time here is fruitful.
- Thank you.
Come on, little chou-chou.
Come here, little chou-chou.
See,
this is how the world ends,
not with a bang,
but with a wimper.
Oh Jane, honey, don't be so negative.
The thing about birds is
you think they care but...
all they really want is food.
Maybe I should go.
- Look over there, here or something.
- Yeah, go look that way.
Yeah, hurry, hurry.
Don't be sad, Jane.
You keep doing that bird call.
- Hey, I'm not late, am I?
- Just give me the bird.
Okay, tell "over here".
Over here!
Okay, take the bird.
- Come on, just--
- Okay, go, go.
I found him.
Take care, Ms. Fedley.
Bonsoir.
Come here you.
And best of luck this bird,
it really is a very good school.
- Thank you.
- Yeah...
It is an hour away but...
You know, if you don't stand
for education, hell,
what do you stand for ?
- Mrs Riche.
- Oh, call me Shereen.
I want to repay you,
how can I repay you
for this great kindness?
Oh, there's nothing you can do, Jane.
We're not the kind of people
who need to be repaid, are we?
Sometimes life's not
about payments, or
meeting deadlines,
playing by the rules.
You know, our life is just...
It comes right out and it hits you.
And before you know it, you got
a missing child and a missing bird.
We know what we are,
but not what we may be.
Right?
Bye, Jane.
Au revoir.
Huh... Have you got a minute?
Mom still got it, huh?
Why sure, Jane.
Better be a rental.
Never trust a thief with
a gold card, baby.
I've missed you.
I've missed you too.
- And how was your day been?
- Good.
I think I'm getting a hangover.
I think you are too.
- I got the kids into Rosemere.
- Oh yeah?
Eighteen grand times three,
how much is that?
That's a lot of money, Wayne.
Well, I've been a crack
open some law books.
See if I can keep this job.
You think it's gonna rain?
I hope not.
Never mind.
Your rock, big hit.
No shit!
~SeriesSub.com~