Previously on the riches...
What*******?
In the woodswhere you buried it.
I want to give it to pete.
You can't bribe pete.
I have to try.
What did you dowith pete?
You ... you killed him.
I hit him,and then ...but he fought back.
What if someonecomes looking for him?
You said yourselfhe didn't have any friends.
What happened with pete?
Did he take the money?
Pete went home.
Doug rich?
I'm a private investigator.
I'm trying to locatepete mincey.
Pete missing.
Well,I wish I could help you,
mister,uh,landry.
Call me chet.
Hi.
Uh,eden falls security.
There you go.
So this is whatyou do all day.
I wanted to see you.
Nina.Jim.
Well,at least I'm not gay.
Hi,cherien.
Uh,this is wes.
He and jim are friends.
I guess you could say
we've cometo an understanding.
I just want a chance,you know,to change my life.
And I want to stop lying.
Cal,why are you livingin a tent in the yard?
He thinks the houseis stealing our souls.
I'd rather be piss-poorwith my dad than
$13 million richerwith whoever you are.
Where you headed,cal?
Just hitting the road.
This is rosaleen.
Hi.
Hi,rosaleen.
We're bunking downhere tonight.Come on.
Let's get you something to eat.
Cherien rich?
That's me.
I'm chet landry.
I'm a private investigator.
My husbanddo something wrong?
No,no.
I'm looking for pete mincey.
You're looking for pete?
Would you like to sit down,
or ... something to drink?
Uh,I'm fine.
- This good?
- Sure.
Thank you.
So,pete is missing?
Well,he's disappeared.
His mother hired meto find him.
You haven't seen him recently,
have you,mrs.Rich?
Well,sure!
He came to visit me andmy
husband about a week ago,
and he was in towna couple nights.
- Mr.Landry ...
- uh,please,please,call me chet.
Chet ... why do you thinkhe is missing?
Well,his mama's birthdaycame and went,
and she didn't get a callfrom her boy.
She became worried.
She had her neighborcontact me.
I'm an old friend.
- Of pete's mother's?
- Of the neighbors.
So,you don't actually know pete.
No.
And,uh,I hope she alsocalled the police.
- Oh,I convinced her not to.
- Really?
Oh,I find police work in these
matters sloppyand incompetent.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Mrs.Rich,I'm afraidI have to ask you something
that's not gonna be easy for youto talk about.
His mother mentionedthat you
and pete might have had a special.
relationship.
- What?
- That he loved you,mrs.Rich.
Oh,I see.
Now,I've spoken toleif solberg,his therapist,
and apparently,pete called him
while he was here and saidhe
was in a kind of a crisis.
Now,that crisisdidn't involve you,did it?
Did your husband find out
about the relationship?
Did pete and dougperhaps have an argument?
No.
Look,I got to be honestwith you ...
he may have had feelingsfor me,
but he never,everacted on them.
You know what I mean?
I mean,he was goingthrough so much.
I had no idea.
I mean,if I had,maybe I could have helped him.
So if you hadany information,I would
hope thatyou would come forward.
Oh,yeah.
Just trying to think.
what?
Oh,my god.
He ... okay,he came over for dinner,
and he was telling usall about losing
his job and his divorce and all.
And then he said,at one point,
I wish I could just walk away,
just start all over again.
I mean,I knew he was unhappy,but.
I guess I ...I didn't know to what extent.
You don't write much down,do you,mr.Landry?
I do not.
I keep most of it up here.
This ... this notebook'sjust a crutch.
Sort of likea security blanket,huh?
I think I've taken upenough of your time.
Sorry I'm the bearerof bad news.
That's all right.
I just assumed your husband would
have told youall about it.
You talked to my husband?
Well,of course.
Best friend missing and all ...
I'm surprisedhe didn't mention it.
You have a nice day now,mrs.Rich.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: XOXO·숫 YOYO·질
The Riches
Season 2 Episode 6
Chet landry?
What the hell?
I was gonna tell you about him.
I didn't know that you talked to
him until he was leaving,wayne!
How could you be so goddamn careless?Huh?
We could have got our stories mixed up.
You're right.I have been just so worried about
this bayou hills thing that ...
you understand we're a P.I.'S wet dream.
He could have seen a picture of doug
and cherien on the internet,you know?
No,no.We've been careful,baby.
Cal went through every photo,
and he switched them out.
What if he had a picture of
doug and cherien on him?
Huh?Maybe that happened.Shit!
He's not looking for the riches.
He's looking for pete.
So now we stick to the plan.
To do the con,we close the deal in one month.
We get our money,and we are gone.
No one's heard from pete since he left our place.
I figured.
There's no time for love.Contractors are here.
We got to hit our bids on bayou hills.
And I need to talk to you.
Ah ... one minute.
We have to be together on this,wayne ...
completely together,completely honest.
Of course.
Hey,you.
How you feeling this morning?
Fine.
Wondering how the hell I ended up in this place.
Stop the bullshit.
You lured me here.
Don't you want to be here?
Itching to move.
Well,I'd really like it if you stayed a while.
Want to meet quinn?
Eamon quinn?
Didn't he kill people with the tire iron?
When'd he get out of prison?
A little while ago,
but he's really happy you're here.
He knows who I am.
He's heard of you.
Come on.
Well,well,well.
Cal malloy.
How does it feel to be home?
Strange way to come home.
We're having a campfire dinner tonight.
Everyone wants to welcome you in.
That's very nice.
That surprises you?
All the attention makes you feel uncomfortable?
People here think highly of you,cal.
Don't fight it.
Not interested in fighting.
Oh,it's written all over your face.
You don't know what's written all over me.
I know that you've traveled a long way,cal malloy,
and I know that you've arrived.
I got a problem,doug.
The meeting'sabout to start.
I need 500 signaturesby the end of the
day,or I can't run for mayor.
500?
Who's got time to stand on the damn street corner?
- I'll handle it.
- This is the problem with democracy.
I'll handle it.
That is musicto my ears,doug,
'cause I promised gee-gee shecould be my
campaign manager,so I need this to happen.
Aubrey,give me the list of ducaine
parishregistered voters.
I'm concerned about you,di di.
You've missed a few daysof school,
and after what happenedwith your
brother,things okay at home?
They're fine.
All of your teachers saythe same thing ...
this is a girl with a future ...
law school or medical school.
They're impressed,but they're also concerned.
You seem.
detached.
You don't seemto apply yourself.
So you want meto apply myself?
Let me ask you,di di ...
do you want to sleepthrough life,
or do you want to beextraordinary?
Well,I ... I don't wantto sleep through life.
Well,good.
Let's get to work,then.
Have you thoughtabout extracurriculars?
Maurice devereux?
Maurice,hi.
It's dahlia malloy.
Look,I just wantedto say,about ...
last night was just awfuland,um,for both of us.
For my part,I'm sorry I lied
about my mode of transportation.
It was ... I know how shittyit is to be lied to.
I'm sorry I let you down.
Um,maurice,I just wantto stay clean,you know?
My body and my conscience.
Hey there,darling!
Oh,I'm sorry.I'm a little late.
Nice wheels.
I want to buy them.
You sure?
Yeah.
So,what are you thinking?
Gmc acadia?
How much down?
Yeah,how much down?
Zero money down.
What's the sticker price?
Well,it's right there.
That includes a navigation radio
with a rearview camera system.
That's zero money down?
Right.
Walk away,dahlia.
- What are you talking about?
- That's a great deal.
You never agreeto the first offer.
Uh,thank youfor your time,sir.
Have you ever bought a car?
No.
I likethat car,though.
We're gonna get that car.
I guarantee dave wilkinson will
deliver the first 50 homesin 5 months.
Now,if you shift your attentionto page 4,
this graph will show youthe cost-and-profit ratio.
Now,after the first 50 homes,
that's gonna jump tenfold.
We are gonna make a lot of moneyhere,
gentlemen ... a lot of money.
Oh,nina,I'm feeling inspired.
I never bought a car before.
So,I need a favor.
I need to move jim's birthday
party to your place tonight.
Why?
The septic tank's broke.
We'll be using your bathroomall night,anyway.
Thanks,honey.
Now,can I count on you to help,
or are you too busy?
- Well ...
- good.
Remember those littlehors d'oeuvre forks
you used at that party where
your black friend outed jim ...
the ones with the little duckson the handle?
Oh,yeah.
I'd love to use thosewith the miniburgers!
Oh,that'd be cute.
Yeah,I think they'rein my kitchen somewhere.
So,are you gonna throw a partywith wes for jim?
Live and let live.
Listen,I did the work,all right?
Here's my book.
I don't want to bore youwith all that,okay?
Let your staff take a lookat that later.
Point here is,sure,I can do the work.
Every guy who comes in herecan do the work,right?
I mean,we wouldn't be up hereif we couldn't do it.
But here's what makes medifferent ... two things.
Numbers ... no one beatsmy numbers,all right?
They all have more overheadthan I do.
They just can't do it.
It's not possible.
And the second thing ... energy.
Look,I'm gonna be frankwith you,okay?
These other guys ... they ...
they just won't have the passion
for this project that I will.
You know,to them,it's justgonna be
another project on a long list of 'em.
To me,no.
I'm gonna sweat blood to makethis
project the best it can be.
So,I'm thinking reilly,
if his numbers add up.
Yeah,yeah.I like reilly.
But I don't know the guy.
And you got to work with peopleyou know,doug.
I mean,I know wilkinsonis
a stiff,but he's my stiff.
We're going with wilkinson.
And so it is written,and so it is sealed.
And.
500 signatures.
Oh,god.All right.
Damn forks.
Oh!Shit!
Oh,there they are.
Doug here.
It's me.
I ... I can't stop thinkingabout pete.
I just got to make surethat
we're on the same page.
Now,you gave him that $40,000
that I buried and sam found.
and he took it,right?
Right.
What's going on?
Oh,I don't know.
Why do I feel likeI'm losing my mind?
Hey,you rememberwhen I was 18
and we was in beaumontat the horse races?
Dahlia,what the hellare you talking about?
You know,I was waiting for you.
I just knewyou'd show up.
even though you hadall the money.
You could have split on mea
million different ways.
I knew I could trust you.
- Listen,baby ...
- get off that phone,doug.
You got to see this.
Uh,cherien,hugh's justcome in.
I got to go.
What do you think?
I'd use a different photo.
That one makes you lookkind of insane.
Gee-gee likes it.
She's my campaign manager.
Yeah,she's yourcampaign manager.
I'm your turd blossom.
Change the frickin' photo.
Hey,have you ever heardof leadership council?
Yeah,me neither.
I guess it's someafter-school committee.
It's meeting today.
They need a president.
I mean,the guy wants me to run
for president of something.
It's just ...
it's hard to takeseriously,I guess.
Well,you're smart.
You deserve it.
Thanks.
Good luck at your audition,all right?
I'm gonna be in the chapeljust studying,
so come get mewhen you're done.
Go.
Mr.Rich,got a moment?
Oh,sure.
Well,it seemed to me like
you liked my presentation.
So I was just wondering
why I didn't get the job.
I'm sorry.
There were a lotof qualified applicants,
and,um,it was a reallydifficult decision.
Why would you hire someone
who bid higher than me?
Look,you weren't hired,
so suck it upand get out of my way.
And a fellow irishmanon top of it.
I'm not irish.
I'm jewish.
You don't look jewish to me.
You look irish.
Uh,we're gonna start in afew,
so enjoy your last cookie.
Remember,you needto sign up today
if you want to runfor president.
Another reminder ...
we do a newcomer c&c celebration
every third friday of the month.
So if you want to come,
raiseyour hand so I can get a count.
Sounds good.
Yes.
Oh,did you get a t-shirt?
No,I ... I didn't knowthere were t-shirts.
Cool & celibate.
Are you serious?
I mean,are you truly serious?
Because.
sometimes I think no oneis
as serious as I am about "no sex.
This is not a joke.
You can't be half a virgin.
You're either a virginor a slut.
So,you all know each other?
I get it ...it's a family project.
Interesting.
So now that you get the picture,
when do I start the job?
We can talk about this later.
Just let me handle it.
Oh,no.
Let me handle it.
Let me tell you a story.
Before I got taken inby travelers,
I lived in an orphanage.
And,uh,one night,there was a fire.
When I woke up,smoke everywhere,
heat,people screaming,burning alive.
We all just ran,jumped out of windows,
did whatever we neededto get out.
But this one kid ...he'd been hiding
his money in the hole in the floor.
He was clawing at the floor,
trying to get the money.
And I told him,"get out while you can!
He didn't listen.
And now I'm telling youthe same thing.
Get out while you can.
'cause I set the fire.
I already had his money.
Oh,and,uh,dale,you're fired.
Funny,funny,funny,doug.
Why don't you justcome on back here
and we can talk about it?
Don't worry about that.
I'll take care of it.
He's just puttingon a show.
You're full of it.
You lied to usfor the last time.
What a day.
What's with all the food?
Nina's shitter broke.
We're gonna havejim's birthday party here ...
some kind of'70s costume thing.
So why are you sitting here.
in the dark?
Why am I sitting herein the dark?
I have no idea.
You know why I'm sitting herein the dark?
Do you have any ideawhy I find myself
sitting here in the totalgoddamn darkness?
Did I miss something?
Well,it's a celebration,wayne!
We're havinga goddamn party!
Now,get out of my way!
What the hell is wrong with you,dahlia?!
Oh,you want to know?You sure?
You really want to know?!
Did you or did you not give petethe $40,000,wayne?
I didn'T.
And what doesthat mean,wayne?
I can explain.
I don't want youto explain.
I want to know what happenedwith pete.
Whoo-hoo!
The party's here!
They're here.
I know you.
I thought that was you.
Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- Um,studying.
What are you doing?
- You...you go here?
- Oh,no,no.
Um,I,uh.my... my dad's friendswith the priest,
and,uh,I was actuallyjust confessing.
Shit.You have to confessto your dad's friend?
Ouch.
No,we --I mean,we just -- we usually just sort oftalk,you know?
It's -- I mean,he's not a bad guy.
Cool.
Well,what'd youtalk about today?
Uh,I just assume that,
if you can tellyour dad's friend,
you can probably tell me.
You don't have to,so.
no,I'm... I don't know.
It may sound corny,but,uh,
we talkedabout feeling small,
you know,not,uh,believing in myself.
I mean,I don't reallybelieve
in god or... well,maybe I do.
I don't...you know,I don't know.
I just... I-I thinkit's important
to feel... feel like a child of god,you know?
To just... to feel and actthat way in life...
I mean,to treat ourselvesand others that way,
like we're all meantto do good things.
Yeah.
What?
Oh,no,no.I...I just,um.
you look good in the chapel.
You too.
hey,a spinny thing.
We always bringour own disco ball.
The captain likes lights.
The captain?
Oh.Fancy.
And what are youdressed as?
Uh,a lawyer.
Okay,everyone,when we get back,
we're gonna start the
auditionsfor "little buttercup.
" What are you doing?
She's a brave young woman.
It's not easy to be alonein this world.
Doesn't strike me as the typeto be alone for long.
Maybe.
What about you?
Are you gonna ignore herall night?
She's dancingfor your benefit.
You say so.
Don't sell yourselfshort,cal.
You're as much a mystery to heras she is to you.
- Did you bribe him?
- I didn'T.
Then how did youget rid of him?
Don't you bullshit me,wayne.
When you came backto the house,
did you talk to peteor not?
I didn'T.
Oh.
Well,I'm --I'm trying really
hard not to lose my mindhere,wayne.
If you didn't talkto pete.
what happenedwhen you came back?
Dale was here.
He had alreadyspoken to pete.
- Dale.
- That's right.
What?Well,then what,wayne?
What did dale do?
Is pete dead?
He's dead.
He's actually dead.
Ohh.
It was an accident.
He meant to justknock him out.
Look,dahlia,it's a tragedy.
It is a terrible tragedy.
Don't you touch me!
Hey.Look.
No one meant for it to happen,
not even dale,but once it happened,
all I wanted to dowas to protect you,
to protect the kidsfrom all of it.
Protect us?
Look what youdestroyed,wayne.
Where's our son?
Where's our marriage?
Look what happenedto our family.
I couldn't stand to tell you.
- I knew...
- oh,no,I'll tell youwhat you knew.
You knew I would never come back to this cursed
and god for sake nhouse if I knew the truth.
Dahlia.
Uh,are you okay?
You want some?
Thank you.
For what?
This is the best birthday partyI ever had.
Jim.
I love you,nina.
You're drunk.
I know.
I've been thinking about you.
Before we go any further,do you love me?
Will you love me forever?
Do you need me?
Will you never leave me?
Will you make me so happyfor the rest of my life?
Will you take me away?
Will you make me your wife?
I got to know right nowbefore we
go any further do you love me?
Will you love me forever?
Sorry.I was lookingfor the bathroom.
Hi,jim!
- Cherien.
- Hi!
We are in the middleof the greatest,
most meaningful songof all time,man.
You ever listento the lyrics?
I love this guy.
I love you.
Hey,would you guys,uh,give me a moment here?
No,come on,man,no.We got to sing.
You can't go till you finishthe song.
Let me sleep on it baby,baby,let me sleep on it
let me sleep on it I'll give
you an answerin the morning
oh,sing with me,jim.
What?
Oh,come...don't!
Don't bring me down,man.
Cherien,listen to mefor a second.
No,come on.
You should know the words.
You should knowthe words,jim.
You take them in,promise to love.
That's what it's all about.
That's it -- and the lie.
How many people do you thinktell each other the lie,jim?
- You want some coffeeor something?
- No,I don't!I want some blow!
Feelings pass.
Nina always says that,and it's true.
What does nina say about.
the lie?
Do they pass?
I don't know about that.
The only thing that lasts,as far
as I'm concerned,is love...true love.
Everything else is.
What do you want,cherien?
I want to be someone else.
Well,you're in the right placefor that.
Hey.
Doug/wayne.
- You okay?
- Yeah,yeah.
Great party.
Where's dahlia?
Oh,my god.Oh,party favors!
Dahlia?
This is for all of you.
I love you.
This money's been my curse.
Let it be your blessing.
Dahlia.
- It's diana.
- Stop it.
Party pooper!
Go away,all of you!
Party favors are donefor the night,all right?
- Listen,baby,I am sorry.
- Oh,shit!I love this song!
Let's go somewherewhere we can talk!
Can't hear you.
Go away.
Hey!Over here,jeremy!
We're playing charades!
Come on,baby.Let's get out of here.
Hands off me,wayne!
It's the first word.
Uh."Crotch.
" Listen to me.
I'm sorry!
A stretched vagina.
Oh!"Vagina monologues"!
Aah!That's it!
Okay,jim,you're up.
Look at me,damn it!
I am sorry I lied to you,and I'm sorry
he's dead,but you needto talk to me now!
I don't need to do shit!
Now,get your hands off meand leave me the hell alone!
Four words.
No,no.
First word.
"The.
" "The.
" And the second word is,uh,"growl.
" The -- the roar of the -- oh!
"The roar of the crowd.
" "Dead calm"!
"Die hard.
Dying bird.
" It ain't a snow angel.
Jim?
Jim!
I can't hear his heartbeat!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Jim!
Hello,yeah.We need an ambulance right away.
Someone has collapsed.
Can you shutthat damn music off?!
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me!
I can't live without you.
I can't!
Don't leave me alone.
Don't leave me.
What happened?
Jim's heart stopped.
He's dead?
I'm afraid so.
Oh,my god.
I'm beat.
Cal's right.
We lost our souls.
We can get through this.
I love you,and I need you.
And sometimes I need you
to remind me I'm not alone anymore.
If you could just give mea second chance.
second chance?
That's what you want?
Where's pete'ssecond chance?
Don't you thinkhe deserves one?
He not gonna get one.
He's not gonna get shit,
'cause he's dead.
He's dead because of us.
Remember?
It's our fault.
Shut up about fault!
I will not take the blamefor
what happened to pete.
I didn't mean for himto die.
Who cares what you meant?
There was nothing I could do about it.
It was an accident!
Oh,yeah?
And deep in your heart,what did you
feel when you saw him lying dead there?
It was an accident.
Stop trying to turn this into something else
because you feel so damn
guilty about a million things
that have got nothing to do with pete.
No one meant for pete to die,and he
died anyway,just like jim died tonight.
No one's to blame.
Is that what you tell yourself these days?
That's how you get out of bed in the morning
and put one foot in front of the other?
I won't do it anymore.
You went too far,wayne.
and I am out.
Dahlia,where are you going?
Just gonna take care of my friend!
Declan and caitlin left?
Yeah,I thought they'd staytill
morning,but,um,I don't know.
Guess we're bothon our own,huh?
I kind of like it here.
Quinn makes me feel likeI'm a part
of something,like I'll be taken care of.
Don't you like quinn?
Everything I've been told about
him...I mean,my whole life...
just doesn't seem like the same person.
Shouldn't have done that,wayne.
What the hell are you doing here?
This is...this is bigger than me.
It's bigger than reilly.
You come into my house again,
you come near meor my family,
I'll slit your throat.
I am asking you.
Please.
What are you scared of?
Nothing.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: XOXO·숫 YOYO·질
The Riches
Season 2 Episode 6