Previously...
I guess you're probably
surprised to see me here, Wayne.
You and I both know
you're not Doug Rich.
Everyone here
seems to think you are.
- Where'd you get this?
- In the woods where you buried it.
- I want to give it to Pete.
- You're going to bribe Pete?
You can't bribe Pete.
I have to try.
If you ask me, you never
should have let him go back.
- Well, I'm not asking you.
- Pete, you okay?
- Jesus!
- I scared you.
I know you're scared.
This is what we do.
We can do this, all right?
We work when we're together.
You know that.
- Well, we're not together, okay?
- What did you do with Pete?
Let's go for a little stroll.
You killed him.
I hit him, and then...
But he fought back.
You murdered him!
Where the hell are Doug
and Cherien Rich?
We split apart. We come back together.
We go on the road.
- This is how we live our lives.
- I changed my mind.
- As it happens, I do have them.
- Have what?
- The guts.
- Tell him not to touch me!
You looking for this?
I should have stopped earlier.
I don't like the smell of this town.
We're gonna get a car,
and get out of here.
Bayou hills, Doug.
We can't pass it up.
If this goes through,
Panco makes $150 million,
and you cash in
on a baker's dozen...
$13 million, Doug.
$13 million?
Put the gun down, Dale.
Just how do you want this to end?
Do you want to go to prison or...
do you want to be my partner?
50-50.
- Is she dead?
- Ma?
Wrap that steak in a napkin.
Go steal me a car.
Well, everything's all right.
Just where do you think
you're going?
Jesus.
This is my van.
Your van?
This looks just like our van,
sir... just like our van.
Shut the hell up.
Think I'm a goddamn moron?
Jesus.
- Get in back!
- Me?
I am done taking shit.
Drive.
Your boss has some great taste
in jewelry.
Where's the light?
I don't know, Hugh.
- Probably stuck in traffic somewhere.
- Lord.
So, what we gonna do about Pete?
Shut up, Dale.
First we cover his tracks.
Then we bury his body.
Are you really gonna execute us?
Shut up!
You flea-bitten shit bag!
Shut up or you're going back
to the pound!
Just because the phone rings
don't mean you got to answer it.
Sir?
I know you're upset because it appeared
that we were taking your van.
Maybe you could take
a nice deep breath.
- This is Bob Day.
- Hi, there, Mr. Day.
This is Rosemary from
the collection agency.
And I'm calling to find out
whether...
You are very stressed.
I know we are living
in very stressful times.
They call it the information age,
but it's really the age of stress.
That's why so many people
take antidepressants.
Shut up!
Jesus Christ!
I can't hear my own thoughts!
- This is Bob Day.
- Hello, Mr. Day.
This is Rosemary calling again.
I tell you what, Rosemary.
I'll send the check in.
And I'll send it in
when I'm goddamn good and ready.
- That's right. Yeah.
- I'm gonna put my manager on the phone.
Fine. No. Put your manager
on the phone.
'cause your manager
can kiss my hairy ass!
- My god!
- What the hell you doing?
Are you out of your goddamn mind?
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Don't do this to me!
- You pace around watching tv.
- Now, what are you doing?!
- Don't you do that!
- Don't do that!
- The son of a bitch is crazy.
I'm tired of you calling me
an asshole!
I'm tired of you...
I thought I told you
I was done taking shit.
Now sit down.
Sit down!
Are you insane?
Nobody steals my goddamn van.
So you're just gonna
execute them?
Do you have to undermine
everything I do?
Gee, why would I undermine you?
You're holding a gun
to a little boy's head.
There's just been
a misunderstanding, ma'am.
We got confused in the heat.
- Why didn't you just call the cops?
- Look at them, miss know-it-all.
What?
They're travelers,
gypsies, scum of the earth.
They're here to rip us off
like the other ones.
The cops ain't gonna do shit.
They're just gonna pay them off.
You're traveler scum?
- No, we...
- We're on our way to a funeral, ma'am.
Yeah, it was our grandmother.
Our grandmother.
She had a heart attack.
We were just on the way
to the funeral, I swear to god.
Transcript
swsub.com
Synchro
Jarick, Grischka
I can't breathe.
I think I'm gonna faint.
My kids are burning up.
Can they please just put their
hands down to fan themselves?
Shut up, bob.
We're not psycho.
Put your hands down.
Thank you, ma'am.
We were supposed to get
air-conditioning this summer,
but somebody
didn't get a job.
Why don't you just fan them
personally?
Why don't you put in
a swimming pool for them?
I'm trying to show them
a little common decency.
You don't show travelers
common decency.
They spit on your common decency.
Sir, I understand that you have
strong feelings about this,
but what do you got
against travelers?
Come on.
We're gonna take
a little field trip.
Shut up!
Show them, Amber.
This guy comes by about
six months ago, real fat guy.
Name plate, helmet.
Says he's in termite control.
We got an infestation. Charges us
an arm and a leg to get rid of them.
Had to take an advance
out on our credit card.
- Now they're charging us 19% interest.
- That's right.
Turns out that bastard put
those termites into our wood.
You think the fat ass
gave you termites?
Yep.
I don't think that's possible.
Maybe you already had an infestation.
- Shut up!
- She's right.
We should have had
a termite check.
I'm juggling, Amber.
I'm fighting to keep all of
our financial balls in the air.
You're fighting?!
60 hours a week!
60 hours a week on my feet at wal-mart
- while you laze around on your ass!
- I'm not lazing around!
Watching tv, hanging around,
threatening to execute children!
- Can I...
- Stay out of it!
I was just saying it's stress.
That's all.
It's just stress.
It's destroying your marriage.
- What do you know about my marriage?
- Nothing.
I'm just...
I know it's money.
Money is the problem.
So?
So, how much money would it take
to get rid of your stress?
Don't listen
to this traveler shit.
Can you put the gun down, please?
Please?
Thank you.
I'm just asking you a question.
I'm just suggesting a possibility.
How much would it take?
I thought you called your office,
told them that you had the flu.
Why are we here?
Pete's rental car,
we got to return it.
I like the way you think.
- God is in the details.
- Shit!
Meryl Streep said that on tv.
- What?
His keys.
They must be in his pocket.
Shit.
- Check the other pocket.
- All right, all right.
Christ.
You got them?
Got them.
Kimmie! Hi!
I thought you had the flu.
Don't come close. I got this cold.
It's really contagious, okay?
Hang back.
Hi. It's a hot one today?
Do I know you?
I'm a friend of doug's.
I'm taking him to the hospital.
Poor guy.
Sick as a dog.
Yeah.
So, you work at panco?
That must be pretty exciting, right?
You're probably pretty important.
I rope through
the accounting receipts.
All I'm saying is
maybe we can help you
get more of what you need,
which is money.
Don't listen to her, sweetheart.
These people got tongues of silk.
They can sell you the fleas off our dog.
No, I'm not trying
to sell you nothing.
I'm asking you,
what do you need?
Me?
What do I need?
What do you need?
I'm hearing all these people calling,
telling you they want this from
you, they want that from you.
I'm asking, what do you need?
What's gonna make you feel better?
What do you want?
What do you think you deserve?
What are you entitled to?
- He needs to...
- You are gonna listen.
You're not gonna put him down.
You're not gonna tell him
how he's failed.
Okay?
'cause he gets it.
Why don't you just let him
tell you what he needs?
What do you need, Bob?
- I need my space.
- Yeah.
Good. That's good.
He needs space.
How about you, Amber?
Jesus Christ.
I don't know where to start.
- Well, start anywhere, sweetheart.
- He forgot our anniversary.
Okay, all right, so...
You need a gift, right?
I'm thinking earrings.
- Some nice earrings maybe?
- You know, I could see you
- in some really nice gold hoops.
- Okay, that's like 50 bucks.
$200. You don't want none of
that gold-plate shit.
You want the real thing.
Anything else?
I need my sundays off.
I need a fan for the kitchen.
Fan. That's $100.
- I need cable.
- Cable, $65 a month.
- I'm tired of internet dial-up.
- Yeah, high-speed.
- And I need a vacation.
- Vacation. Let's say disneyland?
- $1,000 apiece?
- I really, really need a vacation.
And I need to get my hair done.
And I need to be beautiful.
We got, $6,158.87.
Round that up to a nice 7 grand
and give you two a cushion.
Great. Okay.
Is that everything?
- I guess.
- Okay, good.
So, 7 grand's
what I'm gonna get you.
- You're gonna give us 7 grand?
- In cash.
You just got to give us
till midnight.
Well, what do you think,
that we're stupid?
You go.
We'll keep the kids
till you get back.
By midnight.
I can't do it without my kids.
My children are integral
to my operation.
I'll stay.
If they don't come back,
you can shoot me.
I got nothing to lose.
I'm already getting a divorce,
and my...
daughter hates my guts.
Y'all don't come back, the lady dies.
That clear?
Get the hell out of here
before I lose my nerve.
We love you, Nina.
We are coming back for you.
- Sit down.
- Yeah. Okay.
Ma, where are we gonna get
$7,000 in Blunt, Texas?
I'm working on it.
You know, that football game
is all we got.
Yeah, you're right, mom.
Game's where the action is.
It starts at 7:00.
The buffers are gonna know
we're not from around here.
So we go to military school.
Yeah, tell them we're just here
for the game.
- Came back to support Carson.
- Who?
Carson Emory is last year's
quarterback, shattered his knee.
He's in college now,
but his pro-ball prospects
- don't look good.
- You thinking of the spit and shine?
How many hero cars are we gonna
find in Blunt, Texas?
Only need one.
You know what?
I really appreciate your input,
but I'm gonna do this alone.
There's no way you're doing this
by yourself.
No, I am 'cause...
It's been a while. And, you know,
you guys are a bit rusty.
Mom, we can do this.
You can't, okay?
You can't go to jail.
I can't have that.
What about what you said?
- What I said when?
- Packing.
Come on. "We split up. We come back
together. We live our lives."
If this is how we want to live,
this is how we got to
keep living, right?
We're still travelers.
Screw them.
Let's roll the dice.
Well, I just can't believe
you listened to me.
We love you, too.
I can do a last wish.
Honey.
You don't have to do that.
I don't want them to shoot Nina.
Hi, there.
Welcome back, folks.
You pay your bill
and you walk away.
- Excuse me?
- Shut your mouth.
I saw you steal from that lady
this morning.
You pay your bill
and you walk away
and you never
show your face here again.
Okay, now we're gonna screw them.
Nice to have you back.
- Supplies, what do we need?
- We need signs.
We need t-shirts.
- Patriot gear.
- Red carpet.
- What else?
- Raffle tickets.
Maybe a short skirt.
Okay, by 5:00 we got to get
the patriot lineup down.
No problem.
I hate her.
I didn't know you travelers
bothered with divorce.
What?
You said you were getting a divorce.
This has been the worst year
of my life.
It's medical.
To ease the pain.
- We're washing cars!
- Shake it. Shake it. Come on.
I feel like a whore.
Good. Yeah.
Okay.
All right. Running back stats.
Robert Blagman, 1,900 yards,
25 plays per game average.
Tight end stats?
Sam Sullivan, 1,600 yards,
11 plays per game average.
- You're gonna know that shit, right?
- I know it. I got it.
Cougars fan?
Patriots. Beautiful Escalade, though.
You want me to buff it out?
- Go for a joyride, I'll ring your neck.
- Done. $5, please.
Make sure you get the grime
that's caked under the mud caps.
Thank you, sir.
That dickhead shortchanged me.
So? We got our hero car.
Maribelle Johnson.
87 years old,
beloved grandmother.
It says here the funeral
will be today and tomorrow.
Jesus, do I have to spell
everything out for you?
You know what?
I personally am not in the habit
of disposing of corpses,
so maybe I don't possess
the corpse-disposing finesse
that you do.
We have to dig an extra 3 feet
to create a false bottom.
Get it?
Get in.
You don't get to order me around.
Man.
We really are buffers.
What's up?
Nothing.
Don't tell me you're gonna miss
Edenfalls that much.
No, I just...
You know, I didn't even
get to say goodbye to Erick.
I don't want to just disappear,
you know?
Call him.
Tell him dad got transferred to Biloxi.
Yeah, that's what i'm gonna tell him
to explain to him why
i'm never gonna see him again.
Well, if it makes you feel
any better,
I always thought
he was kind of a douche.
Look, you're not gonna
remember him in a week.
I promise.
Yeah, I guess.
Okay. Ready to go.
This reminds me of that story
about the scorpion and the goat,
where they want to get
across the river.
But the scorpion don't go
with the goat because he...
Wait, no, there was also a cabbage.
Right, so, the scorpion
and the goat and the cabbage
want to get across the river.
A cabbage cannot want
to get across a river.
It's a story, Wayne.
A cabbage cannot want
to get across a river.
It's a cabbage. That's the difference
between a cabbage...
and you.
I know the difference between
a cabbage and myself, Wayne.
You always talk to me
like I'm a moron.
I am not a moron.
You know what your problem is, Wayne?
You always think you're better
than everyone else.
We're gonna bury Pete here,
and then that's the end
of our little collaboration.
I'm gonna get in my car.
I'm gonna drive a long way
from here,
and I'm never
gonna see you again.
You've obviously forgotten
about our mutually assured destruction.
It seems to me you could stay
now that I solved
your little problem.
With Pete taken care of,
you could walk away with $13 million
without batting an eye.
Think about
what you could do with $13 million.
You could buy a house.
You could buy three houses.
Hell, you could sail around the world.
You can have everything
that you ever wanted for you
and your precious family.
The body in that trunk
is starting to smell,
and you and I both know
what it smells like.
It smells like freedom,
and it smells like money.
I knew Pete,
all right?
A few hours ago,
he was a living, breathing person.
He sat in my house.
He talked to me about his life.
I had dinner with him.
I always liked the guy.
He'll be dead
whether you take the money or not.
Shut up.
You know you're thinking about it.
Just like Doug Rich.
- Shut up.
- You did kill him.
It wasn't my fault!
It was an accident.
Just like it was an accident
that I killed Pete.
You bludged him!
You smashed his skull with a hammer!
I feel real bad about that.
Which is why you and I...
are so alike.
Get back to work.
Grave ain't go dig itself.
Please leave a message.
If you'd like to leave...
Patriots, yeah!
Are you in Galveston yet?
We got stuck in Blunt, Texas.
Shit. Shit.
Oh, God. Look at my hands.
Do you have any more
of that hand sanitizer shit?
'Cause these open sores,
they can be really dangerous.
I can get an infection and die.
You're not gonna die from a blister.
Hugh says the viruses get in there,
and then they'll poison all your blood.
And viruses are everywhere.
Mutants.
Can't kill them
'cause they're resistant to everything.
He says it's 'cause of the hormones
that we give to cows.
Will you help me?
So, what do you think?
Yes, I think you will die of a virus.
I'm talking about all that money.
What if someone comes looking for him?
You said he didn't have friends.
He's got a mother.
Oh, shit.
I didn't think about his mother.
We should probably say a few words.
Dear Pete...
I'm sorry Dale bashed your brains in.
Amen.
Well, if somebody does come looking,
you just spew some bullshit.
That's what you're good at.
I just want
a little piece of the action, Wayne...
a little job at Panco.
Have some respect, for God's sakes.
Hang in there, big guy.
What's your wish?
What?
I really want to go to...
It's okay, honey.
Don't tire yourself out.
You are doing such a great job, okay?
Wheeze more.
Ah, Christ.
You really got to scrub.
That dirt really gets caked in there.
Wayne, we're in trouble.
We're in real bad trouble.
We're stuck.
We're in Blunt, Texas.
Nina's being held hostage
by some crazy guy with a gun.
You got to get here.
Hey, you want some water for your hands?
Are you still in Blunt?
I hope you're there.
I fixed the RV.
I got delayed, but I'm on my way.
The worst part was the alpacas.
I didn't know travelers had alpacas.
They were Jim's.
Jim and his goddamn alpacas.
Why did Jim have alpacas?
I don't know.
For the wool?
He's gay.
Them gays and their goddamn wool.
I don't care that he's gay.
I'm happy for him.
I'm happy he's happy.
But everything he told me was a lie.
When he said he loved me,
that was a lie.
When he told me I was beautiful,
that was a lie, too.
I think you're beautiful.
You don't have to say that.
I mean it.
Well, I feel invisible.
I know what you mean.
Ever since Desert Storm,
I lie around
while the world passes me by.
I just didn't feel like
I was good enough,
like I don't...
Like I don't deserve to be loved.
That is just so wrong, Bob.
I'm sorry.
I've been such a...
bitch to you.
You have such nice fingers, Bob.
Would you excuse us?
Don't mind me.
Don't go anywhere, all right?
I wouldn't want to have to blow
your head off at this point in the game.
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean? What's it look like?
Didn't sally talk to you?
Yeah, it's for the raffle.
So Carson can get his knee surgery.
Whoever wins gets a new Escalade.
Who donated the car?
Let's just say...
it was a member
of the Blunt football family, you know.
"It takes a village."
Don't you want Carson to play again?
- How much are tickets?
- Tickets are 20 bucks.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Okay, now, here's what I want you to do.
Spit on it,
and rub it on this here
Carson Emory-signed football for luck.
Sweet.
So, what do you think
of Carson's chances?
- Do you think he could start for TCU?
- That's what we're hoping.
It's the best surgery we got.
It's a new experimental surgery
over at Johns Hopkins,
so if the surgery works,
the sky is the limit.
Thank you for helping.
God, that's $100. You want five tickets?
Who's this?
Doug...
I mean Wayne?
Nina! Where are you?
$40, $60, $80...
$6,400.
Plus whatever Sam got.
Let's get Sam, get out of here
before that kid comes back
for his Escalade.
What gives? I heard you guys
are raising money for me.
Oh, good God.
I thought you said
he was still in college.
God, Carson, it's such an honor
that you came to the game.
Yeah, I never like to miss a big game.
Yeah, no. Me either.
God, I love watching you score.
I do.
God, do you remember that game
last september, six seconds to go,
the Patriots are down 45-41,
and you threw that unbelievable pass
to the 15-yard line? Do you remember?
- There was a lot of luck involved.
- That wasn't luck. That was a miracle.
I almost cried.
Okay, let's get Sam.
We'll circle back for Di Di.
I remember them.
I knew it was you,
the minute I heard some assholes
were selling raffle tickets. Grab them!
These people are frauds!
They are using the good name
of Carson Emory to steal your money!
They're not even Patriot fans!
Stop hitting my kid!
- There's no experimental surgery?
- Look, there's still hope.
Shut up, you traveler bitch.
- We got you 6 grand!
- Shut up!
Please don't touch him!
Hey, come on!
Leave him alone!
Shit.
Stay there.
Don't hit him!
Stop it!
Get off!
Everybody freeze!
This is the FBI!
All right, this is an FBI operation.
Everybody stand down.
Sir, put the bat down.
Put it down.
I want you, you, and you
against the fence.
These three. Come on. Move it.
Let's go. Come on, missy.
Assume the position.
These people are travelers.
There are more in the stadium.
Watch out for them.
Watch for your wallets.
Watch for your bags.
This is an FBI operation.
There are other agents in the stadium.
Everyone go back to the game.
Just relax and enjoy yourselves.
I've got the woman and the two kids.
Hands behind the back, Missy.
The show is over here.
Well done, everybody.
Excellent.
All right, you three,
let's head this way.
Sir, could you grab my purse?
Thank you.
We're going to the north fence.
We are going to the north exit.
All right, show's over, kids.
Everyone back to the game.
We're out of here. FBI operation.
We know what we're doing here.
Oh, God.
Cal, you're bleeding like a stuck pig.
Put your head back.
- Is it broken?
- I don't know. Let me see.
I don't think so.
We just got rusty.
Our skills got real rusty.
Geez.
- Let's go.
- Come on, baby.
Okay, hit it, Wayne!
We got to get our timing back.
Would you stop moving your head around?
How'd you find us? How'd you find her?
I found him, and we found you.
Using our charm
and powers of persuasion.
How's it going, Di Di?
It's good.
Dad, I think
the 55 is about a mile up ahead.
But we got to give the Days the 7 grand.
They held us at gunpoint.
If we don't, they're gonna think
all travelers are scum.
- Why would they think that?
- You know what?
Sam's right. A deal's a deal.
We got to go back.
Hon, I think Bob and Amber
are gonna be just fine.
We forgot ma!
Make a left right here.
She's not your mama!
I am not leaving my ma to rot with
jew-hating rednecks. Make that left!
She's not a jew.
Oh, yeah, she is a jew. Okay.
You're not Cherien.
Let's get out of here.
I hear you've been a bad ma.
Thank you, Doug.
You don't need that no more, mama.
God.
I thought
they were gonna kill Cal back there.
He'll be okay.
You weren't there when that freak
held a gun to his head.
I never used to get scared.
That's the thing... That's the thing
that messed up my timing.
What happened with Pete?
Did he take the money?
Pete went home.
He went home?
He took the money?
Sam was right.
Money makes the world go around.
I knew it.
I told you.
What?
You think it's safe to go back now?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Don't be stupid. He's gonna want more.
You think that's his price?
40 grand?
He's gonna own us.
The minute you get what you think
you want, you always want more.
He's not gonna want more.
Everybody wants more... Everybody.
As soon as we get back.
We're going back to Edenfalls?
No, Dad, we can't keep being the Riches.
He's gonna own our goddamn souls.
Look, do I look like I'm driving back?
I mean,
we said Mexico,
we're going to Mexico.
Adiós.
What?
That's all the spanish I know...
Adiós and gracias.
I'm pretty sure they speak
a lot of english in Mexico.
You've never been there.
Where are we gonna live?
How are we gonna get money?
Live in the RV...
you know,
make money like we always did.
You gonna con in spanish?
Si, señorita.
You can't con in spanish.
Hell, I can barely con
in English anymore apparently.
Well, we'll make do.
- We always do.
- You know...
We could keep paying him off.
Ma, we're not going back to Edenfalls.
I'm just saying it's possible.
- Then what?
- I don't know.
See what happens.
See... how it rides.
- We roll the dice?
- In Edenfalls?
Shit, cal, what's your better idea?
Take our chances in some shithole
and you get your ass beat
every day by some townies?
Who knows, next place we go,
you might actually get killed.
At least we'd be doing something
we want to do.
Instead of sitting around in Edenfalls
turning into a bunch of rich assholes.
Situations can change, you know.
What do you mean?
Well...
I wasn't gonna tell you this, but...
There is another way.
I saw Hugh last night, and he's got
one of these big deals closing.
He's always got
some big-ass deal going on.
Yeah, but it's $150 million.
My cut would be 13.
Million?
That's right.
$13 million?
It's a land deal.
If everything goes right,
it should be a few months.
If Pete's a problem,
then we'll just pay him off again.
- Why the hell are we going to Mexico?
- What about Dale?
What the hell is he doing in Edenfalls,
and what does he want from us?
I'll deal with Dale.
Maybe we could buy a house on an island.
For $13 million,
we can get our own castle in Ireland.
- This real?
- Yeah. I saw the papers.
All we got to do is
be the Riches for a few months.
Deal closes, we cash in, check out,
and adiòs, just like any other con.
$13 million?
Well, then we wouldn't always
have to be running.
We wouldn't always have
to be scared of every redneck cop.
Every man has his price.
Now, it's not about that, Cal.
No? What's it about?
It's about being free.
So, which way?
Okay.
Wayne Malloy's got himself
a $150 million deal.