Previously on "The Riches"...
This is a school?
A private school.
- Miss Fedley's the head of Rosemere.
- You're interested in Rosemere?
Why do you want to break in?
The computers
hold the key to our future.
You get us inside,
Lane'll care of the rest.
You now have an A- in calculus.
And where the hell
is my best friend, Doug Rich?
You can't bribe Pete.
I have to try.
Pete, you okay?
Jesus!
- I scared you.
- What did you do with Pete?
You killed him.
I hit him, and then...
But he fought back.
You murdered him!
We said 50-50.
We are in this together.
We're gonna bury Pete, and then
that's the end of our collaboration.
And I'm never gonna see you again.
What happened with Pete?
- Did he take the money?
- Pete's fine. Everything's all right.
Pete went home.
Bayou Hills, it's the deal
of a lifetime, Doug.
$150 million,
- and you cash in on $13 million.
- $13 million?
$13 million?
All we got to do is be
the Riches for a few months,
the deal closes,
we cash in, check out,
and adiós. Just like any other con.
This is home.
Yeah, ma...
For the time being, anyhow.
I'll have a grande mochaccino.
- Yeah, I call the jacuzzi.
- I got the couch in front of the tv.
Think I'm gonna sleep
for about three days.
You're under arrest for breaking
and entering rosemere academy.
That's ridiculous.
- They're just kids.
- Who committed a second-degree felony.
- Excuse me. My son was brought here.
- Name?
Rich, Cal Rich.
We're holding him with the others.
Pay the bail, and he's yours.
- Shit.
- Cal Rich is it?
Now, is he new in school this year?
That name doesn't sound familiar.
Yeah, we just moved here from Tampa.
H.L. Palmer. Kid's brent.
This is Bob Spurlock.
His kid's Willie.
And Afton Boatright, father of Lane.
So what's the story?
Boys supposedly had a business going,
charged money for changing grades.
Little shits are facing
felony computer-fraud charges,
not to mention
breaking and entering.
Ask me, a couple of months
in youth authority
might not be a bad thing
for these boys.
That's fine unless you want your kid
getting into college someday,
'cause no one's getting into
princeton with a criminal record.
I think it's in all our best interests
if we just work on this together.
How do you suggest we do that?
Strategy meeting.
Discuss our options.
What's say I get my secretary
set us all a lunch for tomorrow?
Good.
- Where do I pay this?
- Over there.
- Do you take checks?
- Bail bonds or cash.
- They let you out of the pokey?
- It's not a joke, Di di.
- Could do time for this.
- Come on, ma, I bumped the lock.
I didn't even let them
change my grades.
- Did they take your prints?
- Photographed me and everything.
Great.
With a criminal record, you'll
never get into college now.
Like I'm going to college.
I don't think college
is really the issue.
You don't know
what you're gonna do?
But now you may not
have the option.
Dad, I haven't been convicted yet.
Besides, maybe I should just
disappear for a while.
No, no, this family is gonna
stick together no matter what.
We're just staying around
long enough to get the money,
and then we cash out,
and we're gone.
There's a castle in Galway for sale.
We could get it for $3 million.
That's what i'm talking about.
I'd settle for just
being the Malloys.
Malloys with a shitload of money.
Come on, put you to bed.
Good night.
Is that me?
I need a shower.
That boy can't go to prison.
I won't let it happen.
There's no amount of money
that's worth it.
He is not going to prison.
This time, everything's different.
We're in the big leagues now.
I'm Doug Rich,
a lawyer.
I have power and money
and credibility.
This time,
they can't screw us.
You're not Doug.
Transcript
swsub.com
Subtitles
Jarick, Grischka
FIELD OF DREAMS
Quinn, let's go,
unless you want to stay
for a couple more decades.
I left that book there
for you on the bed.
Do you some good.
You never stop.
Got to go. Schooltime.
- Yes!
- No!
It's just like a normal day.
Everyone doing things as normal.
Not for me.
As soon as I've sorted out your problem,
you're going to school, too.
I got a meeting with Fedley
tomorrow to discuss your arrest.
Okay, everybody's late.
The bus is gonna be here.
You got to get your backpacks.
Di di, come on,
get your clothes on.
- Come on.
- Shit.
Hey, Aubrey, how's it going?
Hugh didn't show up
for an investor meeting.
- What meeting?
- Something about Bayou hills.
Shit.
Tell them he had emergency
appendectomy and reschedule.
Appendectomy?
I'll try and track him down.
What?
Hugh's not there,
didn't turn up again.
I think I know where he is.
You go to work.
I'll meet you there.
What am I supposed to do at Panco?
Just be normal.
Normal day, just like every...
I have to go to
the lunch thing for Cal.
Why not?
Well, you see
with these guys, it's a guy thing.
- Hi, there.
- Hi, Nina.
Hi, Wayne.
So, what's the plan?
The plan?
Well, kids go to school,
and I go to work.
- That's the plan.
- Everything's back to normal?
Normal.
I'm a normal gal.
Wayne's a normal guy.
We're just normal folk
living a normal life, Nina.
Sorry, it's just how it is.
I got to go to work.
Cal made bail.
Normal sucks.
What?
What do you want, Doug?
You had an investors' meeting
this morning. You weren't there.
Screw 'em!
Those guys are minor league.
There are plenty more
where they came from.
What happened to this thing
we were gonna do?
Remember, Bayou Hills,
$150 million, deal of a lifetime?
Relax, we're doing it.
- I just got to do something first.
- Like what?
Like get laid.
- You're drunk.
- Nope.
- sober as a judge.
- What about Gigi?
Well, there's other ships
in the sea, ain't there?
In fact, I'm expecting one
to dock any minute now.
No, no, no, we got a deadline.
Five days, right?
We got to raise this money.
You can do whatever
you want to do,
but I'm getting me
a little taste this morning.
I'd invite you to stay,
but I'm not into that kinky shit.
- Hugh, if you just...
- I know, I know.
I just got to spend some time
with somebody
who doesn't want anything
from me, somebody who...
appreciates me
for what I have to offer.
I get hard at the drop of a hat.
Good.
Thank you for that.
At the drop of a hat, Doug!
I just got to take care
of some business.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Why don't you just come into work?
Be right there!
Well, with the two of you,
$1,500.
- No, thank you, he's not my type.
- Come on in, sweetheart.
- You will be coming in to work?
- Don't you worry.
- Give me the name of a good restaurant.
- Roger's. Best steak in town.
I want to see you in...
It is time for little Hugh
to get himself some.
How are your grades, Di di?
Great. How's the herpes, Kami?
Shut up.
It's regarding my son Cal.
Can you tell Mrs. Fedley that
it's Cherien Rich calling again?
- Yes, I can.
- Yeah, it's very important.
- I know that, but she's very busy.
- Well, I appreciate she's very busy.
Maybe you can remind her
I was very busy the day
that I found her goddamn bird.
You don't have to have profanity.
As soon as she has some time, I will
let her know that you're calling-
- Crap.
- Excuse me?
I got to go, sweetheart.
Hey, there, Cherien.
- Welcome back.
- What you doing here, Dale?
- I'm here to see Doug.
- Well, he's not here, so goodbye.
- I'll wait.
- No, you can't wait.
He's gonna be gone a long time.
Would you leave?
He is expecting me.
What?
Yeah, you can just ask him.
I'll be right over here, and...
I'll read this here magazine,
contractor journal.
Leave a message.
Wayne, would you call me back,
god damn it?
Dale is at Panco, okay?
Call me back.
Son of a bitch.
Geez.
- Thank you.
Shit.
- Gentlemen.
- You come here often?
This is a total mistake.
It's a little,
you know, my friend Hugh
suggested this place.
That's right.
You work with Panetta.
Yeah.
Well, this looks like the sort of place
Hugh Panetta might frequent.
Sure does.
Isn't he married
to a stripper?
There's an excellent chinese restaurant
just across the street.
I know I can get us in there.
So, what do you say? Chinese restaurant,
we'll cross the street, eat there?
I have heard they have some
nicely marbled kobe beef here.
Let's go.
Follow her?
Here's good.
I am sick of waiting.
Let me talk to Hugh.
About what?
About a job.
A job?
- Well, that ain't gonna happen, Dale.
- We'll see.
- Ask him.
- Why would he want to talk to you?
Because him and me got real friendly
the other night at your house.
At my house?
Yeah, him and me and Wayne,
had a good old time.
You might even say we bonded.
You were with them at my house?
I guess Wayne didn't tell you.
That is interesting.
Fedley's a bitch.
Always has been.
Of course, I'm one
of the only board members
who didn't endorse her, so...
she's gonna take this thing
and run with it.
- Very nice.
- $2,500 a bottle, it better be.
So, couldn't we just sue Rosemere?
We could make pursuing this case
very expensive for them.
Dance?
- Now, sweetheart, what is your name?
- Jasmine.
No, thank you. We're working.
- Lighten up, Bob.
- That's right, Bob.
Later then.
- If Muriel was to find out I was here.
- She's not here.
Isn't there something we can do
about Fedley before tomorrow's meeting?
- Like what, Doug, kill her?
- Well...
in my experience,
everyone has their price.
I don't know
where you're from, Doug,
but around here,
we don't bribe.
Of course not.
We donate.
Excellent.
Well, let's donate.
What do we donate to?
That school's always
got its hand out for something.
- Is there anything that Fedley needs?
- To get laid.
Okay, besides that.
She wants a new gym
to compete with Burton's.
She's always hocking the board
about raising more money for it.
- We're still short a million.
- That's it. We get her a gym.
We give her a million?
I'd say keeping my kid
out of jail is worth $250,000.
- How about you fellas?
- Think that would do it?
I'm betting she wants that gym more
than she wants to put our kids away.
- Hell, I'm in.
- Me too. Doug?
I don't see why not.
$250,000?
You need to run that by Muriel?
Look, I'm just really
not that liquid right now.
I think it's a good idea.
I'm just not able
to swing it right now.
Anyway,
my kid says that
he didn't break in or anything.
He just paid
to have his grades changed.
That don't make your kid
any less culpable, Bob.
That's all right.
We'll work something out.
We're all in this together, right?
Excuse me, fellas.
Take your time.
- Hey, baby.
- So,
Dale was at our house when
you saw Hugh the other night?
What are you talking about?
Dale.
Dance?
What?
Dale is here at Panco.
Didn't you get my message?
He's there right now?
Yeah, Wayne, he's here.
He's here.
He's going on about you guys
drinking at my house.
- I told you about that, didn't i?
- No.
No, you didn't.
I told you about Hugh coming over.
Yeah.
And then Dale showed up.
Dale showed up.
Yeah.
Where was Pete during all this?
He'd gone by then,
long gone, gone home.
Sorry, baby.
I forgot to mention Dale.
It's been a crazy couple of days.
Where are you?
I'm still at the Cal
lunch-meeting thing.
Well,
Dale wants to ask you
for a job right now.
Look, baby,
can you deal with that?
I got to go here. All right, bye.
You're home early.
I hate those people.
What happened?
Nothing.
Sorry.
- What?
- We need to talk.
- About what?
- My job at Panco.
I never promised you a job at Panco.
I said I would do what I could.
Well, I like Panco.
Panco isn't really you, Dale.
You said you'd get me a job.
Now, go get me a job at Panco.
- As what?
- I don't know.
Whatever you are.
Well, you're not me, Dale!
You're never gonna be me, right?
I will do
what I can, but I can't guarantee
it's gonna be at Panco.
Eamon Quinn!
Free as a bird.
Well, how is it, man?
It must be pretty weird?
The world must look really
different to you after 20 years.
I bet you never seen no cellphones,
or gameboys
or internet porn.
So, what have you got for me?
I got Wayne Malloy wrapped
around my little finger.
How's that?
It's called people skills, Quinn.
I find I have talent for it.
- That's funny.
- Yeah.
I don't remember that about you.
It's been 20 years.
A lot of life under the bridge.
I've changed.
So, Wayne Malloy?
Yeah, I got like
a mid-level sales position,
just to get the lay of the land
and keep my eye on Wayne.
Bollocks. Wayne Malloy
would never give you that job.
He's not stupid.
Wayne Malloy is not as smart
as you think he is.
I can always tell
when you're full of shit, Dale.
Just like when you were
a spotty, little maggot of 16.
I ain't afraid of you anymore,
Eamon Quinn.
Sure, that's the only thing
I like about you, Dale.
Your one redeeming feature,
you're not that bright.
Still want to be partners?
You make sure you get that job, huh?
Help yourself.
- Shut up.
- What the hell are you doing?
I said...
"shut up."
Now, I got something
I got to say to you, cousin.
Are you crazy?
What is wrong with you?
I am sick and tired of you and Wayne
thinking that you're smarter than me.
I know exactly what you're up to,
and I'm tired
of listening to your bullshit.
Now...
I want you to tell Wayne
to get me a job at Panco,
or you're going back to prison.
It's just one little phone call,
and you're back in the slammer.
How would you like that?
You want to get a job at Panco?
You don't know how to do anything,
you stupid prick.
Get out of here!
It is time you started treating me
with a little respect.
Miss Dahlia.
I am in this thing
whether you like it or not.
And I am gonna get what I want.
God, I love family time.
I want to kill him.
We can't kill him.
I want him to die.
No $13 million, no nothing,
'cause that psycho could turn me
in any time he wants.
But that's not what he's after.
He just wants in on it...
All this...
The dream.
Putting you away
ain't gonna give him shit.
What we gonna do?
We're gonna keep our enemies close.
I think I can get him a job
where he can't cause too much trouble.
At Panco?
Are you crazy?
We ain't got much choice.
He controls our life.
Is that what you're telling me?
And I'm supposed
to just go along with it?
I know what prison is.
This is starting to feel real familiar.
I'm sorry, baby.
It's my fault
that Dale can do this to us.
God damn it.
I'm sorry.
So, that's our new mail boy, huh?
Guess so.
What happened to George?
- That's bullshit.
- George, you're fired.
Deal with it.
Where are you?
You sound like you're in a wind tunnel.
It's the hottest, fastest,
most powerful thing on four wheels,
and it's my ass in the driver's seat.
What are you talking about?
Lamborghini Murcielago LP640 Roadster.
You've already got a car, Hugh.
Several cars.
You don't need a car.
You need to be here at work.
I don't have a car like this, pal.
Do you have any idea
what 640 horsepower feels like?
Whoo, baby!
It's better than sex.
Well, I'm sure it is.
340k, and at that price, it's a steal.
Don't you think it might be
a fun idea to come into work
and try to finance the Bayou Hills deal?
God damn it!
Cal, we got to go.
Cal, we have to be at school
in 10 minutes.
I'm not going.
You're going. You got to be there.
What's the point?
The point is,
if you don't go, you look guilty.
I am guilty.
No, you're not. You are not guilty.
We've worked out a solution,
me and the other dads, so...
just come along and look presentable.
Everything depends upon this.
Everything?
Yes, everything!
Just trust me on this thing.
You're on your way out, huh?
You okay?
It can wait.
Dinner and my dealer...
You want to come?
$1 million.
That is quite a generous donation, H.L.
We'd love to see that new gym built
before the boys graduate, Jane.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I appreciate that.
Now, what can I do for you?
Yes, well...
Your sons broke into my school
and changed
a number of students' grades.
Do you have any idea
how much that could have cost Rosemere
in terms of our reputation?
- We do, and it sickens us...
- Please let me finish.
In all my years at Rosemere,
I have never had
anything like this happen.
If word of this had gotten out
to the college community,
our transcripts
would have been disregarded,
our credibility ruined.
From what we understand, there weren't
that many grades tampered with.
That is not the point, H.L.
Rosemere is dependent on its image
as a scrupulously honest
preparatory school.
Your sons have shat all
over that reputation!
And perhaps
that is the price of privilege.
Jane, we all think that...
I've had to think long and hard
about how to best handle this,
and this is what I've decided.
I will not press charges
against your sons,
provided...
that they tell me who instigated this.
That student will be expelled.
The board is insistent
that I make an example.
So, I put it to you, young gentlemen,
who is it?
Son?
You got something to say?
- It was Willie.
- What?
That's a lie.
Wait, Willie, is this true?
No!
Willie was pissed
about his lousy chemistry grade.
Bullshit.
It was me.
I did it. My whole idea.
I broke into the school.
I changed the grades.
I'm the one that should be punished.
It's only fair.
You should probably expel me.
We good? We done?
You good?
All right, good talk.
Excuse me.
I guess that takes care of it.
What is wrong with you?
Why did you do that?
She agreed to drop the charges.
No one in prison.
Willie could go to another school.
Willie didn't do anything!
Willie had his chemistry grade changed.
It was Brent's idea,
and Lane hacked the computer.
I didn't know
they were gonna blame Willie.
It's not about Willie, Dad.
This is about you, okay?
You sat there and let them nail him.
That's the plan
you were telling me about?
My plan was to keep you out of prison.
I would do anything
to give you the chance I didn't have.
Look, Cal, this world...
it's about power and money,
and that's freedom.
God, Dad, I don't even know who you are.
What you're becoming...
whatever it is,
I don't want anything to do with it.
I'd rather be piss poor with my dad
than $13 million richer
with whoever you are.
Holy mother of shit.
It's Eamon Quinn.
I thought he got life.
How many people
you got to kill these days to get life?
Frank Linehan, that's you?
'Cause you all grown up.
Ain't nobody gonna offer me a beer?
I think you ought to leave.
Little Ginny Dannegan.
Last time I saw you,
you were about 12 years old.
I always knew you'd be a beauty.
You cannot just waltz in here.
I saw you.
I saw what you did
to my daddy and my uncle.
I didn't do nothing
that wasn't meant to be done.
Everybody's got to die sometime.
Memento mori.
Anybody here know what that means?
It means "remember, you're gonna die."
The roman slaves used to say it...
Memento mori.
Remember it,
or you're gonna live your life
like a dumb animal.
Maybe y'all need to read a book
every now and then.
You can take your shot at me now.
Go ahead.
It's the code.
I know you had to do that
on account of what I did
to your daddy and all.
I got no hard feelings.
It would be common courtesy
for somebody to help me to my feet.
Right about now, huh?
Good lads.
Somebody get me something to drink,
for Christ sakes.
Whatever happened to irish hospitality?
What?
I'm scared all the time.
Of what, darling?
Feeling something bad's gonna happen.
Things I should have done, I didn't do.
And now I'm living
in this kind of purgatory.
That's life in Edenfalls, honey.
That's life everywhere.
You know what you need?
I promised Wayne
I wouldn't do that no more.
I'm not talking about drugs, honey.
All I'm saying is you need to...
figure out what it is
that you're afraid of.
What are you afraid of?
Being alone, mostly.
Nobody to be loving me anymore,
Ntaking care of me anymore.
I love you, Nina.
I love you, too.
Now, come on, stop it.
Let's go get us some good shit.
What?
Nina, you're meeting
your dealer at church?
Of course not. It's an A.A. meeting.
What?
No, no, I'm coming right over.
I started using, drinking
around sixth grade.
I dropped out at 10th grade
and started hitchhiking
across the country.
Lost touch with my family.
By the '80s,
I was slamming meth
and robbing people as a way of life.
I ate out of trash cans,
slept in abandoned houses,
until my arrest record
caught up with me,
and I wound up behind bars.
After I did some time,
I got my shit together.
I cleaned up my prison record,
got a whole new life for myself.
It was my 30th birthday.
I figured, things were going so well,
why shouldn't I be able to celebrate?
Two days later,
I woke up in a motel,
naked, sweating, shivering cold.
There I was on parole,
my life hanging by a thread,
and I had relapsed,
and I didn't even know why.
I had a shotgun at the house,
and I thought
I'd put the barrel in my mouth
and pull the trigger.
That way, I'd finally get some peace.
That's it.
Let's get out of here.
Just hold on a second.
As I was walking past my son's bedroom
while he was sleeping,
it hit me.
It's like, "what about him?
"i mean, do you want him to grow up
without a father like you did?"
That straightened me out.
I've been sober ever since.
Thanks for listening
and keep coming back.
Will you just wait for me in the car?
I'm only gonna be a moment.
- Can I talk to you for a minute?
- Sure thing.
Did you ever break parole?
I ain't hanging out
with no more damaged men, okay?
Now you just go, you big, old drunk.
You take him out of here, Doug.
I'm calling the cops.
Hugh, she's gonna call the cops.
She loves this song.
This is her song.
It's my house.
She won't even let me in!
Oh, hell, Doug...
It just doesn't work without her.
What?
None of it.
I lost it, Doug.
You lost what?
My mojo.
Your mojo?
I can't get it up.
Not with a hooker,
not in a Lamborghini, nowhere.
I spent $340,000 on a car.
Something better happen in my pants
or what's the point?
They got pills for that, don't they?
It's not the same. I like it natural.
It only works with Gigi.
I tell you, I'm not a man without her.
I got to get her back.
I'm going to get her back.
That's right... Get her back!
Hugh, that would be a huge mistake.
Gigi stole your mojo.
You go back to her,
and she's just gonna steal more.
She'll suck it right out of your body.
You'll have negative mojo.
Believe me, there's only one way
you're gonna get it back.
How?
You got to reclaim your power.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- This is simple law of physics.
Gigi stole something from you.
You got to replace it
with something equal and opposite.
Yet bigger
and more powerful,
like $150 million...
Bayou Hills, deal of the century,
a lasting legacy to the genius
that is Hugh Panetta.
That's you,
the source of all your power.
Gigi's Delilah to your Samson.
She's kryptonite to your super...
mojo.
And you must avoid her at all costs.
Otherwise...
I don't know.
Well, I do know, Hugh. You got
to get some meaning in your life,
the kind of meaning
that hard-focused, nonstop,
100-hours-a-day-type work's gonna do.
Gigi's is an impediment.
She's an obstacle.
She's a cancer.
You must excise her from your life.
She's toxic.
Most people wouldn't have the balls
to talk to me about my wife like that.
You really are my friend, aren't you?
I love you.
I love you, Doug.
And I'm not even that drunk anymore.
Thank god I puked.
I'm Dahlia Malloy.
And I'm a...
I'm a parole violator.