Previously on The Pretender.
Enough!
We don't want him dead.
[Tires Screeching]
Nice to meet you, Jarod.
I'm Zoe.
- [Jarod] I want to stay with you.
- [Zoe] I know.
But you can't stay, can you?
I can see it in your eyes.
[Jarod] Edna Raines knows things
about your mother, Miss Parker.
I need to talk to you
about your mother and Mirage.
It could be a matter
of life and death.
[Sydney]
Edna Raines is dead.
She knew all the secrets,
especially about the Mirage Project.
[Miss Parker] Jarod's e-mail
said to keep digging.
It's your mother's grave. Miss Parker,
your mother- she's not here.
Then where the hell is she?
Oh, come on. Everybody's been on
at least one vacation.
I swear, Zoe,
I've never been on vacation.
Not even, uh, Mount Rushmore?
- The Alamo?
- Mm-mmm.
What about Niagara Falls?
I definitely would have
remembered that.
Wait, I did eat at a "Stookey's"
off of I-65 once. Does that count?
"Stuckey's." Only if
you bought the pecan log.
- What's a pecan log?
- Oh, you really have never
had a vacation, have you?
Who needs a vacation...
when I have you?
You swear to me
you're in total remission?
Yeah. I probably pissed off
a few H.M.O.'s, but what the hell?
- Zoe-
- Hey.
You're not going
all mushy on me, are you?
- [Ringing]
- [Electronic Voice]
You have a video phone call.
That's my video phone.
- Um, I'll be right back.
- Okay.
[Ringing Continues]
- Hello, Son.
- Oh, my God! Dad!
I've been searching for you for over a year.
Where have you been?
I know. The boy and I
had to go underground for a while.
We kept searching for you too,
but with no luck...
until an anonymous tip came my way.
I was able to unscramble your password,
which got me into you here.
- Then you're both okay?
- Thank God the boy and I are both well.
- The boy?
- He's sort of like my brother. I'll-
I'll explain it to you sometime.
Dad, this is Zoe.
- Zoe, this is my dad.
- Jarod's been pretty damn worried
about you, sir.
He's cute.
What happened to you?
When can I see you?
We have to be careful.
I don't trust the security of this line...
so I'll make it quick.
Jarod, I found Emily.
I found your sister.
What? How? Where is she?
She's a reporter at the Philadelphia Examiner.
For security's sake...
I've left vital information about
her where abouts on your secured e-mail.
She told me that recently,
she was very close to finding you.
She cried when I told her
I knew how to reach you.
I think you should go to her.
- Will you bring her back to me, Jarod?
- Yes!
- Yes, of course I will.
- Good luck, Son. Keep me posted.
My- I found my dad.
Um-
My- I-We've been looking
for my sister for so long...
and now I found her, and I can, uh-
Um-What about our trip?
It can wait.
We'll have time.
And if I have any say in the matter,
lots of it.
You're not gettin' all mushy on me,
are you?
Go find your sister.
[Man]
Somebody call 911!
[Woman]
She's in the alley!
- What happened?
- A reporter was attacked.
- They say she was thrown out of that window.
- A reporter?
An Emily something.
Emily? Emily!
Emily? Emily?
- Please help me.
- That's what I'm here to do.
I'm going to help you.
I'm Jarod. I'm your brother.
- Jarod.
- Stay with me. Stay with me.
- [Gasps, Coughs]
- Emily? Emily?
Somebody call an ambulance!
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent
every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
- [Miss Parker] He defends the weak and abused.
- [Jarod] Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
- Pupils are unresponsive.
Respiration is shallow at 40.
- Pulse is weak and thready.
Probable closed head injury with
internal bleeding and multiple fractures.
Keep her head stabilized.
Start an I.V. drip and run a C.B.C.
Page Radiology. We need
an abdominal and head CAT scan, stat.
- Who initiated C.P.R.?
- I did.
Your actions may have saved her life.
Are you a doctor?
No.
[Jarod]
I'm with the F.B.I.
- The victim is someone we've had
our eye on for sometime now.
- Why?
Let's just say that a few of her journalistic
choices have struck a nerve in D.C.
The victim's office is in here.
Name's Detective Brookins.
Call me Stan.
Agent Jarod Curtis.
Tell me what you know,
the whole story.
Well, the victim came to
the office early this morning.
So early, it was the night shift janitor
that probably saved her life by walking in.
Anyway, from what I can tell,
the woman was ambushed here...
then thrown out this window
two stories to the pavement.
- Any description?
- White male, 35-ish, average build, dark suit.
Got the sketch artist
workin' on it now.
I want all of her files boxed and
sealed and sent to your precinct.
And I'm also gonna need
an office for a few days.
[Miss Parker]
Well, it's about time you got back, Lyle.
So, what's the flavor of the day,
little brother?
Mail-order mamas from Malaysia?
Or cannibal quiche from the Kalahari?
- If you're here to talk with our father, he's gone.
- Well, then find him.
[Chuckles] Pounding boilermakers
is hardly the breakfast of champions.
This isn't about you.
I'm sorry.
Okay, now I know you're sloshed.
What's going on, Parker?
[Sighs]
It's-
It's about our mother.
She's gone.
- Our mother's been dead a long time.
- No.
I mean, she's not there.
I mean, her-
She's not there?
What do you mean she's not there, Parker?
Parker?
You wouldn't understand anyway.
- But I wanna know.
- Bet you do.
[Electronic Female Voice]
Message voice box 04. Record.
- [Beeps]
- It's me.
I've got a bad feeling Miss Parker
knows about Catherine's empty grave.
[Sydney] You believe
someone stole your mother's body?
Except for this scotch-induced
earthquake rattling between my ears...
I'm not sure exactly
what to believe anymore.
Let's face it, Sydney.
Catherine Parker's body being gone...
fits in with all the other
bizarre happenings around here.
The reappearance of Edna Raines who,
after 30 years, everyone thought was dead.
And who now really is dead, thanks
to the bald butcher she called "Hubby."
The murder of that harmless
clerk Leonard down in SL 26...
because he just happened
to see the wrong memo.
And now, Catherine Parker's empty grave.
That's a lot of strange coincidences.
No. Not coincidence.
Mirage.
Mirage? You mean what Edna Raines
told you before she died?
What was on both of those memos,
the one I found on Lyle's desk...
and the one that killed that clerk.
Well, oddities, yes...
but status quo here at the Centre.
I never thought I'd hear you say...
"Murder is business as usual," Syd.
All I'm saying is, at times...
it is best to let some things go.
My mother's grave is empty, Sydney.
Maybe, just maybe, she had otherwishes
that you didn't know about.
For her burial, I mean.
People sometimes make choices...
that are difficult to explain.
No.
This is one big fish I'm reeling in.
Broots, our best evidence-
We follow the body.
In this case, my mother's.
We start with the autopsy records.
Parker?
Why won't you let go of this?
Because something inside me
is telling me to do this.
And I'm listening.
Her condition is only fair,
Agent Curtis.
- So please minimize your time with her.
- I will. Thank you.
Em?
It's your brother...
Jarod.
I was too late this morning.
I'm sorry.
But I'll never be late again.
I promise you.
[Lyle]
How goes the world tour?
Indeference to Winston Churchill...
or whoever the hell said it...
"The sun never sets on the Centre."
And I'm making sure it never sets
on the Parkers either.
- [Elevator Bell Dings]
- Glad to hear it.
Since when is Raines
hosting Triumvirate personnel?
He'll be a blip on our radar as long
as everything goes well with Mirage.
Unfortunately,
we've got company there.
I've all but confirmed
that Sis is on that same track.
- Ah, damn.
- Oh, it's nothing.
She's way behind the curve.
I'll make sure she stays there.
I don't want her knowing
for her own good.
Hell, if she knew the truth,
she'd only wish she didn't.
- Okay.
- [Crunch]
- God! What'd I just step in?
- I don't know.
- But if you hurry, you can still catch it.
- Ew!
[Sydney] I can't believe you actually found
Catherine Parker's autopsy files, Broots.
Well, I haven't found it yet.
But, according to Buzzie...
the only way to download
a visual archive in the Sublevel...
is to tap directly into the Sublevel's
mainframe terminals.
- Who the hell is Buzzie?
- My pal down in Communications.
You know the old guy
with the hearing aids?
He's always griping about
the constant ringing in his ears.
- I've got that problem myself.
- Get this.
You know the rumor that J.F.K.
was kept alive as a vegetable somewhere?
Buzzie claims it was
right here in SL 18.
Yeah, right next door to the alien corpses
Nixon showed Jackie Gleason.
- That was here too?
- [Sydney] Hey!
This is Room 12.
This is it.
[Broots] Wow. This is the room
where they did your mother's autopsy.
- This shouldn't take long.
- [Zipper Unzipping]
Sydney?
- Parker, you okay?
- Fine, Syd.
- I got it.
- [Raines] This begins the visual data archive...
to be known as number 566773.
The autopsy of Catherine Elaine Parker.
Date and time to follow.
Dr. William Raines, M.E.
Versatile guy, that Raines.
Beats 'em, bursts them,
slices and dices.
[Raines]
Initial findings indicate...
a single gunshot wound into
the cranial region as cause of death.
Angle and force of the head wound...
strongly indicate the gunshot
was self-inflicted.
- [Drill Whirring]
- Let's just skip to the end, Broots.
Oh, God. We've heard
all these lies before.
I just need to see
where the body goes.
Box the body for transport
per the family wishes.
On a personal note, I would simply like to go
on record to express my heartfelt remorse...
and to say that this is
and will always be...
a tragic death in
the annals of the Centre...
the likes of which I hope
never to encounter again.
So, what now?
We do a little exploratory
surgery of our own...
see just how remorseful
Dr. Death really is.
[Man] I'm as sorry as I can be
about the attack on Emily.
I wish all my tenants were like her.
I sort of connected
with her right off-
her lookin' for her family...
me not ever knowing
my father and mother.
I'm sorry.
She was so close to changing
all that for herself.
- What do you mean?
- Well, she was hot on the trail
of her brother.
Said she was, like,
this close to finding him.
She'd tear up everytime
she talked about it.
When was the last time that you saw my-
uh, the victim?
Um, must have been
a couple of nights ago.
To tell you the truth,
she seemed a little tense.
Said something about being, uh,
close to a big discovery.
The brother that she was looking for?
I-I don't think so.
This was something disturbing to her.
It wasn't a happy discovery.
Did you find something?
I'm not sure.
Uh, thank you for your time...
but I'd like to look around
for a little bit.
Sure. Hey, you saved me a trip.
I was about to go into town and tell the police
about this guy that was hanging around here.
It-It was the same guy from
the police sketch in the evening paper.
I-I can't believe they left out the most
important part of the description.
What's that?
The fact that-
Well, the guy was missing a thumb.
- [Women Laughing]
- [Lyle] I've never even met you.
Who said anything about breakfast?
Mr. Lyle?
Something tells me you haven't
read the morning's paper.
You try to kill with kindness,
and this is what happens.
Put a team together.
We're goin' back to Philly A.S.A.P.
Right.
Allow me.
I'm not going to Sublevel 18.
Oh. But you should.
It's a regular "Freaks-R-Us" down there.
You know the history.
J.F.K.., dead Martians. The room
where you did my mother's autopsy.
It's gonna be a bitch gettin'
that tank up and down the stairs.
It's common knowledge
I performed your mother's autopsy.
But... is it common knowledge...
that my mother's body
isn't in her grave?
What are you talking about?
What the hell did you do
with her body, you ghoul?
What any responsible
medical examiner would have done-
honor the wishes of the deceased.
If you have a problem with that,
take it up with her...
because this discussion is over.
Miss Parker, you told him
about your mother's empty grave?
He's gonna-
He could- He could-
He could lead us
right to the answer.
[Broots]
You told him on purpose.
That fish I said I'd be reeling in-
I just baited the hook.
Now we troll.
- You with us, Syd?
- [Elevator Bell Dings]
[Woman]
I'm sorry, Agent Curtis...
but I cannot in good conscience
allow the victim to be transferred.
How would your conscience feel when they put
you in jail for violation of a federal order?
- That order is worthless in my eyes.
- I have seen her charts.
Her edema levels are back to normal,
as well as hervital signs.
- The answer's still no.
- Whoever tried to kill her knows he failed...
and he will be back to finish the job,
I guarantee you that.
Releasing her to the next of kin
would be my only option here.
And correct me if I'm wrong...
but so far, none have turned up.
Until now.
I'm Emily's father...
and I think you should give
the agent here what he wants.
I'll prep her for immediate release.
- It's so good to see you.
- How is she?
- She's going to be okay.
- Great.
[Tires Screeching]
Check over there.
Willie, stairs.
You, follow me.
- How many were there?
- Four.
Go! Go!
238.
Damn! Where did she go?
- Released. She just went downstairs.
- Take the stairs.
That ambulance over there is mine.
I know a place that we can be safe.
You drive.
Good way to get yourself killed, pal.
Out of my way.
- See this woman come this way anywhere?
- Nope. Never seen her.
[Siren Wailing]
Damn!
I wanna thank you, Sister Mary,
for everything you've done for us.
After all you've done
for our parish, Jarod...
- you just stay as long as you want.
- [Bells Tolling]
And we'll take
very good care of Emily.
Nothing.
- No luck, huh?
- It's like he doesn't exist.
Well, whoever this guy is,
Emily's been tracking him for a while.
Here, let me give you
a hand with the notes.
"Misplaced personality disorder."
"Man with no name."
"Talks to voices."
"Enigma."
Maybe it's a story
she's been working on.
Or a lifelong mystery
she's been trying to solve.
She thought this guy
might have been you.
She's been searching, just like me.
Just like... we all have.
Why would the Centre
want to murder her?
And how does he fit in?
[Broots]
Boy, you put the worm on...
and he took it hook,
line and sinker.
Man.
But I never pegged Raines
for the rustic type.
In the middle of nowhere,
you can't hear anyone scream.
I need to get to that fire.
[Miss Parker]
Anything, Broots?
Looks like a Raines time capsule.
Everything from old mortgage papers
to his kid's kindergarten artwork.
Move over, Monet.
Looks like "Ethan."
His son?
I've tried not to fire too many synapses
remembering things about the Raines family.
You think Raines used to live here?
Well, we used to visit
his house occasionally...
but it was on
the other side of town.
Maybe he used this place
as some kind of personal storage depot.
Yeah. Well, no offense
against his kid's artwork...
but this is starting to feel
like a dead-end trip down memory lane.
Miss Parker?
I think another street
just opened up.
Huh. St. Christopher medal.
Miss Parker, look.
[Emily Moans]
Emily? Emily?
Hi.
It's me, Em.
It's your brother.
- Jarod?
- Dad's here too.
We're all together now.
[Mutters]
Take your time. Take your time.
What is it you wanna tell us?
I found this picture
in your research files.
You thought he was me, didn't you?
Who is he?
Ethan.
- Ethan?
- He hears the voices. Talks-
He talks to the voices. I read that
in your notebook. What voices, Emily?
Hey, I think she should rest.
Come on.
Okay.
NuGenesis.
NuGenesis?
My God.
The Centre Fertility Clinic?
I have no fond memories of that place.
Here.
"AA8585."
Is that a file number?
- From NuGenesis?
- Does that have anything to do
with this man Ethan?
Follow NuGenesis.
Follow him.
Emily? Emily?
You know, if you consider yourself
any kind of friend of hers...
you'll destroy those disks.
- And you will destroy it now!
- But I can't!
I can't, Sydney. I don't really
have a choice in the matter, do I?
I mean, this is Miss Parker's life.
- This is her past.
She has every right to see it.
- See what?
Do what you must, Broots.
But I won't be a part
of opening this Pandora's box.
[Miss Parker]
What Pandora's box?
[Broots] I was able to reconstruct
one tiny piece of the disks...
we found at Raines's forest house.
- The same place we were today?
- Yeah, but- Just watch.
[Raines] I hope you're feeling
comfortable here, Catherine...
after all you've been through.
I never thought I'd see the day when I'd be
thanking you for your kindness, Dr. Raines.
But thank you.
- My mother was there.
- Yeah. But what's important is the date.
Look. Look at the date code
on the D.S.A.
Your mother was shot and killed
at the Centre in April.
- This says June. There must be a mis-
- No.
It's physically and
technically impossible...
to alter the dates on the Centre
D.S.A. surveillance system.
Sydney didn't want me to show you this.
I don't know why.
But it's a lock.
Your mother did not die
in that elevator, Miss Parker.
Are- Are you saying
my mother is still alive?
Your mother alive?
Does this make any sense?
- Do you think that was hers?
- I don't remember it, but anything's possible.
Keep decoding the forest house archives.
And don't tell anyone.
- Not even Sydney?
- Especially Sydney.
He's done everything except
handcuff me to a freight train...
to keep me from digging into this.
There must be someone you can trust.
Where's Angelo?
Looks like the same kind
of insanity I grew up with.
Are you sure this is the address
Emily gave us for Ethan?
Positive.
He's been videotaping
himself for years.
Is there anything
on NuGenesis AA8585?
Nope. But there's enough material here
to write a dissertation on bomb-making.
But this guy's taken it a step further.
He's designing his own bomb.
Huh. Look.
There's an unmailed letter...
to his parents, the Clausens.
According to this time code, this video
was made less than one hour ago.
There's your little bomb-maker.
Let's see what he's been up to.
Just leave me alone!
- Who's he talking to?
- I know I shouldn't yell.
I won't be bad anymore.
According to Emily's notes...
there were signs of erratic behavior,
of multiple personalities.
He must be wrestling with
some kind of demons inside.
Emily said he could hear the voices,
whatever that means.
[Phone Ringing]
Yeah?
Hey, hey, listen.
I'm in trouble.
I need to talk to you.
Yes, I'm-I'm almost ready with 7677.
I-I just need a few more components.
But I'm tellin' you, I need to talk.
You swear that after the explosion...
the pain will be gone?
They're promising him his inner torture
will end if he pulls off some kind
of bombing for them.
- The Centre.
- Who else?
Okay, I'll do it.
First, I wanna see my mom and dad.
Why won't you let me see
my mom and dad? It's been so long.
I-I-I wrote them a letter.
Why can't I send it?
They do love me!
I know.
I know you do too.
[Line Disconnects, Dial Tone]
[Grunts]
- What? Are you sure?
- What's he doing?
- He's talking to the voices.
- He's gonna- He's gonna hurt my mom and dad?
He can't hurt my mom and dad.
[Major Charles]
Wherever he's going, he's not coming back...
and he's taking his bomb with him.
Come on.
Let's go.
It's not my fault that Jarod found
his sister before the Sweeper team did.
It's your fault she was still alive.
Well, what did you teach me
about water under the bridge?
If it gets deep enough, it'll drown you.
What about Mirage?
- We're still searching.
- Oh, that's perfect.
My daughter is searching for a ghost...
my son is searching for a monster.
Last one alive wins, hmm?
[Angelo]
Secrets and lies.
When it comes to the Centre, Angelo,
secrets and lies are like oxygen.
Lies.
Angelo, I need you
to empath this for me.
It may have belonged to my mother.
Your mother wore this.
Her journey not over.
My mother is still out there?
Illusions are real.
What's that mean?
Mirages are real.
What's "Mirage," Angelo?
Tell me what that means!
Miss Parker. He-
He's on your side.
Angelo sorry.
He doesn't know the answers.
But Sydney knows.
Sydney knows all the secrets and lies.
[Sobbing]
Oh, please.
Please don't be dead.
Please.
[Sobbing]
Don't leave me.
- Please don't leave. Please.
- [Voices Whispering]
You did this.
No, I swear I didn't do this.
You hurt them!
Why? Why?
Ethan, I didn't hurt them.
I swear to you.
I did not kill them.
- [Voices Whispering]
- Somebody hurt them.
Somebody killed my parents.
Please, let me help you.
- Help?
- My sister Emily...
- she followed you because
she wanted to help you.
- [Sirens Wailing]
- That's all I want to do.
- There's no help for me.
- [Tires Screeching]
- Not from you. There's only
one person who can help me now.
Ethan! Ethan!
- Freeze!
- I'm F.B.I. It's okay. It's okay.
F.B.I.
- There were reports of shots fired.
- Upstairs. Two bodies.
I was too late.
You knew my mother was alive,
but you didn't tell me?
Yes.
Then give me one good reason not
to blow your Flemish brains out.
I promised her I wouldn't tell you.
[Sighs]
Well, as you know...
I gave your mother
her last psychiatric session...
less than an hour
before her supposed murder.
- Supposed suicide in the elevator.
- "Supposed."
What does that mean, Sydney?
Catherine?
Catherine, please relax.
Sydney, I just found out that
someone I love is planning to kill me.
- Who?
- I can't tell you. A friend.
But it's forcing me to-
to make a very difficult decision.
I'm going to stage my death
in hopes of saving my life.
- I don't understand.
- And I don't have time to explain it all.
But you know these people,
what they're capable of.
I try not to imagine.
Their latest is
a project called Mirage...
and they've made me a key player.
My only way out is dying,
by their hands or my own.
[Sydney]
This is dangerous talk.
These are dangerous times, Sydney.
I'll do what I have to to survive.
And then I'll come back and rescue
Jarod and Angelo and my little girl.
What about your little girl?
She's my gift from God...
and I don't know how to save her
without causing her this pain.
Promise me, Sydney.
Swear to me that you'll protect her...
that you'll never tell her about this.
- You owe me.
- I know I do.
Whatever happens, no matter
how badly she wants to know...
I don't want my baby girl
to ever have to face the true tragedy...
of her family's secret.
- Promise me.
- I promise.
Godspeed, Catherine.
An hour later,
the gunshot rang out.
You know the rest.
I never saw Catherine again.
- Do you know what it is?
- What?
Mirage. The tragedy...
of my family's secret?
I'm afraid I don't.
That is the truth.
Ethan's parents were murdered
as a message to him.
Finish the 7677 bombing, or else.
Sounds like a message from the Centre to me.
- That has the Centre fingerprints all over it.
- This too.
- You hacked into the NuGenesis mainframe?
- Uh-huh.
And you won't believe
what I found in file number AA8585.
[Jarod]
AA8585 was a shipment...
of cryogenically frozen sperm samples.
They were airlifted
to the Centre decades ago.
Someone wanted
to get pregnant pretty badly.
Yeah, but they weren't
just anyone's samples, Jarod.
They were mine.
- How much does Jarod know?
- [Lyle] We're not sure.
But Major Charles's seminal records
have been compromised at NuGenesis.
[Lyle] And there's more.
Jarod was spotted at the parents' house.
- Before or after they were killed?
- After, thank God.
- And Mirage?
- [Sighs]
He's still out there.
There's gotta be some way to get
to Jarod before he beats us to him.
There is one.
We give him something...
more important to go after.
Something named Zoe.
[Mr. Parker]
Good thinking, Mr. Cox.
[Major Charles]
It only gets stranger and stranger.
- More on your records at NuGenesis?
- Yeah.
For the past 25 years,
comparative genetic test follow-ups...
have been conducted using my D.N.A.
The question is, who or what
are they comparing it to?
It doesn't say. But the results
were sent to a private residence...
in Blue Cove, Delaware.
Come on.
[Engine Starts]
Okay, let's go.
You all right?
Something feels... weird.
- We're talkin' Mr. Raines.
It's supposed to be weird.
- No.
This is weirder than him.
- What are we lookin' for?
- The truth.
I'll check over here.
No.
It's not over there.
How do you know, Son?
I just know. It's-
It's like a strange deja vu.
- What are you mumbling about?
- I decoded some of the archives
from the forest house.
And, well, if a picture's worth
more than a thousand words...
I think I've just
uncovered a thesaurus.
This is about six months
after your mother supposedly died.
- Well?
- He'll be here in a few minutes.
- You sure you wanna do this?
- [Sighs]
I have to.
- What? What did she have to do?
- Well, wait. Just watch that door.
Like you've seen this place before?
It's like I've been here before.
[Gasps]
Oh, my God.
Jarod out of the Centre?
Impossible. How could that be?
Secrets and lies.
- Hi, Jarod.
- Hello, Mrs. Parker.
Thank you for coming.
Close the door.
Gynecological instruments?
What is all this stuff?
Tools of the trade.
- A birthing table?
- The question is, whose?
Come here, Jarod.
There's something I wanna tell you.
My mother was pregnant?
You're going to have a brother.
[Major Charles]
This is just too weird.
Birthing tables, incubators...
genetic follow-ups of my semen.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
I have a brother.
I have a brother?
Jarod and I share a brother?
It must be Ethan.
- But where is he?
- [Ethan] My parents are gone.
Mom is dead.
Dad is dead.
[Raines]
I'm your father now.
[Sydney]
Details are sketchy, Jarod.
I'm just now trying to piece
a lot of this together myself.
This feeling is so strong, Sydney,
that I've been to that forest house before.
But my mind wants to block it out.
I have a feeling too, Jarod,
and it says you're lying.
- Miss Parker.
- I'm glad to hear your mind
hasn't blocked me out yet.
Tell him, Syd.
Like he doesn't know.
Well, we saw the D.S.A.,
and you were definitely there.
- Then why don't I remember it?
- [Miss Parker] You're the genius.
- You tell us.
- If I could I would, Miss Parker. You know that.
I've never held back
when it comes to your mother.
[Miss Parker] You were on
the D.S.A., Jarod. She talked to you.
- She told you secrets.
- I don't remember.
- Did she tell you why she faked her own death?
- I don't know.
Or how in the hell that baby
she was carrying is your brother?
- Look, I don't know.
- Or where she was going,
or where the baby went, or-
I don't know!
[Sydney]
It is entirely possible that...
your subconscious mind has
blocked out those recollections, Jarod...
either by itself or with
the help of someone else.
So those memories could
still be in Jarod's head?
Every waking moment of our lives
is stored somewhere in our minds.
[Jarod] Well, for what it's worth,
Miss Parker, I believe that-
that our brother is a man named Ethan.
Now, I don't know where he is...
but somehow he's involved
with a project called 7677.
You figure out 7677..
you find baby brother.
[Ethan]
I'm almost ready with 7677.
I just need a few more components.
But I'm telling you,
I need to talk. Okay.
[Grunts]
Still nothin' on this guy, Agent?
- Still nothing.
- [Man] You can't drag me
out of my house like that!
I got a whole grilled cheese
goin' right there on the stove.
Hey, where do you want him, Detective?
- Come on!
- [Brookins] Ask, and ye shall receive.
That's the local munitions guy
you asked us to haul in.
Name's Jed Sidel.
Small-time middle man, all-around weasel.
Well, what a coincidence.
Weasel season has just opened.
Jed.
- Agent Curtis, F.B.I.
- Hello.
On behalf of the Bureau,
I would like to say congratulations.
- Hmm?
- Well, you're moving up in the world.
- I am?
- Aiding and abetting in the making ofbombs.
Helping to murder innocent citizens.
I mean, this is hardly fencing stolen TVs.
You're hittin' the big leagues.
Your parents must bevery proud of you.
- You got the wrong guy.
- Really?
Well, he doesn't seem to think so.
I don't know who that is.
- That wasn't my question.
- What-What-What was the question?
Why are you helping
your friend here make bombs?
- No, no. Ethan ain't no friend of mine.
- Ethan?
I thought you didn't know him.
Do you have any idea what this guy's
gonna do to me if I spill to you?
I mean, he talks to people
that aren't even there. He's crazy.
Unlike the lovable lifers
in federal prison.
- Hmm?
- I hear shower time's a real scream,Jed.
Explosives. Yes.
He was looking for explosives.
Like C-4, Semtex, uh, digital fuses.
And all I did,
and this is all I did...
was call a guy on the phone, and I-
and I set up a meeting.
- That's it.
- Where and when?
Mm-hmm.
At the warehouse at midnight.
Broad Street and Franklin.
[Engine Starts]
There was only about
one minute of stuff left on the D.S.A.
But what's there is really telling.
Dr. Raines, leave us alone, please?
Catherine, I don't think
that would be a good idea.
I think it would be a great idea.
Jarod, there's something
I have to tell you...
that you can never forget.
Okay.
I may not live much longer,
and if I don't...
there's something very important
I want you to tell my daughter.
Will you promise me
that you'll tell her?
I promise.
It's something I don't ever
want anyone else to hear.
What's wrong, Broots?
Fix it.
Well, there's nothing to fix.
She unplugged it. That's all there is.
My butt that's all there is.
Make it talk.
- I-I can't.
- My mother's dying secret.
The one thing
she wanted me to know...
is not only lost electronically,
but somewhere inside Jarod's head...
and he can't remember a thing.
Hmm.
Raines. Raines must have
erased that portion of Jarod's brain.
- You mean, like, hypnotized him
or brainwashed him or something?
- Very likely.
I don't know how Raines locked
that memory in Genius Boy's mind...
but I'm gonna free it up
if I have to crack his head open...
and carve it out
with a melon scooper.
- How are we gonna do that?
- We track Raines.
I'll bet my ass
he knows where Ethan is.
We find Ethan, we find Jarod.
Move in, Sam!
[Chattering]
Relax, son.
Everything's going to be just fine.
I feel so alone.
But you're not, Ethan. I'm here for you.
You know that, don't you?
After you earn the trust
of the Triumvirate with the bombing...
you'll come to live at the Centre
where we'll do great things together.
I'll be calling you soon.
[Door Opens, Closes]
Ethan? It's okay.
I'm not here to hurt you.
No, you're the one
who killed my parents.
I didn't kill your parents.
[Voices Whispering]
How do you know I can trust him?
I can't trust anyone.
Not you, not him.
Ethan, I'm your friend.
- [Chain Rattling]
- Ethan, run! Run!
[Gunshot]
[Miss Parker]
Jarod!
Damn it!
Jarod! Your ninth life just ran out.
[Miss Parker]
You look surprised to be here.
Well, I'm surprised I'm still alive.
Dead men tell no tales.
I'm assuming since we're here, this has
nothing to do with Centre business?
No.
It's about me.
I need your help.
Tell me what I need to know,
and you're out of here.
And I should believe you're going
to let me just walk away? Hmm?
Watch this, Jarod.
- [Young Jarod] Hello, Mrs. Parker.
- Thank you for coming.
Close the door.
Come here, Jarod.
There's something I wanna tell you.
You're going to have a brother.
[Jarod] I don't remember this.
Sydney, I don't remember this.
[Sydney]
It's in your mind somewhere.
Then let's get it out.
Three, two, one.
Go back into your memory, Jarod...
to when you were a young boy.
Are you there now?
Go back to a moment when Raines came
to take you from the Centre.
And where did he take you?
[Jarod]
A house in the woods.
- Can you see the house now?
- Yes.
Go inside.
- Are you there?
- Yes.
I smell wood. Wood paneling. Cedar.
Very good, Jarod.
I walk through a sliding door.
- She's there.
- Who is?
Catherine Parker.
She's still alive.
Hi, Jarod.
She didn't die in the elevator.
- She seems troubled.
- By what?
She wants me...
to tell her daughter
something very important.
What?
It's very important that
she know the truth about Ethan.
Ethan?
That's what he told me
his name would be.
I don't understand.
How would he know?
- How do you?
- I call it my inner sense.
Inner sense?
For most, it's the hairs
on the back of your neck...
or that nervous feeling
in your stomach.
[Jarod, Mrs. Parker Together]
For me, it's voices I hear all around me...
usually warning me of things
that are about to happen.
Like souls talking to you?
Something like that.
I've been blessed
with this gift, Jarod.
And though she doesn't know it,
so has my daughter.
Though neither of us quite like Ethan.
Ijust pray his gift isn't
abused by the wrong people.
[Young Jarod]
Why are you telling me this?
Because Ethan is also your brother.
Unknown to me, while I was sedated...
for a minor surgery not long ago...
my husband...
used your father's seed
to impregnate me.
- My father's genetics.
- Yes.
Mr. Parker wanted
to create a child...
with this inner sense...
who could also
be special like you are...
to use, no doubt,
as they have used you.
Mr. Raines showed me proof
of what had been done...
and that Mr. Parker
is planning to kill me...
when the baby is born.
[Young Jarod] Mr. Raines scares me.
Why do you trust him?
I trusted him because-
because he trusted me.
That and...
it was the only way for me to give
this child a chance at a real life.
But now-
Something's wrong.
The voices are telling me
I won't leave this house alive.
[Young Jarod]
That's why you brought me here.
You're special, Jarod,
and I know you won't forget.
I want you to tell my daughter
to complete my plan.
[Young Jarod]
Plan?
She'll understand one day.
Just tell her to trust her inner sense.
It will guide her actions.
Jarod, your soul is a trusting one,
just like your mother's.
- You know my mother?
- Yes.
And one day,
you'll be back together again.
And Ethan will help you find her.
[Jarod, Mrs. Parker Together]
Trust your inner sense.
[Typing]
- Mr. Lyle.
- Any news from Cox about Zoe?
According to his last message,
he's ready.
But this is why I'm here.
Our people at Triumvirate Headquarters...
thought you might find that
quite interesting.
Raines has been a busy boy.
[Broots] I intercepted a communique
between Raines and the Triumvirate...
and I'm probably
not the only one who did.
- Spit it out, Broots.
- It's about 7677.
And that thing, that Mirage-
That "thing" is my brother.
Whoa.
Okay. In a nutshell,
there's some project called 7677.
And if it goes off as planned, Mr. Raines
is gonna be in charge of the Centre.
A Raines coup.
Thank you.
Hello?
Why do I feel Iike you know
what Broots just told me?
- Raines has been working towards
this his whole sordid career.
- Using Ethan.
He took him as a child,
placed him in a surrogate family...
with people who would allow
Raines to control his emotions.
In other words, screwed him up
so badly, he would only trust Raines.
So Raines could have
total control over him...
turn Ethan into
his private assassin.
And when Raines killed
his surrogate parents...
he severed all emotional ties to anything
connected with the outside world.
[Jarod]
Well, that is what Raines does best-
take people away from their families.
What are you going to do?
[Sighs]
I don't know.
Do what your mother would have wanted.
Finish her work.
Work she died trying to accomplish.
My mother may still be alive, Jarod.
What if she's not?
You can stop Raines.
I don't know!
Ow!
Trust your inner sense, Miss Parker.
I do.
Now...
I'm going to find my-
our brother.
Have I ever told you...
how truly inspired this Holy Roller
gag of yours has been?
What are you talking about?
Oh, come on.
You're about as born-again as I am.
But, hey, after you botched things
so badly last year...
this religion thing saved your ass.
There's no shame in that.
Of course...
the way the Triumvirate's been touting
you lately, who needs divine intervention?
- You're making no sense.
- Oh, I am.
Just as much as this communique that
I intercepted from the Triumvirate does.
You've gotten pretty tight
with our bosses in Africa.
7677 and Mirage.
Your power play.
Ringin' a bell?
How did you get this?
If you can find God,
I can sure as hell find that.
And to think all this time,
I thought Bobby Bowman...
was your only special
project on the outside.
I guess you never heard of progress.
What I'm about to propose
is all about progress.
- What do you want?
- I want to run the Centre with you.
The 7677 bombing goes down...
Mirage- or is it Ethan-
comes into the Centre just like you
promised the Triumvirate...
and it all can happen
because I decide...
not to tell Mr. Parker
that you stole his son.
Yeah. That you stole
his prizes Project Mirage.
Now, if I read
that communique correctly...
it's about time for you
to activate Ethan...
and finish 7677.
What do you say, partner?
[Ringing]
[Raines]
7677 is a go.
This is your final call.
After this, it's up to you.
Now, walk three blocks
to the bus station.
Open locker number 9...
and you'll find the final instructions
for the bombing.
[Voices Whispering]
We couldn't stop him now
even if we wanted to.
Happy?
- [Door Opens]
- Damn happy.
- You son of a-
- Hey, hey.
Is that any way to talk
to your new partner?
Whoops.
I mean, new boss?
[Man]
We have a clean trace on the call.
We'll monitor Ethan until he finishes 7677,
and then we'll bring him in.
- No screw-ups.
- Lock him up down in SL 25...
with the rats.
We've had too many years and too much
success for things to end this way.
Who said it's ending for me?
# [Man Singing]
# [Singing Along]
- # [Continues]
- Excuse me?
Hi. Anything I can do to help?
As a matter offact, there is.
# [Continues]
[Bells Tolling]
- Hi.
- How are you feeling?
- Better.
We have so much we have to catch up on.
I'm going to find Mom...
and we're all going to be
together like one big family.
And what about Ethan?
Dad told me everything.
He's not crazy...
not like you thought he was.
Our brother, he's gifted.
He's special.
Don't let them destroy Ethan
like they did our family.
I won't.
I promise.
Sweet dreams.
Why the glum looks?
Well, I recovered more of
the forest house archives.
- And?
- Sit down, Parker.
[Raines]
I can see the head, Catherine.
[Groaning]
- It's a-
- [Mrs. Parker] Boy.
[Raines]
You're right. It is a boy.
Oh!
Hello, Ethan.
Hello.
I'm your mother.
I have such big plans foryou.
- Why didn't you want me to see this?
- There's more, I'm afraid.
After my work was through, I wanted
to raise you and your brother and sister...
like a real family.
But I'm not gonna be able
to do that, little man.
I just realized I'm not going
to be able to seeyou grow up.
But you have a brother and sister
that will find you and protect you.
You tell them to finish my work...
to finish my plan.
I love you.
[Crying]
- Um, I don't think you need to see-
- No.
I need to know.
I'm sorry.
I'm just following orders.
[Mrs. Parker] You really had me convinced
that you had changed...
that you cared about this baby.
There's no other way, Catherine.
[Gunshot]
Raines just executed her.
[Baby Crying]
- Have her cremated.
- Yes, Doctor.
I'm your mommy now.
Raines executed my mother.
He won't take my brother too.
Syd, talk to her.
There's nothing left to say.
[Major Charles]
You found Ethan's computer?
At the warehouse where
he picked up the bomb components.
I reconstructed the hard drive and was able
to break down the bomb schematic.
But even better, I found out
where the bombing is going down.
7677. It's the number of a subway train.
- D.C. Underground.
- The subway's not his target.
It's his delivery system.
Train 7677's route
ends at Freedom Station.
Directly above that
is the National Hotel.
The exact place where hundreds of foreign
dignitaries are staying for a peace conference.
So much for peace.
I broke down the password
on a well-hidden encryption file.
Ethan's programmed the bomb's timer
on this laptop too.
The train is leaving the station
in exactly one hour from now.
- It's just enough time to stop this
and save Ethan.
- Come on.
- [Ringing]
- [Electronic Voice] You have a video phone call.
I'm sorry to call so late, Jarod,
but I thought for sure you'd be interested...
in saving the life of a close friend.
[Groans]
Ouch!
- Zoe!
- Jarod!
- Lyle, let her go!
- That's exactly what I wanna do.
But Mr. Cox actually wants to exploit
the safety and well-being
of your girlfriend...
to his advantage.
All right.
What do you want?
To propose a quid pro quo.
Don't, Jarod!
I don't know why these people want you...
but they will kill you, I know that!
[Mr. Cox]
If you want Zoe to live...
you'll surrender yourself to us
tonight at Rosing's Farm...
Highway 12, outside Blue Cove...
in exactly one hour.
Lyle! Damn it!
One hour from now. That's exactly when
Ethan will be on that subway train.
[Rats Squealing]
From the bottom of my heart,
Miss Parker-
My first memory of you
was in the Centre lobby.
You were smoking a cigarette.
I was six or seven,
and you knelt down...
took a drag and blew smoke in my face.
And here you are...
still blowin' smoke.
For what it's worth, Miss Parker-
I can never have my mother back...
but I can damn well save my brother.
You tell me everything you know
about 7677...
and I consider
letting you live another day.
I'm the last chance saloon here,
Raines.
7677 is a Washington D.C.
subway train...
departing from Beacon Station
in a little over one hour from now.
Then what?
When it pulls into Freedom Station...
the subway and everything
above it will blow up.
It's your brother who will plant
the bomb and guide the subway.
- Our Father, who art in heaven-
- Not so fast.
Before she died, my mother said
something about her "unfinished work"..
about her "plan."
What did she mean by that?
- Then you never found it either?
- Found what?
Word has it your mother left a D.S.A.
explaining exactly what her plan was.
But it was the one piece
of incriminating evidence...
I never found or destroyed.
You find it, you find her plan.
You gotta know
something more about it.
It's about what everything's about,
Miss Parker.
It's about the Centre, all the lies.
Just remember...
whatever answers your mother
may have left behind...
there is still one person alive...
who does know the whole truth.
- Who?
- [Gunshot]
[Sighs]
Daddy?
It's not right for my little girl
to have blood like that on her hands.
Was it the blood
you were worried about...
or the truth?
Jarod should be here in 20 minutes.
Take your positions.
Be ready.
[Mr. Lyle]
And you're sure he'll come?
Oh, he'll come.
Zoe, we couldn't have
done this without you.
- Go to hell.
- All's fair in love and war.
You know, it's too bad
you're not Asian.
But maybe when all this is over, we can
find a place for you in our renewal wing.
- Why can't you just leave Jarod alone?
- Because he belongs to us.
[Screams]
[Coughing]
- It's not Jarod!
- It's Major Charles.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- Dad?
- It's me- Zoe.
- Then you're all right?
- Yeah, everything's okay on this end, Jarod.
Though I am pretty damn curious
about who Cox and Lyle are.
- I am so sorry that you got involved with this.
- Be careful, Jarod.
I will.
Ethan?
- Stay away!
- I'm not going to hurt you.
- [Voices Whispering]
- [Grunting]
- They say not to trust you.
- No, they don't.
- Not all of them.
- I wish I didn't have to hear them!
It's your inner sense, Ethan.
It's what makes you special.
- Who are you?
- I'm your brother.
- She told me about you.
- She?
Of course.
One of the voices.
She's the one you must listen to, Ethan.
- Who is she?
- Your mother.
You never got to know her.
They never allowed you to know her.
But she is your mother.
She's your guide, Ethan.
Listen to her voice.
It's your inner sense.
- Mr. Raines is my guide.
- No, he took your gifts
and he used them against you.
He taught you to fear those voices
instead oflearning how to embrace them.
He used you, Ethan.
He's still using you.
Don't let him use
your gift for destruction.
- I have to follow his word.
- If you do, then innocent people will die.
That's not you, Ethan.
That's not who you are.
Just listen to her voice, Ethan.
Focus on her voice.
Trust him, Son.
Jarod is the one.
Listen to her.
# Cree craw toad's foot #
[Together]
# Geese walk barefoot #
- # Cree craw toad's foot, geese walk barefoot #
- Brother?
Yes.
# Cree craw toad's foot, geese walk barefoot #
You can break free of the hold he has
over you. Just listen to her voice.
You have a family now, a real family.
We'll always be there.
Now tell me, where is the bomb?
You can't stop the train.
The bomb can't be defused.
I was on three bomb squads and two
army demolition units. I can defuse it.
The bomb's on the undercarriage.
There's no stopping it or the train.
Then we're gonna have to send the train
somewhere else. Where's Freedom Station?
- It's on the track veering right.
- Where's the track veering left go?
It's to an abandoned maintenance yard.
They closed it years ago.
- Well, hang on.
- Look, it's no use.
I programmed it to automatically
take the track to the right.
- Did I tell you I was a rocket scientist too?
- 3,000 yards.
- 2,900.
- Come on!
2,800! Do it!
- I got it.
- The train has an auto brake
that engages in 40 seconds.
- The bomb goes off 20 seconds after that.
- Come on! Get out of here!
Freeze it, please!
- Miss Parker, listen to me.
There is a bomb on board.
- I know!
- We have less than 60 seconds.
- Then defuse it!
I can't!
It's underneath the train!
- Then stop the train!
- It's too late!
If we are lucky, this train will
slow down enough for us to jump off.
But I can't stop the explosion.
This is your brother,
Miss Parker. Our brother.
It could be a beginning.
Don't make it an end!
[Mrs. Parker's Voice]
I'm your mother. I love you.
You sound just like her.
[Jarod] It's your mother's voice
he can hear, Miss Parker.
Maybe you can hear it too.
Trust that voice.
Miss Parker?
The auto brake has engaged.
We have less than 20 seconds.
- [Groans]
- What's the matter with him?
Side effects of Raines's work.
Now what's it gonna be, Miss Parker?
Help me save him.
Help me save our family.
It's your choice.
Come on.
Put your arm around me.
Go!
- [Miss Parker] Now what?
- [Jarod] We jump!
Now!
[Car Alarms Blaring]
www.tvsubtitles.net