I am sorry.
Uh, pardon me. Uh-
You're naked.
And you're not.
Uh-uh. No, I-
So, either you take yours offi...
or I'll put mine on.
These people are chasing-
I, uh- I gotta go.
Easy there, Mr. Maintenance Man.
I was just recharging my core.
It's like time travel
in The Terminator.
You've gotta be in the skin.
It's great for your karma.
Karma? What's karma?
Um, every good deed comes back to you.
Like a boomerang, only you don't throw it.
God, your lifeline-
it says you've been alone.
But there are these families
coming together.
Families?
- What?
- They're looking for you.
And while you search for them,
you bring other families together.
Keep doing what you're doing.
The good will come back.
Oh, thank you.
Now I really have to go.
Wait, your lifeline, it said something else.
You are gonna meet somebody just like you.
A kindred spirit.
A kindred spirit. Hmm.
Um, miss, you dropped your bag.
Damn!
"Jenna."
[Naked Woman's Voice]
You bring other families together.
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent
every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
[Miss Parker]
He defends the weak and abused.
Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
How was your breakfast, Mr. Pritchard?
Sam, you missed
some killer pancakes.
- My girl here is a budding chef.
- [Chuckles]
Well, don't thank me.
Thank Bisquick.
Chuck, you're in the back today.
If anybody needs me,
I'll be putting out fires.
Here we go.
Another day, another dollar.
[Car Alarm Blaring]
- Sounds like the Buick.
- Yeah, well, does numb nuts know?
[Coughing]
Secondhand smoke.
It's a killer.
- [Ringing]
- Yeah, babe?
You better get in here.
- Chuck! Chuck?
- [Chuck] Sam! I'm in the trunk!
- Get me outta the trunk!
- Son of a bitch!
Sam! Hurry up!
I'm in the trunk!
- Sam, meet Jarod Gray.
- You're late.
- What is this?
- It's a test. Jarod's with our security company.
The same one we're paying for four-star
protection. The kind we're not getting.
How'd you beat the cameras?
It was very difficult.
Sorry about all the bells and whistles...
but the company likes
to keep our men frosty.
Speaking of which, you might want to get
your head of security out of the trunk.
It's getting a little chilly out there.
Tell Chuck, now he's the night watchman,
and Jarod's the new head of security.
Get him an advance.
Roland, this isn't smart right now.
We got that thing in New Brunswick.
You wanna be the night watchman?
Welcome aboard.
Jarod, do you know Jenna?
You look... so familiar.
I have one of those faces.
[Miss Parker]
Is my little brother gonna be okay?
Well, his lungs were underdeveloped,
but the oxygen should help.
That's my boy.
God's greatest miracle.
[Speaking Gibberish]
The real miracle
would be for you and me...
in the shadow of new life
to start anew.
The Good Book says
"turn the other cheek."
I also remember something
about "eye for an eye."
Oh, Jarod sent a gift.
"Corinthians, 15:25.
Even a child is known by his doings."
Ring a bell there, Johnny Dogma?
God bless you all.
Willie, our work here is done.
[Sydney]
It's wrong?
It's not Corinthians.
It's Proverbs.
- Of course Raines had no clue.
- Well, how did you know?
Corinthians, 15:25.
"For he must reign till he hath
put all enemies under his feet."
The operative term being "reign."
- What do you think Jarod's trying to tell us?
- Raines is no convert.
He actually asked me to forgive him.
Maybe Raines has found God.
Maybe he should have thought of that
before he killed my mother.
- Find out what that son
of a bitch is up to.
- Okay.
[Sam]
Hey, look at the new guy hard at work.
I called the company about you.
I thought only customers
got a background check.
So, what did old Rudy have to say?
Ah, you're from Baltimore, an ex-cop.
That's right.
Six years Homicide.
I got tired of losin' my collars
to the courts.
That's where we gotta
change the books.
2,200 gun laws, more than we can enforce,
and I'm the bad guy? I'm a salesman.
Why would a cop leave a fat pension
to take a bullet for somebody?
Why does a salesman
need two bodyguards?
Well, we all got enemies, Jarod.
Well, maybe you should spread
some better karma around.
- Karma?
- Yeah. It's like a boomerang...
only you don't throw it.
- Long day, Mrs. Pritchard?
- Oh, I'm not Mrs. Pritchard yet.
- Roland's got me on lay away.
- We start makin' wedding plans after Saturday.
- The trip to New Brunswick.
- Yeah. Gotta see a friend.
I'm gonna want the Buick swept
and secured tomorrow morning.
Gotta protect my investment.
- You talkin' about me or the rock?
- Ain't I lucky?
All this and a sense of humor.
She means everything to me.
You take a bullet for her...
before you even think
about takin' one for me.
Well, I certainly hope
it doesn't come to that.
[Car Approaching]
She's my daughter, Dennis.
I have to see her.
She's at St. Charles.
- No, I'm leaving. I'm leaving.
- Not without me, I hope.
Jarod.
It's only going to get worse
after you're married.
He's gonna want you watched all the time.
Then when you have the little ones-
Oh, we won't be having children.
Roland's choice.
- He's a good man.
- I never said he wasn't.
You thought it, though.
Everyone does.
It's this business.
But Roland's made a good life for us.
It's like a... happy ending.
You do believe in happy endings,
don't you?
[Car Approaching]
Get down!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
[Policeman]
Make a list of all those employees that-
I'm supposed to know
when you leave the building.
Thank you.
- [Camera Shutter Clicking]
- Do you have any idea who did this?
I'd rather know how
they got so close.
- It was my fault. I just- I was-
- No, it was my fault.
I went to get the car.
I- I let my guard down.
You saved her life.
That's what matters.
She's gonna have my kids someday.
[Camera Shutter Clicking]
Let's go.
[Jenna's Voice]
She's my daughter, Dennis.
I have to see her.
She's at St. Charles.
Who the hell are you, pal?
[Priest]
The Body of Christ.
- The Body of Christ.
- Amen.
- [Door Opens]
The Body of Christ.
Mr. McGann, your daughter
and I have a deal.
She'd better honor it if she knows
what's good for you and the kid.
- The Body of Christ. The Body of Christ.
- [Door Opens, Closes]
[Gunfire]
Uh- Sorry to interrupt.
I can come back another time.
No, uh, I got work to do.
Great.
- Keep an eye on the prize, will ya?
- Oh. Sure, no problem.
So, uh, thanks again...
for this morning.
We're really gettin'
our money's worth.
You're right. We have met.
At my house.
Agent Dennis Alonzo.
He followed me to your daughter's
first Communion rehearsal at St. Charles.
He seems to be strong-arming
your father. Why?
Is he trying to get you to testify
against your fiance or something?
Look, I can protect you.
And I can help you
get your family back.
But you're going to
have to trust me.
You're wrong, Mr. Gray.
I can't trust anyone.
You have no idea
what you're getting into.
"Operation Fat Cat. Objective:
Secure evidence on Roland Pritchard.
Owns 10 tristate gun shops,
money laundering, illegal files and-"
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm an ex-cop.
And I'm someone who can help you
get your daughter back.
Tell me she's okay. All right,
I'm gonna finish this assignment.
- Just tell me that she's okay.
- Assignment?
Wait a minute.
You're A.T.F.
Oh, my God.
How long have you been undercover?
Twelve months, 13 days.
Twelve months? You've been apart
from your daughter for over a year?
I miss my little girl.
# [Rap]
[Police Siren Wailing]
- This better be good.
- Okay.
The card Jarod sent with the gift-
the chapter and the verse numbers
were a code for Raines's computer.
Every day for the last six months,
Raines has been meeting with that guy.
Oh, my God.
Giuseppe.
- You know him?
- Junior year of high school. Rome.
Look at him.
You guys were like a thing
or something?
He was my date for the spring formal.
He tried to get to third base
in the front seat of his father's Ferrari.
I broke his finger.
Boy, he is still a biscuit.
You mean biscotti, don't you?
[Man]
Look up! Look up! Look up!
Shoot!
# [Rap]
Parker, is that you?
Giuseppe.
You're looking very well.
You too. Very well.
Give me a moment, will ya?
How's the finger?
Oh, it's-it's still bent.
Yeah, I feel bad about that.
Well, I have, uh,
changed a lot since then.
Yes, you have.
This all started when we traced
some guns back to one of Roland's shops.
They'd been used
in a school shooting.
The operation was supposed
to take three months, tops.
That snowballed into a year.
I started out as,
uh, Roland's assistant.
And then one day he asked me out.
A.T.F.. said, "Couldn't hurt."
A cup of coffee
turns into an evening.
[Sighs]
Alonzo forced me to go with it.
The next thing I know,
I'm wearing an engagement ring.
Have you ever been undercover, Jarod?
Once or twice.
She has your eyes.
- You've seen her?
- Yes. Her and your father.
They both look well, considering.
How long has it been
since you saw them?
Two months.
I used to go every week...
but, uh, Alonzo put a stop to that.
Said Roland was getting too close.
And what about you?
Were you getting too close?
[Shouting]
You think I'm enjoying this?
Look, I know Cassie needs me,
but I can't walk!
And what if Roland
finds out about her?
Her father's gone.
She can't lose another parent.
Jenna, just keep your voice down.
I understand.
They've moved Cass and my dad,
and Alonzo won't let me see them.
Whatever it takes to get the fat cat.
Don't you have enough
on Pritchard to put him away?
Roland's not the target.
We still don't know who
all this money washing's for. [Sighs]
- We meet him in two days.
- The old friend in New Brunswick.
Do me a favor.
Keep this.
It belonged to my mother.
I want Cassie to have that... if, uh...
things don't work out.
Everything will work out.
And then what?
I don't know who I am anymore, Jarod.
People change.
We used to call you "Shifty G."
It's no wonder
that you're Raines's priest.
This is about William?
Of course.
Jarod said you'd come.
You know Jarod?
Father Jarod
is the bishop's favorite envoy.
And Mr. Raines is studying
to be a deacon.
That's why he's meeting with you.
No. Daily confession.
William lives with many demons.
But he is also a child ofGod.
He will be granted absolution...
no matter what his sins.
Including murder?
He feels very badly
about Catherine's death...
and regrets profoundly
the pain it caused her daughter.
What other lies did he tell you?
I can't betray what
he told me in confession.
However, Jarod was curious
about something...
Mr. Raines told his associate
in the parking lot.
Something about
the... Veritas Project.
Veritas. Truth.
Overheard in the parking lot.
Is that yourway of betraying a confession?
I was wrong about you.
You're worse than Raines.
So full of anger.
That's my religion.
[Camera Shutter Clicking]
Uh, I'll be right up.
I'm gonna make a phone call.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- This is Alonzo.
- So...
how do I look?
So you're an ex-cop, Detective Jarod Gray.
Six years Baltimore P.D.
That give you some right
to jeopardize my operation?
You're doin' a fine job. I overheard
Jenna yelling atyou on your cell phone.
- You're lucky it was me that
overheard and not Pritchard.
-Jen's a little frayed now.
Who wouldn't be? You've taken her family,
you're practically blackmailing her.
Why don't you admit it?
You're in over your head.
You think I wanted this? These attacks
on Pritchard are gettin' worse.
- I've noticed. Who's tryin' to kill him?
- You tell me.
Obviously you've read my file. You know that
I was a good cop and I'm here to help.
- Now, who is tryin' to kill him?
- The best we can figure it's a client.
Pritchard's skimming from the people
he's laundering money for.
- So he's more dangerous
than I thought he was.
- You have no idea.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Who the hell are you, anyway?
I'm somebody who's trying to make sure
that Agent McGann doesn't end up dead.
About a year ago, right after Jen started
workin' undercover here...
we found one of Pritchard's gun suppliers
dead in the woods, double tap at the chest.
Now, word was he crossed Pritchard,
but we never found a weapon to match ballistics.
So, you weren't able to pin
the murder on Pritchard.
- No.
- And now you're holding
Agent McGann's daughter?
We're not holding her.
We're protecting her.
By making her mother stay
with a killer?
Jen may be in deep,
but she's the best agent I know.
- Three more days, she'll get us what we need.
- Us... or you?
Excuse me, Mr. McGann?
Agent Jarod Gray, A.T.F.
I came down here to tell you
that your daughter will be home soon.
Just in time for Cassie's
first Communion, right?
I don't believe A.T.F. lies anymore.
That's not a lie, sir.
It's a promise.
Cassie. Mr. Gray here works
with your mother.
My mommy catches bad guys.
Yes, Cassie, she does.
She asked me to come down here...
to tell you that she misses you very much,
and she'll see you soon.
I see her at night, in my dreams.
But it's not the same.
Cassie, your mom asked me
to give you this.
She wants you to take
very good care of it.
Look at that, kiddo.
That was your grandma's ring.
Mommy hasn't come in a long time.
Does she not wanna see us?
Of course she does, Cassie.
I tell you what.
You save a seat for her
at your Communion.
That's a mighty big promise
you're making.
[Jarod]
She'll be here.
[Gunfire]
Jenna, Pritchard, get down!
[Gunshot]
[Footsteps Approaching]
Strike me down now, Lord.
Willie.
Miss Parker.
This saintly routine is wearin' kind of thin,
don't you think, Deacon?
You've been talking to my priest.
Please. Sit.
We've been down a dark road, you and I.
Our footprints side-by-side.
But at times...
there was only one set.
That was when I carried you.
Really?
I thought that was when
you were off killing my mother.
Believe what you must believe,
Miss Parker.
But find it in your heart to forgive me.
It will give you inner peace.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
What?
- Where are you?
- You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
This Veritas thing Raines and Willie
were talking about.
It's an experimental
airborne toxin...
developed by the Centre
and shelved in the '80s.
- Raines is resurrecting it.
- Some people can't resist temptation.
- You know the one about
"thou shall not covet"?
- Of course.
That's one commandment
you don't want to break.
- Thanking you is gettin' to be a habit.
- Just doing my job.
- What's the word on the gunman?
- Muretta and I gotta talk to the cops.
You okay?
That look in your eyes,
it's genuine concern for him.
Emotional assimilation.
The psychological side effect
of prolonged undercover work.
You are an expert.
Just don't forget that the man
you're engaged to is a killer.
Roland's done a lot of terrible things,
but he's no killer.
- Alonzo didn't tell you, did he?
- Tell me what?
He's unbelievable.
Jarod?
Alonzo has left out a small detail.
Since he put that ring on your finger,
Pritchard killed a gun supplier.
- What?
- Stay focused or get out.
Okay, uh-
Let's just say that he is a killer.
That's all the more reason
for me to stay under.
I don't want anything
to happen to my little girl.
It's just...
one more night, unless,
of course, you know...
where the meeting is in New Brunswick.
Your fiance keeps that a secret.
Then again, I know
where he keeps those.
[Beeps]
[Beeping]
Looks like your cover's blown,
Agent McGann.
This is what Raines was up to.
Veritas was tested here
in the early '80s.
If this is a dead end, I'm gonna track down
Father Giuseppe and break his other nine digits.
It might be kind of fun, actually.
- More of that forbidden priest thing, huh?
- [Chuckles] Just open the door.
The door seems to be pressurized
or something.
I got it.
[Coughs]
There's some kind of gas!
Broots! Broots! Oh, my God!
Broots! Broots!
[Coughs]
Canary. Canary in a coal mine. Canary.
Canary in a coal mine?
[Coughing Continues]
Broots, I want you to find out anything else
you can about how this gas could possibly be used.
I'm gonna go find Father Giuseppe.
Have Sydney take a look at you.
- Why didn't you tell her?
- Certain details are kept from an agent.
Stop making excuses.
You crossed the line.
- The man is a killer!
- The agent could be compromised!
- The agent was compromised!
- What?
I found Jenna's personnel file
in Pritchard's gun safe.
Listen to me. We don't make a move
until Pritchard makes a move.
What if he makes a move on Jenna?
You prepared to dredge your agent up
from the Hudson?
- She knows the risks.
- What did you just say?
- It's the job!
- Is making her daughter an orphan
part of the job too?
We'll watch Pritchard. He won't take a dump
without us knowing. He won't do anything.
You'd better pray that he doesn't.
You're the bodyguard!
Protect her!
Those mandatory trigger locks,
they're a bitch, aren't they?
They're not mandatory yet.
I got no illusions
about what I do, Jarod.
Let me tell you somethin'.
When some pissed-off day trader...
decides to take an A.K.
to his brokerage firm...
I'm not standin' there
handin' him bullets either.
But what if he needs
some money laundered?
Come again?
I like to know who I'm protecting.
Sometimes knowledge is not power.
Well, in my case, it is.
Jenna isn't exactly
who she says she is.
She's A.T.F.
- Who have you told about this?
- Nobody.
Looks like now you're gonna need
some help calling off your engagement.
Let's just say I have
some experience in this arena.
No. I meant what I said.
You take a bullet for her.
- Jen is my future.
- Are you tellin' me
you're in love with her?
Let's just say I'm in love with what she
can give me- a get-out-of-jail-free card.
So, tonight, when we're safe, Jenna radios
her boss and I give them the fat cat...
and we get a little beach house
in a sexy, non-extradition country.
- If she follows the plan.
- She will.
A Colt 1911 "A."
It can be very convincing.
But I got somethin' better than that.
Jen's daughter.
Cute kid, huh?
Like I said, Jarod,
I got no illusions about what I do.
[Giuseppe]
You know how I stand on this.
[Miss Parker] Raines told me
what he's doing with the Veritas gas.
- He confessed!
- He said nothing about that.
He's a psychotic killer.
And he's up to something horrific.
- Do you define all men by their sins?
- Only the bad ones.
Only the ones that take a girl
in the Basilica de Roma and cop a feel.
That's not true and you know it.
This isn't about two teenagers
groping in a basilica.
- Besides, it was you who came on to me.
- [Scoffs]
- I rejected you. The pain of that
rejection lives inside you.
- Not true.
It is true, Parker.
You've rewritten history.
Create an enemy in your mind because
that's what you needed to survive.
Anger is your religion.
And you need enemies like me
and Mr. Raines to fuel that distorted faith.
If thy brother trespass against you,
rebuke him.
And if he repent, forgive him.
- He killed my mother.
- If he trespassed against thee...
- He has presided over every
moment of pain in my life.
- seven times in a day...
- He's a monster!
- thou shalt forgive him!
And you are not his priest.
You're his coconspirator!
Forgive yourself, Parker.
If you don't, you'll surely be dammed
to a life of eternal suffering.
God forgives.
I don't.
[Bell Tolling]
[Jarod]
You can't put your faith in him.
- He wouldn't hurt her.
- You can't take that chance.
- I don't have a choice!
I have to go with him tonight.
- Jen, listen to-
No. I have to finish this...
and know that son of a bitch
is behind bars.
It's the only way
that Cassie can be safe.
You can't talk me out of this.
- Where's Jarod?
- I sent him home.
Why?
Roll, baby.
I got a confession to make.
Jen! You have to trust me.
Don't do this.
All right, somebody tell me
what the hell is goin' on.
- I know you know who I am.
- Don't tell him anything!
Stop! I'll do what you ask.
I'll help you out of the country.
Just don't hurt my daughter.
- Don't go with him.
- Shut up! You back off.
No matter what he says,
you can't believe him!
He's still going to kill your daughter!
I would never kill a little girl.
[Gasping]
[Groaning]
Jarod, I'm sorry.
Get in the car.
You know what.
It's funny.
But I actually did fall in love with you,
in a strange way.
Then you had to tear my heart out.
But I guess you made the right choice.
Oh, she did.
You missed me!
You know, I heard this song once
that happiness was a warm gun.
Yes, it is.
You needa cooling-down period.
[Grunting]
Shooting an ex-cop.
Not a very smart idea.
Especially when he's put
blanks in your clip.
You see, there's this open case
over at the A. T.F..
Something about a gun supplier
found shot to death in the woods.
They never could make
a ballistics match.
Or find the killer.
Now they will.
[Jenna]
Want to know something funny?
I had feelings for you.
But you had to go...
and threaten my little girl.
Bad decision.
Karma. Ain't it a bitch?
- This is Alonzo. Over.
- [Jarod Over Radio] Alonzo.
-Jarod, you bastard,
what have you done with Jenna?
- She's safe and sound.
- Now, did you ever get the fat cat?
- We got him.
- But no Pritchard.
- Check the third alley off of 18th Street.
Oh, and, uh, I left a little present
for you under your seat.
[Broots] We tracked down some of the properties
of the gas that Raines was developing.
Veritas relaxes the lungs to the point
where they can no longer take in oxygen.
In small doses, it's not even lethal.
I'm sure Raines skipped that part.
Weak lungs is one of the theories
behind sudden infant death syndrome.
Oh, my God. The baby.
[Speaking Gibberish]
Stop!
Get away from him!
I know what you're up to
with the Veritas.
I don't think you do.
A diluted version of Veritas gas
helped me loosen baby Parker's lungs.
[Fussing]
He's free of this ball and chain.
I wish I could say
the same for myself.
I saw the testing room.
There are many villains
in the Centre, Miss Parker.
Iknow you need them to survive.
But I can't be your enemy anymore.
[Priest] This is the Lamb of God
who takes awaythe sins of the world.
Happy are we who are called
to the Lord's Supper.
- The Body of Christ.
- [Girl] Amen.
- [Girl #2] Amen.
- The Body of Christ.
- [Girl #3] Amen.
- Amen.
- The Body of Christ.
- [Girl #4] Amen.
May Almighty God bless you,
the Father...
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
The mass has ended. Let us go in peace
to always love and serve the Lord.
Look at your mother.
- You got the bad guy?
- We got him. Now let's go home.
www.tvsubtitles.net