Previously on One Tree Hill.
Do I know you?
Well you should, I’m your sister-in-law.
We agreed to keep what happened between us a secret.
Relax, Nathan, Haley doesn’t have a clue.
Jenny’s mine now.
Hand her over.
Forget it.
The rumours, they weren’t rumours.
I’m gay.
This is all my stuff, I don’t understand.
I had my mom talk to your parents
and they said that you could stay here till the summer.
Thank you, Karen. You know you saved my life, right?
I’m not gonna make it easy on you and sometimes you’re not gonna like me for it.
It’s just like having a real mom.
Hello?
Think fast, what’s in a gin and tonic?
Taylor?
Can you believe two guys already fell for that one, today?
Drunks are so easy.
Let me guess; you’re in a bar.
Oh, not just any bar.
I will have you know, I am in Athens, Georgia at The famous Swinging Donkey.
What happened to Florida?
Oh, Florida’s still there, I’m just not in it.
So, how bout you?
Well, I think I just passed a place called Slicklizzard, Alabama.
Which means you went chasing after my sister.
Tell me she’s sitting next to you.
No, I’m afraid not.
I’m sorry, Nathan.
Yeah.
Listen, I gotta run.
What’s going on?
Don’t ask.
I’ll see you when I see you.
You sure about this, Luke?
Yeah, trust me. I talked to Nathan before her left.
He said it was okay.
How’s he doing anyway?
Not so good, I guess.
Yeah, well, I mean, I offered to clean this
but it’s a good place to hide out for the next couple of days.
So, get settled. I gotta run over to the dealership before school.
What time are you meeting with your lawyer today?
A couple of hours.
I’m sorry I had to drag you into this mess, I just, I couldn’t involve my parents, you know?
I told you; if you need me, call me.
Alright?
See ya.
Hey, Lucas. What’s up?
Oh… nothing.
I’m just… dropping some papers off for you to sign.
Everything okay?
Yeah, I guess I just didn’t get much sleep last night.
Yeah, I noticed you’re up early.
Been working yourself pretty hard lately.
I’ll be fine.
I’ll tell you what; take the day off tomorrow.
Bet you haven’t been to the Rivercourt in a few days.
Don’t wanna lose your stroke.
It has been a while.
Done.
I’m heading off to a meeting. I’ll see ya later.
Cash?
Yeah.
How much?
Too much to count while my head was in the ceiling.
Did you find anything else?
There was a notebook in one of the bags.
I didn’t get a good look at it but it… looked like a ledger.
Makes sense.
Gotta keep track of all the money.
Yeah, but I’m just wondering;
Why keep it all in the ceiling. Why not keep it in a bank where it’s safe?
Well, there’s two reasons to hide money, Lucas.
Either you don’t want Uncle Sam to know you have it,
or you don’t want him to know how you got it.
- I gotta get that ledger.
- No, you don’t.
Andy.
We gotta get that ledger.
Darby.
Hi, Anna.
What’re you doing here?
I got your e-mail.
Can I come in?
Or we could just stand out here until someone sees us,
starts some rumours and then you can move again.
Darby.
I’m sorry.
That wasn’t funny.
Maybe this was a bad idea.
No.
It’s good to see you.
Come on in.
Okay, look just… tell me what is going on because there’s no way
that a judge would give Nikki custody of Jenny.
Judge has already ruled.
Jake, a warrant’s been issued for your arrest.
Right now, the police are our there and they’re looking for you and your daughter.
Trust me… trust me when I tell you this is your only option.
Can you just… tell me the truth here?
If I give up my daughter today, how long until I get her back?
How long until Jenny’s safe?
Two months. Maybe three.
And if I don’t give her up?
You go to jail, and you stay there until you do.
How bout a gin and tonic?
How bout I see some ID?
So, what brings you to town, sailor?
I just wanted to check out The Swinging Donkey;
see if it’s really as… classy as everybody says it is.
Hmm, what d’ya think?
Not so much.
But, it does have one thing I’m kinda craving.
I know, gin and tonic.
Yeah, that too.
I guess my phone call worked.
You staying the night?
I don’t know.
Haven’t thought that far ahead.
Well, I’m house-sitting the apartment upstairs.
You’re welcome to stay with me if you like.
What d’ya say?
Sounds like a plan.
Now why is it the garbage men always forget to pick up the white trash?
I need to talk to Jake.
Right.
No police, no lawyers, just me and Jake.
The Rivercourt, six o’clock.
By the way… the police are watching you right now.
And you should know, as long as you help Jake hide Jenny, you’re an accessory.
That means when you’re caught with my daughter,
you’re gonna get arrested.
But don’t worry; you can always go to college after prison.
So, I guess you told everybody back at school.
About us.
No. Just me.
How did people take it?
It was pretty divided; still is I guess.
Some people don’t wanna be seen with me. That part sucks.
But I guess you find out who your real friends are.
Look, um… you know, the truth is, Anna,
there were some pretty dark days after you left…
and it hasn’t gotten much easier.
But do I regret being with you? Coming out?
No.
Not for a minute.
And you know what makes it always better?
Vanilla lattes, extra foam.
You know, we should probably… head back.
Hey, Anna.
Hey, Lucas. Ha-oh, um,…
um, this is… Darby. She’s, um…
Actually, Lucas, Darby’s the girl I told you about.
From my old school.
Oh my God! I’ve heard so much about you.
Really?
Yeah, you’re different than I imagined, but…
Oh, thought I’d be more butch?
Okay, I didn’t mean…
Just kidding.
Well, I was just giving Darby the Tree Hill grand tour, do you wanna tag along?
I’d love to, but I gotta go meet someone, so… call me tomorrow, okay?
Pleasure to meet you, Darby.
So that’s the famous Lucas, huh?
He’s cute.
So who’s the better kisser?
- Me or him?
- Stop.
Bevin! Hi!
I have always imagined this room,
just darker
and with Lucas on the bed.
Anyway, get dressed.
What for?
It’s a surprise.
I can’t, I have to work.
I promised Karen I’d help her out at the café.
Well, the cheer squad’s throwing a party tonight and…
you kinda need to be there.
The squad has some serious concerns, Brooke.
Ever since you started this whole… presidency thing, you’ve been… drifting.
I am still your captain, okay? I promise.
Then prove it. Please. We miss you.
Well, Karen did say she only needed me for a few hours
so I guess I could do both.
What do I wear to a cheer intervention anyway?
Jake.
How did you find me here?
Oh, I guess I’m just better at this than you are.
You wanted to talk, let’s talk.
I told you to meet me at six o’clock, it’s only five.
Like I’m gonna fall for that.
Jake, look, you’ve gotta stop this; the hiding, all of it.
I have a right to my daughter.
You’re not getting her.
Fine, well, I guess it’s time
that I tell you something that, at the moment, is… kinda relevant.
Okay, this should be good.
She’s not your daughter.
Think about it…
we always used protection.
Nice try.
I guess it was just a matter of time before you thought of that one, huh?
- It’s the truth.
- No.
This is the only truth,
no matter what, Jenny is, and she will always be, my daughter.
I’m done here.
Okay, get into the game, little girl.
I always knew you were a lightweight but this is getting embarrassing!
I’m just warming up!
You’ve been warming up for the past two hours.
Drag out of the bullpen and do a shot!
Okay.
How did you end up here?
What, at this dream job?
I don’t know, it’s kinda what I do best.
Bartending?
Find random places to party.
Next week, it’ll be someplace else.
Lucky me.
You’re not wearing your wedding ring.
Neither is Haley.
Nathan, you should know that before I called you,-
Taylor, come on, we need you now!
We’ll talk about this later, I gotta get to work.
I thought you said your shift was over.
Somebody’s gotta pay for these drinks.
Something tells me you’re gonna enjoy this.
Karen. Hi.
Did you have fun tonight?
Not really.
The party was kind of weak but I had to be there.
Apparently I’ve been drifting.
You been drinking?
No, drifting.
No, Brooke, I’m asking you if you’ve been drinking tonight.
Just a little.
I expected you at the café.
I know, I lost track of time. I’m sorry.
Well, sorry isn’t good enough.
I advanced your salary and…
I’d like you to return the money I gave you.
I… kind of spent it.
Got to bed. You’re grounded.
Grounded?
I’ve never been grounded in my whole life.
Well there’s a first time for everything.
Well, you’re not my mom.
No. But right now, you’re my responsibility.
But I was drifting.
Okay, are there any security cameras?
Uh, no, just the alarm.
Okay, remember what I said;
in and out, we do this fast.
Yeah.
Okay, just grab the ledger.
I’ll stay here and keep an eye out.
What’ve you got?
It’s gone.
What, the ledger?
All of it.
I don’t understand.
It was right there a few hours ago.
Ah, he knows.
Dan, he knows and he moved it.
So what do we do?
Oh, that’s it, no, no, game over.
So Dan wins?
As much as I would love to keep playing this little game with Dan, it just got serious.
If he knows you found that money, there’s no telling what he’s gonna do.
I’m his son, Andy.
And look what he just did to his brother!
This guy’s got no conscience, Lucas.
I think it’s time you move back in with your mother.
I can’t!
Come on, Andy. We’re so close.
You have to find out if I’m right, okay?
If there’s any chance that he’s on to you, you have to get out.
I will. I promise.
And one more thing;
if your mother asks me anything about this, I’m not gonna lie to her. Understood?
Brooke!?
Yeah?
What’s this?
Just some stuff I ordered from the ‘mark.’ magalogue.
Pretty great, huh?
Are you going somewhere?
Just out for a quick run, but you never know who you’re gonna see.
Aren’t you forgetting something?
Lip-gloss.
Brooke, you’re grounded. That means you don’t get to head out for quick runs.
Since when does grounding apply to fitness?
Since now.
That’s a little harsh, if you ask me.
I’m not asking.
Okay, so what am I supposed to do here?
Lucas does chores.
Chores?
Here’s a list.
So what, I pick the one I wanna do?
Sure… and after you’ve finished with it,
keep on picking until they’re all done.
Okay, no offence, I didn’t come here to be a cleaning lady, lady.
Well, then…
I’ll help you pack your bags and we’ll call your folks.
So I’m, like, imprisoned here?
You can leave the house to go to school and to go to work.
What work? I don’t even have a job.
Oh, but you do have a job.
Until you pay me back the money I gave you, you have a job at the café.
You wanted to see me, coach?
Take a seat next to your partner in crime here.
Well now, Bonnie and Clyde,
I guess you’re wondering why I called you here.
Hey, Luke, I was just actually-
He just… wants to talk to you for a minute, Jake.
I’ll leave you two alone.
I already know my options, coach.
From what I’ve heard, you’ve only got one option.
I can’t give her away.
Son, you’ve got a good chance of getting her back.
I can’t take chances like that.
It beats the alternative, doesn’t it?
Does it?
Coach, you remember last year? Beginning of the season?
We had that away game at Bear Creek?
Yeah, I remember.
It was right after Jenny was born…
and my parents were out of town all week, I couldn’t watch her, so…
I decided to let Nikki have her, for the night.
So I get home from the game and I call Nikki;
there’s no answer.
I go to her house and she’s not home.
So I… I looked everywhere, I called her friends.
Then finally, after about an hour,
I find her car and it’s parked across the street from some bar.
Nikki was passed out in the front seat, the keys were still in the ignition
and there was frost all over the windows; I couldn’t even see her…
and then I look in the back seat…
and there she is, my little girl.
She’s shivering.
She didn’t even have a blanket on her, coach.
- Jake, I-
- One night.
All she had to do was look after Jenny for one night.
She couldn’t do it.
And now they want me to give her my daughter for three months…
worth of nights?
So how’d it feel when you came out to Lucas?
Terrible.
Scary.
Still feels scary.
What about you?
When you told your parents.
Huh, well, uh, believe it or not, I practised in the mirror first.
And then when I thought I had it all memorised,
I went downstairs, took a deep breath, and I told them
I loved them very much but I had something I needed to tell them about myself.
- How did they take it?
- Honesty? Not as well as I’d hoped.
I think they’re still trying to process how it affects their lives.
What d’ya mean?
Well, um, I read this book about coming out,
and it said that for some parents, finding out your child is gay is like losing a loved one.
All the dreams they might have had just vanish;
no weddings, grandchildren.
So I think when I told them, I shattered some of those dreams for them.
Yeah.
Even though things are still kinda weird,
I don’t think I’ve ever been closer to them.
Coz at the end of the day,
I know they still love me.
I know that… that’s what worried me the most.
That they wouldn’t…
Well you’re braver than me, Darby.
No I’m not.
Look…
I didn’t come here to get you to come out to your parents.
I came here to help you understand that when you finally do,
you’re gonna be okay.
I’m gonna go.
Long drive.
I’m glad you came.
Yeah, me too.
I miss you.
So this is you’re ‘A’ game, huh?
You know what my dad always told me?
Forget about practice; as long as you come to play,
on game day when the stakes are high, odds are you’ll come out a winner.
Last time was just a practice round.
Since when are you taking advice from your dad?
I know, alright.
But if there’s one thing he knows about, it’s winning.
Okay, so what are the stakes tonight?
Well, if I make this shot,
we go upstairs.
And do what?
Whatever I want.
And if you miss?
Let’s go.
I can’t do this.
Because of Haley?
No.
Because of me.
Haley called me…
right after you left Austin.
Were you planning on telling me this before or after we had sex?
We weren’t gonna have sex, Nathan.
I knew that; I was just waiting for you to figure it out.
So what, you’re like my, uh… my guardian angel?
No, it’s not that. It’s just…
you’re lost…
and lonely, and I’m pretty good at making people forget how lonely they really are.
Right…
that’s a nice way of describing what you’re really good at.
Sleep if off, Nathan. You have a long drive tomorrow.
What’re you gonna do?
Apparently, what I do best.
Hey, Lucas, come on in.
Uh, hey, um, I was just… returning a book.
What you got there?
‘The Hound of the Baskervilles’. Sherlock Holmes.
Since when’re you a fan of Arthur Conan Doyle?
Since I can remember.
Every kid wants to be Sherlock Holmes at some point.
Well, not me.
I was always partial to Professor Moriarty.
You do realise he was the villain.
That’s one interpretation.
Well, um… thanks for letting me borrow it.
Hey, Cinderella.
You hanging in there?
I take it you’ve heard.
Well, my mom can crack the whip.
I can’t believe she actually grounded me. I thought she liked me.
Oh, Brooke, she does like you.
Hey, she cares enough about you to ground you.
So what number are you up to, huh? Three?
Four. Mop the kitchen floor.
And you’re using a sponge?
Is that wrong?
Okay… Brooke,
this is a mop.
Look, I’ll tell you what, alright;
you take the evens, I’ll take the odds.
And I’ll bet we can bust this out in like… half hour.
Thanks, Luke.
Anything for you.
Mom… dad...
you know I love you…
but there’s something I have to tell you about myself.
When I asked if we could move here,
I told you it was because I couldn’t take the rumours…
but really…
I was just running away from my life.
From who I am.
Because…
the rumours…
they were all true.
I like girls.
You’ve always taught me to be proud of who I am.
That’s not so easy for me because…
I haven’t been able to accept who I am.
Until now.
And I want you to know that this is hard for me…
because I love you so much…
and I never wanna disappoint you.
But I have to stop disappointing myself, too.
And… I just…
I hope you still love me.
Hey, beautiful.
I have to do something tonight.
And I need you to know that I have searched from the bottom of my heart
and I truly believe that this is the best thing for you.
For us.
I just hope that some day, you’ll be able to understand that.
You’re leaving?!
I’m sorry, Peyton.
- No, I’ll go with you.
- No. No, you can’t.
- We can be together.
- Yeah, I wish we could…
Well then at least tell me where you’re going.
Please.
- Maybe I can help.
- I can’t tell you right now.
But I need- I need you to know something. I-
Look, I’ve never been happier than when I’m with you.
Okay, I’ve never… felt this much of… everything.
And if I could, I would stay with you here forever.
But I just can’t.
You’re the only person I can truly count on.
That’s why I need you to do one last thing for me.
Sneaking away without saying goodbye? That’s original.
I, uh… didn’t think you’d wanna see me.
I’m really sorry, Taylor, for what I said.
How I acted.
It’s okay.
You get one free pass with me.
Next time, watch your back.
I had fun, though… before that.
I know you did.
But after a while, all the parties just… blend together.
You know, sometimes I just wish I could start over.
You can. We all can, right?
Not me.
Once people think of you a certain way, you’re never gonna be able to change their minds.
I am who I am and I have to live with that.
But you, nobody’s put a label on you yet.
You can still be whoever you wanna be.
Without Haley.
If she’s not gonna be there for you, you have to start being there for yourself.
- I don’t know if I can.
- You can.
And you will, just… wake up every morning and live your life.
What happens if she comes back?
Well, then, it’ll be your decision.
Get home safe, Nathan.
Try not to go dancing on any bars.
I won’t if you won’t.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, I’m Jake Jagielski.
There’s a warrant out for my arrest.
Hey, Anna, what’s up?
I told my parents.
You told them?
That’s huge!
How’d they take it?
Um… I’m not sure, really.
They, they cried a lot but I think it was just because they were trying to understand…
then, when I was finished,
they told me they loved me.
Which is all I really wanted to hear.
I am… so proud of you, Anna.
There’s more;
I told my parents that they always taught me to be proud of myself
and the only way for me to do that is…
if I go back to my boarding school and finally be who I am.
Oh… does that mean you’re leaving?
Yes.
I wanted to stop in and see Peyton, but…
she’s got enough to deal with right now.
- Tell her I’ll call her soon?
- I will.
I am gonna miss you so much.
You’ve been a great friend.
You, too.
I’m a better person for knowing you, Luke.
How bout one last game of horse, huh?
That sounds perfect.
Tell me you love me.
And tell me you did not just touch that half eaten bagel.
No, I don’t;
yes, I did.
And why are you waving that thing around in my face?
Because it happens to be an invitation to the biggest party of the year.
Thanks, but I think I’ll pass.
And for the record, there have been, like, six ‘biggest parties’ of the year this month,
so get a new rating system.
But this one is a ‘can’t miss’.
And so was the last one.
No, the last one was a ‘shouldn’t miss’.
Just look at the invitation and I won’t say another word.
This is a ‘Courtney Ryan’ party. This is a ‘can’t miss’.
Told ya. The party starts at, like, nine so meet us there around… eleven thirty?
Oh, and Brooke, welcome back.
Lucas!
Come on in.
What’s all this?
I thought it was time to upgrade the security system.
Too many people know the pass-code to the main alarm.
Oh, that’s a good idea.
Besides, outside of the family, you never know who you can trust these days.
I got you something.
Thought you’d like it since you’re into Sherlock Holmes.
I marked my favourite story for you.
Have you read that one?
Yeah, a long time ago.
It wasn’t very popular with the fans, but…
I think it’s some of Doyle’s most honest work.
Why’s that?
Because he wrote what he was feeling.
He got tired of writing that character;
The Snoop.
All the sneaking around…
all the deception.
But he knew when it was time to end it.
That’s why, in the end, the great Sherlock Holmes falls to his death.
Well, I think maybe you missed the point.
Did I?
When Sherlock Holmes falls off the cliff,
he pulls Professor Moriarty down with him.
You see, he sacrificed himself to bring down the bad guy.
That’s the point I think Doyle was trying to make.
Well, like I said,
that’s one interpretation.
Hey, Lucas.
I’ll be seeing you.
Ready?
Jake Jagielski,
you have the right to remain silent.
Ma’am, we have a warrant to search the property.
Anything you say may be used against you in the court of law.
You have the right to have an attorney present during questioning now, or in the future.
If you can not afford an attorney…
one will be appointed to you.
Do you understand your rights as I have explained them to you?
I do.
Brooke, you’re home.
Yeah, I’m grounded, remember?
Not anymore.
I think you’ve learned your lesson.
You have one new message.
Nathan, it’s me.
I just needed to call because I want you to know-
Message has been erased.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I knew you’d talk me out of it.
So, where’s Jenny?
She’s safe.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net