Previously on One Tree Hill.
I’m the one who did it. I broke her windshield.
When I got off the bus, I saw Haley kissing some guy.
He was kinda scrawny, had a guitar case, sort of… hell-t hair.
I took the test.
We’ll know in a couple of days.
Thank you, thank you.
I’m just... I’m tired of running, Peyton.
Come with me.
Let’s bring Jenny back home.
Something happened tonight.
I asked her to marry me.
You and I are the only ones who know the truth about Jules.
And I’m willing to keep it a secret.
What do you want from me?
I’m sure we can work something out.
I think the Latin book’s upside-down.
Like I could read it if it was right-side-up.
How long’s it gonna take you to get these fliers done?
Just gotta download the pics to my computer.
You got a slogan in mind?
Yeah, ‘Brooke Davis for President’.
Short enough for even the stoners to remember.
You gonna leave Keith and Jules alone?
I’m thinking about it.
He’s happy for once.
He’s getting married. Don’t screw that up.
They’re getting married?
I’ll tell you what – I’ll leave them alone…
if you give me a chance to prove that I can be a good father.
Well, how you gonna do that, huh?
Get a lobotomy?
No.
You move in with me.
Haley, we seriously have to hide the matches from your pyro sister.
Be grateful it’s just candles. When we were kids, I set fire to our bunk beds.
Look… where is Haley and, does she know that you’re wearing her shirt?
At school and no, I needed a beach cover-up.
Hey, I borrowed some cash, for beer, I hope you don’t mind.
And, she left the computer on.
Love having you, Taylor.
Come visit anytime.
'Got your message. Don’t think I can leave you alone.'
'Miss you... Thinking of you... I want to kiss you.'
Hey, Luke. I’m taking a poll for the next issue of the paper.
What is your biggest concern for the upcoming student government election?
Having to answer polls.
Well, well, well. If it isn’t my favourite two voters in the same place.
You two can be the first to know I’m running for president. Do I have your support?
Well, do I have any choice?
Ah, let me think about that – no.
And if you’re still doing you newspaper dig, Mighty Mouth,
I’ll give you an exclusive on my campaign.
- Um… yeah, we should set that up.
- Good.
You guys seen Haley?
Uh… I think she’s tutoring.
You okay?
I gotta go.
Alright.
- No way. Is that… Jake?
- What?
Hey!
- When’d you get back?
- Couple days ago.
How’s Jenny?.
- Hey.
- Hi.
She’s great. She’s getting bigger every day.
You’re getting scrawny, man. You better hit that weight room before camp.
Yeah.
Will you still be here then?
Yeah, yeah. I’m back for good now.
I mean, I got some messes to clean up.
I gotta get a lawyer; see if I can… keep Nikki away, but… I’m done running.
Good.
We need you here.
Thanks.
Oh, Jake, I’m so glad you came back. You can still vote here, right?
- You good?
- Yes.
Thank you, for calling him.
You’re a good friend, Luke.
Hey. I heard you were out of town. Fill me in on all the dirt.
I… think you’re the only one who has any.
- Um… I have to ask you something.
- Yeah.
Did you kiss Chris?
How did you know about that?
That is seriously not important.
- It was, like, a goodbye kiss.
- With tongue?
Haley, what’s going on with you?
You know how ugly everything got with me and Brooke and Lucas and…
there were no wedding rings in that scenario.
Look, he just… he just kissed me.
And… I let him and it was a really stupid thing to do.
But… It’s-it didn’t mean anything, you know?
A kiss always means something.
Well, I never though I’d see you darken my door again, Jagielski.
Yeah, I wasn’t so sure myself, coach.
Where the hell’ve you been, son?
Just looking for a safe place in a non-safe world.
You find it?
I don’t think it exists.
So I figured I’d just have to create it myself.
How’s your game?
Well, haven’t had much cause to use it.
How bout your grades?
Well, I’ve been working a lot of hours; just to keep me and Jenny afloat
so I sorta stopped going to school.
That’s a damn fools plan.
Jenny deserves a whole lot better than a high school drop-out for a father.
I know, I know. That’s why I’m here.
I was hoping that you could speak to Principle Turner on my behalf coz…
well he wasn’t really happy last time I talked to him.
You gonna disappear again?
I don’t plan on it, coach.
We got a faculty meeting tonight.
I’ll corner Turner and see what I can do.
I appreciate that.
Oh, and about that safe place you’re building;
don’t do it alone.
There’s a lot of people here ready to help.
Talk to your folks lately?
Uh, yeah actually, my mom sent me an email.
Said dad is dragging em all over Wisconsin looking for, like, the Gouda museum or something.
What about Chris?
Did you go through my emails?
What is this, Haley?
Nothing. I sent him one email to say good luck on your music.
It looks like more than one email to me.
Taylor, must have sent these on my account because...
Yeah, look at the dates; They all start after she got here.
And this one was sent when I was at the café.
So you didn’t kiss Chris?
Taylor is just stirring up trouble like always.
Okay. I’m gonna tell her to leave then. That cool with you?
Yeah. She should go.
Alright.
Good afternoon folks.
Welcome to the first student government information session.
I’m gonna pass out these sign-up sheets for the various offices.
And once you’ve filled these out we’ll talk about scheduling.
Hi.
Erica Marsh.
I never pegged Brooke Davis for student government.
Well, I am captain of the cheerleading squad…
and a former homecoming queen. Can’t be that different, right?
Actually, government is a lot more than just a popularity contest.
Everybody, in this room, has at least a 3.8 GPA and a tonne of outside interest.
Take me; I’m president of the National Auto Society;
head of the French club and co-chair of Tree Hill Big Sisters.
Wow. You do all of that and yet you still have time to talk to us little people?
Maybe I can help you, Brooke.
Have you thought about running for secretary?
Nobody serious ever wants that job.
Actually, I’m running for president.
President?
You realise I’ve been president since seventh grade.
Really?
What’s was your name again?
Erica Marsh.
No, doesn’t ring a bell.
Don’t worry, it will.
Will be in one, Vivica.
Erica.
Whatever.
- Oh, hey.
- Oh, hey. You’re a lifesaver.
Deb’s out of town and I’m backed up on deliveries.
Okay, uh… no problem, I’ll pack up the car. But first…
the test results came.
I don’t have HCM.
Keith’s okay too.
Thank god.
Oh, I don’t think I could take it if anything were wrong with you.
I know.
Well, we should celebrate; anything you want.
I wanna… move in with Dan.
Right, and I wanna drive metal spike into my eyes.
Look, I know it sounds crazy, okay.
But college is gonna start in a few years...
You’re serious?
Yeah.
I wanna move in with Dan.
Over my dead body.
What’s this really about, Lucas?
What’s going on?
Nothing.
And I know this comes as a surprise to you…
and I’m sorry mom, but… it’s what I want. Okay?
You’re late!
Where the hell were you?
I… stopped by to check on Jules.
You should have called. Your office, right now.
Surprise!
What...?
Congratulations, big brother.
I hope Jules makes you as happy as Deb has made me.
But, how did you know?
Good news travels fast in this town.
A toast; to Keith and to Jules.
Two people lucky enough to find each other.
And I hope your lives together… are filled with many more surprises.
Oh no, this is just about the number of people we’re inviting to the wedding, so…
What’re you talking about?
Oh, you know, we’re just gonna… do something small.
Out of the question. You deserve a big blow-out.
No expense spared. It’s my gift.
I wanna give you a day you’ll remember for the rest of your life.
Besides, it’s not for you.
It’s for Jules. Every woman deserves to be a queen for the day.
What the hell are you doing with Lucas?!
So he told you?
Only that he’s moving in with you, not the real reason why!
He wants to get to know his father.
That’s crap and we both know it. You’re manipulating him somehow!
No, I’m letting him make a choice. He’s a big boy, Karen.
He may need something more than just his mommy.
Don't you dare walk away from me, we are nowhere near finished...
What’s going on?
It’s just a little party to celebrate Keith’s engagement.
Champaign?
Hey.
So… Nathan found out that I kissed Chris.
You told him?
No, my idiot sister has been emailing Chris under my screen name because, apparently,
the drama in her own life isn’t enough, and Nathan found the emails.
How’d he take it?
I just told him Taylor made it all up.
So… you lied to him, again?
Yeah, and I feel awful about it, but what’s the point of telling Nathan?
Chris is out of my life, okay?
Nathan would feel worse if he knew the truth.
What is the truth?
That Chris… and I are connected through music.
He understands that part of me in a way that Nathan doesn’t.
Okay, Haley, if… if Chris were in town…
would you be into him? Coz I mean you... kissed him.
I know I kissed him and it was a mistake.
So this whole connection is strictly music?
That’s all it is.
I love Nathan.
So I guess... congratulations are in order.
I’m sorry about this morning. That’s not how I wanted you to find out.
Why didn’t you just tell me?
You know, for as long as I can remember, Karen,
I wanted to be with you.
- And then I proposed...
- Keith.
No, really, it’s… it’s okay.
When you turned me down, I… I thought I’d never have any love in my life.
But now I’ve found the love of my life.
Jules is a lucky woman.
I guess I didn’t tell you because...
I needed to say this first;
I’m glad I loved you all those years.
You know, even if it didn’t work out.
My heart knew what it wanted.
So I was ready when Jules came along.
Did you guys set a date yet?
No, it’ll be soon though.
Lucas has already agreed to be my best man.
Really? I didn’t know.
We haven’t talked about anything but Dan since Lucas asked to move in with him.
Hang on, what?
Yeah, there’s something going on that he’s not telling me.
Hey.
Hey. Like my new campaign posters?
- I have never seen you looking so...
- Presidential?
Funereal.
Funny word coming from you; miss happy, goofy grin queen.
What’s going on with you and Jake anyway?
I don’t know, stop! We’re playing it by the ear.
Is that all you’re playing?
Okay, fine, don’t tell us. I’ll just keep my fingers crossed and expect juicy details later.
'Want a President with a 2.3 GPA?'
'Brooke Davis Skipped 4TH Period 30 Times Last Year!'
Who did that?
In our great democracy, anyone can run for president.
But you deserve a leader you can trust.
I have evidence that Brooke Davis stuffed the ballot box to win homecoming queen.
I knocked it over by accident! I was just putting the ballots back in!
And that might not be all she stuffs.
Oh, please, I haven’t stuffed since puberty. I can’t believe that little bitch went negative.
I can’t believe she beat you to it.
This election, choose honesty;
vote for me – Erica Marsh.
Little frosty in here, today, no?
You here to eat or give a weather report?
Okay, what’s going on?
I thought Lucas took the HCM test and was fine.
Yeah, but now he wants to move in with Dan…
and I haven’t been able to get him to budge so I’m gonna get Keith to try.
Keith.
Who’s getting married to Jules.
Wow, that’s great.
Is it? I mean, how well does he know this girl?
What if he’s just blinded by a pretty face and a hot body?
Well, some would say the same about you.
You can’t let Erica get away with smearing you like that.
You leave this stuff unanswered, it becomes the truth.
So what do you think I should do about Erica’s ads?
Uh… are they true?
Some of them.
Well don’t deny it. Politicians always get caught when they lie.
That’s brilliant, genius.
Stick to slinging hash.
Look, people like you, Brooke.
Just be who you are.
Okay, it’s official, Michelle Branch and Jessica Harp are playing at TRIC tomorrow!
- No way!
- Yes!
That’s awesome!
That will be perfect for my campaign launch party!
Yeah!
Wait, what?
Hey, can you… zip me up, brother?
You’re busted, Taylor.
I’ll take that for a no.
Where the hell have you been?
I met some people at the beach and we partied all night.
What’s your problem?
I know you pretended to be Haley and emailed Chris.
And what kind of a sister does something that twisted?
The kind who’s hoping the baby of the family doesn’t screw up like she did.
Oh, right. Is that why you made up all that stuff about a kiss?
You think I made it up?
I talked to Haley. There was no kiss.
Make whatever phone calls you need to find a place to crash.
You’re outta here.
I was beginning to think you’d skipped town and left all your stuff.
What do you care if I haven’t been around?
You’re kicking me out, right?
Drop the attitude, Tay. You brought this on yourself.
You’ve pulled a lot of crap over the years but emailing Chris as me…
I just, I can’t believe you’d be such a conniving little bitch.
Hey. You’re the bitch who’s kissing a guy that isn’t your husband.
You need a scapegoat, fine, let Nathan think that this is all on me,
but you and I both know the kiss happened.
Hey! Have a Bear Claw, brother.
We’re celebrating.
I’m leaving tonight.
Upgrade. I’m Dan.
And I’m out of your league.
Wanna bet?
What’re you doing here?
That’s the last of your stuff.
Need to make some room; Lucas is moving in.
Lucas is moving in with you?
Yeah, guess I’m not the devil after all.
Enjoy your breakfast.
'Brooke Davis for President, Erica Marsh never parties this hard!'
'Yes, Brooke Davis has a 2.3 GPA, at least she never wheats!'
Are you implying that I cheat for my 4.0?
Absolutely not.
Just like you weren’t implying that I have a double digit IQ.
Hey, Nate.
What’s going on, man?
Is it true you’re moving in with Dan?
Yeah.
Great.
What happened to ‘He can’t make me a substitute Nathan’?
It’s just… it’s more complicated than that.
Whatever, man.
Lucas.
Hey, I have to write a killer platform speech if I’m gonna win this election…
but I have no idea where to start.
Well why don’t you try asking Felix?
Because Whitey told us to read speeches by world leaders...
and then he mentioned this Charles Dicko guy who I thought
was that exchange student that’s always… smelling his fingers in class…
so obviously this is your area of expertise and not mine.
Can you help me?
How bout tonight, right before TRIC?
You’re the best, Lucas. Thank you.
Maybe I should do a contest...
you know, ‘vote for me and win a date’ or offer a makeover.
You don’t need a gimmick, Brooke.
Alright, just…
tell me why you wanna be president.
I am who I am…
no excuses.
But I’d like other people to know that there’s a lot more to me than just some party-girl.
This is from a speech, by John F. Kennedy.
I think it could work for you.
This is all about courage.
Nobody is gonna believe this, coming from me.
I would.
Hey.
Brought you some campaign buttons.
Oh.
Wow thanks, Felix, these are great.
Um… you wanted me to pick you up before TRIC.
Is it that late already?
I totally lost track of time.
Ah, we’re done anyway.
Everything you need to say…
is already in your heart.
Alright, we’re gonna go out to TRIC. Are you gonna be here when we get back?
No. My ride’s coming tonight.
Well where’re you gonna go?
I… met some guy starting a surf shop down in the Keys. I’ll crash there for a while.
And then what?
I don’t know, Haley. I don’t think that far ahead.
Well maybe you should.
Like having a plan has worked so well for you.
Well, listen... it’s not much but… here.
It’s all I’ve got.
I want you to have it.
Thanks…
but this won’t make you feel any less guilty about Chris.
- Hey.
- Are you kidding me?! DJ Bobo?
Where are The Executioners or The Chemical Brothers or anything.
Peyton. DJ has got this under control, okay?
The night’s gonna be great. Come on.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey!
- Welcome back.
- Where’s Nathan?
Uh… Karen needed help with some boxes.
Oh, well, I’ll go help them out.
I’ve been wanting to say hi to Karen, so…
- I’ll see ya.
- See you.
- Hi.
So… okay, this is gonna sound really weird and groupie but…
I’m a huge Michelle Branch fan, I was wondering if you could introduce me.
Yes, I will introduce you.
And I would like to think so,
But do you know that when you go
Hey, guys, I’m sorry.
Oh, hey.
Um… I just wanted to introduce you to a friend of mine.
Michelle Branch, Jessica Harp this is Haley.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hey. Haley James?
- Haley James-Scott actually.
Oh, you know what, we’ve heard a lot about you.
Uh… I don’t think that’s possible.
No, our opening act gave you rave reviews. Didn’t you?
I said she was okay.
So… you’re the opening act?
Not for long.
I’ll be headlining soon.
So, Haley, um… Chris played us your duet and it sounds really great.
You should join him on stage tonight.
Oh, thanks… but... I don’t think…
I’m just-I gotta head out, but it was really nice to meet you guys.
Nice to meet you too.
What the hell do you think you’re doing?
Giving you the biggest break of your life. You’re welcome by the way.
No, no, no, no, no, you did not do me any favours, okay?
I busted my ass to get The Wreckers here.
Yeah, but I sealed the deal.
Why? So you could see Haley?
I know that you kissed her.
Listen, it takes two, okay?
She didn’t exactly push me away.
You’re wasting your time, you know?
She’s over you.
Then you got nothing to worry about.
Hey, you guys. Thanks a lot for coming out tonight to check out The Wreckers.
We have a lot of great music coming your way…
and, we also have… Chris Keller.
What’s he doing here?
I… I didn’t know he was coming, I swear.
You guys still aren’t ready for this.
But I’m in a forgiving mood.
This one’s for you Haley.
I started up my hollow,
A piece of wood to follow,
A day that doesn’t come to the lucky.
And I realise there’s tomorrow,
But I would rather wallow in the rain,
You told Brooke about the windshield?
I’m working up to it.
Vote for me.
Well I’m cruisin’ El Paseo.
In my off-white coupe back ’65,
Oh, I'm cruisin' down my own street,
And my hoopty says to me,
"You better hang on to your benchseat,
I'm gonna take you for a ride",
And I'll let you know,
When it comes, when it comes,
I'll let you know,
But don't stay up for me,
Don't wait up for me if I'm not home, yeah,
So wait for fate to find me...
Maybe we should go.
No. No, I’m gonna waste that guy.
I thought that you weren’t coming.
My ride’s running late.
Who’s the stud?
Chris.
Well this evening just got interesting.
Yes, I'm on the road tomorrow,
So, next time that I see you in school,
It won’t be for too long,
And I'll let you know,
When it comes, when it comes,
I'll let you know,
But don't stay up for me,
Don't wait up for me if I'm not home-
Thanks a lot guys, you’ve been…
acceptable.
The Wreckers up next.
Looking for an autograph?
No, actually, I was looking to kick your ass.
But then I realised;
why bother?
There’s nothing here for you.
Haley sees what you really are;
pathetic poser.
Just wanted to let you know.
You’re wrong.
You’re just trying to silence that voice inside your head.
Yeah, you know the one.
That’s growing louder every day.
It’s saying ‘we’re drifting apart’, ‘I’m losing her’.
Actually, it’s saying ‘shut this guys up, once and for all’.
Okay, maybe I’m wrong. Maybe she does love you.
She does.
What if that’s not enough?
Okay you guys, the wait is over. Please join me in welcoming, to TRIC, recording artists;
Michelle Branch and Jessica Harp – The Wreckers!
Hey, thanks you guys. It’s so great to be here in Tree Hill.
And... vote for Brooke.
Do you want to run away together.
I would say it was your best night ever,
Too bad I fell for it.
And I walked along
Waiting for you to come along
Take my tortured heart by the hand
And write me off
Do you know I cry?
Do you know I die?
And it's not the good kind
You forced me to become strong
When I just cried, being weak
And you think you know
And I would like to think so
Hey.
I have a confession to make.
I’m jealous of Jules.
Ever since I’ve had Lucas - before that, even -
you’ve… been the one person that I could count on.
It’s gonna be hard to lose that.
Karen, we’ll still be in each others lives.
That would never change.
I know.
It’s just… taking some getting used to.
I'm tired of hiding
behind these lying eyes
I'm tired of this smile
That even I don't recognize
Hey.
Um… you played a really great set.
Yeah, I know.
Alright, well…
good luck.
You wanna know about it, don’t you?
The tour; the music.
It’s all happening for me now.
- It could still happen for you, Haley.
- It will, someday.
Well, someday is here.
I talked to Michelle, she wants you on the tour.
- What?
- People love the duet.
It’s real. You know, Jessica started off as Michelle’s back-up singer.
Look at them now.
The difference between wannabees and successes is grabbing opportunity.
Our tour bus leaves in a couple of hours and you know you should be on it.
You brave enough?
You know, now that Taylor’s leaving, maybe we’ll have enough hot water for our own showers.
Haley, what’s wrong?
Michelle Branch likes my voice.
She thinks I could be a singer. A real one.
Chris said that she wants me on tour.
I’m so far ahead with classes and I’d be back in time for finals.
So says the great Chris.
No, this isn’t about him, Nathan. This is about… opportunity.
I have, my entire life, been the reliable one and the dependable one
and I’ve always done… precisely what’s expected of me.
Till we got married.
Exactly. And then I finally did something for me…
something that I wanted…
and the world didn’t end.
And I have that chance again.
- If you leave me....
- This is not the end for us.
This is my shot to find out if I am good enough to have a life in music.
Or if nights at TRIC are all I get.
And this has nothing to do with Chris?
No. Absolutely not.
Then why haven’t you asked me to come with you?
Did you kiss him?
Yes.
I’m sorry. You have to believe me. That’s not what this is about.
Nathan...
Haley, listen; if you wanna go, you should go.
If you do…
we’re done.
Unpack!
I can’t.
I said unpack!
No.
Lucas, Lucas.
If you just tell me what Dan has said or done, we can fight him together.
No.
Mom, we can’t.
Go back to sleep. I’ve got her.
Hey, Mouth, you are just in time. I am so buzzed from the reaction to my campaign
that I am gonna practice my speech.
I’m the one who threw the brick through your car window.
I was drunk and…
I was angry.
Angry about what?
Being a little brother to you.
And everyone else.
I’m not sure we can be friends anymore, Mouth.
Me neither.
It’s too hard.
I thought I knew you.
But I guess it’s easier…
to see what we want,
than to look for the truth.
You think you know me but you don’t;
and that means you don’t know what I can do.
You see me as someone who’s popular… and has all the answers;
that’s not true.
I know what it’s like to search for something more, Haley.
That’s why I’m always running.
But then, I’ve never had a Nathan to come home to.
I may not always know what I’m doing…
but I’ll try make things better.
It’s for you. Come on.
Don’t say I never gave you anything.
And when I make a mistake… because face it,
we all do…
He left.
And I don’t know what to do.
I promise I’ll ask for your help.
Haley?
I’m sorry Nathan… she’s gone.
I can’t do this alone…
But if you’ll take a chance on me, we can do great things together.
I promise, if you believe in me, I’ll find the courage to reach for your every dream.
'Living with HCM'
You got everything you need?
Yeah.
Listen…
thank you for paying for my medication.
I don’t want my mom to know, so…
I need you to keep funding the bill.
Sure… it’ll stay our secret.
But tell me something.
How did you convince her that you didn’t have HCM?
I used Keith’s… negative results letter.
Really?
I wouldn’t have pegged you as being so… duplicitous.
Well I guess I’m your son after all.
John F. Kennedy said the courage of life is a magnificent mixture triumph…
and tragedy.
A man does what he must, in spite of personal consequences…
in spite of obstacles and dangers and pressures…
And that is the basis of all morality.
Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net