Previously on One Tree Hill.
I wanna move in with Dan.
Over my dead body!
What does Dan have over you?
How did you convince her that you didn’t have HCM?
I used Keith’s negative results letter.
She left to be with Chris.
She kissed him, before she left.
My investigator found something interesting about Dan.
Let’s just… go slow.
Okay?
Okay.
You know there’s a girl you had feelings for.
- Nathan...
- Look me in the eye.
Tell me I’m wrong.
You need to talk to her, Luke.
I’ve decided to tell Keith the truth.
Maybe you won’t have to.
I think I’ll just let this one go.
Keith doesn’t ever have to know.
Kahlil Gibran once wrote:
You’re reason and your passion are the rudder…
and the sails of your seafaring soul.
If either be broken,
you can but toss and drift, or else be held at a standstill in mid-seas.
For reason, ruling alone, is a force confining;
and passion, unattended,
is a flame that burn to it’s own destruction.
Hey!
You’re a… little early… and underdressed.
Yeah well, you know, I’m just… making sure everything’s okay.
Anything I can help you with?
No, no.
You’ve done enough.
Everything is perfect.
I’m getting married today.
Didn’t know rock stars were such early risers.
We just finished rehearsing all night.
Yeah.
Don’t let me stop you from falling into bed with Chris.
It’s not like that and you know it.
I don’t know anything, anymore.
You know, I was just calling to tell you that we’re gonna be on TV.
We’re doing this live interview and I was hoping you’d watch.
That’s why you called?
Nathan, none of this means anything if I can’t share it with you.
Keith’s wedding’s today.
He’s getting married?
Yeah.
It won’t last.
What can I say to make things better because I really want to. You know?
You can’t.
See...
it’s a part you have to live with.
That was a word!
That was definitely a word.
In what, Swahili?
She said ‘dada’!
My baby’s a genius.
Okay, major news; Brooke Davis is officially twenty-four hours away
from being student council president and rich again!
What, you and Felix getting married, too?
Please! My dad has this final job interview with this giganto company today;
they’re taking him to play golf…
and while my dad may not be the brightest tool
in… the wherever they keep tools,
he can play golf like freaking Michael Jordan!
Okay…
And hello, Mrs Jagielski, you two are totally in bed together!
Brooke!
This is great, I am gonna go… and do…
almost rich girl things and you are going to call me later with the details.
She’s saying ‘dada’!
Just leave the caviar.
I’ve acquired a taste for it.
You know, there’s gonna be free food at Keith’s wedding today.
No thank you. I’m not going to that.
You really gonna do that to Keith?
Look who’s talking.
I can’t believe you’re actually gonna let them go through with it.
He loves her… and she loves him.
She just made a mistake.
You gonna crucify her for the rest of her life?
Haley called this morning.
That’s great.
Yeah, to tell me she’s gonna be on TV today.
You believe that?
It’s still awesome for her, man.
Yeah, whatever.
Look, Nate, I think you should come to the wedding, man.
A lot of people miss you.
Nathan! I’m so glad you’re here.
Um… let me make you some eggs?
I think you’re out.
It’s so good to see you.
Sorry.
Great day for a wedding.
What do you want?
Bought you a present.
Something blue, right?
I’m not taking it!
Come on, it’s your final payment.
- You said we were done.
- And we are.
Just wanted to say ‘welcome to the family’.
So easy for you, isn’t it?
Dan Scott; king of the world.
But someday, somebody’s gonna bring you down
and I’m gonna watch.
Don’t hold your breath, sweetheart.
Did you talk to your investigator?
I did.
Anything I can use to get Lucas back?
Yeah.
Have you ever heard of Emily Chambers?
No, why?
I think Dan’s having an affair.
Emily Chambers? I’ve never even heard of her.
Well, Dan sure has. He’s paying her rent,
her bills; personal cheque.
Well, why am I even surprised?
Poor Deb!
Karen, I know you care for Deb but… Dan’s not fighting fair here.
If we wanna get Lucas back, we have to beat him at his own game.
My guy’s working on a photo; we should find Emily first.
Little liquid courage for the groom?
Hello, Nathan.
It’s not too late to stop him, you know?
Tell him what kind of hell he’s really in for…
like someone should have done for me.
You’re getting pretty good at the moody, broody bit, aren’t you?
Plan to give Lucas a run for his money?
Whatever! Let’s have it.
And what’s that?
The inspirational story.
Isn’t this the part where you tell me everything’s gonna be okay?
I’m sorry; the pity store’s closed today.
Besides, I’m not sure you’re worth it anymore.
Great!
Look son, you took a big risk and I admire you for that,
but it’s easy to be happy when things are going well.
Marriage is about making it through,
staying together even when things turn to crap.
Looks like I got my story anyway.
Will you grow the hell up?!
You might not like Haley very much right now,
but she’s still your wife and where I come from, that still means something,
whether like it or not!
There’s your story.
By the way, his ID’s fake.
Knock knock!!
Jeez!
Crazy girl, what are you doing to my heart?
Good thing you don’t have that genetic defect!
Yeah.
What’re you doing here?
Well, I just came by to let you know that my safe ride’s program;
‘DW not I’, is officially up and running so pass the word at the reception.
You know, drunk and bitter bridesmaids and…
Deb.
Yeah.
It’s a shame I’m… not gonna be there myself.
To let everyone know…
about the program.
What?
I don’t know;
big… romantic ceremony…
followed by a big fancy party.
Wow!
Oh… I know.
And then there’s the flowers and the dresses and the vows!
Not to mention my best man speech.
Come on, you’re killing me. You know I’m a sucker for weddings!
Any chance you could use a date, in a just friends sorta way to pal around with?
What about Felix?
Grounded; his parents found out the ‘Bash for Brooke’…
and besides, we said we were gonna try to be friends.
Yeah, we did.
Please.
Please, Lucas! Please, please, please, I wanna go so bad!
- Okay.
- Yay!
It’s a date.
Kinda - sorta - not really.
Yeah, whatever, I’m in.
Just… pick me up early.
Hello, hottie!
Oh… yeah, well,
this one wasn’t my mom’s, so…
Yeah, well… neither was this one!
Whoa!
I know, I kinda Anne Frank’d a couple things in the attic before the yard sale.
So you’re going to the wedding?
With… Lucas.
Just as friends.
Really?
Come on, love triangles are so last season.
So, I mean, Felix is totally cool with it, right?
I actually haven’t, um… told him yet.
Brooke!
I know, it’s just, I’ve never just been friends with a guy before except Mouth and…
that’s different.
Well how’s it going?
Good! Felix is my boyfriend, Lucas and I are just friends.
I promise.
But I love you for looking out for me.
Okay.
On the subject of boys;
how are things going with Jake?
You know, still taking it slow.
Oh, slow’s good,
fast is better!
Shut up!
Lucas, hi.
Hey.
You better get dressed.
Yeah, I know.
I know Nathan was kind of abrupt this morning…
just wanted to make sure you were okay.
I’m fine.
Deb…
after my accident…
the doctors prescribed me some… really powerful painkillers
except for they gave them to my mom…
because they knew how easy it would be for me…
or anyone for that matter to become addicted.
Have you been spying on me?
- I was just...
- You are a guest in my house, Lucas…
and as long as you’re living under my roof,
I would appreciate you not snooping around in my life!
Deb, I’m just trying to help.
Oh, go-yeah, that’s just what I need; an adolescent boy to solve all my problems.
Deb!
Get the hell outta here, Lucas.
You are way outta line,
and way out of your league!
So you, uh, still think this looks weird?
And it feels pretty good, too.
I love you.
Oh god, that… that kinda came out, didn’t it?
Not that I… not that I don’t mean it, coz…
I’ve been dying to say that for a-for a while now, it just,
it just never seems like the right time.
You know, what with Lucas being thrown into jail
and me getting a private investigator, it’s just…
well...
I love you.
I love your mind, I love your heart,
I love picturing our future together.
I mean, I hate the thought of you…
ever not being in my life.
- Andy...
- And, I don’t want you to say anything.
You… know, I just…
I just had to get that out.
I love you too.
I was hoping you’d say that!
- Peyton!
- I’m so sorry, I’m not ready yet.
Just give me two seconds. I’m being a total girl.
That’s okay, we got time.
Wow!
‘Total girl’ is right!
It’s a, uh…
good thing that we’re taking it slow, right?
Yeah.
Slow.
- Hi.
You know you look amazing, right?
Thanks.
How’re you feeling?
Happy.
Yeah, me too.
Man, we’re gonna be late.
Weddings always start a little bit late anyway, right?
At least half an hour.
Works for me.
Oh, it’s beautiful!
Thank you for bringing me, Lucas.
You’re welcome.
So… how are things with Felix?
Good! Great!
Yeah?
Yeah. He helped me with my campaign and…
threw me a party.
So you guys are good.
I don’t know.
He’s been… so sweet.
Really, but…
lately, I just kinda find myself feeling…
independent!
Amazingly.
I don’t even know if I want a boyfriend right now!
I guess we’re both…
finding a new way…
for ourselves, huh?
I guess so.
Okay, listen up,
you go out, they’ll ask you a couple of questions.
Now keep it positive. You’re thrilled to be on TV.
It’s all about living the dream.
- Absolutely.
Oh, take off the wedding ring.
What!?
It’s a love song, Haley.
Look, you and Chris, I mean, look, you sound like a couple,
you look like a couple, let them think you’re a couple.
But we’re not a couple!
Details.
Yeah, come on, Haley.
Alright, look…
the girls should wanna be you and the guys should wanna be with you,
alright, the wedding ring kinda gets in the way of it all.
For some people.
Okay, well, you guys can figure it out but…
trust me, I’d lose the ring.
- I’m leaving right now!
- Listen, I’m not...
I can not believe you’re asking me to do this!
Haley, this is our shot! Nothing else matters.
Nathan matters!
Then what are you doing here?
Listen, you made a decision. Don’t blink now!
Alright, I’m Nick Zano and this is Totally Live Week.
That was Chariot, the new one from Gavin DeGraw
who’s on tour right now with The Wreakers,
otherwise known as Michelle Branch and Jessica Harp.
Also on that tour are two newcomers who’s single,
When the Stars Go Blue drops next Tuesday,
we’re here live with Chris Keller and Haley James.
Haley James-Scott.
Uh-oh, three name roll.
Girls with three names are always trouble.
Ah, this one’s no different.
Oh, okay. Now, you guys have great chemistry;
obviously a great sound, now tell the truth,
you a couple in real life?
- Um, actually...
- You know, the music never lies.
Say no more! You heard it here first.
Alright, let’s take another look at those tour dates and we’ll be back, right after this.
Same colour as that shirt. You know where you’re sitting, right?
See you inside.
- Can I get one of you two?
- Absolutely.
Well, well, well, my son cleans up good.
Thank you.
How are you, Deb?
Great!
The place is beautiful.
I think we’re gonna head inside.
Save a slow dance for me Miss. Davis.
Okay!
You old perv!
I’m sorry.
It’s okay. I get worse than that from drunk high school boys every Saturday night.
Yeah, but it’s worse when it’s not drunken high school boys but your dad!
I’ve never heard you call him that before.
I’m trying it out. See how it sounds.
And? What do you think?
Okay, it’s freezing in here.
Yeah, that’s probably by design; Keith’s kind of a sweater,
especially when he’s nervous.
Okay, things I never needed to know.
Sorry.
Look, here you go.
Thank you.
So look, I have to go see Keith, you know, start being the best man.
You gonna be okay?
Well, can your ego handle it if I tell you I just needed someone to get me in the door?
Not really.
Then, boy, I am gonna miss you.
Yeah.
Old habits die hard, huh?
It’s-it’s just water, smart ass.
Yeah.
It’s just so damn hot in there.
You’re gonna be fine.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
But, uh, I’m still glad you’re here though.
Even if you are still living with the Devil.
Hey, listen, I don’t-I don’t wanna get mushy but, um,
I just wanna say thanks.
For what?
Just… for being you, and for being my best man.
You really are it, you know?
And I’m real proud of the man you’re turning out to be.
Nah, who do you think I learned it from?
Um, just… give me a second, huh?
Yeah, I’ll be inside.
You look amazing.
Thanks.
So do you… as always.
It’s good to see you so happy.
Jules is great.
Yeah, she is.
It’s like I finally found my place in the world and it was...
it was right here all along.
I’m glad.
Come here.
Also, I really appreciate you and Deb standing up for Jules, you know?
She really doesn’t have anybody else.
Of course.
Thank you…
and, um, now I’ve got some vows to go make.
Yes you do!
- I’ll see you up there.
- Okay.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. I just gotta go pick something up real quick.
Right now?
Yeah, I’ll be right back, trust me.
I wouldn’t miss seeing you walk down that aisle.
Don’t look at me.
Have you been crying?
Just tearing up a little.
I read your speech.
Brooke!
Don’t leave your journal where I can find that, either.
It was beautiful.
‘Remember tonight for it is the beginning of always’.
That’s Dante.
We read him last semester.
And I need to pay more attention in English.
The rest is me.
The part about taking chances and believing in the possibility,
even when life has given you every reason not to believe…
That’s what’s so great about weddings;
you know, two people come together…
and even if it’s just for one night,
they make us believe again.
Stop! I don’t have anymore tissues!
Here.
I just hope at my wedding, someone says something that nice about me.
I think you can count on that.
Oh my god!
You guys totally did it!
Um… Uh, Brooke, we’re – we’re in a church!
So?! If I can tell, so can He!
Black tie;
I haven’t worn one of these things since Dick Nixon was in office.
Look what happened to him.
Well, I, um, I appreciate the effort.
I feel like a penguin!
Where’re your folks?
Oh, um… they’re on safari, believe it or not.
Dad’s off, uh, killing big animals or something.
What has happened to the world for god’s sake; their son’s getting married!
Yeah well, you know, they offered to cancel but I knew Royal would just pout about it the whole time
so I - I just told them to come on down next month and meet Jules.
So, for right now, you’re all I got.
Lord help you if that’s true.
Maybe you’d like a little boost from Mr J.D.
Um… actually I think I’m gonna do this one sober.
True love! That’s a good one.
Don’t… do it, Keith! Just get out while you can! It’s all a lie!
There’s no such thing as forever!
What the hell are you doing?!
This is a church for god’s sake!
Oh, shut your hole you freaking hypocrite!
I know what you did.
Nathan, it’s okay. Let us help you.
Do what?
Be happy again.
Happy? You don’t even know how to be happy, mom.
Haley and I never stood a chance with you.
Is that what you think?
You, you hire Chris too? Huh?
Don’t make me knock you out, son.
Screw you, you sick son of a bitch!
Hey, come on! Come on. Hey! Hey!
Don’t do this to Keith. Not here.
You alright?
Come on.
Nate...
What’re you doing, man?
She said she was with Chris…
on national TV.
I don’t believe it.
Neither did I.
It’s really over, huh?
Only if you say it is.
I’m hurting, Luke.
It’s gonna be okay.
No, I mean I think I’m gonna puke!
Hey...
‘DW not I’ at your service!
Okay, watch your head.
Okay, this is perfect; and I don’t mean what happened today,
just for ‘DW not I’, it’s so great that Nathan got smashed!
Just make sure he gets inside, okay?
Thanks.
- Oh, thank god you’re back!
- Yeah, we have a problem.
I know, Nathan’s a mess and we have to start...
I’ve found Emily Chambers.
What!?
Emily Chambers is Jules.
You all set?
Yeah, just gotta get my veil.
Sure, let me help you with that...
Emily.
Did Lucas tell you?
He knows that you’re having an affair with Dan?!
I’m not having an affair with Dan.
Oh, really?
Then tell me, why would Dan put you up in an apartment and pay all your bills…
and seemingly control every detail of your life unless…?
Oh my god!
It’s Keith. He’s paying you to get back at Keith!
He was.
You’re a whore!
No. I was in trouble.
The wedding was never part of the plan. It changed.
I told Dan I wanted out.
I fell in love with Keith for real.
How could you do that to Keith?
After everything that he has been through!
You mean after everything you’ve put him through?
How dare you!
How dare you.
You didn’t want him.
Now that he’s actually found someone who loves him back…
you wanna take that away from him, too?
I want him to know…
who you really are.
Moment of truth!
He’s happy, Karen.
Can’t you just let him be happy?
Was it awesome? Just give me a hint.
Brooke!
I know we’re in a church.
So blink once if it was good and twice if it was better than that.
Ooo, my god, I love weddings!
- You okay?
- I don’t know.
What’d she say?
It’s not Dan.
She loves Keith.
And you believe her?
I think I have to.
That’s our cue, gotta go.
Your mom looks beautiful.
I’m sorry.
She left.
- Give me your keys!
- Keith...
Just give me your keys!
Keith!
You said you were done!
That you’d leave them alone.
I didn’t do anything.
I promise you Lucas; I wouldn’t jeopardise my relationship with you again.
You – sick – bastard!
I threatened to tell Keith.
I found out about your arrangement and I went to Jules.
And I threatened to tell the truth.
Nice work, Cupid.
This one’s on you.
Remember tonight,
for it is the beginning of always.
A promise.
Like a reward for persisting through life so long alone.
Jules?!
The belief in each other and the possibility of love.
A decision...
to ignore or simply rise above the pain of the past.
The covenant,
which at once binds two souls and yet severs prior ties.
What have we done?
Karen...
I’m sorry...
I need to see Keith.
The celebration...
of the chance taken, and the challenge that lies ahead.
One down…
…one to go.
- For two will always be stronger than one.
- Hey, baby.
Like a team, braced against the tempest’s of the world.
Can you say ‘dada’?
- Can you say dada?
- Hey, Jenny, who’s that?
- Can you say ‘dada’?
- Who’s that?!
Mama.
Nikki!
And love… will always be the guiding force in our lives.
What’re you doing here?
Making sure you find the kind of happiness…
I can barely remember.
Go get Haley.
She’s your wife.
For tonight is mere formality…
only an announcement to the world for feelings long held.
Promises made long ago in the sacred space of our hearts.
What, more bad news?
My dad got that job.
Brooke, that’s great!
It’s in California!
We’re moving next week.
I don’t wanna go.
What’re we gonna do?
Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net