Previously on "Veronica Mars"...
Hi. Do you remember me, by any chance?
- Harmony, right?
- Right.
What's your problem?
Just that I'm officially
failing mechanical engineering.
Call this number.
It's a tutor.
They raped Claire...
"The blonde in the middle"
I have the ATM photo from that night.
The guy who did this to me?
I have no idea of who this is.
- Is Wang Yi here?
- Why?
Because he raped this girl.
Claire? I doubt it.
She's Wang's girlfriend.
Dean O'Dell, give me a chance to explain.
I don't care what kind of point
you're trying to make.
Fake a rape, then bring in your lawyer?
What universe do you live in?
Have you gone completely insane?
So, is this what you wanted?
You think this is what I wanted.
Angela, get them in here.
If you examine it closely,
dean O'Dell, the facts are still...
The facts are miss Mars' story here,
and she has the notes and evidence
to back it up, I believe.
We have photos. We have witnesses.
We have the boyfriend who helped.
There's no question Claire
lied about the rape,
and the Hearst charter's
quite clear about this.
You want to challenge
the charter, that's fine.
We have lawyers, too,
and they're a lot scarier
than you, Mr. Davis.
Miss Nordhouse,
you're expelled from Hearst college
as of this moment,
and so is your lawyer.
That's all.
Happy?
Madam editor,
why didn't I read this story
in the Hearst paper?
I found the facts fairly
simple to corroborate.
I felt I had a responsibility
to exercise some caution
with a story implying the rapes
might have been faked.
In case you haven't noticed,
it's a powder keg out there.
I noticed, but I didn't see much caution
when you implicated the pi sigma house.
You're supposed to at least
pretend to be objective.
I'm afraid I'm gonna need you to step down
as editor of the Free Press.
It's a student paper. You can't.
I'm a devious old man, Nish.
You'd be surprised what I can do.
You're done there as of this moment.
You'll regret this.
And so will you.
David, sorry for the wait.
It's been a hell of a week. Come on in.
Mr. Fennel?
This is hardly the first time
we've caught an athlete cheating.
With Mr. Fennel,
I'll take some of the blame.
We usually don't take
athletes in the program.
It's just too demanding,
Especially with standardized test
scores as low as his.
If I'd paid closer attention to...
Oh! I'm sorry.
Pardon us. My important lunch.
There better be a cookie in there.
Oh, of course there isn't.
Why do you punish me like this?
Because I'm your wife.
That's what I'm for, remember?
Be merciful.
She probably ate the damn cookie herself.
So, what do you have to say?
I'm with her on the mercy thing.
The whole of human knowledge
right there online,
and these papers are thin.
Am I crazy to expect better?
And if you're confused as to what better is,
let me direct you to the front,
where I've posted our
only example of A-caliber work.
Nice job, Ms. Mars.
Well, this should make me popular.
All righty, that's all for today.
We'll see you next time.
Don't forget, read both chapters... Both.
Professor, I have the Columbia studies.
Maybe we can...
Just make copies for tomorrow, Tim.
Veronica...
you free for lunch?
Databases, chemistry, psychology...
that's where the action is.
Are you taking any psych?
Take Wagner's class. He's the best.
If you want a double major...
Double? I haven't even
declared one major yet.
Consider this a sales talk.
I not only think of you
as a very bright woman in general,
I also think that you're a natural
when it comes to criminal work.
I'm not saying this
to be nice or supportive.
I'm saying it because it's true
and because I want
someone like you in my program.
I think I should be your faculty advisor.
I think you're capable
of great work here, Veronica,
and I'd like to help you do it.
End of sales talk.
He sounds like a hell of a guy.
Not only is he smart,
but he's the biggest gun
in the department, so
him offering to be my advisor...
Yeah, I'm not surprised.
But I wish you would consult with me
before you start phasing
me out of your life.
Dad...
He's smart, huh?
Is he smarter than your old man?
You know, actually,
you two have a lot in common.
You'd like him.
Can I take him in a fight? Be honest.
Hello.
Keith, hi, it's Harmony.
Hi. Uh, is everything okay?
Oh, fine, fine, actually.
I know that our
professional relationship is over,
but I enjoyed, you know, talking.
Uh, yeah, me too.
So, my husband has taken our daughter
to Orlando for a couple of weeks.
I've got passes to the noir festival
at the orient and no one to go with.
And I was thinking,
you're a guy with an interest in...
In... noir business?
Right.
And maybe you might want to,
you know, join me,
just grab a movie.
Keith?
I got a text message saying
you wanted to see me.
I think it was "needed",
not "wanted".
Ah, how did you get this number?
I don't give it out to anyone.
You're not the only one at this school
who has certain... gifts.
Gifts... That was my grandmother's term
for female...
just so you know.
What did you need to see me about?
You know, Hearst has a pretty strict
policy when it comes to plagiarism.
Yes. Did someone plagiarize?
You did.
One of your classmates turned you in.
There's a program we run to check papers.
It scans online for similar phrases.
I know how it works, but I...
Your paper lit up like a Christmas tree.
What?! I didn't copy my paper.
So I assumed, but...
well, that's your paper there.
There's no way. Someone is trying
to screw with me.
You think it's me?
You think I'm trying to get you
out of Landry's class
because I don't like you?
Wait, you don't like me?
This will have to come
to Landry's attention.
It's a bummer, since I know
that you and he are now close.
- So, how about I give you a choice?
- Choice?
Either you can tell him or I can.
Tell who what?
Hi, Infidelity
Hey, pal.
Can you believe this?
Some lady threw her husband
out of the house.
Right now she's having
a garage sale of all of his stuff.
"London calling"... Vinyl...
Unscratched... 99 cents.
Awesome, right?
My would-be-mentor professor
just gave me three days
to prove I didn't plagiarize a major paper.
The universe is currently
aligned against me, so
nothing's awesome.
You know what?
You should come bowling.
Bowling?
You mean, like, just the two of us?
Yeah.
And Wallace... You know, the whole gang.
Thursday nights are $1 night at fun bowl.
Will bowling take my mind off of the fact
that everyone's out to get me?
It worked for Nixon.
It'll be fun.
Dude, I don't get this sad-clown face.
I thought he let you drop the class.
I haven't decided if I'm gonna.
What's to decide?
Two weeks after add/drops, he lets you
drop a class that's kicking your ass.
That's a gift. Take it and smile.
Okay, okay, 5-On-5 scrimmage.
Let's go. Move.
Fennel, you run first team today.
Wait, coach...
You want to keep your starting job, Mason?
Start showing me something.
Let's go!
Apparently, if you look hard enough,
everyone looks like
they're hiding dark secrets.
So, if you're looking for
something specific,
you got to try the direct approach.
Hi, some of you might know
who I am... Veronica Mars.
Okay, so, I wrote that paper,
and now someone in this class
has accused me of plagiarizing it,
which I absolutely did not.
So, I was kind of wondering who it was.
So, is this silence like
it wasn't any of you
or like no one wants to face me?
Or like no one actually did it
and our weaselly T.A. is trying to...
I did it. Jeff Ratner.
Ratner. Um, have we met before?
We have, but you probably
don't remember, so whatever.
- So, you reported me. Why...
- Why?
Maybe 'cause I'm a common-man kind of guy,
and I like it when some teacher's pet
who's destroying the curve for everyone
gets exposed as a cheat.
Yeah, you cheated. I caught you.
Deal with it.
Wallace?
Not here.
And you would be?
Evil Wallace.
And I know Veronica Mars doesn't hang
with the evil and morally bankrupt.
Evil Wallace wouldn't have
confessed and faced punishment.
Nope, you're regular Wallace.
Well, regular Wallace
has been given a chance
to drop mechanical engineering scot-free,
which would mean giving it up as my major.
I mean, man.
This was the first thing I was ever into...
Figuring out how stuff works.
It's all I ever wanted to do.
You'll work it out. I know it.
That's also very regular Wallace.
Oh, by the way, who's the guy
you bought the test from?
So, this whole after-school-special
monologue here
didn't make much of an impression on you.
His name's Max. He's in Clark hall.
Why?
Hi, Max? I was hoping you could help me.
Well, I'm hoping I can, too.
Okay, so, you want a new paper
on modern forensics
but different enough
so that he won't guess who...
No. This paper or
one like it is posted online.
I need to find it.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but you already have that paper.
I told you, my paper got zapped
by the plagiarism scanner.
I need to find out why and from what.
Okay, whatever.
Uh...
hmm...
ah, here you go.
That's my paper.
See, that's why I never
use these free sites...
No security.
Checkers will catch you every time.
Posted last year?
Somebody must have faked that.
I wrote this paper by myself last week.
This must be a real Kafkaesque
experience for you.
Does it say who posted it?
Uh...
rory.finch@hearstcollege.org
That's not you, is it?
That might explain everything.
And pencils down.
Bring them up.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
I'm sorry.
What about?
I called time, and you kept writing.
I can't accept your test.
Yeah, I was just finishing my...
Time was called. I'm sorry.
So you keep saying, dude. Come on.
Do you have any idea who I am?
I don't, and I don't care.
Rules are rules for everyone,
no matter who they think...
That is classic.
It was a proctor.
The professor wasn't even there.
That is so awesome.
But I do not condone it in any way
and had nothing to do
with your decision to do it.
- Do what?
- Cheating.
I told him it was wrong and
he was gonna burn in hell.
You're gonna burn in hell, man.
I'll see you there.
You cheated?
I took 10 extra seconds on a test.
I thought you loved bad boys.
I do, but if that's your idea of bad,
you need to turn in your badge.
Hey, do you want
to go bowling tomorrow night?
Sure, unless it's some
"critical analysis of bowling" seminar.
No, it's just Wallace and his roommate
And some other guys.
Could be fun.
What?
Just Mac's had this project all week,
and Parker's all alone.
I think we should invite her along.
How very "Emma" of you.
Did you just make a Jane Austen reference?
It's official. The end of days are upon us.
Hey, Parker, what's up?
Nothing.
I think I just ate something's beak.
Hey, do you want to come bowling
with us tomorrow night?
Bowling?
Why?
You know, hatchet burying, et cetera.
Plus, Nixon found it soothing.
Look, if you don't want to go
because you'd rather
see me fed to bears, fine.
So, would you call that
an accurate depiction
of life as a private eye?
Pretty close.
I personally have never been hired
to locate a Maltese Falcon, per se,
but there was the case of the maltese dog.
Ooh. Solid-gold dog?
Real dog.
This guy got some lowlife
to kidnap his ex-wife's show dog.
Not exactly how I imagined
the criminal underworld.
If they were all like Peter Lorre, my
job would be a little more interesting.
Thanks, Keith, for coming.
These days my husband
and I are just logistics.
I can't remember the last time
I just hung out and talked.
Sure, it's great talking to someone
for whom "Bogart" isn't a verb.
Well, good night.
The upside of landing Weevil
the maintenance job...
I get to babysit his keys while
he's away at his cousin's wedding.
So if I want to check
the Hearst e-mail files for Rory Finch,
I can do it on my own time.
Of course, he didn't bother
to label them, so...
Veronica?
Dean O'Dell, I'm so glad you're here.
I lost an earring, um, at the meeting,
And I wanted to find it
before they vacuumed.
But it was...
Well, it's a good thing
you happened to show up.
Well, go ahead. Search away.
McCall is starting to go straight back...
You follow boxing?
I only follow sports that are done to music.
Wouldn't this be more comfortable,
say, at home?
Kind of my little secret.
The wife's against it all...
The scotch, the cigars,
the televised violence.
So, I kind of sneak it in
whenever she has a charity function,
a work function, whatever other functions
modern women seem to have all the time.
That's a haymaker.
So, if you run into her, you didn't see me.
Some things she just doesn't need to know.
Absolutely.
Now, I expect these formulas
to be memorized as soon as possible.
Mr. Fennel, I was under
the impression you dropped the class.
I said I'd think about it.
You sure this is a smart choice?
Probably not, but you've seen
my standardized test scores.
I'm not a particularly smart guy, right?
I'm taking a zero.
There are four more tests.
If I average C's or above
on all of them, I'll pass.
Even I can do that math.
Okay, there you go.
You're gonna ruin your eyes
with all that book learning.
I stayed in Winkler's class.
I took the zero.
I need to study.
I suspected that might happen.
So, you figure out what was up
with that plagiarism thing?
As a matter of fact, a paper
just like mine was posted online
by rory.finch@hearstcollege.org...
A Hearst e-Mail,
But there's never been
a student by that name.
The address was set up three days ago
from an I.P. Address at...
get this... the Neptune Grand.
After you turned in your paper.
So, you're off the hook. It's over.
Ah, my innocent and naive Wallace.
When I find out who did this
and I make them sing like
the proverbial fat lady,
that's when it's over.
Okay, you're Rocky.
Mechanical engineering is Mr. T.
"Eye of the tiger" is playing.
I'll see you later on.
Yeah.
What?
When?
Boom. I'm set.
Are you ready for a night of bowling, huh?
Fun, fun, fun.
Fun? I'm pretty sure
I won't ever be having fun again.
Ah, damn, that's tonight.
I'm sorry, man, but it's impossible.
No, dude, you have to go.
I invited Veronica.
I said there's a whole gang going,
including you.
So, if you're not there...
It's gonna look like you asked her out.
Yeah, that sounds awkward.
But it's not my problem. This is.
Hey, dad.
Hey, honey.
So, tomorrow's "Out of the Past".
It's one of my all-time favorites.
I've got a conference at the Neptune grand.
I don't think I'm gonna be free, but
I'd like to do something else.
Okay, well, keep me posted.
Bye.
So, for bowling,
"earnest, I'm really bowling"
or "I'm too cool for bowling,
and I'm only here ironically"?
When did crappy old shirts
with stupid stuff on them become cool?
I don't know why I ask you these things.
I don't either, frankly.
Were you just making a date?
Look at you, Mr. Noir secrets.
No, I was just seeing
if Harmony wanted to see...
Harmony?
Harmony with the husband
who isn't cheating, Harmony?
Yeah, so?
So, you're going on a date
with a married woman.
It's not a date.
We saw a movie, had a drink, and talked.
Which is a date.
That's all we did.
We're mature adults
who happen to be friends.
And I like the dumb shirt.
Hi, honey, I'm home.
Hey, moosetastic, hmm? What's that?
I'm so tired of explaining.
Hey, you've lived here a while.
Do you have any inside connections?
Inside connections like what?
Like someone on staff you're pals with
who might sneak you info
they maybe aren't supposed to?
There you go.
Your pal? Of course.
Hi, Tina. This is Veronica.
Veronica...
Hi. What's going on, Logan?
I got a little favor.
Anything.
I'm trying to find out
if a person was registered here...
- Someone named...
- Rory Finch.
This isn't illegal, is it?
No, I'm just kidding. Hold on.
Yeah, Rory Finch.
She stayed with us for a night a week ago
and a few other times
over the last couple of months.
Always one-night stays.
Is there an address, credit-card number?
Post-Office box and paid in cash.
All I've got's a name.
If I left my cell number, could you
call me if they check back in?
Sure.
Any friend of Logan's...
Girlfriend of Logan's.
Come on, boyfriend, let's bowl.
Hey, Veronica.
Cool shirt. I went the post-ironic route.
Hey, Piz. Where's...
Oh, hey, uh...
Logan... Her boyfriend. We met.
So, where's Wallace
and the rest of this gang?
Right, yeah, the gang.
Well, Wallace had a crisis
so he can't make it, and, um...
So, it's just...
Veronica. Hi.
Hey, Parker, how's it going?
- You met Logan, right?
- Yeah, hi, sure.
- And you remember Piz.
- Yeah, hi.
So, um, where is everyone?
Hey, shoes. We need shoes.
Yeah, let's get shoes.
Darling, what size are those dainty feet
that I love so much?
Six.
So, bowling, huh?
Is this something you do a lot...
You and the gang?
- So, shoe size?
- A whole gang?
Well, Parker...
some people couldn't make it, but it's...
I can't believe you invite me out
For the first time since I was raped
on some cheesy double-date
setup with that Piz guy.
It's not a setup, I swear.
Size seven, but this is not fun.
Yahoo! That's 2/3 of a turkey, bitches!
Hoo!
Oh, you're in a deep hole,
Piznarski.
We're gonna totally humiliate you.
But you know, no pressure.
Refreshments?
10 martinis.
Anyone else? Dearest darling?
Come on, Piznarski, we're dying!
Correct me if I'm wrong, but this is fun.
Veronica, I'm sorry I was so grumpy before.
You're right.
It feels good to just be out in the world.
Oh, no! 7-10?
That's the worst spare in bowling!
Whatever shall you do?
Come on, Piz. We need that spare.
Don't blow it, Piz.
So, what's the story with him?
Him? Nothing.
I've got a boyfriend.
No. No, no, no, no.
I mean, is he free?
Free as in...
...as in he's cute, don't you think?
That went straight to hell.
- Find out what he thinks of me.
- What?
Oh, no more fun. Too exhausting.
Next time we'll get in some
weight training before we bowl.
Just the soap opera.
Parker wants me to find out
if Piz likes her.
What do I do? Pass a note?
Scribble it on his trapper keeper?
Hey, did you get an "A"?
Yeah, but the cheating kind of
cheapens the whole thing.
You're only cheating yourself.
Yeah, well, I got off easy. You know that...
...kid Horshack from that prison experiment?
He got caught doing two tests.
They busted him.
And guess who else.
That psycho guard that
was tormenting him so bad, Rafe,
yeah, he was taking his test for him.
Can you believe that? People are crazy, huh?
Thank god. Real food.
Good evening, Mr. Echolls.
That voice... I recognize that voice.
Wait.
Have a good evening.
Excuse me.
Jeff Ratner... What a surprise.
You guys know each other?
You want to tell him, Ratner?
What's to tell?
This is the guy who's trying to get me
tossed out of Landry's class.
You should be. You cheated.
Now it turns out you work
at the Neptune Grand,
which happens to be where
the fake paper was posted from.
Strange, huh, Rory Finch?
What are you talking about?
I don't "happen to work here".
I've worked here two years.
You've seen me a hundred times, but
you don't notice the little people
'cause you're too busy lounging
with captain moneybags here.
That's admiral moneybags.
- I trust our steak's to your liking?
- Always.
Good night, then.
That's my girl, spreading sunshine
wherever she goes.
That boy doesn't know it yet,
but he's the living dead.
Dude!
Hey, look, man, it's school policy
that if you're dead,
I get to keep your stuff, so
if you are dead, just don't say anything.
Well, that's disappointing.
Oh, crap.
Hey, I could have just left you there
and taken your iPod, so...
you're welcome.
Big shot!
On the left!
Coach.
I'm sorry. I missed my alarm.
Come here.
If it ain't Sleeping Beauty.
Play the game, Mason.
You have a chance to start
this year as a freshman.
Don't blow it by staying up
all night partying.
You need to buckle down, Fennel.
- Now, go suit up.
- Okay.
Take a big shot!
Eight years ago,
I was sent to ask Brad Stark
if he liked Suzy Doyle.
The two of them never spoke again.
In the intervening years,
I haven't gotten any better at this.
We'll talk later, all right? Bye.
Hey, Veronica.
Hey, Piz, thanks for bowling
the other night. That was fun.
Good. Yeah, great.
Did Logan have a good time?
He did, as well. We both did.
So, everyone had a good time.
I declare bowling a success.
And Parker had a good time, too.
Oh, yeah, good. She seems nice.
You think so? The reason I ask is because...
I'm sorry. I'm having a traumatic-stress
flashback to the sixth grade.
Parker thought you were cool...
...and also cute.
Oh.
Well...
oh.
Oh, what?
No, she's really nice,
but she's not really my type.
Oh, you have a type.
Yeah, kind of.
And it's not her.
Okay, so, remember,
this was just a practice quiz,
but all this material
will be on your next exam.
Mr. Fennel... 67... "D" plus.
That's a real improvement.
Hey, Veronica, guess what I just found out.
Piz has a radio show.
- I know.
- Tonight.
You know,
the station's right in student union.
- Let's drop by.
- It'll be late.
Oh, late schmate. It'll be fun.
Everybody's always saying that.
Join us next time when we ask,
"why does everyone hate America?
Is the rest of the world crazy
or just stupid?"
Well, that's it for the Piz.
Stick around for Club Flush.
This is so cool!
Why didn't you say you had a radio show?
You know, I meant to mention it,
but I guess it just slipped my mind.
We were just in the neighborhood.
I always wanted to know how it all works.
Maybe you could show me
what all this stuff is sometime.
The guy who does the club and house
show is supposed to start now, so...
What's everyone doing after?
I could totally use Pizza.
You can have this.
I only licked it a little.
Hey, Veronica.
Hey, Mercer. You're the club and house show?
The down-and-dirty clubbin'-est.
Hi, I'm Mercer.
Hi.
Well, I haven't eaten dinner,
so I could grab a slice.
Actually, we got to go.
We'll see you later, Piz.
Nice meeting you, Parker.
Parker, are you okay?
That guy Mercer. I just... His cologne.
I smelled it before.
Yeah?
It's, like, burned into my brain...
from the night I was raped.
I mean, I can't be sure, but...
I just got the worst...
Vibe? Yeah.
He'll be in there for the next two hours.
I'll look into it.
Because I've still got
24 hours with Weevil's keys.
You want to know why?
'Cause I'll stick my foot so far up your...
Hey.
Could someone let me know
when some girl is in my office?
What are you doing here?
I'm here about the rapes at Hearst.
Already aware of them.
Thanks for coming by. I'm real busy.
This is sketchy, but...
If it's Bigfoot, we checked.
He's got an alibi.
Oh, rape humor. It never gets old.
I know one of the victims.
Yesterday she thought she recognized
the guy who raped her by his cologne.
And then I just happened to be in his room,
and I saw some clippers.
Does this man have a name?
Mercer Hayes.
The kid who ran the card room
that got robbed.
That's him.
What?
We finally found the stolen cashbox, and...
along with all the money,
we found something interesting...
Two vials of G.H.B...
The same date-rape drug
the rapist used on two of his victims.
Hey, how's my Diaper Dandy?
Here to get some extra work in?
Actually, coach, I got this class
that's killing me.
I could drop it, change majors,
but it's what I want to do for a living.
I think I need to take the semester off.
I'd be back by mid-season.
I know you don't have to keep me
on scholarship.
Keep the scholarship, Wallace.
But you do realize you're
throwing away your chance to start.
You probably won't smell
the court this year.
Are you prepared for that?
I assumed after I called Ratner
on this Rory Finch thing it was over,
until my new friend Tina Callas
told me he just made a new reservation.
You rang?
There you are, miss.
What are you doing here?
Just grabbing a drink. Are you...
2 martinis sir.
What are you doing?
Honey, I told you, it's completely
innocent. We're just friends.
"You think the other person's great
and you have a great time
doing stuff together" friends?
And there's nothing wrong with that.
Unless your friend is a very
attractive, unhappily married woman.
Veronica, I know a little more
about this than you.
Don't worry.
I worry.
Okay, number 906, behind which
lies the answer to everything.
- Veronica Mars?
- Mrs. O'Dell?
I was looking into a term-paper thing.
I'm sorry. Wrong room.
So, now I'm actually confused.
What does the dean's wife have
to do with the mysterious Rory Finch?
Oh.
Veronica.
Professor, hi.
I got off on the wrong floor.
Ah.
Well, nice seeing you.
See you in class.
Rory Finch?
Perfect.
Oh. Oh.
You know what they say about martinis.
Something involving breasts?
One's too few, et cetera.
I'll have to settle for one
if I'm gonna make it home.
We don't have to worry,
I mean, if we don't want to.
What do you mean?
I mean...
well, honestly,
I need to tell you something.
I wouldn't, but all alone at the house,
I've got a lot of time on my hands to think.
And one of the things that I think
is knowing that I don't want to be
lying on my deathbed someday
just counting regrets.
I'm still not sure what you mean.
I mean, I got a room here if...
If we think we might have use for...
Oh, no.
Harmony, I don't know
if that's such a good idea right now.
Oh, no, Keith, I'm sorry. I've ruined...
No, you didn't ruin anything
because I really, really,
really want to say yes.
You are an amazing woman, and I just can't.
I don't want to be on my deathbed
counting regrets either,
but I just can't figure out
which I'd regret more...
Going up or not going up.
So, I have to...
I'm sorry.
Oh, man. I totally didn't see that sign.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I am okay.
I'm okay.
Man, I'll get... I'll get some help.
Dad? This nutritious breakfast
isn't gonna eat itself!
Come on. Up and at 'em.
Dad!
Dad, come on.
Miss Mars! Do you need something?
Just to give you this.
This proves that whoever posted
the paper I supposedly copied online
did so after I had already turned mine in.
I didn't cheat, this proves it,
and that's the end of that.
Great. So, you're off the hook.
Did you prove who did it?
More process of elimination.
But I'm still not sure why,
so I thought I'd ask.
Why did you do it?
Why did you want me
to follow that trail to Rory Finch?
You could get in a lot of trouble, you know,
- If I decided to...
- Let me interrupt
and preface this entire conversation
with this.
I didn't do it,
and you can't prove that I did.
Hypothetically, I can see where
one might think someone in my position
would want to set up
this sort of treasure hunt.
I mean, after all, I was professor
Landry's protg for three years
before you showed up...
His star pupil, right-hand man.
I got his dry cleaning,
ordered Chinese when we worked late.
I was like you.
"What a professor!
He's smart, charming,
such a great guy".
And then you find out he had
an affair with the dean's wife.
There were others before.
The dean's wife... That's recent.
A person in my position might have
thought he was doing you a favor.
Since the professor thinks so highly of you,
It might be helpful to demonstrate
who he really is
before you go too far under his spell.
Do me a favor, will you?
Don't do me any more favors.
What's this?
You have the same kind of
crazy press-clipping board
every movie serial killer keeps.
You know, there's been
no DNA evidence so far...
No semen, no hair.
Makes you wonder.
Huh.
You see something I don't?
Maybe.
You really thought Ratner did it?
Oh, crap.
No, no. I did not put those in there.
Hooke's law and a prismatic rod.
Length "L" and cross-sectional area "A"
we treat as a linear spring,
so extension is linearly proportional to
tensile stress by a constant factor...
The inverse of its modulus of elasticity.
Ah, miss Mars, join me, would you?
Uh, sure, dean.
I just don't want more kids coming
and giving me their ideas
about how to run the school...
My biggest problem as dean.
I don't like college students...
Most of them, anyway.
So, why do you eat here?
This damn burger... I love it.
If you see my wife, don't tell her.
There's some things
she's better off not knowing.
Dean...
just some...
Hey, I need to talk to you.
Sorry, I'll be right back.
- So, what's up?
- I need your help.
- What's wrong?
- It's Mercer.
Lamb just arrested him
for the rapes on campus.
He didn't do it, okay? You have to help.
How do you know he didn't do it?
'Cause I was with him
the night of the rape this summer.
Where? Doing what?
I can't tell you, okay? But you have
to trust me. He's innocent.