[The Ditty Bops: Wake Up]
[Meredith] Remember when you were
a kid, and your biggest worry was,
like, if you'd get a bike
for your birthday
or if you'd get
to eat cookies for breakfast?
Being an adult, totally overrated.
I mean, seriously, don't be fooled
by all the hot shoes and the great sex
and the no parents anywhere
telling you what to do.
Adulthood is responsibility.
The lawyer has been managing her estate
with a limited power of attorney,
but your mother's Alzheimer's
is advancing.
So while she's still
lucid enough to consent,
she needs to sign everything
over to you.
Me?
[Meredith] Responsibility,
it really does suck.
Look, I haven't slept in 48 hours.
I'm getting my first shot
at heart surgery this morning.
I'm missing rounds.
Are you sure there isn't anybody here,
or the attorney...?
I mean, do I really have to be
the one to handle this?
We're talking about her estate,
finances, medical care.
You want to leave her life
in someone else's hands?
She's your mother.
[Meredith] Really, really sucks.
Adults have to be places and do things
and earn a living and pay the rent.
And if you're training to be a surgeon,
holding a human heart in your hands...
Hello!
Talk about responsibility!
- What was that, Dr. Grey?
- Sorry, it slipped. My hands...
It's OK. I'm done.
You can release Mrs. Patterson's
heart now, very gently.
All right. Let's warm her up.
Get her off bypass.
Kind of makes bikes and cookies
look really, really good, doesn't it?
I wish I could hold a heart.
A monkey could hold a heart.
You're mad Burke didn't ask you.
George, I need more ice and chips.
- Who else did you invite?
- We said the list was jocks only:
Surgery, Trauma, Plastics.
- Who else?
- Some people from Peds.
You invited the preschoolers
to Meredith's house.
Next thing, you'll say
that you invited the shrinks.
She invited Mental Defects.
This party is DOA.
Meredith thinks this is a small
meet-your-boyfriend cocktail thing.
- Did you clear this with her?
- No, but I will.
I promise.
Why are you wasting the only weekend
your boyfriend is in town
on a big party?
Is he bad in bed?
No. I just want him
to meet some of my friends.
Right. Sixty geeks in scrubs
are your friends.
[Pager beeping]
Ugh!
Bad sex, sucks for you.
- I heard there's a party tonight.
- Really? A party?
- Uh, news to me.
- No party.
We losing her or what?
- Are the grafts...?
- They're open. Temperature?
She's at 96 and rising.
[Burke] She should be
doing this on her own.
[Flatlining]
[Man] That's her falling.
Continue the progressions.
[Burke] Come on,
Mrs. Patterson. Paddles.
- [Man] Sets are below 90.
- [Woman] Charge.
Ten joules.
Clear.
[Flatline continuing]
Come on, Mrs. Patterson.
- Give me 20.
- Charge.
[Man] There. We have rhythm.
[Monitor beeping]
[Burke] Reluctant heart.
All right.
Let's close. Keep an eye on her.
Good work, everyone.
[Meredith] The scariest part
about responsibility?
When you screw up and let it slip
right through your fingers.
Hey, I heard you did
a CABG with Burke.
- Did you get to hold the heart?
- Yeah.
It's an amazing feeling.
You never forget the first time.
It was pretty great just to watch.
- Vicarious thrills, you know?
- Yeah.
[Elevator bell dinging]
[Woman over PA] Dr. Bailey to OR 7.
Dr. Bailey to OR 7.
- See you later.
- Bye.
[Elevator bell dinging]
I think maybe
I did something to the heart
when I was holding it.
I nodded off a little, squeezed it.
Oh, please. The heart's a tough muscle.
It can take a squeeze or two.
My fingernail popped a glove,
cut straight through.
George, what if I punctured
Mrs. Patterson's heart?
If you had punctured it,
you would have known
when they reperfused.
They got her heart beating.
The woman's OK.
- So I shouldn't tell Burke?
- Tell him what?
You know, um...
...nothing happened.
The woman's OK, right?
She's OK.
She's fine.
[Psapp: Nobody Knows]
[Bailey] What do you see, George?
[George] Hyperinflated lungs,
cloudy with bullae.
Seriously diminished capacity.
She must be having trouble breathing.
Course of action?
Bullectomy procedure. Remove
the bullae. Reduce pressure.
It says here we operated
on her back in '99.
So Mrs. Drake has been
through this before,
but talk her through it anyway.
And resist the anti-smoking lectures.
She feels bad enough already.
So, do you think, if they
put a picture of these
in a pack of cigarettes,
people would stop smoking?
How long has your back
been hurting you?
It's chronic.
Means I have it all the time.
I know what "chronic" means.
What pain are you having?
Oh, man, the pain's bad.
It's like a thousand samurai warriors
stabbing their swords into my spine.
I'm allergic to aspirin, most NSAIDs.
So maybe we'll start you on morphine.
No. The only things
that will work are Demerol
or Dilaudid.
A ten of Dilaudid will set me straight.
The standard starting dose is two.
Did you see that Tom Cruise
samurai movie, hmm?
Pow! Pow! Pow!
Exaggerated and overly specific
description of his pain.
A self-prescription. "Pow! Pow! Pow!"?
- He's a Dilaudid junkie.
- What do you do?
Check the database for history,
refer to a program and discharge.
After you give him something.
That's exactly what he wants.
You still have to treat
his pain as if it were real.
- [Pager beeping]
- Why?
The first rule in pain management:
Always err on the side of caution.
He's in our care. He says he's in pain.
Start a central line.
His veins are shot.
The surgery before
was supposed to help.
But it never felt right.
Probably would have been
a good idea to quit smoking.
I did! Four-pack-a-day habit.
It was hell.
- Here you go, Mrs. Drake.
- Didn't do any good.
Really? Because it looked...
I mean, from the damage,
we all thought you probably
were still smoking.
Cold turkey, five years ago,
and what did I get for my trouble?
I still had to quit my job
at the restaurant.
But even sitting, it hurt.
[Nurse] Here you go.
Nobody believed me.
They all said it was in my head.
I've seen the films.
It's not all in your head.
You're right about that.
Hey, come here.
You're too damn young
to be a doctor.
- Hey.
- What?
I'm older than I look.
[Chuckling]
Do you think this is
going to work this time?
I think it's your best option.
- Straight shooter, huh?
- Yes, ma'am.
I like that.
Hi, Mr. Patterson.
Hi.
Hemodynamics stable?
Yeah, map has stayed around 80.
Cardiac output at five.
- That's good, Dr. Grey?
- That's fine, Mr. Patterson.
But it's not good.
Well, heart surgery takes
a lot out of the patient,
but we're monitoring
your wife very carefully,
and she should be fine.
Mr. Sterman, let's see about
getting you out of here today.
How are you feeling?
Pretty OK,
except I don't think I ever want
to have a bowel obstruction again.
Really?
We get people in here
all the time requesting them.
Oh.
So, you keeping down clear fluids?
And my all-time favorite
question: Have you pooped yet?
I'm not exactly sure.
I think you'd probably know.
Passed gas?
Yes.
Really? Because if I bring in
my handy lie detector...
OK, no.
And I shouldn't try and lie, I know.
I went to medical school.
You went to med school?
Yeah, dropped out
my last year at clinical.
Too many hours,
and I was staring into
the ice-cold eyes of divorce.
Wow.
Yeah, I do research now,
and I have a life, a family.
No offense.
No, no, that's OK.
I'm just one of those people
who believe you can have both.
Maybe so.
But your first responsibility's
always gonna be your patient.
[Woman over PA] Dr. Shepherd
to the ER, stat.
Dr. Shepherd to the ER, stat.
[Psapp: Tiger, My Friend]
Just coffee.
Good.
- OK.
[Bailey] We call this
"a spaghetti procedure."
We cut and deflate
the bullae to facilitate
gentle manipulation
of Mrs. Drake's lung.
Dr. Bailey, do you see that?
Sir?
Oh, my ever-lovin'...
We need to open her up.
I'm taking out the scope.
You heard him, people. Let's move.
- Lights.
- Let's get set up.
- Ten blade.
- Here you go.
Retractors.
Scalpel ready.
Towel.
Rib spreader.
Suction.
Is that a towel?
- Get a pan.
- [George] Where did that come from?
Best guess, her surgery five years ago.
Something careless this way comes.
- A towel?
- Not good.
She complained of pressure on her
chest. Nobody took her seriously.
Not good for the patient,
not good for the hospital.
- Not good.
- Cristina, hit the files.
Find out everything you can
about that initial operation.
Who was in that room?
Who was responsible for closing?
George, stay with the patient.
Keep her happy. She seems to like you.
Right, OK, um,
how long do you think...?
I mean, just technically,
I'm off at 6:00.
- Am I invited?
- Excuse me?
Am I invited to the party?
Oh.
Well, yeah. Yes, yeah, of course.
What was I supposed to say?
Ugh!
OK, yeah, great.
All right, 14 cases.
[Pager beeping]
What kind? I don't know.
Maybe an assortment.
Microbrews, locals.
Make sure they throw in some bar nuts.
I'm ordering office supplies.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Microbrews, local.
And throw in some bar nuts.
7:00 would be better than 5:00.
Hey, any luck?
Hey, if I do,
will you invite me to the party?
[Laughing]
[Yelling]
Yeah, great. OK, thanks.
Take it easy.
- Hey, Mr. Frost.
- Where have you been?!
We're going to take care of you,
all right?
- Where the hell have you been?!
- How's that?
When I tell you to start a central line,
you start a central line,
no judgment, no question.
The guy's been in 7 hospitals
in the last 4 months. He's an addict.
The patient has a three-lumbar fusion.
He's a junkie.
We shouldn't be giving him...
Yeah, he's an addict,
but his pain is real.
Lose the attitude,
get down there, start a central line.
[Monitor beeping]
Told me I had a towel inside me.
Who told you that?
A surgeon, an older man.
Handsome.
That's Dr. Webber.
- He's our chief.
- Yeah.
It was a towel that somebody left
the last time.
Yes, ma'am.
Who would do that?
That doesn't seem right, does it?
No, ma'am, no. It doesn't.
I was walking around
with a towel inside of me.
How could that happen?
So? What happens now?
Now you keep this to yourself
while we work it out.
Do this for me.
[Man over PA]
Dr. Stevens, call CCU.
[Elevator bell dinging]
[Telephone ringing]
- You OK?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
Are you sure?
Because you seem not OK.
I'm fine. CABG was long.
Well, let me take you
out to dinner tonight.
You can tell me all about it.
Real food, waiters,
big chunks of carbs in a basket.
- I can't.
- Forget the party.
- You know about the party?
- You and I can be alone somewhere else.
- How do you know about the party?
- Thanks for not inviting me.
Dinner, think about dinner.
Perfect opportunity.
Well...
[pager beeping]
Ugh!
Started having swelling over her
sternum, then blood started gushing.
Dr. Burke is on his way.
Is she dying?
Somebody get him out of here.
- Keep applying pressure.
- Tyler, call for an OR.
- What happened? She got her protamine?
- Per protocol.
No allergic, anaphylactic
or histamine responses.
Her last counts?
BT, PTT, INR,
platelet counts were all stable.
Even her HNH were stable.
What the hell went wrong? Let's move.
Hold on.
- I popped a glove.
- What?
In surgery, when I was holding it,
I popped a glove with my fingernail.
I think I may have nicked her heart.
Let's go, people.
What were you thinking about?
You had every opportunity to
speak up before I closed her chest.
- Suction.
- I'm sorry.
And then you confess
in front of her husband?
You don't even know if you
were the cause. You have no idea.
- I'm sorry.
- Sponge.
There.
Over here.
There. Look at the wall rupture.
It's a hell of a lot more
than a fingernail.
Her ventricular walls are weak.
I just had a conversation
with Mr. Patterson.
I want copies of his wife's
chart in my office by 5:00.
Tomorrow, the two of you
meet with me and Legal,
and you better damn well be able
to explain what happened here.
People poking holes in hearts
and leaving towels.
You're gonna go back
and talk to the husband.
Review the history.
Apologize profusely.
Your ass is on the line here, Dr. Grey.
You got called before the chief?
Tomorrow morning.
I could get kicked out of the program.
- I could, right?
- You're not getting kicked out.
Patterson's just gonna sue.
Patterson is not going to sue.
You're not getting kicked out.
What were you thinking?
Telling Burke?
- I told her not to.
- [Cellphone ringing]
I got to take this.
Thanks. Thank you. Very comforting.
I'll watch your books.
Oh.
OK, so the beer is coming at 7:00,
and some of the floor nurses
are bringing wine.
- You invited nurses?
- Did you clear this with Meredith?
A few more people isn't gonna make
a difference. A party is a party.
And the bigger the party,
the less time for bad sex.
- Would you stop saying that.
- OK.
Hank and I have great sex, all the time.
We'll probably have sex after
the party, or during the party.
As long as you clear it with Meredith.
Hank just needs to realize
that doctors can have fun.
We're not all workaholics
with God complexes.
We are workaholics with God complexes.
And the notary
can be there at 6:30 too?
And the home's physician will be there
to attest to her mental competency?
OK.
Is there anything else I need
to bring beside my license?
My checkbook.
6:30. I'll be there.
I heard.
It's a notary thing,
a thing to get notarized.
I'm talking about the heart thing.
Do you want to talk about it?
We're adults.
When did that happen?
And how do we make it stop?
Dr. Yang.
Dr. Burke.
That bypass graft
got a little complicated.
It's nothing I couldn't handle.
Good.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Listen, I'll call you back.
[Cellphone beeping]
That was my lawyer.
He's advising me not to talk to you.
Mr. Patterson, I know
that you're frustrated and angry,
but I need... We need some
more information about your wife.
The walls of her heart
are abnormally thin.
Hey, don't blame this on my wife.
I heard from your very mouth
what happened. I know.
But we can't treat her.
No, she was
in the best shape of her life.
You ask her cardiologist.
She had lost 100 pounds.
Don't you dare
try to hang this on her.
Mr. Patterson, please.
We're through talking.
[Sighing]
You don't like me very much, do you?
Oh, Jerry, it's not
you specifically. It's just...
It's just people like you, that's all.
Doc, I'm feeling pretty good.
Pain's about a three.
A three? That's excellent.
Mr. Frost, I'm glad
we could help you out,
as well as County,
Mercy West, Seattle Pres.
A lot of people have
helped you out lately, Jerry.
We're pleased we could do our part.
Who's on discharge today, Dr. Karev?
[Alex] Stevens.
Dr. Stevens is gonna discharge you.
Whoa, you can't discharge me.
I'm in pain.
You were in pain. Now you're not.
Dr. Karev is going to recommend
some wonderful
treatment programs for you.
Go home. Get some help.
You can't just do that!
He just did, my friend.
OK, any luck yet?
Nada.
Ugh. Looks like you're gonna
have to spend another night.
I hate to miss the party.
You gonna make it?
You are the last person on my list,
so it's looking pretty good.
So, doctors have lives
after all. Who'd have thunk?
Dr. Stevens, discharge my guy in 342.
Don't look at me like that.
It's not gonna take very long.
It's not.
- You page me?
- I'm gonna be a while.
Do you think you could get home
to sign for the beer?
Why don't you have
your boyfriend sign for it?
You have a very annoying way
of sneaking up on people.
Maybe if you were
a little less creepy...
I wouldn't come. I hate big parties.
Is Meredith the only person who
doesn't know the size of this thing?
I'm telling her.
- You can't. She's gone already.
- What, already?
I think she had... um, excuse me...
...an errand to run.
You don't think Meredith's
going to mind, right?
I want you to make it very clear to her
that I had nothing to do
with this party... nothing.
Oh, I'm sorry I'm late.
It was the traffic.
It doesn't matter, dear.
Don't tell me the notary didn't show.
Oh, everybody's here.
It's just your mother isn't.
Mom?
What do you people want from me?
We need you to sign
the lawyer's papers.
I have a cranial reconstruction
in a half an hour. I need to go.
OK, Mom. We're all here.
We have a notary.
I need you to focus,
and I need you to sign these papers.
Mom, look at me.
It's an emergency surgery.
I don't have time for this.
She can't sign anything now.
We should have done this
earlier in the day.
I couldn't come earlier in the day.
I have a job and a life,
and I'm here now.
You're gonna have to come back
tomorrow, when she's lucid.
You know, why did she
put this off for so long?
And why did you let her?
Doesn't it strike you as irresponsible?
I mean, what the hell
is wrong with you people?!
[Woman] Dr. Lewis to Peds ICU.
Dr. Lewis to Peds ICU.
[Clearing throat]
[Low dialogue]
[Dance music playing]
Lzzie, I'm gonna kill you.
You could touch that,
but I'd have to kill you.
- So, about that towel thing?
- It's been taken care of.
OK.
You don't need
to concern yourself with it.
So, what's gonna happen?
We're not gonna
talk about it anymore
is what's gonna happen, we clear?
Or you had too much alcohol
to understand me?
- We're very clear.
- Good.
You have any bourbon?
You can't discharge a man in pain.
Ow! You're hurting me!
You're the one who's making it
difficult. Stop resisting.
Just give me the hit of Demerol.
The Dilaudid hasn't worn off yet.
Look, I'm not leaving.
- I'm calling Psych.
- No, no.
- Don't call Psych.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Stop, Jerry. Stop. Stop.
[Gasping]
Jerry. Jerry!
Concussion?
He's blown his left pupil. Page
Shepherd. We got to get him to CT.
That was one hard fall.
What do you see?
[Lzzie] Subdural bleed.
With midline shift.
We have to evacuate this now.
Anywhere else you have to be,
Dr. Stevens, or are you in?
- Brain surgery?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you kidding me?
- That's what I thought.
[Interpol: Evil]
Here you go.
Where is lzzie?!
She didn't clear it with you?
This was supposed to be
a meet-the-boyfriend
get-together little thing!
Lzzie has a lot of friends.
Izzie doesn't know this many people.
I told her to clear it with you.
I can't handle this.
You want me to kick everyone out?
I'm going to kick everyone out.
Baby, you made it! Whoo!
[Laughing]
Screw it. Hold this.
And give me this.
[Glass breaking]
I made it!
George! George, come here. Come on.
- See it?
- It's hard to miss.
- More than he bargained for.
- [Alex] Maybe he's lucky.
Maybe this is his way out of the hole.
The hole? Interesting expression.
My father was into smack
pretty heavy. He was a musician.
It's tolerated in his line of work.
Not good for the family at home.
Why do we want
to be surgeons, anyway?
Surgery is a very serious business.
[Belching]
Full house.
[Laughing]
Royal flush.
Get naked, baby boy.
- Surgery is stupid.
- You're so sexy!
It's stupid.
- It's stupid.
- Give me that. You're drunk.
I'm not driving. I'm not on-call.
I'm in my own house. My life is crap.
And it's my party,
and I'll get drunk if I want to.
Is, um, lzzie Stevens...?
Oh, you must be Hank.
[Laughing]
He's very large and hockey-like.
No, lzzie's not here right now.
OK.
You and lzzie will give birth
to very tall, blonde people...
...kind of like Barbies.
Izzie was going to be home.
She didn't say there was a party.
Which pisses both of us off.
Would you like some tequila?
When do you think
she's gonna get here?
Don't know.
Look, we're low on ice, Hank.
- I'm serious.
- So am I.
We're interns, Hank.
The hospital owns us. It's what we do.
Bye.
Nice to meet you.
Can you guys see him
through recovery?
- Yeah, I'll take it.
- No, I can do it.
That's OK, Stevens.
He's my patient now too.
No, I got it. See your hockey player.
I'm serious.
Yeah, OK.
I guess. Thanks, Alex.
No problem.
[Sighing]
- Hey!
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
Mmm.
I'm sorry I didn't
have a chance to call.
My patient needed brain surgery.
Like, we were inside his brain.
How cool is that?
[Laughing] Oh, my God.
There's a party at your house.
Yeah, did you get a chance to hang out?
I wanted you to meet
some of the people I work with.
I don't care about
the people you work with.
I just want to see you.
You didn't mind meeting the people
I worked with when they were models.
Yeah, well, when they were models,
you actually showed up
to your own parties.
Yeah.
This is my life now, Hank.
I work 100-hour weeks.
I can't always show up
to my own parties on time.
My patients have to come first.
It's just...
Yeah, I just flew
across the entire country,
and there's 100 people at your house.
100 people who understand
what I do all day.
I shouldn't have to apologize for that.
No, you shouldn't.
[Lvy: The Edge of the Ocean]
Look, let's just go by the party
for a little while.
You'll really like everyone once
you get a chance to know them.
I should just go.
Hank, come on.
I'll call you.
[Derek] You know, in some states,
you get arrested for that.
So, you blew me off
for a bottle of tequila.
Tequila's no good for you.
Doesn't call, doesn't write.
It's not nearly
as much fun to wake up to.
Take me for a ride, Derek.
You know, it sounds
like the party's winding down.
- Listen to me!
- What?
We should probably
sneak inside now.
We've done enough sneaking
for the night.
It was good sneaking,
but enough sneaking.
Yeah, I'd say
we're pretty good sneakers.
You mind moving this tail wagon?
You're blocking me in.
Apparently not good enough.
[Clearing throat]
[Sighing]
When's your meeting with the chief?
In an hour.
Holy mother of destruction.
You missed Doctor-palooza.
Apparently, you didn't.
I should probably
never speak to you again.
I'm so sorry, Meredith.
I had no idea it was going to get so...
[Meredith] It's OK.
Really, I don't care.
What would I be doing, anyway?
Preparing for your
career-altering meeting.
Sorry.
That heart wall shouldn't have torn.
Anything in the patient's history?
Husband said she was
in the best shape of her life.
She lost 100 pounds last year.
100 pounds in a year...
How's her muscle mass?
Do you even know whose that was?
I'm hoping it was yours.
No.
What do you think?
[Cristina] 50 says Meredith gets
tossed out and Burke walks away clean.
Please be nice to her.
[Sighing]
[Sighing] So, I have done
a lot of research on this,
and Dr. Burke has been
kind enough to help me.
And I understand my responsibility
in what I've done wrong here.
However, I do think
the patient's history
is significant in this case.
She still weighs 200 pounds,
which is why no one even noticed it.
But with that kind of a weight drop,
it doesn't matter how much
you weigh. You're anorexic.
Along with all that fat,
she was losing heart muscle.
That certainly could be the reason
for a small poke
to become a large tear.
That still doesn't change the fact,
though.
The poke wasn't reported
at the time of the occurrence.
- And if I could change that...
- And you can't.
You left yourself and the hospital open
to tremendous liability.
[Burke] Not if the weight loss
caused the problem.
- I have no choice...
- I've spoken to the husband.
His wife remains stable...
I can't take your beliefs
to the bank, Dr. Burke.
Dr. Grey made a huge error here.
- And she reported it.
- Too late.
And in front of the patient's husband.
But she reported it. She spoke up.
Five years ago, as a CT fellow,
I had a nagging feeling
that I didn't check the body cavity
of a lung patient
closely enough before I closed.
The patient seemed fine post-op,
and I was in a hurry.
And yesterday you and Dr. Bailey
pulled a towel out
from under that patient's lung.
Why didn't I report it
at an appropriate time?
Maybe because I was afraid that
I would be called into a meeting
where some hospital lawyer's
fear of liability could end my career.
Even great doctors make mistakes,
and when we do, we've got
to have a chance to speak up
without fear of retribution.
Or everyone suffers.
Dr. Grey spoke up.
[Meredith] Responsibility:
It really does suck.
Meredith. You OK?
- Yeah, one-month probation.
- That's good.
Yep.
Burke saved my ass in there.
Don't you all have something better
to do? Come on, people, move!
He was always gonna
tell them about the towel.
Just wanted to wait
for the right time.
Information is power.
[The Buffseeds: Sparkle Me]
[Meredith] Once you get past
the age of braces and training bras,
responsibility doesn't go away.
Jerry, this is Sloane.
She's here to talk to you,
if you want, about options for rehab.
[Meredith] It can't be avoided.
Mrs. Drake,
I cannot begin to
tell you how truly sorry I am.
Either someone makes us face it,
or we suffer the consequences.
Izzie! I did it! I pooped!
All right!
- Missed your party?
- Life as a surgeon.
And loving every minute of it.
[Meredith] And still,
adulthood has its perks.
Thanks for the coffee.
[Meredith] I mean,
the shoes, the sex,
the no parents anywhere
telling you what to do...
...that's pretty damn good.