Beware assistants
bearing unrequested coffee.
I try to do something nice and you
assume it's because I want something.
I need a small advance.
Is that a new outfit?
A couple of hundred
against next month's salary.
Then I would suggest
you return that outfit.
Come on Vicki,
just this month.
I swear I won't ask again.
Nope, can't do it.
But it's an advance
against my salary.
Yes, for work you
haven't done yet.
Could you plea bring
me the Harvey file?
Are you going to give
me the advance or not?
Not.
Can I have a raise?
Rachel I'm ready
to be a mother,
to open my spirit
and my body to new life.
Good, good.
Now maintain your
visualization, Rachel.
I'm ready to be a mother,
to open my body
and my spirit to new life.
I'm ready to be a mother,
to open my spirit
and my body to new life.
I'm ready to be a mother,
to open my spirit
and my body to new life.
I'm ready to be a mother.
I'm ready to open my spirit
and my body to new life.
- Sottotitolo non tradotto -
Dr. Hobman told us
to talk to the fetus.
Said it was good for
prenatal development.
After a few weeks, Marlisse
stopped talking to the baby
and started talking with it.
What were they talking about?
Begging him to be a good boy.
Asking him not to hurt anybody.
And then she started
hearing things.
It was really quite creepy.
Have you talked
to your doctor about this?
>>es, that's when he asked
Marlisse to check into
the clinic full time.
That was almost a month ago.
Now, when I try to visit or
even to call her, she refuses.
Apparently, my 'negativity aura' is
making her 'anxious and high-strung'.
I think there's something
wrong with my baby
and nobody will
tell me anything.
But she is at the clinic
of her own free will,
is she not?
Now you sound
like the police.
Don't you see?
It's a cult.
They repeat mantras.
They follow him around
like puppies.
He's some sort
of guru to them.
It sounds like you need
a deprogrammer, not a PI.
You're not the first
PI that I've seet
but you are the first one
who hasn't laughed at me.
Miss Nelson, I want my wife
back, and I want to know
that our baby is going
to be all right.
They won't even let me talk to
my wife, don't you understand?
I'll see what I can do.
Here's your change.
$5,00, $5.25, $5.35, $5.45...
Coreen? Just trying to earn my salary.
This poor woman,
she's been through the mill.
She's had everything - in vitro
fertilization, artificial
insemination, donor eggs,
hormone treatments.
I can't imagine wanting
a baby that badly.
I'd do it, wouldn't you?
>>I don't think the world
is ready for a mini-me.
Besides, artificial
insemination is no way
to make a baby.
- How long have you been standing there?
Okay, you want to earn
your salary, I need you
to do some sleuthing for me.
- What's the case?
Vicki's got a client whose
pregnant wife is being held
captive by a mysterious
baby-making cult.
If this is a cult,
we need to move quickly.
So there is a couple
I want you to interview,
the Deskins.
They had treatment at tke
clinic and have a testimonial
up on the doctor's Website.
So I want you to meet
with them as soon as you can
and get back to me.
- Where are you going?
- Husband hunting.
- Husband material.
You're sweet, but you're
just not a morning person.
No, I'm not.
Vicki Mike, I want you
to be my baby daddy.
- I'm good.
- I'm... flattered?
Come on, I want
to show you something.
You've tried everything
to have a baby, but your
hopes have not been realized.
Don't give up!
At the Hobman Clinic, we can
make your dreams come true.
Well, we can't arrest him
for being irritating, yet.
Wait, it gets better.
Traditional therapies
offer traditional results.
We combine cutting edge
technology with
a holistic approach.
As a result, our success rate
is double that of any other
clinic, verifiable results
that mean your search
could be over.
So the thing is, if I want
to get myself an invite
to Hobman's country estate,
I need to look depressed,
and hopeless.
You know, exhausted.
- Don't forget desperate.
- Um-hum.
And have my supportive
husband right there by my side.
As long as you stop
doing that, yeah.
Okay, Ricky,
whatever you say.
- Who's Ricky?
- You're Ricky, I'm Lucy.
I'm so not going
to be Ricky.
I knew a Ricky... once.
- Okay, how about Ike and Tina?
Greg and Marsha?
Moose and Squirrel?
Hey, how about
Mike and Vicki?
You're such a party pooper.
All right, sweetie,
I've got to go.
Those records aren't
going to forge themselves.
No, they're not.
Vicki How many years
have we been married?
Mike Five.
You can stop quizzing me now.
Trying since our wedding
night to have a baby.
Two miscarriages, three
different fertility doctors.
Two naturopaths,
an acupuncturist,
even a psychic healer.
It's all there
in my medical records.
- I know it's hard for Mike
to understand.
He wants to adopt.
I just hate seeing Vicki
get her hopes up
only to have them dashed
again and again.
It's put a huge strain
on our relationship.
- I wouldn't say huge.
- It feels like we argue
all the time.
- Not all the time.
You see?
I know how difficult
this can be for you both.
And I believe this
treatment can work for you.
But it's not right
for everyone.
You would have to spend
at least a month here
and that can be very
difficult for your partner.
Well, doctor, nothing is
worse than seeing Vicki suffer.
I just want to give her
everything and I can't
give her the one thing
that she wants most.
I can.
Let's have a baby.
Dr. Hobman Here you go.
I'll see you soon.
- Okay.
Doctor.
Where did you get those records?
Got to love the Internet!
- Mike?
- Hey, yeah, that's me.
Yes?
- Got a little chore
for you as well.
What...?
Oh, he needs your swimmers.
Right.
Um... so, like, here, now?
No, we have a room for you
right down the hallway.
And, Vicki, I'm going to be
taking you over to the dorm,
so if you would like to say
good-bye to your husband.
Okay.
A little privacy.
Ahem, well.
- Well.
Honey...
- Um...
- Uh-hum.
This feels weird.
- He took us way too easily.
- Yeah.
- Can you do me a favour?
- Um-hum...
besides filling that cup?
I need you to run
the doctor again.
I don't know,
maybe I missed something?
Yup.
Okay.
Um... we can stop kissing now.
Are you sure?
Uh... it'll be over
before you know it.
What?
Your time here,
the separation.
- Right, right.
- Right.
Um... well...
bye, honey.
Bye.
- Mr. Wheeler.
- Yes, yes.
Right this way.
- I don't buy blood.
- But it's good blood.
Great blood, actually.
Plenty of anti-oxidants,
rich in iron and 22 other
essential vitamins.
- No.
- I deliver.
What is it?
Miss Fennel?
Mr. Deskin, thank
you for meeting with us.
Hi, come on in.
I'm a little surprised our
testimonial is still on the Website.
We did the treatment
so long ago.
- But you were pleased?
- Of course.
We... I wouldn't have had
Travis without Dr. Hobman.
He's very sweet.
Yeah, great little guy.
He's my life.
Where's Mrs. Deskin?
Gail passed away
a couple of years ago.
Now, it's just us men.
- I'm so sorry for your loss.
How did she die?
No, no, it's fine.
It was an accident.
One of those stupid ones
you always hear used
as a statistic, you know,
'more people die falling off
a ladder than they do in a crashing airplane'.
- She fell off a ladder?
Could you tell us
about your experience
at the Hobman Center?
It was simple.
I mean my part
was pretty simple.
You fill a cup,
come back in a month.
Gail had the worst of it.
Cooped up in that
place for so long.
We hear they
isolated the women.
They keep them together
for most of the time.
I think they separate
them near the end.
Something about keeping the
mothers calm and relaxed.
But no husbands?
If you don't mind me being
so direct, our client felt
it was a little cult-ish.
It's just Hobman's process.
He calls it total body.
Complete focus on
the mother and baby.
You know, it feels kind of strange
when you're going through it.
But you can't argue
with the results.
Travis, did Tom's dad
walk you home?
I think he hit puberty early.
What is your problem?
You couldn't get out
of there fast enough.
- There was blood on the boy, and the blood wasn't his.
So, your bags
are in your room.
Just relax tonight, and we'll
get started in the morning.
Great.
Thanks.
Welcome.
Rachel Teertstra.
Hi, I'm Vicki Wheeler.
Nice to meet you.
The first few
days are tough.
You're ready to rip someone's
throat out for a latte.
But once you settle in,
it's pretty great.
Great.
We've got organic food
and lots of rest,
and herbal treatments,
hydrotherapy
and an attitude adjustment.
It's like a spa.
Oh, and isn't Dr. Hobman
the greatest?
He's amazing.
I mean he's so compassionate.
- Yes.
I really feel like this
time, it's going to work.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. So is this everyone?
Oh, the Alpha Mommies, all high
risk, they're in another wing.
More alone time for
bonding with baby.
No visitors?
Oh we can visit sometimes, but
only if we bring loving energy.
Well, that is all I have.
Yes, it's lovely here.
The other women
are really welcoming.
Coreen Oh my God,
is it horrible?
I feel like we're going to break into a round
of Kumbaya any minute.
- Hang in there.
So listen, we went to visit
Mr. Deskin last night.
He was fine,
but the kid was not.
- You don't say.
- Creepy eyes all twitchy
and weird and Henry
smelled blood on him.
- What kind of blood?
- Dead pets.
There's all kinds of animals
missing from the neighbourhood.
Oh, my gosh!
You're kidding!
No, there really
are dead pets.
Oh right, this cheerful double speak is hard to decipher sometimes.
Yeah, you should
try it from my side.
Hey, you know what?
Could you do a favour for me?
Try and track down some of the other
families that came through the clinic.
See if there's anything
odd about the kids.
Bring Henry.
See if he notices anything.
Okay?
Because I want to know what
to expect, you know, with
the results and everything.
Because I'm telling you, I'm
willing to do anything for this baby.
Vicki, it's time
for your physical.
Okay.
All right, well, I've got to go.
Thanks for calling.
- You're freaking me out!
Me too!
Bye!
All right.
Mike I understand you had
a practice with Dr. Hobman?
Richard is a fine doctor.
Dedicated.
Always studying.
But when he took time off
to study new IVF techniques
in Austria about ten,
eleven years ago,
his practice changed... a lot.
- How so?
He turned into a true believer.
All that heal yourself with
the power of the mind nonsense.
Does that translate into 'get
pregnant with the power of your mind'?
His success rate
is pretty good,
about double the
average, actually.
So chalk one up
to airy-fairy?
Any physician knows the mind
can definitely affect health.
In that respect the holistic
practice seems reasonable.
But holistic can be
a euphemism for 'untested'.
There could be health concerns for these children
down the line.
- And what about the mothers?
They're the real guinea pigs.
- What is that?
- Many of these herbs
have been used for centuries
in the treatment of infertility,
black cohosh,
red clover blossom.
dong quai, chastetree berry.
It's all part of Dr. Hobman's
patented treatment.
I haven't seen
Dr. Hobman around much.
Well, he's usually
pretty busy in the lab,
cooking up baby cocktails.
But this is all based
on his research, and you
can't argue with the result.
All right.
Have any of the other mothers
ever have problems
with their babies?
All you new moms,
you're always so nervous.
Relax.
That increases the uterine
lining, and moistens
the mucous membrane.
Mm.
Well, bottoms up.
So this is it?
This is the treatment?
Well, this is part
of the preparation.
Everyone gets this, and
lots of rest and relaxation.
But the actual fertilization procedure,
well, that depends on the individual.
And Dr. Hobman
makes that assessment.
That's right.
Keep drinking.
Chunky.
Any day now Marlisse.
Looking good.
Thank you.
Mind if I visit?
Come in.
Of course.
Vicki Wheeler.
Marlisse Lafoy.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
Don't forget your drink,
Marlisse.
- Wow!
- I know.
Thirty-six weeks, almost to full term,
and I've never felt better in my life.
Is that one of Dr. Hobman's
disgusting shakes?
Trust me, you get used to
them, except for the nightmares.
Maybe if they give you
nightmares, you shouldn't
be drinking them.
- Well, they're not really
nightmares.
More like weird dreams.
And Dr. Hobman says it's
a standard side effect.
Anyway you tell me everything
about the outside world...
world events, local news,
celebrity scandals.
Start with the
Is it really
that bad in here?
Resting and relaxation
is part of the program,
but how many sudokus
can I do in a day?
What about your husband?
Mitch has issues
with the pregnancy.
I worked far to hard for this
to let his negative energy
interfere with
my positive aura.
He doesn't understand how
important this is to us.
What's your story?
What?
Oh! Oh, um...
Everybody said "Oh, wait, - you know -
enjoy your youth, have the baby later!".
No one mentioned to me
that the longer I waited
my chances of conceiving
were reduced exponentially.
Woke up one day, realizing
it might be getting too late.
Now I'll just take
all the help I can get.
I mean this is why
I wanted to talk to you.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm delighted to be here,
but no one seems to be able
to tell me what the treatment
is, and I wonder, is the baby
going to be healthy?
Here.
Feel that?
That's healthy.
Uh, oh.
- Marlisse...
- Ummm...?
Does Dr. Hobman think
everything's okay with the baby?
Absolutely, he says
we couldn't be healthier.
Yeah, then
why are you here?
Safety first, and this
is where I got pregnant.
It feels like a second home.
- Speaking of which,
how exactly did you
get pregnant?
Well if you don't know that, Vicki,
your problem might not be infertility.
Yeah, I think I've got
that part figured out.
I'm talking about
the treatment.
I was not optimistic
because I'd had half a dozen
IVF sessions, before, but there's
something magic about this place.
Listen, Marlisse.
My name is Vicki Nelson.
I'm a private detective.
Your husband Mitch hired me
to check in on you.
- Mitch hired you?
Yes, he's very worried
about you and the baby.
Aw, that's sweet.
But he's got to relax.
I kind of think relaxing
might be the problem.
Visiting hours
are over.
Marlisse, I'm sure
you're going to be fine.
Yeah, but be careful, all right?
- Okay.
Time to go.
Marlisse is such
a great role model.
What an inspiration.
You're very eager,
aren't you?
- Yes.
- Good to know.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Is this the Beth
and Steven Young who went
to the Hobman clinic?
Hello?
Hey!
I'm pregnant!
Dr. Hobman did my serum test.
My H-C-G has doubled.
- Great!
- That means I'm pregnant.
Oh! Oh, hey!
Congratulations!
You're next, I can tell.
Jonah likes you.
I think he likes everyone.
No, Vicki,
you don't understand.
Jonah's a lucky charm. He has an
instinct for who gets pregnant.
I don't understand.
What's so urgent that it
couldn't wait 'til the morning?
- Where is your son?
He's upstairs.
Homework.
Coreen Mr. Deskin, have you
ever talked to the other parents
that have used the clinic?
Has there been any suggestion of
similarities between children born there?
Mr. Deskin You hear stories,
you know?
Excuse me.
Stories?
About fertility clinics and
babies that aren't really yours.
You try to put it
out of your mind.
Tell yourself it couldn't
happen to you.
About a year after Travis was
born we got this from one
of the families at the clinic
around the same time.
Its face was pressed up
right against Marlisse's skin.
Babies don't do that.
At least I really
hope they don't.
Marlisse's husband was right.
Hobman is doing something
to these women,
to their babies.
All right.
Well, I checked the doctor out.
He's had no complaints,
He's got no lawsuits.
He's completely clean.
Apparently this clinic
has twice the success rate
as other clinics.
Okay, that's suspicious right
there, especially with these women.
Most of them have undergone
a barrage of treatments
at other clinics
that have all failed.
Why is this one working?
Hey, sweetie, could you
wash this for me?
You want me
to wash your trash?
Hobman is making us all
drink these herbal remedies.
Mine's mixed in with the soil
and in the cup is something
he's giving
the expectant mothers.
Could you just get Mohadevan
to analyze it and tell me
what the hell is in it.
- Wait a second.
Have you been drinking these?
- I've had to chug a couple.
Vicki, maybe it's time
to get out.
I can't Mike.
He is preying on these women,
on their partners
and on their futures.
I'm not going anywhere until
I find out what's going on here.
All right. Okay, I'll have
Mohadevan look into this ASAP.
- Miss you, sweetie.
- Miss you tons.
Okay?
- Yeah.
Love you.
- Okay.
Mr. Daskin Even as a baby,
there was something
in the way his eyes
would follow me.
The feeling never went away.
After his mother's...
accident,
he got cold,
so cold.
Not quite human?
How can I even think that?
But I do.
Gabriel!
Where are you?
I've got some food.
- I changed my mind.
I want to go home.
C'mon, we're supposed
to be adventurers.
I don't want to.
I wanna go home.
Okay, you can only go home
if you do as I say.
First thing is, you've got
to put on this blindfold.
Okay, now you've got to wait a
minute, and then we're going to go.
I'm scared.
Travis!
It's okay.
Just a minute.
Stop!
Quiet. You played with Travis
but he wasn't very nice.
You'll never play
with him again.
Now.
Go...
home.
You will not harm this boy.
He wants me to.
He tells me to.
Who?
Who tells you?
You will not harm
another human being.
I will not harm
You will not harm
people or animals.
I won't harm them.
Henry, I think Travis may
have killed his mother.
He was about to add
to his accomplishments.
- Oh, my god!
- He's under control...
for now, but I don't know
how long it will last.
He's not completely
human, Coreen.
There's a blackness there,
pure evil,
and something else
is controlling it.
He's only ten.
But the darkness
in him is ancient.
I'm ready to be a mother.
Ready to open my spirit
and my body to new life.
I'm ready to be a mother.
I'm ready to open my spirit
and my body to new life.
I'm ready to be a mother.
Hi.
Dr. Hobman What are you
doing here?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I couldn't sleep.
Dr. Hobman Each patient's
treatment is private
and confidential.
- I'm sorry, it's just...
if I'm going to do this
to myself, I want to know
what's what.
- Well, then ask.
Don't go around spying on other
women and their procedures.
A bath is a procedure?
It's the three 'R's', rest,
relaxation, and rejuvenation.
It's all part of the plan and
it only works if you let it.
Well, it is my money,
Dr. Hobman.
And you're free
to have it back.
This isn't a prison,
Mrs. Wheeler.
You're free to
leave at any time.
In fact, I think
that might be best.
- What?
- You're resisting
the program.
You refuse to follow
the simplest rules.
We can't facilitate your dream
if you don't let us.
- Please, I want this baby.
Look, I really do.
Please don't make me leave.
Vicki, I understand this
is a trying time for you.
Clearly you're a take-charge woman
who's used to charting her own course.
But in this case, if you
want to achieve your
heart's desire, if you want
to beat your own biology,
you have to let someone else
steer this particular ship.
You have to trust us.
All right.
- Good night.
Coreen The changeling.
Henry The Deskin boy?
Elves, dwarves, trolls
and even fairies have
all been known to secretly
trade their own twisted,
unwanted offspring for a more
desirable human child.
These legendary creatures
want the human infant
for various reasons,
companionship, servitude,
spite and in some cases,
consumption?
Does Vicki ever talk
about having kids?
- Where did that come from?
- I don't know, just curious.
I don't know.
She hasn't said anything.
But then again older women
are always talking
about how their biological
clocks are ticking.
- Older women?
- You know what I mean.
What about you?
Can vampires even have kids?
When you turn someone they
can feel like your child.
But there's that vampire
territorial instinct.
It's not long before
you want to kill them.
Oh, so like other real kids
and their parents.
Pretty much.
But I feel as though I miss it.
The good elves, blah, blah,
blah, blah... the evil,
dark elves find solace in the dark
spaces and delight in the torment of man.
The dark elves.
A Swartalfen is an evil
elf from proto-Germanic myth
who impregnates women
with his demon seed.
As the children of these
Dark Elves grow older,
they begin to spread death and
destruction wherever they go.
They are the Alfenkindren.
That boy tonight.
And Vicki's in their den.
Vicki Nine months ago...
yesterday.
Hydrotherapy.
Hydrotherapy...
yes, yes, yes.
Jonah.
You are not my type.
Come on, come on, come on...
Mlke Doc, you're killing me. It's way
too early in the morning for statistics.
Mohadevan Those are the test
results from your samples.
Yeah, you care to translate?
Well, the soil sample
produced a concoction of herbs,
cohosh, red clover blossom,
dong quay, chastetree berry.
Care to guess what
they have in common?
They all taste disgusting?
And are all believed
to facilitate conception.
Really.
How about the other sample?
Well, neither sample would
harm someone, but the second
one could make someone quite
happy, sleepy, and compliant.
You're saying
it's a compliancy cocktail?
Precisely.
Yeah, this is Mike Wheeler. I'd
like to talk with my wife, Vicki.
Marlisse, hi!
- Hi!
- How're you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Okay, listen to me.
You have to stop
drinking that stuff.
It's dangerous for the baby.
- What are you talking about?
Dr. Hobman would never
do anything to risk
the health of a baby.
- My friend is a doctor
and she says that
that mixture of herbs
is dangerous for you
and the baby.
- The baby.
- Yes, all right?
Listen to me.
Just do what I say, okay?
Promise me you
won't drink anymore.
I promise.
All right, I'll be back.
- Oh hi, Kate.
- Fax from Vicki.
- Oh, perfect.
- "Miss you, baby.
Don't forget to check
out the foreman's crew... "
Thank you.
"... before we commit
...to the renos...
- Thank you.
...XO, Vicki. "
Is there something
you're not telling me?
- It would take days.
"Foreman's crew. "
Ow, hey!
Enough of that baby.
OH!
How did you meet Dr. Hobman?
What do you
know about my baby?
- What happened?
- I did what you said.
I stopped drinking that green
goop this morning and I saw
something that wasn't right.
You saw it the other day.
Okay, tell me about
the hydrotherapy.
You go into a tub.
It's like a sensory
deprivation tank.
You repeat a mantra.
It's just a guided relaxation.
Now you see, everyone
who's gotten pregnant here
has one thing in common.
Hydrotherapy.
It doesn't make any sense.
It's just a bath.
Something happens in that
bath, okay, and I have reason
to believe that you and your
baby are at risk, all right?
Just let me get
you out of here.
All you need to do is say yes.
- Yes.
- Okay, we're going
to tell them we're going
to get some air.
No one goes outside,
Vicki, rules are rules.
We're just going
to get some air.
What are you doing
to these women?
I'm helping them.
Just like I'll be helping you
later tonight.
Don't make a fuss, Vicki.
You'll upset the
pregnant ladies...
and me.
UH!
You found him?
That's great!
Um... when was that?
1942 to 1960?
What was he doing back then?
A GP?
You've got to be kidding me.
Listen, do you have a photo
of him from back then?
Yeah.
- You and the ladies
toda.
- Uh... just a minute.
A friend of yours
got stopped at the door.
Pushed the metal detector
into the red zone.
We thought we were under siege
but she seems to be
some kind of attack gardener.
Mike Can you fax me
that photo right away?
Okay, what's in the bag?
Henry and I think it's a Swartalfen,
an evil elf from the Norse myth.
I thought elves were
supposed to be good.
Light elves are. But the Swartalfen,
a dark elf, is pure evil, grotesque.
They used to switch
their babies for ours.
The changelings are supposed
to grow up and kill their
parents, but most people
notice the difference.
- Yeah.
- They're breeding with us
to spread death and despair.
Their spawn, the Alfenkindren
are sociopaths,
fledgling serial killers.
Okay, wonderful news.
I guess that lets a lot
of distraught parents
off the hook.
Henry caught one about
to kill another child.
He's only ten years old,
and he's already a killer.
And what's all this?
According to legend,
the Swartalfen worked
the forges for the gods.
They have a pathological
hatred for iron.
I'hoping this will kill it.
What?
You're hoping?
The only other information
I found on killing evil elves
involves rolling
a twenty-sided dice.
We've got to stop that
doctor before it's too late.
Well, it's not the doctor.
It's him.
I'll call Henry.
Oh!
- Miss me?
- Oh...
More than you know.
- We've got to go.
Mike's outside.
It's too dangerous for you here.
Tell me about it.
Hide!
Okay, wait for my signal.
Marlisse has
gone into labour.
Our encounter will
have to wait awhile.
- Go to hell!
- You're upset now.
Once you feel that new life growing
inside you you'll change your mind.
Oh!
Was any of that a signal?
Because if it was,
I completely missed it.
- No, you did fine.
- That's Jonah?
- The nurse.
He gives t women
a therapeutic bath,
and they come out pregnant.
- With his evil spawn.
He's a Swartalfen.
- He's a what?
Just get to the good part.
- Anything that's iron
should kill it.
I'm supposed to get you
out of here
and rendezvous with Mike.
I think we're going
to plan 'B'.
She's in labour.
There's nothing we can do
for her now and the children
aren't in any danger.
- She's scared to death.
- We return when we're
better prepared.
- No, we are ending this now.
Henry Vicki!
Vicki Henry!
A beautiful baby boy,
Marlisse.
Mitch...
Mitch should be here.
Hobman I'll make sure
he's called.
Hi.
Henry.
Vicki!
Henry!
Oh, crap!
I guess iron
really does work.
- What?
- Compliments of Coreen.
- It's gone.
- So does that mean
we're going to kill this thing?
- Damn straight, it does.
- Jonah, are you all right?
- I'm fine.
The baby?
- Hale and hearty.
Another boy.
It must be the water.
May I?
Swartalfen So beautiful.
Henry, The baby!
Feierlich menschen!
Come on!
COME ON!
Give me back my baby!
So?
You still want a baby?
Mitch Marlisse!
Rachel lost the baby.
The Swartalfen's
last act of violence.
Is Marlisse's
baby one of them?
The connection to the
Swartalfen was broken
when it died, but I can still
sense darkness within it.
Well, let's just hope it takes after
its mother's side of the family.
transcript:swsub.com
sincro: alexandraD. www.subsfactory.it