Now this cab is young,
so limited finish, of course,
but still has a nice depth.
I can taste cherries,
a bit of ginger.
Plums and cassis.
And a hint of dark chocolate.
Lovely.
In another five years,
it's going to be an exceptional wine.
Yes, Bruce is a magician
with my grapes.
Of course, he convinced me
to sink a mint
into the vineyard over
the last two years alone, but,
money well spent.
You're going to make Virginia
the next California, Sean.
Doc, wait until you taste the'97.
Gotta be the best year
we've ever had at Bedford Creek.
Wouldn't you say, Bruce?
Perfect balance of sun and rain,
limestone and gravel.
It was a year one dreams about.
Now, some sediment is normal,
especially in such a big wine.
Salut.
Cheers.
- What the hell is going on, Bruce?
- I don't know, sir.
Something's in my glass.
My God, that's a human finger.
It's quite simple.
Whatever Agent Booth says,
you respond with whatever
word or phrase pops into your head.
And vice versa.
That's ridiculous, I can't properly
respond without careful thought.
Can't we just make it
a drinking game?
No. This is a valuable,
psychological tool, Agent Booth.
When you respond viscerally
we can get to the root of your emotional
issues and figure out what
binds you two together as partners.
Donuts.
- Beg your pardon?
- Glazed donuts. I see 'em right there.
- You had no breakfast. You're hungry.
- I'm starving.
- No, that's not the proper response.
- Of course it is.
I'm explaining why he said "donuts."
The point of the exercise
is not to explain, but to respond.
- Children can do this.
- Because it's childish.
- Can we just try it, please?
- All right, okay, fine, here we go.
Are you ready?
- Hunger.
- Sex.
- Horse.
- Cowboy.
- Child.
- Baby.
- Booth.
- What, do you think, I'm a baby?
- You're a father.
- Mother.
- Birth.
- Happy.
- Sperm.
- Isn't this getting a little weird?
No, keep going.
- Okay. Egg.
- I want a baby.
- Horse.
- Wait. Wait a minute.
- We can stop here.
- I actually found that interesting.
- You want to have a baby?
- Yes. I do. I just...
I just realized it.
I should have a progeny, it's...
selfish of me not to.
- Selfish?
- Yes.
Don't you need a,
you know, guy to...?
Just sperm.
You'd be a very good donor,
potentially.
- Me?
- But you need to be tested, of course.
- What, is something wrong?
- Yeah. Okay.
You don't just go around
asking for people's sperm.
Yeah. No, I wasn't talking to you.
Right. Yeah.
On our way.
We got a case.
Wait, perhaps
we should discuss this.
I'm not conflicted, if that's what
you're concerned about.
- I've made a reasonable choice.
- In two seconds over some stupid game.
This is a well researched,
therapeutic technique, Agent Booth.
Really? This happens all the time
patients asking for sperm?
Yeah... no, well,
not this specifically.
Which is why I think
some discussion is in order.
- Shouldn't we go? Don't we have a case?
- Yeah. We gotta get going.
- This is all your fault.
- I know this was surprising, but...
You're the one who's always
touting parenthood,
implying that my life is incomplete
because I don't have a child.
I know, but this is kind of sudden.
- Perhaps you don't want to help me.
- Of course I do.
- So you'll do it?
- I'll think about it.
I don't understand.
It's a simple request.
I'm sure you engage in masturba...
Horse.
Enough. We'll talk about it later.
I'm not asking for you to be involved.
All I want is your sperm.
That's a good one.
"All I want is your sperm."
I never heard that joke before.
- I don't understand.
- Yeah. Okay.
OK. Just close your mouth
and point us to the body.
The barrel's over here.
Dr. Granger said
it was a human bone, but...
that's impossible.
This may be an animal, a rat.
- That could happen, right?
- And you are?
Sean Mortenson. This is my winery.
And Bruce Hanover, my viticulturalist.
The remains are human.
The cask has been sealed since 1997.
I did it myself.
The seal must have been broken
when the body was thrown in here.
Exposure to air turned
the wine to vinegar.
- Looks like a purple Smurf.
- Pelvic bone indicates a male.
More like a rubber purple Smurf.
Bones in vinegar leech calcium and will
become gelatinous within three days.
That is actually cool.
This cask is filled with debris,
decomposed tissue and organs.
It all has to come back to the lab.
Oh, God.
Bones - Season 04 Episode 25
"The Critic in the Cabernet"
Synchro: ShalimarFox
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
Liquefactions suggests
he's been there at least eight months.
Scapula, clavicle.
Fat globule.
We're all just one step away from
dissolving into the primordial ooze.
Manubrium and ilium.
Rendered brain matter.
You got a sock, a belt.
Molar, lateral incisor and canine.
And this is just goo.
I got a grommet, three nickels,
and I am guessing a chocolate kiss.
Bingo!
A chunk of liver,
enough for a tox screen.
My guess,
you'll find a high alcohol content.
Tibia.
I've decided to have a baby.
Capitulum.
Wait.
Baby, like a small human?
Yes. I know I've had
no interest in the past, but,
neither did you and you seem
to find parenthood very fulfilling.
Yes. I do.
And... you brought this up now...
why?
I wanted to give you notice.
I'll be needing some time off
when the baby comes. About...
six weeks I imagine.
The staining makes it very difficult
to see any anomalies on the bones.
Is there a father?
I'd like to use Booth's sperm.
Booth. What do you know?
If Booth doesn't work out,
I donate my sperm monthly.
I have a high IQ, excellent genetics,
and motility.
No emotional baggage.
I'm kind of a catch.
- Down, boy.
- Weren't we investigating a death?
Oh, my God.
Dr. Brennan wants to have a baby.
I offered my sperm, but she's leaning
more toward Agent Booth.
You're joking, right?
Booth and I discussed it
in Sweet's office.
He's thinking it over now.
Although,
I don't understand why
he'd be protective of his semen.
There are six evenly-spaced cavities
along the sides of the frontal
and parietal bones.
Hand me that grommet you found.
Grommet.
The grommet. Yes. Right.
There you go.
Thank you.
I could get you my little swimmers
at a substantial savings.
- Fisher, just scoop, please.
- Sure.
He had a craniofacial implant.
The way they're spaced,
they're positioned
to secure a prosthetic hairpiece.
- Those are not very common.
- I'll strain for the rug.
If there's a missing persons
report on the victim,
it would definitely mention
a surgical hairpiece.
You can also replace the teeth
in the mandible and...
confirm with dentists.
We heard right, didn't we?
A baby.
With Booth.
There's a fracture on the zygomatic.
Probably from a blow to the face.
The guy is pickled, sweetie.
He can wait.
You can't just announce
you're having a baby and walk away.
15,000 babies are born every hour.
It's not all that exceptional.
Brennan... this is crazy.
Why?
I'm intellectually gifted,
financially secure.
Statistically, I could expect to have
an exceptional child.
Fine. Yes. Absolutely.
But you do know how
this is supposed to work, right?
You get naked together.
You devour each other
in a passionate frenzy.
Booth would think that would create
an emotional bond between us.
- Of course that's ridiculous.
- I knew you'd understand.
Then why use Booth at all?
Why don't you use Fisher
and his discount sperm?
No, Booth has a larger mandible
and a more prominent zygomatic
than Fisher, as well as a more
pronounced ratio between
the width of his clavicles and his ilia.
So, it's because Booth is hot.
Now we're getting somewhere.
Statistically, attractive people
are more successful.
I'm only thinking of the child.
Then do this right, sweetie.
I am.
Emotional ties are ephemeral
and undependable.
Look at you and Hodgins.
You and Roxy.
Booth and Rebecca.
Booth and Cam.
Brennan, I...
I appreciate your concern, but
I have thought this through rationally.
This fracture
hasn't fully remodeled.
It occurred within a month of death.
Possibly from an attack.
The victim is Spencer Holt.
Missing almost a year.
He was a wine critic.
Apparently he could destroy
a vineyard with one review.
Everyone likes a dead critic.
I mean there's...
we're going to have
lots of suspects.
Why are you here and why
didn't you just send an e-mail?
You and Brennan,
you're going to have a baby?
- She told you.
- She told everyone.
- It's probably on the news by now.
- I'm just donating.
- So you decided?
- No. I am deciding. I-N-G, ing.
I know you.
You're going to do it.
You want to do it
without really doing it.
It's still doing it even if you're not
doing it the way it should be done.
She wants a kid, okay? It'll make her
more personable with people.
- And what will it do for you?
- She'll get what she wanted.
- A piece of you?
- Look at this.
Holt's wife filed
for a missing persons report.
Now, I have to go tell her
the bad news.
- Sure.
- You done?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
So apparently, Holt's wife
was pregnant when he disappeared.
- So she's raising the child alone?
- I guess so.
You know, and no one
thinks twice about that.
There are millions of single women
raising healthy, productive children.
There was a domestic disturbance
report filed
a month before he disappeared.
You know, if we go,
through with this,
and I'm around,
and if you need help...
I'll have a nanny.
I I figured. But, you know,
if it's her day off.
You don't have faith
that I can do it?
- What? I didn't say that.
- But you think I'd be a good mother?
Yeah, of course.
I know sometimes
you don't think I'm empathetic.
And it can be difficult
for me sometimes.
But I would love my child,
Booth, I would.
I know.
I know that, Bones.
I know people disapprove.
If you're uncomfortable,
Fisher sells his sperm monthly,
he's very intelligent and...
Fisher?
No, you are not having Fisher's kids.
You'd be giving birth
to the spawn of Satan, I'll do it.
No obligation.
I don't want you to feel any obligation.
I'll do it. Don't worry about it.
It's your kid, it's totally yours.
- Not worried about it.
- I just saying I'll do it.
You hold out hope, but in my heart,
I've known for months.
- What happened?
- We don't know yet;
- we're still investigating.
- He was found at Bedford Creek Winery.
At Bedford Creek?
- You been there?
- I'm the wife of a wine critic.
I've had to sit through tastings
at half the places in the country.
I don't even like wine.
Oh, God.
I am all covered.
I'll get her.
Spencer always wanted me
to give up my carpentry business.
Said I smelled of stain.
Ruined the bouquet
when he was tasting wine.
- Bones, you need help?
- No, no, I'm fine.
You got to help with the...
You like
spatial disorientation, don't you?
Yes, you do.
She likes you.
All Spencer could ever talk
about was having a little girl.
He would've made a good father.
Your husband also exhibited
a facial fracture
that hadn't fully remodeled.
Yes. He tried to break up a fight
at the wine expo.
Mortenson was going after
Charles Dunwood.
Mortenson from Bedford Creek?
He's a real bastard.
- He and your husband didn't get along?
- No.
Mortenson loved him.
Spencer gave his cabernet a 99.
No one gets that.
It was Charlie Dunwood
Mortenson hated.
Because Charlie
made a cheap wine next door
and he wouldn't sell out
to Mortenson.
- And you saw this fight?
- No.
They all deny it, of course.
But Spencer told me about it.
There was a domestic
disturbance report filed
approximately one month before
your husband disappeared.
- Can you explain that?
- Our neighbor heard us arguing.
That's all.
She called the police.
The report says it was more
than an argument, Mrs. Holt.
I threw some dishes.
But not at Spencer.
It was just the pregnancy hormones,
you know?
I would never hurt Spencer.
You don't believe the victim's wife?
I think that we should check with
Dunwood. He might've a different story.
What about the owner
of Bedford Creek Winery?
Mortenson is rich.
If he's involved,
you don't want to spook him
or he's just gonna hire
an army full of lawyers
to go make our lives miserable.
Would you like legal protection?
- What?
- With the child
so you feel secure that
I won't be asking for money or support.
- No, I don't need legal protection.
- But if you do...
I don't.
I've made an appointment for you
at the fertility clinic.
They will check
your semen for motility,
morphology, sperm count.
My boys can swim.
All right? I have a child,
do you rember?
This isn't personal.
I'd be remiss if I didn't look
at an analysis of your semen.
It's a very simple process.
You just go to the clinic,
give a sample. It takes five minutes.
They have pornography,
if you need stimulus.
I get it.
You really liked
holding that kid, didn't you?
I've been thinking
about how exciting it will be to
expose my own child
to early pattern recognition.
You know, they like singing and...
when you make
funny faces at them, too.
Yeah, of course.
I will make a diverse schedule.
When it doesn't contain
human remains,
Bedford Creek
makes an excellent cab.
It's very full-bodied.
It's like an Australian Shiraz.
I only drink diet soda.
I'm hoping the preservatives
can add some stability to my life.
Here's a little pocket knife.
And some glass fragments
embedded in the fabric from his shirt.
There's some scraping
on the anterior of this rib.
I got a gouge on the third rib and
one here on the sternum.
- You think he was stabbed?
- I can't tell from the incised edges,
'cause the bones are soft and completely
stained from soaking in the wine.
Man, I can barely get wine stains
out of my shirt, let alone a skeleton.
But your shirt
isn't composed of calcium.
Oh, my God.
I can clean them.
This is weird.
Something good is happening.
Take a deep breath;
I'm sure it'll pass.
The approximate weight of
the bones is 12. 43 kilograms.
I'm gonna need 781 boxes
of denture cleaner.
Shame about Holt. He was a good guy.
One of the only critics
who didn't dump on my wine.
But your wine sells for
three dollars a bottle.
That's right, yeah.
In a bottle or a box.
- It's a good honest drink.
- That's good.
I didn't know you knew
anything about wine.
It's good, like the beer of wine.
Holt got that. He knew
I wasn't trying to be more.
Holt's wife said that,
he had to break up a fight
between you and Mortenson
from Bedford Creek Winery.
Yeah, it was at the wine expo,
in the parking lot.
I told Holt to stay out of it.
I shoved Mortenson, all right?
The guy was in my face.
Holt got in the middle, right when
Mortenson was taking a swing, so
he took the hit.
Mortenson walked out.
Just left him.
What was the fight about?
My vineyard's next door to his, and,
he thinks I'm an embarrassment.
He wants to buy me out.
He threatened some bogus lawsuits.
My family's been working
those fields since 1928.
This is my life.
So you had no issue with Mr. Holt?
Hell, no. You know, if he were alive,
I'd pat him on the back.
For what?
For taking that bastard
Mortenson down a peg.
- Yeah, but he loves Bedford Creek wine.
- Yeah.
But I heard he loves sleeping
with Mortenson's wife even more.
Is that what I think it is?
Were you thinking sodium perborate
and potassium monopersulfate?
Actually, I was thinking
Nana Shirley's teeth.
More like 781
sets of Nana Shirley's teeth.
Fisher says this will remove
the staining.
Could. I said could.
There is no certainty but death
and the incomprehensible
conundrum that is life.
Fisher, have you ever just taken
a moment to forget yourself?
Watch, like, The Three Stooges
and just laugh?
Yeah, I never found
humor in grown men
giving each other concussions
with construction equipment.
I tried.
Tox screen on the remnants
of the liver was inconclusive.
Rhe vinegar will obscure
just about everything.
But I did find some inorganic agents
mixed in with the liquefied tissue.
Might help us find cause of death.
I think I found stab wounds
on the ribs and sternum.
We'll know more
if we can clean the stains.
It's quite simple.
You just ejaculate into the cup.
Here we go, Mr. Booth.
You look a little flushed.
Are you okay?
- Sure. Yeah, I'm fine.
- Sometimes men can feel awkward.
Knowing people out there know
what you're doing in here.
Thanks for that.
You know what to do.
You're kidding, right?
There are magazines and videos,
if you need them. Enjoy.
Why are you here at the bank, Booth?
You've got a hot doctor friend.
Go to her and make
a direct deposit like a man.
That's impossible.
And yet we converse.
Look, a pile of porn.
Delicious.
Give me a peek, Booth.
Just a little peek at a booby?
Please?
What's your problem? You're threatened
by a cute, harmless baby?
Grow a set!
You do want her to have
your baby, don't you?
Of course I do.
It's just,
I want her to have a baby
because it's what she wants.
And you could just walk away
like a heartless cad
while she changes poo
all by her lonesome?
It's what she wants!
Are you okay in there, Mr. Booth?
I'm fine.
Just, fine, thank you.
Listen, could you just go away now, OK?
I don't need your help.
You're not a bad looking fellow,
and if you'd just keep an open mind...
Go back to cartoon land,
wherever you came from. Leave!
You sure? I'm good at pretend games.
That wasn't possible.
- Agent Booth.
- Sweets!
- How you doing?
- I'm fine.
Turns out that, the victim might have
been sleeping with Mortenson's wife?
Jealousy, always a good motive.
Yeah, that's good.
But, I'm more interested in whether
you decided to inseminate Dr. Brennan.
God, you know,
don't say it like that.
I'm sorry. I'm interested
in whether you decided
to provide your semen
for her fertilization.
Saying it like that is worse.
I could go with "baby daddy,"
but that seems even...
I'm gonna do it.
I've already made the deposit.
That's right. Apparently, I am a god.
That's right.
Motile sperm count: 28. 8 million.
I could start my own country.
Okay, then. Well, I'm sure you'll be
going through a lot of emotional changes
because of this,
so if you need to talk...
Thank you, but, it's her baby,
so it's gonna be her life
that's turned upside-down, not mine.
- So you're not at all stressed by this?
- I'm an FBI agent, and a former sniper.
This is not a life or death
situation, you understand?
Yeah, sure.
Well, if you need anything,
I'm available.
I don't need anything.
I am just doing what, you know, anyone
else would in this situation, right?
Like what?
Just...
I got a little, you know,
anxious at the clinic.
- Anxious?
- Anxious. Don't get all shrinky on me.
No, no, what kind of symptoms?
Shortness of breath, lightheaded?
- It's normal, right?
- Absolutely.
Sometimes, donors can feel
an emotional attachment,
even if they don't know
the recipient.
In this case,
since you and Dr. Brennan...
It's normal to imagine things?
Well, not pink elephants, but...
No, no, no, of course not.
Like, baby things.
It'd be odd if you didn't.
It'd be odd if I didn't.
You're my guy.
That's all I needed to hear.
Thanks, Sweets. Thanks.
I gotta go, take care of something.
No problem. Anytime.
There are tiny fractures
near the coronal sutures.
We never would have
noticed these before.
The denture cleaner
was an excellent idea, Mr. Fisher.
Now if I only possessed
rudimentary social skills.
They aren't really
necessary for your work.
I wish my parents were
that understanding.
You're gonna be a good mother.
I would imagine so.
Evidence of hemorrhaging
on the underside of the fractures.
There was a perimortem
blow to the head.
Okay. Booth is waiting for me.
Check the degree of hemorrhagic
staing to see if it was cause of death.
If Booth is still reluctant...
No, he offered
28. 8 million viable sperm
in a mere three milliliters
of ejaculate.
As the feeling of inadequacy
makes me shrivel.
Spencer Holt was a big
supporter of Bedford Creek wines.
- He was here for numerous tastings.
- Your little boy is adorable.
Thank you.
Phalanges, dancing phalanges.
- Bones.
- Right, sorry.
So you...
were sleeping with
Spencer Holt, weren't you?
Subtle.
Sleeping with him?
Of course not. Who told you that?
Seems like your husband
had, quite the temper.
Charlie Dunwood, right?
- That is not your husband's child.
- What?
- I think you should leave.
- The bone markers bear
- a clear resemblance to Spencer Holt.
- They do?
Research shows that babies
strongly resemble their fathers
in the first year of life.
The evolutionary theory being that
they're less likely to be abandoned
if the fathers recognize
themselves in their offspring.
What?
Your kid will look like me,
at least for the first year?
There's a high statistical
probability, yes.
Excuse me.
I can compare these photos
against Spencer Holt's remains.
- The maxilla and nasal aperture...
- Stop.
My husband could come in any moment.
So it's true?
Sean and I tried.
It's all about business with him,
but I really wanted a child.
Spencer understood, and one night
after a little too much wine...
I appreciate everything
Sean does for me,
but Spencer was, you know...
Kind?
I wish he had the chance
to see his child.
So does his wife.
Maybe your husband found out
that you were having an affair,
and, he decided
to get rid of Mr. Holt.
Seems like the kind of guy
who likes to get what he wants.
Sean has a temper,
but he would never hurt anyone.
What the hell are you doing?
We were just asking a few
questions about Spencer Holt.
You keep your mouth shut. I told you
everything when you found him,
and we're not saying anything
else without our attorneys present.
Is that clear?
I tried to talk to Brennan
about that whole baby thing.
- She won't listen to me.
- Neither will Booth.
Guess all we can do is board up
the windows and hope the levees hold.
- It's none of our business.
- Exactly right.
- That kid is gonna be so cute, though.
- Please, we're gonna go nuts.
I bought it a little onesy today.
I got the results back
on the inorganic goo.
Contains calcium arsenates.
- Arsenic?
- Yeah,
it was on his clothes
and mixed in with the tissue.
So, he was poisoned?
This isn't a high enough
concentration to kill him.
Booth said Holt's wife worked
with wood building playsets.
Arsenic is used in stains
and wood preservatives.
It's tough to wash off.
So Jenny Holt found out her husband
was cheating on her, stabbed him,
and left us a chemical fingerprint.
Spencer traveled a lot,
visiting vineyards across the country
and Europe, South America.
That's why I waited to file
the missing persons report.
He was missing for ten days. You didn't
even talk to him during that time?
We'd been having some trouble in
our marriage, but we loved each other.
You know he was having
an affair with, Kim Mortenson?
Yes,
I knew about Kim,
but we would have gotten past it.
When the baby was born, we would've
gotten closer, like we had been.
Did you know he was
the father of Kim's baby, too?
- What?
- Yeah.
No, that's impossible.
Knowing that he was having
an affair is one thing,
but knowing he fathered another
child while you were pregnant...
that would put anyone over the edge.
I didn't kill Spencer.
I loved him.
In your work,
do you use stains or wood
preservatives that contain arsenic?
There are traces, yes.
Arsenic was found on his clothes,
in his wounds
in an amount that could easily
have been transferred
from the assailant during an attack.
Why would I leave my little girl
without a father?
Why would I do that to her?
Where were you for the ten days
he went missing?
That was months ago.
I couldn't tell you. No one could.
All of the injuries to the ribs
and sternum had silica embedded in them
which matched
all of the glass shards
found in the wine cask
and on Holt's clothes.
Yes, these injuries to the ribs
and sternum...
can you connect the impact points?
Why, you think Holt's wife was making
a design when she was attacking him?
There are three main impact points.
What if they were
a circular pattern?
Okay, well, a circumference...
the circle is nine
and a half inches.
What is the circumference
of a wine bottle?
My guess, nine and a half inches.
Yeah, let's see.
Yep, nine and a half inches.
OK, get some Bedford Creek wine.
See if the bottle was sufficient
to cause these injuries
and hemorrhagic staining
at the coronal suture.
You know, a watermelon
is the same density as the human head.
I like the way you think, Fisher.
I have an appointment
with a fertility specialist next week.
I could be inseminated
within a month.
- Really?
- You didn't tell Agent Booth?
I promised him he wouldn't
have to be involved.
Right, exactly, you see,
'cause we have a... an arrangement.
Well, I thought that these sessions
were meant for you
to see how we interact as partners.
How does this relate?
You're using
agent Booth to have a child.
You don't see how that might
relate to your partnership?
Has nothing to do with our work.
Let me just
organize my thoughts here.
It's not like
I'm going to be bringing
the child along
when we interrogate someone.
But you might decide to breastfeed.
It is healthier.
That's true.
So, yes, there might be some crossover.
I can see that now.
I'm sorry. Go on.
I think you need to
acknowledge that there are
some emotional considerations
that you might be denying.
Like what?
There are sperm banks that guarantee
high IQs
and exceptional physical prowess,
yet you specifically
chose Agent Booth. Why?
He has traits like
courage and compassion and empathy
that would be tremendous
assets to my child.
Sperm banks
don't catalog those traits.
Did you just say something nice?
No, I gave an objective evaluation.
Because it sounded like
you said something nice.
How can you two not see
what's going on here?
What is the big deal? She was gonna
have a baby anyway, I mean, with Fisher.
What would you have done?
What I would have done is not important,
but you admitted to feelings of anxiety.
You know what, Sweets?
You are crossing a line right there.
- I agree.
- No, I'm not actually.
In my position, I could make
an evaluation that states
that you two are not
suited to work together
because of interpersonal issues
that are not being dealt with.
- Ridiculous.
- Dreamer.
So perhaps until our next session,
maybe you should think about some
of the things that I brought up today.
It's confirmed by the modeling.
Yep, the shards of glass found
in the cask have the same thatch design
as the base of the
Bedford Creek bottles.
So, we know the bottle
was from Bedford Creek.
Then we don't have to do
the experiment.
We have all the melons
already, you know, and the bottles...
- Confirmation would be beneficial.
- We'd be remiss if we didn't confirm.
Sorry, Mr. Holt.
That bottle was supposed to break.
Yeah, otherwise,
the injuries make no sense.
You're sure a melon has
the same density as a human head?
Would I waste our time?
Give me that.
- I enjoyed that too much, didn't I?
- It's important to love your work.
Maybe she hit him
with the narrow end.
She was a carpenter. More strength.
I was going out to dinner.
- Would you like a towel?
- Very much.
The Bedford Creek bottles,
they wouldn't have broken.
But it would've smashed his skull.
But you said the design
you found on the glass
confirmed that it was
a Bedford Creek bottle.
Yeah, but...
these bottles wouldn't have
provided the injuries that we found.
So... after all this, we have no weapon
or cause of death?
Did you ever think, what if Booth
is the perfect father for your child?
Not just his stuff, but him.
What if you're throwing away the chance
to have a family,
a real family,
because you're scared?
Scared? Why would I be scared?
I've been to Rwanda, to Iraq.
Listen, you said you wanted to do this
alone because feelings are ephemeral.
So is life, Brennan.
We're here one minute,
and then we're gone the next.
You should know that
better than anybody.
If you keep living
trying to protect yourself,
nothing is ever gonna touch you.
Sweets said that it's not his job
to tell somebody what they're feeling
or how they should live their life.
Lucky thing I'm not a shrink.
The bottles were counterfeits.
- Counterfeit?
- Even though the design was the same,
the glass found in the cask had
a lower concentration
of dolomite and magnesium dioxide
than the real Bedford Creek bottles.
Someone's been counterfeiting
Bedford Creek Cabernet.
A bottle of Bedford Creek
sells for over a hundred bucks.
So if someone fills counterfeit
bottles with cheap wine
and ships out a couple thousand
cases saying it's from Bedford Creek,
- they could make some serious money.
- Exactly.
Now, I also found
that the arsenic compound
I thought was from the stain
contains parathion.
We don't know what that means.
It's an organophosphate
used as an insecticide.
The only vineyard in the area licensed
to use it by the EPA is Dunwood Winery.
Charles Dunwood.
We found cases of this
in your warehouse.
You were counterfeiting
Bedford Creek wine.
You charged a hundred dollars
for a three-dollar wine.
The stupid wine snobs,
they don't even know the difference.
But Holt did.
He found out, didn't he? He was...
going to tell Mortenson.
It was none of Holt's business.
I told him to stay out of it.
I need the money to fight
Mortenson's bogus lawsuits.
I wasn't gonna let that
bastard take my place.
My family's been there
for over 80 years.
Is this man a complete dunce?
God.
Booth, what is it?
Why doesn't he just clam up
and ask for a lawyer?
You, sir, are a boob!
Some people, they just feel remorse,
and they
want to set the record straight.
Please! He makes wine a homeless
person wouldn't cook with.
He never felt remorse about that.
Nobody asked you.
- Who are you talking to?
- What's going on?
Nothing, just, go on.
I followed him to Mortenson's.
He had one of the bottles.
It was late and...
And you cornered him in the wine cellar
and beat him to death to shut him up.
Blah, blah, blah. We know.
Will you shut up? Shut up!
Booth, who are you talking to?
So, are you gonna let her have
this baby alone?
- I didn't say that.
- You are!
You're going to abandon your child!
Night's deepest gloom
washes over my tiny frame.
No, I can't away. I never said that, OK?
Do you understand?
I can't walk away. This is my kid.
If I can't be involved,
I don't want her to have the baby.
And the sun shines again!
Good man, Boothie!
- What the hell's going on here?
- You shut up and don't move.
You're coming with me.
Wait! Stop!
You're leaving a helpless
child alone with a killer! Stop!
- What is going on?
- I can't do it.
Listen, I have to be involved.
If I'm the father, then...
I have to be a father.
You were seeing something in
there, what were you seeing?
Stewie, you know,
the baby from The Family Guy.
You, you saw Stewie... in there?
In the interrogation room?
- So, what do you say about the kid?
- Fine, I won't have a baby.
That's it?
No, it doesn't matter now,
we're going to the hospital.
- It's no big deal, OK?
- It is.
Booth, you thought
you saw Luc Robitaille
and then the ghost of a dead friend
and now a cartoon baby.
Trust me, something is wrong.
Trust me.
They should've
the CAT scan results now.
They're getting a second opinion.
Then the other doctor
should've been standing by.
- Are you all right, Sweets?
- No, no, I'm not.
I'm not the level-headed
shrink at the moment.
I'm just the guy
whose friend is in trouble,
and I'm having a hard time
dealing with it. Okay?
I'm sorry.
I just need a moment.
Sure.
Man, just when you think
you know what's what.
Man, we can't take anything
for granted, can we?
Why is it so easy to forget that?
Ange, when we split,
either one of us could've stopped it.
- It would've been easy.
- I know.
It'd be just as easy...
to begin again.
They think it's a cerebellar
pilocytic astrocytoma.
God, that sounds bad.
Brain tumor.
It's usually benign.
Usually.
They're prepping him
for surgery now.
So fast.
- They didn't want to take any chances.
- Go.
He shouldn't be alone
before he goes in there.
I just wanted all of you to know...
statistically, he should be fine.
This isn't about me.
The surgery should take about
two hours.
I was getting used to hallucinating.
I get lonely.
You're gonna be fine, Booth.
Dr. Jurzik is one of the best.
Would you come in there with me,
to the operating room?
No, I'll see you in Recovery.
What are you gonna do,
sit in the waiting room
and read all those old
magazines for hours?
I'm not a neurologist, Booth,
or a surgeon.
Yeah, but you're a genius.
That's good enough for me.
Plus, you'll know
if they're screwing up.
I'll ask.
I'll let you know
when we're ready for that... thanks.
Let me just take a look.
Excuse me.
Can we stop for a second?
Can you just
give me a minute, please?
What's wrong?
Listen, Bones, if I don't make it...
- Booth, you're gonna be fine.
- Yeah, but if I'm not...
I want you to have my stuff.
You know, for our kid.
I want you to.
You're gonna be a really good mom.
You're gonna be fine, Booth.
I'll be right here.
I'm ready.
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--