All right, Cadets, listen up.
What I am cradling
lovingly in my arms
is an M203 40-millimeter
canister launcher.
What's it for?
- Cadet Williams.
- Tear gas.
That's right. That...
is a meth lab,
our boys took it three days ago.
- How do you think they did that?
- Tear gas.
Wrong!
And that is why we are here.
I'm gonna demonstrate for you
why we don't
fire tear gas into a meth lab.
We're gonna need a...
a fire extinguisher.
Then... maybe some sort of
trauma counselor.
Hey, I'm sorry I'm late.
Well, according to Sweets, chronic
lateness is a way of asserting control.
- That's right.
- So, you believe that?
No, I figured there was traffic
or something kept you at work.
Exactly: work... work, Bones.
Okay, I was putting
the final touches on a case
that's about to propel me
into FBI legendary status.
Ah, the big RICO case that...
I'm not supposed
to know anything about.
- Why don't I know about this case?
- Bones, it's top secret.
But you told Dr. Brennan.
She's my partner, OK?
Indictments any minute,
followed by a pay raise,
possible parade and most
definitely my face on a coin.
- Just in time for your birthday.
- Which I will be spending in...
Hawaii. Look at that.
- Shark adventures.
- Sharks.
Oh, I really wish that
you wouldn't... answer your phone.
Jared? Oh, God, give me that.
- That's his brother.
- Booth has a brother?
Sounds good. I'll see you then.
Don't feel bad.
I've never met him, either.
At least you knew he existed.
Okay, that's enough for today,
because obviously you have to go
look at some horribly dismembered...
human remains.
Any idea how the body got in there?
I guess anyone could have done
it anytime in the last three days.
Male, 45 to 50 years old.
Where the rest of the remains are?
One leg is over there, the other's
over there, and the arm is over there.
- Did I kill this man?
- No.
Okay.
This man was shot in the chest.
Would you be at all upset
if I had a little cry?
Yeah, take your time.
What's that there on
the inside of his pocket?
This man was obviously some kind of
technical designer or engineer.
Squint? One of your own.
Bones - Season 04 Episode 09
"The Con Man in the Meth Lab "
TS: ydy.com
Synchro: ShalimarFox, IceFreak
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
So,these are from the notebook
found in our victim's windbreaker?
Blueprints, schematics, sketches.
Automatic toilet scrubber.
It's like those little vacuum
cleaners that move around on their own.
Things in a toilet bowl
should not move.
Look at this. This is a...
a snow shovel with an
attached heating device.
Our victim was an inventor.
Clark, hey.
Oh, God,here we go.
Really, you came back?
You said you didn't want
to work with us anymore.
No, I said my preferred working
style tends towards the professional.
See my tie?
That's an indicator.
So why'd you come back then?
Because this is the finest
forensics facility in the world.
You want to fight MiGs,
you fly MiG Alley, right?
A Korean War reference?
You do know that we have
a brand-new war, right?
It's... been in the news.
Hey, I got a form letter
here from the patent office.
Good work.
Aren't you the least bit curious about
Hodgins and I are back together or not?
And... not work.
Am I the only one that can
tell the difference here?
- Is there a name on that letter?
- No.
There's a patent application number.
We can find out who filed it.
Coleoptera just started feeding
on the Diptera larva,
meaning our victim died
about three days ago.
Thank you.
Aren't you impressed that Angela and
I can still work together so well?
There's no obvious exit wound.
That suggests a.22- or.25-caliber.
I'll keep my eyes open.
Multiple points of possible antemortem
in-bending with concomitant fracture.
These abrasions are patterned.
Repeated blows with
a perforated surface?
Camille?
Jarhead.
It's really you.
Jarheads are Marines. I'm a
lieutenant commander in the Navy.
Not an acceptable mistake.
He's getting so big.
Soon he'll be wanting a later
curfew and a car of his own.
Jared, this here is my partner,
Dr. Temperance Brennan.
That back there is a squint.
This is my little brother.
- Bones.
- Dr. Brennan.
Oh, it is nice to meet you, Jarhead.
I can see the family resemblance.
Your facial structure is
even more symmetrical than Booth's.
- Is she coming on to me?
- No, that's just the way she talks.
Right.
So, the Pentagon?
You're looking at the new head
of Strategic Plans and Policy.
Basically, he runs the place.
So, Cam, Jared has a
favor he'd like to ask.
- I can ask my own favors, Seeley.
- Okay, go ahead.
There's a cocktail party tonight.
I'm in need of a beautiful woman on
my arm, preferably a very smart one.
- I'm quite intelligent.
- No.
Not that you're not intelligent.
I mean, you are intelligent.
I would be delighted.
I got a hit
on the patent application.
It was filed by somebody
named Paul Stegman.
I've got an address there...
There's more than one Booth?
I'm Angela. Montenegro.
Jared Booth.
Okay, Jared, Bones and
I have to work on a case, so...
Yeah, no problem, I will grab a
cab and get settled into my new place.
Okay.
It was very nice to meet you all.
And Cam, I will pick you
up at your place, say, 7:00.
Sounds good.
Are you thinking of
leaving lesbianism behind?
I prefer not to be labeled, okay?
Well, since you were last here,
Angela ran into her ex-girlfriend,
who is now her ex-ex-girlfriend.
Well, the only "ex" I care about are
X-rays.
- Right.
- Apologize for the pun.
Yeah...
don't give up your day job, kid.
Okay, Bones, what do you say we
go solve a murder? Come on.
The remains are those of
a man in his 50s. Bearded.
5'10", approximately 195 pounds.
That matches the
description of my father.
Was the victim wearing a blue
windbreaker with yellow piping?
Yeah, that...
that's my windbreaker.
He borrowed it, Paul.
One of your notebooks must
have been in the pocket.
- When was the last time you saw him?
- Three days ago.
Was he drunk?
- He used to go on binges.
- Honey.
How often did your father
go on these drinking binges?
- We don't really know.
- Jim had just come back into our lives.
He said he quit drinking.
He walked out on me and
my mom when I was a kid.
His father wrapped his car
around a tree drunk driving.
- Paul was injured, and so was his mom.
- He broke both his legs.
As soon as he got crutches,
he was gone.
How did he find you?
There was an article
about me in this magazine.
Dad read it,
called me, said he had cleaned up
his act, wanted to reconnect,
so we invited him to stay with us.
Did your father have
any run-ins recently?
Was my father murdered?
We think it may be foul play, yes.
Mrs. Stegman?
The day before your father
disappeared, I came home from school...
I teach fifth grade.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
I saw Mike leaving the
house. He looked upset.
- Who's Mike?
- Mike Campbell.
We used to be business
partners. We're still friends.
Your dad said he caught Mike
taking something from your workshop.
Yeah, we loan each other
tools all the time.
I mean, I bet Dad just
didn't understand that.
Well, I'm gonna need Mike's number.
So is it true that
you borrowed his tools?
What? I didn't borrow anything.
Well, then, Mr. Campbell, what were
you doing at the Stegman house?
- I went to confront his dad.
- About what?
When I get stuck on
one of my projects,
I like to do
a little off-track betting.
Making predictions based on
statistical models clears my head.
- Makes complete sense.
- Yeah...
So, that day, I go
in, and there's Paul's dad.
He's placing bets and
taking hits off of a flask.
Indicating that hadn't
really stopped drinking.
I confronted him, then the old geezer
slammed me against a walland
told me to mind my own business.
- So, then, you left?
- That's right.
Look, then he disappeared,
so I figured,
why should I spoil
Paul's last memories of his old man?
Your inventions are much more
industrial than Paul Stegman's.
Yeah, that's why we
stopped being partners.
Paul's more into toys and gadgets.
Oh, that is part of a
pressurized industrial sieve.
Its application's in
the sewage industry.
This grating could have caused
the damage to Jim's face.
- Did you catch the murderer?
- We subpoenaed
a possible murder weapon.
Not a bad day's work.
More important than catching a
murderer, I'm dateless tonight.
What happened to Cam?
Oddly, I think it's more
important to catch this murderer.
I'm working.
- So, who else you got for me, Seeley?
- What am I? Your pimp?
- Don't think I'm not appreciative.
- Clark has everything
- under control so I could go.
- What?
Really? Thank you.
- No.
- Wha... what... what, wait.
This... is Bones, right?
Not some ugly FBI
woman with a moustache.
- I don't have a moustache, Jared.
- Seeley, would you mind?
No. Why would I mind?
It's all right.
Which means this is a
great time to hang up.
What did you find?
It's what I didn't
find that's interesting.
- You have got to be kidding me.
- What?
Oh, nothing.
Nothing, nothing, Dr. Brennan.
I just, didn't know
that you were so...
The murder victim was supposed
to be a long-term heavy drinker, yet,
his bones show no signs
of alcoholic osteoporosis.
There's no damage to the cancellous
structure of the long bones either.
Furthermore, he was supposed
to have broken his legs
in a car accident
approximately 25 years ago.
There's no signs of remodeling.
No. These legs were never broken.
We misidentified the victim.
He is not Paul Stegman's father.
Thank you, General. Appreciate it.
Will you gentlemen
excuse me for one second?
- Champagne?
- Thank you.
Don't tell me you're sorry you came.
No, not at all.
It is not often that
I get to observe people
this powerful
in a relaxed situation.
Don't be fooled.
It's a school of piranhas in here.
You're good at this.
They listen to you when you speak.
You want to know the secret?
You have an incredibly beautiful,
incredibly intelligent scientist,
slash-novelist
sitting alone waiting for you
to bring her a drink.
That is too corny.
Definitely.
I was thinking how Booth would
be bored at a function like this.
This kind of event would
make Seeley very nervous.
I don't mean he's incapable.
My brother's very, very capable.
It's just... it's like
Seeley's afraid of success.
He stays in his comfort zone.
It drove our dad nuts.
- Really?
- That's what made him a good sniper.
He doesn't like to be visible above the
ridge line, so he keeps his head low.
Instinct.
Me, on the other hand, well,
I cannot help but run that ridge.
Can you give me an example?
I bet you
Seeley never took that risk.
Nope.
- To a good night?
- Yes. So far.
I found a match for our victim's
DNA on the felony database.
Have you seen
Bones yet this morning?
No, I think she and
Jared had a late night.
Open the attachment I just sent you.
Okay, Anthony Pongetti.
Multiple fraud convictions.
That's our victim.
Right, so...
Pongetti pretends to be Stegman.
Why?
Reads that article on the inventor and
figures there's something to cash in on?
You know,
Bones never gets in this late.
You're the one who said you didn't
mind them going out together.
Bye.
Special Agent Booth.
Wow, look at that: a full
colonel from State Police.
Ryan Wolchuck. Mind if I sit?
No, please, have a seat. If this is
about the RICO investigations,
I've been keeping you guys in
the loop, just like I promised.
I'm here about the meth lab body.
Okay.
It's extremely embarrassing
for the state police
that this homicide victim was
blown up during a training exercise.
And the superintendent, the governor,
various movers and shakers
would look kindly on it if you...
Well, if you simply neglected to
give that small detail to the press.
And if the press digs up
that the bodies
were burned and blown
into several pieces,
that makes the FBI look sneaky.
Well, the FBI is sneaky.
Right.
Not today, sir.
Careers are made when men of
good intent help each other.
I'll tell you what:
why don't we just tell the truth
and take our lumps when we have to.
No signs of remodeling.
Did you just get in?
I haven't been to sleep.
Can I offer you a little insight
into Booth's little brother?
Oh, God, why am I always standing
precisely in the wrong place?
I didn't have sex with him, Cam.
- Didn't have sex with who?
- Jared Booth.
Good!
- Why good?
- Because... because...
Because he's Booth's little brother
and it would just be a creepy
way to have sex with a Booth
without having sex with the real Booth.
Kudos, Angela. I would not have
had the guts to say that out loud.
No, Jared is a real Booth.
Jared's Booth Lite.
Booth is the real Booth.
Well, what if Booth is Booth Lite?
Angela found the real Jim Stegman.
Where?
Here.
In the Jeffersonian cold storage.
Only,
he's known as John Doe 100803.
Looks like a drowning victim.
Only if he drowned after
being shot in the heart.
- How did you find him?
- The real Jim Stegman has DNA on file
stemming from an assault charge
12 years ago.
I ran a search, and this popped up.
He's been a John Doe right here in
the Jeffersonian since last week.
Washed up
at Anacostia Naval Station.
Last known address: Bowie, Maryland.
Well, this is Jim Stegman's place.
Landlord says nobody's been
in here since he went missing.
This guy has gone missing
twice and nobody reports it.
You say Jim ended up shot
and dumped in the river?
That's right. Shot and dumped.
Old Jim did not deserve that ending.
What, with quit drinking
and quit betting.
Well, it looks like he fell
off the, gambling bandwagon.
No sign of booze anywhere. Here.
- Booth.
- Yeah?
One of these is made
out to Anthony Pongetti.
Pongetti?
That old boy is another
whole other earful of wax.
- Bad egg?
- Black-hearted son of a bitch, yeah.
Had him in custody, two months ago.
- For what?
- Running a bogus roof repair company.
He'd give an estimate, and
take a deposit, then skedaddle.
Mind I ask what's going
on here in my own town?
Yeah, the real Jim Stegman,
he was shot,
killed and dumped
in the river a week ago.
Pongetti shot and killed
four days ago.
After pretending to be Jim Stegman.
Sounds like maybe Pongetti killed Jim
and then committed,
whatch a macallit, identity theft.
I'm in trouble. Jared
Yeah, thanks. Bones, you know what?
I gotta get you back to the lab, okay?
Thanks, Sheriff.
Paul Stegman had 66 inventions
in his notebook
and this one was marked with a star.
All it needed
was a little more torque.
Yeah, well,
if the gears can handle it.
Clark, I was wondering if you
had a chance to look at the...
Is this one of Stegman's inventions?
Yeah. It's a garbage sorter.
And thanks to Clark, it works.
I only indulged in this,
diversion after he asked for help.
I wasn't wasting time.
I came in for the...
The grating you got
from Mike Campbell
was not the weapon used to strike
Anthony Pongetti in the face.
The zygomatic bones were fractured.
This screen,
while it resembles stainless steel,
is actually a rather
malleable magnesium alloy.
So, for it to cause
that much damage...
Yes, it would have been
bent from the impact.
Yes.
So, what we're looking
for is something heavier.
Jared Booth, US Navy,
Lieutenant Commander, over.
Copy, notify.
We'll stand by for transport.
You all right?
I fell asleep at the wheel,
but I'm okay.
Yeah, fell asleep.
Local trooper here
says he knows you.
Agent Booth.
Colonel Wolchuck.
Is that what we're going with here?
He fell asleep at the wheel?
I'm sure you'll agree it's best
just to tell the truth,
take our lumps when we have to.
They get me for DUI,
I lose my job, Seeley.
- I mean, I lose my whole career.
- Shut up.
Shut up. Please.
- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah.
The first body you found wasn't
my father, but the second was?
So, the man we actually met,
the one who said
he was Paul's father...
Was not. That's correct.
This Pongetti guy,
did he kill my father?
- We don't know that yet.
- Were we in danger?
- Well, Anthony Pongetti was...
- He was harmless.
He was a con man. That's all.
Did Pongetti leave anything behind?
Luggage or papers?
He left a duffle bag in
the coat closet over there.
Let's check it out.
What did this man want from us?
We think it's possible
that he wanted to...
profit off of your inventions.
He'd be the first one
that ever did then.
Don't do that to yourself.
Look at this thing.
Man, what is this thing, a robot?
That's a battery-operated
electrostatic dust trap.
I gave up on it months ago.
Uh, it's... hold on.
That's not supposed to be in there.
Oh, what is that?
Oh, my God.
20 grand, give or take.
Do we get to keep that?
- He wasn't even really your father.
- So what?
That is the best motive
we've seen yet for murder yet.
Right there.
My name is Colonel Ryan Wolchuck
of the State Police Bureau
of Criminal Investigations.
I have the great pleasure of
announcing today that
the grand jury has handed down 62
indictments following the State Police
crackdown on organized crime.
This victory
is the result of a six-month RICO
investigation by our department.
The State Police would like to
acknowledge the
very fine support work
of several FBI field officers...
Yeah, support.
Hey, Cam, what's up?
What's so urgent?
Your people found a
fingerprint on the bag of money.
I know. W-We don't have an ID.
What... why is that so urgent?
What's going on?
What happened?
I watch TV. State Police getting
all the glory for that big RICO case?
- What the hell?
- Relax
Okay, it's political.
It came down way far
above my head. Right?
Don't you lie to me, big
man. I'm your friend.
I know where this came from,
and it wasn't from on high.
Cam, let this one slip by.
You must be Agent Booth's brother.
Yeah, I'm Jared. You FBI?
FBI. Uh, yeah, yeah. Lance Sweets.
Nice to meet you.
Capitals?
Yeah, I know Seeley's a Flyers
man, but, hey, when in Rome, right?
Please.
Yeah, I still haven't gotten
him anything for his birthday.
Oh, my brother doesn't
like birthday presents.
Anyways, these are more
like a "thank you."
Or an apology.
You know what it's like
with brothers, right?
No. Only child.
Well, having a big brother is like
having an extra dad,
only a dad who protects you
from your real dad.
And always thinks of you as a kid.
I have the same problem with Booth.
There is nothing worse than somebody
who always thinks they're right
and then they're right.
- Right?
- Yeah.
It's a pleasure, Agent Sweets.
Doctor, not Agent.
Jim Stegman was shot four times.
I postulate that each gunshot
was both precise and deliberate
and did not occur in a
rapid-fire succession.
There's no way to tell
that from the bones.
Not from the bones.
Close-range injuries.
Middle of the foot,
middle of the knee,
middle of the shoulder,
dead center on the heart.
Small-caliber weapon.
You believe this
was done on purpose.
Yes. Torture.
Someone was trying to get
information from this man.
Pure conjecture, Dr. Edison.
But it has logical integrity.
So, three years ago, Stegman and
Pongetti, they were arrested.
- They were working some scam together.
- We already knew they were accomplices.
There was a third guy involved.
They ratted him out.
- He went to jail for five years.
- Five-year sentence,
three years with parole.
Is the stool out?
No, you mean "stoolie," and the
third guy wasn't the stoolie.
Stegman and Pongetti were, okay?
You go in there, I'll be in here.
Steve Jackson.
What the hell are you wearing?
I'm on parole. They won't
let me work on Wall Street.
Of course, I'd make less there.
- What's this about?
- Stegman and Pongetti.
Parole officer already told
me to stay away from 'em.
But you didn't stay away
from them. Did you, Steve?
- Fine. I met with Stegman.
- Why?
He was making amends,
apologizing, in the program.
One small parole violation
and the FBI gets involved?
Stegman and Pongetti are both dead.
- You got to be kidding.
- Shot.
It's okay, you can take a moment
to rejoice
in the death of your enemies.
Go ahead.
Pongetti's dead, good.
I'm glad.
Stegman... he was okay.
He ratted you out.
Pongetti ratted me out.
Stegman backed him is all.
I don't begrudge.
I got an alibi anyway.
I didn't tell you when they died.
Tracking device.
Somebody somewhere knows where I am
24 hours a day since
I got out for the next two years.
- Do you think he did it?
- No, we'll check his whereabouts,
but, you know, I don't think so.
Nice hat, huh? Come on. I'll
take you back to the lab.
What happened with your RICO bust?
Nothing. Why?
- Have you been talking to Cam?
- No. Did you do something wrong?
What do you mean?
You didn't get
the credit you deserve.
- What'd you do?
- Life's not always about credit.
That's not what you said before.
You said life was all about credit
and you were going to Hawaii
and they were gonna put
you on a coin.
Let's just forget about it.
Okay, Bones? Forget about it.
Jared warned me that you
tend to sabotage yourself.
Jared said that?
He said that you're
afraid of success.
So basically I'm a loser.
No, he never said the word "loser."
Do you think I'm a loser
like that guy in there...
some clown in some dumb-ass uniform
who basically can't do any better?
Is that what you think?
Anthropologically, males tend to
rank themselves into a hierarchy.
There's no shame in not being
at the top of the hierarchy.
You're not answering the
question, Bones. Answer my question.
Booth.
Your forensic techs got an ID for
the fingerprint on the money bag.
Is it Stegman or Pongetti?
Stegman, but not the
one you're thinking of.
The son?
Nope, the wife.
The fingerprint belongs
to Lily Stegman.
Thanks. The fingerprints
belong to Lily Stegman.
We know that because
she works with kids.
She acted like she'd never
seen that money before.
Well, she was lying.
Bones, let's just
go and do our work.
I thought he was Paul's father.
I would never hurt him.
We found your
fingerprints on the money.
Can you explain that?
I'm ashamed.
Well, whatever you're ashamed
of, believe me, murder is worse.
The day after Jim...
The man we thought was Jim...
The day after he disappeared,
a package arrived for him.
When he didn't come back, I started
to think he meant for us to open it.
That doesn't make any sense.
No, I understand. He's
gone, it's sitting there.
Maybe he meant for you to have it.
Yes.
Plus... you have a family to take care
of. We do whatever we can for family.
I opened it, it was full of cash.
And...
A note.
"Jim, do me a big favor.
"Hold on to this until I
can get it back from you.
Help yourself to
whatever you need, P."
"P"... Pongetti.
I know I should have called
the police, and...
when you came I should have told you,
but by then...
You needed the money,
and in a way, you felt like you earned
it for taking that old man in.
Family.
My teaching salary barely
pays the bills,
and we're trying
to have another child.
So you were the one that hid
the money in the dust trap thing?
Yes.
- What does your husband know?
- Nothing, I promise.
She could just be protecting him.
I am, by not letting him know
about the money you found...
or the...
rest of it.
- The rest of it?
- There's more?
Yes, I put it into our
safety deposit box.
Okay, how much?
$150000...
So I figure what happened is that
Pongetti got his cash in some,
you know, illegal way,
maybe in a way that
could get him killed.
Stegman... He's about
to go visit his son.
So Pongetti sends the cash
to his friend for safety.
Then Stegman gets killed,
so to go get that cash,
Pongetti decides to pretend
to be Stegman.
People make stupid,
irrational decisions.
Brennan.
They act from the heart
sometimes, Bones. It's not a crime.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Cam needs me.
Hello.
Dr. Brennan.
I don't want you to think
this is an intervention.
I don't know what that means.
An intervention is when
a group of loved ones
bands together to help one of their own
make a difficult decision.
Oh, then,
then it is an intervention.
Are you my loved ones?
I was...
troubled by a conversation
I had with Jared Booth.
Sweets came to me with
some theories about
Booth's family life,
and he pretty much nailed it.
- Nailed what?
- Sit down.
Booth and Jared are children
of a physically abusive,
alcoholic father.
Booth's been digging Jared out
of trouble since they were kids.
Jared always comes up smelling
like a rose and Booth takes the hit.
He's denying his brother the opportunity
to take responsibility and learn
from his own mistakes.
You have no evidence of that.
I've known the Booth
boys for 15 years.
Now, i-it's natural to be
protective of a younger sibling.
Of course, Jared is a grown man...
an intelligent,
talented, capable adult.
- I like him very much.
- Yeah, well, cut it out.
Booth shouldn't be threatened
by the fact
that his brother is more successful.
I am absolutely certain
that however it is
Booth lost all the credit
for that RICO bust,
it's because of Jared.
We're all scientists here, right?
Not you.
- What is your evidence?
- How about this?
The last time I told Booth
what I thought of Jared,
he didn't speak
to me for six months.
That is an anecdote.
We're saying maybe Booth deserves
the benefit of the doubt here
until all the evidence is in.
Evidence. I am
comfortable with evidence.
Okay, here's some evidence.
The bullets that killed both Stegman and
Pongetti were fired from the same gun.
Which suggests they were killed
by the same person. Thank you.
Should I tell Booth?
No, I'll do it.
Thanks for coming, Jared.
When a beautiful woman
asks me out for lunch...
Something wrong?
I need to know the truth.
I've heard that about you.
Do you know anything about Booth
losing credit on the RICO case?
No. What? I mean, that's
the first I've heard of it.
People are telling me that
somehow all the credit went to
the state police because of you.
Is that possible?
So it is possible.
What did he say to you?
Nothing.
I think this is something
between brothers.
No offense.
- Tempe.
- You took advantage of him.
You know, you made me
think that he's a loser!
And what really makes me
angry is that I believed you.
I wouldn't blame Booth if
he never spoke to me again.
You're the loser!
You all right?
Why didn't you pick up?
Were you in the bathroom or something?
- To be honest, I was discussing...
- Okay. Never mind.
Just never mind, all right?
Agents recovered
the rest of the cash
from Lily Stegman's
safety deposit box, all right?
The bills were bundled
with evidence bands.
What does that mean?
The money is from the county
sheriff's headquarters in Bowie.
- It was confiscated during a drug bust.
- Oh, so drug money?
It was scheduled for transfer to
the Federal Reserve two weeks ago.
A driver from the reserve shows up.
He flashes his credentials,
drives off with the dough.
Forty minutes later,
the real driver shows up.
Oh, so the fake one was Pongetti?
But it had to be. Right? I mean,
jeez, he got away with over 200 grand.
But he was in custody there.
How come no one recognized him?
What? It's a logical question.
No, you know what?
You are a genius.
- Hold on for a second.
- Why am I a genius?
"Why?" Because I let
that big sheriff know
that we found $20,000
in Stegman's house.
Why is that bad?
Because if he was
in it with Pongetti,
then he thinks he knows
where the rest of the money is.
Thinks.
We turned everything
over to the FBI.
All the money, everything
the guy touched.
Well, it's probably just a breakdown
in jurisdictional communication.
I'll check with the FBI.
Why don't you check
with me right now?
Better yet, why don't you
just come with us now?
The grating is what hit
Pongetti in the face.
Old school, huh? Perp was
handcuffed to the back.
You sped up, slammed on the
breaks. Slam, sped, slam, sped...
- He couldn't protect his face.
- No! Stop! Let her go!
Mr. Stegman, take
your little boy inside!
Do it, honey, please.
Now, this is what's going to happen.
You're going to get in
your vehicle and drive away.
I'm gonna do the same thing,
everybody lives and everybody's happy.
Well, that sounds like a good idea.
No, not a good idea.
You drive off with the
evidence? Not going to happen.
Paul! Oh, God!
Agent Booth, you are by far
the worst hostage negotiator
I have ever run into.
Don't you know you're
supposed to talk?
Disorient, distract the perpetrator?
- Booth?
- Not now, Bones.
- You want me to try to shoot him?
- No.
Why? I'm a good shot.
- You are not a good shot.
- Well, you are.
You know, maybe if
we switched weapons,
you could hit him right
between the eyes.
Bones, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Lily!
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
I would like to propose a toast
to my partner, Seeley Booth.
To Booth.
I know who he is,
but I forget sometimes because...
because he never shines
a light on himself.
He shines it on other people.
Yeah, right after I conk
them on the head with it.
Anthropology teaches us that the
alpha male is the man
wearing the crown,
displaying the most colorful
plumage and the
shiniest baubles.
He stands out from the others.
But I now think that
anthropology may have it wrong.
In working with Booth,
I've come to realize that
the quiet man, the invisible man...
the man who is always there
for friends and family...
that's the real alpha male.
And I promise that my eyes
will never be caught by those...
shiny baubles again.
Happy birthday, Booth.
Happy birthday.
Thanks, Bones. Thank you.
Oh, Bones, all right,
what are we doing?
- Come here.
- What?
Just come here for a second.
What you're doing for
your brother isn't fair.
Come on, Bones. Don't get me mad
at you after that great speech.
All right, not after I got you shot.
You didn't get me shot.
I got me shot.
You know what, I don't want
to talk about my brother.
Would you prefer Sweets do it?
I'm listening.
I forgot all the psychological
stuff, but basically...
when you rescue somebody all the time,
if you keep
- getting them out on bail...
- Bail them out, Bones.
If you bail them out.
You're thwarting their
ability to help themselves.
Now you're angry.
Come on, you have to admit, getting
a psychology lesson from you is like
Getting an anthropology
lesson from you?
The RICO case...
I traded my one shot at glory to
keep my brother from being arrested.
For drunk driving.
You know, what if he does it again?
What if he kills someone next time?
You shouldn't have done that.
Right, says the woman
who got her father
off murder charges.
Face it.
We do things for family.
You're right. You're totally right.
No, I'm not.
What? Why?
There's no risk that your
father will kill again.
Jared?
You, uh, bringing me out here to
give me advice on your partner
because I think
that ship has sailed?
No, no, it's, uh...
What I gotta do here, I...
I gotta stop.
Do you understand?
- "Stop"?
- Yeah. And you should stop, too.
I gotta stop what?
The drinking. Stop it.
I'll take that under advisement.
Seriously, Jared.
No more stepping in
to make things go away.
I carry my own water, Seeley.
Now, you should go back inside
and enjoy your birthday party.
Right.
- Cheers.
- Yeah. Happy birthday to me.
You going to come back in for cake?
Bones, I just need
some time, that's all.
Do you need time and space?
Just some time.
My dad drank.
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--