I can't hear you...
The reception's bad out here.
Aliens? I told you, baby,
I'm done hunting aliens.
I... am on the road.
Yeah, in Florida.
What? No, I'm in my hotel room
working late.
You're just gonna have to trust me.
Yeah. Well... I'm sorry
that's the way you feel.
A souvenir from Florida.
Babe, I can't take a...
like, a list right now.
Well, there are no pens...
Or pads in this hotel.
Oh, my god!
Babe! I found one.
No, not a pen...
An alien.
A real one.
Oh, my god, I gotta
get a picture of this.
What's that?!
Baby... There's more of 'em.
I come in peace.
I'm... Marvin Breekman,
but you can call me Marvin.
Or Marv.
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
I made reservations at the club.
Deejay Spider tonight,
then, back to my place?
I'm not sure
if I can wait for tonight.
Okay, I was fine
until you just said that.
You know, I have a key
to the Egyptian storage room.
Not on campus, not at work.
Come on, are you really
as virtuous as you seem?
I can be very bad
when the time is right.
We do geta generous lunch break,
and there's a little hotel
a few blocks from here.
Dr. Saroyan,
I was just asking Angela
if she could do
some 3-d modeling of a...
shattered femur that I was given
by the archeology DPT.
Save it, Mr. Bray. You think you have
the big secret, but you don't.
I thought we were being subtle.
Man, do you think Hodgins knows?
Can you imagine if we found
an alien... A real one?
You mean someone who slipped illegally
into the country from Mexico or Canada?
Come on, you don't believe that there're
other real life-forms out there?
Well, the probability is very high,
but any aliens visiting this planet
would have sufficient intelligence
not to die
in the middle of the desert.
FBI special agent Seeley Booth.
This is Dr. Temperance
Brennan from the Jeffersonian.
Sheriff Jerry Bonds, but you probably
got that from my shiny badge,
my imposing gun, and my big hat.
- Right.
- Remains are over there.
They're right over there.
Been there for a while.
Looks like an alien to me.
Judging by the pelvic inlet
and the pubic symphysis...
Female, maybe 30 years old.
Earth female?
Body moisture was trapped
by this silver coat
she's wearing, turning some
of her fat into adipocere.
I have no idea why it's so hard.
Didn't even dig a shallow grave.
Just left her here to be eaten.
Which is the smartest possible
way to get rid of human remains.
- What the hell is going on here now?
- Easy.
- FBI. Put the shotgun down, ma'am.
- This is my land.
I've got a right to protect my land.
Yeah, Marsha,
but we got a dead body.
- A woman, seems like.
- Great.
- Now I've got dead people.
- You don't know anything about this?
I want the remains brought back
to the Jeffersonian for examination.
Not going to happen. My jurisdiction,
my body. She stays here.
No, FBI has got jurisdiction on
this case. You want it, right?
The FBI will keep you apprised.
FBI's got jurisdiction
only if I agree.
Otherwise, you need to jump
through several legal hoops,
which will take some time,
during which the victim stays in town.
- Then why did you call us?
- I could use the help,
but I'm not going to take
the heat when people scream
I sent an alien off to
Washington for secret testing.
I've been through that before.
These remains are
not extraterrestrial.
- It's a cell phone.
- You hope.
Bones - Season 5 Episode 11
"The X in the File"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Dark_Chii
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
I trace the cell phone
to the guy who found the remains.
I'm holding him
on trespassing charges.
This is part of our hospital
that got shut down.
It's a perfect place
to examine the remains.
I need to send samples
back to the lab.
Yeah, but the,
the big body part stays here.
Now, the remains are in here,
and, Mr. Breekman's at my office
if you want to come with me,
agent Booth.
Ma'am.
You're going to be okay here
all alone in this spooky hospital
with a dead alien body?
Right... That would be me
who wouldn't want that.
The remains are encased
in adipocere.
If it's OK with sheriff Lobo,
maybe you could send me some.
It appears to be petrified.
A coat alone doesn't account
for that.
I'll send the coat to Hodgins,
see what he can discern from it.
Her skeletal robusticity and large areas
of muscle attachment suggest
extremely good health.
A couple weeks in the desert,
and no critters got at these remains?
Perhaps the result of green radiation
from alien hyperdrive systems?
Or something not crazy.
The man who found them remarked
that he saw several sets of orange eyes
staring at him from the darkness.
Orange-eyeballed aliens?
Tapetum lucidum of the american
coyote glows orange
when light strikes the retina.
What he saw were likely coyotes,
not orange-eyeballed aliens.
You were being facetious.
That's funny.
Wearing your earpiece,
he can't hear me,
so I can help you
with your interrogation.
Some people who chase UFOS
believe in alien abductions.
Now, these people tend to be
dreamy, highly suggestible,
and possess a strong belief
that there is something
larger than them out there,
something that they can't control.
I only found the body.
I didn't make it dead.
Okay, that's
very dissociative language:
"make it dead. "
So, you were abducted
by aliens 5 years ago?
If the aliens are so advanced,
why would they need probes?
I think they like it.
Why would you hook up with aliens
if they like to anally probe you?
There are two races of aliens
and they do not see eye to eye.
Right.
I know things.
I get laughed at, but I persist
because I know things.
It just seems like maybe I deserve
a little respect for that.
All right, of course.
I apologize.
Okay, then, can I go home?
Why were you in the desert
last night?
I was looking for UFOS.
No, I mean to that specific area.
What are the chances
of you stumbling across a body in the...
dark...
the vastness...
... vastness of, of the desert?
You really want me to believe that's
some kind of big coincidence?
Yes, it, it was a coincidence.
I don't believe you.
I think you're lying.
Sometimes I think you just pull me
into these interrogations to show off.
Wait, booth, I...
Until you tell the truth,
you know what?
You're not going home.
You have something on your mind?
This thing
that we have going here...
You're worried about Cam knowing?
I'm worried about
Hodgins not knowing.
Listen...
Hodgins and I are in the past.
I mean, if you were really,
totally in the past,
we wouldn't be keeping
this a secret from him.
- Do you want me to tell Hodgins?
- If you don't mind, I'd like to do it.
He's my friend.
A man-to-man, look-him-
In-the-eye kind of thing?
Yeah, something like that.
Let's do it your way.
You mean talk to Hodgins or...?
You're the worst.
Both.
Consider this a do-over.
- Do you know who I am?
- No, do you know who I am?
FBI?
Military intelligence?
That's an oxymoron,
a term that contradicts itself.
I'm Delmy Polanco.
I'm the most important
UFO blogger in the world.
"Important blogger"...
Talk about an oxymoron.
What can you tell me
about the alien body?
I don't know anything it.
Definitely FBI.
I can practically smell the suit.
I don't wear a suit
all the time, you know.
I see you've met Delmy.
I'm looking for info into a foil
wrapped body with alien features,
pieces of which have already been sent
to the Jeffersonian institution.
I'm invoking
the freedom of information act,
you've to tell me
what I want to know.
The freedom of information act
is not a magic spell, Delmy.
It merely gives a citizen the
right to request information.
I'm gonna post all this
on my blog tonight,
and by tomorrow morning, this whole town
will be swarming with UFO nuts.
Trespassing again?
Well, this facility is clearly
marked private property.
Good... You got here
for the good stuff.
- What good stuff?
- MRI.
It's an older model,
but entirely serviceable.
For future reference,
that's not the good stuff.
Sure it is... Look at all those
remodeled lateral malleolus fractures.
Also, signs of inflammation
to the tannin fibers here
and damaged...
I won't say anything about the scream
if you don't say anything about the gun.
Those terms are satisfactory. Right.
That's five.
Too big to be buckshot.
Photos you sent of the first one show
to be a ball bearing approximately
7.5 millimeters.
This makes number six.
Certainly enough metal
to generate the magnetism
to raise the remains
when exposed to the MRI.
When I receive them, I might be able to
i. d. the manufacturer and intended use,
which I imagine was not murder.
I finished the facial reconstruction
off the MRI...
I'm emailing it now.
Sorry... It is not an alien.
I noticed on the MRI that the victim's
patellas were fractured.
Well, I'll swab the area,
and send the samples
with the ball bearings.
Well, there's no striations on the ball
bearings in this photo you sent,
so there's no evidence
that they were shot.
Shotgun, maybe?
Full of ball bearings?
Well, the owner of the ranch
threatened us with a shotgun.
Not so fast, dr. Brennan.
I know you dislike flesh,
but you need to remove the adipocere
and organs to send them to me.
- Dr. Brennan dealing with flesh.
- Like a cat dealing with water.
Flesh is not my strength.
You're going to need a hair dryer
and some cooking spray.
Yep, I've caught her trespassing
on my ranch a bunch of times.
That's el crazerita.
El crazerita.
You know her real name?
Nope. I don't make
friends with these nuts.
Sheriff says you've been charged
with misdemeanor assault with a firearm
about 3 times.
Someone cut through this fence,
agent Booth.
They were trespassers.
Which is why I was never convicted.
- Even though you shot at them?
- Salt.
- Salt?
Rock salt.
Stings like a sumbitch.
Discourages trespassing.
You ever use ball bearings
instead of salt?
Ball bearings?!
That'd rip somebody apart.
Like when you took a shot at,
ol'el crazerita?
You think I killed her?
You think I'm dumb enough
to spend my life in prison
for killing some alienhead nut
who spent all her time
shooting stupid videos?
Videos? Videos of what?
Videos of everything.
Looking for spacemen.
You want to know about her?
Ask Blaine Miller
at the space place cafe.
She was always hanging out
at his diner with the other fruitcakes.
Sure. I'll take a look at your shotgun
there and run some tests.
You know, just to make sure.
- I did it!
- Very good, Dr. Brennan.
Yes, it was.
Now remove the stomach.
She was covered in ethyl
parathion and aldicarb.
It was all over
her space-age outerwear.
It's an insecticide.
It's extremely illegal in the u. s.,
but it's still sold
south of the border.
It explains why the
adipocere dried so quickly.
So, our victim was using
a dangerous insecticide.
Not unusual for someone who's a couple
of tacos short of a combo plate.
- Nice metaphor.
- Thanks.
I found something!
It's a memory card...
Tied to a string.
It appears to be dental floss.
Check her teeth. Any evidence
of floss still on her teeth?
There's a fragment tied
to the left second premolar.
She was hiding the card.
It's an old prison trick.
She tied one end of the floss
to her tooth,
the other end to the memory card,
so if she needed it,
she could use the floss
to pull it up.
I'll overnight the card to Angela.
Whatever is on it
was important enough to hide.
My guess, it's important enough
to kill for.
Man, did you hear?
Brennan's sending the victim's
sd card from Roswell.
Probably video on there the government
wanted suppressed, because at area 51...
Look, do you have a second?
Sure, yeah.
Something wrong?
We're friends, right?
I don't lie or keep things
from my friends.
Okay, all right.
Angela and I...
You're kidding, right?
Go ahead, kid...
Knock yourself out.
Good luck with that.
What I'm trying to tell you
is that my luck has already been good.
I would never want
you to think that I...
Wendell, stop, stop, stop.
It's been over between
her and me for a long time.
I have moved on.
And you know what?
I'm happy for you, you know?
And for her.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
You're both my friends.
Why wouldn't I be happy for you?
I don't...
Thanks, man.
Of course.
I'll tell you what,
why don't the three of us
grab lunch together?
This is a good thing, Wendell,
this should not be weird for us.
Yeah, yeah, sure, lunch.
That sounds great, man.
Great, good, good.
Stomach acid ate away at the card,
but Angela says she should be able
to pull something off of it.
Vinton said el crazerita
shot a lot of video.
Maybe she filmed the real thing.
What, an extraterrestrial?
You said it was possible, all right?
But they have big eyes and big heads,
you know, for the super-smart brain.
That's far more logical
if they had the eyes of flies
and the exoskeleton of a cockroach.
Insect people?
Insects can't fly a spaceship.
Well, the cockroach
is an evolutionary marvel.
They can withstand radiation,
live without breathing for almost
an hour, go without eating for weeks.
Imagine that combined
with an intelligence
that evolved over many millennia.
Plus, they do have extra arms.
Would you look at this place?
This is so cool.
"UFO museum research center. "
Check this out.
Look at those guns.
No way, Bones! Look at this.
Rocketship 7.
I used to watch that
when I was a little boy.
The sweetlees, and there was
Mr. Beeper and Promo the robot.
Well, the way
this craft is designed,
it could never leave
the earth's atmosphere.
Yeah, but according to
Dave Thomas and rocketship 7,
you would go on
adventures like no other.
You two looking for aliens?
The name's Blaine Miller.
Not exactly.
You hear about that body they found up
at Vinton's place?
We never mentioned a body,
mr. Miller.
Nothing travels faster than the speed
of light than gossip in a small town.
Excuse me, sir?
Why are all these radios on?
This is some of the original equipment
that picked up the signal from the craft
that landed right here in Roswell.
Dave, these are the radios
that heard the aliens.
But that's absurd.
Why would she believe you?
They travel all the way to Roswell to
believe in aliens, like everybody else.
Do you recognize this woman,
mr. Miller?
Sure. This is Ursula Lapine.
She's a regular.
She the one who's dead?
- When was the last time you saw her?
- Maybe a month ago.
She was having an argument with a woman.
I had to tell her to keep it down.
- And who was this woman?
- I don't know; I never saw her before.
African-american, good-looking.
In a suit.
Ursula, she live around here?
Outside of town.
She's in one of those shiny,
spaceship-type trailers.
I think I hear something.
I think I hear a spaceship.
She was serious?
This must be the place...
Spacey-looking trailer.
- One of the windows is broken.
- All right.
Stay behind me, Bones.
- Bones, I think you need to see this.
- And you need to see this.
There's blood on it.
Could have been
what busted her knees.
You got to check this out.
She seems very thorough.
The word loony come to mind?
This is a remarkably well-researched
wall for a crazerita.
Crazerita is right.
What about this here? Look.
Check this out.
- Something was taken.
- Maybe that's why she was killed.
This cinder block
was obviously used in an assault.
We have to analyze the blood.
You know what?
Maybe...
we can pull a print
off the block like this.
All right.
Watch this.
This...
That...
is magic.
Science.
Did you have any luck?
- Was the data damaged?
- A bit.
There might still be
a few corrupted frames.
So it's video.
But I think it's gonna play.
My God, is that what I think it is?
And are those...?
Impossible.
This was doctored.
No... it isn't.
This was verified by the scanning
software at a pixel level.
Are you saying our victim might
have stumbled on a real ufo?
Assuming that the figures
in the Hazmat suits are of
average height,
then this structure here must be
about four to five meters tall.
Why is the ground glowing?
The light seems to be
emitting from a spilled liquid.
UFO fuel.
What are those two
humanoid shapes there,
between the Hazmat-suited
humans and the craft?
I'm gonna keep
working on this footage,
but you guys have to
admit that this makes
the hairs on your arm
stand on end, right?
The hairs on my arm
are not reacting in any way.
But thanks.
It's not a spaceship.
If it smells like a duck,
walks like a duck, quacks like a duck...
But then it would be a duck,
not a spaceship,
- so your point escapes me.
- It's a metaphor...
- Have you decided to let me go?
- We have questions.
You ever been out to
Ursula Lapine's trailer?
We have evidence that you're lying.
You fell into that one.
We have your fingerprints
on a cinder block
that was used
to break into her trailer.
Also, blood.
And you took something off her wall.
If I give it to you, will you drop
the trespassing charges and let me go?
If you don't hand it over, I'll just
charge you with obstructing justice,
he'll charge you with interfering
with a Federal investigation...
Maybe even murder...
and you will pray
for the good old days,
where all you were worrying about
were those silly little
trespassing and burglary charges.
I find he's very useful
in certain situations.
Very useful.
So, gonna hand 'em over?
Holy cow.
Pay dirt.
I gotta get better at frisking.
Wait a minute.
This is Ursula with Marvin.
I'm gonna need a copy
for my article:
"UFO-Obsessed Woman
Dies in Alien Encounter."
So the swab from the
victim's damaged patellas
show traces of sediment,
but it's not cement.
What hit her knees
wasn't cinder block?
No, the sediment is gypsum,
dating back to the Pleistocene
and Holocene eras.
It's probably from the Tularosa
or Estancia Basins.
Mexico?!
Northern Mexico is the closest
occurrence of this rock.
It's an interesting
conjunction of possibilities:
the insecticide that she was soaked in,
it's called "Tres Pasitos."
- Not available in the United States.
- Is it available in Mexico?
- Readily.
- Excellent.
So I took the information
that you gave me,
and it looks as though
the projectiles
first impacted next to
the juncture between
the frontal and parietal bones.
The bearings entered beneath her chin,
then ricocheted around in her skull?
Yeah, that seems
to make the most sense.
But I've never heard
of any projectiles
that would enter at that range
and not fracture the skull.
What about, like,
slow-moving projectiles?
Maybe a paintball gun?
A little more powerful
than that, but not much.
Time for lunch.
To prove we're all fine?
You guys can hold
hands, if you want.
Eat off each other's plates...
Any and all of that kind of
gooey romanticism is
completely fine by me.
We know, Hodgins.
I'm not really the public
display kind of guy.
I'm just saying you don't need
to be afraid or...
There. See?
My head did not explode.
I'm not really okay
with being kissed
when it's not about me.
Sorry.
Panicked,
but everything's fine, right?
Everything's fine.
Everything's not fine.
This is a fraught situation.
It's important
to face these things head-on.
There's nothing to face, okay?
We can see why you'd think that, but
we're all fine.
I am... I'm fine.
Lance, your order's ready.
Thanks.
Why are we here?
We want to know what brought you out
here the night you found Ursula's body.
I told you, I was out UFO spotting.
I don't believe
in that big of a coincidence.
How long were you and Ursula lovers?
Go ahead. Take a look.
Oh, my God.
Ursula understood.
She believed.
My wife thought I was crazy.
What makes this patch of desert
any different to you
than any other patch of desert?
This is where we were
when we first saw the lights.
Where did you see the lights?
Beyond those hills.
Hot spheres, very clear.
- Ursula and I saw them together.
- How far?
Maybe two kilometers.
That would be Mexico.
We were going to check it out together
next time I came through town.
We'd meet every few weeks.
- You and Ursula were true believers.
- Not really.
Ursula... she was convinced
that if she could find proof
of alien visitation,
it would make her rich.
What happened to her, Marvin?
Really.
What do you think?
I think she came out here
without me.
Maybe she thought
I wanted half her money.
She maybe saw the lights
and crossed over,
and they took her...
and experimented on her,
and then they dumped her in the desert,
like the heartless scientists they are.
The footage was pretty rough,
as you saw, so I ran an application
to counteract the motion of the
camera with opposite movement.
Then I translated each pixel
of the infrared spectrum
into a pixel
of the visible color spectrum.
Let's see it.
That's a lot more terrestrial
than I expected.
Two tanker trucks,
some sort of digger.
And this is a hose.
What do you think, three inches?
That's the source
of the glowing liquid.
But what about the alien things?
Fremontodendron mexicanum.
It's Mexican flannelbush.
Weird, glowing liquid
in the Mexican desert,
Hazmat suits.
They must've been
dumping chemicals illegally.
She fell.
That must've been where
she fractured her knees.
But she still managed to get away.
You guys see what happened?
She was out looking for UFOS,
but found this instead.
These guys killed her.
You know, I think I liked this
all better when it was aliens.
I was able to clarify the
chemiluminescent signature
of the materials being
dumped in the video.
Manganese and sodium borohydride.
Used in the manufacture of batteries.
Can you get a specific
manufacturer from that?
I did.
Innatron.
Mexican flannelbush is on
the verge of extinction, right?
Innatron has a plant located
smack-dab in the middle
of the last remaining
flannelbush population...
here in Juarez...
and they use manganese
and sodium borohydride.
Dr. Hodgins, I'm kind of
in the middle of...
You were right, Sweets.
Everything is not fine.
It's not fine at all.
This is a good time.
Don't know if I want to crawl
into a hole and die or...
run over Wendell and Angela
with a truck.
You know, it's natural
to have those feelings.
But I'm a better man than this.
I mean, I...
I want to be happy for them.
You know, I really do.
It's easier for us
to accept loneliness,
as long as the person
we were once with
is also alone.
When she finds happiness
with someone else,
man, it's like being stabbed
in the heart.
It's the human condition.
You know, it's why there
are so many movies
and plays and songs and poems.
Yeah, yeah... art, art.
I get it.
What do I do?
Well, first, you need
to figure out what you want.
I want to not be filled
with anger and-and...
pain and resentment.
I don't want to be jealous.
Do you want Angela back?
I don't think you're jealous.
I think that you're grieving
what you've lost.
Grieving?
As in grief?
The only thing
that cures grief is time.
Unless you're recommending
a lot of alcohol.
I can't really recommend alcohol.
Man, that'd be great
if you could, though, right?
I recommend time.
So, just...
smile and act like a good guy?
You are a good guy.
There was a time
that I thought that Angela and I
would be together forever.
- Can I just sit here for a minute?
- Yeah, take all the time you need.
There is nothing
in this video that indicates
what kind of weapon
was used to kill the victim.
Yeah. It's true.
I doesn't look like anybody's armed.
Now, I was able to salvage
some of the audio track.
- That's just white noise.
- I know, but
I scrubbed the background and separated
the different frequencies,
and then I amplified
the resulting file.
Yo estoy encargada.
Y si no lo terminas
antes del amanecer
te arrepentirás.
- That's Spanish.
- Yeah. I know.
We need a translator.
I was a cop and coroner in New
York City, so I speak some.
Can you play that back?
Yo estoy encargada.
Y si no lo terminas antes
del amanecer te arrepentirás.
"I'm in charge.
If you don't get this done
before sunrise, you'll regret it."
Yo estoy encargada.
- She's not from Mexico, though.
- You can tell that?
The way she says "estoy"
and "arrepentirás."
The Puerto Rican cops used to laugh
when I pronounced my "T"s like that.
You think that...
The speaker is definitely American.
Ursula thought she was filming
a UFO crash site?
But she ended up with footage
of an American dumping toxic waste
in the Mexican desert.
- Rachel Adams.
- American?
She's an Innatron executive,
in charge of waste management.
She's based in Juarez, Mexico.
African-American.
The owner of the diner said
that the victim was seen arguing
with an African-American
businesswoman.
We put together a range of weapons
which might fire ball bearings
at a velocity congruent
with the damage done
to the inside of our victim's skull.
We have a paintball gun,
an air rifle, a BB gun,
and a PVC pipe zip gun.
Each modified
to fire six 17.5-millimeter
ball bearings.
Melons lined with paraffin
and filled with
dense agar gelatin,
which mimics skull and brain matter.
What's with the faces?
Well, I guess, I...
kind of got inspired.
Inspired?
All right, goggles, everyone.
Ready?
All right. Okay.
So, the paintball gun ball bearing
didn't have enough force
to get through my skull.
That's too bad.
I'm next.
I'll shoot you.
That was way too much damage.
That blew your head clear off.
I don't know if anyone should
enjoy their work this much.
You and Dr. Saroyan are
still in the running.
I got it.
Not enough force to
kill Dr. Saroyan.
The balls are rattling,
but your head is still intact.
Call that thing by my name
one more time.
I dare you.
- It was a zip gun.
- A perfect,
untraceable, cheap weapon,
easily homemade.
That was fun.
Boys.
You got that right.
Want to do it again?
I have an appointment,
I don't have to answer
your questions.
We follow all of the rules
set forth by the EPA
and environmental restrictions.
On paper.
- I resent that.
- We have witnesses
at Roswell who said that they saw
you arguing with the witness
on the day that she was murdered.
Did your witness tell you
what we were arguing about?
You were trying to buy video
footage Ursula had taken of you
illegally dumping toxic waste.
She thought she had
real footage of a UFO,
unfortunately for you,
she didn't give it up.
I work for a major corporation
that's just signed a billion-
dollar deal with the Mexicans.
You think you can extradite me?
Take your best shot.
- Here comes something.
- What's it say?
It says that Innatron
contracts its waste disposal
to an independent contractor.
Is it owned by a shell company?
Norte Domesticas.
We'll get D.C. on it,
but I'm going to tell you right now, I
already know who owns that company.
Rachel Adams?
Innatron pays the shell company
thousands of dollars
to get rid of the waste,
and her and her crew...
dump it in the desert
and they pocket the money.
Ursula Lapine thinks
she's photographing
extraterrestrial contact,
they catch her, she ends up dead.
Why would she turn down
the money in the diner,
then agree to meet
out in the desert?
Perhaps that's where they agreed
to swap the video for the money.
I guess.
You say,
"Yeah, I guess," but you mean,
"I don't think so."
Rachel lives in Juarez.
I mean, she could get herself
an untraceable gun,
what, in like 15 minutes?
Instead, she shows up
with a homemade zip gun?
That doesn't make sense.
Right?
It's not me.
- It's Booth.
- Listen.
Could we just focus
on the ball bearings?
What about them?
Could you trace them to Innatron?
- How can you be so sure?
- Because they're obsolete.
They were manufactured
in the '40s and the '50s.
For what?
Roller skates, fishing reels,
yo-yos, turntables.
Toys?!
I'm just closing up.
I turned off
about a half an hour ago.
We're not here to eat, Blaine.
Any of these work back here?
The disruptor there
from Gamma-Gamma Six.
Why isn't this solar system working?
'Cause it's 60 years old.
What is with you people?
You overheard Rachel
offering Ursula payoff money,
didn't you, Blaine?
What? No. I didn't.
You told us you had to ask them
to keep it down.
- How come you don't interrupt Bones?
- I'm a gentlemen.
- How much...
- How much did Rachel offer?
Ten grand? 20?
But Ursula thought
that she had proof of alien life.
How much did she ask for?
A million bucks?
You can't just take stuff like that.
You need a warrant.
- I'll get a warrant.
- We don't need a warrant.
We're just playing.
Like the sign says.
I figure what happens is you told her
- you could get her millions.
- You arranged...
You arranged to meet out, told her to
bring the video, you'd bring the buyer.
- He'staking your credit.
- He's talkative.
Can you hand me those ball
bearings there, will you?
Look at that.
- They seem to fit perfectly.
- Come on,
that's just a toy... you couldn't
hurt a flea with that.
That would be the murder weapon.
I got my rights.
You got the right to shut
the hell up.
Killing that poor crazy woman
for her video.
By the way, that video,
it was hid down her throat
on a thread of dental floss,
you moron.
He is a moron.
You are definitely a moron!
Not literally, figuratively.
It's very satisfying to use
an insulting colloquialism
even when it isn't accurate.
It's better when they resist
and you get to hit them.
- I don't know.
- Yeah, I think so.
Do you feel better?
Being open about our relationship?
You bet.
You know, it's over
between Hodgins and me.
I mean, you believe that now, right?
I think everything is always
more complicated than it looks.
I am telling you, mister, it's not.
Like Dr. Brennan says:
no use jumping to conclusions
before all the evidence is in.
Quite a show?
Shouldn't we get going home?
How many times do you get a chance
to check out a desert sky?
I've been in the desert many times.
Though, usually
I'm digging in the ground,
not looking up.
Now's your chance to look up.
So, look up.
But it's ridiculous to think
there's anything on this planet
worth seeing which merits crossing
what are literally
astronomical distances.
Maybe aliens are anthropologists?
Maybe they just want to
study our religion
and sex and... love
and our funny languages
and line dancing?
That's an interesting
possibility I hadn't considered.
Living creatures, they
like to reach out, Bones.
Living creatures like to
reach out and eat each other.
So what are you saying,
that the aliens just
want to come down here
and drink our spinal fluid?
If the aliens are advanced enough
to fly faster than light,
then they can probably
make spinal fluid.
You just said that aliens are nice.
I did not.
You just basically said
that aliens are nice anthropologists.
I don't think so.
You think
the aliens are you.
You got me.
You know, I'm one of them.
I knew it.
I was sent down as an advance scout.
No probing.
No probing!
Probing is a valuable way
to gather information.
We know how you people
like to probe... right.
Did you hear that?
What was it?
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--