I had a feeling
that my Melolontha melolontha
might hatch this morning,
so I came in at the crack of dawn,
and there they were,
lined up at the door.
What, your Melolontha melolontha?
The Woodchucks.
They appear to be little girls.
Woodchucks are like
girl Scouts, only scientific
and administered by the Jeffersonian.
They brought in the dead body.
A bunch of little girls
brought a dead body here?
Woodchucks are
very industrious marmots.
Okay, now, this is
Dr. Temperance Brennan.
- Why are they applauding?
- Apparently, you're their role model.
Why they aren't all freaked out
and getting trauma counseling.
Because they're the type of children
who idolize Dr. Brennan.
So, they were eco-camping on the banks
of the Savage River.
These remains are
completely saturated.
The girls fished the body
out of the river
and brought it to us.
How?
In our Woodchuck bus.
Very impressive.
I disagree. Those Woodchucks
disturbed a federal crime scene.
The area should have been secured,
samples taken.
They did all that.
Water samples from the river
where the body was found.
Digital photographs
of the entire area.
Plants, insects,
soil samples tagged
with GPS coordinates.
Now, I know my soil samples,
and let me tell you something.
These ladies... they are pros.
Perhaps you should throw them a bone.
Not literally. Metaphorically.
After all,
they were very professional.
Attention, Woodchucks.
You were thorough
and assiduous in your treatment
of the body and the crime scene.
But next time, please leave the evidence
where you found it,
and let the experienced
professionals do their job.
But we helped!
You're mean!
Their moods are capricious.
You couldn't have just let them
have that one, let it go by?
Then they'd never learn.
What causes a corpse
to smell like a fart?
A number of things.
A compromised intestinal tract,
methane, some mining processes,
oil and gas refining.
Volcanoes?
Volcanoes? Awesome.
- Which of those was it this time?
- Probably sulfur.
Tissue samples indicate a high
concentration of hydrogen sulfide.
X-rays indicate
this is a middle-aged male
between 170
and 190 centimeters tall.
Skeleton is pretty banged up.
Bouncing around the Savage River
for two months will do that.
All the distal phalanges are missing
from the interphalangeal joints.
He's missing his fingers.
What does that tell you?
Tells me it was the mob,
snipping off fingerprints.
That very well may be,
but what it tells me
is you're going out
to look for fingertips,
in case the Woodchucks missed them.
The body was found by woodchucks?
Take Hodgins.
He'll explain.
- Hydrogen sulfide?
- Yeah, guy's full of it.
So he smells basically like a fart?
Had to be pretty strong to cover up
the rotting corpse smell?
Maybe somebody
drenched him in sulfur
to deal with the dead body stench.
Or somebody tried to put
him in suspended animation.
That involves sulfides.
Are you referring to ultra-secret
military experiments
to prolong life
by inducing hibernation?
It's not ultra secret.
The Army is doing field trials.
I got a cousin in Iraq.
It maybe saved his life.
It's not ultra secret?
Look, man, the trouble with getting
your info from conspiracy nuts is
- they never know when to turn it off.
- You wait and see.
We're gonna find that our victim was
tortured a little too enthusiastically,
and the government tried
to bring him back to life.
Proving my point there, Hodgins.
Should we call the military
possibility in to Booth?
Just leave out my torture theory.
- So, you got a face on the victim?
- Why are you here?
I would have called.
I thought Hodgins might
have something on this whole
suspended animation thing.
- You listened to Hodgins?
- No, Wendell.
Well, what is DARPA?
It's a Department of Defense agency.
The Defense Advanced Research
Projects Agency.
Hodgins says they're into
some pretty weird stuff.
Like creating super soldiers
who don't need sleep and can
kill with their laser beam eyes.
Right, well, I don't know
about the laser beam eye thing,
but they did have a master sergeant
go missing about a couple of months ago.
Was the sergeant involved with
the hydrogen sulfide trials?
Well, they wouldn't confirm,
but they sounded nervous.
- There's no photograph in here.
- DARPA doesn't give out any photos.
You give me the reconstruction, though,
I can show them that,
and they can tell us
if we got their guy.
What do you have?
Before you freak out,
you should know
that I double and triple checked
the measurements and indicators.
I don't freak out.
Do I freak out?
Some... Sometimes.
Can we just see the image, please?
- Yeah. What's that supposed to be?
- Half man, half chicken?
- Come on.
- I believe this to be fairly accurate.
Okay, so you want me
to go ask the Defense Department
if their experimental super soldier
is half man, half chicken?
Bones - Season 5 Episode 06
"The Tough Man in the Tender Chicken"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Kujathemas,
Dark_Chii
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
DARPA created a chicken soldier?
I do not see the United States Military
making a chicken soldier.
- An eagle, maybe.
- That's why we couldn't find
his so-called fingers.
They were transformed into talons.
I mean, talons...
they would be better weapons.
Human remains in water tend to lose all
their fingers and toes due to predation.
But if I were going
to combine human and animal DNA
with an eye toward creating
a super soldier, I'd go with a flatworm.
- Why?
- Self-regeneration, obviously.
People!
Let's break this down as though
we aren't in a comic book.
No water in the sinuses or
lungs, no pulmonary edema.
- He didn't drown.
- The sinus cavity is
abnormally large.
His whole sinus cavity is scarred.
The septum's almost gone.
Evidence of multiple constrictions of
the arterioles at Kiesselbach's plexus.
That is a lot of scar tissue.
What are we talking,
plastic surgery?
Well, the scarring could explain
why he has a beak-like nose.
Polyps and tumors in the maxillary
and sphenoid could have enlarged it.
The closest thing I've ever seen to that
is a cocaine addict who ran out of drugs
and started snorting things like
sugar and powdered detergent.
Does anyone have any explanation
for these red stripes
extending from the soft palate
down the esophagus?
Lacerations?
May I?
I don't think these are lacerations.
Is that an organism?
Syngamus trachea.
It's a gapeworm.
Where'd it come from?
I don't think
you're gonna like my answer.
It's a parasite found in chickens.
Do not tell me we're back
to super chicken soldier again.
Why a chicken?
Wendell thinks maybe he was
supposed to be an eagle.
You should be getting it now.
You make a super soldier,
you think it would be a robot
or something invisible.
- You're delving into science fiction.
- Like a flatworm...
that's science fiction or a half chicken
that's not considered science fiction.
Yeah. Okay, so we agree that
it does look like a chicken.
No, it is not a joke.
Just tell me if we have
your missing DARPA guy.
Does your missing sergeant look
anything like an animal?
Any kind of an animal?
A bulldog.
So the Defense Department
won't be claiming the body?
Getting a hit off
of Angela's chicken man picture.
Probably from the animal shelter.
- God.
- What?
Is Angela good, or is she good?
Those are the same question.
"Nick Rabin."
He's head of personnel
at Clucksten Farms.
A chicken farm?
This is getting weirder and weirder.
Save a chicken! Fry a worker!
Cluck you! Cluck you!
Close down Clucksten!
- Wonder what they're protesting.
- Well, my first guess...
the stench.
At least they're not
throwing eggs at us?
Chicken killer!
Close down Clucksten!
Rest the voice, Josh.
You the, FBI folks?
Come on in.
We'll find a quieter place to talk.
You're working in a death camp!
So, what's with the protesters?
Maybe half are animal rights nuts.
They might have a point.
The other half must
just hate the smell.
Clucksten Farms has been here
since the 1940s.
We didn't ask anyone
to build a development downwind.
What's that smell?
John.
Mrs. Rabin,
this is Agent Booth
and his associate Dr. Brennan.
They're from the FBI.
This is Gaynor Rabin.
She's the accountant here
at Clucksten.
She's also Nick's wife.
Is this about my husband?
- He's dead, isn't he?
- I'm afraid so.
We're very sorry for your loss.
What happened to him?
We're still in the process
of figuring that out.
You don't seem too surprised.
Nick was never the type to disappear.
I knew it was something terrible.
- Where'd you find him?
- In the Savage River,
approximately 16 kilometers
from here.
Nick drowned?
I don't understand.
He never swam in that river.
Your husband's nose
and sinuses were deformed.
He didn't take the proper
precautions at work, did he?
No, I told him, but he didn't care.
Precautions to what? {\keep
from turning into a chicken?}
It's the hydrogen sulfide we smell.
Without a breathing apparatus,
high concentrations
over a period of time
would deform the sinuses.
Nick worked here
since he was a teenager.
He said he was a chicken farmer,
and he'd take the consequences.
How did my husband end up
in the river?
We were hoping that maybe
you'd be able to help us with that.
When I filed the missing persons report,
I told the police everything.
He just disappeared.
We have reason to believe
this wasn't an accidental drowning.
You think my husband was murdered?
Mr. Clucksten said that Nick was next
in line to take over the business.
First people that you wanna check out
are those anti-chicken fanatics
They always threaten to make
an example out of someone.
Five months and 14 days
- I have been celibate.
- Angela, that is very impressive.
Thank you.
Sweets was right.
Taking sex out of that equation
made me relate to people
in a totally different way.
Yeah, once you got past
the mega-horny stage.
The point is, is that
my six months is almost up.
So...
- No.
- No, what?
I am not gonna be
the one that breaks your fast.
I... I wasn't asking.
In fact, you should know that
I was considering going for a year.
That's definitely a chicken parasite
we found in the victim's esophagus.
I wasn't asking, Jack.
I was just...
keeping you in the loop.
Cluck you! Cluck you!
Save a chicken! Fry a worker!
There's the employees!
Hey, lady, you gonna go
kill some chickens today?!
- Get out of my face and go get a job!
- Murderer!
Murderer now?
What do you want me to do?
She's psycho!
Psycho chicken killer!
I got kids to feed!
You're just...
giving them what they want.
- I'm doing an honest day's work!
- Just go, just go.
You don't wanna be
late for your shift.
They don't seem to like the way
you treat the chickens.
So how do you treat them?
Like delicious birds
that people love to eat.
Look, does anyone in particular here
have a beef with, Nick Rabin?
Josh Parsons.
He snuck in,
he took some unauthorized video,
cut it together in a very damning manner
and he put it on the Internet.
Nick popped him one, too.
Close down Cluckster's!
Veggies, not birds!
FBI Special Agent Booth.
This here is Dr. Temperance Brennan.
You're here to protect them
while they torture
chickens on this farm and the people who
live downwind of its foul emanations?
- You practice that speech much?
- We found Nick Rabin's body.
Now you are our number one suspect.
Please, I didn't kill anyone.
I'm an extreme pacifist.
That's an oxymoron.
You're either extreme or pacifist.
- You can't be both.
- You're working
as a tool of the poultry lobbyists.
Code Yellow! Code Yellow!
They're with the
the chicken lobbyists!
Joke's on you!
Here's your feathers!
Why don't you fly back to Washington?
Okay, you do know that
you're all under arrest, right?
What are you talking about?
The stench of ammonia
and feces overwhelm you,
as 30,000 silent chickens
sit miserably in total darkness
waiting to die.
That's your voice narrating,
isn't it, Mr. Parsons?
Yes, I'm proud of my work.
The FBI believes that
you snuck onto the premises
to record a second video.
You were caught by Nick Rabin
- and you killed him.
- It's what happened.
I don't think it
played out that way.
Dr. Sweets says you're the type of guy
who couldn't kill, except
- in self-defense.
- I never attacked anyone.
- 'Cause you tarred and feathered me.
- It was corn syrup and paper feathers.
I didn't sneak in
and take that video footage.
I got back to my bicycle one night
and there was an envelope in the spokes.
I'm gonna need the name
of your chicken spy on the inside.
- No.
- And the original footage,
- not the stuff you cut together here.
- I will absolutely
not turn over to you any information
which was entrusted to me
by the courageous individual who risked
his or her job to aid innocent creatures
- who are unable to defend themselves.
- You don't hand over the original,
I'm gonna charge you
with assaulting a federal agent.
That's what? $200,000 fine
and one year in a federal prison?
You know, if you're locked up,
who's gonna speak for the chickens?
Just hold on.
That's the raw video footage.
- Exactly the way that I got it.
- See? It all worked out great.
Cause of death, Mr. Bray?
Most of the fractures
are postmortem.
The bone bruising,
probably from going over the dam
and getting stuck in the whirlpool.
Like going through
a giant washing machine.
But this damage to the cervical
vertebrae is not postmortem.
This is an undamaged
cervical section.
Here is our victim.
The C2 vertebra rotated laterally
while the ligaments and facets
of the transverse processes
were subluxed and locked.
A broken neck.
The fracture pattern
suggests a wrenching motion.
You mean wrung?
The chicken man
- was killed by having his neck wrung?
- Yeah.
Ironic, right?
We are gonna have to
catalog these injuries
chronologically.
Talk to Angela.
See if she has some kind of
imaging technique that can help.
Nearly ten billion chickens
are hatched in the U.S. annually.
- Most in places like this.
- It's like a warehouse.
Each chicken is given less
than a half a square foot of space.
And look at this part,
the little baby chicks
get their beaks cut off.
Why?
Supposedly to keep them
from fighting.
How do they fight
when they're penned up?
It's the stress
of being jammed together.
I guess they go crazy.
Are you upset?
Yeah, I am.
- Aren't you?
- I'm not certain how sentient
chickens actually are, Angela.
Yeah, but they can feel.
I mean, you can see that they can.
You know,
if it turns out that there was
some kind of chicken revolution
and they offed this guy, I am with them.
It's our job to figure out
who killed the human being.
Yeah, I guess.
Because it probably
wasn't a chicken revolution.
It was probably another human being.
Fine.
I was able to extract the metadata
that was embedded
in the original video file.
Time and date
that the video was taken and aperture,
make and model of the camera
- including the serial number.
- Could you trace the serial number?
The owner sent in
the manufacturer's warranty.
- Which included the serial number.
- Gaynor Rabin.
The victim's wife.
Thank you, Angela.
And I'm sorry the chickens
make you feel bad.
What about pigs?
Pigs are sentient.
That's a non-sequitur.
Pigs make bacon.
And not only are they sentient,
they're smarter than dogs.
Well, I don't eat bacon.
I'm a vegetarian.
Yeah, for health reasons.
Listen, Brennan.
I want to save this little piglet.
That particular, specific piglet?
Yes. It's gonna be $1,500.
- Are you in?
- No.
Yeah, but look at his face.
How can you resist this face?
Saving one pig or chicken
is symbolic at best, Angela.
This is not a symbol.
This is a face.
It worries me that you can
look into these eyes and be so cold.
I'm sure he's a fine piglet, but...
How are we friends?
How is it possible?
I mean, we have nothing in common.
What, you don't wanna be friends
anymore because the pig is cute?
What if the victim
used his wife's camera
to strike back at the company
that disfigured him?
Maybe he was having an affair.
Or maybe she was just sick
of kissing a guy with a beak.
Today's special: Chicken.
Ironic.
Everything okay there, Bones?
I know when something is wrong with you.
Something's wrong, all right?
What can I do to help?
Angela and I had a fight.
Nothing I can do to help.
- You want to hear about it?
- No.
- Why not?
- Her and Angela are best friends.
And Bones is going to
want me to take her side
and agree that Angela was wrong.
Then the two of them are gonna make up
and then they're gonna be mad at me.
So, no, thank you.
That's very interesting.
You know, the way you
say "very interesting"
is very irritating.
Listen, Bones,
I would do anything for you.
I'd die for you,
I would kill for you,
but I am not getting
in between two best friends.
What were you saying, Sweets?
I've been considering
the symbolism of this murder.
Being tossed over a dam
isn't very chickeny.
You'd think that the
victim would show up
in a rotisserie or a deep fryer.
I remember a month ago,
a chicken restaurant chain
reported human phalanges
in some deep fried treats.
Kid bit into a thumb.
Right, the mom hit a toe.
It was... Bock Box Chicken Hut.
- Maybe the toe is our victim's.
- Totally poetic justice.
If you can get the body parts
from those chicken treats
to the Jeffersonian,
- we'll see if they match our victims.
- Okay.
I'm going back to the lab.
Send the fingers over when you get them.
Listen, Bones,
everything is gonna be okay
between you and Angela, all right?
You two are like sisters.
- I'm not used to not getting along.
- Seriously? 'Cause it seems like...
Thanks, Booth.
Just bring in the human
parts tomorrow, and I'll...
- I'll take a look.
- Okay.
If you combine your
"don't get between women" rule
and your "like sisters" observation,
you know what I come up with?
You dated sisters.
They were identical twins.
- Yeah, it was all wrong.
- No, it's all right. It's all right.
We should stop. Order your wings.
These have been frozen,
flash-fried, microwaved,
bitten, spat out, then
preserved as evidence.
Bone density would indicate
that all four digits
came from the same person.
They all came from the same local
chain of chicken restaurants.
- Bock Box.
- I beg your pardon?
Bock Box Chicken Huts.
Is Clucksten a supplier?
They're one of them.
No way of telling where these particular
human nuggets came from.
There's a lack of bruising on
the bone at the incision point.
Removed postmortem,
so not torture, obviously.
There are symmetrical slice marks.
Also, pinching
in the center of the bone and tissue.
Removed with shears?
You should do a DNA test,
of course, but I'm confident
that all four body's part
came from Nick Rabin.
Are you here because of your
argument with Dr. Brennan?
No, I'm here for a donation.
She told you about our fight?
Booth figured it out.
I was just sitting there.
A donation for what?
It's going to cost $1,500
to save this piglet.
- How much are you in for?
- Are those tears in your eyes?
I'm just...
I can't stop thinking
about this little piglet.
I'm going to suggest
that perhaps it's time for you...
to abandon celibacy a little early.
- What does that have to do?
- You're forming inappropriately strong
attachments
to photographs of baby animals.
Your libido is being rerouted.
- You need to come back to the world.
- Wait a minute.
Inappropriate, my ass.
Can I ask you: what is wrong
with everyone here?
You had a falling out
with your best friend over a pig.
Your perspective is skewed.
It's time
to reconnect with humanity,
gain a little perspective.
All right, so...
if I have sex,
will you donate to save my pig?
That's not really the point
I was trying...
We'll revisit the pig question.
You can keep this.
I have multiples.
You think I killed my husband,
cut off his thumbs,
and then dumped him over
the Savage River Dam?
Thumbs and toes, yes.
Do you recognize this?
It's the video those PECT people
put on the Internet.
It was taken with your camera.
You're making that up.
You can't know that.
No, we can prove that.
Let's start this all over again.
Did you take this footage?
Yes, I took it.
- Did you give it to Josh Parsons?
- Yes.
- I wanted Clucksten's shut down.
- Why?
Your husband is next in line
to take over the business.
Because I was tired of getting
threatening phone calls.
I was tired of being hated
in my own town.
But most of all, Agent Booth,
I wanted my husband
to get his real face back,
so I gave the footage
to the activists.
How is it possible that your...
husband's thumbs
ended up on the menu?
Easy.
Toss them in with the nuggets
just before they're breaded,
fried, and frozen for shipment.
Are you suggesting that
the killer was working
in Clucksten Farms?
You realize Clucksten's
is doomed after this?
- Yeah.
- So you got exactly what you wanted.
No, Agent Booth, I did not.
What I wanted was my husband back.
I understand.
Is there anyone else who benefits
from Clucksten Farms going under?
Probably the anti-smell people,
the people who live downwind.
I need a name, that's all.
The main clean air nut
is Roy Meyers.
He's a baker with a shop
about two miles downwind of Clucksten's.
I got some more data
on the bone bruising.
So I need $1,500.
I need about $40,000
to repay student loans.
What do you need your money for?
I need to save...
this pig.
- From being made into bacon?
- Yeah.
I love bacon.
I love ribs.
I love steak.
I love meat.
I'm a meat eater.
I'm not apologetic about it.
Look at his face.
Look, Angela, I'm sorry.
Here's... 20...
25...
$45?
Take it all.
We'll save your pig.
- Roy Meyers?
- Yes?
FBI, Agent Booth.
This here is Dr. Temperance Brennan.
We understand that
you're trying to get the state
- to shut down Clucksten Farms?
- Sure.
Because nobody will come in
and make them regulate the stench.
- They were here first.
- Yeah, back when it was
a free-range chicken ranch.
It's a different beast now,
factory farm "Heartless",
reasonable people call it.
You'll excuse me.
I took this up as a way
of getting some fresh air,
as ironic as that sounds.
Considering your malodorous habit,
would you say that your dispute
with Clucksten Farms
is more financially motivated
than health-related?
Sure.
You know how a baker sells his wares?
People smell the bread from the outside,
go in, and spend the dough.
Thanks to Clucksten Farms,
to smell my cinnamon buns,
people got to jam their noses
right in the damn thing.
Clucksten Farms is trying
to put you out of business.
Can I take a look at that?
Yeah, me and anybody who
relies on a sense of smell,
- sense of taste.
- Will your thumb fit in this hole?
Don't be sticking that on my thumb.
It's like a mini-guillotine.
You want to be careful with that.
It's sharp as razors.
That'll nip your
thumb off in a jiffy.
What,
some kind of federal crime
to own a cigar clipper?
The human eye
can only perceive color
between wavelengths
of 400 and 750 nanometers.
This full-spectrum light source
simulates both
the visible and UV spectrum.
Angela is brilliant.
So we run the image
through the spectroscope
and now we can detect color differences
that are not visible to the human eye.
I was able to confirm
these as postmortem bruises
likely caused by rocks and debris
from the victim traveling downriver.
Then we assigned
all postmortem bruising
with one distinct color
and perimortem with another.
Now, injuries sustained
before death will appear red
and after death, black.
- Saves me hours and hours of work.
- This is what happens when two people
from different disciplines find
each other and work together closely.
Can you highlight
the perimortem bruising?
Evenly-spaced circular impact bruises to
the right temporal and sphenoid region,
continuing here along
the frontal and parietal bones.
All of them...
have identical directionality.
- What would leave marks like that?
- Some kind of machine.
And why do they stop there?
Something stopped the weapon
from striking down
to the skull in this area.
The microscopic metal deposits
on the clipped thumb bone
don't match
the baker's cigar cutter,
but fortunately
I'm extremely
thorough and tenacious.
There's evidence of streaming
nuclei in the bone cells.
- That was my job to find.
- It's okay, kid.
Around here we step in
for each other as needed.
What?
- You mean work.
- What did you mean?
I'm agreeing. It's work.
Can we move on?
- We have electricity?
- Who does?
The streaming nuclei
suggests voltage.
I know.
A self-cauterizing blade.
There's got to be something like that
in a place that kills thousands
of chickens every day.
Here we go.
This might narrow things down.
He had beak
and feather disease virus.
He had beak and feather
disease in his thumb?
I'm going to go out on a limb here
and guess that maybe
what we're looking for
is a self-cauterizing instrument
that cuts beaks and feathers.
Wait a minute.
The video.
Pluckers beat the
feathers off dead chickens
and beak clippers clip the beaks
off of baby chicks.
That's you, right, Ms. McNamara?
Your occupation is beak clipper?
Baby chicks are jammed
so close together, they get stressed,
attack each other. It's my job
to cut the tips off their beaks.
- Really isn't a good job to have.
- I got demoted from plucker.
Bet you didn't know
there was something worse.
When you were demoted,
was that before or after you charged
- Nick Rabin with sexual harassment?
- After.
Go figure. Nick was a groper.
Never heard the guy coming.
It got old real fast.
How much training does it take
to run the beak-clipping machine?
None. Just got to be
the kind of person
willing to cut the beaks
off of newborn chicks.
Why?
Because your machine was used to
remove Nick's thumbs and big toes.
If I was gonna cut something off of
Nick Rabin, it would not be his thumb.
What people usually do right now
is they insist
- that they didn't kill anyone.
- Maybe I fantasized
about it,
it's like I actually did it.
Do you know anything
about Rabin's death
or the mutilation of his body?
But still, if you could arrange it,
I wouldn't mind getting away
from Clucksten's
and spending a few days in jail.
I don't need a professional
consultation, Sweets.
This is not that. It's
just a friendly conversation.
- Angela will come around.
- I'm certain that she will.
Eventually Angela will see
the rational nature of my argument.
- She will come around.
- I already said that.
Crazy thought-
what if, this time, you were
the one who came around?
Saving one pig is an irrational act.
Are you suggesting that I point
that out to Angela more clearly?
Because that would
make this conversation
very much like
a professional consultation.
No, I'm suggesting,
in a very friendly,
conversational way,
that you help her save that one pig.
We agreed that
that's a meaningless act.
Meaningless by your
definition, not by Angela's.
- My definition is correct.
- And if life were
simply a debate,
you would win, hands down,
but we know that it isn't a debate.
It's something much tougher.
Our very work shows us that,
that those people
that call the world an abattoir
a slaughterhouse
they have a point.
Now, you handle that knowledge
by imposing this...
gossamer web of rationality
over the ugliness.
Angela has a very different way
of handling.
Sometimes you don't save
the world, Dr. Brennan.
Sometimes you just make
your friend happy.
But even when it's irrational?
He is
very, very cute.
I mean,
it's almost like he's smiling.
Wendell and I have been testing
chicken factory implements
to find something that would leave
the symmetrical marks on the victim.
- Searching for the murder weapon.
- Did you find it yet?
No, but we have the parameters.
Please assume the position.
The skull was struck repeatedly.
We need someone to actually
spin Wendell on the stool.
I don't twirl the interns.
Perhaps Angela would do it.
I'll... I'll do it.
Now,
it appears as if
the victim was turning,
and/or rolling.
Someone rolled him?
- That's how it appears.
- The directionality indicates that.
Can Istop turning
while you discuss this?
Not yet.
What we haven't determined
is what he was rolled on
that would've done this.
What if... what if the
victim wasn't spinning?
What if the weapon was spinning?
Oh, thank you, God.
The bruises had
common directionality.
It's likely the victim
was face down at an angle.
If...
the implement striking the
victim's head
was spinning...
I know which piece of
equipment caused these bone bruises
and run the victim's neck
in the same time.
There I go.
Look at that,.
Bones, look at this.
We served a warrant
for your chicken plucker.
We've got blood.
From the chickens?
They are drained
by the time they get here.
There'd barely be any blood left.
What's that?
If my theory is correct,
it'll turn out to be a fragment
of the victim's necktie.
I need your tie to test the theory.
The one I'm wearing now?
This tie?
I'm not certain the
tie will be ruined.
We will reimburse you if it is.
- Just a tie.
- The murderer and victim struggle,
the victim's tie enters
the chicken plucker...
That amount of force would definitely
have wrung the victim's neck.
What? My reasoning is flawless.
Shut that off, will you?
Your theory suggests
that it was an accident.
- I disagree.
- They fight.
- The tie gets caught inadvertently.
- No, this pattern has a missing
component. Here.
It suggests that something
blocked the strike.
Obviously, the murderer's hand.
Like this.
See?
We should see if any employee
of Clucksten Farms was treated
for a broken hand.
These fractures to your second and
third metacarpals
in your left hand...
they were caused by being struck.
- That had to smart.
- How do you have my X-rays?
See, a judge decided that we
had reasonable cause for a warrant.
Why is it that the
head of security reaches
into a moving chicken plucker?
Eight years I worked at
that hellhole. You know why?
Your wife?
We were going to have kids.
Only, she got sick,
because she worked at Clucksten's.
- Did you have evidence of that?
- That's exactly what Nick asked.
But we moved to the next
county and she got better.
That's evidence enough,
if you ask me.
All I wanted from Nick
was a gas allowance.
He said no?
We shoved each other a bit, I guess.
His tie got stuck in
the chicken plucker,
and I reached in.
I tried to save him.
And that's how my hand got broke.
But you didn't intend to kill him.
God, no.
Right, I understand.
I know you trust your gut,
but it's wrong this time.
The directionality of
these fractures shows
that your hand was on Nick Rabin's
face as it went into the machine.
You pushed him.
You killed him.
I drive 68 miles to work every day.
And all I wanted was
a gas allowance.
I work there eight years,
just a gas allowance
so my wife
can stay healthy.
Would I like one of those
fruity drinks?
You know, he fooled me,
he fooled me.
I mean, I actually
believed he was trying
to save the victim.
He's a very good liar.
Now, I could tell
when people are lying.
I mean, I-I could tell
before my whole...
recto-cerebral infracture.
What?
That's not a real medical
- condition.
- Are you sure?
Because that's what I'm
feeling right now.
If it were real,
it'd be pretty disgusting.
- Recto-cerebral...
- I know, I'm losing it.
Look, I just...
I'm not up to speed here.
I woke up this morning and I
realized that I didn't even know
if I like brown sugar on my oatmeal.
Next time call me.
You like brown sugar on everything.
I'm the one who is supposed to
know when people are lying.
Who do I call up for that?
You said he's like a human
lie detector test.
I don't like things at half speed, okay?
I'm a full speed kind of a guy.
Well, even at half speed, you're
twice as fast as anyone else.
You want to see the fastest draw
in the west?
- Sure.
- You want to see it again?
Sweets thinks that I
should humor Angela.
Sweets is a bright kid.
But I want to know what you think.
As a full-grown
man of experience.
I need to know what you think.
I think you should let her
have this one.
What are you doing?
No, wait. Now? No, I
didn't mean this second.
Excuse me.
I want to help you...
Thank you.
It's everything.
You got it. That's great.
- Angela's very happy.
- I can see that.
You said that in a funny way.
You noticed something.
See?
You still got it...
You're not going to ask me
what I saw?
Do I want to know?
Do you want to know, anyway?
It can wait.
I trust you.
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--