Sanders, Dubovich,
check these hot spots
and we're good to go.
What's up?
Pop this wardrobe. Don't want a flare-up
dragging us back out here this weekend.
That's a new one on me.
Order in successful societies
depends upon enforcible rules.
People can do the right
thing left on their own.
History shows otherwise.
A weak government
will always spawn mutiny
and rebellion.
You don't believe in human decency
under circumstances?
Not as a means of controlling
a population. That would be anarchy.
I have to say I agree with
the pretty lady on this one.
Without the strong arm
of the law, we're animals.
Sheriff Gus Abrams,
thank you for coming out here.
What caused the fire?
Well, it could be arson.
The fire boys say
they didn't find any sign
of an accelerant.
The source of the flame
looks like a lit candle.
Was someone killed?
Well, that's why we
asked for you people.
Is that real, Bones?
- Yes.
- I was hoping "no."
The bones were already dry
and de-fleshed prior to the fire.
The victim was elderly, female.
Wait, you usually don't say "oh."
- It was an indication of my surprise.
- Well, I know that, but why?
- The bones have been re-articulated.
- Is that bad?
The skeleton has been reassembled,
quite amateurishly.
See how the right ulna has been
placed with the left radius?
Yeah, shoddy.
That's shoddy work.
Hodgins noticed that there's a path
all the way around the house
And Angela noticed
that it was a circle.
Looks like it acted as a firebreak.
Also dusted with some fine powder.
Those are crows.
You city people may not be familiar.
Crows are carrion birds, Sheriff.
They scavenge for fresh kill.
When she starts flapping
her elbows like that,
she's hot on the trail
for something.
Well, I don't want to think
about what she's after.
- Don't say it.
- I've got to.
"We aren't in Kansas anymore."
I don't like it when dead things move.
Did you see that?
It was moving there.
Who do you want to start with?
The Wicked Witch of the East over here?
East, right?
Right, she wore the red shoes.
We should start
with the more recent remains.
Which are sealed up.
What is it with this job and corpses
encased in mystery wrap?
Dr. Hodgins says it's most likely
polystyrene ceiling insulation
that melted and coated the body.
Could he explain the sparkle?
Fluorescent bulbs exploded afterward,
shattering over the polystyrene.
Perhaps you and Dr. Hodgins
can find a way to unseal the remains.
Let me see if I can get in here.
Wire ligatures around the wrists
indicate foul play.
No evidence of smoke inhalation.
She was dead before the fire.
Now... that one is just weird.
These bones were
found in a sealed wardrobe.
It preserved her in fire.
Female, also Caucasian.
40 to 50 years old.
There's evidence of spinal kyphosis,
which would have given her
a hunched posture.
This stain, here on the forehead,
is the result of contact with copper.
I've seen this before
in disinterred bodies
because of the copper hardware
on coffins.
So, somebody robbed a grave,
strung together a skeleton
and stuck it in a wedding dress?
- That's a reasonable conclusion.
- These are greenstick fractures.
Extreme force
was applied to the chest.
And...
there's a clean-edged
indentation of the spinous processes,
L-2 and L-3.
Thoracic crushing, combined
with the puncture wound.
This woman was subjected
to a kind of torture
that was used in the 17th century.
Torture?
These injuries are consistent
with a form of punishment
used during the Salem Witch Trials.
She was a witch?
Bones - Season 5 Episode 20
"The Witch in the Wardrobe"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Kujathemas,
Dark_Chii
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
You know what I think?
I think Cam sent us both
to the crime scene because
of the tension between us.
"Tension"? There's
no tension between us.
Yeah, at first I thought it was
because I'm suddenly...
I don't know, available again.
And...
then I thought maybe it was because
you think that I treated Wendell badly.
Hold on. Wendell said
that it was totally mutual.
- He said that you were wonderful.
- I'm not sure
how I feel about you two
discussing me.
Not "discussing" you.
Complimenting you.
Okay, fine.
No more compliments.
You don't look good today.
Your smile is ordinary at best,
and it is not cool that we finally
get to work together
again in the field.
Okay, that's fine.
I can live with that.
Yeah, this symbol
is very creepy on this chimney.
All right, let me see.
- See?
- Yeah. It could be a lot of things.
What is that?
The Prius helps you stay
in your lane.
- That's kind of cool.
- It is cool.
Let's do that again.
- That is not cool.
- I didn't even see him there.
He's pretty sneaky.
Pull over.
I'll pour on the charm.
It's Sheriff Abrams
from the crime scene.
Perfect.
Good afternoon, sir. I observed you
crossing the double-yellow.
- How much have you had to drink today?
- Sheriff Abrams, it's us.
We just left the crime scene.
We're heading up north to
drop off our stuff at the lab.
I know, Dr. Hodgins.
I'm just following the law.
Have you had anything
to drink today?
Listen,
I really do like a man in uniform
who loves his job.
So, neither one of us
has had anything to drink. No.
Hello, Ms. Montenegro.
But I'm afraid I need
the driver to respond.
Yeah, I've had several martinis,
some absinthe and a barrel of mead.
License and registration, please.
He was kidding.
He's just being an idiot.
You, too, please.
A real Salem witch?
- That's awesome!
- Relax. Simmer down.
The strontium isotope results
verify Massachusetts.
- Can I see it?
- What's the big deal?
My first published work concerned
the collective sociopathology
behind the Salem Witch Trials.
- I'm a leading expert.
- Shrinkery meets witchery.
Your head's probably
about ready to explode?
It's a completely acceptable
arena of study, even for a psychologist.
Thank you.
At last, I feel validated.
Most cultures believe that some sort
of supernatural power can be
elicited through ritual.
Like, you going to church.
At least I don't
ride there on my broomstick.
Most witches align themselves
with the Wiccans,
but witchcraft is an extremely
heterogeneous subject
which encompasses the dark arts
like evil spells, sacrifices...
So you're saying this creepy, old witch
came from the dead to kill this victim?
Of course not,
but we are talking about
a three-century-year-old body
that was rearticulated
and costumed as a virgin,
are we not, Dr. Brennan?
Well, given that women
in those times
were expected to be virgins on
their wedding days, that's reasonable.
I want to work on the case.
What are you going to do,
cast a spell?
I want to see if I could find
a link between the old witch
and the new witch.
Go for it.
There's no evidence that
the other as a witch.
Aside from the fact
that she was wearing
red slippers and her feet
curled up after she was dead.
What?
There's a completely scientific
explanation for it.
Cheri Byrd.
That creepy house belonged
to a woman by the name
of Cheri Byrd, and she has
a surviving brother.
Are you sure it's Cheri?
Dental records confirm her identity.
When was the last time
you spoke to her?
Two, three months ago.
Someone made an offer on the house.
Our grandfather left it to us both.
I wanted to sell.
She refused.
We haven't spoken since.
You don't seem too surprised
that she's dead.
Cheri and I used to be really close.
You know, but, last ten years,
she got into some
really... weird stuff.
Witchcraft?
Started ordering us to call her
Zephyra.
I told her I wouldn't.
Thought it was stupid.
The fact that she didn't sell the house,
didn't get you upset or angry?
No, I didn't care about the money.
I wanted her to move to the city.
Thought her mind might go back to normal
if she saw more people.
- Who wanted to buy the house?
- Guy named Mario
Trivisini, Trivisonno...
Making some big development.
Said Cheri's place was the key.
"The key," why?
Lake access.
When Cheri said "no",
he had to give up on the whole project.
You're not Hodgins.
He's not here
and I can't wait any longer.
- Wait for what?
- Dr. Brennan
wants me
to identify the best solvent
to remove polystyrene
from the bones.
So I put myself
in the mindset of Dr. Hodgins
and came up with...
this experiment.
I have a new appreciation
for Dr. Hodgins.
This device slowly fills
each polystyrene cup up
with kerosene, propylene,
turpentine,
hydrochloric acid and...
acetone.
Acetone.
It's not like Hodgins to be late.
Can you come get me
as soon as he shows up?
And I think the acetone
is eating through your shoes.
What?
I love these shoes.
We live in a fascist state.
If you know that,
then why did you taunt
the guy with the gun?
You expect me to just roll over?
Praying that you do, though.
Here he comes.
Listen,
be nice, or I will
cause you great pain.
Have we cleared this up, Officer?
Not quite.
Now,
the problem is
that Miss Montenegro here is a criminal.
I found an outstanding bench
warrant on you, young lady.
What?
For what?
For defying a notice to appear
on a speeding charge.
That? I didn't speed.
But you did defy a bench warrant,
which is worse than speeding.
And Dr. Hodgins, you also
have a warrant
for escaping police custody
during a Freedom of Information
protest eight years ago.
They have a right to know.
But not a right to run away.
Okay. All right, listen.
I will appear,
and Hodgins will surrender
as soon as we get back.
Word of honor.
It's not up to me.
I can't let you go until the
judge rules on your warrants.
When will that be?
Whenever one shows up.
In the meantime, I suggest
you two make the best of things,
the best you can.
Speeding?
Don't you dare.
So, thanks so much for coming in there,
Mr. Trivisi...?
- Trivisonno. Trivisonno Properties.
- Right.
So, this is something new for me
to be called in by the FBI.
What's this all about?
Yeah. I know this house.
Bet you get a good deal on that now.
Yeah. Why is that?
You don't know where
I'm going with this, pal?
Maybe it was your aunt
that lived there?
You're thinking
I want to buy the place now?
No way. I learned my lesson.
What do you mean by that?
You see me now?
You see me there?
- See the difference?
- Yeah. You shaved your head.
I did not shave my head.
Your aunt put a curse on me,
and all the hairs fell off my body.
All the important ones.
First of all, Cheri Byrd is not my aunt.
And secondly,
she's dead.
Here's hoping a curse loses its oomph
after the voodoo lady dies.
Apparently, she was murdered,
so, you want to know what I'm thinking?
Guy thinks he's cursed,
he loses his hair, he wants her dead.
No, you couldn't get me
anywhere near that lady.
Not to kill her, not for anything.
She painted this symbol
on the bricks
on the chimney and inside,
there was all this spooky stuff.
Black candles.
The day she cursed me, a dead cat
was laid out on the dining room table.
- You ditched the project?
- A month ago.
I'm a professional.
You think I need it to get around
an evil witch lived
on the development?
I know when to cut and run.
Just wish
I'd done it a week earlier.
Hodgins isn't back yet?
No, but I've made some progress.
I found this.
Sharp instrument trauma
on the xiphoid press of the sternum.
And anteriomedial aspect of ribs 1
and 4 bilaterally.
She was stabbed repeatedly.
Make casts to analyze the striations
and kerf characteristics
to determine the weapon.
I also
found this on the manubrium.
What is it?
That's a Dr. Hodgins' job.
If we had him...
which we don't.
You haven't heard from him?
He and Angela never came back.
And since they used to be intimates,
I decided not to push it
because that's none of my concern.
None at all.
- It's a little icky.
- It's not like them
to just disappear,
something could be wrong.
- It's ringing.
- Tell them we've got the evidence
from the crime scene.
They'll get us out.
Yeah, hi.
And Hodgins. Help!
- Where are you?
- We're in Berryville.
Maryland, we're in jail.
Why are you in jail?
Well, it goes a little like this:
Hodgins got pulled over
for driving like an old lady.
Yeah, and Angela
had an outstanding bench warrant.
You have a warrant, too, Mr. Clean.
Where is the evidence
you collected yesterday?
- It's in jail with us.
- We're stuck here
until the judge shows up to set our bail
and who knows when that's going to be.
Well, we need that evidence.
I'll tell Cam to come and get you.
Okay, also...
Will you tell Clark to throw
a blanket over my molting swallowtail
caterpillars at 4:30
or they will die.
I'm afraid we might have
to check out a little early there, pal.
I hope that's okay.
That sheriff out in Podunk
was a decent guy.
I'm sure Hodgins getting
arrested for really good reason.
So, I've been thinking
about dead cats.
That doesn't seem like
a good use of your time.
Witches, the bad kind,
use animal sacrifices in their spells.
Black cats are particularly meaningful.
I told Sweets that
the developer saw a dead cat
on the victim's dining room table
before he went bald.
- What's the connection?
- He thinks that she put a spell on him.
- You should talk to their local coven.
- Wait a second. There's a local coven?
The Circle of Moonwick.
You said that Wiccans were good,
whereas the victim was bad.
They're probably competing
for the same eye of newt.
No, Wiccan ceremonies honor nature
and the sanctity of life
above all else.
- They don't use eye of newt.
- Okay, tonight is
their Waning Moon ceremony.
Now.
I logged into their Web site,
using the name Lilith82.
I got directions.
Witches have Web sites?
Gotta love the Internet.
- So, witch hunt tonight?
- All right.
If you bring the candles,
I'll bring the broomstick.
This is the hardest bench
that I have ever sat on in my life.
Sat on?
Slept on.
My shoulders are killing me.
Tell me about it.
Come here.
Why?
I'll give you a little rub.
You know, work out the kinks.
Are you really that mad at me
that you don't want a little massage?
Only because I hurt.
Yes, down, down.
A little lower. Lower.
Thank you, God.
"God" is a little formal.
Hodgins is fine.
Looks to me like, you two are doing
just fine in here.
Did you spring us?
These two aren't Bonnie and Clyde.
Can't you let them go?
Not until the judge.
I'll post bail, pay the fine, whatever.
We need them to solve this murder.
You have the evidence.
They can be reached here
any time to assist.
Don't you think
you're being a little...
rigid?
You are a law enforcement
professional,
- are you not, madam?
- Yes, but...
Well, then you know
the law can't be twisted to our will
or chaos will ensue.
Where does it end?
Today, a seemingly
minor bench warrant, tomorrow
we overlook another piece of paper
and a murderer goes free.
You are like
the last upright man in America.
Well, I wouldn't say that.
But I'm a good sheriff
And I love the law.
That's very impressive, Sheriff.
My God, he's getting to her.
I'm sure the judge
will be coming soon.
No, no, you're kidding, right?
Sorry. It was like arguing
with one of the Founding Fathers.
I've got the evidence.
We'll talk, okay?
- My God.
- No.
See you guys later.
Could you not walk so loudly?
Don't tell me that
you're afraid of witches.
Wiccans, and no,
but why waste an opportunity
to observe them when they don't know
- they're being observed?
- Want to spy on witches?
Wiccans.
No, I want you to spy on them,
while I study them
anthropologically.
Ground zero.
Fascinating.
What are they doing with
that Blair Witch thingy?
It's a miniature effigy.
Okay, why is it
when things like this happen,
it always happens to people
you don't want to see naked?
Okay, so we have...
Rowan and Eden, right?
- Ember.
- Ember. Exactly.
We'll give you
the names society assigned to us,
but not while in the Sacred Grove.
Okay, dancing naked is okay,
but Christian names are forbidden.
- Got it.
- We weren't doing anything wrong.
Why are you disrupting
a religious service?
You know what happened to Zephyra?
Is this by any chance
a totem representing her?
We were marking
the end of Zephyra's corporeal life.
Celebrating the unification
of her spirit with the elements.
Why would you do that?
Unless she was a member
of your coven.
She was not one of us.
- A bad witch.
- Sadly,
Zephyra performed magic for profit.
She was known to use human relics.
Such as the body of a Salem witch?
I don't know
where she would get that,
but that would be an immensely
powerful relic, yes.
So she has other clients.
We're gonna have to talk to them.
The dark arts are fragile,
Agent Booth.
Zephyra's clients employed her
to do evil.
Bad people getting other bad people
to do bad things.
What's that?
Fragments of the hyoid
and the throat cartilage.
Some of the smaller bones were
broken when the house collapsed.
They're very difficult to clean.
I may need to go back in with acetone.
Well, it's time to multi-task.
I have the evidence Angela
and Hodgins gathered from the scene.
I thought your intention
was to bring back Hodgins and Angela.
They had to wait for the judge,
and you can't bend the law
to help your friends.
We're going to do this without them.
They can coach us
and consult, but, yeah,
it's you and me.
So you expect me to deal with dirt.
Great.
Close, but now I'm up 18 cents.
Yeah, for now.
Nice!
Only 17.
Do you realize how long it's been since
we've spent this much time together?
Outside the lab, I mean?
Yeah, I know. God.
I keep thinking about
that crappy cabin
that we stayed in in the mountains.
Do you remember that?
30 degrees, there was no heat.
Man, this jail is way better
than that cabin.
That was a good weekend, though.
Keeping warm.
Your lab called.
This computer may not be
state-of-the-art,
- but we got the Internets.
- Sure.
Let's, throw some coal
in that thing and fire it up.
Cheri Byrd was a dark witch,
perhaps even a Satanist.
The Wiccans really seemed afraid of her.
What is this?
I found the transcripts
of the Salem Witch Trials.
I thought maybe we could identify
the remains that Cheri Byrd
dressed up in the wedding dress.
"Prudence Sullivan, female.
48 years of age, of small stature
"with back bent as though burdened
by great
- weight of guilt"?
- "Guilt."
It sort of matches
Dr. Brennan's description, right?
"Old, short, hunched over."
Sounds like every other witch.
No, no, that's a stereotype.
48 is old?
Well, it was back then.
I can't believe you got all this stuff.
Okay, trust me,
a Salem witch doesn't just
show up in Maryland.
Her grave was robbed for a reason.
I know my witches, all right?
- Sorry.
- Just put it down.
Relax. Slow down. Just sit.
I did so...
so much reading.
Nice cell.
It's not much, but we call it home.
We're thinking
of redoing the kitchen.
Okay, it's amber. It melts
at 400 to 700 degrees Fahrenheit...
temperatures easily
reached in the fire.
Is that a bug?
Oh, yeah, baby.
Check out those tibial bristles.
There's plenty of room in here, Sheriff,
if you want to join us.
That's against regulations.
You can verify
with the Entomology Department,
but I'm fairly certain
we're looking at
Nedocosia naiba.
It's a fungus gnat.
- Does that help with time of death?
- No.
This gnat would have had his last
fungus about a hundred
million years ago
in the Lower Cretaceous.
So, if we remove the DNA,
we could re-create dinosaurs, right?
It was probably an amber pendant
from an ordinary piece of jewelry.
What's with the hair?
- What hair?
- Yeah, she's right.
Check out the speck at 3:00 o'clock.
The amber probably picked up a piece
of hair when it melted in the fire.
But our victim's hair
was gray and wavy.
But this one is dark.
If the root bulb's present,
it could indicate that
the hair was forcibly removed.
So it could be from the perp.
I'm sorry. Caught up in
the thrill of the chase.
I'll run DNA.
So how are you guys doing?
I mean, we'd like to get out of here,
if that's what you mean.
I'm sure you will. Thanks, guys.
The hair in the amber gave us a hit.
CODIS says it belongs
to one Murray Huddler,
convicted of assault in 2008,
paroled last October.
Now this may possibly
go towards motive.
It certainly goes toward
"creepy coincidence."
"Dumped Hubby Decks Attorney."
So this man was incarcerated
for assaulting his
ex-wife's attorney?
Huddler's wife dumped him,
hosed him in a divorce,
then married the lawyer
that represented her. But look at this.
Anything look familiar to you?
She's wearing this dress.
Murray Huddler.
You know a woman by the
name of Cheri Byrd?
How about a witch named Zephyra?
- I'll take that as a yes.
- I hired her.
- Hired her for...?
- To put a hex
on my bitch ex-wife, okay?
- Is that illegal?
- Zephyra's dead.
She was murdered, house torched.
- You think I did it?
- I don't know.
Depends how much you
paid for the hex.
Two grand up front.
Three if it took.
- Did it take?
- No, it did not take.
I'm thinking you killed Zephyra,
and in the struggle,
- she yanked out some of your hair.
- No, I gave her my hair
for the spell.
That and my ex-wife's wedding dress.
Right. We found that in your truck.
That's not what you think it is.
I went fishing on Friday.
Fishing?
But you know if this blade
matches the stab marks
on Cheri Byrd's bones,
that could spell trouble for you.
Huddler's fishing knife is thin,
very sharp on one edge,
and has a slight curve at the tip.
The blade that made these cuts
is thicker, evenly tapered
and sharp on both edges,
like a dagger.
Definitely not a match.
What's this?
Fragments of the hyoid
and throat cartilage,
damaged by a fire and
crushed by a house.
- The acetone didn't help.
- These bones
certainly resemble the hyoid
and surrounding cartilage,
but not all of these are human.
What?
Okay, is this whole witchy thing
about to get creepier?
This looks like part
of a tiny joint.
I believe these bones are the incomplete
skeleton of a small animal.
What do you think?
A little outside my expertise,
but they look like bat bones to me.
You missed that, Clark?
Clark's error is
completely understandable,
given the condition of these remains
and the bizarre nature
of these circumstances.
Thank you, Dr. Brennan.
But I made the
call on a piece-of-crap
cathode-ray tube while in jail.
That's right: you're a criminal.
Are we thinking a woman
had a bat shoved down her throat?
Yes, that's exactly what happened.
- Thank you, Dr. Hodgins.
- What?
Another round?
Really? You sure?
You're down 31 cents.
32.
What?
Do you ever wonder
what happened to us...
on the day we broke up?
Every day.
I run through that
conversation word for word.
Me, too.
You said, "All you had
to do was trust me."
And you said, "Hey,
you're the one who's leaving."
And then you said, "You're the one
who isn't stopping me."
And I left.
Right.
Well, I wish I hadn't.
The biggest regret of my life
is I didn't stop you.
What was up with that?
I panicked.
I lost faith that I could
sustain that kind of happiness.
- You talk to Sweets?
- Kid's got the goods.
It was like we were both
playing chicken, and then we...
we both swerved.
What we should have done is
crashed right into each other.
At the speed of light.
The judge is here.
- The judge is a barber.
- Keeps me grounded.
It's against the rules for prisoners
to fraternize sexually
while in custody.
Maybe give it a rest, Gus?
Let's get you two out of here.
- Bat bones?
- A Myotis albescens.
Not indigenous to the United States,
but the bones are available online.
Like everything else.
I'll look.
So, I think I've identified
our skeleton bride.
- Look at that!
- You identified human remains?
Dr. Brennan, you said that
the woman was subjected
to a form of torture known
as "pressing".
Yes. That's how I surmised
we were dealing with the
remains of a Salem witch.
In fact, only one Salem witch
died as a result of pressing.
One female witch
and a 80-year-old man.
You don't care about the old man
Emily Quimby died November 1692.
Buried in Salem
in unconsecrated ground, of course,
but her grave was
robbed six months ago.
You think the victim dug
up the old witch's bones
- to increase her own power?
- Absolutely.
This is interesting,
but not pertinent to the case.
- Wait for it.
- Wait for it. Here it is.
Upon finding Emily Quimby's grave,
I researched her family tree,
and there's a 16-generation
remove, but...
- look.
- "Mary Harden Trent."
Direct descendant.
Why is that name familiar?
Mary Harden Trent is a member
of the Circle of Moonwick Coven.
Her witch name is "Ember".
Digging up great-grandma is not the
worst motive for murder I've ever heard.
what I'm doing here is releasing
you two on your own recognizance.
Thank you.
Yes, we will pay our fines and
make our court appearances.
I'm sure.
Gus will come after you if you
don't follow the letter of the law.
Let me notarize this stuff
and get you on your way.
Thank you.
How long did he say he'd be gone?
Mary Harden Trent.
That is your signature, correct?
Yes, though I prefer
to go by "Ember".
What do you say we step
outside your magic forest,
stay on point, okay?
Our credit card records show
that you purchased bat bones online.
Is that true?
Bat bones are an integral
part of my religion.
Did you shove those bat bones down her
throat before or after you stabbed her?
No! No, I swear upon the goddess
that I'm incapable of such violence.
- How tall are you?
- Five-two.
She may be too small to inflict
the injuries that killed our victim.
She may be small,
but she's full of anger.
There.
That is your great-great
something-grandmother Emily Quimby.
She was a witch, too.
And she didn't deserve to die.
What, did you boast to Zephyra
that witchism ran in your family?
Then she dug up your
ancestors' bones to use them
in what you call "dark rites".
What are you talking about?
How could anyone do something like that?
I had no idea.
Dr. Brennan. I finally
got the results back
on the powder
collected on the pathway
- around the victim's house.
- The circular path.
Usually the person standing
inside the circle is safe
from the dark forces.
In this case, oddly,
everything inside the
circle was destroyed.
- The powder was...
- Angela isn't here for a computer
re-creation, so we have to make do.
Please hold 1 and 4 in
the proper position.
Sweets, it's bilateral.
Do the same.
Booth believes a witch named
Ember to be the killer,
but the victim was a large
heavily muscled woman.
- Ember wasn't strong enough.
- I observed her in the woods.
She and the other one
were standing in a circle
taking turns with their
ceremonial object.
These stab marks...
reflect a similar pattern.
Now these injuries...
are clustered.
Five groupings of three.
So a total of 15 strikes.
In the same pattern
as the dots on the chimney.
It's a pentagram.
It's an ancient Wiccan symbol
that stands
for solidarity, some say sisterhood.
There are 15 women in
the Circle of Moonwick.
Ember alone wasn't the killer.
The entire coven took part.
They're white witches.
They stand for goodness.
What if they were stoned
out of their minds?
The powder on the path is called
Secale cereale: rye flour.
And it's infested with the fungus
Claviceps purpurea.
Formed in the ergot stage
of fungal development.
It's hallucinogenic. The natural
substance from which LSD is derived.
It was used for
ceremonial purposes centuries
ago in Salem.
Some people think that the exact
same substance was responsible
for the hysteria surrounding the
Witch Trials in the first place.
- Those naked ladies were trippin'.
- Add that to their rituals,
they may have thought the demon
they were slaying was real.
Wiccans do not ingest
any kind
of consciousness-altering drugs.
- Not on purpose.
- We believe
you were performing a ritual meant
to keep Zephyra's evil from
spreading past the circle.
A ritual using rye flour.
We use rye flour in many ceremonies.
And it has LSD fungus in it.
It's what made you afraid of Zephyra.
You thought that her obsession with
black arts could destroy you.
You also knew that she had
Ember's ancestor's
bones on her side.
You're good witches.
You're nice. You don't lie,
but when you make a mistake,
you want to make that
mistake right, right?
We were just trying to help.
We wanted Zephyra to live
in harmony, but she kept
cursing at us and casting spells.
We just wanted to
restore the balance.
Dearly beloved,
we're gathered here today
to join in holy wedded matrimony
Angela Pearly Gates Montenegro
and Jack Stanley Hodgins IV.
There's...
there's one small problem.
Please don't change your mind.
Oh, no. That's not it.
It's...
that's not my real name.
- How bad could it be?
- Yeah, did you get mine?
It's Stanley.
My dad is,
he's sort of unique,
and, he's Texan, and...
other things, so...
do you mind if I just,
if I whisper it to you?
- That'll work.
- Thank you.
We are here to wed these two people.
Vows?
Vows.
Angela...
or whatever your name is...
I'm your guy.
Stanley...
we're gonna live together
and're gonna love together
and we're gonna have so much fun,
and a little pain,
and we're gonna live a life
that's gonna make other people
die with jealousy
wishing they were us.
- Do you have rings?
- Yes.
Where'd you get that?
I've kept this in my wallet
since our first wedding.
- What?
- No, we didn't go through with it.
- Where'd you get that?
- I'll tell you later.
You may exchange the rings.
By the power vested in me
and the state of Maryland,
I now pronounce you husband
and wife. You may...
They were good.
Good people who butchered
another human being.
They were being attacked.
They weren't in their right mind,
and sometimes, people...
they just get carried away.
Crazy people.
What is that?
This was given to me by the witches.
It's you, Little Bones.
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is, you see?
The witch said that if I burned this
in your presence,
then the wish I make
for you will come true.
You think I care, but I don't.
It's just superstition.
And for superstition to work,
the person has to believe that he
is cursed... Watch!
You don't burn your fingers.
Want to know what I wished for?
No, it doesn't matter.
Completely irrelevant.
I wished...
I wished that
you could find happiness.
I don't know what that means.
Happiness, love, laughter,
friendship, purpose...
and a dance.
Then thank you.
Why is that funny?
'You wouldn't have thanked me
if you didn't think that
part of it was true.
No, I was thanking
you for your kindness,
not because I believed
in the outcome.
- I detected relief.
- No, no, you didn't.
Relief that the mojo
was good and not bad.
Now you're just mixing
up belief systems.
You want me to burn another one?
- No... how many do you have?
- Got a lot.