You know, we're gonna have
to break this to Sweets very gently.
Why? He should be grateful.
- He can be grateful later.
- What do you mean?
You know how people are grateful
when you yell fire,
but before they're grateful,
they panic, and run into walls?
You think Sweets is going
to panic and run into a wall?
Metaphorically. I got it.
He's not gonna like it.
If there was a mistake
- in one of my books, I'd want to know.
- What you call a mistake,
Sweets calls an interpretation.
Interpretation?
No, it's an actual factual error.
Okay, what exactly do you think,
you think we're telling him about?
Page 31. And I quote,
"Subjects worked together
for the first time in solving the murder
of pregnant congressional intern
Cleo Eller. "
Right, yeah.
That's right. We worked
that other case before that.
What did you think we were
going to talk to him about?
The whole... love thing?
The love thing?
His conclusion that we're in love?
I don't care about that.
- What mistake?
- Hint: It's not what you think.
You disagree with my conclusion
that the two of you are in love.
And the sublimating energies of
that connection are responsible
for the energy,
vigor and rigor that you bring
to your homicide investigations.
I just told you,
it's not what you think,
and you immediately say
what you think.
That's your interpretation.
We recognize your right to interpret.
You do?
That's your right as a psychologist
to get everything wrong.
I have circled some typos.
Other than that, and the fact that
the Cleo Eller murder
was not our first case,
you're ready to publish.
My interpretation of your working
relationship is based on
the unfolding, interpersonal dynamics
of that first case.
It wasn't our first case.
It's not your first case.
Well, then, please
tell me all about that real first case
to see if my conclusions
are still valid.
A girl was murdered,
and her remains were
thrown in a landfill.
Well, her name was Gemma Harrington.
The case was going nowhere.
I was at an early morning
Gamblers Anonymous meeting.
You snapped the nine.
Rack 'em.
Booth had a gambling problem
before he met me.
Well, since I mostly won,
it wasn't really a problem.
But it took your focus away
from more important things,
like work.
I was getting it under control.
- Nice shot, Tex.
- Thanks.
Right. Okay, on my way.
Thank you for seeing me.
Victim's mother, Jocelyn,
came to see me
to tell me that the New York
coroner's office was releasing
her daughter's remains for burial.
She was all upset.
Upset why?
The police had given up hope
of finding her daughter's killer.
The case was a split jurisdiction.
The girl was last seen in DC,
but her body was found
in New York in a landfill.
The New York coroner was in town,
and, I decided to meet with her.
I can get you Gemma's file,
but you know the definition of insanity
is to do the same thing,
expecting a different outcome.
Okay. Maybe I missed something?
How's about you get
another point of view?
Partner up.
You know I don't do that.
There's a forensic anthropologist
at the Jeffersonian.
I read that she solved how
Stone Age Hunter was murdered.
How does that help?
She can solve a 4,000-year-old homicide,
maybe she can help on Gemma Harrington.
- I could release the remains to her.
- You know what?
I'll catch up with you later, all right?
Forensics don't solve crimes. Cops do.
Same activity, same results.
Speaking of which, you look
like you've been up all night.
- I'm fine.
- Meaning you won?
That's when he said...
- What's that scientist's name?
- And Cam answered...
Which is me.
Most methods of removing flesh
have disadvantages.
I was lecturing
on defleshing techniques
at American University.
Methods which preserve the bone
perfectly require patience.
Bones was not what I expected.
... works quickly, but the bone itself
is cooked, transforming the marrow.
The first step is to use conventional
surgical implements,
being very careful that the scalpel
or forceps never come
in contact with bone.
Any questions?
I have a question.
Seems to me, if you,
remove the flesh,
aren't you, destroying the evidence?
On the contrary,
I am revealing evidence.
Thank you.
See you next week.
Just, one more thing.
I mean,
isn't all the good evidence
in the flesh?
You know, like, the poison
and the stab wounds and the bullets?
The important indicators are written
in the bone, if you look carefully.
So that's your thing.
Yes. I'm the best in the world.
You're serious.
He thought I was being humorous.
That turns out to be true.
But you didn't know that yet.
Are you a student here?
Special Agent Seeley Booth
from the FBI.
I'm Dr. Temperance Brennan
of the Jeffersonian Institution.
- Do you believe in fate?
- Absolutely not.
Ludicrous.
- I still don't.
- And I still do.
Bones - Season 5 Episode 16
"The Parts in the Sum of the Whole"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Kujathemas,
Dark_Chii
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
Booth decided not to provide me
with the murder victim's identity.
I wanted to see if she could find out
what I already knew.
A modicum of connective tissue
indicates that,
depending upon burial conditions,
the remains are less
than 200 years old.
Zack, we have to shift the paradigm.
This is a recent murder.
- What does this FBI agent want?
- Identification of the remains.
Apparently, the FBI has had no luck
with dental records or missing persons.
Pelvis tells us female
who has never given birth.
Eruption of the third molar
indicates adolescent.
The fingernails
have lacquer on them.
Fractures to the pars
interarticularis of the C2
indicate a blow to the forehead,
which may have caused unconsciousness,
but not death.
- What are you doing?
- We are identifying a murder victim.
From this century?
I'm taking the clothing.
I have asked you before
not to be so unpleasant.
- Please? I'm taking the clothing.
- Why?
- You are a botanist.
- Yeah, and a mineralogist
and a an entomologist,
which gives me the same number
of doctorates
as the two of you put together,
because you don't have any.
Look, I could find fibers, or spores
or other particulates.
Cause of death...
the sharp, symmetrical traumas
to both right and left temporals.
You can take the clothing
and leave now.
Yeah? You can take that femur
and shove...
Naomi from Paleontology suggests
that Hodgins is like that
because he needs to get laid.
That means engage in coitus.
- This is not a good likeness.
- Oh, my God.
No, this is...
This is accurate.
- Actually, this is very accurate.
- I disagree.
In reality, his nose
looks like a yam.
Could you go over there
and just wait for me over there?
So, you want to do, a caricature?
But an accurate one.
It's for my work.
- Oh, my God, that looks real.
- It is real.
Could-you provide me with a face?
- That, that's real?
- It's a murder victim.
Murder? Brennan, I thought
that your job was
mummies and cavemen.
- I mean, how did he die?
- She. It's a teenager.
Someone or something
crushed her skull.
Poor thing.
Could you maybe just
put that away now?
Well, the FBI wants
to know who she is.
But why me?
I mean, we've only known
each other a month.
Well, I interacted with you
at your art exhibit
because I was very impressed
with your command
of underlying structure.
- You will be paid.
- I'm in.
- I'm saving to go back to Paris.
- How much do you have saved up so far?
Whatever you're gonna pay
for that skull, facial murder,
barf-making monstrosity.
Transcripts, interviews,
phone logs, timelines.
They dropped the body off
at the Jeffersonian this morning.
- What did you tell them about it?
- Nothing.
The gambler in you
checking out the players.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
Don't thank me, Seeley.
Nobody wants this case anymore.
I'm sorry.
Traditionally, people disembarked
the elevator before reloading began.
I'm gonna take that
as an acceptance of my apology.
But it wasn't an acceptance.
It was an observation of social mores.
You're Dr. Brennan, right?
We met at a conference on decapitation.
Never mind.
Your victim was 16 years old,
biracial.
She died between three
and four years ago,
and her body was left in a landfill
for approximately one year.
She was born in Southern Alabama
but moved north
when she was eight years old.
She was injured in a pre-1998
automobile, no airbags,
when she was 13.
- What?
- I'm not done.
Judging by her ribcage
and diaphragm attachments,
she was either a swimmer,
a singer or an asthmatic,
or any combination thereof.
This preliminary sketch...
gives you a general idea
of what she looks like.
I'm sorry, but we've been unable
to find out her name.
Just for future reference, those
human remains are forensic evidence.
You should be wearing gloves.
I will adjust my behavior
accordingly.
- What is this?
- Just watch.
She bares a marked resemblance
to the sketch I gave you.
Gemma Harrington.
She's been dead for four years.
Her body was found in a landfill
3 years ago.
She's the murder victim?
Listen, I'm sorry.
- Sorry for the victim?
- Sorry for holding back her identity.
Even though my time
and expertise are extremely valuable,
I accept your decision
to test my abilities.
Obviously,
I passed with a lot of color.
- Pardon me?
- It means I did very well.
Right.
Flying colors.
- You passed with flying colors.
- Yes. I know.
But passing your tests
suggests you have something
more important in mind.
I want to catch this bastard{\ bastard
who killed her}.
But how do you know he was a bastard?
How do you even know it was a man?
You know who that is?
Judge Myles Hasty.
That's a federal judge.
Well, I don't follow current events
past the industrial revolution.
- He killed Gemma.
- But why haven't you arrested him?
- I don't have enough proof.
- Then how do you know it's him?
I just know.
And I'd like to ask you
to help me to catch him.
- I won't do that.
- Why?
I will help you find out the truth,
and if the truth is that he killed her,
I will help you catch him.
But first the truth, then the catching.
Look, all I need is the kind of crap
that persuades a jury.
But it seems to me someone like you
could benefit hugely
from an association
with someone like me.
You're being serious.
You're serious.
I was just kidding.
You know, I was having some fun.
It is fun.
This all happened a year
before the Cleo Eller case?
Almost to the day.
13 months, less a week.
And you didn't argue?
Even though he withheld
information and tested you.
Well, my abilities were
outside his experience.
He called evidence crap.
And she basically
called you stupid.
We were feeling each other up.
Like a honeymoon period.
"Out".
We were feeling each other out.
You want to hear the rest
of that story?
I only knew Hodgins slightly
as a very unpleasant authority
on ancient spores and insects.
But he was the one who figured out
that the remains were
in a landfill for a year
before being discovered.
And that wasn't all.
I found a sliver
on the dead girl's clothing.
The term is nebulous.
Wood.
I found a splinter of wood.
Maple, to be exact.
So, your murder victim
most likely struck
with something made out of maple.
Still an observation so vague
as to approach meaninglessness.
Is he trying to piss me off?
You are always angry.
You have an anger management problem.
I'm in a program.
Supposed to snap this
every time I get angry.
I'd be happy to do that for you.
The victim's boyfriend was in town
the day she disappeared.
Trying out for a minor league
baseball team.
- Okay. So?
- What are baseball bats made of?
Maple?
Maple.
I should've thought of that.
I'm not so sure a baseball bat attack
would leave behind splinters.
Then why posit it as a weapon?
Doubts.
I have doubts, you see.
I am doubtful.
Perhaps the two of you could
design an experiment.
What?
No. Wait.
Work together?
I brought in Gemma's baseball-playing
boyfriend
for questioning for murder,
but I know he didn't do it.
- Well, how do you know?
- Why, because the killer's Judge Hasty.
Feeling isn't knowing.
When you know something
you can argue fact,
not merely make insupportable claims
in a passionate tone.
You said that in a passionate
tone without facts.
You see, when it comes down to it,
it's all about what you feel.
Why are you interrogating the boyfriend
if you're already convinced?
Because I want to convince you.
That's very kind.
Can I come in and watch you
broil the suspect?
Yeah, well, I could broil,
but I think you mean grill.
I fell apart after I heard
that Gemma got killed.
Couldn't concentrate on anything,
you know?
Couldn't hold it together.
Some people might say the result
of a guilty conscience.
I was in DC
to try out for a minor
league baseball team.
My dad was with me,
three of my uncles and four cousins.
I wasn't away from anybody
long enough to kill Gemma,
and transport her body
to New York City.
He has alibis?
Tell Dr. Brennan how you did
at your tryouts.
I did great.
What does that have to do with anything?
Your tryouts were
after Gemma was killed.
Yeah, but I didn't know that yet.
I thought everything was great.
I didn't fall apart until after
I found out Gemma was murdered.
I still dream about being there
when that happened.
About protecting her.
Psychologically consistent.
I'm not well-acquainted with psychology,
but anthropologically speaking,
men are programmed
to consider themselves
the protectors of their mates.
It was unnecessary
to put you through this again.
I don't mind coming and
answering questions,
'cause it means that you guys
are still looking.
And I want that.
Why are you the deliver of the blow
while I am the recipient?
Because you grunted
when you picked up the bat.
Brace yourself.
Excuse me.
Go back to work, please.
Conclusions thus far?
No, nothing.
The bat did not leave any slivers,
even though the suit is more abrasive
than the cotton the victim was wearing.
A blow like that would have left behind
unmistakable bone damage.
Have you tried striking Zack
in the soft tissue or in the liver?
- What?
- Yeah, anatomy's really not my thing.
That one had some pepper!
That would most certainly
have caused hemorrhaging in
the liver followed by death.
Nothing.
The bat is so honed
and close-grained, it cannot be broken
on the soft tissues of a human being.
We can try striking his head.
What?!
Unnecessary.
I guess a baseball bat
was not the murder weapon.
I found something interesting
in the victim's X-rays.
The bones of the inner ear
are missing here.
Indicating that they may
have been extracted during the assault.
Did you set up the UV light source?
Look, I'll do it, Zack.
Thank you, Dr. Brennan.
It's hard to move in this suit.
These bone bruisings
occurred before death.
Possibilities?
Recurring patterns.
So, either struck repeatedly
with the same narrow weapon,
or perhaps
crushed beneath some kind of grid.
Could you please measure
the exact distances
- between the bruises?
- Of course.
So, at 6:30 P. M.,
Gemma and her choir sang here
for a group of hoity-toits.
I don't know what that means.
Shakers and machers you know,
and influential types,
including Judge Hasty.
There was a reception at 9:00 P. M.
Gemma was seen
at the beginning of the reception
and then poof.
A year later, her remains were found
in a New York City landfill.
What are we looking for?
The source of the pattern
of bone bruising
that happened very shortly
before she died.
Regular strikes approximately
33 centimeters apart,
spanning the remains
from forehead down to mid-femur.
I was thinking something
made of maple.
A heavy bookcase,
scaffolding, a ladder.
I gotta tell you.
I really am enjoying working with you.
- Bones is not my name.
- Well, it's a nickname?
Yes, I see.
I could call you Shoes.
Shoes? Why Shoes?
Yes, because they are so very shiny.
Shoes, they're part of my uniform.
The FBI,
they just have a way of doing things.
Anthropologically speaking,
paramilitaristic organizations tend
to constrain individuality.
That's for sure.
But in any group,
no matter how restrictive,
the freethinkers, the mavericks,
the rebels with leadership quality
find ways to declare
their distinctiveness.
You know,
I'm a freethinking rogue rebel.
Are you seeing anyone?
Right to the point there, Bones?
Casually, but she doesn't
really like my hours.
You?
A physicist has been asking me out.
I was thinking of saying yes.
I'd ask you out if I could.
Why can't you?
Well, FBI rules again.
No fraternizing with other agents
or consultants.
That's too bad.
Glad you think so.
These stairs.
They're made out of maple.
The sliver on the victim's
clothing could have
come from violent contact
with stairs.
What about the bone bruising?
The hypotenuse of the triangle
formed by the riser
and tread looks to be
approximately 33 centimeters.
Gemma was probably trying to escape.
Down here and the judge...
probably dragged her
to the exit right over here.
There it is.
The killer could've driven back here
and taken her away
without being seen.
You think that Gemma Harrington
was chased by Judge Hasty?
He played football.
Then he swung her
into a wall or something?
No, no, no.
- The next part here shows that...
- Who's this now?
I'm Angela Montenegro.
I'm an artist.
Who are you?
She's a federal prosecutor.
On our side.
Tell her Angela possesses extremely
keen spatial awareness.
- And who's this now?
- That's Squint.
I'm Dr. Temperance Brennan
from the Jeffersonian.
Don't bother. You know?
Never remember Squints.
- That's correct, and you know why?
- Why?
Because they get all wishy-washy and
flip-floppy on the witness stand.
So it's better
I don't remember the last time
they let me down
when I meet them again.
Here, continue
with the flip book there.
So the judge tackles Gemma...
You remember?
Football in college.
... and grabs her ankle.
There. All of a sudden,
he's got an unconscious girl.
And you know, he thinks she's dead.
Loads her into his car
at the bottom of the stairs,
and drives her to a landfill
in New York.
- Why was he chasing?
- Who cares why?
Let's see. A judge, a jury,
the press, and me.
All I need
is a warrant to arrest Judge Hasty.
Well, maybe if this little
stick figure thing
was a big computer,
lots of bells and whistles,
but right now, it just looks like
a sadistic children's book.
What's the
pinch-of-death grip thing
that killed the girl?
We don't know yet.
This won't get me a warrant.
I'm a lowly federal prosecutor, and
Hasty is a big-shot federal judge.
A hoity-toit.
I see what's going on here.
You've always wanted this office.
Tired of sitting out there
in the bullpen.
Well, I'm not committing career suicide
because you're cute and want a window.
We should go, yeah.
Listen, he is very cute.
I do respond to the breadth of
his shoulders and his strong jaw line.
Guys, guys, okay.
Caroline says
that we can't arrest the judge
but she doesn't say
we can't ask him a few questions.
Thanks so much for coming down,
Judge Hasty.
As you pointed out, if I refused,
the headline news would read:
"Federal Judge declines
to Cooperate in Homicide Investigation".
What we think is that you chased
Gemma Harrington,
and she fell down those stairs.
Okay. Way to jump right in there.
- She was trying to escape you.
- Why?
- I'm a very nice man.
- Did you use that line on her, too?
The only words I ever spoke to the girl
were "You have a lovely voice".
I said it in front
of a hundred people.
What did you not do in front
of a hundred people, Judge?
Booth is suggesting sexual
impropriety.
So I chased her
through the opera house.
That's very melodramatic.
And then what?
I pushed her down the stairs?
No. She was trying to get away from you,
and you tripped her, and she fell down.
- And she died?
- No. Those injuries didn't kill her.
You're making this all up.
And she's making you look like an idiot.
No. In fact, I am very intelligent.
You could have fooled me.
You're ridiculous.
Is this very bad?
I have been wanting
to do that for years.
You are so hot!
That's great!
That woman punched a federal judge
in the nose!
Twice!
Self-defense. He was panicking.
All right, we got a right.
Fire her and cut all ties.
- With luck, Hasty sues her and not us.
- I can't do that.
She should never have been in the field.
I'm sympathetic.
I have let a pretty face lead me down
the path of unrighteousness.
Yours, for example.
Well, it's not like that.
Of course it is. Watching you two
together is like being at prom.
But it's not highschool now, Booth.
It's grownup time.
The beautiful scientist is fired.
She just doesn't know it yet.
That oversight is what
you must rectify.
My advice? Get her drunk first.
Me?
I'm trying to estimate the force needed
to cause this damage to the skull.
Alligator bites have been
measured at 2,000 pounds of force.
Hyenas at a thousand, sharks at 330.
Whatever did this damage was somewhere
between a human and a chimpanzee,
meaning approximately
250 pounds of force.
I just had a terrible thought.
We removed the flesh by boiling.
What if there were particulates on
the bone which Hodgins could identify?
But we're not used to dealing with
such fresh kills. We must adapt.
Could I help?
This place is huge.
Angela, this is my assistant,
Zack Addy.
Zack, this is my
friend, Angela Montenegro.
It's Jimmy Neutron, huh?
Boy scientist?
- I don't know what that means.
- Neither do I.
It occurred to me when I did
the facial reconstruction that
the girl's head was slammed.
Well, a door would have crushed
the entire side of her head, Ange.
Right, but what if it were
some kind of protuberance,
like a bolt or something?
- A sliding door?
- Well, I don't know.
I'm an artist. I belong in Paris.
What about a car trunk
with a catch and a latch?
How much force would a
slamming car trunk generate?
Is he doing that in his head?
260 force pounds, give or take.
That could fit.
I have to go meet Booth.
I have a little math
problem you can't solve.
Can God create a bigger
rock than he can roll?
Think about it.
Drink up, eh? All right?
So all we have to do
is compare the wounds
in the victim's skull
with the judge's cars.
Let's just stop talking about the case,
just for one moment, all right?
Check this out.
I am declaring my individuality.
I am going rogue.
You have gone rogue.
You can handle
your liquor very well.
This is nothing compared to the bang
I had to drink in India.
It's made of fermented cannabis.
Here's to bang.
To bang.
You're fired.
What?! Why?
Because I drank bang?
But that was in pursuit
of scholarly research.
Why am I fired?
Because you
assaulted a federal judge.
- You thought that was hot.
- I did. I did. It was very hot.
Cheers.
If we don't work together anymore,
then we could have sex.
I'll call a cab.
Hold on, listen.
Hold that cab. Listen,
I got something to confess.
Is it the fact that
you're a direct descendant
of John Wilkes Booth?
I already know that.
- Wait. How do you know that?
- From your bone structure.
Just keep that under your hat,
okay, for now, all right?
Okay.
What I wanted to confess was...
See, I have a gambling problem,
but I'm dealing with it.
Why did you feel you
had to tell me that?
I don't know. I just feel like...
this is going somewhere.
Why did you feel like
this is going somewhere?
I just... I feel like
I'm gonna kiss you.
You kissed?
There was tongue contact.
My book is crap.
That's why we wanted to come here.
We wanted to warn you, so you wouldn't
be barking up the wrong tree.
How long did this affair last?
- Should we tell him?
- Yes! Yes, you should.
We are not spending
the night together.
Of course we aren't. Why?
Tequila.
Hey, hold the cab.
Hold the cab.
So you're afraid that when I look at you
in the morning, I'll have regrets?
That would never happen.
I went home and went to bed.
So did I.
We have to tell you something.
Zack told me how bad you felt about
boiling all the particulates.
- I need some coffee.
- This is coffee.
Thanks.
Despite the boiling, I was able to get
microscopic samples from the bones.
Have I mentioned how excited
I am to be working with you?
Yeah, you-you mentioned it.
Dr. Hodgins found
microscopic fragments
of steel and traces
of lubricating oil.
Zack and I compared manufacturer's specs
for the judge's trunk to the victim's
gaping head wound.
One of them matched.
- We got fired.
- A '56 Bel Air.
- What?
We got fired? Is this
because you slept with Booth?
I didn't sleep with Booth.
Why did you say that?
- Tequila.
- What is happening?
I got us fired because I punched
a judge in the schnozz.
I'm never gonna make it to Paris.
Angela, I can offer you steady
employment reconstructing
- ancient remains and tombs and digs.
- Really?
I've always wanted
to go to Paris with an artist.
Zack, take all of the
evidence to Booth at the FBI.
Then we all can go
back to our normal jobs.
You ever feel like you saw something
great that almost happened,
then it didn't?
- Are you Special Agent Booth?
- What are you?
The Jeffersonian, right.
You must be one of the Squints.
I'm not familiar with that term.
Squint. You know, you guys...
you squint when you look at things.
Just like that.
This is proof that Federal Judge
Myles Hasty murdered Gemma Harrington.
What proof?
It was immensely stupid
of you to fire us.
Sorry, but did you
just call me stupid?
I can only conclude that
you are immensely stupid.
You fired
the Jeffersonian Institution?
I don't know what
any of this stuff means.
Yeah, Caroline made me.
Dr. Bones punched the
judge right in the nose.
- They got the judge.
- They got the judge?This is good news.
What did I tell you?
The girl's head was smashed in
by the locking mechanism
of a '56 Bel Air.
- Here's the evidence.
- Oh, more stickman cartoons?
Yes, but, you can jazz it up
with computers before trial.
- Look at the evidence.
- If you're wrong about this,
my career is over.
So, don't tell me to
look at the evidence,
because you know I will.
And, you, reassure me.
Cam and I,
we did look at the evidence,
and we both feel
that there is enough here to
get a warrant to search
the judge's vehicle.
He'd better have done this, because
irritating a federal judge...
very unwise.
A small trace of blood, any DNA
would be enough to make an arrest.
- You fire the Jeffersonian already?
- Of course.
- Hire her back.
- Okay.
And push come to shove,
you be ready to testify that judge
walked into a door or something.
I'll have your warrant in an hour.
So why are you still here?
You're back, baby!
You're rehired!
- But I've moved on.
- What is that, a monkey?
No, this is Ardipithecus ramidus
kadabba, the earliest known...
Okay, abracadabra can wait.
All right, we have a
warrant for the judge's car.
So, let's go. What's the matter?
Get your coat. Chop-chop.
Is something wrong?
I find I'm annoyed with you.
Because I fired you and hired you back?
It's the government.
No, because you got me drunk to fire me,
and then have sex with me.
No, I got myself drunk
so I could fire you,
and you decided
not to have sex with me,
which I accepted gracefully.
So, you're regretting that decision?
No. I'm not. It was a very
good decision. I stand by it.
What's going on, Bones?
Do not call me Bones.
This car's been cleaned, sanded
and repainted, and the rug is new.
- Nothing?
- Nothing.
Can I have my car back?
I see no reason why not.
You've done nothing but cooperate
at every stage of this investigation.
- That's it?
- We don't have anything.
- My people should look at it.
- Why?
- Because we're smarter than you.
- I beg your pardon?
Do you really think brightest
go into law enforcement?
They go to the Jeffersonian.
Really? Because, the one I met couldn't
pick his nose without instruction.
The locking mechanism
should be removed.
Excuse me. You know what?
You really need to learn
how to speak to human beings.
I speak six languages. Two of
which you've never even heard of.
- You're a cold fish.
- You're a superstitious moron.
- Get a soul.
- Get a brain.
What?
I'm Agent Booth. What?
What is that?
- I have no idea.
- It's a stapes.
- It's a bone from the inner ear.
- Gemma Harrington's?
I have to do some tests.
Anyone who took science
should know that.
Anyone with a high school education
would figure,"Who else's could it be?"
Send this to the Jeffersonian.
We'll check it for DNA.
All right, you know what?
That's fine, all right. That's it.
Judge Hasty,
you are under arrest, pal.
- Are you okay?
- Here, have a glass of water.
It's like... it's like
you two missed your moment.
And then you punished
each other for it.
And you know who ends
up paying the price?
Me.
I do.
Okay, what happened next?
The minute I had the judge
in the interrogation room,
he started to mess up.
Stapes.
It was Gemma Harrington's stapes,
of course.
So, we had proof she had been
killed in the trunk of his car.
Nice car. That's her locking.
We also had testimony from
the valet who
saw him pull in the back alley.
Lie upon lie.
Fact upon fact.
But I just...
I didn't know why.
Booth is obsessed with
why people do things.
What did Gemma see?
Why did Hasty chase her
through the back of the theater?
- But you figured it out, right?
- Not me.
Me.
I noticed the way he touched
his nose very gingerly.
Now, considering you have no motive,
I'm sure you can see
there's no sense in
detaining my client.
I know what happened.
When the prosecutor tells the
jury, they're going to believe it, too.
It had to be something that
would've ruined his career.
But also destroyed his judgment.
You've had your septum replaced.
What was it?
Cocaine? Crystal meth?
Gemma saw you snorting something.
He thought he killed her on the stairs,
so he went to his car.
She regained consciousness as
he loaded her into the truck.
He panicked and slammed the lid,
which... killed her.
I just wanted to stop her.
Reason with her.
Maybe offer her a bribe.
- But she ran.
- That's enough, Myles.
And it was.
Judge Hasty will be eligible
for parole in ten years.
That's the story of our first case.
Orry about your book.
No, it's not. It's not.
What happened between you two?
We started to argue.
In front of the victim's mother.
I was worried that we still
didn't have enough evidence to convict.
I told her this was definitely
not the place to bring this up.
- Let go of me!
- I will, if you would just...
- What the hell?
- You are a bully!
You grab my arm just like the judge.
You use your badge and your
gun to intimidate people.
The way you use your brain to make
people around you feel stupid.
You are a stupid man.
I hate you.
You hate me.
Are you ten years old?
I'm not your dad.
- I will never work with you again.
- Who asked you?
- You struck him?
- I shouldn't have grabbed her.
We're sorry about your book.
Okay, this is... you...
you are totally messed up.
I always said that you could never kiss,
because then the dam would break.
And now it turns out that you kissed.
Did the dam break?
What does that mean?
He still thinks
that we slept together.
We're not in love with each other.
It took us a year after we kissed to
be in the same room together, right?
Oh, absolutely.
Right. No more kissing or anything.
If you're not, then
how come you haven't been in any serious
relationships since you first met?
- I don't really do that.
- You know, a job, son.
One of you has to have the
courage to break this stalemate.
You. It's got to be you,
because you're the gambler.
For once,
make that work for you.
Something to eat?
- I could eat.
- Okay. Sorry about that book.
In his book, Sweets wrote that being
abandoned by my parents made me
convinced that all meaningful
relationships are doomed.
He wrote that I got
white knight syndrome,
because of my physically,
abusive, alcoholic father.
Hate psychology.
I'm the gambler.
I believe in giving this a chance.
Look, I want to give this a shot.
You mean us?
- The FBI won't let us work together.
- Don't do that. That is no reason...
- No!
- Why? Why?
You thought you're protecting me,
but you're the one who needs it.
- Protecting from what?
- From me.
I don't have your
kind of open heart.
Give it a chance.
That's all I'm asking.
You said it yourself.
The definition of insanity
is doing the same thing
over and over again and expecting
a different outcome.
Then let's go for a different outcome,
all right? Hear me out, all right?
When you talk to older couples who
have been in love for 30
or 40 or 50 years, all right?
It's always the guy
who says "I knew".
I knew.
Right from the beginning.
Your evidence is anecdotal.
I'm that guy.
- Bones, I'm that guy.
- I know.
I am not a gambler.
I'm a scientist.
I can't change.
I don't know how.
Please don't look so sad.
You're right. You're right.
Can we still work together?
Thank you.
But I got to move on.
You know,
I got to find someone who's,
who's going to love me
in 30 years or 40 or 50.
I know.
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--