Dr. Brennan, Dr. Hodgins,
Mr. Vega, thank you for coming.
You get a "notice to appear"
from a federal judge.
- You appear?
- I assume
this has something to do
with the Grave Digger.
The only thing the 3 of us
have in common is that kidnapper.
My name is Heather Taffet.
I'm the United States Attorney
assigned to the Grave Digger case
last month.
- What happened to Ms. Kurland?
- She was killed
in a car accident in Boston.
You think the Grave Digger had Kurland
killed because she was getting close?
She wasn't getting close.
She was barely conducting
an investigation.
Nothing has moved in
the Grave Digger case in months.
It turns out something did move.
Some evidence has gone missing.
You suspect that one of us
stole Grave Digger evidence?
From the FBI?
Mr. Vega is a former FBI agent
as well as a best-selling author
on the Grave Digger.
- You both contract out to the FBI...
- Let me make this very clear:
if any of you has any evidence
linked to the Grave Digger case,
I am ordering you as a federal judge
to turn it over to Ms. Taffet.
Turn it over to me today,
and you get full immunity.
Look at that.
Oh, it's got to be Bones,
I guarantee ya.
Yep. I'm hurrying, Bones.
- Do you need directions?
- No, I do not need directions,
because I am driving.
My GPS can provide perfect
directions in several languages.
Well, get this.
Okay, Parker
got me this new watch
and it does the same thing.
- In several languages?
- No.
Then it's not the same thing.
I bet you are looking beautiful?
Because I am in the finest tux
that money can rent.
I'm on my way home to get dressed,
you need to be there an hour and a half
before me to watch the tribute video.
My GPS indicates that it is
a 25 minute drive for you.
- This is my big night.
- All right, listen, don't worry.
I will be there when they crown
you super scientist.
I will be the guy
in the cocky belt buckle
and the snazzy rented tux.
- Someone's knocking on my door.
- How can there be a knock
at your door
if you're already driving?
- You're late.
- I know.
It took my longer
to get dressed than I thought.
But don't worry,
my GPS will get us there on time.
It's not a time machine, sweetie.
I call shotgun.
No.
I have taken Seeley Booth.
He has been buried alive.
He has 21 hours to live.
Bring the evidence
to the SW5 DC boundary stone
in return for which
you will receive GPS coordinates.
If you involve law enforcement,
I will know
and Seeley Booth will die.
This is my final communication.
What's going on?
The Grave Digger has Booth.
He's not here. I told you.
I was hoping it was like a prank call
or something.
- The door was locked.
- What does that mean?
I doubt that the Grave Digger
would take the time to...
Give me the shoe.
Would take the time to lock
the front door on his way out.
Yeah, especially lugging 190 pounds
of unconscious Booth.
He was dragged to the window.
Oh, my God.
Okay, all right,
we need to call the authorities.
We're in way over our heads here.
No. I read up on this guy.
If we want Booth back,
we need to pay the ransom.
The Grave Digger wanted evidence.
- What evidence?
- It has to be the same
that the state attorney and the FBI
think that I have, which I don't.
- What... What are you doing?
- They called in Hodgins, too.
- You think he stole the evidence?
- I know you didn't.
Bones - Season 04 Episode 14
"The Hero in the Hold"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, IceFreak
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
- Could you stop that, please?
- I was just working off adrenaline.
How long ago did the Grave Digger
get Booth? What kind of time do we have?
I know you have
what the Grave Digger wants.
The evidence that the judge
told us about.
The Grave Digger
thinks that I have it.
But he's wrong. It's you.
Give it to me.
Who's there?
- Who's that?
- It's me.
Who's me?
Best buddy you ever had.
Your words.
Teddy?
This isn't real.
I'm gonna go with real.
Nice monkey suit, by the way.
I never would have thought
to go formal to a kidnapping.
Look, no... no offense,
but, you know, I've been...
I've been drugged, electrocuted,
stuffed in a Beatles toy.
You're...
You're an hallucination,
that's what you are... an hallucination.
That's nice.
I show up to help you,
and you toss me off
as a hallucination.
You're dead, Corporal.
I felt your heart stop.
No use crying
over spilt milk, Sarge.
You know what? This isn't real.
I am going to focus
on what is real, right?
Real,
like getting out of this place. Okay.
Nah, Sarge, it's too high.
How about that one?
I already saw that.
You're getting competive
with a hallucination.
What? Oh, right. Nah, still here.
You really haven't changed, Sarge.
Once you knew what had to be done,
nothing could stop you.
- Enough already, okay?
- Yes, sir, Sergeant.
I got this.
Hey, look at that, making progress.
There.
- That's everything.
- The judge was after a specific piece.
Something that you stole
from the FBI.
I remember that.
- That was embedded in your leg.
- Yeah.
Probably came off
the bumper of the vehicle
the Grave Digger used
to run me over.
That would be shortly before
he buried me alive.
With me.
Pretty close to
discovering the manufacturer.
Which will help us narrow down
the suspect pool.
Booth doesn't have
that kind of time.
- What is that?
- Evidence that the Grave Digger wants.
Sweets, you shouldn't be here.
The Grave Digger said
no FBI involvement.
- I'm a psychologist, not a agent.
- An FBI psychologist.
Dr. Sweets, get gone now.
You stole evidence?
You don't know what it was like...
being buried in that car.
- I do. I was there.
- I know.
And if we turn over that evidence,
we will never catch the Grave Digger.
Booth only has 19 hours.
OK, OK, then let's just take 10 of those
hours and see if we can do both.
I'm telling you the answer is there.
Ten hours.
Eight.
And Dr. Hodgins is never left alone.
- You don't trust him?
- No, I don't.
I scanned the new recording.
Bring the evidence to the SW5 DC
boundary stone
in return for which you will receive
GPS coordinates.
If you involved
law enforcement, I will know
and Seeley Booth will die.
This is my final communication.
Along with the recording that
the Grave Digger gave when
you and Hodgins were kidnapped.
You okay to hear that?
Temperance Brennan and Jack Hodgins
have been buried alive.
Wire transfer $8 million
to the following Grand Cayman accounts
or they will suffocate to death.
... and Seeley Booth will die.
... or they will suffocate to death.
Now, despite the voice scrambler,
I was able to extract
specific phonemes
by running the waveform through
a Fourier Transform.
Graphically, they're identical.
Can we hear the unscrambled voice?
No, the coding was too complicated.
But the voice scrambler
was triggered to compress
at a certain set level.
Now, in this case,
it was set to the volume
of a human voice.
So when the Grave Digger
isn't speaking...
The background noise
pops into the foreground,
uncompressed.
What is that?
I'm... still working on that.
Sorry, I...
We'll get Booth back.
You can't know that.
- I just think that...
- Just...
work, please.
Let me try another algorithm.
Birds?
Gulls. Seagulls.
The Grave Digger was near the water.
Fresh one?
What?
Hallucinations can't help out a little?
- Give me that.
- You're welcome.
No, Sarge, pry with your legs.
Watch you don't hurt your back.
That can't be good.
Hang on, Teddy,
you're gonna make it.
Might want to close that up, Sarge.
Hey, guys.
There was no voice match, but
there was a point of origin on the call.
- Seagulls?
- I talked to Booth
an hour and 47 minutes
before I got the ransom call.
That merry-go-round...
The boardwalk.
King's Beach boardwalk.
I got it.
Vega lives in a penthouse apartment
just off the boardwalk.
You think this is my fault.
If you hadn't stolen the evidence,
he would never have taken Booth.
Rationally speaking,
it was inevitable.
It would have happened
anytime we got close.
Is that Vega's car?
- Who is that?
- It's Vega.
He's dead.
Looks like he was killed somewhere else
and then placed here.
We should take his body
back to the lab.
Obviously,
the Grave Digger killed him.
There's got to be evidence
that we can use.
Remove a body from a crime scene?
That would be a very bad idea.
Step away from the car, please.
Agent Perotta.
Look, if the water rises up
far enough,
I'll be able to get to that door
and open it.
What, the room isn't filling up
quickly enough for you already?
You were here for an interview?
He was writing
"Surviving the Grave Digger".
- He wanted to talk to us.
- At 5:00 in the morning?
It was a breakfast meeting.
- Were you following us, Agent Perotta?
- Yes, Dr. Brennan, I was.
You two are suspected
of stealing evidence.
This doesn't exactly
clear you of suspicion.
Well, was he under surveillance?
Because a fat lot of good
the FBI did him.
Well, it appears that he was the one
who had the evidence.
- Are we free to go now?
- Why not?
They have us under surveillance.
I'll be in touch.
Tell you what, you were always the guy
to be with in a tough spot.
You never said anything
like that, Sarge.
Mostly, you just grunted,
made me get coffee.
You think what's behind, hatch is gonna
be better than the last thing we opened?
I'll tell you what, I'm either gonna
drown fast or really, really slow.
Coming up pretty fast here, Sarge.
Vega's dead.
Right, like murdered dead?
We had no opportunity to
to examine the remains before
the FBI interrupted us.
What? FBI?
Yep, FBI Special Agent Perotta.
We're going to swing by,
pick up the evidence
and deliver it to the Grave Digger.
- You mean just do what he wants?
- We have no other choice.
You spoke to the FBI.
We didn't talk to the FBI,
they talked to us.
I don't think the Grave Digger's gonna
take that into consideration.
We still have time to catch
the Grave Digger and to save Booth.
- The odds are not acceptable.
- Why?
- Because we don't have Booth to help!
- Let's be clear here.
What we intend to do next
constitutes felony conspiracy.
Not you.
Me. I can do it alone.
No, no.
Nobody does anything alone.
Vega was alone.
What's the hell
is that supposed to be for?
It's a fulcrum, Sarge.
We... both work it together.
There, right there.
Ready?
- All right, get in.
- Real people go first, Sarge.
Get in before
I change my mind, will you?
Okay, get-get a grip, Sarge.
You're attacking your own hallucination.
Only you are not an hallucination.
You helped me open up that hatch.
I wouldn't have been able to open up
without you.
So what does that make me?
You are a ghost.
I'm a ghost?
Hey, why aren't you scared?
You being a ghost is not even
on the list of things that scare me.
I kept telling you, I said,
"Learn to pick a lock."
- You remember your response, Sarge?
- Yeah.
"Any lock worth picking
is worth kicking."
And I still stand by it.
Hey, please, stand by it.
Advice like that, it's a miracle
I lived as long as I did.
- You got a cuff link?
- Yeah.
Twenty.
What's that?
You were 20 years old when you died.
Still am. You, Sarge,
I got to say,
you've put a couple years on.
Is it true that the 30s is when your
body really starts going south on you?
- Hey, you got any kids, Sarge?
- Yeah, I got a boy.
What's his name?
Ah, you're probably
gonna take this wrong.
Why? What'd you do?
You name him something stupid,
like Cutter?
What, Tanner? Brady?
Oh, God, you didn't name him
Sebastian?
Parker.
I named him Parker.
That's my name.
It's your last name.
You know,
and your lock picking sucks.
You named your kid after me?
Yeah.
- What's he like?
- He's just like a kid, you know?
But, he's even better.
- Does he like you?
- Of course he likes me.
He loves me.
I'm his dad, you know?
He even got me this watch.
- What about his mom?
- Yeah, she... she likes me.
But...
she didn't love me.
- You loved her though?
- Of course I loved her.
I still do. I just...
I just don't like her too much.
You saw I picked the lock, right?
We're on a ship.
- Sarge?
- Yeah.
This particular ship ain't gonna be
floating much longer.
C-4 explosives.
There's a boundary
stone through the clearing.
This is weird...
Something nearby is
broadcasting a video signal.
There.
A camera.
Up in that tree.
That's how the grave digger will see
that we brought what he wants.
I might be able to hack into
the camera's broadcast frequency.
I got to say, doesn't seem
to be the smartest move
to just hand over this evidence.
We need to be rational.
We should maximize the chances
to catch the grave digger,
not minimize them.
Listen to me, Brennan.
Somebody you love is buried alive.
You're allowed to save them,
no matter how irrational.
- I don't love Booth.
- Yes, you do.
So do I.
So do all of us.
Just take my advice, and hand
over the evidence and get Booth.
Let's do it.
Come on, let's do it.
Watch your monitor.
Tell me if anything changes, okay?
- By anything, you mean...
- Anything.
Okay, I'm in.
I've locked into the video feed.
I hate this guy.
I mean, I really, really hate him.
I will find you!
Did you do that?
That's the grave digger.
It's the vial he's after.
God, and his receiver's
within a 500-yard radius.
He's really close.
Oh, Angela, this pointy
bit here just got way pointier.
- At what frequency?
- 2.2 something.
Oh, my god!
What? That signal's
not coming from the camera.
Get back!
Run!
Go, go! Go!
What the hell is going on here?
- You okay?
- Yeah. Come on.
We followed Dr. Brennan's
car to the boundary stone.
We arrived moments
after the explosion.
- What the hell were you people doing?
- We have nothing to say.
We found evidence at the crime scene
believed to be related
to the grave digger investigation.
I believe they returned
evidence to the grave digger.
Agent perotta, you will deny all
of these people access to this case.
May I make a request, your honor?
I'd like to see
Thomas Vega's remains.
- I need to examine them immediately.
- You will examine nothing.
You people will stay away from
anything to do with the grave digger.
We're in a ship
stuffed with toys and explosives.
And that make some
kind of sense to you?
What they do, Sarge,
is they sink ships for reefs.
They get school kids
to do all the decorating.
Why?
The fish.
Why else?
Fish love decorations.
Here's the transponder.
We have six hours
and 23 minutes here.
What, no ideas?
According to you, I'm already a ghost.
As a result, I got no sense of urgency.
Hang on.
Maybe we can use the transponder
- to send a signal.
- But that's the only fail-safe.
Once you disconnect the transponder,
nothing can stop the ship
from blowing to hell
in six hours and 22 minutes.
Sense of urgency now?
It's been almost two hours.
Why hasn't the grave digger
sent us Booth's coordinates?
I think we have to accept that the
grave digger isn't gonna release Booth.
- He's cleaning up.
- Cleaning up?
He destroyed the evidence,
now he's trying to destroy everyone
who had gotten close to him.
- Vega, agent Booth, you and Hodgins.
- It's over.
Booth's dead.
It's my fault.
We're out of options.
No. No, it's not over.
And I know exactly
who to ask for help.
So what's so important you
couldn't tell me on the phone?
Your brother has been
kidnapped by the grave digger.
Seeley's been kidnapped?
When?
Booth will be dead in six hours.
What I need for you to do...
is hijack the remains of a murder
victim and then bring them to me.
I'm in military intelligence.
We don't hijack dead bodies.
The victim's name is Thomas Vega.
So you want me to steal the remains
of a murder victim from the FBI?
Yes.
- As soon as possible, please.
- I can make a few calls...
No, this is not a situation
where you make a few phone calls.
That's who I am, tempe.
I am the guy who makes a few calls.
Booth has never turned
his back on you.
You are a selfish coward
and you never deserved him.
We can feed the transponder's
signal through the...
ship's antennae.
You taught me sometimes you
gotta stand and fight and sometimes
you gotta run like hell for help.
Hang on, teddy.
Stay with me.
Sarge?
We never should have
gone on that last mission.
I mean...
Taking out another sniper,
that was...
It was way beyond your capabilities.
It was...
You couldn't have...
That's why you're haunting me,
right? You're...
Can't an old army buddy just
show up to lend a helping hand?
Yeah.
You got a partner now?
You two tight?
Yeah, we're, uh...
You would, you'd like her. She's...
Her?
- Way to go, sarge.
- Look, just focus here, all right?
Corporal, all right, whoever...
is monitoring the... sinking...
of the ship should be able
to pick up the signal, right?
Very cool, sir.
You shorted it out.
It's useless now.
No.
Look, don't worry, sarge.
Hey, at least we still
got this flashlight.
Vega's remains.
Thank you.
So, just to sum things up,
the ship's about to explode,
and now there's no way to stop it.
Rub it in.
I got you killed twice.
Where we going?
We got to get out of here.
Even if we get up out on the deck,
we're gonna have to jump into the ocean.
That's right.
Where if the fall doesn't kill us,
we'll get hypothermia and drown.
Oh, no, I get hypothermia and drown.
Who knows what'll happen to you.
If you die, sarge, i'm gone.
There's not a single person left
on the planet who will rember me.
It'd be like I was never here.
No.
- No?
- No, there's...
There's that girl.
She won't forget you.
You mean claire?
Yeah, claire.
You know, every day
on the anniversary of your death,
I go to your grave and I visit you and
there's always flowers from her there.
- You ever see her?
- From a distance, yeah.
- Why don't you talk to her?
- 'cause she blames me for your death.
- That's crazy.
- That's not crazy.
I blame me, too.
Here we go.
- Sarge?
- Yeah?
Tomorrow's the anniversary.
I need a favor.
If I survive this, anything.
I need you to tell
claire I loved her.
- You never told her?
- I was 20.
- I didn't know how to say it.
- Well, you say "i love you."
I mean, what's so hard about that?
What, you've never loved
somebody and didn't say it to 'em?
See? Maybe that's why I'm here.
Get you to say
I love you to somebody.
- We can get through here.
- Get through the solid metal wall?
No, the stairs.
You see? The stairs...
the thinnest interior bulkhead of
a ship is gonna be along the stairs.
We're gonna blast
our way through this.
Rigor indicates he's
been dead less than 24 hours.
About the same time
Booth disappeared.
Vega must have been killed just
after we were threatened by that judge.
Two full-thickness burns
to the posterior
triangle of the neck
corresponding with
a high-amperage stun gun.
Stun gun.
How did you pull this off?
It's masked as a military intelligence
operation, National security.
How long before
they find out the truth?
- Not long if you keep talking so loud.
- You're gonna get in trouble, Jared.
Definitely lose your job.
I'm aware.
These burn marks are
not in the usual place.
On all the other victims,
they were equidistant from
the inferior nuchal line.
This time they're angled
about four centimeters to the right.
This is deep.
The stun gun was held here
near his heart for an extended time.
Caused fatal fibrillation.
That'll be cause of death.
Here's a hairline fracture
to the olecranon process
of the right ulna.
- What does that mean?
- The victim damaged his
right medial and lateral epicondyles
as well as his coronoid fossa,
possibly consistent with a defensive
response to a posterior assault.
Our victim got
a piece of the bad guy.
He elbowed the assailant.
Striking someone that hard,
there's going to be damage,
at least broken ribs.
Got it.
Good job, kid.
What the hell is
that supposed to be.
A well-shaped charge.
It's a mermaid, get it?
It's not sexist 'cause
she's mostly fish.
All right.
Okay.
All we need now is a power source.
Right, that's what
the flashlight was for.
I have an injunction here reclaiming
- jurisdiction in this case.
- On what grounds?
One missing FBI agent is
not a case of national security.
Grab a coffee, guys.
Do you have the warrant?
Right here, signed by the judge.
I don't think there's any more
reason for us
to keep the truth from Ms. Taffet.
No, wait,
the grave digger said that we...
You've been in touch
with the grave digger?
The grave digger has agent Booth?
She can't seem to extend her arm.
What?
What do you think?
About what?
It's possible.
She had complete access
to FBI files and evidence.
Nobody wanted the grave digger case.
It's a career killer.
But with kurland out of the way...
Have you injured yourself recently,
Ms. Taffet?
What the hell does
that have to do with anything?
Don't let dr. Hodgins go.
Could I see the warrant, please?
Broken ribs.
She's the grave digger?
- It's her.
- Can you prove it?
No, we can't.
Is that a problem?
Not for me.
You got a place to lock her up?
Where's Booth?
- She's not gonna say anything.
- You haven't even asked.
Yeah, I've read extensively
on the grave digger.
I'm acquainted with the profile.
Very intelligent, very calm.
She won't speak.
- Then what do we do?
- You have to do spring cleaning on her.
What is that?
Is that some kind of torture?
Nothing.
It doesn't exist.
The government keeps secret, black,
illegal files on every U.S. citizen.
It's called spring cleaning,
'cause everything's
brought out into the light
and turned upside down.
O- okay,
that is complete paranoia, right?
I'll need access
to a secure terminal.
Follow me.
And only conspiracy nuts
call it spring cleaning.
Sarge?
Corporal Parker, I really need you to
stifle yourself at this juncture, okay?
Okay. Yeah, I get it.
I mean, if these two leads touch,
that explodes, you become Booth jam.
That's correct.
Or if, say, a bead of sweat
completes the circuit, then...
- Can I ask you one question?
- What is it, corporal?
It's just,
how are you gonna complete the circuit
from a 100 yards away, at which
distance you might
survive the blast?
One thing at a time, okay?
First time I've ever
heard of a cowardly ghost...
What a wuss.
I'd like to kill you.
I hate her.
I think I could murder her.
If any group of people could murder
someone and get away with it,
it'll be us.
I'm not gonna ask you any questions.
I'm just gonna tell you
what's going on right now.
I went through your file.
As heather taffet, you have
lead a very tiny, transparent life.
But in 1998,
you married a man
named william burton
for exactly one month before
you had the marriage annulled.
Which was long enough to create
an entire identity,
a whole, untraceable identity...
which you used for
one thing and one thing only.
To rent a storage
locker in spring hill.
I gotcha, bitch.
- I got to get closer.
- You're too close now, sarge.
You're too close.
I'll get it.
Teddy...
you got to get your hands
on some truth-telling drugs.
- What?
- Would you rather torture her?
- I know a little bit about that.
- No. What? We don't do that.
Booth will die.
Character is
who you are under pressure,
not who you are when
everything's fine.
We're the good guys,
we don't torture people.
Evidence is being compiled against
you as we speak,
Tell us where agent Booth is.
You don't want another
murder on your head.
That's not gonna work.
Her pathology necessitates
controlling the game.
- She's created her own morality...
- She's not gonna relinquish control.
They brought in everything
from her storage locker.
Okay, back to work, everybody.
- Teddy?
- Yeah?
I can't see very well.
I looked at the flash.
You're okay? Yeah?
I think I could use some help.
Is that light?
Did we find a way out?
- You always find a way out, sarge.
- I'll be your legs.
You be my eyes.
Come on, Teddy.
Which way, corporal?
Towards the light.
Oh, that sounds bad, huh?
"Move towards the light."
Hold up... These boots
were worn recently.
Hey, Jared,
can I see your black file
of spring cleaning or whatever?
- The contents are on my pda.
- Talk to me while you analyze.
Aedes sollicitans...
It's a common marsh mosquito.
- Blood's still in its gut.
- Indicating it was worn how recently?
At least in the last
24 hours for sure, but...
Wait a second.
I got some paint chips here.
Run it through the mass spec, see if
there's anything about that paint.
Yep. I'm on it.
You still with me, teddy?
Yeah.
But I got to tell you,
I feel like we've kind of...
been here before.
I'm sorry I got you killed.
I was so anxious to get off that shot,
take out my target, that I forgot
to tell you...
You told me to get down twice.
You gave the order,
and I didn't listen.
What?
Sarge... Stop.
I didn't come here to haunt you.
I came to tell you
it wasn't your fault.
Active amine hydrogen,
epoxy, hydroxyapatite and silica.
It's an obsolete composition
of deck coating used
by the navy prior to 1961.
So she was on a navy vessel
within the last 24 hours?
Yes. Yeah, an old one...
- Most likely decommissioned.
- Wait a minute, a ship?
Listen to this.
Taffet was a volunteer
at the aquarium.
They were prepping some
sort of old navy ship to be sunk.
- What?
- They're making some sort of reef.
The navy's not afraid
of explosions or sinking ships.
Plus, it'll really annoy my brother,
the army ranger, to be saved by a squid.
Brennan, they know where Booth is.
Jared is getting
a helicopter to take you there.
He's on an old navy ship.
You can put me down, sarge.
- You don't have to carry me anymore.
- Doesn't work that way, teddy.
Jared, can you hear me?
I'm patched through via cell phone.
Jared, I don't understand, why aren't
you here in the helicopter with me?
Typical navy red tape,
nothing to worry about.
But listen,
they couldn't cancel the detonation.
- Something wrong with the transponder.
- What do we do now?
The ship blows in 9 minutes...
The navy's only giving you five
to get there and get Seeley off.
No, Jared! Booth could
be anywhere on that ship!
5 minutes is not enough time!
These guys don't negotiate, tempe.
They won't risk any more lives.
Are you all right?
It's all worth it as
long as you save my brother.
Rangers lead the way, sarge.
Rangers lead the way, corporal.
There. All right?
Sarge.
I knew what you did for me.
How far you carried me.
Sarge.
One more thing I got to tell you.
No way you're getting
the deposit back on that tux.
Booth!
Hurry! Come on!
Hurry, Booth! Come on!
Booth, come on! Hurry!
Thanks for coming to get me, bones.
You should have stayed
in the hospital another day.
No, I didn't mean...
getting me out of the hospital,
I meant...
coming out on
the helicopter to the ship.
Thanks for saving my life.
I got you this.
Cocky! How'd you find that?
That's hard to find.
I read through your report.
Seems you would need two
people to do most of what you did.
I had help.
There was a ghost.
You were... injured,
drugged, disoriented,
breathing bad air.
There are no such things as ghosts.
Whatever you have to tell
yourself there, Bones.
Whose ghost?
He's buried over there.
The ghost?
Corporal Edward Parker.
He was slain while serving
his country.
He was 20.
He was just a kid.
Was it...
Your fault that he died?
No.
The fortunes of war.
It wasn't my fault.
You see that woman over there?
Her name is Claire.
I have a message for her from Teddy.
What?
A message from a ghost?
You wait here, okay?
But you're gonna deliver a message
to that woman from a ghost?
Beautiful day.
Makes you glad to be alive,
doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--