Ademon who likes to kill witches.
Well, that narrows it down to about
every page in the Book.
We have one clue.
We know he likes to use an athame.
- How does that help?
- Well, it means he has hands.
Keep flipping.
So I hear you and Leo are thinking
about having a baby.
Where did you hear that from?
From Phoebe.
Oh, did I just break some sort
of sister confidentiality clause?
- No, you didn't. And, no, we aren't.
- Really?
Don't you want to? Not to be nosy,
but if I'm gonna be an aunt and all...
You're not gonna be an aunt, all right.
At least not any time soon.
It's too risky.
It would be in constant
danger around us.
What does Leo think?
Leo thinks that there's
enough magic around here
we'd be able to protect it.
Maybe he's right.
Maybe he's not. Keep flipping.
I'm flipping.
You know, it's not like having a baby
isn't hard enough.
Even without demons attacking.
But for what it's worth,
there are ways of seeing what it's
like before you actually have one.
Great. Well, the next time you pass a
baby-rental, pick one up for Leo.
Maybe I will.
So did you find anything out?
Yeah. I scried for the location
of the demon,
using the slime from the last victim.
And Phoebe and Cole
are checking it out.
All right, I hope that it pans out
because with two dead witches,
they're pretty concerned up there.
Okay, well, we are very
concerned down here too.
Hey, I think I got something.
Upper-level demon who likes to
kill witches using an athame.
Sometimes energy balls.
His name is Belthazor.
I don't think so.
Why not?
Well, because that's Cole
in his demonic form.
You knew he was half demon.
Yeah, but I didn't know
he could turn into that.
Hello?
We're at Battery and Clay,
but there's no sign of any demons.
Okay, I'll scry for him again.
Talk to Paige.
Hi, Phoebe.
How's Cole?
- Morphed into any demons lately?
- What?
Paige.
Battery and Clay. He's still there.
Piper says he's still there.
Piper says he's still here somewhere.
- Hold on!
- No, I can't!
Three. Two. One!
We have to stop meeting like this.
- Marry me.
- What?
Don't you think we should
talk about this?
Talk about what?
Wow, looks like you
two got a juicy one.
Yeah, but unfortunately not the
one who kills witches.
How do you know?
Upper-level demons
have a human form,
and they bleed red, not green.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going up to take a shower first,
and then I'm gonna check out
the Book of Shadows.
I wanna lD this demon that I'm
wearing, try to find some answers.
Speaking of unanswered questions--
There is a demon on the loose, Cole.
We don't have time for this.
- Shouldn't we make time for it?
- No. Not now we shouldn't.
- What are you guys talking about?
- Nothing.
Nothing.
Please, Cole, let's just focus
on vanquishing the demon.
Fine. I'll go see what I can find out.
Honey, did you two have a fight?
No, he just...
Never mind.
Witch.
You're next.
Yes, I'd like to report
a terrible murder.
A beautiful young woman in the alley
behind the Cannon Theater.
Hey, are you gonna be long?
What, are you deaf?
I need to use the phone.
Hold on.
Hurry, please.
Before anyone else gets hurt.
Okay, so the demon that Cole and l
nailed is a scavenger demon.
Apparently, he feeds on the remains
of other demons' victims.
Nice, huh?
Well, that explains why we
scried for him accidentally.
Are you gonna tell me
what happened out there?
Well, there's not much to tell.
I mean, the demon jumped
in behind us, and we--
That's not what I mean.
What happened
between you and Cole?
Oh, yeah, that.
I'm not exactly sure.
He asked me to marry him.
What? He did what? He did?
More or less.
- Well, what did you say?
- I didn't know what to say.
I was too surprised.
I mean, all my power of premonition,
and I never saw that one coming.
I don't think a witch
is allowed to marry a demon.
Honey, we can't have
a demon in the family.
Piper, that is the least
of my concerns right now.
Well, don't kid yourself.
If you decide to
go through with this,
it's gonna be a source of huge
concerns, especially for them.
I have to be concerned
with my own concerns, you know.
I love Cole.
You know I do.
But demon stuff aside, I just never
thought of myself as the marrying type.
You know, it's not something
I fantasized about.
Ever.
So then, what are
you gonna tell him?
I don't know.
Well, you have to
tell him something
because a question like that
just doesn't go away by itself.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
- Hey.
I'll...
...be downstairs.
I couldn't find out who the demon is.
But at least I ruled out
the usual suspects.
Any idea of who it could be?
No, just another upper-level demon
trying to build a reputation
by killing witches
to move up the ladder.
Anyway, I guess I'll keep checking.
No, Cole, wait.
- We should talk.
- All right.
It's just hard.
It's just me.
Okay.
Let me ask you a question.
When you...
...you know, proposed...
...did you mean to?
Or did it just come out in
the heat of the moment?
Well, does that matter?
Well, yeah, it matters to me.
It just came out in the heat
of the moment.
But that doesn't mean that once I said
it I wasn't serious, because I was.
I still am.
Cole.
Phoebe, listen to me.
I know it was crazy to ask.
And I know it doesn't make any sense
because of who we are, but...
That shouldn't matter.
If it did, we never would have
fallen in love in the first place.
I love you, Phoebe.
And I don't know where
we go from here,
but I do know that wherever it is...
... I want it to be with you.
Is that a baby crying?
You told me to rent one.
So I did.
Well, I didn't think that you could.
Where did you get it?
- The clinic.
- Great. Take it back.
What's going on?
Piper and Leo wanted
to try out having
a baby before
actually having one.
So I got them a mechanical baby.
We use them in parenting classes
all the time.
- Wow, it sounds so real.
- And so annoying.
Look, Paige,
I appreciate the thought,
but we are on a demon hunt.
And the last thing I want to do is
protect a fake baby.
Oh, really?
See, your instincts were to save it.
My instincts were to shut it up.
The doll has a sensor.
It'll stop crying if you just hold it.
But I don't want to.
Come on. Just try it.
If it doesn't work,
I will take it back. I promise.
Okay, now you just rock it gently.
Phoebe.
I know how to hold a baby.
That is not the issue. Thank you.
Just give it a shot.
What have you got to lose?
Another witch has been killed.
- Oh, no.
- The police found her body
behind the Cannon Theater.
We should go there
and see what we can find out.
We gotta call Morris on the way.
Make sure he can get us in.
And no, you cannot come.
Someone might recognize you
from when you posed as a DA.
I don't get to go anywhere anymore.
You were a demon and a lawyer?
Insert joke here.
Where did you get it?
- It's Paige's.
- No, it's yours.
You need to figure it out.
Yeah, Daddy, figure it out.
Excuse me.
Don't look at me.
I can't guarantee you
much time on this.
Promise me you'll stay on the fringe.
We promise.
So, what do we know?
A man called 91 1 from that pay phone
and reported he found a body.
Looks like she wasn't the only victim.
Scorch mark. Definitely demonic.
Looks like one of Cole's, actually.
Don't you mean Belthazor?
It's too bad Cole can't check it out.
Probably be able to tell us who did it.
Is anyone from the DA's office here?
Yeah, that guy over there is an ADA.
He's interviewing
a friend of the victim.
I also found this on the victim.
A triple crescent.
Does this mean something to you?
I studied it in one of Piper's quizzes.
It's an ancient Wiccan symbol.
A cousin to the triquetra.
Could be the mark of a coven.
A coven someone's trying
to wipe out.
We have to figure out
who else is in it.
Maybe the victim's friend.
- Only one way to find out.
- Phoebe.
- Fringe, okay?
- Fringe.
And she hadn't complained about
any disgruntled friends, coworkers,
- ex-boyfriends?
- No.
Kari was a beautiful person.
Everyone loved her.
If you can think of anything else at all,
please, don't hesitate to call.
I like your necklace.
Do I know you?
No.
But you might know of me
and my sisters.
The Charmed Ones.
You and Kari were
in the same coven?
Yes.
And your mark is the triple crescent.
What is it? Are you all right?
What happened? What'd you see?
The demon. He's after her.
- Where?
- By the steps
in some park.
I think it was like
an old amphitheatre or something.
I know that.
That's in Stanley Arboretum.
I walk past it every day
going to work.
What did the demon look like?
Like Belthazor.
I mean, not exactly like him.
Just similar.
What the hell is going on here?
This is a murder investigation.
Who are these people?
I'll get rid of them.
Come on, ladies, move along.
First time I ask nicely.
We're going, mister.
I don't understand. If you know
the demon is meant to attack here,
shouldn't we go someplace else?
Not if we want to
get rid of him for good.
Power of three spell?
No, the only way to vanquish
an upper-level demon
is with a potion of his own flesh.
Sounds like you've done this before.
Once, on my fiancé.
Your fiancé?
Yeah, I just wanted to hear
how it sounded.
- And...?
- Kind of weird.
- Yeah.
- Wait. Back up.
Did you say you once tried
to vanquish Cole?
No, Belthazor. There's a difference.
- Is there?
- Okay, let's review.
I play decoy. Demon attacks.
Piper freezes. You slice and dice
until we get the demon sushi.
And then we get out of there.
Everybody ready?
As ready as I'll ever be.
Okay, I'm gonna need
your coat and your hat.
And your necklace.
Okay, we gotta get Susan
someplace safe. Leo!
Hi, honey. Could you
orb Susan out of here?
Sure. Any place in mind?
I don't think home is a good idea.
You should take her to my old loft.
I don't think it's rented yet.
All right, take my hand.
Where's the baby?
See? We can make this work.
Go away, and you drop
Robo-kid off at the manor.
Please. Thank you.
Okay, we gotta do this fast
because this demon won't
stay frozen for long. Ready?
Let's go.
Hello, witch.
Goodbye...
...demon.
I had him.
Who the hell are you?
He used this to kill my fiancé.
It's a ceremonial knife.
The demon left it behind
after the struggle.
I've been hunting him down
for the last year and a half.
It's all I care about.
May l?
Look familiar?
- He looked familiar to me.
- I meant the athame.
It's one used by the Brotherhood.
Emma, do you know why the demon
wanted to kill your fiancé?
Because Andrew was a witch.
- Are you a witch too?
- No.
But after Andrew died, I studied his
books and devoted myself to the craft.
To continue his work?
To track down his killer.
You happened to be it in the park
the same time the demon
was going to attack Susan?
I know his m.o.
I know when he kills a witch
he goes after the entire coven.
You've taught yourself well.
But still, if we hadn't come along,
we would have lost you both.
Vengeance empowers me.
But it won't save you.
Your desire for revenge
is keeping you from the truth.
You want the demon vanquished,
you should stand back and let
the Charmed Ones handle it.
This is my fight.
Then you shall lose it.
Cole's right.
You have to trust us.
Trust that we want
the same thing you do.
It's just--
His face has haunted me
ever since Andrew died.
It's the face of pure evil.
I can't let him get away.
Why don't you scry for him again while
we prepare the vanquishing potion.
Once we get a piece
of his flesh, he's dust.
We'll get him.
I swear we'll get him.
Ignore that.
Piper.
All right. Excuse me.
She has a baby?
Actually, she's not sure yet.
Inspector Morris,
he's based downtown.
I want you to get in touch
with his captain.
And you tell him my office wants
to see all of his recent case files.
Got it.
In fact, better go make
that request in person.
This way, they can't
duck you on the phone.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
That's okay. Take your time.
I'm gonna lure the witch here.
I'm gonna need you to stand guard
in case the ones who
ambushed me show up.
You understand?
Fortunately, they won't recognize
me in my human form.
Your old boss, Belthazor,
he was right about one thing.
Posing as a DA is perfect cover.
Leave me.
How much longer do you think
I'll have to stay here?
Well, I'll talk to your whitelighter.
My instincts tell me that everyone
in your coven
should break their routine
until this threat is over.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Miss Coleman, this is the
assistant district attorney Sykes.
- Who is it?
- ADA.
I'm sorry. Yes, hi.
I'm calling because I've received
new evidence.
I'd like to talk to you about it
if that's all right.
Okay, when?
Can you come over
to the offiice now?
- He wants me to come in.
- Okay.
All right, I'll be right there.
I'll be waiting.
I feel the crystal pulling.
He's still in the area.
I can't find him in the Book anywhere.
Did you notice how he vanished?
Did he smoke out? Flame out?
Actually he shimmered like Belthazor.
- I think I found him.
- Where?
- He's at Prescott and--
- Pine.
How did you know?
That's where we are.
Wait, he's here in the house?
I'll go check upstairs.
You find your sisters, get ready.
Hello?
Miss Coleman. Who's this?
I'm a friend.
Is it a problem?
No, no. No problem at all.
Why don't you just wait over there,
and I'll let you know when it's over.
Right this way.
Phoebe.
- He's not upstairs.
- Not downstairs either.
It's the ADA.
- Sykes?
- He tried to kill her.
I don't know if
he followed us here or not.
Watch out!
Take her upstairs.
You're gonna have to do
better than that.
Hurry, slice him.
Oh, Paige, just do it.
This is no time to be squeamish.
Got it.
Oh, my God.
Belthazor, we meet at last.
But not for long.
We'll finish this later.
Is everybody okay?
I'm okay.
Emma?
He's not the demon
who killed my fiancé.
He is.
He's a killer! What is
the matter with you people?
Emma, I know you're upset.
But you don't understand.
- Let go of me.
- You're making a huge mistake.
He's not who you think he is.
He's the demon who killed my fiancé,
and that is all I need to know.
Hey!
How can you protect a murderer?
How can you live with yourself?
Is she right?
Are you the one who killed him?
Honey, now is not the time.
We have to worry about Sykes.
We got what we need.
You guys work on
the vanquishing potion.
We need to talk.
Don't tell me you're scared of me.
No, don't be ridiculous.
That's good.
Because I think Emma's right.
I am the one who killed her fiancé.
This is mine.
I don't even remember doing it.
I don't even remember
what he looked like.
Didn't matter what they looked like.
It only mattered
that I did what I was told.
He was a witch.
The Source viewed him as a threat.
You don't have to explain
yourself to me.
- Yes, I do.
- No, you don't.
I know who you were.
Who you used to be.
And that's not the person
you are anymore.
Aren't l?
Belthazor still exists inside of me.
That hasn't changed,
nor does it change what I've done.
But just think of all the good
you've done since then.
Doesn't balance out.
Doesn't even come close.
And now the very thing
I've been trying so hard not to be
is the very thing
I might have to become.
What do you mean?
Sykes has done a good job
of emulating me, emulating Belthazor,
which means,
if the potion doesn't work,
the only way to destroy him
is for me to turn into Belthazor.
Yeah, but then afterwards
you'll turn back into Cole.
I may not be able to.
To stop him, I'll have to embrace
my demonic self completely.
There may be no coming back
from that.
Well, then we'll just have to make sure
that potion works very well.
Won't we?
I'll be back.
- Where are you going?
- To find Emma.
Try to explain.
It won't make any difference.
Well, it will if I can keep her
out of the craziness.
Keep her from getting hurt.
I'm more concerned with keeping you
out of the craziness.
Keeping you from getting hurt.
You still have some of that Belthazor
vanquishing potion left, don't you?
- Yes, but--
- Get it.
Just in case.
It might be the only way to stop me.
Okay, we just need the pigs' feet
over there by the mandrake root.
Poor piggy, piggy.
They're sensitive creatures, you know.
- Smart too.
- Yeah, not that one.
Okay, so all we need to do
is drop in the Sykes' flesh.
Go ahead. Just drop it in.
- You did that on purpose, didn't you?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it happened to me last year.
No substitute for experience.
- You girls all right?
- Yeah.
We were just doing a little
sisterly bonding, that's all.
Where's Phoebe?
The potion will be ready
in a couple of minutes.
Yeah, she wanted to talk to Emma,
explain things.
Good luck.
Look, I don't need
the guilt from you, okay?
I've got enough of my own
to deal with.
What, and you think that covers it?
What you did?
Paige, don't.
Don't what, Piper? He killed a man.
Are you condoning that?
No, of course not.
But it's just not that simple.
He can't change the past.
And you've seen how much good
he's helped us do.
That's who he is now.
And we accept that.
Well, if you say so.
Thank you.
- You want me to help you find Sykes?
- Can you?
If he's still emulating me, all I have
to do is figure out what I'd do next.
Which would be?
Go after the Charmed Ones.
Oh, that's nice.
But first I'd have to
regroup somewhere.
- Tend to my cut.
- The mausoleum?
Except Sykes will anticipate that.
He'll be expecting you
to come after him,
which means he'll probably
be lying in wait.
Maybe even set some kind of trap.
One that you could identify.
So let's go.
Wait, don't we need Phoebe?
No, all we need is this.
Besides, it's better to keep Emma
away from the action.
Oh, honey, what happened?
Sykes. Guess you were right.
Sweetie, I didn't want to be right.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Who's gonna pay for this?
Well?
We're gonna go after Sykes,
so you should probably orb Susan
out of here, just to be safe.
Emma.
Emma, please, I need to talk to you.
Look, I know that
there's nothing I can say
that can change what happened.
But I think there is something
that may help.
I want you to know that Cole has
dedicated his life to good now.
And I'm not saying that
it excuses what he did.
Damn right, it doesn't.
All I'm saying is the demon
you're searching for no longer exists.
Oh, my God.
Who are you trying to kid?
Are you blind?
Did you not see what he turned into?
That monster still exists,
whether you want to believe it or not.
- Technically, yes, but--
- Not technically.
Actually.
He's alive.
And I'm not gonna rest until he's dead,
no matter what you say.
All that would do is keep him
from doing future good
and put your life at risk
in the process.
Emma, please, please, let it go.
Let it go?
Have you ever lost someone?
To evil, I mean.
Yes.
And did you just...
...Iet it go?
Any sign of him?
What?
Trap. Back up.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Well, why would he set a trap for us
and not be here?
Unless this is just a distraction.
What do you mean, "distraction"?
You said he was after us.
I was wrong. He's after me.
The best way to get to me
is through--
Phoebe.
Cole?
Close.
What do you want?
The same thing you do.
Only I call him Belthazor.
Except I don't need a potion
to vanquish him.
I just need you.
Phoebe.
I'll check upstairs.
You check downstairs.
You must be
something very special.
Turn a demon.
Something very special indeed.
Unfortunately, though,
when you made him less evil,
you made him less powerful.
I wonder.
You gonna have the same effect
on me after I kill him?
Well, well, well.
The mighty Belthazor.
You don't disappoint.
I knew you'd figure out
what I was up to.
Sooner or later.
Cole, get out of here.
He won't hurt me. He's bluffing.
- I can't take that chance.
It's kind of eerie, isn't it?
How I know you better than
you know yourself.
The student has surpassed
his mentor.
I was never your mentor, Sykes.
By reputation you were.
By your legend.
It'll be an honour to kill you
and assume your rightful place
in the hierarchy.
You remember what I told you?
What I asked you to do?
Cole, please don't.
Did you hear that?
- Die!
- Cole.
Cole.
It's over. You can turn back now.
Cole, you can do it.
For me. For us.
Hurry, throw the potion.
Maybe it'll work on him.
No, don't. Cole, please.
You can do this. You're good.
What happened?
That was the power-stripping potion
I made to free Cole.
Are you okay?
No!
You got your revenge.
You killed the demon you were after.
Belthazor is dead, gone forever.
Cole's a human being.
An innocent.
You know, this baby was your idea.
I know, I know.
That's why I'm paying for half of it.
Still haven't quite figured out
how I'm gonna explain
what happened to it, though.
- Thank you.
- Well, at least it served its purpose.
In spades, unfortunately.
Oh, honey, it doesn't mean
that we can't ever have children.
Just, you know,
we have to wait till it's safe.
Promise?
Promise.
That's sweet.
You two ought to get married.
Unlike Phoebe and Cole.
You don't think they should?
I don't know.
I guess it's not my business.
Probably just reeling from the fact
that Cole killed people.
Yeah, but that wasn't Cole.
It was Belthazor.
Splitting hairs, if you ask me.
It's not, though.
His human half had absolutely
nothing to do with any of that.
It was totally subjugated.
Phoebe's right. He's an innocent.
The question is,
what does he do now?
Cole. Oh, my God, I was so worried.
Oh, I'm sorry. I just...
I had to take a walk.
And I lost track of time.
And I tried to shimmer back here,
and I realized l...
I didn't have my powers anymore.
But that's a good thing.
Isn't that what we always wanted?
I don't know. Did we?
I mean, I get it that
I'm finally off The Source's radar
and that I don't have to
worry about demons
tracking me down all the time, but...
I'm grateful for that,
don't get me wrong. It's just...
What?
Come here.
Phoebe.
For all intents and purposes,
I've been a demon for...
...over 1 00 years.
It's all I've ever known.
Or been.
What am I supposed to do now?
Who am l?
You're still the good man
that I fell in love with.
But not the one you want to marry.
I love you, Cole.
And nothing will ever change that.
But I'm not ready.
Not yet.
And that's got more to do
with me and my issues
than it does you.
I still don't know where that
leaves us, especially now.
Well, just because
you're not a demon anymore,
doesn't mean we can't live in sin.