-Wheat-germ pancakes?
- Bagel.
Bagel?
Has anyone seen
my deposition papers?
I thought they were in this folder
with the cream-cheese stain.
Try the one with the jelly stain.
I got it, thanks.
Phoebe, don't forget, my law firm's
having a party tonight.
I want to show off my new bride.
If I could finish my work here,
that would be great.
- Cole, pancakes?
- Trying to watch my cholesterol.
How about you, Phoebe?
I know you want some of these.
No, you know what I want?
I want quiet.
My advice column is due today.
- No pancakes?
- No pancakes.
But shush with some syrup on it
would be good.
Leo, just in time for some
delicious wheat-germ pancakes.
No, I don't have time.
I just came to get my toolbox.
All right, you know what? I'm not
cooking for you people anymore.
From now on,
you're all on your own.
My bagel!
Could everybody please be quiet?
Oh, no. My battery died.
Smoke alarm.
You know, you'd get all the quiet
you want if we had our own place.
Gotta go. I'm interviewing
personal assistants today.
Bye.
And I am off to quieter pastures.
Honey, you look tired.
I've been working double shifts.
The Elders have been piling it on me
since you guys took out The Source.
What's with the toolbox?
Leo poses as a heavenly handyman.
It's actually how we met.
The Elders want me to check out
a potential whitelighter.
She's a schoolteacher
about to fall off the path.
She needs some inspiration.
Speaking of inspiration,
it's the 60th anniversary
of the Battle of Guadalcanal,
and they're having a reunion
for local veterans, so I RSVP'd for you.
Piper, I can't be seen there.
Well, no, it's okay. I told them
that you were your grandson.
Well, that's not it. I don't want to go.
You would have known that
if you would have asked me
or talked to me about it
instead of just making
decisions for me.
I'll bet she scares easily.
- Can I scare her?
- No.
Come on, Rick.
Just let me moan once.
One of those bone-chilling moans.
You know, could be the wind,
could be a ghost.
Just watch her.
We've been watching this place
for about 60 years, man.
We're never gonna find
what we're looking for.
I swear, sometimes I don't know
why I stay here with you.
Because I stayed with you, bro.
I promised to protect you
when we enlisted, and I failed.
I'm not gonna fail again.
Well, this is something.
Leo Wyatt's grandson is gonna attend
the reunion with his wife.
I told you one of them
would show up eventually.
Well, let's go.
What's the address?
I can't see it. Lean back, granny.
Can I scare her now?
1 329 Prescott Street.
- Let's go.
- Not yet.
You've had your fun.
Now, let me show you how it's done.
Rick, Rick, wait!
We're after Wyatt.
We're not after her.
Phoebe, have you seen
my keys anywhere?
No.
Leo is not answering my call.
Is it an emergency?
No, but I just want to talk to him,
so I can figure out
why he's so mad at me.
I mean, I can't believe it's just because
he doesn't wanna go to the reunion.
Maybe it's because, I don't know,
he died at Guadalcanal?
Yeah, but he died a hero.
Although, come to think of it,
he doesn't really
talk about it very much.
Phoebe.
Phoebe, come on.
What do you think?
I think, Piper, that I came in here
to get away from all the chatter, okay?
I have a deadline.
I am Working Phoebe.
Found them.
- Who are you?
- What?
- Wait, you can see me?
- More like through you.
Paige, stand back.
Phoebe!
What?
We just saw a ghost, that's what.
Yeah, and my first one too.
I mean, that I wasn't related to.
It was kind of cool.
No, not cool.
Unless he was friendly,
which, considering who we are
and what we do, probably not.
This is great.
This is exactly what I need today.
- What do we do?
- You go back to your deadline.
I'll go get the Book
and brush up on my ghost-busting.
No, no, no. I'll go do it.
You just said you were
late for work.
Yeah, but I mean, he's a ghost.
Who knows where he came from?
What era.
He's like a piece
of man-hunk history.
Knock yourself out.
Recon report?
Well, Wyatt's grandson
is definitely living the good life.
- Not for long.
- Not so fast, Rick.
His wife was there...
...and she could see me.
A witch?
Plus two sisters,
for a grand total of three witches.
Listen, Rick, I was thinking maybe
we should just forget about this.
Forget about what?
What Wyatt did to us?
The fact that he trapped us
in this hell on earth?
You want to forget him?
No way.
The grandson's gonna pay
for what the grandfather did to us.
Someday, you're gonna have
to show me how you did that.
No time like the present.
Some say hatred
can harden the heart.
I've found that it can also
harden the body.
Now it's your turn, Nathan.
Focus on everything
that Wyatt stole from us.
Our life,
our family, our future.
Feel the hatred
and bring it to the surface.
I did it.
Now, take the bayonet.
You'll need the practice.
Because with witches around,
we're gonna have to be
at the top of our game.
What kind of legal documents
did you draft as a paralegal?
Discovery, administrative,
pretrial, trial, motions, pleadings.
- What's your dictation speed?
- 1 20 words a minute.
How fast can you shimmer
across town?
Thirty miles in two seconds.
- Demonic powers?
- Fireballs, shape-shifting.
- Your last kill?
- Two years ago.
Two years ago? Why so long?
Killing's messy.
My services are usually
a little more discreet.
I'll give you a trial run, Julie.
I'm trying to separate my wife from
the harmful influence of her sisters.
The Charmed Ones.
It's very important for me
to keep Phoebe away from them.
She might be pregnant with my son.
You almost say that
like you love her.
A part of me does, unfortunately.
Anyway, my plan is
more insidious than overt.
I set off the fire alarm this morning.
I'll cut the power this afternoon.
Whatever it takes to make Phoebe's
home feel cramped and unlivable.
And seduce her
with the promise of a better life.
Exactly.
But it takes caution.
Focus.
I need someone to cover me
at work, watch my back.
Well, I'll watch
whatever part you want.
He couldn't believe I suspended him,
but what could I do?
He brought a knife
into my classroom.
Now he's threatening me,
says he knows where I live.
See, that's why I'm a plumber.
Pipes are a lot easier
to deal with than with kids today.
I always wanted to be a teacher,
but not at the cost of my life.
That's why I've decided to quit.
That's too bad.
All the good you're gonna do
in this world, gone forever?
- Going to do?
- I mean, can do.
I don't want to quit.
I just don't have the courage to stay.
Well, the only courage that matters
is the kind that gets you
from one moment to the next.
Maybe you should just
focus on that.
You bill as a plumber or a therapist?
Whatever it takes to stop the leak.
Which, by the way, is healed.
I mean, sealed.
- What do I owe you?
- This one's on the house.
Did you know there's a potion
in here to vanquish ghosts?
Yeah, you pour it over their bones.
We used it a couple years ago.
That's weird. Look at this.
- What is it?
- Leo's Medal of Honor.
And it's just stuffed in his old Army file
like it doesn't mean anything.
Maybe he's just being humble.
No, it's not that. It's something else.
I know it. I know him.
There's also a spell
to vanquish ghosts.
It should be in
the Book somewhere.
Yeah, it's in here all right.
The only problem is that you have
to be a ghost yourself to say it,
which is fairly lame.
- Not again.
- Oh, no, no, no!
I didn't save any of it.
I just lost half my document.
All right, relax.
I'll check the circuit breaker.
I really need to get my own place.
- Sorry?
- Nothing.
- Cole Turner's office.
- Hi, who's this?
I'm Julie, Mr. Turner's new assistant.
Who is this?
I'm Phoebe, Mr. Turner's new wife.
Oh, really?
- I didn't realise he was married.
- Yeah, he is.
And I really need to talk to him.
It's very important.
I'm afraid he's not in his office.
Can I take a message?
No, I'm sorry, you can't.
Look, he said he'd be
in the office all day,
and I really, really need
to talk to him right away.
Hi, baby. What, did you hire
your new assistant on the spot?
Well, you could have at least told her
that you were married.
Look, I hate to bother you,
but I was kind of hoping
that you could help me.
Power's on.
I just can't get any work done here,
and I am so pushing my deadline.
- What can I do?
- I can't go to the offiice, right,
because they're painting it.
- So I was wondering--
- If I knew a place you could work?
As a matter of fact, I do.
Why don't you meet me
at the Towers in 20 minutes.
The Towers where
the party is tonight?
Yeah, but that's tonight.
Nobody's using them today.
Okay, sounds good.
- You're hired.
- I'll see you there. Thanks.
Call me on my cell
if you need anything, okay?
I gotta go.
Nice job with the lights, sis.
Can't figure out
what keeps tripping the breaker.
Maybe it's a ghost.
Found this in the file.
The guy to the left of Leo,
does he look familiar?
That's our ghost, killed in action.
His brother's on the right.
They died the same day as Leo.
Could be a reunion
he wants to avoid having?
Leo.
Leo, I mean it this time!
What? What is it?
- Nathan.
- Yeah, we just met him.
Looked pretty good.
A little transparent, but otherwise
he looked pretty good for a dead guy.
Talk to me.
There's nothing to talk about.
Hey, Wyatt.
You're right, little brother.
He is the spitting image
of his grandfather.
Rick, don't!
Rick? How did he know your name?
Leo.
- I can explain.
- Rick, let's go.
Rick, come on, let's go. Come on!
I can't believe they've been
holding on this long just to hurt me.
What I don't understand is why
they're not transparent anymore.
I mean, other than
the walking through walls thing,
- they kind of seem normal to me.
- They've been practicing.
Corporealizing, so they can
move things.
Yeah, like butcher knives.
Well, they're holding on
to their pain.
That's what keeps them
from moving on.
Their pain?
Leo, they just tried to kill you.
Yeah, lucky they're not darklighters.
Otherwise, you would have
been killed.
Again.
You don't understand.
We were friends.
We grew up together
down in Burlingame.
I went to school with Nathan.
When the war came, we made a deal
with our recruitment officer
that we would enlist as long as
they kept us in the same unit.
- You were close.
- Yeah.
So, what do they think you did?
Now, we'd just got
transferred onto the island.
We got ambushed
outside the airfield.
Heavy artillery.
Mortar fire.
We couldn't keep up
with the injuries.
The bodies.
Then I heard Rick's voice.
Leo!
Leo, get over here quick!
Get over here! Nathan's been hit!
Stabilise his leg!
Get him on the jeep! Go, go, go!
It's bad, isn't it?
- What hit him?
- Mortar frag.
They hit us with heavy artillery
out of nowhere.
The whole battalion's down.
- We gotta get him inside!
- Yeah. Up. Let's get him up.
Get in the tent!
Get the sulfa powder.
If we don't stop the bleeding,
he's going into shock.
- How many soldiers down out there?
- I don't know. They hit us so hard.
Maybe 1 5 or 20, I don't know.
I need a morphine kit.
You gotta help him. He needs you.
We both need you.
- Is there a medic out in the field?
- I don't know. I don't know.
Look, try and stabilise him.
- What are you doing?
- Going to help those men.
- What?
- Wilkinson will take care of him.
No, you're gonna take care of him!
That's Nathan on that bed!
There's men dying
and nobody to take care of them!
You're gonna choose them over us?
I'm sorry.
Wyatt! We're your friends!
Nathan's gonna die!
Don't let him die! Wyatt!
I should have stayed.
I should have tried to save Nathan
and get him out of there.
Then you would have
all died in the tent.
And all the guys in the field that
you did save would have died too.
You did the right thing.
And, Leo, for God's sakes,
you were awarded the Medal of Honor.
Posthumously, I might add.
I didn't deserve it.
Right.
So I suppose you didn't deserve
to be a whitelighter
for sacrificing your life
to save others?
Yeah, but were those lives any more
important than Nathan's or Rick's?
Or anyone else in that tent?
You know, a good friend
put his life in my hands.
And I left him to die.
All the good that I've done
since then can't erase that fact.
Maybe I didn't deserve
to become a whitelighter.
Hey, newsflash:
Friends don't kill each other.
Okay, I say we douse their dusty bones
with our magic potion
and vanquish their sorry asses.
No, you can't do that.
They didn't do anything wrong.
Okay. So, what do you suggest?
I don't know, if I could talk to them,
make them understand
why I did what I did,
then maybe they can move on.
Maybe you all can.
We need to find where they're buried
so we can summon them.
Before they try to hurt anybody else.
Yeah, like us.
A whitelighter. I still can't believe
they made him a fricking angel.
How could they reward him
for turning his back on his friends?
Yeah.
But did you see the look
on his face when he saw us?
Guilt, total guilt.
At least he knows he's living a lie
built on our corpses.
So what? Who cares?
I still want him dead.
You can't kill a whitelighter.
Maybe not.
But we can hurt him
by taking the things...
...that he holds dear.
Make him dread his eternal life.
We can punish him,
make him feel like the fraud he is,
by killing those he loves.
Who knows? Maybe then,
we will be able to kill him.
Payback is a witch.
Are you kidding me?
The firm leases it for parties,
retreats, special occasions.
I think you qualify.
It's so big and beautiful.
And big.
- Wait, listen.
- What?
I don't hear anything.
Exactly.
The caterers aren't coming till 4,
so you can use it till then.
And you're sure
you won't get in trouble?
I'm already in trouble. I'm in love.
I have to ask you a question.
Were you serious this morning
when you suggested
that we get a place
of our own together?
- What do you think?
- I don't know.
Wrenching a Halliwell
away from the manor,
it's never been done before.
I like a challenge.
It's not that I don't want to.
It's just...
How do I break up
the power of three?
You guys don't have to keep
living together to be charmed.
Not anymore.
The Source is dead,
Leo can orb you back
at a moment's notice.
So can Paige, for that matter.
If we don't do it now, then when?
Piper will kill me.
The manor's too crowded.
There's not enough room.
Hell, there's not enough electricity.
Or privacy.
You just enjoy
your peace here today.
We'll talk more tonight at the party.
Oh, no, the party. I totally forgot.
I didn't bring anything to wear.
Don't worry. You just concentrate
on your advice column.
I'll take care of everything.
I promise.
Going down?
My wife needs a dress
for the party tonight.
Something like this?
Classy, but too safe.
I want Phoebe noticed.
Not that noticed.
- Perfect.
- Thank you.
You sure you don't want to see
that red number again?
Just save it, okay.
I'm not interested.
I'm a one-woman demon.
You're the boss.
I'll be in touch.
Found them.
Rick and Nathan Lang,
buried November 22nd, 1 942,
at the local VA.
Okay, where's the Book?
We need the summoning spell.
Already ahead of you.
Who you gonna call?
Cute. Let's go.
Wait, something's wrong.
It's Maria the teacher.
She's in trouble.
- I have to go to her.
- But what about the ghosts?
I thought we had to find them
before they hurt someone else.
- If something happens to my charge--
- No, no, it's okay.
Go and just meet us there
when you're done.
It's all gonna be okay.
Let's go.
Should we wait
for the sisters to separate?
No, we can take care of them later.
We're following Wyatt.
Wyatt, why?
Because nothing pushes
a whitelighter over the edge
faster than losing a charge.
Let's go.
I told you, lady.
I told you, don't sweat me!
- Easy.
- Leo.
Who are you? The boyfriend?
Well, you've come just in time
to see the show.
Sit down, clown.
There's a front-row seat.
Listen, just put the knife down,
and we can talk about it.
- You wanna talk, chump?
- Greg, don't!
You dissed me, teach.
Got me in a whole lot of trouble here.
Now somebody's gonna pay.
Don't be afraid.
- Teach.
- Shut up.
Shut up. You're the one who should
be afraid right about now!
Stop it, Greg. Don't be stupid.
Stupid? Is that what I am?
If you hurt him, you will be. It'll be
the stupidest thing you've ever done,
and there won't be
any coming back from it.
Your life will be over.
- My life's already over!
- No, it's not. Not yet.
It takes more courage
to put down that knife than to use it.
Believe me.
Give me the knife, Greg.
- You'll call the police.
- No, I won't.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I think so.
You did a good job
teaching him a lesson.
Thanks to you.
What did I do?
Helped me remember
why I wanted to be a teacher.
No!
Maria!
You, watch her die
like you watched us die.
No!
Maria!
No.
Let go!
Don't! Fight it!
Her blood is on your hands.
Maria.
Why?
She didn't do anything!
She was innocent!
So were we!
Okay, you go get
the vanquishing spell,
and I'll get-- Leo!
Don't you mean potion?
Remember, the spell
only works if you're dead.
Right. Spell, potion, whatever. Leo!
So does that mean we're not
interested in helping them move on?
To hell maybe,
that's what they deserve.
We went to the VA to help
misguided ghosts, not killer ghosts.
We don't know for sure
that they killed that guard.
Vanquishing potion, I'm all over it.
- Phoebe.
- What's the matter?
Don't you recognise me?
- What do you think?
- You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Cole is kind of splurging lately, huh?
Yeah, and I am not complaining.
I enjoy being the belle of the ball.
Well, sorry, Cinderella,
but the ball's been cancelled.
We have killer ghosts.
You're kidding.
You are not kidding.
Okay, well, is it possible that you guys
could maybe handle this without me?
Phoebe, they tried to kill Leo.
- What?
- Grudge from the past.
I'll go do the potion.
Okay, and I'll call Cole
and tell him no to the party.
I guess I could tell him no
for everything.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing, nothing.
Cole wants us to get our own place.
What? You mean move out?
Yeah, you know,
like normal married couples do.
We didn't.
- Yeah, but you're not normal.
- Neither are you.
Look, I don't want
to fight about this.
But I just don't like the feeling
that sometimes I have to choose
between my sisters
and my husband.
It's not about that, and you know it.
How long are we all
gonna stay here?
Another year? Another five years?
Another 50 years?
You know, at what point
do we move on with our lives
and not let evil dictate them?
You're right.
Go to your party.
We'll take care of the ghosts.
You hate me right now.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, she does.
Look, we can talk about this later.
Right now, you need to go
take care of your man,
and I need to take care of mine.
It's as simple as that.
We don't need
the power of three to do this.
You know, I've got
a bone to pick with you.
Seeing as how you practically
forced me to move in here...
Where's Leo?
I already called for him twice.
Leo?
You're half whitelighter,
see if you can sense him.
Sense him?
I've never done that before.
Well, try now.
- I think he's in trouble.
- Well, go find him. Now.
Leo.
I tried to stop them but I couldn't.
Okay, come on. Come on.
Let's get up, let's go over here.
That's it.
Okay, what happened?
They're getting even with me.
They killed her because of me.
Who? Rick and Nathan?
Because I left them to die,
they're making me pay.
Come on, let's get you home.
No.
I don't have my powers anymore.
What happened?
I can't orb or heal.
- But how?
- It doesn't matter how.
I shouldn't have been given them
in the first place.
That is not true.
Your powers must be tied
to your emotions, like ours.
That means you can get them back.
You just have to pick yourself up.
Don't let them defeat you.
You are not responsible
for their actions.
Aren't l?
They're ghosts because of me.
Their rage comes from
something that I did.
If I can just give myself to them...
They'd kill you.
Because without your powers,
you're defenceless.
Like a mortal.
- Okay, we gotta get you home.
- No!
Nobody else is gonna die
because of me.
Do you understand?
These are my demons, not yours!
Okay, just give me a minute.
I am gonna go, and I'm gonna
get Phoebe and Piper.
I will be right back, I promise.
Don't leave.
Defenceless as a mortal, huh?
We got him
right where we want him.
I don't know, Rick.
You don't know?
After waiting all this time,
you're having second thoughts?
No, just the opposite.
It doesn't feel like it's enough
just killing him.
I want him to suffer first.
Follow me.
Penny for your thoughts,
counsellor?
Just that I hope
I never disappoint you.
I wouldn't worry about that
if I were you.
Welcome aboard, Turner.
We're lucky to have you.
Thank you.
Baby, I am so proud of you.
You have come so far.
Further than anyone here in this room
could even imagine.
Even me, I'm seeing you
in a totally different light.
We've both come a long way.
We deserve all of this. And more.
Just everything is happening
so fast, you know.
So many changes.
It's a little scary sometimes.
So maybe we shouldn't
move out of the manor then?
Maybe.
Now who's disappointing who?
You could never disappoint me.
- Sorry to interrupt.
- Paige? What are you doing here?
I thought I'd track you down first.
Leo needs our help, bad.
- By all means, go.
- Okay.
Call me.
I'll kill you.
That potion only works
on my bones, remember?
No calling out for help, Mrs. Wyatt.
Not this time.
Not that he could help you anyway.
Come on, Rick.
Let's go, man. Let's go!
No, I want to enjoy this.
Every last beat.
Your husband's next.
There.
- Hey!
- Piper!
We'll be back.
Fourteen, 1 5. Come on, breathe.
- Where's Leo?
- He wasn't at Maria's.
- Where's the ambulance?
- Still not here.
- Is she--?
- No.
As long as we keep the blood flowing,
she still has a chance.
Put some pressure
on her wound, please.
Piper!
Leo, upstairs, hurry!
- What happened?
- Where have you been?
- Looking for them.
- And here we are.
You can't hurt us,
but we can hurt you.
Wait! You don't want them,
you want me.
You want to get even,
get even with me!
You're right. I trusted you
with my life and you left me!
- What's going on?
- Piper.
Oh, my.
You were our friend,
and you left us to die.
Quick, get the Book. The spell.
- Which one?
- The one only a ghost can say.
Do it.
- Ashes to ashes
- What the hell?
Spirit to spirit
Take their souls, banish this evil
No!
Rick!
- A little help here, people.
- Damn it, Leo, do something!
You're a whitelighter for a reason,
because you did good things.
Think of all the lives you've saved,
all the good you've done.
And all the lives you won't save
if you give up now,
including your wife's.
Piper.
Come on, damn it. Breathe.
Don't die. Not this way.
Not because of me.
Well, it's about time.
That was close.
Really close.
Everything all right?
Yes, it's better now.
Let's see, Leo lost his powers,
and then Piper died,
and it got really dicey
when she turned into a ghost,
but everything worked out.
Glad it was nothing serious.
- You ready to go home?
- No.
- Can't we stay a little while longer?
- Well...
We can stay as long as you like.
The place is ours.
- Excuse me?
- The firm's offered it to me.
All we have to do is say yes.
Well, I guess
now that Paige can orb to me
if something comes up,
and seeing as how we just proved
we could still save the day...
Yes.
Yes?
Yeah.
- Nice to see you.
- How are you?
- Good to see you.
- Hi there.
Come on.
You belong here.
I don't know.
I still don't think it's a good idea.
Your grandfather
would want you to be here.
Hey, you.
Dear God, I'm looking at a ghost.
You know him?
Yeah.
You're related to Leo Wyatt,
aren't you?
Yes, this is his grandson,
Leo Wyatt the third.
Billy! Frank!
I want you to meet the grandson
of the man who made it possible
for you to be born.
His grandfather died
saving my life 60 years ago.
You wouldn't be here today
if it wasn't for that man.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Mr. Wyatt.
My dad's been telling me stories
about your grandpa since I was a boy.
I'd like you to meet my family.
- Hey, guys, come here.
- Franklin! Surdez!
He's kin to Leo Wyatt.
He's the one
who saved your butts too.
God bless you, son.
A pleasure to meet you.
- Nice meeting you, son.
- Leo Wyatt.
- Leo.
- Oh, yeah.
- The medic.
- Medic.
What's going on? Who is that?
My hero.
Boys, boys, come over here.
I want you to meet somebody.