Okay, move it or lose it, people.
Coming through.
Hey, I was using that.
Yeah, well, I'm late,
and I need caffeine, so sue me.
Two weeks of jury duty,
and suddenly she's lawyer-y.
You know, normally, I would have
a witty comeback for that,
but I am too tired.
I'd be tired too if I had to decide
whether or not someone lived or died.
What's your decision?
Paige, you know
I can't talk about the case.
Besides, that's not why I can't sleep.
I can't sleep because
I miss Cole too much.
If he doesn't come home soon,
I'm gonna turn into a vampire.
Jokes like that in this house,
- not so funny.
- Not so funny.
When do you think
he's gonna come back?
Who knows?
He said he needed
some time to find himself
and figure out who he was
without his demon side.
Does that mean he's off banging
on drums in the woods somewhere?
God, I hope not.
- Oh, gotta go.
- Wait!
- Who's testifying today?
- Nobody, it's closing arguments.
- Already? That was fast.
- Oh, no, not you too.
Oh, come on, Phoebe,
it's only natural to be curious.
- Forget it.
- Listen,
nobody keeps secrets better than us.
We are the mistresses of secrets.
- Well...?
- Well...
Let's just say it will be
my supreme pleasure to send
that murdering bastard
straight to hell,
by legal means, not magical.
You might actually be
the first person
who enjoys jury duty.
You know what it is?
It's just-- It might actually be nice
for a change
to get some kudos
for vanquishing the bad guy.
I mean punishing.
You know what I mean.
Okay.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Is Paige home?
- Yeah, she is, but I'm not.
Bye.
- Hey.
- Glen, it's so good to see you.
What are you doing here?
I'm done with Australia, finally,
and I'm actually thinking about Nepal.
I just wanted to stop by
and see how you're doing.
It's so great to see you.
- Oh, that's my sister Piper.
- Of course, of course.
Hi.
I still can't believe you got sisters.
Yeah, it takes some getting used to.
So where are you staying?
I don't know yet, actually.
Good, you'll stay here.
- What?
- Yeah, first door up, top of the stairs.
- Are you sure that's all right?
- Yeah, don't be ridiculous.
I'll be right back.
Great. Thank you.
Paige.
What?
I don't think it's a good idea
for your boyfriend to stay here.
He's not my boyfriend.
Sometimes he's my boyfriend, but
mostly he's just my really good friend.
Well, we usually
don't have houseguests,
because of all the obvious reasons.
You can trust Glen. He's been
my friend since-- God, kindergarten.
You haven't been a witch
since kindergarten.
- I don't think you understand--
- I understand
that I also pay rent here.
There is no rent.
- It's an expression.
- No, it's not.
Well, it should be.
There is no excuse,
Iadies and gentlemen of the jury.
The defendant has no alibi,
no credible explanation
for how he was able
to lead the police
directly to his ex-wife's body.
Other than his--
How did he describe it?
Psychic vision.
No.
Premonition.
That's it.
That was his alibi.
That's what Mr. Provozoli
expects you to believe.
To counter the overwhelming evidence
against him, including,
with the court's permission,
people's 1 7, the murder weapon.
One that he has admitted
to using in his own magic show.
And then he used it to rob
Angela Provozoli
of her life.
Return the verdict
you know you must.
Murder
in the first degree.
Are you all right, ma'am?
Ma'am, are you all right?
This shouldn't take long.
Should be pretty quick.
Oh, man.
It's hot.
You gonna sit there?
Hey.
Hey, I just got a premonition.
We'll be out of here
in time for lunch.
Okay, well, I think
that the proper procedure
is that first we review the evidence.
We heard the evidence, so let's
take a vote and get out of here.
- Still, as the foreman, it's my job--
- All those in favour of guilty.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten, 1 1...
Come on, lady, what's it gonna be?
I have to go to the bathroom.
Leo. Leo.
- Phoebe, what?
- Quick. Orb me to the manor.
I thought you said it was
an open and shut case.
So did l. But the killer,
in my premonition,
was definitely not Stan Provozoli.
Okay, now, I didn't see his face,
but he had this tattoo on his arm,
Iike a Medusa's head with snakes.
- What are you gonna do?
- Well, I'm gonna stall
while you guys try to get Darryl
to get you in to see Stan.
Describe the tattoo,
maybe he knows the real killer.
I don't know. He must not have seen
him in his premonition, otherwise--
He had a premonition?
That's how he claims
to have known where the body was.
And you of all people
did not believe him.
Piper, he's just a club magician.
I assumed that he was a fraud.
Believe me, I feel horrible about this.
All right, we'll fix it somehow.
Do we hunt killers
that aren't demons?
Well, I had that
premonition for a reason.
Just because the killer
isn't supernatural--
Hey there, Glen.
- What did you hear?
- Excuse me?
- She said, "What are you doing here?"
- I was just looking for the kitchen.
Didn't you--?
Didn't you leave already?
Yeah, yeah, but now I'm back.
But I better get going again
before somebody wonders
what happened to me.
I'll just take Glen to the kitchen
and show him
where to make a sandwich.
Is he staying here?
I think you need to talk to her.
I did, and apparently
I was the only one paying attention.
What the hell's going on in there?
Come on, open the damn door!
Maybe something's wrong.
I'll call for the bailiff.
I am so sorry.
It's that time of the month.
Look,
the rest of us finished voting,
1 1 guilty. What's it gonna be?
Well...
Before I cast my vote,
I think that we should
all consider the possibility
that the defendant might
actually be a psychic.
What?
And all he is guilty of
is having a special gift.
You're the foreman. Make her vote.
- Yeah.
- Not until I review the evidence.
Every single piece.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
So I have to go to work,
but if you want,
you can drop me off
and then use my car.
Oh, no, I'm wiped.
I'm just gonna hang here if it's cool.
Paige, is everything okay?
What was going on in there?
Oh, that? That's just
a family meeting,
deciding who's gonna
take out the trash
or whose turn it is to clean
the bathroom.
We take it all very seriously here.
I heard words like "killer"
and "supernatural."
That doesn't really sound
like housework to me.
We never really could lie
to each other very well.
Well, maybe that's why
we didn't make it as a couple.
I've been worried about you,
since the last time I saw you,
just before you moved in here.
And the vibe that I've been getting
since I got here
doesn't make me worry any less.
Everything is fine, Glen, just fine.
Things are just...
...different now.
Yeah, you have sisters to talk to,
and I think that's great, I really do.
But that doesn't mean that we still
can't be there for each other, does it?
Talk to me, Paige. What's--?
What's going on?
Paige?
Darryl got us that thing
with the guy that Phoebe
was talking about.
Are you coming?
Yeah, I can't. I have to go to work.
All right, well, keep
your cell phone available,
just in case anything comes up.
I'll see you later.
Excuse me.
Paige, you're gonna leave him
here alone?
Well, he can't fit
in my cubicle with me at work.
Paige, keeping your secret
has to be the most important thing.
I know, which is why
I just lied to my best friend.
It didn't feel good, Leo, but I did it.
That's not good enough.
It's irresponsible to leave him here.
You told me when I became a witch
I'd still have a life.
- I call having a friend having a life.
- But that doesn't mean you can--
Paige, Paige--
- I'm interrupting again.
- Yeah.
All right, we gotta go,
so be sure to lock up
all the doors before you go.
She always that friendly?
Yeah, pretty much.
I'll see you later.
I still don't understand exactly
who you people are.
Did lnspector Morris vouch for us?
Yes, but that doesn't really--
All you need to know is that
we may be able to save your client.
Isn't that enough?
Look, the jury's deliberating.
Nothing short of a miracle
can help him now.
Precisely.
Don't tell me they reached a verdict?
No, they haven't.
These people wanted to talk to you.
Who are you?
We're people who believe
you're innocent.
So if you don't mind, we'd like
to ask you a few questions.
Was there anything
in your premonition
to indicate who the killer might be?
- Yeah, all right, that's it. Out.
- What? Why?
Because we're not hanging
any more of this case
on that so-called vision of his,
unless you want him to plead insanity.
No, wait, wait!
You actually believe me
about having had a premonition?
Yes, we do.
That's why we need to know
exactly what you saw,
if we have any chance
of saving you.
I don't need a premonition
to know who killed Angie.
It was Wyke, Andrew Wyke.
He owns the magic club
where I performed.
Why do you think he killed her?
Angie kept the books for the club,
even after we got divorced.
She found out that Wyke was using
the club to launder dirty money.
And when he found out
that she told me about it,
well, he killed her with
one of my knives to frame me.
Then I go and help him by telling
the police where Angie's body was.
Do you know if Wyke has a tattoo
of a Medusa head on his arm?
I don't know.
Well, let's hope he does. Thank you.
Look out, Nancy Drew,
coming through.
Maybe we should come back
at night when they're open.
I don't think we have that kind of time.
How does this place stay in business?
Demons you can handle,
but not rats?
Hey, what are you doing in here?
- Who the hell are you?
- We're friends of Stan Provozoli's.
Good for you. We're closed.
Yeah, I see that. I was just hoping--
I said we're closed, and I don't want
to have to say it again. Leave.
All I am saying is to reach
a fair and just verdict,
we have to analyze
every aspect of this case.
- We've done that.
- Twice.
You know what? Maybe we
should do it a third time.
Because it seems to me that you
people care more about getting home
for dinner than about the fact
that the evidence
against Stan Provozoli
is entirely circumstantial.
He led the police to the body!
You heard the shrink say
that's as good as a confession.
- Unless it was a premonition.
- She's back to that again.
Is it so hard for you
to believe that that's possible?
That there are powers
beyond what we can see?
Okay.
Haven't any of you ever known
who's calling before
you answer the phone?
That's not magic.
Oh, no? Then what is it?
Look, just because
you don't understand magic
doesn't mean that you have
to be afraid of it.
It's around us all the time.
Like a friend, guiding us,
giving us inspiration,
helping us fall in love.
Giving our lives meaning.
And I'm sorry, but l...
...think that we all need
to believe that magic exists.
Tanya,
why are you wearing an angel pin?
I don't know. Just because
my mother gave it to me.
But why did she give it to you?
- To watch over me.
- That's magic.
Something that you can't see.
You can't quite put your finger on it,
but you know that it's there.
The man killed a woman!
Period! End of story!
- All those in favour of another vote...
- Here.
- Aye.
- Aye
- Nature calls.
- Oh, no.
- No, you don't. No, no, no.
- I can't believe this.
No way.
She's stalling.
We gotta do something about this.
- Hi.
- We found the killer.
- The owner of the club,
- a guy named Andrew Wyke.
- Can you prove it?
That's the next step.
Okay, well, you gotta hurry
because I'm dying in there.
Be easier if we vanquish him.
You can't, but you might be able
to use your magic.
Well, there is one guy
I'd love to turn into a wart hog.
Not on the jury. On the killer.
You and Paige could use your powers
to scare him into confessing.
And show our powers to Wyke?
I do not think so.
You think anybody's gonna
believe him?
Not this jury.
Hey, come on!
Sorry!
Can somebody find me a plunger?
Oh, great.
What? Gotta buy
some time somehow.
And you gotta call Paige.
Maybe there's a spell
in the Book of Shadows we can use?
Okay, go, go, go.
Okay.
Piper, you up here?
What's the emergency?
Oh, my God, Glen,
what are you doing up here?
It's funny. See, after you left,
I was still hungry,
so I opened the fridge.
I found some bags labelled
"pig's feet,"
"rabbit blood,"
"frog tongue."
So I decided to take
a little look around.
I found more than
what I bargained for.
Look, I can explain everything,
okay? I really can.
I'll just have to explain it
later because if Piper
- finds us up here she's gonna freak.
- Piper's gonna freak?
I just found out that your new sisters
have been messing with the occult
in a serious way.
And you're worried about
how they're gonna freak?
Look, we're not "messing around"
with the occult.
We're witches.
My sisters and I are
born good witches.
We do good magic.
This book is full of pictures
of demons and warlocks.
Well, demons and warlocks
that we fight and destroy.
These girls have you brainwashed.
How do you even know
they are your sisters?
Glen, you gotta trust me, please.
I am not brainwashed.
I am still the same old Paige,
only now
if I make a rhyme, magic happens.
Paige.
Look, you've been to Africa.
You've met those
witch doctors on your travels, right?
Yeah, but these guys
were like 1 00 years old,
and they speak in tongues.
And you're you.
- There is a spell in here...
- What?
...to stretch the imagination.
It should be able to help you
understand and accept
the truth about me.
So you're gonna cast a spell on me?
- With your permission.
- And when nothing happens--
When nothing happens,
you can drag me out to the funny farm,
tell them I've been brainwashed.
Believe me, I could use the vacation.
Oh, here it is.
Let mind and body soar
To heights not reached before
Let limits stretch, that you may catch
A new truth to explore
I don't feel any different.
That's weird. It always works.
- Paige, where are you?
- God, we gotta hide you. Come on.
No, wait--
It's the spell. Just pull it back.
Oh, I was giving Glen
a tour of the house.
Next stop, the basement.
Come on, Glen.
Why don't you get a head start.
A tour? Of the attic?
- You showed him the Book?
- Well, he went into the fridge,
and he saw the potion ingredients.
So understandably,
he started looking around
and he found the Book.
So you didn't lock the attic?
- It didn't occur to me.
- What do you mean?
I told you to lock all
the doors before you go.
I thought you meant the front door.
You should have been
more specific.
Well, I was speaking in code.
Listen, I trust Glen.
But you're trusting him with a secret
that is all of ours, not just yours.
Honey, she didn't tell him about it.
He discovered it.
Because she left him in the house,
because she let him stay
here in the first place.
So you're saying I have to choose
between having friends
and being a witch?
- Yes, I have.
- Well, I won't.
Okay,
we all need to put this on hold
for a second, okay?
Let's take a deep breath,
Iet's calm down. We have a lot of work
to do and not a lot of time to do it.
- What do we have to do?
- Piper will fill you in on the way.
I need to go check on Phoebe.
So actually, the origin of magic
dates back to prehistoric times.
- People from all cultures believed in--
- Let's vote,
- now.
- Wait.
No, no, we vote.
Okay? If we can't agree,
we declare a hung jury.
All in favour of a guilty verdict...
People, please!
There is magic in the world.
There are angels. Tanya, you could
tell your mother that she's right.
They're real. And there are fairies.
They're real too. I mean,
just think back to your childhood
before you were too jaded
to believe in them.
And Cupid, not a myth.
I mean, he doesn't actually use
arrows, but he's real too.
- Sit down.
- Please.
Bailiff!
- What are you doing?
- We don't have
to declare a hung jury after all.
We don't?
Foreman?
Tell the judge that we have
a juror who's...
...not quite right.
We're asking that she be dismissed
and that you bring in
one of the alternates.
Are you kidding me?
- And you all agree?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- No, wait, wait, wait.
I have an idea.
If I can convince you,
all of you,
that magic really does exist,
will that be enough
reasonable doubt for an acquittal?
Lady, you're late for your shrink.
Like two years late.
Well, what do you mean, "magic"?
Like Siegfried and Roy stuff?
No. I mean real magic.
No trap doors,
no smoke, no mirrors,
just real, supernatural magic.
Come on, she's stalling.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid I might actually
be able to pull it off?
Well, we've been here this long.
I say we let her take it on home.
All right.
But if you fail,
you vote guilty with the rest of us.
Good point.
- Call the judge.
- Okay, okay, okay.
It's a deal.
All right.
Show us some magic.
I'm gonna need a few things.
- A sage stick, five white candles and--
- A magic wand.
No, incense.
I'm gonna summon the dead.
Okay, just remember,
you play good witch,
I play bad witch.
Okay, but won't that risk
exposing our powers?
No, I'm only gonna show
my powers to Wyke,
and once we get him to talk,
we'll use the tape to force him
to confess to the police.
So it's okay to show our powers
to a murderer but not to Glen?
Saving an innocent's life
is worth the risk.
Entertaining friends is not.
What the hell?
What are you?
- What do you want?
- We want a confession.
That's what we want.
Careful, you might kill him.
- So?
- I don't know
- what you're talking about.
- Sure, you do.
Angela Provozoli found out about
your little money
laundering operation,
so you killed her, didn't you?
I've never seen her like this, pal.
You might wanna talk.
You know what?
This is getting boring.
What do you say we move
on to some body parts?
Okay, okay, okay! All right.
All right, I admit it.
I killed her.
She was ready to march
the cops down to Pier 86.
If I hadn't killed her,
they would have.
And then they would have killed me!
Who, the cops?
No. No, not the cops.
They...
Look, believe me,
- you don't wanna know.
- Try me.
What the--?
He's pretty good.
Where'd he go?
There's gotta be a trap door.
Here.
- How does this thing work?
- There's gotta be stairs here.
Wait.
All right, don't.
I can explain.
You stupid human!
You told the witches everything.
- And they've got it on tape!
- So what?
- They'll never find out about you guys.
- Not from you, they won't.
No, no. No!
Dinnertime.
What, demons you can handle
but not rats?
Right back at you.
I don't get it. Where'd he go?
Is hell too much to hope for?
Yeah, well, at least
we got his taped confession.
Yeah, but that's not
gonna save Stan,
or Phoebe, for that matter.
Why don't we just give it
to the police?
Well, without Wyke,
the confession is no good.
I mean, Darryl could open up
an investigation
but not in time to exonerate--
Now I actually sound
like Nancy Drew.
So, what, we're supposed
to go find Wyke?
How are we gonna do that?
We have no idea where he is.
What?
- What?
- That noise.
Noise?
- I feel like I'm in Switzerland.
- Switzerland?
- There it is again.
- What?
That annoying echo.
Paige, what's going on?
Nothing. Nothing's going on, Piper.
Hey!
Piper, don't!
You!
You cast a spell on him?
Are you crazy?
No, but somebody is.
I was just trying
to have some fun. Sorry.
Okay, but this is not supposed
to be fun for you.
It's not supposed to be for you at all.
Well, then I guess
I better call off the tabloids.
- He was just making a bad joke.
- Yeah.
Funny how that's the first thing
that came to his mind.
He just thought he was being funny.
Nobody got hurt.
Yeah, maybe you'd feel
a little differently
if you had lost a sister.
Don't ask.
Did you get Wyke to confess?
Yeah, and then he got away.
How's Phoebe doing?
Not so good. She's trying
to summon the victim, Angela.
Wait a second.
So it's not okay for me
to tell my best friend Glen
that I'm a witch, but it's okay for Phoebe
to tell an entire room of strangers?
They were gonna
kick her off the jury.
I think it was worth a try.
Only it's not going so good.
I believe she needs
the power of three.
Yeah, well, she's not gonna get it.
Better for them
to think she's a nut job
than think she's a witch.
There's an innocent man
at stake, Piper.
They'll convict him,
then we'll go to the police.
There'll be a new trial,
and they'll release him.
You don't know that.
All right, I have an idea.
- What?
- I'll explain on the way. Let's go.
What about him?
Yeah, just unfreeze him.
He won't tell anyone.
What--?
Where'd you come from?
Just stay here, order a pizza.
I'll be back soon.
What?
What--?
Where did they go?
Beloved spirit Angela
I seek your guidance
I ask that you commune with me
And move among us
- Beloved spirit Angela--
- That's enough. Bailiff!
Tell the judge
that we've reached a verdict.
Yeah, a deal's a deal.
- All those in favour of guilty?
- Aye.
- I'll get the lights.
Beloved spirit Angela
I seek your guidance
I ask that you commune with me
And move among us
- Phoebe, 1 1 jurors?
- I know.
I know, but this guy is innocent.
And he's being persecuted
for having the same gift that I do.
So if you guys aren't here
to help me summon Angela--
We are.
- We are?
- Yes.
If Leo will help us clean it up
after we're done.
No.
What do you mean, "no"?
You've done it before.
No, it is completely forbidden,
except in cases of dire emergency.
What's forbidden?
Using memory dust on people.
Oh, my God. This is brilliant.
We'll erase their short-term
memories after they vote not guilty.
Wait a second. Whitelighters
can erase people's memories
with some sort of special dust?
Why don't you just use it all the time?
Because you don't know
what you might be erasing.
Doctors' appointments,
children's birthdays...
Leo, this is an emergency.
I cannot live with these people
knowing our secret,
knowing that at any minute
we could have to relive
the hell we went through with Prue.
Okay.
Hear these words, hear our cry
Spirit from the other side
Come to us, we summon thee
Cross now, the great divide
Beloved spirit Angela
We seek your guidance
We ask that you commune with us
And move amongst us
Cold wind, that's our cue.
- See you later.
- Okay, thank you, thank you.
Are you all seeing that?
Dear God.
What happened?
Where am l?
We summoned you, Angela.
We need your help.
Actually your ex-husband
needs your help.
Stan? Why?
He's on trial for your murder.
Stan?
Are you kidding?
He couldn't hurt a fly.
- Even his gift terrified him.
- His gift?
What are you doing?
I'm looking for wires.
This is some kind of trick.
Did you find any?
What about his gift?
Stan could see things.
The past, the future. It scared him.
He hated it.
That's why he never nurtured it.
All the good he could have done,
wasted.
So he didn't kill you?
No.
The club owner did.
Andrew Wyke.
I found out he was laundering money
from some company at Pier 86.
Stan warned me to keep it to myself.
But I didn't.
He is a good man.
He is an innocent man.
Blessed be.
Shall we vote?
Not guilty.
Unbelievable.
So say you one?
So say you all?
- Yes, Your Honour.
This case is dismissed.
The defendant is hereby released,
and this court is adjourned.
Dust them, Leo.
Don't forget the bailiff.
I don't understand.
- How'd you do it?
- We didn't. Angela did.
- Hi.
You have a very special gift.
And you did the right thing
by going to the police.
It doesn't matter
what anybody else thinks.
All that matters is that
you use your gift to help people.
That's a beautiful thing.
So you guys have told people
about being witches lots of times?
Yes, innocents, but only when
we didn't have any other choice.
Our secret is never more important
than saving somebody's life.
Can't you guys just enjoy saving
this innocent for a minute and a half
before getting back
to the great debate?
Well, it's not over yet.
The killer is still out there somewhere.
Oh, Glen!
You have one hour
to deliver the tape,
or Stretch here is dead.
Paige, it's gonna be okay.
Just try to breathe.
Oh, my God.
If anything happens to him--
We won't let it.
When did this demon
become involved?
I thought this killer
was supposed to be human?
He was. But apparently,
he was fronting for demons.
Since when do demons
give a rat's ass, no pun intended,
about laundering money?
Because they need money
to insinuate themselves into our world.
To buy clothes, rent apartments,
to fit in with us.
That's probably the same way
they made Cole
Iegitimate when he was a demon.
I mean, they put him
through law school.
Which put him
in a position to hurt us.
Water under the bridge.
How is any of this gonna help us
get Glen back?
Even if we give
that rat-demon thing the tape,
what's to stop him from killing Glen?
We have no leverage.
Okay. Do we have to call him
the rat-demon?
Because it's very hard
to be appropriately frightened.
We could go over his head.
Look, I guarantee you that this club
is just the tip of the iceberg.
If we went to rat-demon's--
But what are we supposed to call him?
One hour, Leo, we have one hour.
Right. Look, so if we go
to their bosses
and we threaten to expose
their entire operation,
they're not gonna be
very pleased with him.
So we offer him up in exchange
for Glen. Might work.
Might work? It has to work.
Okay, so the only question is,
where is demon central?
Angela said something
about Pier 86.
So did Wyke. So we split up.
Phoebe, since you have
stalling down to a science,
you and Paige go to the club
and buy some time.
- Leo and I will go to--
- No.
- No, I'm gonna go.
- Well, Piper has more firepower.
- And if they get hostile--
- I'll just have Leo orb me out of there
if it gets too hairy.
I'm the one who put Glen,
my best friend,
in massive amounts of danger.
So I'm gonna get him out.
Just do me a favour and keep him
alive at the club until I get back.
I don't know if this is the right place.
Listen.
- Rats.
- Lots of them.
- Time to go.
- No.
- Paige, I really think that we should--
- No, Leo, they've got Glen.
Listen up!
We know what you're doing.
We're prepared to tell everyone.
And just so you know,
killing me won't help.
My sisters will take you down.
Maybe you've heard of us.
The Charmed Ones?
Now, who am I talking to?
We're listening.
- The tape.
- Where's our friend, mouse-man?
After I get the tape.
No, before.
- I could take it from you.
- You could try.
Just so you know,
if anything happens to me,
anything at all,
the ring will decapitate him.
That's new.
So much for a quick getaway.
Are there any copies?
- No.
- Now let him go.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
I'm a rat. What'd you expect?
Don't. Don't. It might chop off
Glen's head.
What am I supposed to do?
Enjoy the show.
Did we just do that?
- Only copy?
- Yes.
How do we know?
What do you mean,
how do you know?
You just gotta trust us.
We're the good guys,
for crying out loud.
Guess we'll call this one a draw.
Almost done.
This is taking too long.
Can't you just use a little magic?
Well, don't you think
we've used enough magic lately?
Besides, I like working
with my hands.
Yeah, I kind of like a guy
in a tool belt.
Really?
Oh, leaving so soon?
Yeah, Glen's gonna go stay
with a friend of his across the Bay.
I can't imagine why you wouldn't
wanna hang around here.
Yeah, well, I like adventure.
Just not that much adventure.
So you're gonna stick
around a while?
Yeah. Keep an eye on Noogie here.
- Noogie?
- Glen, I think it's time for you to go.
Thanks for saving my life.
- I reversed the spell.
- Just checking.
- Bye.
Bye, you.
Okay, do you want it now?
Or should I e-mail it to you?
- What?
- My apology.
You were right.
Keeping our secret
is the most important thing.
I should have listened to you.
Do you want more?
Should I keep grovelling?
Fun as that would be...
I'm sorry too. I can be a little harsh,
but it's part of my charm.
You'll learn to love me for it.
We actually have a door.
Imagine that.
So how's the jury?
Fine. I knocked on Tanya's door,
and she thought I was the Avon lady.
So, good job, Leo.
Thanks, but I don't wanna
think about it, ever.
Can "ever" wait for a minute or so?
I was thinking maybe we should use
some of that dust on Glen.
You know, I don't want you guys
to have to be nervous.
Well, do you think
he's gonna tell anybody?
- No.
- And you trust him completely?
- Yes.
- Then so do we.
Thank God.
And whether we think
it's smart or not,
at least you have one person
outside the family that you can talk to.
Yeah, let's just keep it to one.