Come in.
My queen,
it's time for your tonic.
Can you do anything
about this thunder?
Because it's making me nuts!
I have no sway over the weather.
I do have a friend
who works with wind,
but she's out of town.
What about demons?
Any sway over them?
Because I swear,
if they don't shut up...
I hate this stuff.
It's for your own good.
Well, whatever happened
to regular old vitamins?
There is nothing regular
about your pregnancy.
The new power you're experiencing
is a mere shadow
of what's to come.
The tonic strengthens you
to bear the weight of it.
Okay. Well, then do me a favour.
Find something that strengthens me
and doesn't taste like crap.
Are you feeling all right?
Yeah, it's just...
I have all this work that I have to do,
and I can't concentrate!
But you are queen now.
There's no reason for you to
continue with this work at all.
I like my work.
It's a good distraction.
A distraction from what?
Still struggling with your decision?
No, I mean...
I love Cole, and, you know,
don't get me wrong,
this whole queen thing
is kind of fun. It's just...
Your sisters.
Yeah, I don't understand
why they have to be so stubborn.
Why they can't just
respect my decision.
Because it's not in the nature
of good to compromise.
They'll never understand.
They'll only want to change you back.
The sooner you accept that
and let them go,
the happier you will be.
Here, drink your tonic.
What the hell is going on out there?
You know, ever since the coronation,
all he does is work.
The underworld's been
in chaos for some time.
- And he has a great task--
- I don't care.
I want some attention
from my husband.
You're excused.
Make certain
you drink that upon waking.
It is after midnight, Cole.
Come to bed.
Phoebe, please,
we're in the middle of a ceremony.
We're almost done.
"Almost" doesn't work for me.
I thought we talked about this.
Sorry, it's hormones.
Damn it,
I have read through this 1 5 times.
There's nothing even remotely helpful
about how to save Phoebe.
I told you, she made a choice.
There's no magical cure for that.
Yeah, well, she's pregnant, Piper,
so she's being influenced
by the baby inside.
And we could have helped her
overcome that, but she chose Cole.
Will you just stop
with the potions already?
You've already overrun the kitchen.
I'd say we have enough.
This one duplicates
my freezing power,
plus it scalds the flesh,
so we should only use it
in a dire emergency.
No.
I will not scald Phoebe's flesh.
She's still our sister.
Paige.
How is she?
She's like Piper Light.
All the personality without any
of those messy emotions.
We'll see.
Rumour on the demonic grapevine is,
their new queen
is killing upper-level demons.
- Word is, she killed two just last night.
- What does that mean?
It means it looks like Phoebe's working
from the inside for the good guys.
That's great.
Since when
do you guys believe rumours
that are spread by demons?
Alison Whitt.
Among other things,
she's spearheading the campaign
to clean up Dolores Park.
That's my district.
I got men there too.
- Since when?
- Since I put them there.
- Then they're working my territory.
- Gentlemen.
It's all my territory.
Next.
Gregory Conroy,
a probation officer
to juvenile offenders.
Manages to rehabilitate
the worst of the worst.
He's cost us
several potential demons.
He's yours.
He works at the--
Relax, boys.
I'm here to cook, not kill.
Although I'd keep
your voices down if I were you.
Hi, honey.
Honey?
Will your friends
be staying for dinner?
I'm gonna find it hard to convince
them to stay unless you stop
- threatening to kill them.
- I was kidding.
You killed five of my best demons
this week, so forgive me
if I'm missing the joke.
Oh, baby, I'm sorry.
I know I've been working a lot.
But that should lighten up soon.
In the meantime,
no more killing.
Promise?
Promise.
It's hard enough for them
to accept the fact
that my queen
is a former Charmed One.
We don't want them
to think you're playing both sides.
I said, I promise.
But if it will make you feel better...
Hi.
I just want to say that I'm really sorry
for killing your friends last night.
Oh, and the night before that.
And it's nothing personal,
you know. It's just...
- Phoebe, was that a...?
- Cramp.
I just need to lay down.
Should I call the Seer?
No.
No. I'm fine.
Where were we?
Gregory Conroy.
Malek's in for the kill.
He spends his time
at the Mission Hill Community Centre.
These are meant
to slow an attacker down
but not do real serious harm.
It's kind of like magical Mace.
Sounds reasonable, I guess.
These are a little more lethal.
Explosives, paralytics,
your garden-variety poisons.
So you're gonna poison Phoebe?
Leo, she's carrying
the spawn of The Source.
She's throwing fire from her hands.
If she shows up here,
we'll do what we have to do
to protect ourselves.
You're not even giving her a chance.
Paige, we gave her
every chance in the world
to come back to us.
And she threw it in our faces.
She chose The Source of All Evil
over her own family.
Surprise.
Nice to see you too, Piper.
What do you want?
And here I thought
you'd be happy to see me.
I'm happy to see you.
- Paige.
- What?
Unless you're here
to tell us you filed for divorce,
we don't really have much
to talk about.
Oh, that's not true.
For instance, we could talk
about how rigid you are.
It's really not
a very attractive quality.
Wait.
Phoebe, what are you doing here?
I had a premonition.
We have an innocent to save
and not a lot of time.
That is so great. Look, I told you.
Don't get excited.
It's not what you think.
I haven't changed my mind.
I'm not leaving Cole,
and I'm not renouncing my crown.
It's just,
I've never ignored
a premonition in my life,
and I'm not about to start now.
Phoebe, you're evil.
You're, like, the queen of all evil.
Literally.
- That's beside the point.
- How can that be besides the point?
I say we do it.
- What?
- Excuse me.
Look, this is what
we've been hoping for:
A sign that there's still good in her.
Why else would she care
about saving an innocent?
Because it's a trap.
Piper, this could be our only chance.
I think Paige is right.
Maybe by helping her do good,
it might sway her back to our side.
Fine.
Okay, you're on. We'll follow you.
What's that for?
Insurance.
Why do I always have to land
in the mud?
Come on, over here.
How do you know
when he's gonna get attacked?
I know.
There he is.
Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Stop.
My queen.
Leave that innocent alone.
Go.
What?
He's one of my subjects.
How--? How could you do that?
How could you just let him go?
I don't know why you're so upset.
We saved the innocent, didn't we?
I can't talk to her. You talk to her.
- Phoebe--
- Things are not as black-and-white
as they used to be.
Okay, I can't just go around
killing demons anymore.
Why not? We heard
you just killed two last night.
Yeah, well, that was different.
He was getting on my nerves.
I promised Cole
I wouldn't kill anymore.
And killing Malek
would have been a huge betrayal.
Malek? You're on a first-name basis
with the demons?
If you were gonna order him to stop,
you could've done that on your own.
- Why did you even come to us?
- Because I missed you guys!
Okay? Is that so wrong?
I missed you.
Well, Phoebe, you can't be
the queen of the underworld
and a Charmed One.
You can't have it both ways.
Why not?
Just because it's different
doesn't mean that it can't work.
And you all miss me too,
even though I'm sure
Piper probably doesn't want
to admit it to herself.
- Of course we miss you, honey.
- Well, you can have me back.
You can have
the power of three back.
You just have to be willing
to meet me halfway.
Phoebe,
you can't protect the innocent
and save demons.
It just doesn't work that way.
Apparently, it does.
He's alive, isn't he?
Yeah, but your friend Malek
is gonna come back.
- You don't know that.
- That's what they do Phoebe,
they come back.
They snarl and come back.
Now we have to worry
about protecting him
instead of trying to save you.
- You think I need saving?
- Are you kidding me?
That baby inside you
has corrupted you
more than you think.
- Piper--
- Don't "Piper" me.
This is insane.
What you are saying is insane.
You cannot come back.
You cannot work with us
as long as you are married
- to The Source.
- So, what do you want me to do?
- You want me to leave my husband?
- Yes.
- That is not fair!
- It's not fair, Phoebe,
but you have to pick a side.
Good or evil. That's how it works.
Even though it means giving up
someone you love,
you have to choose.
I'm really sorry you feel that way.
I can't do this.
What about Greg?
Oh, no, not again.
Did you guys see
anybody take off
on a chrome and orange bicycle?
No, sorry.
I don't even know
why I bother to lock it.
- What should we do?
- Follow him.
They were animal-sacrifice caverns.
For the most part,
they've been abandoned.
Waste of space, don't you think?
Put a team on it.
Have it cleaned out--
My liege.
- State your business.
- I have news for The Source.
It concerns his queen.
- What happened? Is she hurt?
- No.
The Charmed Ones interfered
with my kill.
I have no control over my in-laws.
If you want them out of the way,
I suggest you take backup.
I mean all three of them,
including the queen.
She ordered me
not to harm the innocent.
I thought you should know.
Have you told anyone else?
No. I came straight to you.
Thank you...
...for your loyalty.
- Am I next?
- No, Dane.
You...
...I trust.
- It's just my damn wife.
- With all due respect...
...I think you better take care
of the innocent...
...before others hear of this.
My liege.
Get up. I have a job for you.
The only requirement for membership
is a desire to stop drinking.
There are no dues or fees
for membership.
We are self-supporting
through our own contribution.
We do not wish to engage
in any controversy,
neither endorse nor oppose--
So you really think Piper's okay?
I don't know. I think it's good
that she's feeling something again.
Right.
Right. You're right.
She's probably fine.
Is anyone celebrating
30 days today?
So you think I just need
to give her some space, right?
You could try that, yeah.
It's just when Piper lost Prue,
she barely survived,
and she thinks
she's gonna lose Phoebe.
She might just...
Listen, just go talk to her, okay?
Remind her that we have
a demon to fight.
And that will do her some good
and take her mind off Phoebe.
Right, right.
- What about you?
- Me? I'm fine.
Listen, I don't think
Malek's gonna attack
in front of all these people.
So just go get Piper
and bring her back
before the meeting's over.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
Let me start by...
First, let me start
by congratulating the chip-takers.
- Where's the real column?
- Excuse me?
This is cute, very clever,
and I appreciate
the evening chuckle,
but I need to see the real pages.
Are you calling my writing a joke?
"Dear Betrayed,
I suggest you beat
your cheating husband
with his secretary's stapler.
Then he'll think twice
before bending her
over her desk again."
Well,
might be a little harsh,
but I think it makes a point.
What it makes is a lawsuit.
So unless you're looking
to lose your job...
Are you threatening me?
I am telling you
to get a shrink if you have to,
but get it together.
Rewrite that column and do it fast.
Excuse me.
If you wanna kill your boss,
we have people
who can take care of that for you.
Aren't you sweet.
Truth is...
...she's right.
My advice was a little off this week.
I don't understand
what you're doing here.
- You're queen.
- And you're cranky.
I told you I'm not quitting my job.
And what about your other job,
you gonna keep that too?
And what job would that be, Cole?
The Charmed One.
Malek told me what you did.
So what? I let him go.
- That doesn't make it okay!
- Keep your voice down.
This is where I work.
You can't save an innocent
and free a demon, Phoebe.
It doesn't work like that.
- You sound like Piper.
- Well, Piper's right.
You made a choice when you stood
by me at the coronation.
If you're questioning
that choice now, if you're not sure
you wanna be with me,
you need to let me know.
Of course I wanna be with you.
I just don't understand
- why you have to be so rigid.
- Because I am The Source!
Because you are my queen!
Because there are expectations!
Do you think I care
about anyone's expectations?
This is not a game, Phoebe.
You walked through a one-way door.
You try to turn around now,
they will destroy us.
Who?
- My sisters?
- The underworld.
If they think
we're working both sides...
...they will revolt.
If they do that...
If they unite against us...
...I promise,
we will pray for death.
I'm sorry.
- I didn't--
- I get it, Phoebe.
Better than anyone,
I know what you're going through.
It will rip you apart if you let it.
How do I not let it?
You make a choice.
And you stick to it.
Even though it's hard.
Even though it means
giving up the people that you love.
Let's go home.
We're closed.
- Honey--
- I don't want to talk.
- I know you're feeling--
- Even more than I don't want to talk,
I do not want a pep talk.
Piper.
What are you doing?
What does it look like I am doing?
I am trying to stop myself
from feeling like
the failure that I am.
You're not a failure.
- It's not your fault that Phoebe--
- I am the oldest sister, okay?
It is my job
to keep the family together.
And see, at this, my friend,
I am a failure.
That's enough.
Paige could see
that Cole clearly had turned evil.
And she tried to tell me
over and over and over
and over and over and over.
That doesn't even sound
like a word anymore.
You know, I didn't see
that he was evil, Piper.
Phoebe didn't see it at first.
We didn't want to see it.
We wanted a normal, happy family.
That's just human nature.
She is my baby sister.
And I let him destroy her.
That is not human nature.
That is the nature of failure.
All right, I'm not gonna listen
to this anymore.
You are a good witch, and--
I said, no pep talks.
Nobody listens
around here anymore.
Trey.
- Congratulations on your 30 days.
- Thanks.
Leo.
You again.
Are you following me?
Yes.
Strangely, I am,
and I would love to explain it to you.
But it would be better if we
could go talk inside by the crowd.
No!
What the hell?
Leo!
Athame!
Damn it, where are my sisters?
Oh, my God. Piper.
--and a good sister.
Paige, what--?
You were frozen, Leo,
and I'm guessing
- demons didn't get her.
- No, more like inner demons.
I can't believe she froze me.
- Are you okay?
- Barely.
It was a different demon this time.
They really want that guy dead.
You have to heal him
and orb him somewhere safe.
And then what?
Then I'm gonna put this family
back together.
Can you heal Piper?
No, I can't heal
self-inflicted wounds.
Great, now I'm down two sisters.
My queen?
It is time for your tonic.
What if I promise never to save
any innocents with them ever again?
Then can I see my sisters?
You'll feel better after this.
Oh, my God.
- It's poison.
- No.
- You told me it was good for me.
- It is.
- You're lying!
- Think about it.
Last night you were strong,
angry perhaps.
But now look at you, whining.
It's a weakness unbefitting
of a queen.
- What's in it?
- Pure evil.
The baby feeds on it.
- And as he grows stronger...
- I get weaker.
Only the good in you.
You're trying to destroy me.
I am trying to help you.
I gave you clarity
where now you have confusion.
I gave you conviction
where now you have pain.
- You took away my will.
- No.
You made the choice
to stand by your husband
all on your own. For you, for Cole
and for your baby.
Don't risk all of your lives
by questioning that now.
Drink the tonic, Phoebe.
What gives you the authority
to call a meeting and summon me?
I summoned you, my liege,
but I didn't call this meeting.
We all did.
Then someone had better speak.
- The concern--
- Someone else.
Malek is missing.
And the Charmed Ones
are guarding his mark.
Word on the street is that the queen
worked alongside her sisters,
who interfered with the kill.
I wonder how that news spread.
Forgive our confusion,
but we were under the impression
that the power of three
no longer existed.
The queen is pregnant.
She's prone to hormonal fits.
But I can assure you all
that the power of three
is indeed extinct.
Then who killed Malek?
I did.
I was convinced
he was about to betray me.
Nevertheless, his mark still lives.
Then assign someone
to finish the task, Dane.
I believe you already tried that,
- my liege.
- Are you questioning me?
The innocent
is still in the hands of the witches.
Until we've seen evidence
that the queen's...
...hormones
are indeed under control,
it might be best
if you took out the mark,
personally.
For morale.
How many hangover cures
do you have?
A lot. There was a time in my life
when I needed these often.
I'm sorry, Paige,
I don't know what got into me.
I mean, it's one thing
when your sister has a husband
that you can't stand. It's another
when he is The Source of All Evil.
Drink up. We got some work to do.
I can't lose her.
I can't lose another sister.
I don't think I'll survive it.
I've been thinking about it.
Phoebe was different today.
Yeah, she was nuts.
Yeah, but she cared about us,
about Greg.
Something has changed, and I think
now is our chance to get her back.
- How?
- Well, I think we storm the penthouse,
bring the crystals.
We still know the spell.
We vanquish The Source
the same way we did the last time.
Yeah, but now,
this time, The Source is Cole.
Do you really think she's gonna say
a little spell with us to vanquish him?
If she doesn't, we die.
Is that supposed to be comforting?
Actually, yeah.
The good in Phoebe
is fighting to the surface.
We saw that today.
I don't think she's just gonna stand by
and watch Cole kill us.
Are you willing
to bet your life on that?
Aren't you?
You know,
you're pretty amazing, Paige.
I mean, a year ago
you were an only child.
And I don't want to be again.
Let's go.
There we go.
I'll get the crystals.
Phoebe.
Cole is gonna kill Greg Conroy.
And I can't let that happen.
So, what do you wanna do?
I think that we
have to vanquish Cole.
I knew it. I knew she was ready.
We have to use Greg as bait.
Bait? He's an innocent.
I know, but Cole is looking for him.
He'll find him wherever he is,
so he's safest here.
So we have Leo bring Greg here,
but then when Cole arrives,
Leo's gotta orb Greg out of here.
And then we vanquish Cole.
I'll get the crystals.
Phoebe...
... I know how much you love Cole.
- And I'm really--
- I can't get
emotional about this now,
Piper. If I do,
I won't be able to go through with it.
Ready.
Leo, bring Greg.
So how long do you think
till Cole gets here?
Sooner than you think.
Phoebe, we have to--
What's the matter?
Did you know
about the Seer's tonic?
What it really does?
What's this?
You're planning to leave me?
I wrote two letters.
One saying goodbye to you, and one
saying goodbye to my sisters.
I haven't decided
which one I'm gonna send.
Well, you better decide.
- Right now.
- Did you know about the tonic?
Yes.
So you knew
she was poisoning me with evil.
You took my hand
and walked me
through that coronation
Iong before anybody
gave you anything to drink.
If you wanna pretend
that you're poisoned--
So why even bother with the tonic?
Why not just let me think for myself?
I know how it feels to have
good and evil fighting inside of you,
ripping your insides out.
I wanted to save you that pain.
You should have trusted me...
...to stand by you,
all on my own.
So...
...show me I can.
You know what's in the tonic now.
You know how it works.
Drink it.
All on your own.
Cole.
I don't have time
for games, Phoebe.
Just drink the tonic,
or leave now.
What is going on with you?
- What happened?
- What happened is, you had to go
- play demon catcher with your sisters.
- Cole, it's who I am!
And now we're in danger.
Serious danger.
If you don't care about your life
or mine
or the baby's,
what about Paige and Piper?
Don't you threaten them.
I'm not.
If there's a coup, do you think whoever
takes over for me will let them live?
Without the power of three,
they're sitting ducks.
I don't know what to do.
You can't go back.
There is only one choice.
Drink the tonic.
You have to know
that I would never do
anything to hurt you.
Please?
For us.
For our son.
I love you, Phoebe.
Just remember,
whatever happens next,
we can handle it
as long as we stay together.
What do you mean,
"whatever happens next"?
The Conroy thing got serious.
I had to take care of it.
- You killed him?
- It was your mess.
- I was just cleaning it up.
- Cole, they're gonna come after you.
- They're gonna come here.
- Well, if they do--
No.
Phoebe, if it comes down
to them or us...
Oh, God.
Phoebe, wait.
Phoebe.
Phoebe?
You evil son of a bitch.
Phoebe. Get out here
and help us, damn it.
Paige.
Don't make me kill you.
Phoebe? You heard what he said.
He's gonna kill us. Help us.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
It's...
It's for the best.
I know it is.
Phoebe?
I'm sorry too.
Phoebe, no.
- No!
- I'm sorry, baby.
I'm so sorry.
Prudence, Penelope
Patricia, Melinda
Astrid, Helena
Laura and Grace
I'll always love you.
Halliwell witches
Stand strong beside us
Vanquish this evil
From time and space
- Hey.
Why don't you go up and see her.
I don't know what to say.
I mean, I can't imagine...
If it had been you...
Hey.
How is she doing?
I don't know.
She hasn't come down yet.
How long you been standing there?
A while.
Maybe we should go see her?
Okay.
What if she wants to be alone?
She's gonna be alone a lot.
Maybe right now she needs us.
Right.