Can you hand me that tyre iron?
Yeah, sure. Here.
That's a lug bolt.
It's all right. I got it.
That's a tyre iron?
Well, I... I really appreciate
you doing this for me.
I mean, I probably
could've just called a tow truck.
It's no problem. Too bad
you didn't get this before class.
Could've avoided Dr Rousseau's
lecture on cognitive dissonance.
Yeah, pretty dull.
Thought about leaving, but...
I felt bad about skipping class,
so I ended up staying.
To avoid your own dissonance?
You're pretty good
at this psychology stuff.
- You should read my column.
- I do.
Why don't we get together
sometime and study?
Well, I may not know the difference
between a lug bolt and a tyre iron,
but I do believe that you
just asked me out on a date, Tim.
Yeah, so...
How about dinner tomorrow night?
Okay. But it's my treat.
It's the least I can do.
- Deal.
- You're gonna take me up on that?
It's reverse psychology.
Whoa.
Tim! Tim!
Help! Somebody help me!
Phoebe, what happened? Paige
called and said you were attacked.
No, I wasn't. A guy from my class was.
- Is he okay?
- No.
- He's dead.
- Oh, God!
It was so weird.
One second he was helping me
with my flat tyre, and then the next...
And I don't get it.
The demon didn't seem interested in me.
He went right after Tim.
- Did you find anything in the Book?
- It was a raptor demon. A hired gun.
Hired by who?
That's what we're trying to figure out.
Paige's trying to find a lead.
I just don't understand
why he attacked him.
There's a reason.
How well did you know him?
We sat next to each other in class
and, you know,
talked occasionally and flirted a bit.
In fact, he asked me out
on a date for tomorrow night.
It's just my luck, huh?
Phoebe, stop it. It's not like
you're cursed or something.
We don't know that. I might be cursed.
We don't know what's going on.
Tim could have been a witch,
or another demon.
No, he's definitely not a demon.
Okay, then there's
probably another reason.
I don't know, but what
I do know is it's not your fault.
Look, why don't you call Darryl and see
if he can do a background check on Tim.
Maybe you should go to the morgue to see
if you can get
a premonition from his body.
I don't wanna see him.
What if it's the only way
to find out why he was killed?
Okay.
You keep checking the Book.
Sure.
Impressive.
Most impressive.
But you're gonna learn to like me yet.
Well, it's about time.
Where's the body?
- Why didn't you bring it?
- Patience, my old friend.
Have I ever failed
to deliver on a promise?
I don't know.
It has been an eternity
since we... worked together.
Yes, those were the days. The Crusades,
the September massacres,
the Black Plague.
- Good times.
- Good times, good times.
- So let's get on with it already.
- No.
No. It's taken me
months to get this far.
I'm not gonna blow it all now
by moving too quickly.
You gotta understand,
when the dead are involved,
I get a little... excited.
That's exactly why you'll never
become anything more than an Alchemist.
You're unable to see the bigger picture.
- And you can?
- I study the sisters.
With all the knowledge I've gained,
I'm gonna shake them to their core.
Make them more vulnerable
than they've ever been.
That's why you had
Phoebe's friend killed.
It seemed a little petty of you.
But he served a much greater purpose.
Imagine how upset Phoebe
will be when she realises...
...he died just because he knew her.
Imagine how cursed she will feel.
Do you really think that's enough
to make them vulnerable?
Of course not.
If I am to get what I'm after,
I'm going to have to attack them all.
Not as witches, but as women.
Phoebe, I'll meet you at the morgue.
This isn't a good idea.
Are you ready to go?
Sheila... Honey...
Darryl, please don't
tell me you have to work.
- We bought tickets three months ago.
- Listen, I know. I'm really sorry.
- Why don't you take your friend Nadine?
- That's who I took last time.
- Can't you get somebody to cover?
- Not on this one I can't.
- It's the sisters, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- They okay?
- Lieutenant, we need to talk.
A Halliwell has reported
yet another suspicious murder.
Inspector Sheridan,
you've met my wife Sheila?
No, actually.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
- I'm surprised we haven't met.
- We did.
Six months ago at the medal ceremony?
That must have been before I got hurt.
Yeah, I've been having
memory problems since then, so...
Really? Darryl never mentioned it.
You know what,
we really gotta be going now.
- Date night?
- It was.
Listen, I'll call you tomorrow, okay?
- What happened to her?
- You don't wanna know.
Darryl, what aren't you telling me?
Honey, I really have
to get to Phoebe. I'm sorry.
Hello? We're home!
Traffic was horrible.
We should've been home an hour ago.
We want a normal life.
That means we give up the cosmic taxi.
Doesn't mean I gave up
the right to complain about it.
Phoebe? Paige?
- Where do you want the party supplies?
- Put 'em on the table.
- I'm not sure we're gonna need 'em.
- Why not?
I don't know if it's right
to give Chris a birthday party
- when Phoebe's friend was just killed.
- We can't put everything on hold
- every time a demon attacks.
- Yeah...
- You guys just getting home?
- We started when you called,
but the freeway's a nightmare.
How's Phoebe?
- Not so good.
- Is she upstairs?
No, she's at the morgue.
I thought she said you knew.
How would I know?
I haven't talked to her.
- I'm kind of worried about Phoebe.
- Why?
I mean I know we've
seen a lot of deaths,
but she's taking
this one particularly hard.
I was talking to her on the phone
and she thinks she's cursed.
That's silly.
I know, but I'm thinking
if we can figure out
why this guy was killed, maybe
we can prove to her that she isn't?
- Find anything at Magic School?
- No. I'm not gonna be able to go back.
- I've got to meet Joanna.
- Joanna?
New charge. She's a Whitelighter-to-be.
She doesn't know magic exists
and thinks we're just friends.
Elders are worried
about her falling off the path.
I'm gonna guide her
in the right direction.
Go. The Elders wouldn't worry
unless they had reason.
- Piper and I are here. We can help.
- What about Chris's party?
- I think we're gonna have to postpone.
- What? No!
- No, Phoebe wouldn't want you to.
- I know, but...
We can make this work. I know we can.
Keep planning that party.
I'm gonna meet my charge,
give her a pep talk.
By the time Phoebe's back, I'll be home.
We can do this.
Mommy wants to teach you a new word.
It's called "denial."
Let's hurry and get out.
Sheridan's suspicious enough.
- I can't worry about her right now.
- Maybe you should worry.
That memory dust won't
matter anymore if this keeps up.
She's already linked you
to too many murders.
- It's getting harder to cover.
- I know, and I'm sorry.
She's got nothing.
She's going off a hunch.
But if we accidentally trigger
her memories, everything comes back.
And then that's it.
It's over. For all of us.
Well, maybe that's not such a bad thing.
- What do you mean by that?
- Nothing.
You sure you wanna do this?
Yeah...
I mean, I have to know what happened.
- Oh, God!
- Maybe we should go.
No...
I have to do this.
It looks like somebody
was trying to send a message.
What? Why would you say that?
It's vicious, it's calculated.
I see this all the time.
It's like he makes you
think twice when you see him.
Maybe that's the point.
Do demons send messages like this?
Well, if it is a message,
it's obviously for me.
I gotta go.
- Poor Phoebe...
- So troubled.
It's only gonna get worse for her.
So many bodies.
It's a shame to take just one.
Business first, pleasure later.
Can it be done?
Rigor hasn't set in yet.
It's barely a challenge.
I'll make it up to you, I promise.
Let's get to work.
It's the only thing that makes sense.
Tim was killed 'cause he was with me.
You don't know that for sure.
There has to be
some sort of an explanation.
- Okay?
- Well, I'm open to suggestions.
Phoebe, listen, we really have to go.
When I get home,
we'll figure out who sent the demon.
You need to get some rest.
That'd be the best thing for you now.
Rest? How am I supposed to rest
when I'm the reason that Tim's dead?
That's why you need some sleep,
'cause you are not thinking clearly.
Don't talk to me like I'm crazy!
I was there. I know what happened.
Fine. When I get home,
we will figure this out together.
But, for now, please,
please try to get some rest.
Take care, okay?
Listen... Phoebe,
don't do this to yourself.
It is not your fault.
There's nothing you could've done.
Hey. Sorry, that was my sister.
I might have to cut this a little short.
That's okay. Karl didn't want me
coming out tonight anyway.
- You're still seeing him?
- I know what you're gonna say, Paige,
- but he's a good guy. I swear.
- I'm just worried about you.
'Cause honestly, I kind of get
a little bit of a bad vibe from him.
But you don't know him like I do.
I know you've had a tough time lately,
and I don't wanna see you
- get hurt by this guy.
- I won't, I promise.
Trust me, he's the only thing
that's good in my life right now.
- Other than you, of course.
- Well, thank you.
Really. You've been such a good friend.
I don't know what I would've done
- without you the last few weeks.
- Sweetie, here's the thing.
You have an amazing future ahead of you.
You're just gonna
have to have a little faith.
Joanna.
- I told you I didn't want you with her.
- What're you doing?
- Getting her away from you.
- Don't be rude.
She's been trying to get between us
since day one. I know she has.
Look, come on, let's get out of here.
I... I'll be right there.
He probably just had
a bad day, that's all.
Yeah. I'm sure that's what it is.
You know, you don't have to go with him.
I'll be fine. I promise.
I'll call you later, okay?
It was your fault.
I died because of you.
Now I'm gonna make you pay!
- Phoebe, what's wrong? What is it?
- He's trying to kill me!
Who?
I'm telling you, he was there.
And he blamed me for letting him die.
And you're sure you
didn't just dream this?
I'm sure. How many times
do I have to tell you that?
It's a valid question, considering
Leo and I didn't see anybody.
That doesn't mean he wasn't there.
Okay, but isn't it possible
that maybe you were just dreaming?
Maybe it's your subconscious,
'cause you've been feeling guilty.
- It wasn't a dream.
- She might be right.
I found something
on the undead here in the Book.
- Undead, like zombies?
- According to the Book,
demonic alchemists have the ability
to control the undead,
but lack the power
to bring them to life.
They need a upper-level demon
for that.
Now we're looking for two demons?
Which means Tim'll be back,
'cause he wants to make me pay.
- Who knows? Maybe I deserve it.
- Come on, you can't think like that.
If the demons are behind this
and controlling Tim,
- they're just trying to freak you out.
- It's working.
Which is why you need
to get back to business as usual,
before you drive yourself crazy.
Why don't you go to work?
- I don't wanna go to work.
- Might not be a bad idea.
It's public.
Nobody's gonna attack you there.
As soon as we come up with a plan,
I'll come get you.
Come on, you're not doing
anybody any good like this.
Just get up and go to work.
Okay. But if you find the Alchemist,
you have to come get me.
It's Joanna.
Now can we cancel Chris's party?
Before any walking dead crash it?
I guess we have to.
On the bright side, he's only one.
He's not gonna remember it.
We will.
She got in a big fight
with her boyfriend, she's upset.
- I have to go.
- A lover's spat?
That something her Whitelighter
needs to deal with? Especially now?
Her boyfriend.
I get a bad vibe from him.
- I feel like he's gonna hurt her.
- Then you should go.
And we should call Morris and make sure
that Tim's body is still in the morgue.
Or not.
You don't need to keep him like this.
Revive him.
I can control him.
I'll revive him when I'm ready.
But you've barely even used him.
I had to pull him out
before Piper saw him.
I can't allow the sisters
to figure us out too quickly.
They will in time.
Of course, but by then they won't
be able to ignore the emotional fallout.
Besides, right now your friend
there will only distract us.
- We need to keep our eye on the prize.
- Your prize! Not mine!
What if I were to give you a body
that's been dead quite a bit longer.
Would that satisfy your appetite?
Depends...
How long has he been dead?
Four years, give or take.
Was he embalmed?
Was the casket wood or metal?
Let's find out.
Metal. What do you know?
- Interested?
- You know me too well.
But why this body, out of all
the wonderful choices in the world?
As I said, I know the sisters.
This will help remind Phoebe
of the cost of the eternal fight.
Of all the innocents she failed to save.
That's hardly enough to make
all the sisters doubt themselves.
No, but as Phoebe
loses faith in herself,
she'll spread that feeling
to the other two. Starting with Paige,
who by then will be
ripe for a crisis of faith.
- I'll see to that.
- You better be sure about this.
Believe me, I am.
The sisters and the
Book of Shadows are linked.
Always have been.
By weakening them,
I'll weaken the Book's defences too.
Enough to make it mine.
- Damn it!
- I figured you'd come sooner or later.
- What are you doing here, Sheridan?
- The coroner called the captain.
Told him Tim Cross's body was missing.
And that you were
the last one to see it.
- You wanna tell me why you're here?
- I got an anonymous tip.
I decided to check it out.
Any chance that tip
came from a Halliwell?
- I said anonymous.
- I see.
Coroner also said that you
came by with a woman last night.
Phoebe Halliwell?
She was friends with the victim.
She needed closure.
She must need a lot of closure,
given the number of murders
she's been connected to.
Several of which
include law enforcement officers.
- Trudeau, Rodriguez...
- The sisters did not kill them.
Morris...
Darryl.
I know you're a good cop.
I can't believe you'd help killers.
I don't know what these women
have on you...
- They don't have anything.
- Why are you protecting them?
You know what you're doing to yourself?
To your career? Your family?
Your wife know the risk you're taking?
- Leave her out of this.
- Then come clean with me.
Tell me what you know.
Maybe I can help you
before it's too late.
Before you force me
to take you down too.
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna pull through this.
I'm not. This always happens.
Just when I think I've found
the right guy, it all falls apart.
But Karl might not be
the right guy for you.
You might really
be better off without him.
Why? So I can just be alone forever?
As if my life isn't bad enough already.
You can't talk like that.
- You can't just give up on yourself.
- Says who?
Sometimes I think maybe
the world'd be better off without me.
Now, that's absolutely not true. You're
gonna have to believe me on that one.
Now what?
Just give me a second, okay?
Hey, I thought you said
you could do this without me.
Well, you know, things change.
I just talked to Darryl.
Tim's body is missing.
Missing? I guess Phoebe
wasn't dreaming after all.
I'm gonna get to work
on a vanquishing potion
to get rid of the Alchemist.
Hopefully, if we do that,
it'll reverse his magic
and Tim can rest in peace.
We still don't know why the Alchemist's
doing this or who he's working with.
Well, we're just gonna have
to find him and make him tell us.
I need you to get Phoebe
and bring her home.
I don't wanna leave Joanna right now.
- Is it life or death?
- No.
Well, this is. Paige,
the faster we get rid of the demons,
the faster you can get to your charge.
Fine, I'll be there as soon as I can.
I'm gonna have to go.
I've got a bit of a family emergency.
What if Karl comes back?
I don't want to face him alone.
You won't have to. Just call me.
I'll be here in a second.
But what if you're far away?
If you really need me,
just yell my name loudly.
- But...
- No buts. It's okay.
You have to trust me.
I'm always watching out for you.
I promise.
Lock the door behind me.
If Karl comes by, do not open the door.
All right?
I'll be back as soon as I can.
What's the matter, Joanna?
I thought you loved being alone with me.
How did you get in here?
Magic.
Paige? Is that who
you're trying to call out for?
Well, I'm afraid Paige
has abandoned you.
But if it makes you feel any better,
I'm sure she'll be very upset
she had to miss this.
Send these Priority Mail. Actually,
overnight. These people need help.
- What are they?
- Advice to my readers.
- You're answering directly?
- Can only print so many in the paper.
Don't wanna let anybody down.
You can send my e-mails through.
You don't have to sort through them,
okay? Great, thanks.
- Thought she'd never leave.
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
It's really busy today. Letters
don't answer themselves, you know.
- Great, you're feeling better then.
- Yeah.
I didn't wanna come in,
but you guys were right,
- it's really helped me a lot.
- Well, fantastic.
We should go, 'cause you told me to come
get you when we have something and...
- We have something.
- Can it wait?
Excuse me?
I have all these letters
that I have to answer.
Not to mention e-mails,
phone messages and faxes...
- So?
- These people need me.
I can't just let them down, you know.
- I see what's going on here, missy.
- What do you mean?
Nothing's going on, I'm just
helping innocents in need, that's all.
You're feeling guilty
and you're overcompensating.
That's ridiculous, I'm not.
I'm just doing my job. I thought
I was the one studying psychology.
I may not have studied psychology,
but I've studied you,
and this is classic Phoebe.
You're running from your pain.
You cannot run away from this.
Well, I can try, can't I?
He was just helping me
with a flat tyre, that's all.
He didn't do anything wrong.
He was just...
...with me.
And how am I supposed to deal with that?
Well, I think you deal with it
by vanquishing the demons responsible.
Making Tim's death count for something.
We don't know who's responsible,
or why they're doing this.
I'm starting to think
there's only one demon
who could be responsible for this.
Careful. Take it easy.
Careful. Not so much.
Yes, yes! He's alive!
Welcome back, Inspector.
Where am I?
What am I doing here?
Beginning your new life.
What's the last thing you remember?
You've been so brave, Inspector.
- Don't ruin it now.
- Open the gate!
A demon...
...attacked me. Bit me.
- It killed you.
More than four years ago.
I brought you back.
We brought you back.
I don't understand.
Well, then let us help you, my child.
You remember Phoebe Halliwell?
Miss Halliwell, I think you
know more than you're letting on.
You're scared.
You're afraid that if I find the truth,
you're gonna get in trouble.
Am I right?
I wish I could help you.
But I can't.
She could've warned you. Saved you.
Think of all that she cost you.
A wife, a family.
You were just doing your job.
It was quite selfish of her, really.
She lived on while they suffered,
grieving over your death.
It's time to even the score.
Zankou?
He's certainly powerful enough
to help the Alchemist.
He knows us well enough
to try something like this.
- Maybe he's finally going after us.
- Yeah, but why kill an innocent?
- Why not just come after me?
- Maybe he's trying to break you.
I'm beginning to like it better
when I thought I was cursed.
- You know you're not, right?
- Right, I do now.
- I should've listened to you yesterday.
- What do you mean?
You know, the talk we had in the attic.
Wait, was that not you?
It was probably Zankou,
he shapeshifted into us before.
Okay, well how do
I know this is you now?
How do I know you're not Zankou now?
- Because I'm not.
- Prove it.
Jake Singer. Back seat, tenth grade.
Can Zankou tell you all about that?
- I think I'm losing my mind.
- Where are you going?
To the Book. To find a way to vanquish
Zankou before I do lose my mind!
What are we gonna do about her?
The only thing we can do.
Help her vanquish Zankou.
Okay, well, then I guess
we won't be needing that potion.
Actually, we need to get to the
Alchemist who can lead us to Zankou.
Hopefully, when we
get rid of both of them,
Phoebe will be able to sleep again.
- Where's Phoebe going?
- Probably to a mental institution.
- You put the kids down for their nap?
- Yes.
And I started calling
our friends to cancel Chris's party.
- I'm sorry you guys had to do that.
- Next year, he'll have two.
I have to go check on Joanna.
Make sure she's okay.
- Okay, hurry back.
- I will.
Hey Joanna, it's me, Paige.
I'm back.
Joanna, open up.
You okay?
I told you to keep the door locked.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
Lieutenant. We've been waiting for you.
Sheila.
What are you doing here?
What's wrong?
I called her. I thought
that someone should fill her in.
And I'm glad she did.
At least somebody's
telling me what's going on.
- You're way out of line on this one.
- Am I?
I'll leave you two alone to talk.
What did she tell you?
She said you could
lose your job or go to prison.
- How could you hide this?
- I'm trying to protect you.
I wanna know when I'm gonna lose you.
- You are not about to lose me.
- You don't know that!
Did you say anything to her about them?
Don't worry, I kept their secret.
I always will, no matter what happens.
Come on, Darryl. I know
you've had to struggle with this,
with how far you can go
to help the sisters.
- Baby, I'm so past that.
- No, you're not. How can you be?
I used to stay up late worrying
because of all the criminals out there.
That is nothing compared
to what I have to worry about now!
- This is not the time or the place.
- No? When is the time?
When I bring our kids to jail
to see you or to your funeral?
This is not your fight, Darryl.
It's theirs.
That's them, isn't it?
Please don't answer that, Darryl.
I'm begging you.
Come on, Darryl, pick up the phone.
Sheila, baby. They are in trouble.
So are we.
It's our family or theirs.
Darryl's not answering.
How can he not answer?
I'm beginning to think
he can't help anyway.
I have to call the police. I can't
let Karl just get away with this.
I should have been there with her.
I should not have left her alone.
You can't blame yourself. You have
responsibilities you can't ignore.
You said I'm supposed
to sense my charges, and I didn't.
- Tell me what's wrong with me.
- Nothing is wrong with you.
It takes time to form the bond
between charges and Whitelighters.
That's not good enough.
I promised her that
I was gonna be there and I failed!
No, you didn't, sweetie.
I think Zankou wants you
to think you did.
- Zankou?
- It has to be him.
First Phoebe's friend, now her charge.
Can't be a coincidence.
- Karl's working with Zankou?
- I think he is Zankou.
Think about it,
he knew exactly what he was doing.
- He's targeting people in our lives.
- Well, what good would that do?
I don't know. Maybe if he thinks
we're rattled, we'll be vulnerable.
- No one in your life's been targeted.
- Not yet.
That's why you need to get Leo
and the boys to Magic School.
I'm not gonna run and hide
every time a demon attacks.
Leo, this is not just another demon,
and this is not about you hiding.
This is about the safety of our family.
You need to go. Now.
All right. I'll get the boys.
Piper, what about
the other people in your life?
The best way to protect them is
to get Zankou. For that we need Phoebe.
Piper?
- Paige?
- Guess again.
Who are you?
What do you want?
What you took from me! My life!
What's the matter?
Don't you recognise me?
- Inspector Davidson?
- In the flesh.
- What's left of it.
- Oh, no. Not again.
Hold on, hold on.
I wanna talk to you!
- I think you owe me that much.
- Who did this to you? Zankou?
I didn't get a name.
It was obviously someone
who knows you pretty well.
Don't worry, death's not so bad.
- I think you're gonna like it.
- I tried to save you.
- You should've tried harder!
- I couldn't.
- The angel of death was after you.
- At the end.
You're forgetting the months before.
All those times
I asked you to come clean!
- If you told me the truth just once!
- I couldn't. I'm sorry.
Did you go to my funeral?
Did you see my wife, my kids?
They're growing up
without a father because of you.
- I'm so sorry.
- I bet you are, now.
You're gonna be even more sorry
when I'm through with you.
Paige!
Piper! Piper!
He's right behind me.
Get him! Get him!
Phoebe, there's no one there.
He was there. I swear it.
Who?
Inspector Davidson.
Reece Davidson?
He died four years ago.
Getting closer.
I guess I'm gonna have
to kick things up a notch.
It's clear.
- No one dead or undead.
- You sure?
- Pretty sure, unless they're invisible.
- Think they could be invisible?
No. Come on, we gotta find
the Alchemist and, hopefully, Zankou.
Paige!
I was getting Leo and the boys
settled in at Magic School.
I need you to see
if you can find Joanna, quickly.
- I thought I told you, she's dead.
- Yeah, not for long.
- Think Joanna's gonna come back too?
- I'm counting on it.
So, you need to see
if you can sense her.
Anything?
No, but Leo said
our bond hadn't fully formed yet.
Okay, then we're gonna have to
scry for her the old-fashioned way.
Do you think she's
even gonna turn into a zombie?
It fits the pattern.
Trust me, you don't wanna
be surprised once it happens.
Just concentrate, she was your charge.
If anybody can find her, you can.
You know, I'd rather not find her,
considering I'm the reason she's dead.
Join the club.
The faster we find Joanna,
we'll find the Alchemist.
And Zankou, before he kills
anybody else in our lives.
Found her.
Cemetery.
Not good, never good.
Oh, God, that's her.
Miss me?
Looks like it's time for payback!
- Look, we don't wanna hurt you.
- It's a little late for that.
Paige, maybe you
should orb us out of here.
No, the Alchemist
has to be around here.
I see my reputation precedes me.
But if you want to get to me,
you have to get through them.
These are all innocents I've lost.
That's right. You three have done
a hell of a lot of damage in your time.
Seriously, have you
done any good at all?
Phoebe!
Friend, my ass!
Yes.
Yes, my children. Good!
Don't make me do this.
God help us.
No!
- It's okay, you had to.
- We all had to.
You. He told me you wouldn't.
- You couldn't!
- I lied.
- He served his purpose.
- Why would you do that?
What do you have to gain?
You'll soon find out.
Inspector Sheridan. Got a minute?
- First of all, you had no right.
- I had every right.
We're cops. Crimes are being
committed and that gives me the right.
Look, as I said before, you are either
with me on this or you're against me.
I'm taking some vacation time...
to be with my family.
That's curious timing.
I don't like being put in this position.
You put yourself
in this position, Lieutenant.
You're not gonna be able
to take them down. They won't let you.
What, is that supposed
to be some kind of a threat?
It's a friendly warning.
What they're doing,
and what they're all about...
...it's above reproach.
I wouldn't mess with them if I were you.
Have a nice vacation.
Why can't we vanquish Zankou the
same way we vanquished The Source?
He'll be ready for that.
That's why we need something new.
Why did he vanquish
the Alchemist himself?
I don't know,
maybe there's something in the Book.
Where's the Book?
- Zankou.
- Yeah, but how did he get it?
It doesn't matter, he's got it now.
The question is,
what's he gonna do with it?
Now the fun really begins.