Ow!
Are you okay?
Yeah, nothing a little sleep can't fix.
- Let me heal that.
- No.
- Come on!
- I said no.
We have to talk about this.
What we need to do is find
where the next attack is gonna be.
And I think I just did.
Pentagram. Naturally.
What do you want from me?
What do I have to do to prove
that I've changed, that I'm okay?
- Did Phoebe and Paige finish the dye?
- You didn't answer my question!
- You don't have to answer mine?
- What questions?
The question I've been asking you for
days now. What aren't you telling me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, right. Excuse me.
I can't get into this
with you right now, okay?
I've got an invisible demon
killing innocents.
For all we know, they could
be working with the Avatars.
They're not working with the Avatars!
How do you know?
I don't! I don't think they're the
threat everyone thinks they are.
- Why?
- Wouldn't they have attacked?
Sending a demon to possess you
doesn't count?
Still, I think that was their way of
communicating with me... with us.
Why didn't they just
try calling you, Leo?
Are you hiding something?
- No.
- Yes.
Are you sure those are gonna work?
Yeah, as sure as I can be at five a.m.
- Before...
- Know where the demon's gonna attack?
They're making a pentagram.
We need to get there before sunrise.
You can't walk out!
You're right, we should orb.
- Sixteenth and Mission.
- Got it.
Damn it! I said no!
- Ow!
- What happened?
Nothing a little sleep won't fix.
It's fine.
- Didn't you just say that?
- What?
Nothing.
I think I found where
the next demon attack is gonna be.
A pentagram. Naturally.
Did Phoebe and Paige
finish that dye yet?
I don't know.
Excuse me.
Why did you do this?
We didn't, you did.
You need to be more careful
about your new powers, Leo.
Reversing time can be...
...very dangerous.
Our powers are not meant to be
used for personal reasons, Leo.
You know that.
I know. I didn't mean to,
it just happened.
Yes, because you wanted it to happen.
You must be more careful in the future.
Learn to control your emotions.
Control is the first discipline
of an Avatar.
Otherwise our powers
can become dangerous to others...
...as well as to ourselves.
- What do you mean?
Reversing time the way you did
requires great power.
It drains the collective
and it puts us at risk.
And we must remain at full strength
if we are to defeat the forces of evil.
If we are to implement... the change.
I get that.
But Piper's my wife.
She knows something's up.
I can't keep lying to her.
We understand your position, Leo.
But to tell her outright
might cause her to overreact,
and mistakenly view us as a threat.
As might her sisters as well.
They must come to the truth
in their own time and in their own way.
Just as you did.
What if they don't?
What if Piper never
sees the future you promised?
You must help her to see it, Leo.
You must gently guide her to it.
This is the burden that you took
upon becoming an Avatar.
I'm not just an Avatar.
I'm a husband, and I'm a father,
and I joined you to get that back.
And you will get it back, Leo.
You will!
Once we have ended this perpetual
battle between good and evil.
Once we have brought forth...
...a better way.
Okay, it's almost dawn
and nothing's happening.
Can we go home
and go to sleep now?
Just stay focused.
Right, focused.
Maybe you drew the pentagram wrong.
I know how to draw a pentagram,
thank you.
But did you use a felt marker?
'Cause maybe the thickness of the tip
led us astray a couple of blocks, huh?
What's the matter with you guys?
Do you want to save an innocent or not?
Of course we do, it's just...
What? It's just what?
Now you're not telling me something?
- Leo's what.
- What?
We just think that you may have been
so eager to avoid Leo
that you miscalculated the demon attack.
What she said.
All right, fine, I admit it,
I may be avoiding Leo, but that
does not mean I am wrong about this.
Why? Why are you so upset with him?
He's been an angel lately.
Yeah, well that's the problem.
He's been too perfect, even for him.
And I just keep waiting
for the other shoe to drop.
Why don't you just talk to him about it?
I have about a dozen times and he
just thinks I'm crazy or something.
Which is why I am channelling
my frustration into something useful.
I just want this demon to attack soon,
so I can make
my breakfast date with Kyle.
Yeah, see breakfast is not a date.
Dinner's a date.
Lunch is definitely maybe a date.
Breakfast is always just breakfast.
As long as he doesn't talk about
the Avatars, I will consider it a date.
Who is calling you at this hour?
No one.
Avoiding someone?
Is that our innocent?
We're about to find out.
Get the dye.
He'll have to become visible
to attack, let's go.
Who the hell are you?
It won't matter.
Hey!
Kill them.
Throw the dye!
Energy ball!
Heads up, guys.
That didn't go too well. They're a lot
more powerful than I thought.
He's still alive.
Let's get him to Magic School
and find out who they are.
And make more potions.
The innocent has been marked,
the territory staked.
Soon, every mortal within the pentagram
will be ours alone to prey upon.
But the innocent lives.
Our rivals...
Can no more easily kill than we can.
Now that the Charmed Ones
are protecting him.
Then how is the territory staked?
As long as he lives, the Sokols could
still try to claim it for themselves.
And we want them to try.
Or at least make it look like they did.
Witches don't know who we are, right?
Right.
So we put them on our rival's trail
by making them think
the Sokols attacked them.
Excuse me, there you are.
Thank you.
So, this place is great.
Yeah? Are you sure?
I mean you do like the place?
Well, I've never had breakfast here,
but I'm sure it's terrific.
I guess I should have
asked you out to dinner.
It's fine, I'm up this early anyway.
I figured since we got the first kiss
out of the way and everything.
Out of the way?
Sorry.
I didn't mean that. I did not mean that.
I just, you know, I'm rusty.
All Avatars, all the time?
Yeah, something like that.
I've been chasing them for so long.
It hasn't left much time
for a social life.
Then maybe it's time you start
changing that, don't you think?
Yes, I think.
It's just that they're so close, Paige.
I mean I know it, I can feel...
But... you promised.
You're right. You're right, that's it.
No more Avatar talk, I swear.
Good. It's a good start.
What?
It's... it's vibrating, it just
tickles a little bit, that's all.
It's off. I promise.
No more distractions.
That's my emergency line,
I gotta take this. Sorry.
Brody.
What?
As soon as you get
those numbers, call me.
Intel just detected another
unusual power spike in the area.
This could mean
some serious Avatar activity!
You know what this means?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
It means that you eat alone.
I'm sorry.
Paige, come on.
Idiot.
The good thing about getting up
so early is how much you can get done.
Already today, I've made demon dye,
I've saved an innocent,
I e-mailed in my column,
plucked my eyebrows.
If it wasn't for sleep deprivation,
I would be okay.
What about the demons?
I couldn't find anything in the Book
to help identify them.
I did get to read up
on the family history.
Did you know that Beatrice Warren
only had one leg?
You're making spaghetti sauce?
No, that's demon blood.
I got it from the salvage yard.
I was gonna use it to scry for them
after I make the vanquishing potion.
Wow, jacklebeet.
So exactly which state
are you trying to blow off the map?
I don't want to take any chances.
We need two kitchens.
Do you know where the beetle toe is?
I think it's in the attic.
When you're avoiding something,
you really do a number.
I seem to remember someone
doing some avoiding a little while back.
Yeah, if you're talking about Leslie,
you're absolutely right.
But my big sister gave me some advice
that I'm gonna give back to you.
Stop dodging. Just talk to Leo.
On the subject of dodging,
who called this morning?
Yeah, your
"I'm covering something" look
hasn't worked since the 6th grade,
so spill.
Okay. But you can't tell Paige.
I don't want her to get paranoid.
Why would she get paranoid?
Darryl thinks Brody had something
to do with Sheridan's disappearance.
That's why I'm keeping it low key.
Darryl's on his way over. We're
gonna talk while Paige is on her date.
He's talking to us again?
Kinda. Baby steps.
Hi.
I'll be in the attic.
Well, go talk to her, would you!
Hurry up, go!
- Hey.
Is this a good time to talk?
Well, actually yeah,
Paige is out on a date.
- What did you find out?
- Nothing.
Nothing? Okay, well,
nothing is good, right?
No. I mean I can't find anything.
It's like Sheridan's disappeared
off the face of the earth.
What are you saying?
I think that maybe Brody did something
to make Sheridan disappear.
Something bad maybe.
No, I don't believe that.
You don't want to believe that.
Brody may have saved your butts,
I get that.
But if he did something to hurt
Sheridan... wrong is wrong.
Okay, well maybe I can get
a premonition and see where she is.
No. No magic.
I've done some soul-searching.
I want to help again,
but I don't want to go there any more.
Darryl, you gotta get over this.
I mean really,
one bad experience with magic
can't outweigh six years of good,
can it?
Hey.
Hi, Paige.
Hey, Darryl.
- I thought you were on your date.
- Yeah, so did I.
Look, tell Piper I said hello, okay?
Take care.
We're friends again?
Yeah. Weird.
Bygones.
Leo, please,
this is not the time or place.
I just want my family back, Piper.
I just want you back.
- I don't want to talk about this now.
- Why not?
This is a little dicey here.
- That's why we need to talk.
- No, not that, this.
If I make one mistake,
I can blow up the entire house.
Okay, so this is a bad time.
I just wish you'd trust me.
Yeah, well maybe you should
try telling me the truth.
This is so frustrating.
This can't keep happening, Leo.
We've had this conversation!
I can't help it,
I can't keep doing this.
You must keep up pretenses,
there's no other way.
There is another way.
I could tell her the truth.
Leo.
I know Piper. She doesn't want
to live like this any more than I do.
She hates hunting demons all the time.
She wants nothing but the best
for herself, her family, for all of us.
She can handle the truth,
I know she can.
But if she can't,
if she's not open to our way...
...it would risk everything we hope
to achieve, everything we covet.
And cause her to lose perspective
in the process.
Ignore what shouldn't be ignored.
Which would put her at risk as well.
There's too much at stake, Leo.
She can handle it.
He needs to see for himself.
But what of the risk?
It's no greater than that of him
tapping into the collective...
without intending to.
Very well.
But if anything goes wrong,
everything may be lost.
Our powers are not inexhaustible.
What is the matter?
I... I need to tell you something.
I'm listening.
Well, the reason I know the demons
aren't working with the Avatars...
...is because I'm an Avatar.
What?
Oh my God!
Piper!
No! You stay away from me!
What happened?
- Let me help.
- Don't!
Piper, please!
Could someone please
tell us what happened?
The potion blew up and...
Leo's an Avatar.
- What?
Oh, you know, the gathering storm,
looming threat, that would be Leo.
We're trying to save the world
from itself.
Wait.
Did he just say we?
I think he just said we.
They said you had to come to it
on your own, I said you could handle it.
That you're what everybody's
afraid of? Even the Elders?
They're afraid because
they don't understand.
The Avatars are beyond good and evil,
everything we've been searching for.
- Okay, he's cracked.
- Absolutely.
I have never been more clear. Piper,
I beg you not to be closed to this.
It's everything we've been
searching for, I promise.
I think you need to take
the boys to Magic School.
- But...
- I need time to think about this.
Are you sure you can trust him?
I can trust my husband
with our children, now please go.
Do you think he's telling the truth?
It would be a really stupid lie
if he wasn't, don't you think?
Sorry.
It's okay.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know, but we have
a demon to vanquish first,
and an innocent to protect, so...
Yeah, but...
Just re-make the potion for me
and I'll go get cleaned up and...
...be careful of the beetle toe.
Okay, we have bigger things
to worry about than potions.
I agree. We have to save Leo.
Then we're gonna have
to ask for Kyle's help.
Now what?
- Put them on.
- Why?
We're going to attack
the Charmed Ones next.
Malvoc, that's suicide.
Only if we die.
But I only plan to fight long enough
for them to identify us... as Sokols.
Then our enemies
become their enemies.
They'll vanquish them. Others
will challenge us for the territory.
They won't be able to
after we kill the innocent.
Those ancient rules are etched in...
...brimstone.
After, they'll think the threat
to the innocent is passed.
And then return him.
We'll need more of these.
Something's happened, Leo.
I have to get back to Piper.
We've detected a power surge,
a time shift.
That could only mean one thing.
The Avatars are making their move.
How do you know it's them?
No demon has this kind of power,
not since the Source.
So, what do you want from me?
We want you to alert the Charmed Ones.
We expect that the Avatars
will come after them first.
What is it?
- I don't know how much we know.
- We know they're a threat.
- Because they have power?
- Yes.
The kind of power that in the wrong
hands could be a danger to us.
Okay, so are we a threat?
I'm sorry.
Elders, I mean we have a great power.
But we're only a threat to demons.
And your point is?
We don't know enough about them
to fear them.
How do we know
they're not benevolent?
I mean, who are we to judge them?
If they were,
they wouldn't lurk insidiously,
they would show themselves.
This is no time to lose your faith
in all that we're about, Leo,
despite all that's happened in the past.
We need you on our side.
Have you seen Phoebe and Paige?
Aren't they upstairs making potions?
No. How are the boys?
They're fine.
Miss Donovan's with 'em.
And the innocent?
Sleeping. Still under
the effects of the potions.
How are you?
- How am I?
- I mean with all this.
I don't know. I have questions.
Well, you can ask me.
I can answer them now.
What are they exactly?
Or should I say what are you exactly?
I'm the same man you married, Piper.
Someone who wants nothing
but the best for his family.
And the Avatars
are gonna give us that how?
By using their powers, our powers,
to change what has always been,
to re-make what is.
That sounds like a lot of crap.
I know it does, but it's not.
For all we know, they're like
everything else we're fighting.
They want to end everything we're
fighting against, once and for all.
That's impossible.
I know, I used to think it was too.
Now I know it's not. They want
to make the world better.
Those floating heads that
tormented you made your life better?
That was just a way to get my attention.
Make me open to a new idea.
Leo.
Piper, think about it.
A demon-free world.
It's everything we've
always dreamed about.
We should consider that after
everything we've been through?
It's just a graze.
They really want that innocent.
I just wish I knew why.
There'll be more of them.
Well, at least we have a way
to find 'em now.
I don't mean just them, Piper.
I mean demons.
They'll keep coming back,
like they always have,
unless we let the Avatars
stop 'em, forever.
Oh, Paige! I was...
Hey.
Okay. I'm sorry about breakfast.
I didn't handle it well.
And look,
I'm obsessed about the Avatars, I know.
That's not it, it's just...
It's not gonna happen again.
All right? I promise.
Leo's an Avatar!
He told us this morning.
What? How?
We don't know. He didn't say.
He dropped the bomb on us this morning.
We don't know exactly what it means.
Where are you going?
Parking sucks in this city.
How's he taking it?
- Hello?
- Hey, it's Darryl.
I'm stumped.
Maybe you could use hocus pocus to
find out what Brody did with Sheridan.
Okay, but now's not a good time.
So can I call you back in a little bit?
All right, bye.
- What are you looking for?
- This.
- Does he know where the others are?
- Who?
The other Avatars!
No, he didn't say. Why?
What is that?
That's a potion.
For what?
For killing Avatars.
Where is he?
- Kyle, would you stop please?
- We're not gonna let you kill Leo.
You don't understand.
He's an Avatar now.
No, he's actually our brother in law.
How can you be so sure
the potion's gonna work?
They killed my parents over it.
One potion. You cannot
get even with them all.
The hell I can't. Their powers
are all tied together.
You kill one of them,
it weakens them all.
This is ridiculous!
Leo did not kill your parents!
If he's one, he did.
He just became one of them.
We didn't come to you
so you could kill Leo.
We came to you
to help us get rid of them.
This is the only way
to get rid of them.
When my parents uncovered this,
they didn't discover a potion,
they discovered a battle that happened
5000 years ago over our future.
They fought the Avatars then
and we gotta fight 'em now.
What happened in here?
- Piper!
- Upstairs!
At least we know she's okay.
Looks like the demons didn't wait for
us to go after them, they came first.
How do you know
the Avatars didn't do it?
He'll kill you first, you won't
get that bottle out of your hand.
We'll see.
I get that this is about your parents.
Yes, it is about my parents.
No, you don't get it.
The hell I don't.
My parents were killed too, remember?
Paige, my parents were murdered.
Look, Leo is not the bad guy here.
For all we know, he was brainwashed
or possessed or something.
Just... please.
Give us a minute, just wait down here.
Please?
Just don't let him go, all right?
I spent 20 years looking for the
Avatars, I'm not about to lose 'em now.
Piper, what happened?
Are you okay?
No thanks to you.
What is that supposed to mean?
It would have been nice
to have a vanquishing potion
when we were ambushed, a potion that
you were supposed to make, by the way.
- Oops.
- Yeah, oops. Where the hell were you?
I was at Kyle's.
- What were you doing there?
- Trying to save you.
Trying to save me? I don't need saving,
I know what I'm doing.
Kyle's parents were killed
by the Avatars?
It goes against everything
they believe in.
You have to come up with a better
argument than that if you go downstairs.
Why is that?
He's downstairs?
- Why is he downstairs?
- You don't wanna know.
He thinks you're a threat, Leo,
to all of us.
- Well, he's wrong.
- How do you know?
Because! Look, I know
this is a shock to everyone,
but he didn't have to tell us the truth,
he wouldn't have if it was a bad thing.
Piper, everything points to them
being bad. Even the Elders think so.
Because they don't understand.
We're just supposed
to take your word for it?
How do we know
you're not possessed right now?
Come on.
No, Leo, I'm serious!
How do we know?
They haven't threatened
anything we believe in.
It's all good.
We at least need to think about it.
Since when did you jump
on his Avatar train?
When I started thinking
about my kids,
fighting battles we've
been fighting our entire lives.
That's what we were born to do.
That does not mean
we have to die doing it.
You should talk to Kyle,
hear his side of the story.
I don't need to,
I need to vanquish demons again!
Now what?
How is it you're the only one
who still lives?
I wasn't with them. I swear!
I don't know what happened to them!
Something is not right!
Why would Malvoc attack only
to retreat? How would that help him?
Lose something?
What was that?
All part of the package.
That was a lot of power.
Yeah, but it's used wisely.
See, the Avatars could destroy us
or force us to change. But they don't.
Isn't that enough reason to trust them?
How could you let him go?
How could you let the Avatar go?
Okay, he's still Leo. So would you stop
referring to him as the Avatar, please?
We gotta fix this and we gotta
fix it fast. Now where did he go?
He orbed out with Piper.
How do you know
he didn't go to alert the others?
- He didn't.
- How do you know?
How can you be so sure?
I cannot believe you let him get away!
Something is wrong,
he's not acting like himself.
Orb that potion away from him
before he does something stupid.
- What if he flipped out?
- I think he already has flipped out...
What did you do?
It's just a tranq. She'll be fine.
What are you doing?
I'm killing an Avatar.
And nobody's gonna stop me.
He should wake up
in a couple of minutes.
Thanks, Piper.
For?
For believing in me.
I always have.
I always will, it's the only way.
I know.
Thanks for helping.
What happened?
We vanquished them.
- No, we didn't.
- Yeah, we did.
We vanquished the wrong ones,
he had different markings.
What do you mean?
We were tricked.
We wouldn't have been
if Paige and Phoebe
weren't off chasing Avatars
instead of helping me!
Paige!
She's fine.
You and I are gonna have a little chat.
All right, let's just take a deep breath
here, we can talk this out.
Leo.
I don't want to hurt her
but I will if I have to.
Your kind is responsible
for a nightmare that won't go away.
For all those nights,
waking up in a sweat,
begging that the flashbacks
were just a dream.
Kyle, please.
It's not a dream though, is it?
You Avatars are as real as the air that
we breathe and just as vacant!
My parents were murdered by them.
So if I were you Leo,
I'd do what I say.
The Avatars couldn't
have killed your parents.
They believe in peace.
I'll give you three seconds
to summon one of your buddies,
so I can kill him.
If you don't, I'm gonna kill you.
- I can't do that.
- One...
- Avatars aren't the enemy.
- Two...
- Leo.
- Three!
No!
Oh! Leo?
Piper, it wasn't supposed
to happen like this.
No, it's okay. It's okay.
Oh, God! Not now! Please!
Leo, Leo, come on!
How did this happen?
The potion is real, Leo.
It kills Avatars.
The collective weakens
with every last breath you take.
We told you, the truth must come
to them in their own time, not yours.
But Piper, she...
Understood, yes.
But the others were not able to.
And so we became the enemy,
out of fear, and ignorance.
And an innocent was lost because of it.
Everything was lost.
I was trying to make things right
with Piper.
Of course.
But you've learned
and now you can save yourself.
You have it in you to rewind time
to just before you told Piper the truth.
If you hurry.
If we all hurry.
It worked.
Yes.
But at a price.
All that's happened has
taken a great toll on our power.
As it is, we may not have
enough to implement our plan.
To rid the world of demons, to end
the duality requires all that we had.
Won't the sister's powers
add to the collective?
Yes. But it may not be enough.
You must not try this ever again, Leo.
You can never tell Piper about us.
Not until she's truly ready.
Leo, this is not
the time or place, okay?
I don't want to get into this now.
This is a little dicey.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
You're distracted.
Please, don't tell me how to demon hunt.
I'm not. I didn't mean to. But just
focus on getting the demons.
Not too much beetle toe.
- You don't want to blow up the place.
- No.
Why are you being so nice
all of a sudden?
I don't know.
I guess I just realise
I can't force things on you.
If you're gonna trust me, you're
gonna come to it in your own time.
There may be hope for you yet.
Bottle up the potions, I think I know
where the demons are gonna attack next.
Now!
That was easy.
Wait.
Hi.
All right, now all we have to do
is get rid of the other gang
and we can bring the innocent back.
All right, I give up.
How did you figure all this out?
You don't want to know.
Believe me.
What?
Nothing.
Just glad you gave me
another shot, that's all.
You didn't think I would?
Well, I didn't hear from you
after I botched breakfast.
Well, breakfast isn't
really a date anyway, right?
A dinner, much better.
And dessert?
Dessert too. Dessert is good.
Now Agent Brody,
you are a damn fine cook.
Any other secrets
I should know about you?
Other than my crazed obsession
with Avatars...
Nah, you're not so crazed.
No? Wait till I meet one.
Forget that.
Let's... rewind,
and you can ask me
the secrets question again, okay?
Do you...
...Kyle Brody, have any secrets?
No.
Are they asleep?
Yeah. Finally.
Piper?
I know you think there's something
I haven't been telling you.
Leo, not now.
Just hear me out.
There is something I'm not telling you
but not because I don't want to.
It's because I can't.
What do you mean you can't?
The Elders won't let you?
Oh, I can't even tell you that.
I can tell you
you're gonna find out soon.
- And you're gonna be okay with it.
- Oh yeah? How do you know?
I know you.