Any idea what this meeting's all about?
- Probably to do with the kids.
- Why, did something happen?
I'm sure they've gotten kidnapped
by the latest demon or something.
Paige, that is so not funny.
You get so emotional when you're PMS.
- Yeah, and you get mean.
- I do not get mean!
I'm above it all. Nothing happens to me.
Alrighty, then...
Right, nothing happens to you,
you're above it all.
Fine, so I get a little jumpy.
- I get a little pissy, so watch it.
- We know.
Good news is,
we're over it at the same time.
As long as we don't
kill each other in the process.
Which brings me
to what we need to talk about.
That sounds serious.
That calls for ice cream
with three spoons.
Personal gain!
I know, but screw it, it's too good.
Anyway, I've been wanting
to tell you guys something for a while,
- I just didn't know how to say it.
- God, are you pregnant again?
No, this is not a good thing.
Do you guys remember Zola,
the Elder who disappeared?
- Yeah.
- Well, he didn't disappear.
He was killed.
Leo killed him.
Leo killed him?
It was an accident, he didn't mean to.
- I mean, he was tricked.
- You might want to tell that to Zola.
Hey, hey. What was that?
I was angry.
Yeah, but you blew it up
without even looking at it.
Our emotions are tied to our powers.
Apparently, I'm feeling a little weird.
Okay, but...
I was just looking for
a little understanding, that's all.
I know, we're sorry. It's just,
we're not fans of the Elders now.
It's not like Leo could hurt anybody.
We don't believe he could do that.
The Elders don't think that way.
If they prove he did,
they won't think he did by accident.
Sorry to interrupt. I have to tell you
something you're not gonna like.
Did you kill anybody else?
I'm sorry.
- You told them?
- I had to, it affects them too.
More than you know. They wanna
assign you a new Whitelighter.
- What?
- They're getting suspicious.
They wanna make sure you're protected.
- Protected from what? You?
- They're out of their minds.
- He's gonna be here tomorrow.
- I hope I don't blow him up.
- You can't blow up a Whitelighter.
- Why? She blows you up all the time.
We have enough people orbing in and out
on a daily basis. We don't need another.
Got it.
That was a great toaster.
You probably shouldn't
be doing that out in the open.
Please, nobody's here. It's midnight.
Besides, I would have sensed
if anybody was coming.
- You didn't sense me.
- You're an Elder.
Or, at least, you used to be.
I'm just here to tell you
that maybe you don't want
to go by the sisters' house tomorrow.
- Just a friendly warning.
- Oh, yeah?
Did you warn Zola too,
before something happened to him?
See, the word's out.
Nobody knows
which side you're on anymore.
Which is precisely why
I am going to the sisters'.
It's a dream job for any Whitelighter.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to prepare myself.
Leo?
Oh, no! Oh, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no!
That's the second batch!
Would you turn that thing off?
I'll get the ladder.
Forget it!
- Okay, what is going on with you guys?
- Witches with PMS, look out!
Great. Now, not only am I exhausted,
but I'm starving.
I see your exhausted and your starving
and I raise you bloated.
Oh, no! No, that is so sad!
No weeping, you promised.
Have you guys seen
the new Whitelighter yet?
- No, you probably scared him off.
- No, that's the thing, I didn't.
He should've been here by now.
I'll be back.
Better not be with that Whitelighter.
Anyone else have weird dreams?
- No, you?
- Yeah, they were violent and painful.
- Hey, wanna go somewhere with me?
- Where?
I have to go over to Agent Brody's
place and try to snoop around.
Find out if he's a demon or not.
You think he's a demon?
- No, I don't. But Piper does.
- I don't know what he is.
More importantly,
we need to find out what he wants.
We have enough to worry about
without having to worry about him.
Can you go with Miss Jumpy, make sure
she doesn't orb out in front of him,
in case he is a Fed and nothing else?
- I can control myself.
- I can't go. I have to go to work.
I thought you weren't
going for a couple of days.
I'm not, but that's
when Les leaves and I...
I have this feeling he's pulling away.
Maybe he's pulling away from you
because he's, I don't know, leaving?
That might be true.
Okay, would you just
please be careful around Brody,
and we'll talk about
Leo moving in when I get back.
Odin?
- Where have you been?
- With the girls.
Why? What happened?
- What's wrong with him?
- You don't know?
No, I don't know.
- Think I did this?
- We don't know.
He was to report to the Charmed Ones
and you didn't want him to.
That makes me guilty? How do
you know a Darklighter didn't do this?
Does it look like a Darklighter
did that? You were the last to see him,
just like you were the last to see Zola.
- It wasn't me.
- No?
Then who was it?
Have a nice nap. Sweet dreams.
- Hey, can we talk to you for a sec?
- What about?
Well, it's about Leo.
You know, moving back in.
- Is there a problem?
- You know, we love... love Leo. But...
- But?
- You sure this is a good time for this?
I mean, like you said,
it's really crazy. So much is going on.
- Yeah, Zola, the Elders...
- Agent Brody.
And... he does hear voices.
We all hear voices sometimes.
We might hear voices, but we don't
see floating heads going with them.
All the more reason he should
be here, where he is safe.
- What about the boys?
- What?
Aren't you afraid they'll be in danger?
From who, Leo? That's ridiculous.
- No, whoever's after Leo.
- Have you thought it through?
Look, I just want my family back,
isn't that enough?
What is going on with our powers lately?
I don't know,
but it's getting awfully expensive.
- What happened?
- Good question.
I'll be with Leslie, we'll talk about
what we were talking about later.
- Nothing to talk about.
- Want me to cast a spell to clean?
No more magic unless we have to.
We might have to.
I found out why the Whitelighter
didn't show. He was attacked.
- By a Darklighter?
- No, by me.
- That's what the Elders think.
- You've gotta be kidding.
- I was the last one to see him.
- Well, obviously not.
- Maybe the Elders are setting you up.
- Piper...
What? They haven't been
your greatest allies lately.
I'm concerned that it
has to do with you guys.
I mean, he was gonna come here
and be your Whitelighter, your guide.
Maybe somebody doesn't want that.
- I'll check the Book of Shadows.
- I'll do it. Find out about Brody.
He could have something to do with this.
Listen, I'm sorry
for getting you into all this.
It's not your fault. Let's go prove it.
Since when do you read horoscopes?
Since I decided to make
Conflicted in Castro my last letter.
She doesn't know
if she should stay with someone.
Worries that their signs
might not be compatible.
- I didn't know you believed in that.
- Well, I don't, but I know you do.
I'm just channelling the boss here.
Let me see.
"Expect the unexpected when the
mystical second blue moon of the year
rises over the next three nights, and
Mars and Aries... Romance can flourish."
- Sounds promising.
- Yeah, for her maybe.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
Les, something's wrong.
I know it is.
I've been feeling it the last few days.
- I've been feeling the same from you.
- Do you wanna talk about it?
What's there to talk about? I'm moving,
you're back and that's it, isn't it?
- It doesn't have to be.
- Doesn't it?
What are we gonna do,
fly back and forth and see each other?
- You're only moving to LA.
- After that I'm moving to Philly.
- We'll work it out.
- We barely see each other.
- How're we gonna do it long-distance?
- We see each other.
Only when you don't bail at
the last minute. Which you do, admit it.
- Yeah...
- Editorial is waiting on your copy.
All right, all right.
I... I gotta do this.
Okay, so when do you wanna talk?
I don't know.
How about tonight at dinner?
I can't do it tonight.
But I can do breakfast tomorrow,
and then maybe dinner?
And then maybe breakfast again?
I'll hold you to it.
Definitely a bachelor.
Hey!
Guess the secret's out.
- Can you do that whenever you want to?
- And apparently when I don't want.
Piper's gonna kill me.
- I won't tell her.
- Thank you.
Not as long as you tell me
why you broke into my apartment.
Blackmailing.
I knew there'd be something.
Let me guess.
You don't believe I'm a federal agent.
You came here to find out
if I'm a demon or something, right?
Maybe.
Best way to find out
is to test my blood, isn't it?
Funny, for a guy
who claims he's not a demon,
- you sure do know a lot about them.
- No, I know a lot about witches.
I know a lot about you.
Go ahead, forensic kit's right there.
I've got nothing to hide.
- May I?
- You may.
- If that's O positive, you owe me.
- I don't owe you anything.
I don't have much time Paige.
None of us do.
If I'm right, there's a threat coming.
A power unlike anything you've seen.
- You're gonna need my help to stop it.
- How do I know you're not the threat?
I don't wanna hurt you.
- I give up.
- We've gotta be missing something.
Only thing that attacks
a Whitelighter is a Darklighter.
He wasn't shot with poison,
he was mauled.
- What do you mean, like, by an animal?
- I don't know.
Whatever it was,
it's gotta be supernatural.
Otherwise, he would've orbed out.
There's gotta be more than one,
he was so messed up.
- So we'll set a trap.
- A trap?
- With crystals, we've done it before.
- What'll you use to lure the demons?
Whitelighter, if they're after that.
- Elders'll never go for it.
- Nobody's gonna get hurt.
We'll set the trap for whoever
or whatever it is before they attack.
If we don't find out who's doing this,
they're gonna keep blaming you.
This could exonerate you for everything.
I'll get the boys,
you should take them to Magic School.
You can't be saved.
You're a danger to them all.
Well, that oughta do it.
That ought to do what?
Burn down the house?
Remember, we don't know
what we're up against.
So I just thought
I'd throw in the works.
You're not ready yet? You're still
working on the vanquishing potion?
- I'm refining it.
- You called me down here an hour ago!
- We don't know when they'll attack.
- You mean maul me.
You know, for a Whitelighter,
you're really wimpy.
- That's why they sent him.
- I heard that.
Relax, will you, please?
We're not gonna let anybody hurt you.
Hey, where's Leo?
At Magic School so he
has an alibi when they attack.
When they attack,
all we do is trigger the crystals?
Theoretically,
but that's why we have backup.
- Did you test Brody's blood yet?
- Yeah, he's not a demon.
That makes him tomorrow's problem.
- How's it going in here?
- The sitting duck is still sitting.
- Grumpy. Very grumpy.
- Remember, it's almost midnight.
- That's when things get exciting.
- Especially with a blue moon rising.
Wait a second.
That reminds me
of something I read in the Book
about how if there are
two blue moons in one year,
that seems
to only happen every 50 years.
That doesn't bode well.
Pretty...
What the hell?
- Wake up. Wake up, wake up!
- Where are the boys?
- The boys are fine, we're not!
- Keep it down.
- Hey!
- Hey, yourself! Look!
Oh, my God! Oh, God!
- What happened?
- We're what happened to him.
- What are you talking about?
- We're in the cage.
I think we trapped ourselves.
- No, we didn't. Did we?
- I think that dream I had was real.
So, you're saying
that we did this to him?
- You have a better explanation?
- That is crazy.
As you were saying?
Okay, what does this mean?
We're demons?
- No, we didn't turn into demons.
- We turned into monsters.
We're testy, but that's ridiculous.
It can't be that.
It's gotta be something else.
- The blue moon?
- We gotta get out, this is crazy.
Paige, try to orb
one of these crystals away.
Crystal!
Blue moon?
Bright side,
the Elders can't blame Leo any more.
No, now they can blame us.
Take him to Magic School
and find someone to heal him.
How do I explain that?
Tell them that we got knocked out.
Whatever you do, stay calm and don't
turn into anything in front of them.
Gotta find a way
to stop this from happening.
I can't. I have to go
meet Leslie for breakfast.
- Come on!
- I know, but if I don't show up again,
he's never gonna talk
to me again. Gotta go.
Better be home before the moon rises.
And stay away from red meat.
I thought you were
supposed to trap them?
- It kinda caught us by surprise.
- You see what they look like? Demons?
It was night.
We have to find who did this
and vanquish them before they attack.
I'm ordering a lockdown
until we catch these beasts.
"Beasts". That's a harsh word,
don't you think?
At least you've been exonerated.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
So am I.
We have a lot of healing to do,
Leo, I admit.
Forgiveness must prevail
if we're to work together.
Now, this New Power that we're sensing,
it is coming closer
and it's more threatening.
- Okay, New Power. What New Power?
- We don't know exactly.
But if it's responsible for this attack,
Elders could be next.
Help us, Leo.
- Okay, I have to find Agent Brody.
- Why?
He talked about that New Power thing.
He must know something about it.
Be careful. Watch out for those beasts.
- About those beasts... That would be us.
- What are you talking about?
Those funky powers,
the sharp fangs, the claws.
We're the ones attacking Whitelighters.
Something is transforming us.
It may not be
this blue moon thing, after all.
I have to go.
Leslie! Hi! I am so sorry.
I'm here now. Things got
a little wild back at the house.
- Phoebe, it's a quarter to ten!
- I know, and I would have called, but...
Leslie, please... I said I was sorry!
I know you are. You always are.
Don't be mad at me.
- Come on, I really wanted to be here.
- Let me guess, something came up?
- Yes.
- You can't tell me, you never can.
- Not because I don't want to...
- It's complicated. I know.
Would you stop
finishing my sentences, please?
Well, why not?
They all end the same way!
Look... I'm sorry, it's just...
I'm frustrated.
I didn't think
I was gonna like you this much.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
I gotta go to work.
Wouldn't wanna be late on my last day.
Paige.
Since when do you use doors?
Look, I need to talk to you.
Great, don't tell me I didn't check out.
What? No, you checked out.
You knew you would.
I need to talk to you about the New
Power thing you were telling me about.
- Did something happen?
- I'm not sure.
Let's just say that you aren't
the only one who's concerned.
- Did you see? Did they attack?
- Just curious,
how do you even know
about them anyway?
- That's a... That's a long story.
- Why not give me the short version?
Look, you said you
wanted my help, didn't you?
No, I said that you would need mine.
Please, will you
just tell me what you know?
I just know they're coming.
That's why I'm here. I... I don't know.
Everything seems
to fit a certain pattern.
Pattern? What pattern?
All I know is that they come from
ancient times, when they were in power.
I'm not sure why, but something
happened and they went away.
Now they're trying to come back.
They've been trying for some time.
And to do that, they need power.
And that's the pattern.
I mean, they're always after it.
It won't be long
before they come after yours.
I think they may have already tried.
You can't let them.
You gotta do everything
you can to stop them, otherwise...
- Otherwise what?
- They're gonna kill you.
Just like they killed my parents.
I was... five when it happened.
No one knew who did it.
That's why I became a cop. To find out.
I never would've imagined that it
would've brought me to here, but it has.
I am not leaving this city
until I prove it.
You're certain he's the most powerful?
- He's their leader.
- Was their leader.
You're not going anywhere.
Why are you doing this? Who are you?
- I think a direct approach is best.
- We tried that, it's not working.
Leo's being drawn
back to his family, back to good.
But he's not there yet.
We must drive him away,
make them afraid of him,
if we're to succeed.
And you're going
to help us do exactly that.
This one should work
if the beasts are possessing us.
This'll work if the last one doesn't.
It should knock out about ten of 'em.
This one... Well, this one,
only use if you really, really have to.
Why, what is it?
A little bit of everything,
just in case.
- Piper, I'm not using these on you.
- You might have to.
It's the last night of a blue moon.
All we have to do
is wait until it passes.
Unless it's not
the blue moon that's doing this.
- Paige said that...
- The New Power, I know.
If it's after power, why do all this?
- It doesn't make sense.
- Better safe than sorry.
Paige and Phoebe
are coming home in a couple of minutes.
- We need the cage ready.
- I know you're scared.
I'm not scared. I'm worried
we're gonna kill somebody.
You're not gonna kill anybody.
I promise.
You saved me, now let me save you.
Then maybe... it'll be time
for me to move back in again.
It already is.
Grab those.
- Who are you?
- Actually, I'm about to be you.
- Are you coming?
- I'll be right there.
Do you think we should
put some snacks in the cage?
- Like what, a wildebeest?
- Please don't say "beast".
We don't know how long we're
gonna be in here. What if I get hungry?
We'll have Leo throw us
a Whitelighter, don't worry about it.
Well, I do worry about it.
I just don't like
not knowing what's going on.
Leo thinks it's the blue moon.
All we have to do
is make it till morning
without eating anyone,
and we'll be fine.
What if Leo's wrong? I mean,
it's not like he's been himself lately.
- We've been through this.
- No, not enough.
Look, trust me, we don't
have to worry about him any more.
Talking about me?
- Where are the potions?
- Potions?
I think I left them in the kitchen.
What was that?
What was what?
Okay, I'll get them from the kitchen.
Keep your eye on us after we transform
and make sure we don't
move any of the crystals.
Oh, no. I don't want Leo here,
in case we attack him.
- Who could that be?
- Oh, I think I know.
- I'll take care of it.
- You'd better hurry.
Why would you attack me?
Technically, you're still an Elder.
We feel the same way about Elders
as we do Whitelighters, so...
...just to be safe.
- So, you'd view me as a threat?
Probably.
- Hi!
- Leslie, hey.
- Let me guess, bad time?
- Actually...
- I just wanted to apologise.
- For what?
Well, for the way I acted earlier.
I was... I was just so...
- Yeah, really upset, I know.
- Now who's finishing whose sentences?
- Yeah...
- I didn't wanna leave it like that,
- that's all.
- And I don't either.
Is it possible
I could call you tomorrow?
We're running out of tomorrows.
Yeah, I know. I'm gonna call you
tomorrow, I promise. Okay.
Take care.
- Leo, what are you doing?
- Television!
- Piper, are you okay?
- No.
Still think Leo's fine?
That wasn't Leo.
He was possessed or something.
- Again? Well, it seems to happen a lot.
- And if it did happen again,
it can't be connected
to the blue moon, it's not up yet.
Maybe it's the New Power thing.
- Maybe that's who's setting Leo up.
- But why? For what?
Well, if Agent Brody's right,
for power.
- Okay, now what?
- Throw the potion!
Hey, over here!
Piper!
You have betrayed us! Again!
What're you doing?
- I'm warning you! Stay out of this!
- Oh, no, Piper! Do not...
You'll be stopped!
- What happened?
- You attacked us.
Really? How come
I'm the one with the headache?
We were forced to defend ourselves.
- Where's Leo?
- I sent him away.
- Away where?
- That's none of your concern now.
You attempted to save him,
you failed, that's that.
The hell it is!
He tried to kill two more Elders!
No, he was possessed,
you just didn't see it.
What I saw was something
I never would've imagined.
The Charmed Ones turning into demons.
No, that wasn't demonic, that was...
...you know, that time of month.
- No, it was a blue moon.
We didn't have a choice,
we can't control it.
I'm keeping you
till we figure what to do with you.
What to do with us?
Let us go so we can
- find out who the demon is.
- Out of the question.
You won't be finding out
about that New Power.
Only they could've
sent the demon after Leo.
You said yourself they
may be coming after the Elders.
But what if you turn back into?
That was just the blue moon.
It won't happen for 50 years.
By that time we'll just be a menace to
our rest home. So I think you're safe.
Very well. See what you can find out.
- Nope, not without Leo first.
- He can't be trusted.
He wouldn't be
vulnerable to possession if...
You can give us Leo,
or you can find your own
damn connection to the New Power.
What's going on?
You're about to be exonerated, again.
Book of Shadows.
What else do you want from me?
I did what you asked.
You gotta protect me. They'll find me!
We already have.
Who were you talking to?
What happened?
Did you just freeze me?
She asked you a question.
- Would you rather I blew you up?
- Wait, don't.
- If I tell you, they'll kill me.
- If you don't tell us, we'll kill you.
You may want to pick your poison.
They're more powerful
than anything you've seen.
Who is?
No!
Well, I guess Leo
wasn't seeing things after all.
Can we get out of here now, please?
Whoever you are,
stay away from my husband.
Brody.
Paige, hey. I was getting worried.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I wanted to call you,
to let you know I was okay.
I'm glad you did.
So, what happened?
This New Power wasn't really after you?
No, it was actually...
...after something else.
I mean that's... That's good, obviously.
I was just hoping to, you know,
get a lead out of this, that's all.
If it makes you feel any better,
they were after my brother-in-law.
- Brother-in-law?
- Yeah, well, not directly.
They actually used
a demon to get to him.
A demon?
He's fine now, we dispossessed him.
- Wait, you did what?
- Well, we got rid of the demon.
We get possessed all the time,
it's no big deal.
Hello?
Yeah, sorry. I guess
I'm just a little new at this stuff.
I thought you said
you knew about demons?
No, I said I knew a lot about witches.
The rest are just... theories.
That is, until I met you.
Well, be careful what you wish for.
- What'd you mean?
- What you don't know can't hurt.
It's already hurt me,
that's why I'm here.
I'm glad you're okay, Paige.
Thanks.
- Bye.
- Yeah.
Hey.
Packing up?
Yep, packing up.
I left your stuff in the cabinet.
I can put it back if you want.
That's okay, I can do it.
What time's your flight?
Noon.
- You ready to come back?
- More than you know.
- Thanks to you.
- Me? No, I didn't do anything.
- I just kept the seat warm for you.
- You did more than that.
And you know it.
When I first met you, I was...
...totally lost.
That's why I needed to get away
from all of this, you know?
I couldn't give advice...
...especially not about love.
And I realised that...
...I was just afraid.
But I'm not afraid any more.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I guess it just wasn't meant to be?
You and me?
Maybe not right now.
But I do think
our signs are compatible, so...
See ya.
Where were you? I was worried.
I was just... checking on the boys.
We found the possessor demon
right where you said he'd be.
Did you vanquish him?
No, but some creature head thing did.
- You saw him?
- Yeah, we saw it.
- Don't think we've seen the last of it.
- That's what I'm worried about.
Come on, let's go home.
I can't.
Well, the Elders said
you were free to go.
It's not the Elders
I'm worried about, Piper.
I'm worried about you.
I'm worried about everybody.
The Elders were right.
This New Power was after me
because I was vulnerable.
You know, vulnerable enough
to put my family at risk.
Piper, you were
almost killed because of me.
Because of what they did to me.
I can't let that happen. I won't.
Leo, I know
you've been through a lot. I do.
But you fought so hard.
And the boys need you. I need you.
It's too dangerous.
I have to stay away from you
for your own sake.
I'm sorry.