So the wizard didn't realise
the weight of the book.
And after he put them on the shelves,
they blew up and he had to re-conjure
the entire library magically.
Because he was a wizard,
it only took him a couple of minutes.
Yeah, it's a cute story.
The first couple
thousand times you tell it.
- Excuse me?
- Nothing.
That's pretty much the bulk of the tour.
Would you like to know anything about
the facilities, students, teachers?
Boy!
That was swinging!
- Hi.
This is Professor Drake.
This is April, one of the students
who's applying.
Oh, salutations.
How do you do? Hello.
Drake is our visiting lecturer
on advanced magical compositions.
In this case,
magical musical compositions.
That's the use of meter and tempo
in spell casting and conjuring.
The troll is here.
Why don't we see if he'll dance for us.
Come on.
Hey, you put them down!
All of 'em.
- Wow, will I get to take his class?
- Sure, why not?
Yeah, actually, Professor Drake's
gonna be on sabbatical in about a week.
That's right.
I forgot about that little wrinkle.
But with eager minds,
and the power of magic,
it's midsummer madness all the time.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I gotta cut in.
They'll burn! They'll burn!
Don't you understand? They'll burn.
We have to help them!
I don't want to hurt anybody.
They're burning...
I don't wanna hurt nobody,
but I need somebody to listen!
We need help!
You don't understand.
You don't understand. The fire...
Relax, pal, you're under arrest.
Get up!
- We gotta help Marie!
- Just calm down, buddy.
- Come on, everything's gonna be okay.
- No, it won't.
You don't understand! The fire!
You have to let me go so I can get help!
They're gonna burn!
Let me out!
- Rain gear for the kids?
- Yes.
- Camera and film?
- Of course.
Extra room for my... pattini?
Pattini?
Shoes.
It's not a vacation in Italia
if you don't have new shoes.
Right.
- What's the matter?
- I don't know.
I still don't think this is a good idea.
Why not? In Hong Kong
we'll buy you some suits
or bootleg DVDs or something.
It's not the shopping.
It's this whole world vacation thing.
I think we should stay here
and wait for the Elders' decision on me.
Absolutely not.
That's precisely why we should be going.
We're all together,
we deserve a vacation.
We're not gonna wait
for the other pattini to drop.
- So that's that. We're going.
- What about the travel and the cost?
For God sakes, we're orbing!
Okay, well...
What about Phoebe and Paige?
- What about them?
- They made us this big
- send-off dinner last night.
- Oh, please! They ordered pizza.
And we're not helping with the clean up.
Wow, if that's the best you got,
you really do need a vacation.
But...
Look, Phoebe and Paige
just remade the world.
I think they can handle the kitchen.
Now, unless you have
any more objections...
Leaning Tower of Pisa, here we come!
I know, but Elise, why can't
we just do the interview here?
You know, kind of like
a Ask Phoebe at home thing?
Yeah, the place looks great.
Yeah, call him, I'll hold on.
That sounds exciting.
- I guess.
- What do you mean?
You have Cosmo profiling you.
That'd be great anytime.
I know, but I still want
to make the most out of my day.
Phoebe, you asked to meet me here at...
...8.22. That's not making
the most of your day,
that's some sort of weird OCD thing.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Meeting Drake and realising
what little time he has left
has made me wanna make
the most of the time I have.
- You know, time's a'wastin'.
- Yeah.
Well, at least you're not wasting
all your time at Magic School.
Yeah, Elise, I'm still here.
They can move it, that's perfect.
Okay, as long as
the shoot's over by 3.00,
'cause I'm speaking at City College.
All right, I'll be there in 25 minutes.
- You're a machine.
- Every moment counts.
Do me a favour and help
get this place cleaned by 2.00?
Great, thanks!
- How you doing? Gotta go.
- Wait. Hold on. I need...
- I need your help. Hi, Paige.
- I was afraid you were gonna say that.
- What's the matter?
- Not sure. I've been around you enough
- to know when something's not right.
- What? Magically wrong?
- Don't know what else.
- I'm on the clock, gotta speed this up.
My friend Mike, my mentor, he's
the one that brought me into the force.
I think that... he might be,
you know, possessed, maybe.
He's not crazy.
I don't care what anybody says.
Mike would not hurt a fly.
Wait. Back up to the
possessed thing, please.
Since Mike retired, he's been working
this jewellery store security on Market.
And lately he's been
having these... episodes.
What kind of episodes?
They've been happening more frequently.
Yesterday he snapped.
Started waving his gun around,
talking about he's gonna die at
some terrible fire at Cabaret Fantome.
I haven't heard of that place.
Look, I haven't asked you guys
for help like this before.
Okay. Well, if I move
my staff meeting to 11.00,
and my 1 to 1.30, I should
be able to help you right now.
So I will check
the archives for the club.
Paige, you go with Darryl
and check out this Mike guy.
We'll meet back here at like,
I don't know, 1.10.
No! I need...
I need somebody to listen to me!
I don't have much time.
You understand?
I don't have much time!
You see what I mean?
It doesn't seem demonic.
Not demonic? I'm telling you,
he doesn't even know who I am.
- He doesn't know who he is.
- I gotta get out!
- Help! Let me get out of here!
- He mostly seems afraid and panicky.
All right, here goes.
- Hi, I... I'm...
- Marie!
No, I'm Paige. Who's Marie?
My fiancée. She's trapped too.
- Trapped where?
- At the club with everybody else.
Cabaret Fantome?
Yes! Yes, you know it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You believe me?
- Just relax, Mike.
No! My name is George.
I keep telling you that!
We're gonna die.
Don't you understand?
If that's not possession, what is it?
Cabaret Fantome, deadly fire.
Maybe Darryl's friend isn't so crazy.
The Count's club was the biggest,
most corrupt in the city.
Until it burned down,
killing everyone inside.
Why would the Count set the fire
in the club, only to die in it?
I don't know, maybe he
couldn't get out fast enough?
- Maybe we should talk to George.
- George? Who's George?
If I'm right, he's somebody
who died in the fire.
I think he's a spirit that's possessed
Mike and he's crying out for help.
But why would he need help?
The fire happened over 100 years ago.
Help from the pain
of being a Lost Soul, perhaps.
Paige asked me to do a little
research in between classes.
"Possessions, Confessions,
and Ghostly Obsessions:
A Demon's Guide to Everything Magical."
I used to sell these.
Talk about a tough item to move.
"Lost Souls are spirits of the dead,
unable to move on
because of spiritual confusion"?
That's when souls die
a violent death together.
The fires of Gomorrah,
the Flood, Pompeii.
I would step back. The book
likes to show off a little, don't you?
What the hell?
Don't be afraid,
it's simply illustrating a point.
When souls die at once,
the good ones can't move on
because the bad ones
are holding 'em back. And vice versa.
They're lost, they're stuck
in their respective afterlives,
unaware of their tragic fate.
It's really sad, actually.
But if they're unaware,
how are we supposed to help George?
We can't.
Unless we enter his world
and find out which one of those
bad souls is holding him back.
- Excuse me?
- Well, this spell would get us there,
but I'm not gonna tell you
what it is unless you take me.
Wait, us?
How many chances
do we have to go to the 1890s?
It's not going to the 1890s
that's the problem.
- It's getting back.
- Don't worry, little lady.
The spell'll only keep us with the souls
till the moment they become lost.
- In this case, when the fire begins.
- How do we free George?
I don't know, we wing it.
Okay. I don't know. I'm gonna
go check out some other things.
All right. You don't have to go,
but you do.
- I can't! I have an interview.
- Interview shminterview.
How does an interview weigh in
against the fate of an innocent?
Your premonition skills
could prove essential.
And it is the next logical step
in our whirlwind romance.
What whirlwind romance?
The one we'd be having if we had time.
Come on, I don't have
long to live, I'm dying here.
A soul needs your help.
So, what do you say?
Are you sure this is the place?
It says here it's where
the cabaret used to be.
A vacant lot after 106 years?
It's probably haunted.
Or better yet cursed. Cool, let's go.
There a reason we
can't do this from home?
The closer to where the souls were lost,
the better the chances of finding
the exact one we are looking for.
Excuse me. Safety first.
What?
- What are you doing?
- Getting comfortable. What else?
You don't want my body...
slumped in the front seat.
It's too conspicuous.
Phoebe, living isn't about tasks.
It's about living.
All right. Paige, are you gonna make
sure Elise bumps my interview two hours?
- I'm all over it.
- We will be back before two hours?
We'll return just when the fire begins.
Which, based on what you
said about George, seems imminent.
Free our souls from their shells
See where the lost spirits dwell
Long enough to find their pain
Quick enough to return again
Oh, my!
- This is...
- Fantastic.
Well, you look stunning.
Why, thank you.
You don't look so bad yourself.
Well, thank you very much.
- So, what do we do now?
- We mingle.
Ladies, please.
Toulouse, who the hell is that?
Never seen 'em before, boss.
Nor have I. Find out who they are.
Pardon us.
So all these people are stuck
in some, like, ghostly limbo?
- As if the fire never happened?
- It happened.
Otherwise they wouldn't be here.
Keep your eyes in your socket.
We're here for George, remember?
That doesn't mean
we can't enjoy ourselves.
Come on, it's 1899.
You may not remember, but I do.
What, the Gilded Age?
It's a time when everyone thought
life couldn't possibly get any better.
There was science.
There was art. There was peace and love.
And romance.
Everything was a celebration.
This is a celebration?
Everyone's dead, just like...
George? George?
- What'd you do to him?
- Don't know what you're talking about.
Don't lie to me. I saw him
talking to you and now he's gone.
What can I say.
He likes my cards.
Still, I don't know where he is.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Excuse me?
I couldn't help but overhear.
Do you know George?
- Who are you?
- That doesn't matter.
But what does matter
is that George came to us for help.
- About the fire?
- What fire? What are you talking about?
- I don't have time for this!
- She doesn't know either?
That's because it hasn't happened yet.
Not as far as she's concerned.
Not as far as they're all concerned.
They're doomed to repeat the last
few hours over and over.
It's like a never-ending loop.
That's just terrible. What could
possibly cause such a thing?
What or who?
- Well?
- Well, they're not the law.
- I don't know where they came from.
- I'm interested in how they got in.
And if they're my way out.
What do you mean?
Toulouse, what if I was
to tell you everyone in this room
has been reliving
this same night for over 100 years?
Like rats on a wheel.
I mean, nobody knows it but me.
And what if,
no matter what anybody did,
or how hard they tried,
there's absolutely no way out?
And all the drinking
and gambling and... the girls.
Well, what if they didn't mean squat?
What if, you'll love this,
I told you that it was
going to be like that forever?
Forever. What would you say then?
Well... Would I get to keep my tips?
Bring me a Scotch.
Champagne for the lady,
and a cigar for the gentleman.
I want them to be comfortable
when I meet them.
Yes, sir.
Okay, if you guys
are not back in two minutes,
I'm calling Piper!
Hey, Elise. What are you doing here?
Well, what do you mean?
I'm here with Cosmo for the photo shoot.
Where's Phoebe?
Phoebe...
Didn't you get her message?
She said she's gonna have to reschedule.
- What?!
- Yeah, just for a couple hours.
I never got the message
to push the shoot.
Are you out of your mind?
We're talking national exposure here
for her column!
The kind you can't buy,
and the deadline is tonight!
And no, I can't just...
Phoebe? Phoebe, we talked about this.
Blow it with Cosmo once,
you don't get a second chance.
- What is the matter with her?
- Well...
- I'd say that she's got food poisoning.
- Food poisoning?!
I think the more she can sleep,
the quicker she'll get better.
- When? When is she gonna get better?
- Well, like I was trying to say...
A couple hours.
Have you thought about
doing it at the office?
Well, that is where
I originally wanted it, but...
See? You're brilliant.
Really, a brilliant woman.
Okay, I promise you'll have her there.
She better be.
Piper!
Piper, Leo!
- How was the vacation?
- This better be an emergency.
We were just about
to go for a gondola ride.
Oh, for the love of God.
Hey, a fan dance.
I love a fan dance.
Wait'll you see this. Never mind.
Yes, it is quite a sight.
A beautiful woman onstage,
nothing between her and the audience
except two ostrich fans.
The allure of the dance is to watch
how she moves with the fans.
Showing only what she wants,
not an inch more.
Is the dance ever performed by a man?
So, tell me, my new friends,
how exactly do you know George?
What makes you think that we do?
Well, I saw you talking
to his fiancée, Marie.
She seems terribly distraught,
doesn't she?
- She doesn't know what happened to him.
- Do you?
I've been concerned about him recently.
Keeping an eye on him, you know.
He is my best barkeep, after all.
- And you don't know what happened?
- I wish I did.
So, how did you come to learn
about Cabaret Fantome?
Word gets out.
Hard to keep a place like this
hidden forever.
- Do you like the cigar?
- Quite.
They're hand rolled in Havana, and
shipped to my dealer Philippe, special.
He's right across the street.
Would you like to take in the night air,
pay him a visit?
- He loves new customers.
- Sure. Care to join us?
Sadly, I'm unable to leave the club.
- And why is that?
- Because as they say...
...the show must go on, right?
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome your host, Count Roget.
Feel free to enjoy the show from here.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
We're dying to see it.
Right on time.
Could have waited till after the show.
Come on, we gotta get to the spot.
George!
- George!
- We have to help her!
George, where are you?
We can't. We stay, we burn.
Don't worry, she'll be back tomorrow.
The fire!
What's wrong? What's going on?
- Go, go get some help.
- Right away.
Marie!
Just hold on.
There's nothing in the Book
that tells us how to get 'em back.
Since I can't talk to the Elders...
- Phoebe?
- Are you all right?
I don't know.
And that's when the good souls
tried to escape, but couldn't.
- Couldn't?
- Yeah, the exits were magically sealed.
I got dead leg.
I'll be down here. Sorry.
At least nobody knows
they're gonna re-live it.
The Count knew. He just stood there
watching everybody burn.
- You think he's a demon?
- If he was, he wouldn't be reliving it.
No, but maybe he made
a deal with a demon.
If he's the soul trying
to hold everyone back,
he'd do anything
to keep from moving on.
Doesn't seem like much of a deal,
though. He's stuck as well.
But anything's better
than Purgatory. Trust me, it's...
He's probably trying to buy time.
Find another way out.
How do we help George
and the other souls move on?
Find a way to separate
their souls from the Count's.
- How?
- Find who he made the deal with
and get him to break it.
- Think that demon's around?
- This one is.
Yeah, but not for long.
Besides, that's not really the point.
I mean, enough about me.
What do you think of me?
Let's go check the Book.
Andiamo!
Ciao, ciao!
Maybe we should talk to George
and see if he remembers
what the demon looks like.
Hello! Hello!
Magazine. Interview.
Cosmo. Cancelling twice.
I think this is more important
than Cosmo, don't you?
Paige, there's a lot more
to life than work.
- There's adventure.
- Really? I wouldn't know.
Hey, I have an idea.
Why don't you do it?
- What?
- Be me!
You can glamour.
You've done it before.
It'll give you a taste of life
outside Magic School.
Besides, if anyone knows me as well
as I know me, it's you. Just fake it!
Why don't I just go talk to George?
Because if we have to go back
at the cabaret afterwards,
the Count is expecting Phoebe.
Feathers and all.
- Feathers?
- Don't ask.
The doctors are saying that
he's schizophrenic or something.
First he's George, then he's back
to being Mike again. Now he's George.
That must be who we saw
get back in the club before we left.
Perhaps the fire's what pulled
George back in the time warp.
He knows what's going on.
And can only escape long enough
to cry for help.
What are you talking about?
The fire your friend's
screaming about is real. Very real.
- The fire. Help me, please!
- That's how poor George died.
The only way he knows how
to cry for help
- is to possess your friend.
- But why Mike?
Proximity.
- I need to get out of here!
- You ready?
- No.
- Let's go.
I gotta get out of the fire!
It's coming back!
- I need somebody to believe me!
- We believe you, George.
George?
- Then you do believe me?
- Yes.
We also saw Marie just as we left.
Well, you...
Well, you can go in and out
without getting burned? How?
Well, you kinda have to die first.
We can go back in
to free you and everybody else,
- but we're gonna need your help.
- Anything! Anything!
- What can you tell us about the Count?
- He's the one who did this.
- He cursed everybody to save himself.
- Yeah, we know.
Maybe he was talking
to someone else, maybe there's...
Did you see him talk to anybody else,
anyone unusual that night?
Yes, yes!
Every night before the show,
he sits with this frightening-looking
man at the centre table.
And then the Count,
he signs something.
- That could be the deal.
- They might still be there.
This may be a silly question.
Is there anything we can do
to make you more comfortable?
Save Marie.
Kids are down for the count.
No pun intended.
- What are you doing?
- Me? Nothing.
Yes, you are.
You're writing in the Book?
No, I was just looking for demons.
"Tips for future Whitelighters."
What?
It's just something I was
working on for the kids. You know...
No, I don't know. Why can't you tell
them this yourself when they're ready?
Because I might not be around.
- Come on.
- I know you wanna ignore everything
going on with the Elders,
but I can't.
We don't know what
they're gonna do or when.
They can't just
yank you out of our lives, Leo.
- How do you know that?
- Because they can't.
And if they did, I'd quit.
We'd all quit.
Is that why you didn't want
to go around the world in 80 orbs?
Yeah, I just wanted to finish it.
Just in case.
Okay.
Did you even look for demons?
Yeah, I found this one.
Sargon. Traders of souls,
preys on the afterlife.
Well, it certainly looks
like our guy except...
...we vanquished him already.
I can do this.
I can do this. I can do this.
You owe me.
Hello, sis.
Phoebe, there you are! You look great!
You feeling better? You are so late!
- I know. Maybe we should reschedule.
- Not a chance! Come meet everybody.
- Hi, I'm Cameron.
- Hi, it's nice to meet you.
- So, you're the photographer?
- I'm interviewing you.
We spoke on the phone? Twice?
That's right, I'm sorry.
I got confused.
I thought you said,
"I'm the camera man."
Okay, so I'm gonna ask you questions
while they shoot.
- That all right with you?
- Sure.
- Okay, great.
- Shoot away.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. It's just new contacts.
So why don't we start with
what inspired you
to become an advice columnist?
That's a really good question.
Well, I guess growing up
as an only child...
I'm sorry, only child?
I meant Paige grew up as an only child.
I mean, that's how she grew up until
she met her sisters, you know, us... me.
And that had absolutely nothing to do
with why Phoebe
became an advice columnist.
She talks about herself
in the third person.
Yeah, what I meant to say was that
Paige really had
a lot to do with my decision.
Well, she opened up
a whole new world for me,
and made me see
how much I really have to offer.
And I can honestly say,
that I would not be standing here today
- if it wasn't for Paige.
- Oh, great!
Hi, okay. According to Mike...
- George.
- Whatever.
There was a demon
in the club that night who...
We vanquished, five years ago.
- What? Are you serious?
- 'Fraid so.
According to the Book,
there aren't other demons
- who could've made the deal.
- How do we get 'em to unmake it?
- We go back.
- No! What? No!
No, he's right. It's the only way
we're gonna find the demon.
You said you'd barely
made it out alive last time.
You don't even know what he looks like.
- George told us where to find him.
- It's simple.
We go back. I talk to him demon
to demon, talon to talon, claw to claw.
- Make him unmake the deal.
- Hopefully, the souls'll be released.
- Yeah.
- Okay. Let's do it.
This time no messing around, okay?
We get in, we find him, we get out.
- Might wanna stay for the show.
- Wait!
- What are we supposed to do?
- What you always do. Worry.
We're late.
No, we're not. Let's go.
There's nobody at that centre table.
Your demon is long gone.
In fact, he left 106 years ago.
Right after we made the deal.
Long before the fire.
You know... The fire!
It's coming back! You gotta believe me!
Sit down.
Please, you gotta help me and Marie!
Or something like that?
Oh, my God.
That was you in Mike's body.
- You tricked us!
- Slow down.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome your host, Count Roget.
I regret to inform you that tonight's
fan dance is going to be cancelled.
Really think that gun's
gonna do anything?
Indeed. If you can burn,
you can bleed.
You really shouldn't bother.
Both of you will die soon enough.
Since your friend George
has found a temporary way out,
I now have found
my permanent way out.
You know, they haven't
been gone that long, relax.
Oh, no! I can't relax.
I worry, remember?
Drake. What happened?
Why isn't Phoebe waking up?
Drake? Did you hear me?
What the hell is wrong with Phoebe?
I suppose she didn't make it.
What do you mean she didn't make it?
How is that possible?
I don't know. Clumsy...
- What's the matter with you?
- Nothing.
Actually, I'm splendid.
I mean... swell.
You have to get her
before the fire starts.
It's already begun.
Then you need to go get her. Go!
No! What do you mean, go back there?
- Forget it.
- Why not?
Perhaps if I go...
...outside...
Have a smoke, you know, like...
Consider the possibility of going back.
- I gotta go. Excuse me.
- Who are you?
Count Roget!
Oh, not bad!
I guess I did choose the right body.
No, don't.
You're in enough trouble already with...
...the Elders.
Go. I'm gonna die anyway.
Get out of here!
Not like this. If George can get out, we
can too. We have to think about this.
- Fortune teller.
- Okay.
Perfect.
Perfect escape from the ordinary.
Five card spread.
Listen, odds are
the Count's possessed my body.
Until he's evicted, I got nowhere to go.
Only you can get out to your body.
Even though I'm into your body,
- I still can't get out.
- I'll come back for you.
If he puts up a fight,
you vanquish my sorry ass.
I don't care.
But only as a last resort.
Okay.
Vita Brevis Abraxis
Can I get a water?
This should dispossess him,
if we can find him.
He's off the radar. There's nothing
in the Book to help locate him.
You were onto something a minute ago.
- Phoebe?
- Where's the Count?
Wait a minute.
What's my middle name?
- Surly?
- That's my girl.
Whatever, where's Drake's body?
- We don't know.
- We can't scry for him.
We're thinking maybe
he's in a pub, or a restaurant.
Or a tobacco shop.
I think I know where to find him.
- What kind of terrible world is this?
- One you'll be leaving soon.
- No. They'll take me away!
- Go to hell!
Darryl.
Mike. Is that you?
Of course it's me.
What's... what's going on here?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
- Welcome back.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for bringing me back.
Thank you.
This boy was getting hot.
I'll bet.
Leonardo, it's bene.
The vacation was a great idea.
Just not great timing.
Yeah, well. Life is short, bella.
- Are you quoting Drake now?
- He's got a point.
Thanks for trying to distract me
from the Elders.
I wish it would've worked out
the way I planned.
Could be worse.
I think from now on I'm gonna stop
trying to control every little moment.
The best ones kinda
sneak up on you anyway.
- Excuse me, have you seen Phoebe?
- Very funny.
Wow, I haven't seen you
this relaxed in quite a long time.
After having been you, I kinda see why.
Well, I'm trying to take a step back
and enjoy every moment.
Hey, thank you.
You did a great job.
Nobody ever knew.
Well, you're welcome.
I think after reading the article,
you'll find that your little sister
got praised quite a bit.
Deservedly so.
- I think I got more out of it than you.
- Yeah.
I kinda miss being out there
in the real world.
Maybe you should
do something about that.
Maybe I will.
Ladies and gentlemen,
P3 is proud to present
- a one night only show by...
- What's going on?
...Drake Demond.
Oh, my God.
This is what happens
when you have one week to live?
- What is he up to?
- Just be grateful it's not a fan dance.