Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
www.sub-way.fr (1.00)
You want me to blow up
a couple of dozen FBI agents?
You got a problem with that?
Agent Walker, it's Jack. Get your men
out of the building. It's a trap.
You got the canister?
Clearly, Hodges is behind this.
I want him taken to the FBI
for interrogation.
He's a sociopath, Mom.
He's not going to talk.
He'll want to make some kind of deal
in exchange for his cooperation.
- Mom, you're not considering that.
- Olivia...
You know what this man is,
what he did to Roger.
I've upset the cart, have I?
That bioweapon that you developed for us
was not intended for personal use.
There's no reason for your family
to pay for your mistakes.
This will induce a cardiac arrest
and leave no trace in your system.
We are rerouting
to West Arlington Hospital.
Have you heard from Almeida?
- I called him before I met with Hodges.
- Has he secured the canister?
- Soon.
- Your guy better not screw this up.
I have faith he'll come through.
Why don't you go back to FBI Medical
and let them treat you?
There is no treatment.
There is no cure.
Almost like they knew.
They'd have need time
to wire here with explosives.
This is the last sector
we were due to search. What?
- What is your involvement?
- You're not thinking straight.
The toxin's starting
to affect your judgment.
- Put the gun down.
- Don't you move!
I never wanted to hurt you, Jack.
I told you to stay out of it.
We get some help here?
This man's having a seizure.
You should
be feeling better already.
I'm giving you pendopamine.
It'll de-constrict your muscles.
Just hang in there.
Don't talk.
Your vocal cords are in spasm.
- What the hell happened?
- Almeida found him in full seizure.
- What about the medication pack?
- He wasn't carrying it.
- Stop.
- Mr. Bauer, please don't speak.
Tony? I don't understand.
He's... second man.
- Jack, what...
- Put out an APB.
- How do you know this?
- Do it!
All patrols and perimeter teams,
this is Alpha One.
I'm issuing a priority APB on Almeida.
Approach with extreme caution.
He's colluding with Galvez
and should be considered hostile.
All units who engage the suspect
should do so with extreme caution.
Okay, you really need to give yourself
more time to recover.
Here's another med pack.
Make sure he doesn't lose it.
I need to go tend
to the other wounded.
Tell me what the hell is going on.
Tony was working
with Galvez all along.
He used us, all of us,
so that he could get to the canister.
So, wait, what are you saying,
that...
Tony killed Larry?
They must have ambushed him
as the chopper was setting down.
Tony stayed behind
so he could monitor our search,
set the trap and make sure Galvez
could get beyond the perimeter.
- Oh, God.
- I'm so sorry.
This is my fault.
I vouched for him to you,
to the president.
I made a terrible, terrible mistake.
I felt that something was wrong.
Things weren't adding up. I just...
I just wanted to believe.
- Alpha One, this is Agent Kilner.
- Alpha One. Go ahead.
Agent Walker,
I'm at checkpoint Delta.
I've got two agents dead, shot
point-blank. Their vehicle is missing.
He's made it past the perimeter.
Tracking on the vehicle has been
disabled. Position is unknown.
Widen the perimeter,
keep looking for Almeida.
If we lose him,
we lose the canister.
You're not gonna find him,
he's gone.
We need to phone the president.
Let's go.
You made it.
You sound surprised.
After Bauer called you out,
I wasn't sure you would.
You don't have to worry
about Jack Bauer.
He's not gonna be a problem.
So, where is the canister?
Where's the money?
Hey, that was our agreement.
Money first.
There you go.
It's all there,
wired into your account.
You can check it if you want.
I want.
Everything okay?
So, where is the canister?
Right here.
So, what are you planning
on doing with it?
Not really your business, is it?
You gonna sell it?
- You don't want to do this.
- Hey, now who's the damn buyer?
Where's the canister?
Where is the damn canister?
One of the marines
that was guarding Hodges
noticed he was trying
to swallow something.
He got him to the hospital before
the poison could be completely ingested.
So, he'll survive?
Yes, ma'am, but the doctors
are surprised he pulled through.
That's because they never met
the son of a bitch.
How did Hodges get this poison?
We suspect from a woman
who claimed to be his attorney.
- Claimed to be?
- She was an impostor.
DC Police found the body of Hodges'
real attorney about five minutes ago.
We're still trying to determine
how she managed to breach security.
Madam President,
Agent Walker and Jack Bauer.
- Put them through.
- Yes, ma'am.
This is President Taylor.
I'm here with Tim Woods.
- Madam President...
- Have you secured the canister?
I'm afraid not, ma'am. Our suspect
escaped beyond the perimeter.
I was told that the area
was locked down. What happened?
He had help, Madam President.
From Tony Almeida.
- Almeida?
- Yes, ma'am.
- He was working for us.
- It only appeared that way.
Apparently, he pursued his own agenda,
trying to get his hands on the canister.
Madam President,
I know I vouched for him.
All I can tell you right now
is that I was wrong and I'm sorry.
Now that we know he has the canister,
do we know what he intends to do?
- No, not yet.
- Or where he is?
We're all hands on deck here, sir,
regrouping to develop leads.
I may have one.
As Hodges was taken into custody,
he yelled at me about some larger group
that would continue on after his arrest.
Something
that I wouldn't be able to stop.
- What do you think he meant?
- Well, all I know for sure
is that someone
doesn't want Hodges to talk.
Shortly after he was arrested,
Hodges was visited
by a woman impersonating his lawyer.
She apparently gave him
some kind of lethal drug,
because ten minutes later,
he tried to commit suicide.
- Tried to commit suicide?
- Oh, he's still alive.
Jonas Hodge
was completely unrepentant.
Now, this suicide attempt
must have been coerced.
They're holding something over him,
most likely his family.
If that's the case,
we need to talk to him.
Jack, even after everything
that's happened today,
I will not allow any kind
of coercive interrogation.
Madam President,
that won't be necessary. He'll talk.
- How can you be sure?
- We can offer him something he needs.
- And what's that?
- Proof of death.
Convince the people that wanted him dead
that they succeeded.
The only way to protect his family.
Madam President, right now,
he's the only lead we've got.
I'll assume that was necessary.
Don't start with me.
I'm not in the mood.
All right.
Mr. Galvez decided
to hide the canister from me,
so, I had to find out where it was.
We've got a delivery to make.
- Shall we go?
- No, I don't think we should.
- They're expecting us.
- Yeah, well, the way I see it,
they're gonna take this canister
that I sweated blood for
and sit on it for six months.
Not sit on it. They're gonna use it
to make more pathogen.
We had 27 canisters.
Now we have one.
I say one's enough.
Look,
the government's reeling.
The FBI is stretched thin,
scrambling, making mistakes.
Another attack today is all we need
to push this thing right over the edge.
This is no time to pull back.
I say we take that canister,
and finish the job off today.
I don't disagree with you
but it's not our decision to make.
Fine.
Then run it by your group
or your gang
or whatever the hell they are.
But they'll know one thing.
Finish your enemy off when he's down.
Don't let him get back up and reload.
I guarantee you,
this thing's gonna be a lot harder
to pull off six months from now.
And you can say what you want
about Jonas Hodges,
the fact is, he gave us
an opportunity today.
Let's take it.
I'll contact the group.
Good.
What did she say exactly?
Only that she needs to see you
and that it's urgent.
I heard rumors
about the FBI operation.
I'm sure your mother
will fill you in, ma'am.
Is it true
the FBI perimeter was breached?
I'm afraid so.
The canister is now outside the cordon.
- What are we doing to get it back?
- Tim, would you excuse us for a moment?
Of course.
What is it?
I need you to call
the Attorney General
and draft a witness protection
agreement for Jonas Hodges.
Witness protection?
You can't be serious.
Less than an hour ago,
Hodges tried to kill himself.
And we all believe
that he must've been coerced.
By whom?
You remember his rant...
that he is a cog
in a larger conspiracy,
that there are others
who will carry on.
You think they're the ones
who took the canister?
We need to find out. Which is why
we need to get Hodges to talk.
Olivia, we feel confident that he will
if we can assure him
that these people will believe
his suicide attempt actually succeed.
We need to make him disappear.
Which is why
I need the protection agreement.
There is no other way he'll talk.
Designate him an enemy combatant,
then treat him like one.
We don't do that.
Not in this administration.
And it's not as
if he's getting a free pass.
He'll always be
under federal supervision.
On a hundred acre ranch in Colorado!
This man murdered your son!
My brother.
Not to mention
hundreds of innocent civilians.
I don't need you
to tell me what he's done.
- Apparently you do.
- Olivia, stop it!
What would Dad say?
- I bet you're afraid to ask.
- I said stop!
Do you think
that this is easy for me?
You think it doesn't tear me apart?
I'm Roger's mother.
But I am also
the President of the United States
and I placed my hand on a Bible
and swore to protect and defend
the Constitution.
You are my Chief of Staff.
I need you to act like one.
Now, Jonas Hodges is at the FBI,
and Jack Bauer will be there shortly.
I need an agreement drafted.
Do that please.
The plan is straightforward...
an attack today this morning
during rush hour
using the bioweapon that Tony Almeida
retrieved from Starkwood.
You should have each received a data
pack when you logged on to this call.
Please open it now.
The attack will be attributed
to this man,
Jibraan Al-Zarian...
whose body
will be left at the scene.
The evidence trail implicating him
will include fabricated e-mails,
phone records,
and a large wire transfer
to his account
via our favorite Yemini bank.
I'm looking
at the briefing materials
and I'm not seeing how this man is
actually connected to a terrorist group.
He isn't.
As previously discussed,
there are considerable tactical
advantages to using an innocent.
- But what about his unpredictability?
- Al-Zarian has no agenda of his own.
He'll in fact be easier to control
and manipulate than a real terrorist.
So what are the casualty estimates?
Page 3 describes the casualties
estimates as well as secondary effects.
- As you can see, we've listed...
- Hold on.
Forget about what casualties
may or may not be.
We're talking about launching
a new operation in the next few hours.
Without any planning.
And with only one canister.
The plan for this operation
was already in place.
We just accelerate.
We were going to have
6 months to prepare.
There's no way
to pull it together in a few hours.
I believe there is.
With the support of this group.
Support for whom?
This Tony Almeida we barely know?
And what about postattack plans?
How's this group going to end up
where we need to be?
I agree.
How we handle ourselves politically
in the aftermath of this event is just
as important as the attack itself.
It always has been.
In your opinion, is there time then
to achieve all our objectives
in the current scenario?
- Not with the same level of certainty.
- Or anonymity.
That's right.
Maybe it's definitive.
- What do you mean?
- There's no downside to waiting.
There's a huge downside
to going in unprepared.
Things go wrong,
we're looking at exposure...
- for all of us.
- No, I still don't see it that way.
Gentlemen.
Ladies.
I've listened to your comments
and there's wisdom
in what I've heard.
But there's also wisdom
in something I haven't heard.
Jonas Hodges was a loose cannon,
and the group is well rid of him.
But, in his lunacy,
he did us a favor.
He did half our job for us.
More than half.
He pushed this country to the brink.
You don't get many gifts like that.
I say we take it.
We have a quorum,
I'd like to call for an immediate vote.
How'd it go?
Take a look.
We're a go.
- Where's Hodges?
- Down the hall.
We've set up a medical suite
in Secure Z.
- And the death certificate?
- Done.
As far as the world knows,
he's molding on a slab at the coroner's.
Keep it that way.
No one knows he's alive
unless they have to.
Just the ambulance driver,
the medical team and 3 security.
All trustworthy.
Wait.
Are you sure he's up for this?
I know what happened.
- Medication worked.
- I'm not talking about the seizure.
I'm talking
about the Tony Almeida situation.
What about it?
His former partner betrays him,
he tries to have you all killed...
Jack must have some feelings
about that.
Yeah, I think
it's what's keeping him going.
Listen to me.
Is anyone listening?
I know you're watching.
I see the cameras!
Do you realize
what you people have done?
You didn't save me,
you killed my family!
You killed them!
- How long has he been conscious?
- 10 min.
He's been talking about his family
ever since.
Biometrics are over here. Cardiac,
respiratory, plus dermal infrared.
Good. We'll know if he's lying.
The president is monitoring this.
Sergeant, I'm asking you,
soldier to soldier,
let me have your firearm.
I'll use one bullet on myself.
- Please.
- Relax, Mr. Hodges.
You're already dead.
Sergeant.
Who are you?
My name is Jack Bauer.
Right now, I'm the only chance your wife
and children have to stay alive.
Explain that to me.
The people that wanted you dead
don't know you survived.
Tell us who they are,
and we'll keep it that way.
The President has agreed to provide you
a death certificate and protection
in exchange
for actionable information.
I can't watch this anymore.
If you refuse,
it'll be released to the press
that you are alive and in our custody
and that you're cooperating.
We'll let your friends
take care of the rest.
My family is innocent.
The president would never allow that
to happen.
She doesn't have the stomach for it.
You might be right about that.
But make no mistake about it, sir.
I do.
Trust me.
Do your family a favor.
Just tell me
who you've been working with.
I am...
I was...
part of a larger group
of like minds.
You mean,
other companies like Starkwood.
People who can protect this country
better than any government ever could.
There are hundreds of private
military companies in this country,
we're talking
tens of thousands of people.
But only a handful
with the guts and the vision
to do what was necessary.
And what is that?
The plan was to launch
simultaneous attacks early next year.
Multiple cities.
So the public would finally see
that the government can't protect them.
They'd demand drastic measures
and we'd step in.
How would you justify that
to the American people?
Simple.
Offload the blame.
We were gonna supply the enemies
that want to destroy this country.
Muhammed this, Achmed that.
From sleeper cells
the apologists say don't even exist.
You of all people should understand.
Understand what?
I watched the Senate hearing
yesterday,
and I was disgusted
with how you were treated.
You should be regarded as a hero,
not a criminal.
I broke the law.
You were following your instinct
to protect your country, just like me.
Mr. Hodges, I need the names
of the people that you are working with.
I have spent my entire life
protecting this country
from enemies large and small.
I created Starkwood
from the ground up.
And the government used us
to great effect.
And now they think
they can just throw us away.
Are you telling me
that this has been about
protecting your contracts, about money?
I tried to tell the politicians
how vulnerable we are,
they wouldn't listen.
- So we decided to show them.
- By attacking your own country
with a biological weapon?
By killing innocent people?
Yes, a few innocent lives...
would be lost, but only
to save the greater number.
Having the courage to make those hard
choices gives us a lot in common.
Let me explain something to you.
You and I have absolutely
nothing in common.
All that you have done today
is create a scenario
by attacking your own country
that has made you valuable again.
Today has been nothing short
of a desperate grab for power,
and it has failed.
You have failed,
and unless you want me to go public
with the fact that you are still alive,
you are gonna give me the names
of the people that you're working with.
- I don't have them.
- I want the names.
- I want the names!
- I don't know any!
Fine.
Patch me through to Amy Meyer
at the Washington Post.
Amy, it's Jack.
I have a statement I need to make.
Wait!
Give me the names!
I swear I don't have them.
This whole project
was based on anonymity.
We never met in person.
Everything was handled through a woman.
She never told me who she was.
She never told me her name.
- I never asked her.
- The woman that gave you the poison?
Amy, I'm sorry. Something's come up.
I've got to call you back.
You tell yourself whatever you want.
You are a traitor.
Witness Protection was your promise.
Madam President, did you hear
everything that Hodges had to say?
Yes. Is any of it even credible?
All of it is. Biometric monitors here
indicate that he was telling the truth.
Whoever they are, this group went
through an awful lot of trouble
to get their hands
on that last canister.
It seems very clear to me
that their plan is still on.
- You mean another attack?
- Yes, ma'am.
You should proceed under the assumption
that they might strike immediately.
Hold on.
Hodges said some time next year.
No. Hodges said that was the plan.
Given the chaos
that he created today,
the smart strategic move
would be to act right now.
I believe the canister
is still in this area,
so we'll have to alert Homeland, have
them identifying and raiding targets.
Hodges said that the plan was
to enlist parties with terrorist ties.
I think that might be
our most solid lead.
Madam President, I agree with her.
We need to make a threat assessment
with all known terrorist activity.
The fastest way
to get that information
is to gain access to the CTU servers
that have been sealed as a result
of Senator Mayer's investigation.
I'll have them
recommissioned immediately.
And consider the resources
of this government at your disposal.
Thank you.
- I need those servers right away.
- They're in DOJ evidence lockers.
- I'll have I.T. break them out.
- OK, good.
We have a shift of analysts coming in.
Tell them what you're looking for.
We don't have time. We need someone
who already knows the protocols.
I'll take care of it.
Just get me those servers.
- Who is it?
- Hey, it's me Jack.
Jack, where are you?
The FBI headquarters.
I've been trying to reach you all night.
No one will tell me anything.
Is it true about Bill?
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
What happened?
He was killed
during the White House siege.
Chloe, you should know,
Bill sacrificed his life
to save the president.
This threat is not over.
We believe that there's gonna be
a biological attack
somewhere in the area.
Soon.
- I need your help to stop it.
- How?
I need you to reconstitute
the CTU servers.
They were seized
when the CTU was decommissioned.
- I don't have access to them.
- You will by the time you get here.
Who's doing this?
We don't have all the players.
I'll fill you in with as much
as I know when you get here.
I'm sending a car over
to your hotel.
Send a car.
Thank you.
- Morris, wake up.
- What?
- Are you speaking to me again now?
- I have to go.
I need you to take Prescott
and get out of the city.
- Why?
- I just spoke with Jack.
There's going to be another attack.
This time, it's biological.
OK, then we'll all get out
of here together.
I can't. FBI needs me.
But the last time
you worked for these people,
- they arrested you.
- I know.
But I'm the only one that can get
the servers back online.
Well, I'm not gonna leave you here.
Not with the possibility
of a biological attack.
Please.
I'm the only one that can do this.
And Jack needs me.
And I just need for you
and Prescott to be safe.
I'll see you back at home.
Just...
be careful.
I will.
All right, before we begin,
everyone make sure
you have your updated briefing packets,
and the latest CDC abstract.
- Jack, whenever you're ready.
- Thank you.
I know many of you have lost friends
and colleagues today.
I have, too.
Unfortunately, the time to mourn these
brave people is going to have to wait.
'Cause, as many of you
are already aware,
we are facing the threat of a terrorist
event somewhere on the Eastern seaboard.
We don't have specific intel
as to the time table of this attack,
but we have reason to believe
that the people that are behind this
- will want to strike immediately.
- Excuse me.
Tim Moran, field ops.
Who are the people behind this?
Right now, we only have
two confirmed suspects.
Tony Almeida
and the woman he's been working with.
We're trying to identify her.
The assumption is, the two of them
are part of a broader conspiracy
as outlined
in your briefing material.
And the nature of the attack?
All it says here is biological.
The actual pathogen
is a prion variant,
designed to attack the central nervous
system and ultimately destroy it.
- Do we know what the target is?
- No, not yet.
We're also unclear on the specifics
of the delivery device.
- What leads do we have?
- Right now,
we are solely
working off an operational theory
that the people that are behind this
will need to manufacture evidence
in an effort to offload the blame
for this attack to another group
or an individual
with terrorist sympathies.
During the ensuing panic, these people
will move in and seize power
under the guise of creating
and maintaing stability.
So, our job here is to look for traces
of that manufactured evidence.
How exactly?
Pattern searches of suspicious
financial transactions.
Keyword intercepts of existing wiretaps,
websites and e-mails.
And data-ming all NSA and CIA
intelligence on jihadist activities
- over the past six months.
- Excuse me.
Not only is that type
of blanket surveillance illegal.
We don't have the capacity
to pull it off.
The search algorithms
simply don't exist.
Yes, they do. At CTU.
Those servers were decommissioned.
Not anymore. They're here. We're in
the process of installing them now.
What does that make us, CTU-lite?
Last I heard,
the Bureau was a federal entity
bound by federal statute.
Do this or I'll find
someone else who will.
- I don't have time to argue.
- I'm not arguing. I'm asking.
Moving on.
I've got her from here. Thanks.
- Thanks for coming.
- You look like hell. Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
- You don't look fine.
Maybe a little tired.
Did you get the report I sent you?
I read it on the way over.
- It's terrifying. How real is this?
- Real.
We get access
to the CTU servers, right?
- They're coming online now.
- Shouldn't I be supervising this?
There's something I need to talk
to you about before we get started.
There's no easy way
for me to say this.
But Tony's been responsible
for these attacks.
- That's not possible.
- He was using you and Bill all along.
He's been working for
a group of private military firms
trying to destabilize this country
in an effort to seize power.
So far today, his actions have cost
the lives of hundreds of people.
But he's threatening thousands more.
It doesn't make any sense.
He was devastated over Michelle...
Chloe, he's not your friend.
The Tony that you knew,
he doesn't exist anymore.
- There has to be a reason.
- A reason for what?
Bringing down two passenger planes?
Trying to ambush 25 federal agents?
He tried to kill me.
He betrayed us all, you, me,
and Bill,
and right now our responsibility
is to stop him.
I need to know that you can treat him
as an enemy combatant,
that you are with me on this.
I'll do whatever you say.
I need to know that you,
are with me on this.
I'm with you.
Let's go.
His name is Jibraan Al-Zarian.
27 years old.
He's a day laborer at
Cabrera Granite Construction.
- Immigration status?
- Illegal.
His visa expired as of January.
Ties to any extremist groups?
No, none, but there's definitely
anger there.
Both parents were killed in a U.S.
air strike by the Pakistani border.
He was eleven at the time.
Fits the psych profile.
Bit of a loner,
a mystery to his co-workers,
and we build the rest.
And the family?
One younger brother, who he's pretty
much raised on his own.
It's perfect.
Though it is doubtful
that anyone sleeps very well in D.C.
tonight a certain calm has now settled
over the streets of Capitol Hill
after an unprecedented series
of terror attacks left people
all over the country shaken
and demanding answers.
In her speech,
President Taylor went a long way...
Morning.
Pour yourself some orange juice.
I'm not really very hungry.
Sit down,
eat some breakfast for once.
It's unhealthy not to.
What are you doing up anyway?
I couldn't sleep.
Listen, I want you to come home
straight after work today.
No dillydallying.
Why?
Just in case.
In case of what?
These attacks, this terrorism,
it's all over the news.
It's not a good day to be a Muslim.
Muslims had nothing to do with it.
Doesn't matter.
Nobody cares, believe me.
Most of the guys at my work think
I'm Puerto Rican anyway.
It's about time.
Come in.
Excuse me, Ms. Taylor.
What is it?
The attorney general asked me
to check in with you.
He is waiting to sign off
on a document
I was told you were reviewing.
Anyone happen to mention to you
what this document is about?
No, I imagine they wouldn't.
It's a secret,
highly classified.
Not that I give a damn.
It's a get-out-of-jail-free card
for Jonas Hodges,
the bastard responsible
for my brother's death,
and so many others.
I don't understand, ma'am.
Mr. Hodges died in the hospital.
I wish that were the case, but no,
and once the A.G. signs
this witness protection agreement,
Hodges is going to live out his days
in comfort and anonymity
while my brother lies in his grave
in Arlington Cemetery.
Does that sound like justice to you?
No, ma'am, it does not.
And yet my mother saw fit to reward
this monster for his cooperation.
I'm sure it was a difficult decision
for the president to make.
Not difficult enough.
My mother may be able to live with it,
but I'm not sure I can.
I have seen the guilty walk free
many times.
I understand
your anger and frustration,
and I am genuinely sorry.
Tell the A.G.
I've reviewed the agreement
and we can move ahead.
Thank you, ma'am.
Is there anything else
that I can do for you?
Other than kill Jonas Hodges, no.
I'm sorry, Aaron.
I didn't mean that.
I was just venting.
- Hello?
- Martin?
It's Olivia Taylor. Did I wake you?
Well, as a matter of fact, yes.
What time is it?
Almost 4:00.
Actually I didn't expect
to catch you at home.
I thought you were in Florida doing
opposition for the Gainor campaign.
No, that didn't really work out.
Why not?
Let's just say
my methods were a little hardball
for the governor's taste.
What can I do for you, Olivia?
You heard about the attack?
Yeah, I watched your mother's address
to the nation. Really impressive.
She continues to surprise,
doesn't she?
Listen, I need your help.
- Can we meet?
- Now?
What's this about, Olivia?
I can't talk about
it over the phone.
It's the middle of the night, you know?
You got to do better than that.
We were in a dive
hotel bar in Atlanta,
right after we picked Hayworth
to be the running mate on the ticket.
There was an issue regarding his abuse
of a certain prescription drug,
and a local reporter who couldn't
be persuaded to shut up about it.
I remember,
you turned to me and said
there was no problem
that couldn't be handled or eliminated.
I was drunk.
You were serious.
You're right. We shouldn't be talking
about this over the phone.
How soon can you be
at the White House?
How's 15 minutes sound?
Good.
- You done with that?
- I'm not familiar with these commands.
You don't want to boot
the subnet with server 2.
It has a faulty bus that we weren't able
to fix before you guys impounded it.
Maybe you'd like to take over.
Only if you want it to work right.
I don't like this either.
- Is there a problem?
- There is.
I'm not comfortable doing this.
I agreed to it, but I don't like it.
What exactly aren't you
comfortable with?
The Bill of Rights being violated,
for one,
so if you're gonna be doing
anything grossly illegal, please...
We'll make sure we notify you
so you can leave the building.
Hello, Big Brother.
If you think your need to complain
is more important than the lives
of the people who count on us,
go whine somewhere else!
- Jack, it's okay.
- No, it's not okay!
President David Palmer
recommissioned these servers
because he felt it was vital
to national security.
President Palmer made the call.
Is that gonna be
good enough for you?
- Answer me!
- Yes.
There's something wrong.
He said President Palmer.
He meant Taylor.
He said it twice.
What is this now?
Probably a fuse.
Here, you do what
you can to finish up.
I'm gonna go check the box.
Keep your mouth shut
and no one gets hurt.
Who are you? What do you want?
- Shut up!
- What did you do to my brother?
One more word,
I put a bullet in your brain.
Understand?
- You understand?
- Yes!