Colonel Dubaku, we are just
leaving the township now, sir.
- How many do you have?
- Five.
- Only five?
- By the time we got to the field,
- most of the boys were gone.
- I need soldiers, not excuses.
I will bring some more, sir, I promise.
Just bring them to me.
You will learn to fight like men.
Of that, I have no doubt.
This...
will make you strong, little soldiers.
This will make you free.
Come.
Take it.
How does it make you feel?
Powerful, yes?
Come.
Your mothers and your fathers...
they have made you weak,
but General Juma...
he will make you strong.
He will make you strong
so you can take back the country
from the government
and the traitors that work for them...
like this cockroach here!
This cockroach
who works for the government
and their white masters...
They have taken our land.
But soon, all that will change.
Soon, all the land
will belong to the people again.
Soldier...
you must buy our freedom
with the blood of this cockroach.
And you know what we do to cockroaches.
Kill the cockroach.
Kill the cockroach!
Episode 7x00
"Redemption"
VO By:
Kasius, Mkn,
Gaillots et ¤AkaZab¤
[Sub-way.fr]
{\The following takes place
between 3:00 pm and 5:00 pm}
I thought I told you to turn up
the air-conditioning.
All right, sir, I do.
- But we need another player.
- Find somebody else.
Who? Tell me, Willie,
who can handle the ball better than you?
- That's right, no one.
- We're not supposed to go to town
- without Mr. Benton.
- He worries too much. So do you.
Hey, Desmond.
Hurry or the bus will leave. Come on.
- Let's go.
- You're not my father.
I'm your brother,
and you'll do what I say.
Fine, then.
The truck is here!
I wasn't stealing it. I swear.
I was just looking.
Forgot these.
Very pretty. For a woman, yes?
I was gonna give it
to my daughter one day.
You have a daughter?
Where did you get it?
Rajasthan.
India.
- You ask a lot of questions.
- That's what Mr. Benton says.
I bet.
When were you there?
- Last summer.
- Before you came here?
- And before that, where were you?
- Different places.
When are you going home?
I'm not going home.
Listen, I told the boys I'd help them
unload the truck.
- If you want that, you can have it.
- Really?
Really.
You're gonna have to give me back
my knife though.
Go on.
Hey, Willie.
The supply truck's here.
- Boys could use some help.
- Look what Jack gave me.
- Very nice.
- It's from India.
Jack, this is Frank Tramell.
He's the ambassador's
chief political officer.
I know who he is.
He left some messages for you
to come at the embassy.
I got his messages.
- What's going on, Jack?
- I'll tell you.
A Senate subcommittee has questions
about the illegal detention
and torture of certain prisoners
in Mr. Bauer's custody.
I have a subpoena requesting you
to appear, and it's way past due,
so consider yourself served.
I told the boys I'd help them
unload the truck. Excuse me.
Failure to comply to a subpoena
is a federal offense, Mr. Bauer.
- You are bound by law to respond.
- Then give them my response.
If they want me back in Washington,
they can come and get me.
The ambassador said that you and Bauer
were in Special Forces together.
- How long has he been here?
- A few months.
He never mentioned a subpoena?
He's been ducking it for a year,
across three different continents.
Washington is leaning
on the ambassador to deliver him.
And now, the ambassador's
leaning on you.
If Bauer doesn't come back to the States
on his own, they'll come for him.
That would be a mistake.
You're doing God's work here, Carl.
Between malaria and the wars,
these kids never had a chance.
Now you're giving them a decent life.
It'd be a shame if the funding dried up.
- Don't threaten me, Frank.
- I'm just giving you the facts.
You're his friend.
Talk some damn sense into him.
There he is,
the mighty warrior who traded his gun
for a wheelbarrow.
Why are you here?
To do penance for all your sins?
You don't want to talk about it.
I don't blame you.
Careful, don't drop her.
The government won't be able
to hold out against us for long.
Except we have more weapons
than soldiers who can use them.
We need to overrun
the main garrison from the west.
We have minefields here and here.
Then I'll bring you more little soldiers
to clear them. Do not worry.
Our father would be
really proud, Youssou.
Very proud.
You'll have your little soldiers.
- This is Colonel Dubaku.
- Hodges here.
I just heard
some troubling news, Colonel,
that your recruiting numbers are,
are still coming up a little short.
I want you to know, my offer stands.
I've got personnel standing
by right across the border.
- They can be deployed within the hour.
- That won't be necessary.
Do some thinking now.
I'm offering you
professional soldiers, not children
that you haven't had time to train.
You provided the weapons.
- We will fight our own war.
- Well,
- Well, it's your country.
- It will be soon.
Is there anything else, Mr. Hodges?
Tell General Juma to give me a call
- when he gets there, will you?
- I'll let him know.
Good.
That's one hard-nosed son of a bitch.
It is his country.
But I'm paying for it.
I don't want those transactions
traceable,
Mr. Nichols.
Not by the SEC, the IRS,
or any of my ex-wives.
You understand me, don't you?
John, what do you want me to tell you?
You've got to hang in there
and be patient, my friend.
Yes, I know, I know.
Hold on, hold on.
Stop, stop, we got caught by the margin.
It's going to turn around.
Yes, yes, it is.
Yes, it is.
Yeah, you've got to give it time
And just... yeah, be patient.
Yeah. Okay.
Yes, yes. Okay, all right.
Bye-Bye.
- Yeah?
- Would you come in here please?
- Who's that guy?
- A client.
I need you to close out
Abu Dhabi and Eritrea.
Burn the records and bury the ashes.
- Go.
- Yeah!
- Can i have a word?
- Yeah.
Willie, go on out to the truck.
Pick up another load.
I think you should take a look at this.
I don't need to.
I know what it says.
Don't worry, Carl.
I'll be gone by dark.
I'm not asking you to leave, Jack.
I'm asking you to have a conversation.
Tramell says this subpoena's been
chasing you for over a year now.
It's going to catch up
with you sometime.
I'm not going back.
I'm not saying you should.
But a year's a long time
to spend looking over your shoulder.
A lifetime of that's
going to drive you out of your mind.
Whatever I've done,
I've paid for in full.
All I've got left is my freedom. I'm not
letting them take that away from me.
"Freedom."
What kind of freedom is this, Jack?
- You're running away.
- What do you want from me, Carl?
I want you to trust me, Jack.
I am your friend.
I'm sorry.
When you called me up
for the first time in what,
ten years,
I hoped...
You were maybe looking for something
more than just a place to stay...
Trying to find a way
to make some sense of it all.
It's a normal impulse.
Especially for people like us.
Yeah, except you found
what you were looking for.
Yeah.
I just meant it's different for me.
You know, I'm not so sure
I have found what I was looking for.
But I have found a
way to live with myself.
It took a long time.
The first thing I had to do
was stop running.
I meant what I said, Jack.
You can stay here.
Don't worry about Tramell.
The State Department's
not the only place with money.
I appreciate what you're trying to do,
Carl, but this is my problem.
I'm not gonna let it become yours.
What you've done with this place...
the school, what you've done
for the boys is worth protecting.
You and I both know
it will be better
for everyone if I leave.
Sorry, Jack.
Me, too.
Thank you, Carl.
Always.
Yeah.
You're spreading rumors.
You'll start a panic over nothing.
- They're not rumors. It's the truth.
- You are just a boy.
You do not know you are talking about.
Juma is killing our children.
The United Nations
has no evidence of that.
What do you know?
This isn't even your country, huh?
What's going on?
Thomas is talking nonsense.
He's spreading rumors about Juma.
"Rumors"?
They are not rumors.
Juma's soldiers have been crossing
the border and stealing our children.
Juma has no soldiers,
and he has no weapons.
- Everyone knows that.
- My cousin is missing.
He went to the market yesterday,
and he has not returned.
Then it was gun-runners who took him.
Or someone from the diamond mines.
My brother is in town with James.
You see that, hmm?
Now you have the boy all worried.
He should be worried.
We should all be worried.
Stop it! Both of you.
Finish up work. I'll go to town and
see if I can find out what's going on.
Fine.
But you are wasting your time.
I thought I told you kids not
to go into town without telling me.
Desmond never listens
to anyone but Desmond.
- Where'd he go?
- Playing football.
There's a field, just past the bridge.
- I'll be back soon.
- Benton!
You're not seriously worried
about all of this, are you?
If Juma was making trouble,
we would have heard something, no?
Probably. But this is Sangala.
I'm not taking any chances.
- What'd you think that was, huh?
- Nothing.
- What'd you say "nothing"?
- Nothing. Now, you're going to cry?
He's so powerful, guys.
Give him a hand.
You just threw the ball away...
Fire! Fire!
Run!
You are now soldiers
in the People's Freedom Army.
You will all have the honor of fighting
the imperialists until
we have taken back our land.
Samuel tells me you are from
the American school in Okavango.
These Americans make our people slaves.
But we will free you.
And we will free the other
children so they can become soldiers.
Take them.
- Tell me your name.
- Sive.
- Louder.
Are you a baby, Sive?
I asked you a question.
Are you a baby?
- No.
- Good.
Because we need soldiers, Sive,
not babies who wet themselves.
Now stop crying,
or I will stop you myself.
Commander!
Put them in the truck!
Lest Go.
What are you doing?!
Idiot!
They are no good to us dead!
With the inauguration
less than two hours away,
President Daniels is scheduled
to meet with his successor
here at the White House
to review final details
for the transfer of power.
Their respective transition
teams have been working together
for several weeks to
ensure a smooth turnover.
Stop looking at me like that.
- Shouldn't you be getting dressed?
- We've got time.
I need to talk to you, Rog.
Chris?
- I think I might be in trouble.
- Okay.
- Are you using again?
- That's not what this is about.
You didn't answer my question.
I can't...
I can't really talk on the phone, okay?
I was hoping that I could...
I could meet up with you face-to-face.
Now?
Hang on a sec, Rog.
- Chris?
- I know, I know, it's terrible timing.
Believe me, I know.
But I wouldn't be asking
if it wasn't really important.
I got to leave in 45 minutes, man.
- I can be there in 20.
- Chris...
I am not gonna stay long.
I swear, Rog. Just please.
Do this for me?
Fine, but I'm out of here in 45 minutes.
Thank you. Thank you.
You're letting Chris
come here right now?
He's having some kind of relapse or
something. What am I supposed to do?
Exactly.
What are you supposed to do?
Make sure he calls his sponsor.
- I don't know.
- This is so Chris.
He's been a friend
for a really long time.
He got me my job.
Which, if he hadn't.
- Stop it.
- I wouldn't have met you.
Don't do this.
Just don't be late for
your mother's inauguration,
okay?
Madame President.
- Not yet.
- This way.
- How are you feeling?
- Excited.
- Nervous.
- You should be.
In a few hours, you're going to be
the most powerful person in the world.
As if you're not already
hard enough to live with.
- Ma'am. Mr. Taylor.
- Tom.
The president apologizes he could
not be here to greet you in person,
- but something urgent has come up.
- Something urgent?
Whatever it is, Tom, it's going
to land on my desk in about two hours.
Could I just have a moment?
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be. Go ahead.
Our embassy in Sangala just
got word of an imminent coup.
- How imminent?
- Very.
- Where's the president now?
- He's in the telepresence suite.
He's on a secure line
with Prime Minister Matobo.
Juma is moving his forces
toward the capitol as we speak.
This video was taken moments ago.
Mr. Prime Minister,
this news has caught us all by surprise.
But our priority here
in Washington is to ensure
the safety of you and your family.
My priority is to defend
my country from this monster Juma.
And the only way that
can happen is if you accelerate
the military assistance your congress
has already pledged to us.
Unfortunately, I'm not in
a position to make that happen.
Certainly not today.
What about your successor?
Will she be in a better
position to help us?
I'm afraid I can't speak for her.
- Will you excuse us for a moment?
- Yes, of course.
You were right, sir. Taylor does
want to weigh in on this.
- Where is she?
- Just outside.
I'm sorry, Mr. Prime Minister,
but I have to cut this short.
The president-elect is waiting for me.
Please, sir, convey to her
my request for military assistance.
I'll do that.
Mr. President.
Senator Taylor.
Tom told me what's happening in Sangala.
- It is a damn tough situation.
- Yeah, I don't understand.
How could Juma raise an army
without our getting wind of it?
We disarmed him three years ago.
The UN's been monitoring the situation.
Not closely enough, apparently.
Then you have no idea
who's supplying him?
All we know is,
Juma's secured some fairly
advanced weapons systems, which is why
Prime Minister Matobo
is asking for our military assistance.
- And what did you tell him?
- The truth: It's not a viable option.
You don't agree.
We have troops in the region.
A show of force might make Juma blink.
And if it doesn't,
we get caught up in another civil
quagmire halfway around the world.
Now, that is a hard sell.
Especially when there's nothing
in Sangala worth protecting.
No natural resources,
no substantial economic ties,
nothing that threatens
our national security.
The last time Juma made a power grab,
he ignited a tribal war
that killed tens
of thousands of civilians.
Our involvement could avert a genocide.
And this war will be tragic, too.
But it isn't our war.
Which is why I've ordered
the ambassador to begin evacuating
all non-military nationals.
I think that's a mistake.
I don't want any Americans caught in
the crossfire when Juma starts shooting.
Closing our embassy sends a signal
to the world that we are willing
to sell out
a democratic ally to a war criminal.
I appreciate your idealism.
I can't say the same for your cynicism.
Let's talk...
after you've been sitting
in my chair for a while.
And until then,
we still have
some transition business to go over.
So, I suggest we get started.
Send in Tom Lennox.
Desmond?
Desmond.
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes!
Stay with me, Desmond.
Stay with me.
Open your eyes. Open your eyes!
Do not go to sleep!
Do you understand?
Do not go to sleep.
Good lad.
Don't go to sleep.
It's not heavy.
I can carry it.
I want to go with you.
Me and my brother Desmond, too.
We can carry your
things and work for you.
- Why not?
- Because you can't.
I'm going alone.
People who like to be alone are witches,
my grandfather says.
Well, there you go.
Your grandfather wouldn't be happy if
you left here with a witch now,
- would he?
- He would want me to go to America.
His favorite was Elvis Presley.
I'm not going to America.
- Where are you going, then?
- I don't know yet.
I don't know yet is better than here.
You sure about that?
Here doesn't seem so bad to me.
Mr. Benton is very nice, but there
are too many ghosts walking around.
Ghosts?
My mother,
my father and my three sisters.
They live in the bush
and come out at night,
but you wouldn't see them
because you arepoo-mui.
- Poo-mui?
- A white person.
Willie, you and I are friends, right?
I want you to do me a favor as a friend.
I want you to stay here with Mr. Benton
and help take care of the other boys.
Will you do that?
- You promise?
- Promise.
Okay.
Thank you.
Benton's on Direct Connect.
He says he needs to talk to you.
James is dead, Desmond's been shot.
- What happened?
- Juma's raising an army.
Desmond says they're
headed for the school.
They're coming for the boys, Jack.
You got to get them into the shelter.
- Thomas knows where it is.
- How many guns are coming?
Maybe a dozen. I don't know. You have
to hold them off till I get there.
Carl, you need to call the embassy.
Get them to send some marines out here.
I've been trying. I can't get through.
Jack, go into my room.
You'll find what you need
in a locker under my sink.
The key's on top of the cupboard.
- How far out are you?
- Maybe five minutes.
Jack, don't let them take my kids.
- Don't let them take the children.
- Carl, I won't.
Everybody!
Everybody, I want you to listen. I want
you to go to the shelter with Thomas.
- He's gonna take you there now.
- What's going on?
I don't have time to explain. Just go
with Thomas, and ring the bell. Now!
What about my brother?
Your brother's with Mr. Benton.
Everybody, follow me!
Juma's men are coming.
Do you have a weapon?
How do you know it's just not another
rumor? Do you have a weapon or not?
If they are coming, I will talk to them.
- They will listen to me.
- Save your helmet for the parade.
Two of our boys have already been shot!
The United Nations remains
neutral in this matter.
Still want to talk to them?
I didn't think so.
Why don't you go hide in
the shelter with the other children?
- Are you the last?
- Yeah.
Wait!
Wait for me.
Find the boys. Find them!
Fire!
Do not kill him yet.
Not until he tells us
where the children are hiding.
Stay here. Stay here.
- Where are you going?
- I'll be back in a bit.
- U.S. citizens only.
- I have a sister in Chicago.
- She has a job.
- She needs to sponsor you.
By then, it will be too late.
My husband died fighting Juma.
Juma will kill me.
He will kill my child.
I'm sorry.
Whatever you want me to do for you,
I will do.
Please,
just take me from here.
Anything at all.
I can't.
- I'm sorry.
- Sir, it's Carl Benton.
Please don't let them
kill my baby, please!
Please!
Benton? I've been trying
to get through to you.
- Yeah, our lines are overloaded.
- Juma's men are here.
- They're raising an army.
- We know.
You know?
We don't know how he managed
to pull it off. No one saw it coming,
but he's got soldiers
and they're moving in on the capital.
They're here right now, Frank.
They're at my school.
You have to send some marines to help.
Well, I can't spare any. They're all
being deployed for the evacuation.
Evacuation?
The orders came down from the president.
We're rolling up all US nationals.
We already started ferrying
people to the border.
Frank, look,
I've got 14 kids hiding in a shelter,
and one is gonna bleed to death
if he doesn't get medical attention.
Look, if you want us to get you out,
you need to get here on your own.
The last chopper's leaving in an hour.
Frank, don't...
don't strand me like this, please.
My hands are tied, Carl.
- Please.
- I'm sorry.
Damn it!
I'm running out of
ways to ask the question.
Where are the children?
You're wasting your time.
They're not gonna find anything.
I already told you they're not here.
You're lying.
No, I'm not.
If you want to find
soldiers for your army,
you're gonna have
to look somewhere else.
Where...
are the children?
I told you... I don't know.
I will keep doing this
until you beg me to kill you.
But I won't kill you even then.
Not until you tell me...
what I want to know.
I'll show you where the kids are.
Tell me.
I need to show you.
They're in an underground shelter.
You will tell me where this shelter is.
Okay, okay, okay.
About 200 meters up the footpath.
Behind the tree line
there's a wooden hatch
under a mound of dirt.
Get the children.
I'll stay here with him.
Don't worry.
Once I have these children,
I will kill you quickly.
- You all right, Jack?
- Yeah.
The kids are in the shelter.
How is Desmond?
He's lost a lot of blood.
The border's five hours from here.
I don't think he's gonna make it.
I'll try and get him to the embassy.
They've started evacuating already.
How are you gonna get the kids asylum?
They're not U.S. nationals.
I've got sponsorship papers.
Tramell's gonna let them in,
but I have to go now, Jack.
The last chopper leaves in an hour.
- You all right?
- Go!
Good luck.
Stay here.
Jack may need our help.
And if they catch you, they
will make you tell them where we are.
You are endangering the rest of us.
We wouldn't have been in danger if
you'd done something about Juma
instead of looking the other way.
All right.
Everyone out.
Quickly.
Go to the bus, quickly.
Thomas, go get Desmond.
He's in the jeep by the
end of the footpath, all right?
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Go to the bus, go to the bus.
- Go to the bus.
- Where is my brother?
- Thomas is gonna get him.
- Then he's all right?
He will be, he will be.
Go to the bus.
Quickly, quickly.
Desmond.
It's not as bad as it looks.
On the bus. Move.
Quickly. Quickly.
Solenz?
Where are you going?
I told Mr. Bauer before.
The United Nations remains
neutral in this conflict.
A UN escort might help
us get where we need to go.
Solenz!
Let him go.
He's just trying to save his own ass
because he knows
the children are a target.
You're gonna need my help, Carl.
Juma's men are gonna set up roadblocks,
checkpoints all the way into the city.
I got one of the soldiers'walkies.
We can use it to try and avoid them.
Jack, you won't have to
go anywhere near the embassy.
Just help me get the kids to the city.
You can head to the border from there.
Thank you, can you take it easy, please?
- Just keep your hands where I can see.
- I thought told you he's expecting me.
Rog, can you call your
watchdog off, please?
Agent Vossler, he's a friend of mine,
you can let him in.
Your friend's jacked up on something.
I'll take care of it.
It's all right.
- I'll be outside.
- Thank you.
Look, man, I know that my timing right
now must, you know,
suck,
so thank you.
It's just, I'm...
I think I'm in a little
bit of trouble here, so...
What kind of trouble?
Coke, pills?
You know what, don't
get all righteous on me, Rog, okay?
I seem to remember most nights
you party me under the table.
- That was a long time ago.
- Yeah, not that long ago.
All right,
you got five minutes, so talk fast.
A couple months ago,
Nichols calls me into his office,
says he wants me to
manage a special project.
- Special project?
- Yeah. That's what he calls it.
He says that he knows that I've taken
some serious hits in the stock market,
and, he's gonna give me
a chance to recover my losses.
I mean, the money he paid me...
It was crazy.
All I had to do was keep my mouth shut.
What did he have you do?
You know, open a few offshore accounts,
move a bunch of money in and out,
that type of thing.
So, you helped Nichols
embezzle money from his own firm?
Yeah, that's what I thought
I was doing at first, but, Rog,
three days ago,
recognized the prefix
on one of the accounts.
It's something the Justice Department
has red-flagged for traders to report,
do a little digging
and...
... turns out that the...
the account holder
is on the terrorist watch list.
I know, it's crazy, and it's
all getting a little too weird for me.
This morning, there was this
creepy guy in Nichols'office who...
Look, I don't know what he's doing.
I don't want to have
anything to do with it.
I'm willing to turn state's evidence.
Good, you should go to the FBI.
Man, I was just thinking that...
I could probably cut a much better deal
if we take this directly
to your mother, you know.
You want my mother
to clean up your mess?
Chris, what do you
expect me to say to that?
What do I... I don't know, Rog.
How about...
"I'm sorry to hear
that you're in trouble,
"but you're a friend of mine,
and I'm gonna do whatever
I can do to help you out."
Do you even have any evidence?
Nichols asked me
to destroy some records.
I didn't do it.
I...
I sent them to my hard
drive at home instead.
They're coded, but,
you know, they're probably traceable.
- Hello, Chris.
- Hey, Sam,
- you look great.
- Thank you.
We really need to leave now.
We're already pushing it.
Agent Vossler's in the car waiting.
I'll meet you there.
I'm right behind you.
- See you at work later?
- Right.
- I have to go.
- I know, I know, I know.
Look, if I forward you these records,
will you at least
show them to your mother?
I'm not talking to anybody
until I see them for myself.
Okay, all right, that's...
Look, Rog,
thank you. Just, can you check
your e-mail in one hour?
Clean yourself up, okay?
16 mortar teams supported
by 20 forward observers.
Make sure we all have
the same encryption codes.
And have a backup in case the
government tries to jam communication.
Sir, General Juma is here.
Welcome home, General.
Colonel Dubaku.
Look what you've built here.
Our American friends
have been very helpful.
- Did they send us the howitzers?
- Yes.
We have them in position about
20 kilometers from the capitol.
We can hit any target in the city.
All we need is your order
to begin the bombardment.
Sir...
one of our checkpoints.
Excuse me, General.
Colonel, this is Lieutenant Kintu,
checkpoint delta.
We have a man in custody,
a UN relief worker.
He was driving to his base, but
we have detained him for questioning.
He says he has information
about your brother.
What sort of information?
He says your brother is dead, sir.
Your brother and his men... they were
ambushed at the American school.
He says that he can help us
find the man who killed your brother.
I'll be right back.
I managed to stop the bleeding,
but Desmond's fever is spiking.
If we don't get him to a hospital soon,
he's going to go into shock.
We're five kilometers from the city.
I'm really sorry about the school.
I know how much you put into it.
Just a bunch of cement and 2x4s, right?
What the hell was I thinking?
Letting myself believe that
things were finally different here,
that this country had turned a corner.
The bus is from the American school.
They are heading into
the city from Okavango.
There is only one
of two roads they can go.
I am seeing patrols on both.
This is Patrol One, sir.
We have not seen a bus
matching that description.
- Where is your position?
- Heading east,
one kilometer west of Okavango Junction.
Jack, they're right in front of us.
Everybody, hold on.
Hold on.
What is it?
A rebel patrol.
Carl, we can't get back on that road.
Follow the river.
If we follow the river.
It leads into the city.
Desmond will not make it that far.
Then you help him, Thomas,
but we're not getting back on that road.
- Where are we going?
- We're going to walk to the embassy.
Let's go, quickly, quickly.
Hurry up.
The Decision Book.
Master protocols for the command
and control of our nuclear arsenal.
I never knew how much I
didn't know till I read that book.
Are the gold codes in here?
Not yet.
Dan Wilcox will deliver
them to your designate.
All right, then.
If we're finished here,
I should get going.
Join me for a drink.
A toast to your administration.
As much as I'd like to, it's
still a little early in the morning.
You sure?
To your administration.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Please extend my gratitude
to your transition team
for all they've done.
You know what the
talking heads are saying?
They're saying that I lost this election
because I didn't want to win it.
They're saying that...
my heart wasn't in it.
What about you?
Me?
Her is dead, sir.
I don't believe there's
a simple answer to that question.
You are right.
Nothing about this job lends
itself to simple answers, just...
jagged edges and moving parts.
Most you won't even see coming
till they've smacked you in the head.
So...
... be careful,
Madame President.
See you at the inauguration.
- Are you all right?
- I'm not sure yet.
We just got word of a coup in Sangala.
Daniels has ordered the embassy
to evacuate without even consulting me.
- Is it the right call?
- Right or wrong
he should
have brought me in on the decision.
Maybe he's still bitter
about the election.
Noah Daniels isn't that vindictive.
You think he has a reason for pulling
out of Sangala before you take office?
Maybe.
I'll call Ethan from the car.
If Daniels is hiding anything about
Sangala, he'll be able to dig it up.
It's definitely the bus from Okavango.
They were here not too long ago,
at least a dozen boys.
I don't care how many boys.
How many men?
Just Benton, or is he with
that bastard that killed my brother?
There were two men.
Along the river would
be their fastest route.
Good.
Colonel Dubaku.
I am sorry to hear about your brother,
but I need you here.
- Are you ordering me to stay?
- Our campaign is just beginning,
and you are critical to its success.
There will be time for you to avenge
your brother after we have taken power.
The man who killed my brother
is heading toward the American Embassy.
They are evacuating within an hour.
That is all the time I have
and all the time I need.
Sir.
Excuse me, General.
Sir, the men are ready, sir.
Is this everything, Mr. Whitley?
You've been stealing financial
records from your office.
Those files are private property,
and I'm here to recover them.
Is this everything?
Look I, I saw something that didn't look
right... took it home to check it out.
- That's probably a mistake.
- Just calm down. Answer my question.
Yeah, that's everything. It's all there.
What about your laptop?
It's... it's in my briefcase
if you want to check it.
Did you make any hard copies?
No, I swear. I...
I barely even looked at those files.
Who have you shown them to?
No one. Nobody.
So...
just erase it and then you take
whatever you want then you leave.
Okay? Are we cool?
Hey, hey, do we look like fools to you?
Do we, do we?
Then don't talk to us like we are.
- Okay.
- Sit down.
Open your shirt, Mr. Whitley.
- Why?
- Your shirt.
- What are you doing?
- You're going to tell us
everything you know.
And we'll know if you're lying.
Just leave it alone, okay?
Chris asked me not to tell anyone.
- I... I am not anyone.
- Come on, Sam.
- I don't trust him.
- Then trust me.
- We're here, sir.
- You made great time, Edward.
Look, I know that Chris is your friend.
It's just this idea of you
having some kind of secret with him?
I gave him my word
that I wouldn't tell anyone.
You need to respect that, okay?
Okay?
Okay.
Big turnout.
It's crazy...
having a mother who's
the hottest ticket in town.
It took some doing,
but we managed to recover the files.
- What's our exposure?
- Unclear.
We're working on it now.
Find out and call me back.
We're clear.
Stay close. Okay.
There's a road through those
trees that takes us to the city.
We should be safe when we get there.
You follow the riverbed,
that'll take you to the border.
All right?
You'll get there before dark.
- You sure?
- Jack, we'll be fine.
Thanks for helping us get this far.
You take care of yourself, Carl.
Get the kids in the trees.
In the trees, now! Move!
Run, run!
I can't see them.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Take cover! Take cover!
Okay, put us down.
We'll follow them on foot.
Come on.
It's or right, let's go.
Wait, come back. Come back.
Willie, get back here.
Willie, stop! Stop!
Stay there. Don't move.
- Don't come near me.
- I didn't want to leave this.
I know, I know. It's all right.
Go with Thomas.
Willie, it's all right.
Come with me.
Slowly, slowly.
Stay on the path.
Go with the other boys. Go.
Forget it, Jack.
Just go.
Take the kids and go.
Damn it, Jack.
There's nothing you can do.
Okay, it's round, in a gray casing,
with a Cyrillic B, and the number 291
stenciled on the side.
Spring-loaded.
Russian antipersonnel mine, five kilo.
I take my weight off and that's it.
Going to try and disassemble
the trigger mechanism.
- It's got an anti-tamper system.
- That's all right find a workaround.
Even if you had the right tools,
it'd take more an hour to disarm.
Damn it, there's got to be
a kill switch, just let me find it.
- There's no time, Jack. Stop.
- Just give me a second.
It's all right, Jack.
I can die like this.
Just take the kids to the embassy.
- Make sure they're safe.
- Carl, don't do this.
Here, take, take these.
Papers, sponsorship papers.
Give them to Tramell.
Please, Jack, please.
Give me the rifle.
Let me buy you some time, Jack.
Maybe more.
Go ahead with Jack.
- I'll be right behind.
- Mr. Benton!
I'll catch up.
We got to go.
Please, come on, let's go.
I'll tell him.
Colonel,
sir...
we cannot follow them into the city.
It's still under government control.
Since when do you start giving orders?
I spoke to Udo.
He has some men inside the city,
looking for Benton and the other man.
With the children,
they won't be hard to find.
Well, I will find them
and kill them myself,
even if I have to go into the city.
Now, go.
Colonel Dubaku, look.
Who are you?
I'm Benton.
Where's your friend?
Which one?
Where is he?
I don't know what you're talking about.
All right!
He's taking them...
- What?
- He's taking them there.
What are you saying?
- What are you saying?
- He's taking them to...
Bring him to me.
Go to hell.
- What was that?
- Just keep moving.
Keep going.
Come on, move.
How far to the embassy?
Two more blocks that way.
But we only have ten minutes.
Okay, as soon as we get there,
I'm gonna give you all the paperwork.
I want you give that to Mr Tramell. He's
gonna take care everything from there.
Then you're not coming with us?
- Where's Mr. Benton?
- He's not coming.
- Why?
- He's dead.
He was supposed to be behind us!
He said he was coming!
- He lied! Why?!
- Stop it!
- He lied to me. Why?
Mr. Benton did not lie.
He made one promise to all of you boys,
and that was to protect you
and to make sure that you were safe.
Mr. Benton died to make sure
that Juma's soldiers couldn't follow us.
Mr. Benton died to make
sure you could get to the embassy.
sure that you would be safe.
I'm so sorry.
Willie, we have to go.
It's what Mr.
Benton would have wanted.
Okay?
You okay?
Let's go. Come on.
Willie, come on, come on.
It's okay. Come on. Let's go, let's go.
Stop.
Thomas, take the boys,
hide behind the car now. Move. Move.
Get behind the car.
Everybody, now.
Down, down.
Kill the cockroach.
Put the gun down.
I don't want to hurt you.
Just put the gun down.
Willie, wait!
I know you're scared. Just put the gun
down. I'm not gonna hurt you.
Just put the gun down now.
You see those boys?
They're just like you.
I'm trying to get them out
of the country somewhere safe.
Somewhere where no one can
hurt them. You can come with us.
Just put the gun down.
Come on. Just like me. Watch. See?
It's going down.
Like me.
Come with me,
I promise you no one will hurt you.
No one will hurt you.
- Wait.
- Come on, Jack, we have to go!
We have to go now!
Boys!
Come with me now. Come on.
Let's go.
Everybody hold hands.
Come on!
Expecting a call?
This is about Chris, isn't it?
He was supposed to send
me something 15 min ago.
Call him later. Your mother's here.
It's been a long journey,
Madame President.
I'm afraid we're just getting started.
Our Africa group is preparing
a brief on Sangala.
You'll have it on your desk
as soon as you're done here.
- Good morning.
- Good morning. Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Good to see you.
- Good morning.
Thank you so much.
You look beautiful, Madame President.
Thank you, Samantha.
Father.
It's nice to see you on time for once.
- How are you holding up?
- It still doesn't feel quite real.
It will soon enough.
Whitley need some encouragement,
but he told my man everything.
- How much does Roger Taylor know?
- Nothing you need to worry about.
But he knows Nichols was involved.
All he knows is that his desperate,
drug-addicted friend
told him some crazy story.
He's got no evidence.
If he finds Nichols, he could find me.
Not without evidence.
Sir, Whitley's no longer a problem.
We limited the damage.
But you haven't eliminated it.
Keep your eye on Taylor.
Stay together! Stay together!
Sergeant!
I need to see Frank Tramell
he's expecting me!
- Who are you?
- Jack Bauer!
Don't worry, Desmond!
We made it!
We're going to America!
Tramell!
Listen to me, I've got 14
children seeking political asylum.
All of them are R-1 status!
One of them needs urgent medical care!
- Where's Benton?
- He's dead!
Wait! Wait!
I've got their paperwork.
- Show me.
- Keep Desmond up.
There!
Desmond, it's all right.
Just stay with me. Come on!
- They appear to be in order.
- Then open the gate, and let them in!
There's just one small problem.
They need the legal
guardianship of a US citizen.
Guardianship?!
I already told you, Benton is dead!
He died getting these children here!
Then don't let him have died in vain.
Surrender yourself to the subpoena,
and the Ambassador will
waive the issue of guardianship.
Tramell, I am warning you,
leave me out of this.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
We are talking about innocent children.
Whatever happens to them is all on you.
Would really leave these
children out here in the street,
knowing what you do about Juma?!
Damn it, Frank!
They'll be used as cannon fodder!
Or slaughtered in the soccer
stadium for entertainment!
I am giving you the chance
to make sure that doesn't happen!
The choice is yours.
I don't have a choice,
you son of a bitch. Open the gate.
Hold on, boys.
Hold on. Desmond, come on!
You in first, Bauer.
It's all right, Willie. It's all right.
It's all right.
All right,
take him into custody right now.
Let them in! Let them in!
Let them in!
They're with me! Let them in, damn it!
No! Those two are with me, too!
All of them! All of them!
It's all right, Willie. Just go
with them. Go with the soldiers.
Put them on the choppers.
It's all right.
Raise your right hand
and repeat after me.
I, Allison Taylor, do solemnly swear...
That I will faithfully execute
the office of the President
of the United States.
That I will faithfully execute
the office of the President
of the United States.
And will to the best of my ability,
preserve,
protect and defend
the Constitution of the United States.
And will to the best of my ability,
preserve,
protect, and defend
the Constitution of the United States.
- So help me, God.
- Congratulations, Madame President.
- Thank you.
When the founders of our country
boldly declared America's
independence to the world,
they knew that they derived
their power to govern
from three basic human rights:
life, liberty
and the pursuit of happiness.
Today,
we rededicate ourselves
to the preservation
of those inalienable rights.
But even as we carry forth the torch lit
by those great men,
we need to rember,
its light doesn't always
shine as brightly as it should.
It flickers and grows dim
because of apathy,
greed...
and fear.
De Tocqueville said,
"In every democracy,
the people get the government
they deserve."
Today...
I am asking each of you
to help me give you
the government you deserve.
We all share the responsibility
history has placed in our hands.
The future.
Our future.
Depends on it.