Did you find
something out about Kyle?
It looks like it.
I think Kyle may be connected to a murder.
Some hikers found it
near Victor Falls.
The other night, we found Kyle sitting
right next to the spot.
You yourself said that trauma
may have caused his amnesia.
Well, yes it's possible
that he witnesd the attack.
Has he started
to remember anything?
We both know you like him
more than you let on.
That doesn't mean that
I expect this big commitment.
Just the truth.
I bet your family's
searching for you right now.
You didn't just
fall from the sky.
This symbol was on some sort
of security key card we found near the remains.
Does this mean anything to you?
No.
Linda sync FRM
by www.1000fr.com
It was my first dream.
At least the first
I could remember.
My subconscious mind
was weaving a tale of love and loss,
even though my memories
contained no such stories.
I wondered what it meant.
Was it something I had
already experienced...
or simply a vision
of things to come?
I wished to go back
to that moment with Amanda.
I wanted to see
how it would end.
You sure you didn't draw this
after you saw the key card?
No, I noticed these markings
on his drawings well before.
Kyle, why did you
draw this in pieces?
That's how I saw it.
It's possible that fractured
pieces of his past are starting to enter
his consciousness.
I've seen it before
in patients who have trauma-based amnesia.
Everyone was concerned about the images
coming from my head.
I couldn't explain them any more
than I could explain my dream about Amanda.
My mind was doing things the rest of me
didn't understand.
Where you goin', Lori?
Uh, yeah, where you goin', Lori?
The pool?
You know,last time I checked,
looking after Kyle actually
meant looking after Kyle.
But he's busy.
Actually, we're
done here...for now.
Kyle, do you want to go to the pool?
I'm the only girl in America
who has to baby-sit a fully grown teenager.
Take your brother, too,
'cause we have to go
to the high school to register Kyle.
Uhh...choice?
What if I don't want
to go to the pool?
Uh, maybe you don't want
to spend the rest of the day with your summer
reading list, either.
I'll go get my stuff.
Fabulous.
10 years of service
to the company, Tom.
Sorry to see you go.
Time to move on.
Is this your
forwarding address?
Yeah.
Good.
The company likes
to keep in touch,
especially now with Kern
still MIA.
Well, I'm sure
you'll track him down.
Goes without saying.
A friendly reminder:
you know how aggressively
we enforce these confidentiality
agreements?
Yeah.
One more thing.
Your security card.
Of course.
Both of you stay at least
20 feet from me at all times--
close enough I can see
you're in trouble,
far enough away
I can choose to ignore it.
Lori! Come on!
Over here.
And don't drown.
I'll tell you, brother,
give a woman
an ounce of power,
and she'll run
right over you.
Why is Amanda
sitting up there?
She's a lifeguard.
She guards life?
Sorta.
She'll jump in to save you
if you can't swim.
He's, like seriously manorexic.
Eat a sandwich!
Yo, Trager.
What's up?
Are you still mad
at him for lying,
or are you back to the
playing hard to get game?
Not a game. I'm over it.
Really.
So you're not
secretly yearning he'll call you over?
Nope.
And you're not
quietly wishing he'd sit here with you?
Not in the least.
And somewhere deepin your subconscious,
you have no desire to sleep with him
at Preston's party Friday,
even though we both swore
we wouldn't go back to school
with our virginities intact?
My virginity.
Yours hasn't been an issue
for quite some time.
Whatever.
Are you serious?
You're really over him.
I'm done with the whole
friends with benefits thing.
It's not fun anymore.
We're not really friends,
which means we're just benefits,
and if I'm gonna be giving
benefits to anyone,
it should mean something.
Look who's all protective
of her first time.
You've wanted to sleep
with Declan for, like, ever.
I still do, but
I'm not giving it up to some guy
whose idea of fun is crawling
into my bedroom drk at 3:00 in the morning.
Well, we'll just have to find you another
devirginizing opportunity...
like yummity goodness
over there.
Ew.
Hillary.
Fine, I'll take him.
You are so not allowed
to corrupt Kyle.
Why not?
Because it's, like...wrong.
When do we swim?
We don't come here to swim.
We come here
to scope babes.
Babes?
You know. The ladies.
Hot mamas.
Girls with C-cup
Like her.
Good Lord of the Rings.
Is she a friend of yours?
Dude, a chick like that
doesn't know I exist.
So you won't go talk to her?
Talk to her? Are you nuts?
So we come to the pool,
but don't swim.
And we scope babes,
but we don't talk to 'em?
It's a cruel world.
I just live in it.
Did she just--
Don't move.
Lori, my favorite
sister of all time.
No.Come on. Go in the bathroom--
No.
Seriously.
Go in the girls' locker room.
Get the name and number
of the girl in the pink bikini
with the polka dots
on her what-nots.
Her what-nots?
Forget it.
Look, you're gonna
go in there right now,
or I'm gonna yell
"Lori Trager stuffs her bra"
at the top of my lungs.
You are the devil.
Fine, you manipulative
little freak.
He has no records,
no history of schooling?
As I explained,
Kyle's situation is unique.
Certainly is.
But he's exceptionally bright.
You're requesting
a one-on-one tutor.
That's, um--well, that's
an expensive arrangement.
Legally, you're
obligated to provide it.
£¿
?
Are you sure he wouldn't
be better suited for a special-ed program?
He's not disabled.
I'm sure. But to be fair,
high school can be
a very difficult experience
even for the most well-adjusted students.
If this boy is special,
it may not be the easiest
of transitions for him.
I assume you'll
pass our request up the administrative ladder.
Of course.
Good.
Did you find her?
There is one girl in there.
Gorgeous, great body.
She's in the shower right now.
Naked.
That's her.
That's impossible.
Josh, she's a 10.
There is no way a girl
that hot would come within a mile of you.
Get back in there
and find out her name.
It's not her.
Quit messin' around, Lori.
Quit buggin' me, Josh.
Lori Trager stuffs her bra!
Josh Trager
has wet dreams!
You are so dead.
You guys...where's Kyle?
It felt just like my dream.
And just like Josh said,
she came to help me.
Is he okay?
How long was he under?
My whole body tensed and tingled.
I suddenly felt a strange sort of pressure.
Good pressure.
[laughs] No way!
Oh.
Oh!
Kyle, cover up.
Guy had a lot of nerve
implying Kyle didn't belong there.
Hooper's not an educator,
he's a bureaucrat,worried about the bottom line.
He was totally inappropriate.
Well, he's not subtle,that's for sure,
but he has a point.
Hey, honey.
Houston, we have a problem.
What's up?
Funny you should ask.
Rough day?
You want to talk
about what happened...
at the pool?
You mean...
Yeah.
Everybody laughed at me.
And you don't know why?
No.
You never had
an erection before?
Not that I can remember.
Okay, then.
Well, first of all,
you have to understand
that what happened to you
was completely normal.
You just don't typically
want it to happen in public.
Then it's not normal.
No, it is.
It's you body's way of...
telling you how you feel.
In fact...it's a very
honest physical response.
Then why should it be hidden?
Well...
Uh...
Poor Daddy  ??
I ??
Your're good at it ??
You think?
I feel ??
I'm  ??
Trust me¡£There're nothing for £¿£¿
Hi.
Hello.
Is Lori around?
Declan.
Hi.
Thanks, Mom.
You're welcome.
Come in.
So...you're, um...
at my house...
Yeah.
In daylight...
through the front door.
Who'da thunk?
Why?
I didn't see you
leave the pool.
Yeah, I had to bail.
Anyway, Hillary said
you'd be home.
We still haven't covered
the "why" part yet.
I thought you might
want to go to Preston's party on Friday.
Of course. Everyone's going.
No. I meant, um...with me.
Oh.
All this back and forth,
Trager, I'm tired of it.
And I'm sorry for whatever
I did to piss you off.
I think it's time
we went out together--
really went out.
But if you're not into it--
No, I'm into it.
Well, good.
So we'll go?
Yeah.
Cool.
Oh, do you want me to, like,
pick you up, or somethin'?
I can meet you there.
Sounds like a plan.
All right.
Later, Trager.
Later.
Okay, look, I've been on
the other side of that talk.
It ain't pretty.
He said when it happens again
in front of people,
I should think of
something I don't like.
Totally.
I usually go wh zits
and old people.
You?
Grapefruit.
Hmm.
You should know there
are other ways to handle the little problem.
Ta-da.
Charlotte?
No, Charlotte's mine, dude.
You are not ready
for Charlotte.
Meet Ginger.
What do I do with it?
You look at it.
Like at the pool.
Scope babes.
Except when you're here alone,
you can lock your door...
and do...other things.
Is Kyle around?
I feel horrible about
what happened today.
Straight back,
other side of the kitchen.
Thanks.
Hi.
I have to go.
How would you like
to get out of watching Kyle
for a couple hours every day?
I'm listening.
Well, I can make it happen
in exchange for Miss Pink Bikini's digits.
Are we still on that?
Are you interested or not?
Of course.
Hi, Mom.
What do you want?
So Lori and I were thinking,
maybe we shouldn't bring
Kyle to the pool today.
I mean, not after yesterday.
Because of the..."incident"?
No, I was more worried
about the whole drowning thing.
What drowning thing?
Kyle doesn't know
how to swim.
That's no reason he should
miss out on going to the pool.
We should get him lessons.
That's a great idea.
They offer lessons down there.
Couple hours every day.
He'll be swimmin' in no time.
Amanda, your next
leon's here.
Thanks.
She hates me.
Just don't hump her leg,
and you'll be fine.
Hi. You're Ashley, right?
Yeah. Hi.
Hi. Can I talk to you
for a second?
Mission accomplished.
Ditched responsibility,
and paid off a debt,
all at once.
You know, I'd happily
give Kyle swimming lessons.
I'd show him
the breast stroke.
You're seriously
grossing me out.
Okay, prudey.
Please, I am so not a prude.
Ye, just a virgin.
By a very minor technicality.
Besides, I decided you're
right about the sex thing.
You're kidding.
Well, it's not like
I'm waiting for true love,
and the only reason
I've held out this long
is he hadn't done anything
to deserve it.
But if he's
finally stepping up,
there's no reason
why I shouldn't.
So...cup your hand
and pull the water along with you.
You have to float.
Float.
Yeah. You know.
You don't know.
Uh, here.
See?
Let the water hold you up.
Grapefruit.
Her name is Ashley Redmond.
She's your age.
Catholic School.
You better call now and get
the humiliation over with.
Oh, sweet. Thanks.
Whatever.
Hello?
Damn.
Buoyancy.
Strokes.
Breathing.
It all made sense in theory.
Now it was time
to put it into practice.
Where'd he go?
You must be a great teacher.
Hey.
Are you sure you've never
been swimming before?
Yesterday.
That wasn't swimming.
That was drowning.
You don't have
a belly button.
No.
Why not?
I don't know.
And you still don't remember anything
about your life before?
No.
But you can jump off tall buildings
and swim likean Olympic champion.
Josh tnks I'm an alien.
Or Superman.
You're not angry anymore.
I never was.
I just...thought your drawings
were kind of weird.
Why?
There were a lot of me.
I--I draw everything exactly
how I see it in my head.
But you're special.
I can't seem to get you right.
How come?
Seems like there's
something missing.
My mom's gonna be out
tomorrow afternoon.
Come by my house.
I wanna show you something.
Hey. I spoke to
Detective Breen again.
Did he have anything
new about the logo?
Nothing. The logo doesn't
match corporation on record.
And they haven't
been able to decrypt
the computerized strip
on the key card.
Wow, that muste some
sophisticated security system,whatever it's for.
Oh, this worries me, Stephen.
We've no idea what Kyle
might have witnessed.
Well, you're doin' what you can
to help him remember.
Well, maybe now's not the best time
to send him to school.
Oh, please tell me you're not letting
that vice principal get to you.
Well, he's right.
I want to protect Kyle,
not thrust him into another
traumatizing experience.
Don't you thinkhe should try to live
like a normal teenage boy?
I'd feel better
if I believed he was normal.
Tom.
What are you doing here?
Something's been
botherin' me.
I thought we should
have a little chat.
Your key card--
I ran it through the system
to deactivate it,
but the clearance code
didn't match your assignment.
Strae.
That's what I said.
Thought maybe
it was a computer error.
And then, I discovered that Kern
was cleared to that level.
Interesting coincidence,
him being missing and all.
I thought it might be a piece of information
you might find worth something.
Something you might
want me to keep quiet.
Get out.
Think about it.
I have a feeling you don't want the company to know
what you've been up to.
This is my dad's.
He was an artist too.
Not for, like,a living, but...
it was his thing.
Was?
He died last year.
He's what's missing.
Anyways...take a look.
He saw this in his head?
Kind of.
Art is about drawing
what you feel,
not just what you see.
How do you draw a feeling?
It's like piano.
Right now, I'm just
playg notes.
But art is about putting your
whole self into something...
everything you feel.
How do you feel?
Just listen.
I didn't know that I could make a picture
of how I felt inside,
but I really wanted to try.
Hello?
Josh Trager?
Uh...hi?
I saw the caller ID.
Your sister said
I would hear from you.
She did?
I'm totally psyched.
You are?
Are you going to Jeff Preston's
party tonight?
I don't know him,
but everyone goes, right?
Right.
Awesome. So see you there.
Wardrobe crisis?
The usual.
I love that red shirt
you have.
I think I'm gonna go
with the blue.
Josh wants to go to the party.
I know you have a date.
Date? Mom, so '80s.
Okay, whatever you want
to call it.
Anyway,I was gonna say no,
and then he went into this sales pitch
about how it's a rite of passage into high school.
Well, he's sort of rht.
But don't worry.
It's chaperoned.
And I'll look out for him.
Unless he embarrasses me,
in which case I will kill him.
Thank you, Lori.
So, this Declan.
Is he a good guy?
Mmm, most of the time.
Kyle...
you're comin' to the party.
I don't like parties.
You have to come.
Everyone goes.
Even Amanda?
Guaranteed.
Good. I have
something for her.
Great. Bring it.
Get dressed.
Bye, guys.
Kyle, you're not going?
Lori, see you at midnight.
Kyle and Josh, 10:00 or you
won't live to see 10:01.
But--
Go ahead.
Have a good time.
Let's get this over with.
I thought you'd come around.
I underestimated you, Tom.
I never thought the quiet guy
from work would be cap--
member the rules--
no drinking, no puking,outta here by 9:45.
I'll be watching.And I will narc.
I don't see Ashley.
Or Amanda.
I should've knownit was too good to be true.
Oh, there sh
Hi, Josh.
[squeaky voice]Ashley...
[clears throat]Hey.
I'm so glad you made it.I don't know anyone here.
Come on.
I like your shirt.
Thanks.
I was going fornaughty and nice.
[chuckles]It's working.
Yo, Preston.
Oh, hey. What's up, guys?
Great party.
Yeah.
It'd be better if my parentsweren't lurkin'.
But I hid a bunch of beeraround the property,
so help yourselves.
Thanks, man.You know it.
Thirsty?
Always.
Oh, my God.That's funny.
Oh, sweet.
I didn't bring a suit.
Damn. Me, neither.
What doin'?
I don't wanna get my clothes wet.
What are you doing?
Checking forthe hidden cameras.
You're funny.
It's my thing.
Right. Sorry.
Why are you sorry?
[giggling]You're hot.
It's warm outside.
No, I mean hot hot...
like smokin'.[gig]
Sister Mary Lourdes woulddefinitely not approve.
What she doesn't knowwon't hurt her.
This is totally fun.
When I saw you at the poolthe other day,
I was hoping you'd come talk to me.
You were?
I thought you were cute.
You did?
There aren't anyother boys at my school
to compare you to...but yeah.
What the hell is going on?
Mr. and Mrs. Preston?
Get out of there right now.
[exhales sharply]Honey, come on.
Young man?
I can't.
Zits. Old people.
I'm gonna count to 3.
1...
2...
Grapefruit!
So,
Yeah.
Um, was that your, uh--
Yeah. Yours?
No.
I mean, I haven't done it a ton,
but it--it wasn't my first.
It gets better.
Well, I'd better go back to the party.
Everyone thinks I'm a slut just because
of the eighth gradefield trip to Tacoma.
But I just want a sweet guyto cuddle with.
Is that so wrong?
You feel nice.
Hillary made my body feel good.
But just like the girls in Joss maganes,
something didn't feel right.
There was a piece missing.
Hillary, get off of him.
Go away.
God, you slut.Ow!
I told you to leave him alone.
What are you so worried I'll do?
Gee, I wonder.
Do you really think I'm such a super is
You've held out on one thing,
and you act likethe freakin' purity police.
That's not what I'm--
I'm tired of it.
Poor Declan.
I never should havetold him to ask you out.
What?
I told him you weren't gonna put out anymore
unless he stepped up.
But that's--She didn't say it like that.
That--that's not what--
Don't talk to me.
You two totally did it,didn't you?
Who knew after all this time you'd be so easy?
Declan, man, dude, you gotta come check this out.
It's hilarious.Come here.
Eh, eh, outta the way.
Still in the non-speaking part of the evening?
How could you let him go to that party?
Well, we let Josh go,and he's younger.
I'm not worried about Josh being able to hand himself.
And I'm not worried about Kyle.
But he is--
Listen, Nicole, you need to ease up on the reins
just a little bit.
Kyle needs to get out there and experience life.
He needs to have it knock him around a little bit.
We took him in so we could protect him.
Not by keeping him in a bubble.
All right, look.
I realize that he's your patient.
Yes.
But it's hard for me to stay clinical about him.
Well, of course it is.
So let's handle him like we handle Josh and Lori.
The reason they're well-adjusted
is because we treat them with respect.
We let 'em go out there and make their mistakes,
and they know we're herewhen they need us.
We need to give Kyle the same chance.
I hope you're right.
It had to happen sometime.
Everyone ??
None ??
What're you doning ?
Hidding??
From what  ??
Everyting ??
Everybody ??
So you finally tapped that, huh?
No, man.
She's not like that.
Seeing Amanda, I realized something.
I had been struggling to understand
what my mind and body were trying to tell me.
And right then, I knew what it was.
Everything was working together,
sending a message to my heart.
Kyle.
Amda. There you are.
Hey.
[Man]We were waiting for you.
Oh, Charlie, this
is my neighbor Kyle.
Kyle, this is Charlie,my boyfriend.
Hey. Nice to meet you, man.
And now my heart was sending a message
to the rest of my body--
So you guys live acrossthe street from each other.
pain.
[Amanda] Uh, next door.Yeah, he just moved in.
[Charlie]Oh, wow. Cool.
Life is a puzzle.
Every piece fits together to create who we are,
what we do, how we feel.
Every experience shapes us
into who we will eventually become.
I began as a blank slate.
Maybe my hidden memories tell a different story.
Maybe I hold the key to a mystery
even greater than that of my past.
I've been so eager to remember,
to grow up
and experience life like Lori and Josh...
but in that one moment,
I wish I could go back to that blank slate...
when life was...easier.
I think they wished for it, too.
Ready?
Let's go home.
Okay.
Linda sync FRM
by www.1000fr.com