liukan sync FRM
by www.1000fr.com
????
felt familiar.
This place was different...
and so was I.
The school is supposed to
provide one-on-one instruction.
I thought you understood
Kyle's special needs.
Mrs. Trager, I strive
to meet the needs
of every student.
And given Kyle's situation,
a personal tutor
is probably best.
But that is
a costly arrangement,
and I have some
additional concerns.
He spent time at a juvenile
detention center.
That was an
improper placement.
Where he engaged
in an altercation.
Another resident punched him.
Kyle never hit back.
He is currently involved
in a homicide investigation.
As a possible witness.
He still can't
remember anything.
And I am afraid that his memory
issues may become problematic.
Mr. Hooper, Kyle is
an exceptionally bright boy
who is eager to learn.
I think this school would be
lucky to have him.
We have five hours
of testing ahead of us.
We should get started.
I've already tested Kyle.
His I.Q. is phenomenal.
Mrs. Trager, aptitude and I.Q.
are not the same thing.
And since we do not have any
former school records for Kyle,
I can't even consider
a personal tutor
until we determine
his grade level.
What kind of tests
are we talking about?
Well, assuming he's around 16,
I'll administer
the standard tenth grade
placement exams,
and we shall see
how he does.
He's a great kid.
And he's so happy to be here.
[Teacher] Hello, everybody.
I hope your instruments
haven't gathered too much dust
over the summer,
but my guess is
it's the first time
most of them have been
out of their cases since June.
Kyle, there you are.
I have to leave now,
but Mr. Hooper's
gonna give you some tests.
Tests?
Yeah, to see what
you've learned
and  what the school
still needs to teach you.
He loves math.
That's a good place to start.
Thank you.
I'll take it from here.
Okay, so you have
your money for lunch,
and I think you're all set.
Thanks.
You're gonna do fine.
Bye.
All right, Kyle.
Let's get started.
Okay.
Fire up those brains
and check this out, people.
Solve it by the end
of the semester,
you get an automatic "A"
in my class.
A professor at M.I.T.
presented this problem.
It took his students
six weeks to crack it.
Sort of like a mathematical
Mount Everest, if you will.
Trager, comma, Lori.
Discussing the Jacobi
algorithm?
Um...what?
Didn't think so.
Conduct your personal business
on your own time.
And as for wasting mine,
I'll see you after school.
[Woman]
"It was a cold, damp morning.
The mist clung to the ground
like a silver cloak."
Continue with the next
paragraph...Toby.
Pass.
I'm afraid I don't offer
that option.
"Grandfather's hat
was still...
in the gravel--"
"--path...
near the gern--geraniums."
[laughing]
That's enough!
Toby, continue.
From where we left off.
"Near the geraniums he hadn't
finished planting.
"Rich earth was piled
next to a hole he'd prepared,
like a mound of dirt
beside a fresh grave."
This is not math.
We're going to start
with history.
90 minutes for that portion.
I'll check on you then.
[Narrating]
Page after page
of names and dates,
all of them unfamiliar.
1492.
1812.
George Washington.
Marie Antoinette.
I hadn't been taught
anything yet,
but I was expected
to complete a test.
I thought I was here
to ask questions,
not answer them.
That bell again.
Apparently, it rang
at precise intervals,
moving students
at a regular pace.
At least this time
I knew what to do.
Time to find a place again.
In a morning
filled with confusion,
here was something that
spoke to me clearly.
Finally, a test I could pass.
Someone solved it.
[Narrating]
I'd learned to follow
the ebb and flow of students.
But this time, instead of
scattering in every direction,
they all moved
to the same place.
It seemed everyone
was welcome here.
And I thought I might find
a place to belong.
Hey, you.
Whoa, I wouldn't sit there.
Unless you want to be known
as Geekman's friend.
That's what everyone calls me
'cause my last name's Deichman.
Except some people say
"Dykeman," so they might also
think you're Dykeman's friend,
which would make you a lesbian.
Nope.
Whatever. Do what you want.
I can't see?
This is a joke. Right?
Someone told you to sit here?
Very funny!
No. I draw, too.
Shut up.
You do?
[Josh]
See where Kyle's sitting?
Look, if you need five bucks
for lunch--
He's sitting with
L.K. "Dykeman."
And?
That's social suicide.
You're supposed to look out
for him, Lori.
Well, so are you.
Let him sit with your
punk-ass little posse.
So, Lori got, like, ten shades
of pissy and called me a slut,
after her freakazoid
foster brother is groping me.
Like I'd ever go there.
But you've been, like,
salivating over him
since he messed with that cop
at Declan's party.
Well, not anymore.
Look at him.
He's friends with Geekman.
Okay, so do you want to hear
something funny?
Nadine Velasquez,
last period, same shirt.
Laugh riot.
You call her a slut, too?
Come on, Hills.
Truce?
I'm so over fighting.
For reals?
'Cause I'm so over you.
Girls, coming?
You guys, come on.
Should have taken
off the shirt.
He doesn't look like an alien.
I'm telling ya, the stuff
I've seen him do...
I got a whole file.
Right.
So instead of taking over
the world,
he's here in high school?
It's part of his master plan.
To recruit an army of losers
like L.K. Deichman?
[laughing]
Speaking of losers,
how was Schultz this mornin'?
I'm the king of that class.
A bunch of morons
who can't read.
Man, that's pathetic.
[Deichman]
That's the thing
about comics.
The mainstream stuff,
it's pretty cheesy.
[mockingly]
Anime.
It's just a fancy word
for "cartoons."
I like the indie
press stuff...
comics like...
[slurping]
like Diesel Danny...
Tarsus....Vera Zero.
Why do they have
secret identities?
To hide their
amazing abilities.
So they can help people
without freakin' them out.
I mean, this is basic stuff.
How can you not know this?
I don't know.
But what about
George Washington?
Mmm...yeah.
How 'bout him.
Is he a superhero, too?
He's the first president
ever of America.
And Hathor, is she
on another test?
Superheroes aren't real.
What's wrong with you?
Look, seriously, I know
it's your first day and all,
but don't you know anything?
That's why I came here...
to learn.
You came to high school...
That's a good one.
Okay, look, maybe I can
help you.
You get the sushi?
Got the sushi.
[laughs]
I can't believe we have
an hour alone.
Oh, an hour is
barely enough time.
We'll make the most of it.
Are you close?
I'm around the corner, baby.
I'll be waiting.
Nicole?
Uh, hang on. I just
heard something.
Hello?
Stephen, I think someone's
breaking in.
Get out. Now!
[Man] I'll try to make this
as quick as possible.
[Nicole]
My husband has
a security problem.
Nicole!
Oh, Stephen, I was just
gonna call you.
This is Tom from
our security company.
Hello, sir.
What's goin' on?
Well, I was on patrol
and saw someone
break in your window.
Tom scared him off.
Does that belong to anyone?
No.
I'm sure he dropped it.
Probably used the handle
to break the glass.
Any idea who it might be?
No, I'm sorry.
I didn't get a good look.
But there's been
a number of break-ins
in the neighborhood lately.
I've already called
in the incident,
and I'll make sure that
the police are aware as well.
You okay?
I am now.
I'm sorry I scared you.
As long as you're okay.
Yeah.
You just happened
to be driving by?
Yeah. It's a lucky thing, huh?
Now, if I can just
finish up this report,
I'll get out
of your way, okay?
Sure.
This room is...what?
Oh, um...
it's a guest room.
Oh.
Pardon me, but our
records indicate that
all your bedrooms
are upstairs, no?
Well, we have a temporary
foster care situation.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Well, that's nice of you folks
to take someone in.
How's that workin' out?
Fine.
What happens if he comes back?
I'll just drive by
more often, and I'll keep
an eye on the house.
Well, we'd appreciate that.
That's my job.
Thank you.
[gasps]
Gosh! Sorry.
Sure, you are.
I hope I didn't ruin it.
Anything you want to know,
this is the place to find it.
It's like the fortress
of solitude.
More like a good place to nap.
Ah.
Might as well
start with this.
It's like...everything.
Boiled down.
Thank you.
No problem.
Okay.
Look, I guess, um...
I'll see you around.
Kyle?
Amanda.
How's it goin'?
Oh. You remember Charlie.
Hey, yeah, we met
at Preston's party.
Yes, I remember.
Little, uh...light reading?
Listen, uh, I know
it's your first day,
and I remember
when I moved.
It took a lot
of getting used to.
So, if you need anything,
just give me a shout.
Well, uh...okay.
Bye, Kyle.
We'll see you later.
Big talker.
Well, he can be shy,
but he's really sweet.
I could be wrong, but I think
he's got a problem with me.
Hey...who could ever have
a problem with you?
I'm tellin' you,
she was triple-X hot,
totally into me.
Dude, you're such a liar.
As if you were anywhere
near that hot tub.
All true, man.
Our stock is goin'
way up this year.
Dude, what was that about?
I don't know.
I think I insulted him.
Well, un-insult him.
That's Toby Neuwirth.
He's got major
anger management issues.
[snickers]
No kidding.
Still on hold?
Yep.
It's probably nothing,
but I haven't seen that guy
on patrol before,
and he shows up just in time?
Have you heard of any
break-ins in the neighborhood?
Uh-uh.
[on phone]
Mr. Trager?
Sorry to keep you
waiting, sir.
Yes, Tom is
a new employee here.
Tom Foss.
He just started this week.
I don't know. It's just
that we didn't know him.
I assume you do
background checks?
Oh, absolutely.
In fact, Tom has
a very impressive
military background.
He's a decorated veteran,
plus several years
in private security,
so nothin' to worry about.
Sounds good.
Thank you.
No problem.
He checked out fine.
These suburban types,
I'm tellin' you.
Must be somethin' about
payin' a mortgage,
makes 'em all jumpy.
Meanwhile, they got a guy
like you lookin' out for them.
Shoot, couldn't be
in better hands.
[Narrating]
22 volumes,
over 17,000 articles.
In one afternoon, I'd covered
the span of human history
and circled the globe.
I thought you'd
still be here.
Kyle?
Charlie's a really great guy.
I think you'd really like him.
Because I think
you're a great guy, too.
But...you know...
you know there's
nothing...between...
I mean, he thought
there might be, but...
I just--I wanted
to make sure that--
You don't...like me, do you?
[Narrating]
I'd just learned
of every human tragedy:
war and disaster.
But Amanda presented
the most difficult lesson.
I could tell which answer
would relieve her
and which she didn't
want to hear.
Kyle?
You're my friend.
Yeah.
We're friends.
Telling Amanda my true feelings
might have brought us closer.
But she belonged
with Charlie,
which meant I still
belonged...nowhere.
Kyle, wait.
You don't have to learn
everything in one day.
School's over for today.
Two more seconds.
Now it's over.
Well, so much for
our afternoon rendezvous.
So, you gonna call
the insurance company?
Yeah. The glass company, too.
Now, hold on.
I can hang a window
over the weekend.
Oh.
Thanks for comin'
to my rescue.
You're welcome.
Don't get that.
Hello?
Yes.
I'm sorry. What?
Oh, I'll be right there.
That was the school.
Trouble?
Yeah.
Which kid?
Kyle.
Yeah, it's gonna
be a great game.
I'll check you out later.
Hey, Trager.
What's up with you today?
I'm late for detention.
Look, if you want to talk
about what happened--
What happened?
Yeah, you know--
You want to talk about
what happened now.
I figured that we could--
It wasn't some friggin'
basketball game, Declan.
Hey, man, you catch that sex
we had last weekend?
Yeah, man, that
sex was awesome.
Nice offense.
Like, I don't know
Hillary told you
to ask me to the party.
Like you guys didn't sit there
and yuk it up at lunch.
Hey, Trager,
you got it all wrong.
I was just checking up on you.
If you really wanted
to check up on me,
you woulda called.
And you didn't, which
is fine. It's honest.
But this sudden interest
in my feelings
or whatever, it's so fake
and unnecessary
because the sex was awful,
because you could give a crap
about my feelings,
and because you are
the absolute last person
that I want
to talk to right now.
I was asking about
what happened today.
With Hillary.
Hey.
Hey, man.
You're in Schultz
with me, right?
Little wise-ass.
Dude, I don't know why
you've got a problem with me.
I don't got a problem.
You got a problem.
You're right, I do,
and I'll go take care of that.
Think you're smart, huh?
Dude, I'm in remedial.
Oh, with a bunch
of morons then, huh?
Stop.
Why'd you hit him?
Who's this, your boyfriend?
Let's go.
You know, you really
are an idiot.
Oh!
What's happening here?
The other student insists
Kyle threw the first punch.
I didn't hit anyone.
That is not how it appeared.
Mr. Hooper, all we saw
was Kyle holding that boy.
It looked like he was
stopping him, not pushing him.
Are you looking for reasons
to discredit him?
Mrs. Trager,
that altercation
plus Kyle's complete
disregard for school rules,
his wandering, the tests
he simply ignored...
I'm sorry, but there's just
no place for a boy like Kyle
in this school.
Trager, comma, Lori.
Have a seat.
1 + 2 - 1
until you reach 500.
Legibly.
How is this possible?
Someone answered it?
Yeah.
You know, I put it up every year
just to motivate you kids.
Hardly anyone attempts it,
let alone answers it.
Well, congratulations.
Someone must know
a mathematician.
Or search the Internet,
you know.
No student here could
possibly solve this on his own.
Mr. Miller, if I can point you
in the right direction,
can we forget about detention?
He's entitled
to a one-on-one tutor.
Not after today's performance.
That's him.
Mr. Miller, I'm
in a conference.
Excuse me.
This is important.
Did you solve
my math problem?
Kyle?
Yes, I did.
Okay, how did you do it?
The Fourier series?
You used Bessel functions?
Kronecker delta?
I just looked at it
and I knew.
Please, tell me
what's going on.
Um...Mr. Hooper,
this student just solved
a grad school-level math problem
and he can't tell me how.
Well, I'm afraid
this young man
is not a student
at this school.
Well, he has to be.
I have to work with him.
He didn't answer
a single question.
Kyle. Why didn't you?
I didn't know the answers.
You see?
But I do now.
Let him take the test.
Testing must be completed
in a five-hour period
for the scores to be valid.
There's 30 minutes left.
Just give him the test.
[sighs]
So? How'd your day go?
Awesome.
I want to transfer.
Hey, what happened?
I'll be outside.
Yeah, that's
just crazy.
Coach is goin' nuts.
He was
all over me, though.
I'll see you guys later.
[answers, indistinct]
Look...
I know I was super harsh
before. I thought--
I know what you thought.
Look, this whole day sucked,
so it wasn't about you, okay?
It was a little about me.
Yeah, well...it was
mostly bad timing.
Declan, we're going
for coffee.
Come with?
Nah, I'm good.
You didn't have to do that.
Wanted to.
I should apologize.
Yes, you should.
But you don't have to.
Look, I screw up all the time.
Maybe it's your turn.
Sounds fair.
You okay?
I'll live.
Hey, Trager, define "awful."
I'll see you tomorrow.
Done.
Done?
With, uh, which section?
All of 'em.
[Josh laughing]
That's...that's not possible.
Totally is.
Good goin', Kyle.
Now, hold on here.
I still have to grade them.
I think that's just
a formality, Mr. Hooper.
So, when can he start
with his tutor?
Well, if...if his scores
measure up,
first thing tomorrow morning.
Nice job, Kyle.
I'll see you soon.
I don't want a tutor.
But, Kyle, I thought you
wanted to go to school.
I do, but not like that.
Now, explain this to me:
that whole private tutor
was such a sweet deal.
But you want to go to class
with the rest of us?
If I don't, I'll be alone.
You'll be lucky.
No vicious backstabbers
to deal with.
And those are her friends.
Seriously, it's not like
you need to go to school.
You already know everything.
Facts.
Maybe some dates.
But if I'm stuck
with a tutor all day,
I'll never learn what
I really need to know.
Why do people do
what they do?
Hey.
Thanks for helpin' me today.
No worries.
People...are looking.
So?
It's weird.
I think weird is good.
I saw what you did.
Ka-blow!
Swoosh!
Bam!
You know, vanquished.
Ka-blow?
I know I said superheroes
aren't real, but...
Keep it.
I still don't know if I'd ever
been to school before that day,
and I wish I could
have learned something,
anything, that would've
helped me remember my past.
Still, every day
I spent here became
a part of my own history,
and if I wanted
to learn people,
I knew that part of that meant
learning from my own choices...
and making new choices
tomorrow.
He said he read
the entire encyclopedia.
He probably flipped through
and jogged his memory.
And then got a perfect score?
How could he know that much?