Previously on Criminal Minds...
Please, I don't want it.
I don't want it.
It helps.
What is the matter with you ?
What do you mean, what's
the matter with me ?
I have never seen
you act like this.
Really ?  Oh, in the months
that you know me,
You've never seen me act this way ?
Hey, no offense, Emily, but...
You don't really know what
you're talking about, do you ?
Earlier this morning katrina
crashed into the gulf coast,
With sustained winds
above 125 an hour.
As many houses are being destroyed.
Residents are trying to evacuate.
Are you listening to me, pop ?
Grab your wallet and get
the hell out of there.
The buses are filling up.
This case is eatin' at me, Billy.
Dad.
Forget the damn case.
What the hell am I missing here ?
Dad, people are drowning in their homes.
The... Whole world's
gonna be underwater.
I got another letter, Billy.
Screw the letter.
Forget the serial killer.
They're opening the superdome.
I want you to meet me there.
I'll be damned.
... Please, I'm begging you, pop.
Pop ?
Behavioral analysis unit
We've got a serial killer
in New Orleans
Who killed at least
3 men pre-Katrina.
Until now, the New Orleans
police department
Believed that the serial
killer died in the storm.
What's happened to tell
them otherwise ?
A fourth body was found in
the french quarter last night.
Same M.O. Another male.
Throat slashed, eviscerated.
A year and a half ?  That's a
long cooling-Off period.
Are we sure this
is the same unsub ?
He claims to be.
He sent a letter
to William Lamontagne,
The head detective on the case.
Does Lamontagne have any leads ?
He died in Katrina.
His son is actually
leading the case now.
Hmm. That can't be easy.
Well, we need to pour over the evidence
From the first 3 murders
and determine the pattern.
Katrina washed everything away.
The 3 victims we know of,
their autopsy reports,
Witness statements.
DNA test results.
So, basically, all we have
to go on is the latest victim ?
Yeah.
Until he kills again.
Criminal minds 218
Robert Kennedy once said,
"Tragedy is a tool for
the living to gain wisdom,
Not a guide by which to live."
Hey, Reid.
What's goin' on up there ?
From Las Vegas... Ethan.
I'm pretty sure he lives
in New Orleans now.
Really ?  Gonna give him a call ?
Grew up competing against each other
In absolutely everything.
Spelling bees, science fairs.
We also both had our hearts set
on joining the bureau, but...
First day at quantico he backed out.
He probably just couldn't take the heat.
It's not really for us
to judge, is it ?
Right.
My bad.
These are copies of the newspaper
articles on the murders,
Dating back to early august 2005.
It's all we have to go on.
He killed 3 times,
he stopped for 18 months,
Then he started killing again.
We should have garcia run a list
Of any offenders in the area.
Anyone who spent the last year
and a half doing time.
Or anyone that relocated after
Katrina and recently moved back.
What is the victimology
in killing a mechanic,
A real estate broker, and a cook,
With ages ranging from 22 to 45 ?
And this latest is
a 33-Year-Old taxi driver.
They just don't seem to have
very much in common.
Besides being male and walking
the french quarter late at night.
Which is notorious for muggings
off the main drag.
Yeah, but this guy isn't
in a rush to flee the scene.
A slaughter like this takes time.
Andrei Chikatilo fantasized that
the men he killed were his captives
And then torturing and mutilating them
Somehow made him a hero.
The city's barely back to life.
Something like this could
cripple its psyche.
So where do we start ?
Well, with no case file there's
only one place we can start.
At square one.
You must be B.A.U.
Bill Lamontagne.
Hi. Jennifer Jareau.
We spoke on the phone.
Well, ok, then.
I pictured you different.
Uh, these are agents
Gideon and Morgan.
This is detective
William Lamontagne JR.
Appreciate you guys being here.
My daddy was too stubborn
to ever ask for any help.
Sorry for your loss.
I understand you received a letter.
Yeah. Before they were
lost in Katrina,
My daddy received 2 letters.
This one came addressed to him yesterday.
They passed it on to me.
You sure it's from
the same killer ?
It's a detailed account
of what he did to the body.
4 layers of fatty tissue
sliced through like butter.
I only seen that 3 other times.
You work this case initially ?
Nah. You don't forget victims like this.
It's like they were dissected.
I can still smell the alcohol on him.
This is New Orleans.
Dead or alive,
it' a smell you get used to.
The victim has no defense wounds.
Meaning this is most
likely a blitz attack.
No hesitation marks or rapid thrusts.
Cuts were methodical.
Almost procedural.
My guess... Whoever gutted
this guy was taught to.
So you think he might have
some medical training ?
How else could he carve
around every organ
And leave each one intact ?
Have any of his relatives
come to claim the body ?
Anyone we could speak with ?
No. I'll end up boxing up
the poor bastard's ashes,
Left to collect dust in storage.
All the bodies I've been through
in the last year and a half,
It's a wonder I still have room.
It'd be pretty easy to hide out
in one of these alcoves,
Wait for the victim
without ever being seen.
Yeah, all 4 murders occurred
within a 10-Block radius
Here inside the french quarter.
On any given night, there'd
have to be thousands of people
Walking through here from the bars.
Tens of thousands.
When I first started as a cop,
I worked the quarter.
It's like being in the riot
squad every night.
Every sunday I'd get off
work around sunrise,
I'm ready to pass out,
My daddy'd be waiting
for me at my house.
Make me drive him uptown to Frankie
and Johnny's for poorboys.
Called it communing with New Orleans.
Did your father tell you anything else
about this case that we should know ?
He tried to.
But you guys should
see that for yourself.
This wall is still standing
where daddy carved the message
Right before he died.
There's no doubt he's still
working from the grave.
"Jones." That name mean
anything to you ?
No. I ran it through the database
Against every offender
in New Orleans.
And you can imagine
how many hits I got.
But nothing came up
in connection with this case.
But in your dad's final moments,
It was the most important
thing he wanted to say.
Learned how to play
the drums in this house,
Grew up with 2 dogs in this house.
All it's gonna be now is the word
"jones" carved into that wall.
Detective, if he had
written the unsub's name,
I think you would have
found him by now.
Jones is the one
piece of the puzzle
That your daddy did know.
He trusted you to figure out the rest.
Yeah, I know it.
But I've pored over
it a thousand times
And I still can't put it together.
I can't get it out of my head.
You ok ?
Yeah.
I just don't want to disappoint him.
Is that the letter from the unsub ?
Yeah.
I'm back with a vengeance.
I wanted you to know.
The last guy made it easy,
being out so late,
Stumbling home drunk.
I enjoyed slicing around his organs.
I thought about sending you one.
He was asking to be ripped,
don't you think, boss ?
Yours truly."
Hey.
Ok.
To say that the victims
were asking to be killed
Denies all culpability.
Most sexual sadists rationalize
their own behavior
By blaming the victims like that.
But there was no evidence
of sexual assault in the autopsy.
He could be a homosexual male
Stabbing because he needs
violence for arousal.
Every kill he's acting
out a fantasy of revenge.
What if he's trying to act
out something else ?  Like what ?
Except for the victims were men,
it's the same M.O.
What are you talking about ?
All 4 victims were found with
their throats slashed, eviscerated,
And the murders perpetrated
in semi-Public places after dark.
Investigators taunted with
the letters addressed to "boss."
The only difference is that
case was 100 years ago
And the murders took place in London.
Jack the ripper.
The unsub wants us to think
That he's the modern-Day version
loose in New Orleans.
Please.Don't
So the 3 of you were out
together last night ?
Mark had just paid his tab at one bar
And he was on his way
to meet us at another.
You guys get in any trouble ?
Drunken brawl ?
Anyone get out of hand ?
We were just out
to have fun, you know ?
Minded our own business.
Could mark have met a girl ?
Maybe upset her boyfriend ?
No, sir.
He struck out like we all did.
Thanks, guys.
Ok.
Getting hard to keep up
with this guy.
Well, if he's mimicking
Jack the ripper,
That might be precisely the point.
He terrorized london for months
Without ever getting caught.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd gather your men.
We'd like to give you a profile
of who you're up against.
The offender we're looking
for is friendly,
Agile, somewhere between 30 and 35.
He'll allure with charm
And kill with rage.
We believe he's murdering men
To reclaim his power.
This unsub suffers
from low self-Esteem,
But he probably covers it well.
He dresses impeccably
to feed the facade.
Jack the ripper himself
Was an impetuous lust murderer,
Whereas this offender is organized,
Calculating.
He might even stalk
his victims for days
Before the actual kill.
We believe this killer identifies
with Jack the ripper
Because he's lost his own identity.
Maybe through years
of child abuse...
Or some catastrophic event.
Because he overcompensates
to hide his insecurities,
We believe he may hold a position
of authority at work.
And since we think he's had
medical training,
Consider emts, doctors, veterinarians.
Please be careful.
For this unsub,
The french quarter's
a hunting ground.
He's certainly already proven
he knows the terrain.
Jeez !
Reid, you scared me.
Always been one step
ahead of you, man.
Yeah, whatever helps
you sleep at night.
I'm glad you called.
It's good to see you.
You, too.
Let's get a drink.
Prentiss.
What was the thing
Jack the ripper took from
one of his victims ?
Besides, well, you know, her life ?
Oh. Uh... Uh...
Mmm.
Tick tock...
Tick tock.
I don't know.
A kidney.
How horrify ingly
fantastic is that ?
Mm-Hmm. And are you
going anywhere with this ?
Just that I found an unsolved murder
that happened 4 months ago
In Galveston, Texas,
With the same M.O.,
The victim missing
That very organ.
I amaze myself.
Yeah. Me, too.
Great work.
What's that ?
Garcia found a similar
case in Galveston, Texas.
A lot of Katrina refugees
relocated there.
It could be the same guy.
He removed the kidney
just like Jack the ripper.
Call Reid and Morgan.
I want the 3 of you on a plane
to Texas tonight.
Ok.
So...
Are you gonna ask the question ?
What question ?
Come on, man.
It's me here.
We haven't talked
to each other in years.
I know it's why you called me.
Ask the question.
Why did you quit after only
one day of fbi training ?
Well...
I'm sure you've
considered the evidence,
Analyzed the signs.
You were battling what's
your own demons.
You didn't have time
to analyze someone else's.
Not bad. Not bad.
Those days, I did prefer
Jack Daniel's to Jeff Dahmer.
They both weigh on
your soul eventually.
Sorry
The bat phone.
Let me ask you this, Ethan.
Do you ever regret it ?
You know, I may not be
changing the world, but...
My music makes me happy.
It doesn't take a profiler
to see that you're not.
It's not easy. And it's not...
I... don't think you'd believe some of
the things that I've seen.
John Coltrane.
He was a genius, too.
Died of cancer.
But most people think
it was the booze and heroin
That did him in.
What are you tryingsay ?
You look like hell.
I'm fine.
Come on, man.
I'm a jazz musician
in New Orleans.
I know what it looks like
when someone's not well.
This may be the one time
I can tell you something
That you don't already know.
That might help you forget,
But it won't make it go away.
And if I can tell...
You're surrounded by some of
the best minds in the world,
And if you think they don't notice...
Well...
For a genius,
That's just dumb.
Hey. Hey.
Where's Reid ?
I was hoping he was with you.
I thought you said you called him.
I did, 4 times. Nothing.
The victim's fiancee is expecting us.
What are we supposed to do ?
We got one option.
Wheels up.
Thank you.
It's not right.
The french quarter's one of the only
parts of the city that dodged Katrina.
Now there's a serial killer loose.
It's a small area,
And we're narrowing down the profile.
We'll find him.
You always drink while
you're still on the clock ?
This is New Orleans, honey.
It's a cultural thing.
Where are you from ?
Pennsylvania.
I take it the folks
Are a little rigid about
the rules up that way.
Well, if it makes you feel better...
We'll play it
Pennsylvania style tonight.
I just hate that this guy
has a leg up on us, you know ?
I promise, as soon as my team
knows anything, we'll hear.
Ok ?
Why aren't you married ?
Uh, that involves this case how ?
It doesn't.
I'm just flirtin'.
It's unprofessional.
You don't have to answer that.
Excuse me.
Compliments of the woman
in the blue top.
Wow. That was... bold.
She might have thought
we were just working.
We are.
Are you jealous ?
No. I just... I...
I'm surprised, that's all.
And you're a lousy liar, too.
You haven't had much practice, huh ?
It's a culture thing.
You see.
There you go.
Everybody kept sayg
Crime's gonna skyrocket
after the relocation.
You just never think
it's gonna happen to you.
The report said that your fiance
Was bar-Hopping for his bachelor party
On the night he was killed.
We were supposed
to be married in october.
He was just out
celebrating that with friends.
Was there anyone at Leonard's
bachelor party
You didn't know ?
We all grew up together.
They're like family to me.
Whether they met
somebody out, you know,
That's a different story.
They're a rowdy bunch.
And they'd party with anybody.
Each of the last 2 victims
was traveling in a group.
Both were drinking, both
in public arenas, bar-Hopping.
So how could their friends
not see anything ?
It like when a lion preys
upon an antelope.
You lost me.
That's because you,
Emily Prentiss,
Have never been
one of the antelope.
Oh, scratch that.
You totally lost me.
Ok. Check this out.
The antelope travel in packs.
So the lion just sits and waits.
Waits for just one of the antelope
To break away from its herd.
So when he's alone,
Vulnerable, and completely unprotected,
That's when the lion strikes.
That's when she makes her move.
Wait a minute. Her move ?
Prentiss, there's only one thing
That's gonna make a straight man
Leave his friends on guys night out.
And it'll make him leave every time.
One of the victims was out
for his bachelor party.
Another one out with just the guys.
What's the only temptation
That's gonna lure these men
away from each other ?  A woman.
J.J.
Ok.
Yeah, he's right here with me.
Thanks.
What's going on ?
The ansub...
Hey.
We're not making a media
spectacle out of this.
People need to know that
this killer is a woman.
What ?
Listen.
Tourists are just starting
to filter back here.
That's not the issue.
I can't create mass hysteria
in a city trying to rebuild.
Besides, we'll be playing
right into her hands.
So be it.
Look, um...
I'm trying not to go
above your head here.
Yeah.
I got that.
Then set up the press conference.
Hey, you guys are
back from Galveston ?
First light this
morning. Where were you ?
I was out with a friend.
I already told you.
I called you 4 times.
I didn't have any cell
phone reception,
So I didn't get your
message until late.
Right.
What's going on ?
Our unsub's a woman.
We just found another
body in the quarter.
Throat's been cut.
He's been disemboweled, too.
Reeks of booze.
It's more than a pattern.
Only this time he cut
off the earlobe.
She's sticking with
the ripper's paradigm.
What do you mean ?
In one letter
of correspondence,
Jack the ripper promised
to cut the earlobe off
Of his next victim.
He did.
It was the one day
that he killed twice.
So she's gonna kill again
by the end of the day.
Ok, what do we know about
female serial killers ?
Basically, you have 2 types.
The sante kimes model.
Cold, calculating.
Preys on men for money.
Takes her time building
relationships.
It's more likely
we're dealing with
The aileen wuornos archetype,
Motivated by paranoia and fear,
Luring men with sex.
Our unsub's organized.
She follows a routine.
She meets men in a bar,
flirts with them over drinks,
And suggests that they consummate
the evening in an alley.
We need to be in those streets.
Office just brought me this.
Dear boss,
By now I have rid the
world of one more.
So many men, so little time.
I hope you don't mind the mess.
They make is so easy,
I just can't help myself.
Yours truly.
So were looking for a woman
who will approach men,
Comfortable being
the aggressor, no ?
And I'm guessing she'd have
to be quite attractive
In order to lure them away.
Most of the women are out in groups,
So keep your eyes open
for someone on their own.
"So many men, so little time."
So she's on a quest...
To wipe out the race.
Or... the father
who molested her ?
Some people think Jack
the ripper mutilated women
After his mother sexually
abused him for years.
For someone so enraged...
This unsub sounds oddly apologetic
For leaving a bloody crime scene.
Why ?
That might be what
Lamontagne figured out
Right before he died.
You gotta admit, these guys
are making it pretty easy.
I wouldn't follow
a stranger into an alley
No matter how wasted I was.
Yeah, but you're not a man.
Testosterone will follow
a woman to Thailand.
Barefoot.
It's just a fact.
Did you give that newest
letter to Reid ?
He knows that ripper case inside out.
He might see something I'm missing.
I don't think, uh...
What is it ?
Nothing.
Come on.
You think I'm not aware
something's going on with him ?
You gonna tell me why you missed
that flight to Galveston ?
I already told you.
It was no cell reception.
Right.
What ?
I mean, anytime
you want to come up
With a better answer,
I'm standing right here.
Dark Curls, 3 o'clock.
I got it.
She's eyeing those guys
outside that bar.
Let's go.
Oh !  Oh, I'm... I'm sorry.
I hate it when that happens.
You all right ?
What can I do to say I'm sorry ?
How about a drink ?
Have a drink. That's cool.
That's cool.
Sure.
Yeah, that's totally fine.
Yeah...
Yeah.
Danny.
You fool.
You dropped your wallet out there.
Thanks.
Next drink is on me.
So...
Where are your friends tonight ?
I didn't bring any.
They get in the way.
Now, see, I like that.
'Cause, uh, most girls,
They won't go nowhere alone.
I'm not most girls.
We got nothin'.
Well, the day's almost over,
So if you're right,
we just ran out of time.
Your hair's wet.
Oh, my god !  Aah !
She's mocking us.
And she's true to her word.
Do you have any tweezers ?
Thank you.
What is that ?
I have no idea.
It's a note from the unsub,
Addressed to your father.
Let's see it.
Dear boss,
He wanted it,
With that sharp tongue
and vulgar hand.
Thought you'd like to know
Another will soon
get what he deserves.
Yours truly.
It's weird. Typically, offenders
write letters to be heard.
Jack the ripper bragged
about not being caught.
This unsub isn't
using correspondence
To flaunt her latest kill,
Only to explain why she did it.
It's possible she considers
herself a vigilante.
That the men she's killing
deserve to die.
Or maybe she's contacting your father,
Not because he was the lead detective
On the case, but...
Because she believes he'd understand.
You think he knew her somehow ?
Can you think of a woman
in your dad's life
He helped through a tough time ?
Might be another police officer,
I don't know, a prostitute
he helped get off the street ?
He hasn't dealt with prostitutes
Since he worked sex crimes.
The unsub wrote,
"he was asking to be ripped."
"I just couldn't help
myself," and he wanted it."
What if she's mirroring
the man who raped her ?
Where are the files stored
from your sex crime division ?
They were housed the same
place as homicide.
Most of them were washed away.
Did your dad have a partner ?
Yeah. J.R. Smith.
Smitty, they called him.
He might remember something.
Yeah, but they had a falling out.
What about ?
I don't know. They stopped
talking when he left sex crimes.
Do you have a problem calling him ?
Not if it means breaking this case.
May I borrow your hand for a minute ?
I'll be damned.
What is it ?
The stamp on the victim's hand...
It's admittance into the mon cherie.
It's a bar in the french quarter.
Oh, yeah ?
Yeah.
9 years ago it was called Jones.
Bingo.
Get Garcia on the horn.
O captain, my captain.
I need you.
Anything. Talk to me.
Is there any newspaper reports
About a rape at a bar called Jones ?
Zilch.
You sure ?  It would have beenav
About 9 years ago.
Nada.
Ok. Uh...
Cross-Reference William Lamontagne
With Jones bar.
Bull's-Eye.
Police blotter...
Answered a disturbance
At Jones bar in the french quarter,
February 19, 1998.
Looks like it was during mardi gras.
You are the best ever.
Ohh... and you're the
most perceptive.
Smitty.
How are you ?
I hope you got a good reason
Dredging this crap up.
Well, I was hoping
You might remember
being called here
With my daddy 9 years ago.
Is that a joke ?
No.
My name's Jason Gideon.
We're from the FBI.
We're investigating
the series of murders
In the french quarter.
What's that got to do with me ?
We need you to tell us
what happened
The night you and detective
Lamontagne answered the call
In this bar.
Am I missing something ?
You really don't know, do you ?
After that night, your daddy
Tried to bring me up on sanctions.
Why ?
It was mardi gras.
Some girl claimed she was raped.
In this bar.
I wasn't buying it.
What did she say happened to her ?
Brass backed me up.
They ended up transferring
your daddy out
To shut him up.
What happened here ?
It almost cost me my career.
Do you mind telling us what happened ?
My best recollection,
She said she was sitting at the bar
With 2 friends.
One of the boys asked her
if she wanted to play some pool.
Witnesses claim she was up
for anything.
She followed him up here ?
His friend not far behind.
She knew he was there.
That girl was a tease.
She was looking for a good time.
Anyway, a couple of guys
were going along with that.
Did she yell for help ?
She said she did.
But not a single person
claimed that they heard her.
That's what you registered
as a disturbance ?
It was mardi gras.
Listen to me.
That girl had enough beads
hanging from her neck
To jewel a small city.
Anyone exposes themselves
that much in one day
Is not a credible witness in my book.
But she wanted to press charges.
I told her it was a waste of time.
I knew one of the accused.
He was a good kid.
He didn't need the stink
of that accusation.
So you protected a rapist ?
Well, that right there
Was a bone of contention
between his daddy and i.
As far as I was concerned,
No such rape ever took place.
Are you gonna tell me
Why you went and dragged
this dirt back through my life ?
You know the serial killer
Who's cutting up men
in the french quarter ?
She was your victim.
We're trying to find a name.
You don't even remember her name ?
It was 9 years ago.
What about the name of the
"good kid" who raped her ?
Smitty...
You tell me right now or I'll file
a new sanction against you,
And I guarantee you,
this time it'll stick.
Mr. Tibideaux, we need you
to answer a few questions
About a disturbance you were
involved with in 1998.
I don't know what you're talking about.
At a bar called Jones.
It was mardi gras.
Well, then,
I must have been drinking some,
'Cause I don't remember a thing.
We just need to know the name...
Look, I told you, I don't know
what you're talking about.
The statute of limitations is up.
We just need a name.
Someone accuses me of rape,
­
I'm going to remember her name.
What can I tell you, cher ?
I guess she didn't make
that good of an impression.
Unlike yourself, right now.
You know, I'm guessing if someone
Did do something
to that girl that night,
Then she was probably asking for it.
Maybe even liked it.
Guy's not giving up anything.
Right after the double murder,
What was the ripper's next move ?
He mutilated and
dismembered Mary Kelly
In her one-Room flat until
she was unrecognizable.
It's believed to be his most
vicious kill of all.
'Cause he had privacy.
And time to torture his victim
before killing her.
Maybe we're not too late.
She murdered these men,
And I'm guessing it's only
a matter of time
Before she works
her way back to the one
She really wants to kill.
She make an impression now ?
Work me.
We have a name... Sarah Danlin.
I need an address.
1141 Sherman Avenue.
It looks like she was
a med student at tulane,
But she dropped out.
Let me guess... February 1998.
Yeah. Thanks.
We got her.
I'm John, by the way.
John.
Take off your clothes.
Sarah Danlin, F.B.I. !
Open the door.
The things I'm gonna do to you.
Me first.
F.B.I. !
Clear. Clear.
She's not here.
Guys, there are some ripperologists
Who speculate that Mary Kelly
Was actually killed in a flat
That Jack the ripper
rented for the night.
I'm going to have Garcia
check Sarah Danlin's
Credit card accounts.
It's a long shot,
But maybe we can trace her room
back to her charge cards.
Aah !
What the hell was that ?
Shh.
You're crazy.
You never did explain those
"things" you could do to me.
Souvenirs.
These are from bars
in the french quarter.
This is from mon cherie.
She's trolling for victims
in the place where it all began.
She can't move on.
The rape isn't the whole story.
I'll bet there's a history
of sexual abuse
That contributes to her rage as well.
It's almost like by taking
on the ripper persona,
She was trying to kill
something within herself.
Yeah, mama, what do you got ?
Sarah Danlin's visa was charged
An hour ago at the Royal Ruby Inn.
Ah, baby girl, you never
disappoint. Thank you.
Royal Ruby Inn.
That's 2 blocks from here.
Let's go
Please !
Please. Please.
I have... I have children.
Stop...
Please.
You asked...
FBI !
Drop the knife. Drop the weapon.
He wanted it... and he got it.
Put it down now.
We need an emt tech right away.
What are you waiting for ?
Ma'am, we don't want to shoot you.
Be such a shame to waste this.
Do you want it, too ?
What I want is for you
to put that knife down.
Come on.
Don't fight it.
Sarah, we don't want to hurt you.
Men.
Sarah, my name's
William Lamontagne JR.
You knew my daddy ?
Yeah, yeah.
You trusted him. So trust me.
Where is he ?
The storm took him.
Come on. It's over.
It's over.
Hey.
Hey there.
The medic says that her
victim's going to be ok.
I heard what you did in there.
Your dad would be really proud.
It's weird.
I spent all this time focused
on closing this case for him...
And now it's over.
Yeah.
I thought I'd feel happy,
but I just feel lost.
Because you've...
And now you're leaving ?
How will I survive a woman
like you going so far away ?
Well, despite what
you may have heard...
Cell phones can be very
good for your health.
See ya.
How'd you find me ?
You're not all that hard to profile.
Your friend is good.
I missed that plane on purpose.
I know.
I'm struggling.
Well... anybody who's been through
What you've been through recently...
Would.
This is all I was groomed for.
I never even...
I never even considered
another option.
Now you're questioning
whether or not
You're strong enough to be here ?
Yeah.
I have been playing at this job
In one way or another
for almost 30 years.
I've felt lost.
I've felt great.
I have felt scared,
Sick,
And insane.
I don't know.
I guess the day this job stops
gnawing at your soul and...
Hands... your hands stop feeling cold...
Maybe that's the time to leave.
I guess I just needed
to try to figure out
If I could step away from this job.
And ?
I'll never miss another plane again.
Transcript : www.1000fr.com
Modification : Flolo pour seriessub.com
Resynch REPACK-LOL : jayson.sosweet pour seriessub.com