Cream Team
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
Life always present choices.
Where you can take the high-road
or the low-road.
This is Pete Gilroy.
He runs others researches
in development department.
Pete is a low-road guy.
Is this anyone's hoagie?
Anyone? No.
I asked.
I, on the other hand, try
to stay on the high road.
Two? But only paid for one.
That's it.
Oh, almost...
there.
Ted on his back,
straining with effort?
There's a picture
I can call back later.
That's gonna hurt for a while.
Strengthening your hand
for that big date with yourself?
Nope, just practicing for later
when I squeeze your mom's boobs.
I'm not proud of that.
I actually had a lovely conversation
with Pete's mom at the Christmas party.
The mat and the vest
are both magnetized.
When a child puts on the vest
and steps on the mat,
the magnets repel each other,
making the child almost weightless,
like an astronaut
bouncing on the moon.
Now every child can have
hours of repulsive fun.
Pete Gilroy's team
is working on a similar system,
and the company will only go forward
with one.
So we need to make damn sure
that it is
"the floater."
That's not such a good name.
What about "the astro-nut"?
You know, because it's crazy.
Has waving your hands
ever sold me on anything?
Remember
"corpse-eating battlefield robot"?
What we have here is...
"The dream glider."
- That's fantastic.
This technology also has
a exciting military potential.
Imagine soldiers hovering
above a magnetized battlefield.
The Chinese won't know what hit 'em.
Come on.
We all know that war is coming.
Can't we develop one thing that doesn't
end up being used to kill people?
Even our fat-free cinnamon roll
led to that new sticky bomb.
You're so moral and perfect
all the time.
Do singing birds and mice dress you
and brush your hair in the morning?
Although my dad does call me "princess,"
and there's a dwarf in my building.
We need your help.
- We were working really hard.
- And we had this pinata.
Pinata? That doesn't sound
like really hard work.
It was stuffed with science.
And...
Pinata!
And now the thermostat's broken,
and we were wondering if you would
tell the company so they'll fix it.
We're worried if we report it,
the company will retaliate,
like when I broke the flywheel
and they canceled my gym membership.
I mean, you remember
how ripped I was gettin'.
Guys, you broke the thermostat.
Just take the high road and report it.
And they canceled your gym membership
'cause no matter what class you were in,
you did jazzercise.
But I don't want
to take the high road.
It's high.
I agree.
We could fall off.
I can't stand that Veronica
makes fun of me in meetings.
If the boss doesn't respect me,
other people won't,
including the little Linda
in my head.
And even on a good day,
that bitch never shuts up.
Veronica just has trouble
relating to you.
She thinks you always
want to do the right thing.
I don't alway do the right thing.
Hey, daddy. Hi, Linda.
Hey, sweetie. Want to go smoke
a cigarette in the bathroom?
See? I can be bad.
Don't ever smoke. Every time you smoke
a cigarette, Santa Claus kills an elf.
What, helping or hurting?
Because I can throw Jesus into the mix.
I think we're good.
Honey, you ready to go down to the hive?
The hive? I thought you didn't like
Veridian's after-school care
because they use the kids for free
janitorial work around the building.
The hive has changed. A lot of
the executives' kids go there now.
So they teach music and Chinese,
the weaknesses of the Chinese...
Chet just call.
Oh, hi, Rose. You look fabulous.
Have you lost weight?
I have been playing
a lot of dodgeball.
Well, it's working for you.
I'm trying to teach Rose
that it's not all about looks.
- She's also very smart.
- Smart enough to stay skinny.
Anyway, Chet wants us to come up
and pitch him the dream glider.
Dream glider?
I know. It's fantastic.
Of course,
lady pope over here thinks it's immoral.
I'm no lady pope. I once slept
with my cousin's husband.
They were breaking up,
and I was really drunk.
And don't ever do that either,
or the tooth fairy will put
other people's teeth in your mouth.
I'll meet you in Chet's office
after I drop off Rose.
Come on, sweetie.
Let's go try to forget
all the stuff that Linda said.
Allowing a child of 80 pounds or less
to hover, roll,
spin or flip without ever
leaving their home planet.
We'll see what testing says,
but I'm flipping for this.
That's funny, because you just used
one of the words Ted just said.
No, that's great, guys. It's a really
good job. I do have one question.
Are little boys gonna want
to look like they have a set of boobies?
Chet, my eyes are up here.
Let's see if I can get the...
the tassels going in...
in different directions.
There we go.
Anyway, I think it's a home run.
Pete, why don't you show Chet
what our team has come up with?
It may not sexualize children,
but we think that every kid's
gonna want to wear one of these.
Lower center of gravity.
Allows the kid to be even safer
and jump even higher.
Sure, they're doing whatever they can
to get out of that diaper.
Pete and I have a long history
of trying to undermine each other.
Solar painting. It absorbs the sun's
energy, cutting heating costs...
Fantastic.
I have one question.
Can you make the color
look even more like barf?
Maybe add some bits of chewed-up
hot dog to complete the effect.
It's a purification straw.
Any water you drink through it,
no matter how polluted,
- becomes safe for consumption.
- That's a great idea.
"No dessert, kids, until you
finish drinking your sewage."
Occasionally, Veronica tried
to get her licks in, too.
Unfortunately, she took big swings
but rarely connected.
Pete, with your diaper,
kids won't have to stop
playing to go to the bathroom.
Do those come in disposable
or do you have
to wash 'em out each time?
Wait. I can do this.
Is it true that in space,
no one can hear you poop?
Oh, come on. That was hilarious.
I hate Pete.
We need to crush that wanker,
- teach him not to mess with us anymore.
- I'm sick of this war.
It just hurts both our teams.
We need to change tactics, get along
with Pete... Take the high road.
I don't take the high road, Ted.
The high road leads to pansy town.
Or maybe it leads
to a more effective way
of handling an adversary... ville.
You take your road. I'll take mine.
Look at that thing.
Somewhere, a naked sumo wrestler
is looking for his pants.
Damn it! That's fantastic.
Veridian Dynamics
Doing the right thing...
It's important.
What does it mean in business?
We have no idea.
We know what wrong is.
Actually, no, we don't,
because we're a successful company,
not some boring ethics professor...
Veridian Dynamics
Right and Wrong. It means something.
We just don't know what.
For guys who spend as much time
thinking about boobs as we do,
you'd think
we would have caught this one.
- Man, it is hot in here.
- Yes, it's very unpleasant.
So you've decided
not to report the thermostat?
You guys have more brains
than a zombie Thanksgiving,
and your genius plan
is to do nothing?
We're not doing nothing.
Doing nothing is passive.
We're waiting,
from the action verb "to wait..."
For someone who finds this heat
so intolerable, they have to report it.
Can I get you some hot tea
or Mexican chilies?
For God sake, Ted, help us!
I'm sorry, but you made this bed.
Now you gotta sweat in it.
So I need you to look at Pete's version
of the dream glider.
See if you can redesign it so it doesn't
look like a toilet strapped to your ass.
- Why would we want to help Pete?
- Or you? Making us suffer like this.
It's a goodwill gesture.
I'm trying to make peace with Pete,
you know,
warm things up between us,
get things cooking.
Light a fire under our friendship.
Sweaty, sweaty, sweaty, sweaty.
Oh, I get it.
Because zombies would eat
brains for Thanksgiving.
That's outrageous.
You make no sound when you walk.
Then I am ready to leave the monastery
and avenge my parents.
I'm kidding.
I just buy expensive shoes
made from very soft animals.
I know you're too much of a she-Gandhi
to ever do anything wrong,
but I need a person who will
and thought maybe
you could suggest someone
- who's not as...
- Me!
Yes, exactly. Not as you.
No, I mean, I suggest me.
I'm not some scout girl.
You are eager
and desperate for my approval.
And that's two of the three qualities
I look for in a partner.
I need someone who knows
about testing and is willing to cheat
to make sure
Pete's magnet pants test badly.
Then you need me.
As testing coordinator,
I totally know how to manipulate it.
I mean, the testing process
is so flawed anyway.
Really, the whole thing
is a bunch of garbage.
- I gotta go.
- Okay, bye, daddy.
I'll be upstairs if you need me.
What are you doing here?
I come every afternoon
for the juice boxes and story time.
I have a daughter.
Your daughter's into those pioneer
girl dolls that come with the books.
- Your daughter collect those?
- Only, like, all of 'em.
We just got Ida Mae.
- Ida Mae kills me.
- I know. The girl has rickets,
and she wants to teach
her brother to square-dance?
I'll die if she doesn't
survive the typhus epidemic.
She's a fighter.
So, Pete, actually,
I was on my way to see you.
I had my guys make some adjustments
on your magnet pants
so they look less like
something you'd drop a deuce in.
Yes, I get it. They're diapery.
What's your game?
We've been attacking each other's
projects for years. It's time we stop.
Let our ideas live
or die on their own merits.
You're trying to glom on to my project
because you heard it's testing first.
You're testing first?
Look at the big, saucer eyes.
Like you didn't know.
You're not testing for another week.
By the time they test your boob vest,
it'll be dead.
It's not a boob vest.
You're a boob vest.
That's not what I'm doing, anyway.
I'm reaching out to you, dipwad.
Screw you.
Fine.
I was trying to be a grown-up,
except for the dipwad thing.
But I can see you're not interested.
So the gloves are off.
By the way,
Ida Mae survives
the typhus epidemic...
But then gets trampled to death
by a Buffalo.
You are a special kind of monster.
Pete's project is testing today.
I want to burn his diaper
and salt the earth beneath it
so no new product
will ever grow there.
Test groups are easy to manipulate.
People always agree
with the strongest voice in the room.
All we have to do is
get one charismac person
and make sure that person
is relentlessly negative,
and then we'll be puttin'
on a pair of brand-new happy hats.
What is it like in there?
Actually,
today is a pretty good day.
So Pete's product
is gonna be tested by children.
Then we have to find
a charismatic child.
We'd like to check out Rose, please.
It's ready to go.
Now all we have to do is get Patricia
to touch it, and it becomes her problem.
I called her. She's on her way.
Have you ever noticed
how much of men's lives are spent
trying to trick women
into touching something?
Hey, guys. You wanted to see me?
If you think it's so damn hot in here,
turn down the thermostat.
I mean, hi, Patricia.
You know, it is awfully hot in here.
We like it hot.
Keeps out the... penguins.
There's a bunch of 'em back there
that have been trying to get in.
There's no air in this room.
It's making you guys weird.
What did you do,
break the thermostat? Yes.
I barely touched it.
- Is that how you're gonna play it?
- But I didn't even...
We're past that now.
Now we're on to how you're gonna fix it.
I can't tell the company. They'll
poison my food to make me infertile.
They don't do things like that
or cancel gym memberships.
I guess I'll just have to pay
to get it fixed myself.
Really? You're going to fix it
with your own money?
Maybe you'll learn a valuable lesson
and be more careful next time.
And so I joined Lem and Phil
on the low road.
And since testing first
is a huge advantage,
I need to make sure
that my project goes before Pete's.
William.
Look what I found.
It is a signed first edition.
Harry E. Wilson's
"Ethics in testing"?
And it's yours
if you do me one favor.
There's nothing I wouldn't do
to get my hands on that book.
You're going to be in a room
filled with weak, malleable children,
and a man will bring in a toy.
When he does, you're gonna say
very bad things about it.
- Why?
- We're telling you to,
and you should always do
what adults tell you to do,
especially when they give you candy.
It's just a fun game we're playing,
like dress-up,
only instead of clothes,
we're dressing up the things
that are coming out of your mouth.
I want you to start by calling
the toy a creative misfire,
an ill-conceived design paradigm
that's irrelevant to your demographic.
- Is she talking to me?
- She's trying to.
She's a kid. She has to say things
that a kid would say,
like, "that's not phat. It's whack."
Do the kids still talk like that?
It was very hip when I was 8.
Let's put a pin in the lingo,
flavor flav.
If anyone says something positive,
you dismiss it
with a derisive laugh.
A what?
No, no. It's more like...
- Like that.
- It's more like a...
No, it's an actual laugh. It...
It's more of a gesture.
It's a scoff. It's a, "huh."
She's so sweet.
Our little killing machine.
She's gonna destroy
Pete's moon diaper.
You're phat, Linda.
Why would you say that to me?
I mean "phat" with a p-h.
I'm reaching out to you
with your own lingo.
I couldn't have done this
without you.
Ain't no thang.
Hi, kids. My name's William,
and I'm here to show you
an exciting new Veridian product.
She nailed the laugh.
She's very useful.
Oh, God. That's our dream glider!
Mother...
Good news. I switched the testing.
What's Rose doing in there?
So any first impressions?
I'd never play with that.
I think it's stupid.
It looks dangerous,
like it could kill a Jonas Brother.
So any other thoughts?
I got an estimate.
Fixing the particle-based environmental
control thermostat costs $2,000.
That's a lot.
But you did really break it.
I can't afford that,
so I called my ex-boyfriend Rolf.
He works in AC.
He'll fix it for free
if I have sex with him.
Sex is good, right?
Not the way Rolf does it.
We're sorry.
Why? You guys didn't do anything.
We broke the thermostat
and made you think it was you.
So in that sense, we did.
- Why? I thought we were friends.
- We are.
- Maybe not good friends.
- Good friends would never do this.
- We're not even good people.
- We're really not.
You jerks get
your own thermostat fixed.
Plus, each of you give me $500
or I'll tell the company you broke it.
We're not giving you any money.
No way.
Then... Fight each other.
- What?
- That's crazy.
That's the deal.
Either you pay me the money,
or you fight.
And now it's $700.
That's insane, okay? We're friends.
There's no way Phil and I...
I can't believe that you involved
my daughter, and you got her to lie.
She was a star, Ted.
And you're not so pure.
You're the one who switched the testing.
What were you thinking?
And pulling little Rose into it?
That was us.
Switching the testing...
how dare you?
Testing is a sacred
covenant between our company
and the American consumer.
You defiled that trust.
Stop, both of you.
You must stop talking.
I think we're winning.
Yhe project is now dead
because we all took the low road.
I was right. We should always
stay on the high road.
Lesson learned. The end.
- And you two are worse than me.
- Actually, I think the lesson here is,
when we're on the low road,
we really have to coordinate better.
Now hear me out. Ted, I need you
to set up another round of testing.
You mentioned
you have access to a dwarf.
- We dress him as a kid...
- First of all, he's 74 years old.
And at the risk of
you not respecting me,
I'm gonna have to say, I'm done.
I'm starting to feel
like a Bond villain.
Here's what's gonna happen.
First, you'll tell all those children
that what you did was wrong.
Most importantly, I need your word
that the dwarf will live out the rest
of his life without our involvement.
I can't promise that.
You never know
when we might need an elderly dwarf.
Listen, I just looked over the specs
that you gave me with my guys,
and there's some really good stuff here.
So thanks.
You're welcome.
So maybe next time we can try
not to undermine each other so much.
- That's what I'm thinking.
- Really?
- Maybe we can even be friends.
- I'd like that.
Great. I just remembered...
You tried to rig the testing
with your daughter.
So we can't be friends,
'cause you're a douche.
Maybe I don't want
to be your friend either.
You hear that? Even a douche
doesn't want to be your friend!
I'm not proud of that.
And then we went back to his place.
I mean, he was my cousin's husband,
and I knew it was wrong,
but they were splitting up.
And you know how it is
when you're ovulating.
I think we've heard enough
about not doing bad things.
See?
We're out of here in five minutes.
Told you that would work.