Cream Team
www.seriessub.com
www.sous-titres.eu
Sometimes when you're working on an
important project with a hard deadline,
you put in a lot of late nights.
Are you sure you don't want me
to have Lucinda come pick you up?
She wouldn't mind eating all my bars
while you sleep,
and then hiding the wrappers
from Mr. Ted.
- I want to stay here with you.
- Good.
Good night.
We did it, Ted.
We now have a working prototype
for the Veridian sleep system.
All the hard work, late nights
and no rest have paid off.
We've cured sleeplessness
and demonstrated irony.
That's great, because the relaxation
convention's only a week away.
I know. It's so exciting.
We heard a commercial for it
this morning.
"Relaxxxacon!
"The world's largest gathering
of relaxation technology."
"72 hours of nonstop, in-your-face,
cutting-edge relaxation."
"Sammy Hagar! Alice Cooper!
And the navy's blue angels!"
We're a little loopy
due to the exhaustion.
Behold.
Inside this box is a transmitter
which will induce the human brain
to emit alpha waves,
gently lulling it
into a restful sleep.
That sounds means it's working.
If you can put up
with it for three minutes,
hello, dreamland!
Turn it off!
Just turn it off!
I have a note.
It's the sound, right?
- It's too loud, correct?
- You've got a few days to crack this.
Otherwise, we are not
gonna make this year's.
Relaxxxacon!
The extra "x" is for more z's.
That is fun.
- One more week. How you holding up?
- I'm a little tired,
and working these hours
is making everyone unhappy.
Bob stole Amy's danish.
She got so mad, she stapled
his lip to his cubicle.
He tried to call for help,
but it came out "helf."
It was actually horrifying.
They had to call an ambulance.
This is bitter.
God, you idiot!
Jenkins, I'm so tired,
I thought you were a sink.
I'm so tired, I thought
you were my mouth.
- Morale does seem pretty low.
- It's like that time
they paid our holiday bonuses
in frozen food.
Potpie Christmas. It did not help
that they made them with real reindeer.
We have a morale problem.
You're always coming to me
with a problem.
Just once I wish you'd greet me
with a sparkler and cotton candy
and tell me I have
the number one album in America.
You handed out
"Veronica in the key of love",
and no one threw it back at you.
Consider that a victory.
Listen,
this deadline is coming up fast,
we've gotta do something
to keep them motivated.
If there's a morale problem,
the company recommends
you take the hardest-working
employee and fire them.
That'll scare the rest of the peasants
back into the fields.
What if,
instead of scaring employees,
we single out the hardest working ones
and reward them with something fun?
Less Stephen King,
more Stephen... The Clown.
I couldn't think of a fun Stephen.
Segal. No, that one's no good either.
Fine. The workers pushed the button
and lit up the light.
They can have their monkey chow.
Now you've all been working
really hard this week,
but no one harder than Jenkins.
He was here when I left last night,
and was here before me.
If I had known this,
I wouldn't have thrown my coffee at him.
You should never
throw your coffee at anyone,
because you never know
if they're going to become a great man.
I threw coffee at a cardinal
on a plane. Now he's the pope.
Back then he was just a guy
in a big hat blocking the movie.
All right, guys.
For he's a jolly good...
Okay, I was wrong.
It's more than a morale problem.
- We worked a man to death.
- I heard about Jenkins' death.
The company feels terrible about it.
People are working too hard.
We need to slow down.
Legal's position is, we don't know
if hard work killed Jenkins.
But he may have had
high cholesterol.
And also that idea that his being dead
may have been a preexisting condition,
and that he may not have been alive
when we hired him.
Apparently he was pretty quiet
in his job interview.
We need to get back
to a normal work schedule,
even if that means we don't make
the Relaxxxacon deadline.
We can introduce our sleep system
next month at the Snooze-a-Palooza
or in July
at the Texas pillow and gun show.
Look, they're giving everyone
an afternoon off.
And we're throwing the guy
a big memorial,
something nice he would never have
treated himself to.
- So that's it? A half a day off?
- Sorry, Ted.
The company feels that if we ease up
just because someone died,
it will only encourage
other people to die.
If it's one thing this company
understands, it's how human beings work.
You better not let Ted see you
looting Jenkins' things.
Ted asked me to clean out Jenkins' desk
so we can ship it all to Florida.
I think Jenkins has family there.
Either that or Florida has a shortage of
miniature mouthwash and cartoons.
This cartoon resonates
with my own experience of office life,
but through a comical lens.
God. You're here one minute,
and then... poof.
You've exhaled your last minty fresh
breath and died in your office,
cakeless.
That's why it's important to always
appreciate the moment you're in,
because the future is a cake
which may never come.
Look how profound
this moment just got.
Let it wash over you, Linda,
because now it's gone.
Did you appreciate it?
I did,
because I always live
in the present.
This is a good moment, too.
Savor it. I am.
And now it's gone.
I wish I could live
completely in the present.
That's something about me
I've always wanted to work on.
Maybe I'll attack it this summer.
No, I was gonna do some traveling,
maybe go to Europe.
Also, I want to go up in a blimp...
God! My eyes.
What the hell?
I was helping you
to live in this moment.
It hurts!
Exactly. You're in pain,
and so you're completely
in the present.
When you're in there,
you're living your life.
You're not caught up in what
could have been or what might be.
That makes sense.
And so the student
becomes the master.
I'm in this moment.
Excellent. Now quick,
look at the Dilbert cartoon.
It's fun now.
Because you're giving it
your complete focus.
Now let's go listen to my CD.
It'll blow your mind.
Since the company wouldn't ease up on
the schedule, I'd use the memorial
to encourage everyone
to take better care of themselves.
You know what I remember about Jenkins?
He used to be alive.
So pace yourself, know your limits,
and if you feel yourself dying...
tell your supervisor.
I can't believe Ted's making me
speak at this thing.
- You knew Jenkins better than anybody.
- I didn't know him.
Nobody did.
All I did was throw coffee at him.
Things were not always smooth
between the two of you,
but in the end,
you understood each other.
Chest bump for good luck?
Now I'd like to ask Lem Hewitt
to say a few words.
These sugar cookies are great.
I'll have 'em at my memorial.
I love sugar cookies.
When I was a kid, my mom
used to make them.
But instead of sugar,
she'd use Brandy.
And instead of dipping them in milk,
she'd dip them in Brandy...
What's going on?
My mind was drifting,
I'm trying to stay in the moment.
Now I know what a beard
of fingers would feel like.
It's just as I had imagined.
Gordon Jenkins was a good man.
But he was also a complex man.
For example, he liked coffee,
but he didn't like having
coffee thrown at him.
In fact, Jenkins hated being
burned by any hot liquid.
In that way, he was like many of us,
sensitive to heat.
What a character.
Goodbye, Jenkins.
I hope you're throwing
coffee at God right now.
Nice work. Goose bumps.
- Really?
- Sure. Why not?
- Are you sure that's right?
- That's fine.
Was a man who loved his work.
He lived for it,
and in all but the
legally culpable sense,
he died for it.
And so we must ask ourselves,
how do honor this great man?
By giving up on the project
he held so dear?
I said, by giving up
on the project he held so dear?
By quitting on him
and his dream of creating
the most advanced sleep
system in human history?
Or by finishing the job
Carl Gordon Jenkins
Gordon Jenkins started
so that his death
will not be in vain?
By working day and night
to meet our deadline
and storm the walls of relaxation.
My friends, we will complete
this project on time,
and we will do it for Jenkins!
- For Jenkins
- I can't hear you.
- For Jenkins!
- Avenge him!
Who do we kill?!
Insomnia, and who do we kill it for?
- Jenkins!
- You're damn right.
Now let's go upstairs
and get back to work,
for tonight, we dine in hell!
Sorry, Ted.
The company didn't think
sad was the way to go.
Veronica's speech inspired people
to work even harder.
The company liked what it saw,
so the next day,
it shifted the Jenkins mobile
into turbo drive.
After day care,
- I'll sleep in your office again?
- Look at you, saying "get to"
to make me feel better.
Honey, I know my being busy is hard,
- but it's just for a few more days.
- At least your couch is comfortable.
So we're doing posters now?
The company got us these
to remind us what we're working for.
Plus, they got us these neat little
rubber wristbands for free.
It says, "Work strong for Jenkins."
The company is exploiting Jenkins' death
to make people work harder.
The company said that Jenkins said
that some people would say that.
I just can't believe
it's one of the finders.
The finders?
One of the eight people
who found his body.
Lem!
Wake up!
The cool accountants
are on their way down.
- Damn it. And the lab is such a mess.
- Perry and Todd and beaver?
Why are they coming down here?
Stop questioning me.
Help clean this place up.
- Clean lab, bro.
- Yeah, whatever.
So you were friends with Jenkins?
Me?
We were pretty tight. Sure.
That's sick.
What was he really like?
He had a huge heart.
I remember him saying once,
"Lem, you are my best
friend, and if I should die,
"at least I'll die knowing
one really cool guy.
"You, Lem, the cool guy
I'm referring to."
Nice.
We're gonna step outside
to take a cigarette break.
- Do you want to come?
- I don't smoke,
- but I'd love to watch you guys smoke.
- Me, too.
Then it's settled. We all get
to hang out with you guys.
Oh, sorry, odd lab dude.
The smoking area's kinda small.
Well, isn't it all of the outdoors?
For the love of God,
please don't ruin this for me.
Linda, I need your testing report
on the sleep system packaging.
Marketing keeps...
I'm going to count to one.
Sorry.
It helps me stay in the moment.
If they don't hold
your attention, look deeper
until you find what's interesting.
Like right now, I'm losing
interest in this moment.
And so I'm going to...
Sweep the leg.
That's what this moment needed.
The company's exploiting Jenkins
to get people to work harder.
There's posters and bracelets.
There's an inspirational video
about him playing.
I got them to use one of the songs from
"Veronica in the key of love."
The settlers crossing the prairie.
Jonas Salk discovering
the polio vaccine
Gordon Jenkins writing
the table of contents
for the Veridian
sleep system manual.
Great achievements take hard work.
Shouldn't you try to be
more like Gordon Jenkins?
Yes, you should.
It was the best elevator video since
the soft-core porn one about recycling.
But if the company keeps
using Jenkins to rev people up,
someone else'll get hurt or dead.
It's just for a few more
days until relaxation,
and then the Jenkins thing will end.
Because knowing how much
this company loves productivity,
14-hour days'll become
the new normal.
- The Jenkins thing will end.
- And so will the 14-hour days.
- Veronica, the 14-hour days?
Jenkins, goodbye. Adios, Jenkins.
- Jenkins no more.
- You gotta be kidding me.
So they really are gonna
make this permanent?
None of us'll see
our families again. And I like Rose.
I wasn't entirely sold
in the first six months,
but I'm way into her.
I'm gonna go tell everyone
in this department
- and they are not gonna stand for it.
- Ted, you adorable little flower.
They'll quit? If they do,
the company will just replace them.
Then I go upstairs
and convince management
that what they're doing is immoral.
I'm glad I tried that one
out on you before going up there.
Ted, no one knows
how many licks it takes
to get to my moral center,
but I can see how this is important
to you, so here's the deal...
if you want to get the company
off this, you have to show them
that this pace'll cost them money,
'cause the company loves its money.
If they could, they'd go to strip clubs
and throw naked women at money.
So Jenkins hooks this 6-foot trout,
and it's freaking out,
flopping around the boat.
And Jenkins hated the sight of blood
because of his time in the Mossad.
So I had to reach past
those razor-sharp teeth
and pull the hook out for him.
We hugged and wept,
and Jenkins said to me, "Lem,
"you... are my best friend."
- Can I talk to you for a minute?
- Oh, sure.
That was our fishing story
but it was you who were flopping around,
and I was the one who took it out,
and there was no fish because
it happened at a sporting goods store.
- And it is my wife who was in Mossad.
- Phil, the cool accountants like me.
They let me go buy them cigarettes.
And I need more Jenkins stories
than that coffee spilling one.
I feel like Jenkins is replacing me.
That's ridiculous.
Let's have lunch later,
just you and me.
It's broasting chicken day
in the cafeteria.
It'll give us another chance
to figure out what broasting is.
I do want to get
to the bottom of that.
We'll have lunch.
I just hope "broasting" is not a typo,
like that butter crotch pudding.
So I've been trying to live in
the moment, but it's really hard
because a lot of my moments
aren't that interesting.
So I was wondering...
do you want to have sex right now?
That feels really right,
but I'm in the middle of something.
In fact, you can help me.
I need to sabotage the sleep system
and make sure it's not finished
for Relaxxxacon.
Cool. That's not sex but it beats
getting knocked to the floor so hard,
you want to go back to Wisconsin and
get your master's in cheese sciences.
Yes, it does.
I need to show that overworking people
will make them so tired,
they'll make mistakes,
and that will cost the company money.
Yeah. This could be a great moment.
We'll go to the basement
and get a fire hose.
Then we get ten pies,
a ramp and a motorcycle...
All I need is your computer. You have
access to the shipping database.
And I need to cancel an order of parts
for the sleep system prototype.
And you want to use my computer
so you don't get in trouble.
Nice try, crisp.
Sweep the leg.
You're not gonna get in trouble.
It'll just look like an anonymous worker
making a sleepy mistake.
Fine.
Lem, I talked to the chef, it turns out
that broasting is a combination of,
and I'm quoting, "roasting
and get the hell out of my kitchen."
He wouldn't tell me the proportions.
Who's in the urn?
It's him, isn't it?
Jenkins has no family out here,
so the company asked me
to pick up his ashes.
I see.
Well, you two enjoy your lunch.
What was I supposed to do,
leave him in a car?
It's a hot day.
He's already ashes.
I know you don't like him,
but he is my friend now.
So why don't you come
join us for lunch?
I'm sure the three of us
can work this out.
Or...
why don't I do this?!
You two are jerks.
It is 8:00 PM and the shipment of parts
for the sleep system never got here.
Now we won't make our deadline,
and the company will learn
that pushing people too hard
leads to mistakes.
How do I feel about that?
The parts shipment didn't arrive.
We'll never be ready in time.
Where's your Jenkins now?
They didn't come?
This is terrible. What are we gonna do,
go home to our families?
Okay.
Can I have everyone's attention,
please?
We are all disappointed
we're not gonna make the deadline.
Now Jenkins' soul is going to hell!
No, Sheila.
That's just something the elevator said.
When we push ourselves too hard,
mistakes get made.
- And now there's no possible way...
- I've got the parts!
No way.
They didn't come 'coz someone was tired
so the company can't work us so hard.
Last night, I was so sleepy,
I accidentally opened the database,
and I saw
someone had canceled the order.
So I drove all night to Stockton,
brought the order back.
I've been driving for 20 straight hours.
I took everything.
Watch how fast I can run.
Now we can go back to work.
For Jenkins!
- For Jenkins!
- No, wait!
The company is using Jenkins
to get you all to work harder.
But the thing is,
it's not gonna be just for this project.
The company wants to make
these crazy hours the new normal.
But we can't work this way forever.
No, we can't.
So I'm going back to my old schedule.
I don't care what they do to me. I'm
taking my daughter and I'm going home.
So we weren't working
this hard for Jenkins?
We were doing it all
for the company?
But Jenkins was still
a great man, right?
You were with him when he helped
that killer whale find its way home.
I had not heard that one.
Was that an embellishment of the time
I helped that large woman
with the hole in the top of her head
find her way back to her apartment?
Actually, I stole
that story from "Free Willy."
I've been using Jenkins for my own gain,
just like the company.
All those stories I told about Jenkins
were really just things I did with Phil.
Phil is the great man
and Phil is my best friend.
Who's Phil?
- Where are you going?
- I've had it. I'm going home.
But it's still dark out.
I have to pee.
Can it wait?
We're kinda having a moment here.
Nope. Sorry.
Hold the door!
- I'm going with you.
- You're supporting me on this?
Oh, no. I just have a dinner date.
All my stuff's still here. They didn't
spring the trap door on me in the lobby.
So I guess I haven't been fired.
Nope. We won.
Apparently after we stormed out
last night,
the whole department
filed out behind us.
So the company backed down
on the new hours?
I... we did it,
because I/we stood up
for what was right.
I/we am proud of me/us.
I/me, too, Ted.
Together, we're like Gandhi.
I'm skinny, and you're tan.