Communication... It's important
to any successful relationship.
It's true between people
and between a company and its employees.
Debbie.
Relax.
Breathe.
Turn.
I wanted to communicate to you an idea
about the meals-ready-to-eat project.
- I'm sorry. It's my fault.
- What's your fault?
- I'm not prepared to have a meeting.
- We're not having a meeting.
I'm not prepared. I wish I was.
Because when I'm not prepared,
I get nervous
and repeat-y.
Repeat-y.
Why don't I just jot my idea down
and send it to you?
That would be fantastic.
Fantastic.
She gets all nervous around me.
Luckily, talking to Debbie isn't
the only way we communicate around here.
There's also the memo.
Memo 314...
employees must not use
offensive or insulting language
in the workplace.
"Employees must now use offensive
or insulting language in the workplace"?
This has to be a mistake. Why would
they want us to swear at each other?
Maybe they're trying to make the people
at work seem more like a real family,
butt-munch.
This is gonna be good.
Like everything the company does to us,
it's gotta be about saving money.
Maybe when someone's called
a "lazy sack of crap," they work harder
so they can just be
a "sack of crap."
This will be a problem.
People here follows memos.
Especially since that memo came out
saying we have to follow memos.
This one is gonna cause
potty-mouth chaos.
Ted's gearing up for a burst of
middle-management leadership.
Out goes the chest,
up goes the chin...
I am going to go get this fixed.
And away.
This whole memo thing is bringing up
this strange sensation.
It's like my feelings are itchy.
Sounds like something human
is trying to fight its way out of you.
Yes, I think it's an emotion...
Like joy or spicy food.
Technically, spicy food isn't a...
So what is it about the memo
that brings all this up?
It reminds me of another memo five years
ago, when I was promoted to this job.
I was up against Walter...
Who had the same last name as I do,
although we pronounce it differently.
There's another way
to pronounce "Palmer"?
In his family, the "p" is silent.
I think they're dutch.
Sounds like their stupid handiwork,
with their cheeses
and their giant propeller buildings.
So Walter... "Almer"?
I know.
Those people are unbelievable.
Anyway, they announced
the promotion in a memo,
Congratulating V. Palmer, only then,
it went on to wish him well.
I put through the paperwork,
but I've never known whether that job
was really meant for me or Walter.
Maybe that itchy feeling you have
is guilt.
Guilt is a powerful emotion.
Every Thanksgiving,
it makes me take three planes
just so I can visit
my racist aunt Cookie.
So this is guilt?
I always used to counteract
this feeling with other emotions,
like sugar or drunk.
You should talk Walter.
Maybe find some way to help him.
Guilt is a terrible thing
to carry around.
Well, I do hate this feeling.
- I hate it like I hate...
- Don't tell me. The dutch?
I don't hate the dutch.
I love the dutch.
That's why I hold them
to a higher standard.
I don't know where this came from,
but it's a mistake,
so I was hoping
HR could put out a correction.
- We'll look into the matter.
- Really?
The company doesn't
make mistakes like this, Mr. Crisp.
What about that memo
announcing "casual fribsday"?
The company said
that wasn't a mistake.
They explained that the ancient
Mayans prophesied fribsday...
The first ever eighth day of the week
which will occur in 2024.
And the company believes
should be celebrated casually.
I'll wear a denim pantsuit.
And when they urged
all employees to "carpoop"?
That was not mandatory.
Thank god.
But we found out what people will do
to park slightly closer to the building.
So you're not gonna
help me with this?
Sorry. I like the memo.
All day long, I have to listen
to people like you complain.
Now I can finally tell 'em
what I think,
you white-toothed Ken doll.
Having white teeth and looking like
a handsome doll is not exactly...
Turd-hat.
They weren't going to retract the memo
about being to be rude and abusive,
and that meant things were going to get
very confusing for Phil and Lem
who unfortunately
never read their memos.
And so this new line
of meals-ready-to-eat
gives the soldier in the field
a portable meal
with the home-cooked flavor of something
mom used to chemically dehydrate
and vacuum pack.
I was wondering
if there's enough protein content,
you boob.
Excuse me?
- I was wondering about the protein.
- But then you said...
- You boob.
- There it is.
I suppose we could add
more protein to the thing we call
"beige block three,"
or "stroganoff."
It's got plenty of protein,
you big-eyed stick insect.
- The problem is the vegetables.
- Okay,
let's just try to keep it
under control here.
Don't listen to these bucktoothed
hillbillies. Taste is the real problem.
It's a battlefield, not a four-star
restaurant, back-alley crab muffin.
I gotta ask... What's going on?
Because this meeting is a lot saucier
than the one yesterday.
Looks like somebody didn't
get the memo.
He asks a simple question and you give
him sarcasm for the eighties?
It's an actual memo.
They want us to insult each other...
Sir?
That wasn't a good one.
But in my meetings,
that won't happen.
- But the memo said we had to.
- We're not doing it in here, Pudberger.
What?
That's his last name.
So Veronica went down
to the basement...
Hoping she'd feel better
if she talked to Walter Palmer.
Hello, Walter.
I don't believe it. Veronica Palmer.
I'm sorry, Palmer. I never could
get used to the way you pronounce it.
Here, I brought you a cake
and a jar of herring.
Maybe you can wait until I leave
before you smear the cake with it.
I'm not dutch.
And the dutch don't smear herring
on half the things you say they do.
But thanks for the cake.
Is it my birthday?
I sort of lose track
of time down here.
No, I just want to say
I've always felt bad
that we had to compete
for the same job.
Please.
I'm the one who feels bad.
I've hated how I acted in the bull pen
after losing that promotion.
It was not a good impression of you,
and I'm sorry
I stretched out your shoes.
Don't worry. They were
the cheap footwear of my former life.
Can I buy you something
to cheer this place up?
Maybe a lava lamp
or a freezer of steaks.
I'm the one who feels guilty
about the way I handled your promotion.
Let me make it up to you...
Take you out for a drink or something.
Ew.
Are very thoughtful, but I can't.
OI get it. You're still mad at me.
I'm such a jerk.
And I deserve to carry this guilt around
back and forth in this tiny basement.
I'll have a drink with you.
Any chance you have a bottle
so we can just knock it out right now?
That meeting was chaos.
I hate all the name-calling.
And it's not because my mama is fat
and does sit around the house.
I kind of like it.
It makes people freer...
Like they can say
whatever's on their mind.
Even Debbie spoke up today,
and she never talks in meetings.
We're not doing it in here,
Pudberger.
That's his last name.
- Let's just try to regroup.
- Wait!
You pretty-boy suit rack.
What this MRE needs
is Ethiopian stew.
It's hearty, nutritious and simple,
like all of you bastards.
She's never opened her mouth before,
- and it was a good suggestion.
- It was a good idea.
But Mark called her a Tory-loving
royalist, and it all fell apart again.
You don't like this because
you always have to be in control.
- You're a control freak.
- I don't always have to be in control.
Although,
it is my exact job description.
You're tall, you're handsome,
you got the power tie, the power suit.
People think you're intimidating,
and you like that because it means
- you get everything you want.
- First of all,
my appearance is not my fault.
God made me this way, and then
he told me where to shop for suits.
Ted, a little chaos
can be a good thing.
My grandpa met my grandma
when a Tornado blew her into his barn.
He pulled the rake out of her chest
and proposed on the spot.
We really should have
been reading these memos.
Damn! We didn't have to work
on Thanksgiving?
And look! Like I suspected, we were
supposed to be wearing lead aprons
when we were working
on that genital x-Ray project.
Here it is.
"Employees must now use
offensive or insulting language
"in the workplace."
I can play this game.
I wrote that humorous column
in my college newspaper...
"Lem's snappy answers
to theoretical physics questions."
You've been Lem-basted.
I'm terrible at insults.
As a child,
I was beaten up constantly.
The best comeback
I ever came up with was,
"You're right.
I'll work on that."
I can help you,
you sad jar of hobo urine.
I've been Lem-basted.
Who is that relaxed
and approachable guy?
Is that Ted?
Why, yes, it is.
You look like you're on your way
to mix cocktails.
I was thinking about what you said.
About how I might seem a little
controlling and intimidating.
So I tell you to take a look
at the way you approach life,
and you put different clothes on?
What a dill weed.
And that's not
a company-mandated insult.
That one came from the heart.
Come on. The clothes are symbolic...
the first step in saying
that I'm willing to make a change.
Actually, I was hoping
the clothes would cover it.
I had the worst night last night.
Didn't you get the memo?
Casual fribsday is not until 2024.
I'm trying to be less intimidating.
Apparently, my...
That's the fastest
I've ever lost interest in something.
I went out with Walter Palmer
last night because of you.
Me? What did I do?
You started questioning memos,
which brought up this guilt,
so I agreed to have drinks with the guy.
He told me, after he lost the promotion,
his wife left.
I felt even more guilty,
so I let him take me out to dinner,
where I learned
he also lost his house.
Then I find out
he's living in his parents' basement,
which is so damp, his dog got arthritis,
fell down the stairs
and now has to be carried around
like a suitcase.
- So I let him kiss me.
- Oh, my God!
But then I still felt guilty,
so I let him feel me up.
Yeah. I'm thinking
I might need new breasts.
These are covered in sadness.
This is like the most
depressing "penthouse" letter ever.
I kept waiting for the guilt to lift,
but it never did.
What am I gonna do?
Maybe I'll buy him a boat.
Guys like boats, right?
I had a great time last night.
I was wondering if maybe
I could take you to dinner later
for a little Walter and Veronica,
version 2.0.
How would you like a boat?
Something you could just get in
and go...
Really shove off...
Just get out of here.
I couldn't take a gift like that
from you. I'd feel too guilty.
Yeah, guilt. What a horrible thing.
See you at 8:00.
And this time, please don't say,
"thank you for kissing with me."
Can you press "10" for me,
you rat-face Nazi?
Your breasts should be on display
at the swiss museum of miniatures.
You said 10, right?
Before we start,
I realize some people may think
I'm controlling and a intimidating.
But I want you to know,
all ideas are welcome.
Really.
I want to hear from everyone.
Could you repeat that in English?
I don't speak wuss-ass.
We're not doing that in here.
I'm so very sorry.
You won't hear another word out of me.
So not being controlling
lasted for about one second?
Sorry.
The naggity-nag-nag bitchy-bitch
is right.
Anything anyone wants to say
is fine by me.
You heard the corporate chimp.
Start making suggestions
for meals-ready-to-eat
before his head
goes back up his butt.
I like fresh tomatoes,
right off the vine.
Mark, use your head.
How are we gonna get fresh...
Open forum, chim chim.
Just let the ideas flow.
I'm sorry, Mark.
I'm writing it down.
Sometimes when I'm lonely,
I like to watch myself eat.
- Why don't we put a mirror?
- You like to watch yourself eat?
I'm writing it down.
I like to have some wine
with dinner.
They're soldiers!
Writing it down.
- I need your help, slut.
- What's the problem, tight-ass?
Easy, Linda.
It's a memo, not a magic shield.
I need to make a man
run screaming from my life.
I'm happy you came to me for advice,
but sad
this is my area of expertise.
I went out again with Walter.
Now if I blow him off, he'll think
that I hurt him five years ago,
then looked him up, got him to fall in
love with me so I could hurt him again.
Plus, I backed over his foot
when I was leaving,
which,
according to our relationship math,
means tonight's the night.
In my experience,
scaring a man away is pretty easy.
Basically, you're gonna want to put
three words into heavy rotation:
future, babies, commitment.
Back off! I need my space.
Those words are powerful.
What are you ciphering there,
Jethro?
I've really enjoyed repeating
the put-downs you've been feeding me,
but I want to do it on my own.
Give a man an insult,
he can hurt people for a day.
Teach a man to insult,
he can hurt people who tease him
because he never learned to fish.
Anyway, I've devised a formula.
Look at that.
You had a problem in your life
and who stepped up to help you? Math.
She has always been there for you.
If she ever took physical form,
I'd leave my wife and marry her.
Stand in line, my friend.
It's really quite simple.
You take a person's
most marked physical feature,
compare it to genitalia...
Male, female or animal...
And end with the suffix
"-bag," "-wipe" or "-muncher."
You could also add
an optional reference to excretion
from any of the glorious openings
offered by the human body.
Should we take her for a spin?
Excuse me, Roger?
Your head looks like lizard butt flap,
you snot wipe.
It looks like
somebody can't get enough of me.
You're right. I can't.
In fact, we need to talk about us
and the future of our babies
and how they'll be committed.
That's a lot to take in. Okay.
I need this relationship to have
a future because I need babies.
That's right...
Big, screaming babies
shooting out of my uterus,
just stacking up like cordwood.
- Really?
- Yes, sir.
That's all I ever think about...
The future, babies and commitment.
Slow down!
This is happening a little fast.
Okay! I'll do it!
- Babies, babies, babies, babies...
- Yes!
As many as you want!
My parents always say
that since my wife left,
I've been too cautious
about relationships, but damn it!
This is the one. I know it is.
Let's light this candle
and blast off into a calm, settled,
monogamous relationship.
Look at me.
I'm so happy, I can't feel my legs.
So I took everyone's ideas
for the meals-ready-to-eat project,
and here it is.
The specs called for a soldier to carry
three of these in his backpack.
Now we have to design
a 14-foot soldier.
Good news, Ted.
I cured Walter
of his fear of commitment.
He wants to get portraits painted
of the two of us with his suitcase dog,
all wearing turtlenecks.
I've got a box lunch
the size of a handball court.
Now I gotta go find Phil and Lem
and straighten out this MRE disaster.
Don't "boo-hoo" me.
Did that MRE touch your boobies?
Then shut the hell up.
What I didn't know was
Phil and Lem weren't in the lab.
They were having
an entirely different adventure.
Test-driving
their new insult-generating formula.
Your eyes look like
two beady rabbit pellets
on the face
of a monkey-licking pus-bomb.
- You've just been Phil-abusted.
- Nice!
That's it.
Sill up your canker-blossomed hole,
you ale-soused apple-John.
That was the elizabethan model.
Ye have been served.
Nice man-boobs,
for a panty-snatching steroid muncher.
What's the matter?
Didn't you get the memo?
He didn't.
He delivers the water.
He doesn't work here.
Thank God, that finally broke.
I may go home early today
and never come back.
You can't go home.
I need you guys.
And that's it... the insulting
language stuff has got to end,
you douche-nozzles.
Sorry. That was one for the road.
We just got Ted-ucated.
Look, Janet, it's crazy out there.
Two of my guys
just got beaten with water.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing I can do, Mr. Crisp.
I don't like
that memo anymore either.
Way too many people
are having fun with my name.
I'm surprised it took this memo
to get that train out of the station.
I've had several complaints,
but the company is not going to admit
it made a mistake.
What if it didn't have to admit it?
What if it could just say
that it's making a new policy,
based on a groundswell
of employee opinion?
Look at that pretty little head
of yours, working up ideas.
I'm a fan.
I like you, too.
So we gonna do this?
What are we talking about, exactly?
End this policy.
That.
If we call it a groundswell,
I think the company would go for it.
That way,
it gets to pat itself on the back
for listening
and being a great communicationer.
"Communicator."
That's not what it says
in the handbook.
I just got this memo. We don't get
to swear at each other anymore.
It was due to a "groundsmell."
The good news is,
this company does not squander
its best and brightest typing memos.
So is this all going in the MRE?
It now stands for
"meal really enormous."
This is what happens
when you take everyone's suggestions.
Why did you do that?
Because someone I care about
thought I was controlling.
You care that much
what I think about you?
You are talking about me?
So is any of this stuff usable?
Debbie's ethiopian stew
is pretty good.
And when it hardens,
it forms an unbreakable arch support
in your foot.
Well, see? There you go.
All you needed was one good idea.
And you got that
because you listened to everyone,
which you did
because you listened to me.
In case you missed it,
the lesson here is listen to me.
What's this I'm hearing
about ethiopian stew shoes?
It's all they're talking about
upstairs.
Speaking of exciting developments...
When I was in HR,
I dug up this old memo
about your promotion.
All the executives
had to sign off on it.
Really?
"I know we agreed not to let women
into upper management,
but Veronica Palmer is man-smart.
And, hello, as she breaks
through the glass ceiling,
we can all look up her skirt."
That promotion was mine.
I didn't ruin Walter's life.
What is wrong
with those old farts upstairs?
Seriously, they wrote that in 2005.
I am off to scrape Walter
off my shoe.
- You may want to be more gentle...
- I have a hickey on my belly.
And so,
Veronica went down to the basement
and broke up with Walter.
But then she made it up to him
by giving him a new aboveground office.
Thank you.
Phil and Lem
retired their insult formula
and made amends with the water guy.
And I realized communication
isn't just about talking.
It's about listening.
I just wanted to say
I appreciated your work on the MRE,
and when it comes to any other thoughts
you may have, I'm listening.
I think we should go out, Ted.
You can do whatever you want to me.
And just because I listen doesn't mean
I have to take every suggestion.