Cream Team
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
I like the people I work with,
but I've always believed it's important
to keep your personal life separate
from your work life. Otherwise...
- You had sex with that girl last night?
- Gee, that's totally your business.
But, I'm trying to keep
my personal life...
Much more accessible to all of us?
Good, that makes work interesting.
- I think work makes work interesting.
- No wonder she wouldn't have sex.
That... That wasn't...
I was the one...
We both felt...
You shoulda shown her that flustered
thing. It woulda totally sealed it.
- No, I wasn't...
- Yeah, that.
Good morning, Lem.
- What's with the red lab coat?
- I don't know.
When I went to my locker this morning,
instead of a white lab coat,
which is what's been in my locker
every morning for the last 11 years,
there was this.
Are all our lab coats red?
No. Mine is still white.
Okay. I am not angry. I just need
to know what's happening.
I don't know.
Well, change doesn't always
have to be bad, right?
Remember when I stopped doing that
finger gun thing? Everyone liked that.
Oh, my god. It's true.
It's even redder than I imagined.
And I imagined it quite red.
- What does it mean?
- We don't know.
You're lying!
I'm sorry. It's the coat.
Its differentness is making
me say things.
That's it.
We need answers.
I've spent my entire life
trying to blend in.
When I shaved off my fu manchu,
I thought I was there. Now this?
I iss that fu manchu.
Talk about pizzazz.
So the testing results
were inconclusive.
Usually that's what people say
when something tests badly,
and this is a good example of that.
Turns out developing cheese that
never spoils is harder than we thought.
Right now, it's more of a
cheddar-colored fabric that does spoil.
So we need you to talk to Chet
and get him to push the deadline.
Are you purring?
Or growling?
Oh, man. Are you gonna start
growling now when you're mad?
Because that's gonna be hard
to adjust to.
- What? What is so damn important?
- You fell asleep.
Well, maybe you two are boring.
Did you ever think of that?
Veronica has
a very high-powered job.
To blow off steam, she recently started
a new, very exciting relationship
with an extremely passionate man
with huge appetites
named Mordor.
He's also a world-class magician.
Unfortunately, this new relationship
has made Veronica
a little distracted at work.
Occupied.
You're spreading cream cheese
on your iPhone?
Then where's my bagel?
The relationship is very intense.
This weekend, Mordor and I
are going scuba diving.
Last weekend, we raced cars
in the desert and ate a rattlesnake...
And a goat that wandered into our camp
and then a light salad.
But mostly, we have sex...
Hours and hours of it.
Last weekend, I helped my daughter
build a house of legos.
I know I've been a little
distracted lately, but I'll be fine.
I'm just living an exciting
and full life...
Burning the candle at both ends,
the way my great-grandfather,
a misunderstood candle maker,
insisted candles should be burned.
Whenever I have sex, I have to be alert
the next day so I don't make mistakes.
I have to be alert during sex
so I don't make mistakes.
I always have to be alert.
A woman that make mistakes during sex
can make mistakes during sex?
I'm on a very tight deadline
with this, Ted.
I need Veronica to focus.
You know her boyfriend.
You should tell him to dial it down
so Veronica can do her job.
Let's see.
Would a guy welcome another guy telling
him to have less sex with his girl?
Yeah. That a normal thing
guys tell each other to do.
You think it's okay for a relationship
to be completely on the man's terms?
- God, you'd be hard to go out with.
- I am fantastic to go out with.
I'm thoughtful as a man can be
while still pillaging like
a viking in the bedroom.
But I am not getting involved
in Veronica's personal life.
So my boss gets to have
all the sex-fun of a relationship
while all the stress of being
exhausted trickles down to me?
Man, capitalism blows.
We have a problem.
- What's with the red lab coat?
- Exactly.
- The company wants me to wear it.
- Why?
Exactly.
I called the laundry people, it was
assigned to me but they don't know why.
The laundry people...
Useless.
Well, they do do laundry.
You love the laundry people.
You take their side in everything.
First of all,
I do love the laundry people.
Secondly, i'll look into the coat.
In the meantime,
maybe it's not a bad thing.
Maybe the company is singling you out
because you did something good.
Maybe it's an honor.
I did finish the super-fast spy
pigeon project ahead of schedule.
I worked on this project.
I'm the one that made it wireless.
Before me, it could only spy
on people right next to it.
- Why didn't I get a red lab coat?
- I did more work than you.
I was late one day
because my wife was choking.
It's not fair! I'm penalized
because my wife eats breakfast fast.
She's hungry in the morning.
- He's here.
- Oh, thank god.
- Who?
- I don't care. It gets me out of this.
Mordor. Veronica's boyfriend.
He says he's surprising her
and taking her to lunch and sex.
The man is relentless
and very candid.
Can you imagine how great
it would be to just take Veronica
out in the middle of the day
and have lunch with her?
You should try to aim higher
with your fantasies.
Veronica is supposed to meet with Chet
this afternoon, get us that extension.
What if she comes back
exhausted and purring?
You're right. All right.
I'll go talk to Mordor.
The man lives a life of excess.
I could sell him on the adventure of
having less sex with his hot girlfriend.
I may phrase it differently.
I need to talk to you about something.
That's a little awkward.
- You have a crush on me.
- What? No. What?
Men often do, Ted. I find it's best
to just get it out there.
No, no.
This is about Veronica.
See, she has
a very high-pressure job.
And she does it with 100% focus.
Oh, she's the same in bed
or when dismembering a goat.
Right. So you and the other
animals have seen it.
The thing is, lately,
she hasn't been getting enough sleep...
Because she's with you...
Doing things, things that are fun,
but, you know, tire a gal out.
Are you suggesting that sometimes
when I'm with Veronica, I should
- Just let her go to sleep?
- Exactly.
Then have sex with her?
I start again.
It would be good if you had
less sex with veronica.
The end.
Hey.
What did you say to Mordor?
I didn't tell him to have sex
with her while she's sleeping.
Why? What did he do?
I walked in to the supply closet,
he was there with Ashley
and they were not
looking for supplies
unless she uses her ya-ha
to store office supplies
and he uses his yang-doodle
to look for things.
- That's what mom calls it.
- All I said was
he should dial it down a little bit.
He take that as
a green light to fool around,
he was going here
like he wanted Sparks to come out.
Maybe it was a mistake to get involved
in Veronica's personal life.
Oh, don't be that guy
who points fingers.
No one likes a pointer.
Even in the dog world,
they're seen as insufferable.
- Veronica has to know what's going on.
- Oh, no. She doesn't need to know.
No one needs to know.
In fact, you should forget.
And I will, too.
Forget what? Don't even remember.
It's happening in the office.
She's gonna find out.
- Not from office gossip.
- Me?
I didn't want to get involved
in this in the first place.
Still bringing that up! Got a stick up
your boodle-doodle about that.
We need to talk.
What?
I was having the best dream
about Mordor.
He makes me so happy.
I feel free and untethered,
like a spy pigeon without a wire.
So what's up?
The red lab coat.
- The guys 're wondering what it means.
- You can't tell them,
but it has no meaning whatsoever.
- It was given out randomly.
- Why?
The company commissioned a study
which showed that any change
in the work environment
increases productivity.
- Any change, it doesn't matter what.
- That's crazy.
Giving one person a different lab coat
can't make everybody work harder.
- I am going to win that coat tomorrow.
- No, you're not,
I'm working faster
and more efficiently than ever.
So the painted stripe, that appeared
in the hallway last week?
You mean two days
before quarterly reports were due,
all of which were turned in early?
And the drinking fountain
that stopped working for no reason?
That was broken, Ted.
You people are paranoid.
No wonder the company has to
secretly manipulate you.
So... Is there anything else?
Nope.
Mordor is having an affair
with somebody in the office.
Someone walked in on them
and I thought I should tell you. Sorry.
- But why?
- Why would he do this?
He's getting enough from me.
Well, who knows why people
do what they do, you know?
The important thing
is not to blame anyone
or look for answers, really.
Some things shouldn't be probed.
The's an unfortunate
choice of words.
I rambled on like that for ten minutes,
somehow using the words
"thrust," "prod," "rigid"
and "impale."
All comforting terms.
It's good she knows about Mordor.
If it were me, I'd want to know.
Is she okay?
I think so.
They haven't been
together that long.
I'm guessing they'll be okay.
Hey, scuba girl. You ready to go?
You shot me!
I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
So?
Who's Ashley?
I was packing up the spear-gun,
and it just went off.
An accident.
Of course it was an accident.
Although, the man
was cheating on me,
and my subconscious
is very protective,
and sometimes, kind of a douche.
- I'm so angry, Ted.
- You have every right to be.
- I'm angry at you.
- You have no right to be.
Why did you tell me
mordor was cheating ome?
I thought you'd want to know.
- Linda would want to know.
- Of course I'd want to know,
but not when there's a spear-gun
sitting 3 feet away
from me and my douchey subconscious.
What were you thinking?
- Ms. Palmer?
- Yes.
He's out of surgery, and he'll fine.
However, we could not save
the spear.
Old joke.
I use it with all the family
of loved ones who survive.
Don't anymore.
Now I have to break up with him,
which is gonna be that much harder
since I just shot him.
Look what you made me do.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm trying to get my wife
to eat slower in the morning.
It's a project.
- What happened to your red lab coat?
- Wasn't in my locker this morning.
I don't get it.
You worked so hard yesterday.
But then, so did I.
Oh. Now I'm sad again.
Morning, ladies.
Notice anything redder
about me?
I am literally shaking
with jealousy. Get out!
I don't want the coat to see me
like this. No, wait.
Let me touch it.
No.
No. Wait.
Your call.
I've been thinking about
how I behaved last night,
I've realized, it wasn't your fault
that Mordor somehow got himself shot.
And so I'd like to apologize.
That's okay.
I'm just glad you're rid of him.
That guy was
a self-absorbed dill-hole.
"Ooh, I'm Mordor. I think
all men are in love with me."
- I mean, seriously, what a doofus.
- We made up.
Oh, good,
'cause now I can stop pretending
I don't like him.
He had an affair, and I shot him.
So we decided to call in.
Plus, I found out why he did it.
Apparently somebody suggested
- that he ease up on our relationship.
- I didn't mean...
It was you?
- What was me?
- My god, Ted.
You don't tell a man like Mordor
to be less passionate.
It's like telling Gandhi
to be less...
Whatever he was.
Thin.
Your job wasn't done.
You were falling asleep
at work with your eyes open.
What if they dried out?
They would've lost their luster.
I was worried.
I don't need you or anyone else
interfering in my life.
You're responsible for
my boyfriend screwing around.
You're the one who shot him.
In my mind.
And then, you call him a dill-hole
right to his face.
- No.
- In my mind.
I think you and I need
a little distance from each other.
That's a good idea.
I'll go to my office.
Actually,
I was thinking
a little more distance.
And so Veronica sent me down
to the ridiculously tiny office.
This is not as bad as I imagined.
Your chair and desk look gigantic
it's cool.
Plus, it would be impossible
to lose anything in here.
It's all great.
So what's up, fellas?
'cause I'm busy getting into my chair.
We're...
unhappy about something.
Is it the coat?
I worked my ass off yesterday
to get that thing.
I can't tell you exactly
what's going on.
I'm in trouble
as it is with Veronica.
But the coat may not be something
you want to work extra hard to get.
It's so beautiful.
Only because you think
it means something, which it may not.
- I know what's going on.
- We're confused.
That's exactly what's happening.
I can't believe
you trashed Veronica's boyfriend.
You never trash the boyfriend.
What if they get back together?
I don't care anymore.
I'm out.
I am done getting in the middle
of Veronica's relationship.
Because believe it or not,
there's an office smaller,
and you have to share it
with someone.
You should be out,
you know nothing about relationships.
I don't know anything
about relationships?
It's because
of your relationship geniusness
that I'm stuck
in Polly Pocket's house.
- We should go.
- We want to go.
Thanks to me? I never told you
to tell her that her boyfriend sucks.
I wouldn't have kept talking about
her sucky boyfriend
- if you hadn't kept bringing him up.
- I had to bring it up,
because you think relationships
are all about what the guy wants.
And by the way, genius,
Polly Pockets doesn't live in a house,
but in a clamshell!
- I know where she lives.
- Really?
Because I think you know less about
Polly Pockets than relationships.
That's better.
So if the coat's not a reward something good},
then that must mean...
It's a punishment
for doing something bad.
It's like a scarlet letter.
Only it's worse,
because it covers the body in shame.
So why'd the company give it to me?
You did break the dieoxolater
defibulation splung manifold last week,
and that sucka is expensive.
If I hadn't tried to protect my eyes,
I might have been able to save it.
Stupid reflexes.
The next morning, I checked in
to see if I could come back.
Good morning, sunshine.
Not yet.
And in the lab...
It was in my locker this morning.
I worked so hard yesterday
to avoid this exact thing.
All we can do is buckle down
and push ourselves even harder.
I hope Veronica forgives me soon,
because I really like doing this...
Which I totally took
for granted before.
What the hell?
Ted! I thought
you were working out of the basement.
I'm getting papers.
What are you doing?
This is...
Tiffany.
Thank you.
See,
I figured it out.
I hurt Veronica by fooling around,
but then she shooted me with a speargun,
that reset the relationship.
So I can fool around again,
as long as I'm willing to let Veronica
hurt me again, which I am,
'cause I like promiscuous sex
far more than I dislike pain.
You know, I didn't want to get involved
in Veronica's personal life,
but now I'm glad I did,
because you don't deserve her.
She is smart, and beautiful,
and confident... Wildly fun in bed...
I've been there. She is
the whole package. You're just a jerk.
And, yes, a mammoth dill-hole.
All right, Ted.
Let's go.
You started this whole thing,
and you insult me in front of Tiffany.
- Let's get this over with.
- I won't fight you, you loon.
Loon?
Could a loon do this?
I think a loon would do that.
It's called quad-dela-ron-sha.
It's an ancient peruvian martial art
involving forceful, repeated slapping.
I'm not gonna fight you.
Wait.
Yes, I'll fight you.
What the hell?
It's like you have
a hundred fingers.
Go get help!
Quad-dela-ron-sha...
It's impossible to defend against.
It's why Peru was never conquered.
Didn't the spanish conquer Peru?
Yes, but then they left quickly.
In fact, quad-dela-ron-sha means:
"Leave,
or we'll start with the slapping."
Did Mordor tell you this?
'cause it's not on Google.
Maybe that was also a lie.
I'm through with him.
I'm sorry about everything.
You stood up for me.
No one's ever done that before.
Thank you.
Maybe it's impossible
to keep your personal life
completely separate from work,
especially when you care about
the people you work with...
And they care about you.
Is he all right?
He's great.
I can't believe he fought
to defend your honor. That is so...
- Hot?
- Actually, It kind of is.
And I told him he didn't know
anything about relationships.
He may not
but he'd sure be good in one.
Again?
What have I done?
{And since I do care about
the people I work with,
I decided to end their suffering.
Since any change helps productivity,
why not make it a positive change
and do something
people can feel good about?
What does it mean?
Maybe we've been asking
too many questions.
Maybe this is the company's equivalent
of sending a dead fish.