A Cream Team
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
Sometimes, a project comes along
that kicks the stress level up.
I need to stay especially calm,
so my people will stay calm.
Cats and kittens, what is going on with
the multi-language translator device?
Ted's overcompensating
for his stress.
- The project must be in huge trouble.
- Our lives as we know them are over!
I just want to make sure
we're on track with the translator.
The Germans are gonna be here
this afternoon for a demonstration.
Oh. Well, we can do that.
- What'd you come in here all calm for?
- The Germans are worried
about working with us,
because, ironically, they think
that we are ruthlessly efficient
and bent on world domination.
That's like when Irish auditors thought
our accounting department drank
- and wrote overly depressing poetry.
- Maybe you could put away
some of your
especially evil creations.
- In case they want to see the lab.
- Evil?
We don't create evil things.
Some might see this long-range
people-skinning laser as evil-ish.
That was designed so you could peel
an orange in your kitchen
while sitting in your living room.
It's used to peel enemy soldiers,
while you sit at the Pentagon.
What about this device?
It'll make it easier for people
to talk to each other,
and with the exception
of almost everything
my wife ever says to me,
- communication is always good.
- They use it to interrogate prisoners.
Why don't we clear everything away,
- except the ficus?
- You mean the man-eating ficus?
All right. I'll try
to keep the Germans upstairs.
Is everything we do down here evil?
Well, that's crazy.
We make a lot of nice stuff, like,
kills.
Slowly kills.
Quickly kills.
Helps shed unwanted pounds!
But also kills.
Oh, my God
Maybe we're evil scientists.
I'm sorry.
I laugh like that when faced
with an unpleasant truth.
That's why I got thrown out
of that Al Gore movie.
Hey, excuse me.
This isn't a library. You can't leave
your trash wherever you want.
Jeez.
Brett, you see that
awesome youtube video
of that goat that sounds like a man?
He keeps yelling "Mark!"
I love that goat.
He's all... "Mark! Mark!"
Do you mind?
That's the last time forward
anything to you guys.
Worried about the deal
with the Germans,
Veronica was also
under a lot of stress.
We believe
the multi-language translator
will create a furor in Germany,
a furor that will sweep
across Europe,
crushing...
No.
What's going on?
Do you live here?
Do all the cubicle workers have
little hobbit holes like this?
No, some of us nest in trees,
others have underground warrens.
Actually, I just found this empty room,
so I decorated a little,
and come here occasionally
to get a break
- from that corporate pit out there.
- Was that thumping noise
the sound of you banging
your head against the wall,
summoning the hobbits
to feast and dance?
Why don't you lay off?
If you want. I'm sorry.
I'm a little sensitive
about the hobbit jokes,
because I think of myself
as having big, floppy feet.
I know. It's crazy, right?
Fine. Don't reassure me
about my giant feet
which I might be
too sensitive about.
Again, thank you.
Anyway, that thumping sound
was this game I came up with
to blow off steam.
You take a bagel,
you stand on this coffee stain,
and you try to bounce it off that wall
and into that air vent.
It's pretty tricky.
Not for me,
because I'm good at everything I do.
I'm not bragging, because bragging is
the one thing I'm not good at.
Although, if I wanted to be,
I'd be excellent at that, too,
- as I've just proved.
- Really?
You'd be better at Linda bagel?
Because, you know... I'm Linda.
And I'm Veronica.
So bagel me.
Veronica is late for our big meeting
with the Germans,
who, of course, are right on time.
What? It's a positive stereotype.
Anyway, now I am stuck
having to charm them all by myself.
Which suddenly, I am fine with.
Pots-damn!
Hello, I'm Ted crisp.
Guten tag, I'm Hans Muller.
This is Carl Hoffman
und our C.E.O. Greta Schulz.
Hello, I am being happy to meet you.
You and I... Do it, I hope.
The coming together?
Okay. I hope so, too.
Fraulein Schulz is not fluent
in English.
She hopes this deal
between our two companies
will come together.
Thanks for the clarification,
Herr buzz kill.
Nothin' but vent!
Do I look like a bus?
'cause I just took you to school.
Suck my big hobbit feet!
Keep your flippers in your clown shoes.
We're going again.
The multiple language
trslator device
will instantaneously
translate any language into any other
and turn this dial
to the desired language.
Sorry I'm late.
There was an emergency
with the dough-based projectile
ventilation targeting system.
Please... Continue.
Phil, who speaks fluent German,
will now speak into the device,
which will translate
what he says into english.
Hello.
I am your friend.
Do not be afraid.
It's me! Phil!
- I thought you worked on the voice.
- We made it more awesome.
Who wouldn't want to sound
like a 90-foot robot, you know?
Our ships are hovering
above all your cities.
Oh, God.
We have unhappy Germans.
Nothing good has ever come
from that.
Okay, we will have this voice fixed
in a couple days.
In the meantime, why don't you relax?
Maybe do some sightseeing?
Yes, on us! Throw on
some leather shorts,
dark shoes, socks up to the knees,
and stomp around our fine city.
Perhaps Ted can stomp me.
Ah, stomp with me.
I not wish to die
from Ted's under-boot.
I got new under-boots.
I'd hate to have
to scrape you off them.
Don't translate that.
Tell her I'd be happy
to take her around.
I saw what was going on in there
between you and her.
When you show her around town,
keep your hands off her gretels.
I was just being friendly.
This deal is too important,
and sex can screw things up.
Why do you think the three stooges
went through so many curlys?
Look at her.
I can have a personal relationship
and not screw up a business deal.
I'm notlike the three stooges.
I have never spent the night
in a mummy museum
or smuggled a chicken
into the opera.
Hello, Toad.
Ted.
Eat me?
Let's go to dinner.
I'm gonna teach you the word "with."
Phil and Lem couldn't stand
the thought of being evil scientists.
Maybe if we came up
with something that's pure good
that the company
couldn't possibly use for evil.
Or... What if we invent something
that's already pure evil?
Then maybe the company will
turn it into something good,
like a horrible device
that drops heavy things on your feet
and tells you the end of movies
you really wanted to see.
I thought you saw "The 6th Sense,"
I was setting down my end of the sofa.
I hadn't, and my toe
will never be the same.
How are glasses and mustache doing
with the translator voice?
Glasses and mustache
are the same person.
And Lem and Phil
need a little bit more time.
The Germans
aren't going to like this.
They're in no hurry to leave town.
Oh, my God. You're jackhammering Gretel
like she's the Berlin wall.
It was a little more romantic
than that.
There was a lot of cheering in German,
followed by heartfelt congratulations.
If something goes wrong,
you could blow this whole deal.
You think nothing will go wrong,
because it's you.
I do not think that, although nothing
will go wrong. It's me.
That's hubris. You're cocky.
You think you can't lose.
It's very self-destructive.
You should take a hard look at...
Linda, rematch in 30 minutes,
and this time, there's no way I lose.
Okay, but I don't think
you used my proper title.
Oh, queen Linda the dainty-footed.
Anyway. You're gonna end up
making a fool of yourself.
Why is Veronica talking to you
like a waitress at medieval times?
I made up this bagel toss game,
when she loses, I make her say stuff.
And she always loses.
Chick throws a bagel like
the horse is still attached.
That works better for horseshoes.
Look, Veronica's got the better job,
the better car,
the better shoe size.
This is the only thing I'll ever do
that I'm better at than she is.
It's the most important thing.
I can see by the spittle
flying out of your mouth
that you're in a good place,
but you should know,
she will strike back.
I don't care. It's worth it,
as long as I keep winning.
Which I will,
because I am Linda of Linda bagel.
That's hubris. You're cocky.
You think you can't lose.
It's very self-destructive.
You should take a hard look at...
It's greta.
We've got a date. It'll be awesome.
This little extra work requires
your royal touch, queen Linda.
Heavy is the head
that wears the $10 haircut.
No problem. It's as easy as throwing
a bagel through a vent.
Oh, I'm sorry. For some people,
that's practically impossible.
In spite of not being able
to speak very well,
Greta and I were having
no trouble communicating.
It is here.
Herr Muller bring for me.
Surprise.
I tell Lem and the little bird man,
"mach schnell.
I must speak with mein Ted."
Really? They fixed it.
That is fantastic.
I really like you, Ted.
You're a very special man.
Is that Phil's voice?
What's wrong?
I like this voice.
It's warm and friendly
and almost gender-neutral.
The device works.
Our business deal will be a success.
Kiss me, Ted.
Kiss me hard on the lips.
What?
I thought you'd be happy
we can finally know each other.
Our relationship wasn't
just about sex, was it?
No.
Nein.
Then let's go into the bedroom,
we can make love and talk
and make love and talk all night.
Phil, why on earth would you use
your voice for the translator device?
It was the fastest way to fix it,
we already had
my voice in the computer
- from a failed project.
- Stupid thing wouldn't stop screamin
- when putting it on the burner.
- It was critical.
"You really need that much butter?"
Screw you, frying pan.
Okay, fellas. Excuse us.
So here's the deal.
Greta and I are dating.
But... It's hard for me
to fulfill my manly duties
when Phil keeps telling me
how much I'm pleasuring him.
- Oh, my god.
- Yes. You said that a lot last night.
Guys, I need your help.
I really like Greta,
and I don't want this thing between
us to go south, plus if it does,
I could foul up this deal,
and Veronica will kill me.
Recording and loading a new voice
could take days.
We still have those Nixon tapes.
I guess we could pull from those.
I'm beginning to think
you guys really are evil scientists.
Hi, Ted.
How are things going with Greta?
- You screw that up yet?
- No. We really like each other.
Plus, she is very happy with
the new voice on the translator.
The guys just need
a little time to tweak it.
- It's close, it's close. It's so close.
- Man. I have to go.
I need you to design me
a perfect bagel.
Perfect but somehow evil?
Like halfway down your throat,
it triples in size
or tells you the end to "Rocky IV"?
No, just a dozen perfect,
aerodynamically balanced bagels.
A perfect bagel, there's no way
that could be used for anything bad.
I'm using them to cheat.
Linda sucked me
into this stupid game,
and your super-bagels
will help me destroy her.
- Boom. We're back in the evil business.
- And throw in a pint of cream cheese.
I don't care how evil you are. You don't
show up with bagels and no schmear.
So if a guy asked you not to talk
during sex, would you be offended?
No woman likes to be told
to shut up during sex.
Wait. Did Paul from accounting
tell you to ask me that?
Because all we did was make out,
and all I said was, "get off my hair."
Paul from accounting? Really?
No. Gotcha.
Would you leave?
I have a lot of work to do.
What is all this?
- Veronica's retaliating.
- Why don't you just let her win?
What are you afraid of?
Not to enter
the time-wasters' hall of fame?
No. My position there is secure
from getting my art history degree.
I just can't make myself lose.
I've tried,
but it feels so good to beat her.
Find a way to end it without losing.
When Rose gets frustrated with checkers,
she flips the board over.
I once tried the same thing in Vegas
with a craps' table.
Got it up just high enough
to tear every muscle in my back.
Interesting. Like when Van Gogh
got so frustrated with his paintings,
he ripped up his canvases.
That little factoid cost my parents
$60,000 in tuition.
Since I couldn't tell Greta not to talk,
I tried to make it so I couldn't hear.
Ted, the music is so loud.
Ich weiss. Ist es nicht erotisch?
I know your friend's voice
bothers you,
but isn't it worth it
to hear my feelings and instructions
about the best way
to touch my breasts?
If we can't communicate,
then this is all just about sex,
and that doesn't work for me.
Es ist nicht nur sex, Phil... Greta.
Sehen sie das problem?
Why don't you take that schnitzel
you brought me and go home?
Ich will das zu den schnitzel ast.
Den schnitzel macht dich glucklich.
That's because I thought
the schnitzel meant something.
But I was wrong...
so wrong...
about you and the schnitzel.
Good morning. Fraulein Schulz
has decided we do not want
to partner with your company
on the device.
Goodbye.
Was much promising, but not true.
Damn it, Ted.
You were much promising
but not true.
She wanted to use it
with Phil's voice during sex.
I don't care if she wanted
to use Phil during sex.
You screwed this up because you were
so sure you were smarter than
- the Three Stooges.
- You're right.
And I like Greta.
I don't want it to end like this.
I'll go talk to her.
Greta, wait. Can we talk?
Damn it. I told them
not to put Klingon on this thing.
Warten sie, Greta.
Konnen wir sprechen?
You have one minute.
Veronica just called.
She's about to play another game
and wants to use the bagels to cheat.
We're completely corrupted now.
We're like Michael Corleone
at the end of "The Godfather."
- Damn it, Lem!
- You should watch a movie occasionally.
Look at them.
They're so beautiful.
Using them for wickedness would be like
beating a unicorn to death
with a bag of rainbows.
Maybe we should take a stand.
Maybe we should say this is the one
thing that must not be used for evil.
Or maybe we say that the next thing
we make must not be used for evil,
but this one we're fine with.
And maybe the next one after that, too.
But someday,
they will push us too far.
- And then next time after that, we...
- No. The time is now...
12:35.
Let's discuss this for another 20 min,
and then commit to something.
Good. You made it.
Go inside.
I'll be in in a minute.
Lem and Phil
are bringing me something.
It has nothing to do with the game.
It's a...
lucky hat.
I may decide not to wear it.
So if I come in without a hat,
don't give it a second thought.
I have devastating news.
Somehow, security found out
about the room.
I don't know how. Nobody does,
and nobody ever will, so just drop that.
But they don't like people
screwing around on company time,
so they're coming right now
to lock it up.
No! It can't end until I win.
Fine, I'll play without my...
Whatever the hell I said
I was waiting for. Come on.
Okay, Ted, I will give you
another chance.
Lock the door and take me,
and don't be gentle.
Aber konnten wir uber unsere
gefuhl nicht gerade sprechen?
And none of that silly foreplay
this time. Just go for it.
I've tied it up.
Your turn, meat.
You gonna blow it?
Huh, meat? You gonna choke?
I'm Linda. I'm choking.
I've got a big chunk of pressure
lodged in my throat.
It's like a chicken bone.
Come on, chicken bone. Chicken bone.
I'm really gonna miss this.
Oh, Ted. That feels so good.
More, more. Don't stop.
What the hell is that?
What are Phil and Ted doing?
Is that distracting?
Come on, chicken bone, focus.
Don't think about Ted nailing Phil.
You are so good with the sex, Ted.
- What?!
- Throw the bagel, chicken bone.
Throw it! Throw it! Throw it!
This is it.
This is
for the world championship...
of the world.
I did it! I beat you!
Yeah, whatever. Seriously,
what is up with Ted and Phil?
I have to get that bagel.
It's going in my trophy case.
Also, I have to get a trophy case.
It's way back there.
You sure this is right?
I've never been so sure about being
unsure of anything in my life.
Good. Then we're on the same page.
Let's do it.
Veronica, we've made a decision.
Maybe we should ask her
why she just fell through the ceiling.
No. No small talk.
These bagels are the one thing
we will not allow to be used for evil.
I won.
Congratulations. The deal
with the Germans just went through.
And to you too
for falling through the ceiling
in a metal tube and winning that game.
That's gotta feel good.
You'll have to speak up.
I'm temporarily deaf in one ear.
As you may know, I fell through
the ceiling in a metal tube.
But at least I won that game,
and that feels good.
These super-bagels are terrible. You can
totally taste the high impact carbon.
That's because they're
98% high impact carbon.
Whenever you go past 97%,
it's hard to mask the taste.
So I was able to navigate
that tricky situation with Greta,
so you were wrong.
I am not like the Three Stooges.
A couple of wise guys, eh?