Do you think I look like
a possum in this shirt?
No.
Why?
My wife went on and on
this morning about
how this shirt makes me
look like a possum.
Sometimes I don't know
how you put up with that woman.
Usually I hold perfectly
still until she goes away.
The company has a problem.
A recent survey found employee morale
has dropped from "low"
Which they were okay with:
To "I'd like to burn this place down"
Which, frankly,
I'm surprised is one of the options.
This is Clark.
He conducted the survey.
Right now he's telling Veronica
what the employees think about her,
which means right now,
Veronica hates Clark.
63% found you too intimidating.
Is there such a thing
as too intimidating?
Is there?
Answer me, you little bean counter.
I've told you three times
I don't like being called that.
Sorry.
I was told my evaluation was at 11:00.
We're done.
It seems everyone's afraid of me,
which to me, sounds like their problem,
- but apparently not.
- The company is worried
that a decrease in morale
is hurting productivity.
We think it would help
if you softened your image a little,
compliment people, be more supportive.
If people feel appreciated,
they work harder.
I'm sure we're all gonna have
to make adjustments.
Not you.
Everyone likes me?
- You so desperately want to be loved.
- No, I don't.
Yes, I do.
I mean, who doesn't?
Mr. Crisp, you had
a near-unanimous rating of "excellent."
In fact, there were
even several write-ins of "adorable."
Brother.
Look out, Jesus.
Wait. "Near-unanimous"...
Does that mean a few less
than unanimous or a few more?
Really the only group
you didn't score well with
were men over 50
in lower management.
Too bad, Ted. Men over 50
in lower management loved me.
- No, they didn't.
- Shut up, you little bean counter.
I don't get it.
What did I do to men over 50?
You're young,
good-looking, successful.
Honestly,
they probably just resent you.
Maybe I'll just have
to make them get to know me.
I mean, my father's over 50,
and he...
Wait.
- You wanted to see me, boss?
- Yes, employee.
As part of an effort
to raise morale,
I've been told to find out
what would make our workers happy,
and I thought I'd ask you,
since you're the smartest,
most observant person
in the whole company.
Let me guess. You've also been told
to compliment people.
See how smart you are?
Thank you.
But what makes you think I know
how to make employees happy?
Because
you're the suggestion box lady.
They call like that you upstairs.
I've never put my name on any
of my helpful but ignored ideas.
- How do they know they're from me?
- Other people suggested
that you stop hogging
the suggestion box.
Sitting out there
in those identical cubicles,
people start to feel anonymous.
There's no sense of community.
Personally,
I've always felt disconnected,
like I'm just some faceless cog
in a giant,
dehumanizing machine.
Slow down, chairman mao.
I don't need a manifesto.
I need something
to make people happy.
The company could start
by letting us individualize our space,
you know, decorate our cubicles,
put up photos and artwork.
Really?
That's all it would take?
You drones are so easy.
That's not a compliment.
Good morning.
Rick, I think I've been replaced
by someone who likes cats.
My cubicle's been decorated
with space stuff.
It's a very aggressive move,
but by who?
Nice sweater, Lily.
I support your decision to wear it.
Hi, balding guy.
I love what you've done
with the hair you have left.
Hello, mob.
You look confused.
We were just wondering
about our new...
and lovely cubicles.
- Linda suggested...
- Great. I love where this is going.
That you all be allowed
to decorate your workplaces
to express your individuality.
The company thought
it would be too risky to just let
people do whatever
the hell they wanted,
they've expressed
your individuality for you
in four exciting
and inoffensive themes...
Green bay packers.
Cats.
Space.
And classic cars.
Isn't that great?
Enjoy your new personalities.
Nice job, Linda.
I know!
Can you believe this place
and the things they do
to all of us sometimes?
Teamwork...
It's a beautiful thing.
In business, it means working together
for a common goal.
X- rays show
that when people work together,
they're happier
and less likely
to do something weird...
What about me screams
"cat lady" to you?
Maybe the way you pounce on a fella
who's just trying to get cup of coffee.
The company personalized my cubicle
with all the stupid cat stuff.
What are they trying to tell me,
that I'm gonna die old and alone,
with a hundred cats chewing
on my decomposing body?
If you fed the cats once in a while,
your story would have a happier ending.
Would you just say they're wrong
about me, please?
In spite of what my new poster says,
I'm having trouble hanging in there.
The company does all sorts
of crazy things.
That doesn't mean
we have to be crazy, too.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to go seduce a 55-year-old man.
Manny, right?
I'm Ted.
I know who you are.
I have always heard
so much about you.
You're practically
a legend in this place.
I can't believe it's the first time
we've met
It's not. We've worked together
on three projects before.
I meant the first time we've met,
outside of those three projects.
It's not.
What do you want, Ted?
I want to take you to lunch.
Screw that.
Just fire me now.
- I won't make a scene.
- No, it's not like that.
30 years I give to this company,
30 years, and this is how it ends.
A: inside voices,
and B: no one's firing you.
I just wanna get to know you
and you to know me.
You can bring some friends, if you like,
so they can, know me, too.
How about Bill and Jeremy?
Don't you have any friends who are,
you know, older?
Hey, guys.
I just want you both to know
that you're doing great work.
Your specs on the robotic
firefighting technology really...
blew my mind.
That's gotta feel good, right?
Boost your morale?
Thank you.
Thank you...
You're welcome.
And, Phil, I like that outfit.
That was incredible.
- I'm, like, tingly.
- Our specs weren't that great.
I reject her compliment.
- Then can I have your half?
- It doesn't mean anything.
She's only saying nice things because
the company ordered the executives
to boost our morale.
You shouldn't have any trouble
giving up your half.
I see the company
made you a cat person,
The company can go lick its ass.
I'm sorry.
I just don't see myself as a cat person.
Neither did i,
but I realized
that we're cat people.
That's insane.
They're saying we're cats.
I don't mean actual cats.
They're saying we share
the same qualities.
Cats are quick, smart and independent,
just like you, me, Debbie and Bruce.
You think I'm quick,
smart and independent?
Everybody does.
We've all talked about it.
Really?
I never thought of myself
in cat terms.
But I do like to think
I have those attributes.
Or should I say "cat-tributes"?
Cat-tributes...
Can I use that?
No, it's mine.
What's wrong with this picture?
Five steaks, one caesar salad,
low-fat dressing on the side.
I like a light lunch.
It keeps me sharp
for the rest of the day.
Look at Mr. Perfect,
Mr. Stays-awake-at-work.
You're so put together.
It's like you stepped out of a magazine.
Didn't you ever get a mustard stain
on your shirt or...
A hooker's vomit on your pants?
I did do one of those things
when I was 12, at a baseball game.
I won't tell you which one it is,
but it was the game of my life.
Look, fellas, I can have fun.
What are you drinking, iced Tea?
In our day, it was okay
to knock back a few at lunch.
I tell you what. I can go old-school.
Drinks all around.
And now, you can call me:
"Mr. Has-a-drink-at-lunch
But-let's-not-go-overboard
It's-still-a-work-day."
I know. It's long,
but it makes some good points.
Have you met Debbie, Bruce and Rita?
They're also cat people.
Sure, I've seen some of you around,
- but we've never actually met.
- Now we all have something in common.
Being surrounded by pictures of cats
has made me realize how much I want one.
I hate myself for being allergic.
Have you guys seen
that Youtube video
that Janet sent around,
with the cat that flushes the toilet?
I didn't get that.
It's really cute.
He thinks he's people.
It turned out
it wasn't the school's mascot.
It was just some random pig
I'd stolen.
This guy's hilarious.
And what an operator.
He comes back from lunch
with the hostess' phone number.
I am totally gonna make love to her.
You would have loved it
back in the old days, Teddy.
There was no such thing
as sexual harassment.
There was nothing sweeter than
telling some broad who wouldn't do ya
to clean out her desk,
put her crap in a box and go home.
Gee, that sounds great.
You be sure to tell everyone
in your age group how much fun you had.
Tomorrow'll be even better.
You are part of the group now.
- Tomorrow we're taking you to lunch.
- Bring some dollar bills and a lap.
I just made three new friends. Maybe
I was wrong about the cubicle themes.
For the first time since I'm here,
I feel like I'm part of something.
Glad to hear it.
I have to go to a strip club tomorrow
with a bunch of old men.
What theme did the company give you?
Veronica and her hair
were working hard
on the company's campaign
to improve morale.
They both put on a good front,
but one of them was feeling frustrated
and the other was feeling
dry and flaky.
You wanted to see me?
We isolated rat r.n.a using t.r.i.
Would you like to see it?
Sure.
- That is very impressive. Nice work.
- Wait. Let me turn it on.
That is very impressive.
Nice work, thanks for calling me down
here to see it. Nice work on that, too.
I could listen to her praise me
all day.
It's not real.
Any grad student
can isolate rat r. n. a
And I looked at our average specs
from the other day.
I rejected her compliment then,
and I re-reject it now.
Excuse me. Some of us
aren't married to my wife.
I've gotta grab all the compliments.
I'm sorry, but when I hear
an undeserved compliment,
My ears want to throw up.
Your ears are always
throwing up about something.
I can't believe
you guys got me a kitten.
Linda had finally found that sense
of community she'd been missing.
Janet on the fourth floor
also a cat person was giving them away.
We thought you'd want one.
And they thought right,
didn't they, boots?
Sandals?
I should get away from footwear.
Stapler. Now I'm just looking
at things on my desk.
That's good.
It's great having a strong,
young friend around.
How do you know when your need
to be liked has become unhealthy?
Do me. Do me next.
Seriously, how do you know?
Because clearly,
I'm having trouble finding the line.
Hello, space people.
Is this space taken?
Houston, we have a problem.
I guess not.
Janet upstairs is giving away
the cutest kittens.
Have you guys seen them?
- Houston, we have a problem.
- What's that, joe?
It's just, we were talking
about space stuff.
It might be over your head
by 50 miles...
That's where space starts.
I know where space starts.
It's not like you're in a secret club.
Shut up.
Why are you sitting over here?
All of us cat people
have our own table.
I thought I'd mix it up a little,
see what the other groups are up to,
check out the final frontier.
I heard Pluto's not a planet anymore.
How do we feel about that, fellas?
- What?
- I thought we were friends.
You know, cats of a feather.
We are friends, but I also want
to be friends with other people.
Did you just say
"cats of a feather"?
If you were sitting at our table,
you would have seen the shirts
that bruce made for us.
It's just one lunch. I can't believe
you're making such a big deal.
I'm not.
But we gave you a cat.
A cat.
You're disgusting.
I haven't seen you here before.
Don't be silly. I'm down here
all the time. What's that smell?
It's my plate.
Yum!
The food here's not very good.
I like to say even the salt needs salt.
You're a very funny man.
You think?
In fact,
I think you're "Phil-arious."
My wife says I wouldn't know comedy
if it ripped my face off.
Good for you for having a wife.
What happened, Linda?
It looks like the cats abandoned you
like you abandoned them.
They abandoned you.
I hope they didn't leave you
any little gifts
on the seat of your car.
My car's in the shop.
I didn't drive today.
That's right. You better run.
I'm gonna mess you up.
- Join us.
- Guys, what's going on?
I was hoping foreplay.
All right, this party is over.
Don't be that guy,
that uptight guy
we thought you were.
You know what?
I am that guy.
The guy you want me
to be gets taken advantage of,
so I'm this guy, and this guy
wants all of you out of my office.
And why is that sticky?
Where's the frakking aspirin?
There it is.
Good job, cabinet.
God. I must stop.
This will kill everything, right?
That's why we weren't allowed
to sell it.
I'm losing my mind.
I just saw Bob Gershon's butt.
I think it touched my desk.
I've been saying
so many nice things to people
I've started making words up.
This morning, I called Phil
"magniflorious."
About Phil.
He's falling in love with you.
And if that doesn't sound "horrifliffic"
I don't know what does.
God.
See, that's why I keep my hair up.
It creates a distance,
an unapproachability.
I miss that me.
I don't know who I am anymore.
You know who you are?
You are a great boss
who gets things done.
- That should be all that matters.
- Thank you.
And you shouldn't be wiping wrinkly
butt prints off your desk.
I know. I shouldn't care
what men over 50 think about me,
except my father,
and that ship has sailed.
You're right.
About my father?
Did he say something to you?
I'm talking about here.
You can't win with some
of them anyway.
I found cat feces in my car.
Speaking of cat-related vandalism...
What are you doing?
Clearly, I'm losing my mind.
I thought decorating the cubicles
would create
this great sense of community.
But you can't base a community
on made-up personalities.
That's like high school,
only no one's on drugs
and everyone's trying to get pregnant.
The druggie teen slut is right.
I said you were right.
- It's time to end this madness.
- Agreed.
Drones...
Can I have your attention?
Something tells me
I should have known you in high school.
I actually went to an all-girls school
and was totally straight.
But I'm very trampy now.
Recently,
we've tried doing things a little...
I have never seen you this excited
about schematics before.
Now that I've redone them,
I think they're some of my best work.
I finally have something worthy
of Veronica's praise.
And since, unlike you,
I've earned this moment,
I'm going to enjoy it.
And while it may have been
a worthy experiment,
it is now over.
And so from now on,
there will be no more praise.
And I will no longer
be complimenting any of you...
Damn it!
Unless it is truly your best work.
And the next time some survey asks
how happy you are,
you check "very,"
or I'll give you something
to be happy about.
- I'm not sure that makes any...
- The hair is up. That's all they hear.
And so things got back to normal.
I think we need to talk.
- Sweet.
- Look, you are a very nice man...
I like hearing that.
That is, I like you as afriend.
Step one... check.
Nothing is ever gonna happen
with us.
I see.
And now I must get out
of the room as quickly as possible.
Wait.
Another time, another place,
two other people...
It could've been magniflorious.
You mean that?
I do,
especially the part about
two other people.
And things got back to normal
for Linda, too,
although she did get that sense
of community she was looking for.
Unfortunately,
it was centered around blaming her
for getting things back to normal.
And as for me,
I kinda like the idea of not caring
what people think of me.
Go to hell, Ted.
Will do.