Pushing Daisies - Season 02 Episode 12
"Water and Power"
Subtitles (BIA v.1.00): A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
Young Emerson Cod is 11 years,
2 months, 8 days and 3 hours old.
He is in big trouble.
For this was his sixth visit
in ten days to the principal's office.
The previous Tuesday had seen
young Emerson punch future frat boy
and current lunch money extorter,
Guy Baxter.
Wednesday saw the return
of young Emerson to the big couch
for the crime of inappropriate
intentional double entendre
during the science fair.
He returned the following Monday
after a second encounter with Baxter.
Young Emerson assured everyone
that he would leave Guy alone now,
as the bully had no more eyes.
Specialists were summoned,
tests given, therapies administered.
A boy of above-average intelligence
who previously had nothing
but respect for rules and regulation,
young Emerson's mischief
remained an utter mystery.
Because what troubled him
was not parental alienation
or sublimated anger.
It was a heart.
He was in love
with Principal Eleanor Swindle.
That year, young Emerson
learned his most important lesson,
love makes you stupid.
Randy Mann, what brings you in
out of the cold?
I think we're in
for a mid-winter thaw.
Normally, in the mornings, I can see
my breath from under the sheets,
which is kind of daunting
because I sleep in the nude.
But as long as I cocoon myself
in my comforter and...
Can I help you with that?
I'll be okay if there's a satisfying
and unexpected point to this story.
I couldn't see my breath
this morning.
And I'm looking for Olive.
- Now we're talking. Olive?
- Yeah?
You have a gentleman caller
coming out of the thaw.
What he did what what?
Randy, hi.
- I need to...
- Go!
- Randy's back.
- To see Olive in an awkward
"I was nowhere near your neighborhood
but I thought I'd stop by" kinda way.
Look, it's so sweet.
Yeah, I'm happy.
She's been through a tough patch
I've made tougher,
and by that, I mean definitely did.
I want this to work out with Randy.
What better place
to nurture romance than the Pie Hole?
Warmth, pie, snuggly booths.
All the right ingredients.
Love doesn't need the right ingredients,
it's heartier than that.
- What?
- You said love was heartier.
Well, it is heartier.
I mean, we're like those...
blind fish that live in volcanoes
at the bottom of the ocean.
Only we're two fish
that can't even touch.
Cause normally fish
are all over each other.
Our love has grown and survived in spite
of everything we've been through.
We've been through a lot.
Here is to us
for successfully navigating
some extremely rough
and very complicated seas.
And here's to Randy and Olive.
May they have smooth sailing ahead.
Cheers.
- What are we toasting to?
- You and...
Why is... Randy leaving?
Just decided to call it quits.
Too much, too soon.
Actually, it was just me. Singular.
So, more accurately, I would say
it was me who decided to call it quits.
I'll be in the kitchen
rationalizing my panic attack.
Man overboard.
Randy, you know
when people are nervous sometimes,
it's really easy to misunderstand
what they mean.
Yeah, I mean, everything
was going fine and then,
suddenly she said "goodbye",
and "Thanks for coming".
Then she shook my hand,
which was weird.
It's been hard for Olive. She's been
through a sticky swamp of emotions.
She just...
She doesn't wanna get stuck again.
Well, I know all about her
getting stuck on Ned,
- but she said she was over it.
- It's scary starting something new.
It's about exposing your heart to...
a stranger and putting your faith
in the idea of someone
before you even have a chance to get
to know the truth about who they are.
You know what it's like?
It's like driving a car blindfolded.
You just have to relax.
Relax.
Relax?
Maybe bull fighting
is the wrong comparison,
but it's hard making
these things work.
You're telling me these things
are hard to make work?
I know that because you taught me.
Maybe that's why Randy's scary
to you.
Because you're not used to something
being easy and maybe really great.
Oh, my God,
I'm that girl.
I'm that girl in high school
who's afraid of real relationships
so she's always attracted
to guys in college,
or Canada.
Or you.
I just want you to be happy, Olive.
So what you're saying is
I shouldn't run away from Randy?
That Randy might be just
what I need right now.
Yes.
A quick fling to heal the scars
and rub ointment on the burns from us
and then rip off and toss away
like a used square of gauze.
Not yes.
- He's Randy Rebound.
- No, he's not.
As the pie maker began to doubt his plan
to reunite the would be lovers,
a mile to the west,
another reunion was taking place.
Simone Hundin,
breeder of well-heeled dogs...
Stay.
Recently returned from the Merryweather
Multi City Canine Cavalcade
with her dog, Bubblegum.
Without constant reinforcement,
even the best training gets forgotten.
You take off like that again
and I may just forget
we got something going on.
No such luck.
You should know neither Bubblegum
nor I are prone to bolting.
That's good.
That's very good.
- Sounds like there's a story.
- There was a story.
Emerson had once fallen
for a woman who had bolted
and taken their baby daughter
to boot.
Does it have to do with this book?
Emerson had written a pop-up book
about his missing daughter,
in hopes that one day
he would get it published
and she would read it
and come find him.
It's nothing.
I realize what we have
is in the paper trailing phase,
but we did agree to be honest.
- I am being honest...
- I like you.
I'm intensely optimistic
about our prospects
but you need to know that,
like any animal in a new situation,
the thing I hate most
is being surprised.
Forgive me but your door was ajar.
Just being ajar
doesn't change the fact
it was a door before it was ajar,
which would indicate to most people
to a-knock before a-entering.
How are you, Emerson?
Simone, this is
Miss Amelia Stingwell,
sister of Roland Rollie Stingwell,
owner of Papen County Dam.
I'd tell you more about it except for,
due to various reasons,
we haven't spoken in nine years.
Those various reasons are dead now.
Rollie was killed last night.
I'm sorry about your loss.
He'd pop a vein if he knew I were here
asking you to solve his murder but...
you've always been the best in town.
Whoever killed Rollie must have
also taken the dam ruby.
- It's gone.
- The damn ruby?
The D-A-M drop-the-N ruby,
as in a very valuable precious stone
dug up when they built the dam.
He always had it with him,
never took it off.
You find that ruby...
and you'll find Rollie's killer.
After everything that happened
all those years ago, Emerson,
I'd say it was the least
that you could do.
Good day.
What happened
between you and Rollie?
Nothin'.
The facts were these.
Roland Rollie Stingwell, millionaire
builder of the Papen County Dam,
sole director of the Papen County
Water and Power Department,
was last seen getting ready to leave
after a busy day at the office.
His assistant said nothing
seemed unusual as she said...
Good night.
And headed out early
for a dinner engagement.
What engagements engaged
Rollie Stingwell in the following hours
were not known
until the next morning
when his body was discovered
in a dry river bed
one half mile from the dam.
Thanks for coming down.
The poor man and his poor head!
Think of him like an owl.
That was funny.
He said "Hoo" like an owl.
And how's it going, Rollie?
Of all people, I did not expect
to see you here, Emerson Cod.
- You know each other?
- We're affiliates,
affiliated
with a common third party.
There was nothing common
about her and you know it.
He stole away the love of my life,
and the dopey thing about it
is I paid him to do it.
- I trusted you, Cod.
- Hey, you got your money back.
And it ain't stealing if the thing
you're stealing wants to be stolen.
I have questions,
which I will wait to ask.
Strange.
I spent my life
being angry about this,
but now,
here in...
A limbo with non-denominational
way station.
The anger has gone...
and I can see I spent my life
living in a haze of a broken heart.
I don't mean to step on toes
but shouldn't someone ask who did it?
I have tamed nature,
I have stopped rivers from flowing.
But there is one thing I could never do
and that was make that woman love me.
Well, if it makes you feel
any better, Stingwell,
neither could I.
It does make me feel better.
- Who killed you, Stingwell?
- You really wanna know?
It was Lila Robinson herself.
I assume she came back
to steal the ruby.
Man, I wish you'd have said
anyone else.
Thank you for your time.
Who the heck is Lila Robinson?
She's the baby momma
that took my daughter.
How can you not tell me
that you had a daughter?
We have buried bodies together.
I mean, you have a daughter,
a daughter.
Have you known all this time
and didn't tell me?
You know you ain't
foolin' nobody, right?
I know that every secret I tell you
spends about 20 seconds being a secret
before it spills out of your mouth
and into dead girl's ears.
- Now, that is not true.
- It is.
It's true. But I still can't believe
you didn't tell me.
What about Simone?
Does she know?
I'll take that as a no.
As much as I'd love to sit ruminating
about my pain for past over a pie,
can we please find something else
to chatter about?
Emerson shouldn't feel any pressure
to divulge the details of his past.
It's not like we've ever shared
big secrets with him.
It's complicated.
What is so complicated about finding
your baby-stealing baby momma
and getting your daughter back?
If Lila killed Roland Stingwell
and stole that dam ruby,
we've just been hired to track her down
and find your daughter.
Chuck's right. We should trace
Mr Stingwell's last steps.
Maybe Lila left a trail behind.
I've spent the last seven years
tracking down her and my kid.
Lila is a wily genius,
a man-eating, shape-shifting grifter
who knows how to get in and get out
and vanish like heat off a blacktop.
At least we could try.
We need to try.
Maybe I could give it one more shot.
I don't know your daughter's name.
Penny.
My daughter's name is Penny.
The facts were these.
9 years, 2 months, 14 days
and 9 minutes earlier,
Rollie Stingwell hired the PI
to tail his fiancée,
Miss Emily von Alistair,
who Rollie suspected
was having an affair.
The affair, however,
was with a dead man,
one Henry David Thuroe.
And her furtive trips away
seemed to show only her desire
for a moment of solitude
and ornithology
to avoid the hubbub
of wedding planning.
But hiding from a bird watcher
in a Lincoln Continental is not easy.
And so...
Emily von Alistair
began sharing her daily solitude,
as well as her sandwich
and thermos of tomato soup.
While unconventional,
Emerson reasoned he was still
very much keeping an eye on Emily.
With each passing thermos,
the private investigator
grew more blind to the fact
that he was fast approaching
the thin line
between stakeout and make out.
Emerson hesitated,
knowing it was wrong,
but Emily had a solution,
and that was to tell the truth.
There's something I need to tell you
that I should probably keep to myself.
Emerson Cod would discover
that Emily was Lila Robinson,
a grifter come to town
to steal Stingwell's dam ruby.
She did not love
the millionaire at all.
22 days later, the PI returned the money
Stingwell had paid him.
What he could not return
was his client's fiancée,
or the new life growing inside her.
Furious, Stingwell swore
if the grifter ever grifted again,
he'd made sure
she got put away for good.
Lila promised to keep
on the straight and narrow
while Stingwell went on to build
Papen County Water and Power
into a juggernaut.
If we're gonna find Lila,
we need to retrace Stingwell's steps,
figure out how he ended up
half a mile away from here.
Welcome to the Papen County Dam, source
of Papen County's water and power.
My name is Taylor Philbean,
and should you choose to take a tour
of this landmark and working utility,
I'll be your dam guide.
When there's a bigger group, this is
where I wait for the laugh to die down.
Actually, we're invited guests
of the Stingwell family,
here on account of
Roland Stingwell's untimely death.
Damn sad is what it is.
If you wait here, I'll get you passes
and take you up to his private office.
You said Lila
chose to leave behind her life of crime.
What happened?
People's nature is like a river. You can
only keep it dammed up for so long.
One day, Lila packed up bags
and broke back into Stingwell's house
looking for the dam ruby.
When she couldn't find that,
she stole 50 grand in cash.
Knowing Stingwell'd track her down
to the ends of the earth,
she took Penny
and they just disappeared.
If you'll follow me.
But you knew who Lila was.
Did you really not see it coming?
I guess I was just blinded.
Say cheese!
Does this camera take pictures
of every visitor?
Yes, for security reasons.
Should you be planning to blow up
the dam and flood the valley,
one copy is kept on file
and another is available
for purchase as a keepsake
in our gift shop on the way out.
This way.
Have you seen this woman before?
Name's Lila Robinson. That picture was
taken as she was entering the building
the same day your boss was killed.
I remember the woman.
She did have a private meeting
with Mr Stingwell,
but I believe she said
her name was Mary Beth Acres.
The police have already been
here asking questions.
- They ask you about Mary Beth?
- No.
They were asking about
the multi-million dollar contracts
that Mr Stingwell was negotiating
to replace all the old pipes
that bring water into the city.
Yeah, I'd say the police
are on the wrong track.
I agree.
I tried to tell them my theory
but they weren't interested.
I'm interested.
I caught a local factory
dumping toxic chemicals
into the dam reservoir.
And you blew the whistle?
You go, girl.
It's my duty as a citizen
to watch the reservoir.
You know, one drop
of certain mind altering drugs
and we'll be zombies under the control
of those secret signals on FM radio.
Oh, brother.
It's a public health issue.
Yeah, yeah. What's this door?
Well, that's Mr Stingwell's
private exit.
It leads back through the inside
of the dam to a private stairwell.
Do you care that I have
important information?
Oh, we do. We wanna hear
all about your theory.
Come on, woman, give me something.
Who are you talking to, Cod?
Detective Puget.
Been a while.
Figured the Stingwells would hire
a private peep around this one.
They never did like a cop
they couldn't buy.
You know, being cocky in a cheap suit
is less effective than you think, Puget.
What about Papen County's finest?
They got any leads?
Who didn't wanna
knock off Stingwell?
He got valuable re-piping
contracts up for grabs,
he got 100 angry farmers
who had to cough up bill for water
because he dammed up their river.
Not to mention that ruby
that he flaunted like a trophy wife
at a high school reunion.
Well, maybe I got a lead for you.
Maybe the only lead
you need to follow.
Name's Lila Robinson.
Last known address was local
but she's been on the fly for a while.
Never known you to share, Cod.
What's your angle?
Maybe I wouldn't mind help bringing down
the hammer of justice on who did this.
Doesn't matter to me if the hammer's
public or private. You catch my drift?
I do not.
Catch the bitch.
And use everything you got
and move quickly,
cause I guaran-damn-tee you,
she's moving fast
and the trail's getting cold.
- How did you get in?
- There's something I have to tell you.
There's something I gotta tell you too,
and I really hate to tell you now
because now it looks like
I'm just telling you cause I have to,
not cause I want to.
That book on my desk...
Emerson, may I go first?
- Sure.
- I'm sorry.
What are you sorry about?
Long time, no see, honey.
Lila.
- Lila.
- Lila?
She told me her name
was Priscilla Saltpeter.
Said she'd shoot me
if I let on she was here.
She's told a lot of people
a lot of things.
You here to see a dead man
about a ruby?
I'm in town to see you.
You really should lock your office door.
No telling what riffraff will blow in.
Where's Penny?
Penny is somewhere you can't find her.
But I'll make you a deal.
I didn't kill Stingwell
or steal his dam ruby.
As soon as the cops find out
I was there when he was killed,
they'll be all over me
like weevils on rice.
Maybe they know already.
Then your job just got
significantly harder.
Find the real killer,
put me in the clear
and I'll let you see Penny.
Hang a red lantern in your office window
and I'll arrange for a reunion.
But the moment I get a whiff
that the cops are closing in on me,
you won't see me
or your Penny again.
Who's Penny?
Penny's the price I paid for thinking
with my heart and not my head.
Penny's my daughter.
That's what I was
just about to tell you.
Surprise.
- I'll give you 48 hours.
- She's lying.
It's in her eyes.
She's lied so damn much in her life,
eyes look like that permanently.
What's to stop me
from taking that toy gun of yours
and pushing your delicate frame
through my wall?
Xylazine.
Come again?
- Wait. It was what?
- It was horse tranquillizer.
When we woke up, Emerson made sure
I was okay and then left.
He was gonna start with all the farmers
and find out who the real killer was.
But we know who the killer is,
the dead man told us so.
In so far as a dead man
can tell anything
by way of some very strong leads
acquired in a straightforward way.
If Lila has Penny,
then she holds all the cards.
We don't even know for sure
if Lila has his daughter.
She could be lying about that, too.
She's playing him,
dominating his will until he's no longer
listening to his instincts.
You don't dominate Emerson.
You really think he's  interviewing
suspects he knows innocent,
following leads
he knows lead nowhere?
He wouldn't do that.
That's not who he is.
But what if who he is
isn't who he is right now?
Instead of analyzing him,
we should be there helping him.
Doesn't matter how crazy it seems.
Forgive me, but if helping Emerson
means we blind ourselves to truth,
then I won't be part of it.
When someone backs you into a corner,
you don't get obedient, you bite back.
Simone, wait.
All I ask from him is that we start out
with honesty and no surprises.
I would say this qualifies
as a surprise.
- Thank you for coming back, Randy.
- Sure.
First, I wanna say
I'm sorry if it feels like
I'm sending you mixed signals
by asking you to come back.
I guess I was a little surprised.
Well, signals are like nuts,
mixed is better.
No one's all the same kind, right?
And what's important is
that we have a fresh start.
Right...
Can I ask you a question?
You're not just planning on using me
to get over Ned, are you?
Sometimes things are so absurd
that I can't even hear them.
Like, you just blew a dog whistle
full of crazy and I'm not a dog.
Well, I get that.
If you're not ready, I get that.
But, you know,
I've been through this before...
And I don't wanna be
your rebound guy.
Wait, there it is again.
Nothing.
Is this a bad time to talk?
I just wanted to say
I think Randy's gonna do the trick.
You know, wiping
the emotional slate clean.
- He's picking me up tonight after work.
- That's great, Olive.
See, soon I'll be the one lost
in some distracted thought,
not caring while you prattle on
about your relationship problems.
I'm sorry, I do care
and I am distracty.
I have a question.
Can love make you do
something absolutely crazy?
I went...
to a nunnery.
- Have a great time tonight.
- Yeah.
You're right. If Emerson's desperate
enough not to see the truth,
- he's desperate enough to do anything.
- He needs us.
Let's go.
It was the end of a long day,
and Emerson, Chuck and the Pie Maker
had interviewed
28 disgruntled farmers,
concluding that none were guilty
of the murder of Roland Stingwell.
But as Lila had told Emerson,
if he proved her innocence,
he could see his daughter again.
They moved on to farmer number 29.
Mr Brunch, you had about
200 acres of river front farmland
before they build the dam, right?
My farm used to be
the most prosperous in the county.
Now with what I pay
to truck in water,
I can barely pay the rent,
same as everybody else.
But what else would I do?
- Now, when is your birthday, precious?
- December.
Funny, I would have bet
on an autumn birthday.
The deep orange of orchid embers
and asiatic lilies
makes your skin tone glow.
Well, actually, I have two birthdays
and my second one's in the fall, so...
actually, you're right.
Your gibberish is sweet, honey.
Keep the flowers.
- Oh, no, I'm telling the truth.
- So am I.
If I killed Stingwell, I supposed
I would have done it years ago
when my anger was fresh cut,
but nothing's gonna change.
Whoever has the water has the power.
What about the contracts
to re-pipe the county water supply?
Might be some bad blood there.
Stingwell would have been
behind the plan
but the mayor would have been
in charge of bidding out  construction.
There's no motive.
We got nothin'.
What about the big business
polluter angle?
Don't humour me.
If you didn't think
we were out of leads
and I wasn't high
on Lila berry juice,
then what would you call
the big business polluter angle?
I may call it that crazy conspiracy
theory by Stingwell's crazy assistant.
Or the last ditch crackpot angle.
But it's something.
It's all we've got left.
And we're running out of time.
We appreciate you coming out
to talk to us on short notice.
We're investigating
the death of Roland Stingwell.
His assistant said there was a heated
legal dispute between Mr. Stingwell
and your clients,
the Fits And Giggles Novelty company.
And we know that Mr. Stingwell was about
to make public that
one of your clients' factories
was illegally disposing
dangerous chemicals
into the Papen County Dam reservoir.
These are baseless allegations.
Our client did not, nor would ever,
dispose chemicals in a reservoir.
This is a categorical denial.
- Maybe once.
- And one time only.
Once we may have
inadvertently allowed
a small amount
of chemicals into the reservoir,
but it was a long time ago.
- It was Tuesday.
- Very, very early Tuesday.
- Nearly Monday.
- What kind of lawyers are you?
We are Mennonites,
which would not normally be
a liability were it not for our
own commitment not to lie.
But to be clear,
in regards to the chemicals
- that were or weren't...
- Were.
Dumped  at an indeterminate time.
- Last Tuesday.
- 2:00 am-ish.
- 2:39 in the morning.
- There was a spill.
And that's the truth.
Plastics division had an overflow
but it was only the chemicals we use
to make things glow in the dark,
which are near identical
to pure drinking water.
Pure drinking water
with chemicals in it.
We will pay the fine
to the appropriate authorities.
They're polluters
but they're no killers.
- Every road's a dead end.
- Except one road
but we can't go down that road.
No, we can't.
The police are gonna
go down that road.
Let's say they find Lila.
What's to say they don't also find Penny
and put an end to this?
Yeah, and what if you're wrong?
Penny's the only leverage Lila has.
What if Lila has it already set up
that the minute she sees those flashing
red and blue lights on the wall.
She's on the phone to some accomplice
who puts Penny on a bus to Mexico?
Yeah, maybe my love for my daughter
has made me stupid,
but Lila doesn't seem
to have that problem,
so I'm gonna continue to jump
through any hoop I have to...
to get face to face
to my little girl!
What if Lila's lying to you?
What if she doesn't have Penny?
Well, then, I guess I'm a chump.
But at least I'm not a chump
just sitting here and doing nothing.
Poor Emerson. We can't just sit here.
We've got to do something.
Quick gawking at each other
and let's go.
Across town, a signal was set.
As Olive came in from the cold...
Are you in here?
I heard about what's happened.
Who are you? Did you hang
the lantern in the window?
Who are you?
I hung the lantern, bitch.
We need to talk.
Sit tight, sister.
You're in the jam now.
I should have skedaddled
when I had the chance.
Emerson always was a sucker
for a tricky dame.
Your tricks work on Emerson
because he thinks
you have him by the collar.
I was ready to leave him
for not showing me all his cards.
Now I know the card he was stakeholding
was the Lying Queen Of Empty Hearts,
I'm back to deal again.
Then deal. You've got the gun.
Penny's a bluff.
A two bit grifter like you
wouldn't get saddled with a child.
My guess is you ditched her
a long time ago.
Then when you ran out of money,
you came back to try again
- for the ruby and rubbed Stingwell out.
- Witch!
I'm sorry. Am I playing, too?
No, I'm not. Continue.
I did come back to see Stingwell,
and he thought
I was there to kill him
but we talked it out
and I gave him back all his money,
every dime I stole when I ran away.
So we're to believe that somehow, along
the way, you suddenly grew a conscience?
I did grow a conscience,
and she's sitting in a hotel room
watching television...
and eating string cheese.
She has my eyes
and Emerson's big heart.
That's so sweet.
And evil, right?
The gun!
Watch it!
I got it!
I got the gun!
Aw, shoot!
Looking for this?
I suppose you're right,
Emerson is still a sucker
for a tricky dame.
Get her!
Nice job, well played.
Thank you.
- Did you get her?
- She was in a big rush.
See if you can follow them in the van.
I need to find Emerson.
This is so much more fun
than dinner and a movie.
- It's so exciting!
- Yeah, I know.
Lila Robinson had often found herself
on the run from a tricky situation.
In her rush to disappear, however,
the player failed to realize
she herself was being played
by Chuck and the pie maker.
Across town,
the desperate investigator returned
one last time in search
of some dam evidence.
Looking for more pictures
of your girlfriend, Cod?
I think I've found your angle.
Lila Robinson,
a.k.a. Emily von Alistair.
This wasn't the first time she'd tried
to steal the dam ruby from Stingwell.
She's been on the run
from him for years.
You got it all wrong, Puget.
What I got wrong was you.
Thought you were wild goosing me
with the bogus tip
- to throw us monkey suits off.
- Maybe that's exactly what I did.
Maybe I got you hook,
line and sinker
wasting time chasing Lila,
while I pop the real perp.
Come on, Puge.
All you've got is proof she entered
the building three hours before
Stingwell disappeared.
Here she is on her way out,
a half hour after Stingwell's assistant
saw our victim
for the last time.
That's motive and opportunity.
How she got the body
where she got it.
I'll just let
the jury use their imaginations.
Thanks for the tip, Cod.
And don't worry,
if she's still within 100 miles,
we'll have her in custody
by morning.
At that moment, Emerson Cod
was overcome with 100% certainty
that he would never see
his daughter again.
And then he was un-overcome
by an idea that had a 1% chance
of being correct.
Wait a minute.
I knew you'd come back
to the scene of the crime.
I'm sorry I bolted on you.
That's OK, you're here now.
Come on.
As the private eye set off
to test his new theory for leaks,
the tall drink of water driving
into the darkness
remained unaware
of her hidden cargo.
If love does make you stupid,
then we must really love Emerson.
It'll all be worth
it if we find Penny.
- Ned?
- Yeah.
When I said
that our love was hearty...
it was just another way
of saying it's hard.
More than for other people?
OK, maybe more
than for other people.
If Emerson wasn't blinded by love,
there would never have been a Penny
and he wouldn't have had anything
to lose, which would be so much easier.
Do you want us to be easier?
I dunno.
Maybe it's the exhaust fumes.
But why do we love something
if loving just makes us stupid and...
just have more to lose?
Why love something?
Because we can.
In my experience, when you're hiding
in the trunk of a car,
it's best not to chat.
- How did you lose them?
- Well, they were 3 blocks away.
I wasn't comfortable
jumping the kerb.
They're OK, right? They have to be.
Yeah, after you disarmed
that crazy-ass she wolf.
Is it insensitive of me
to say this is fun?
Only if they're dead.
But they're not, right? They're fine.
Yeah, OK.
Can I be honest with you?
If you could read my mind
and I'm really glad you can't.
But it doesn't matter cause
I'm gonna tell you anyway.
When?
Now, now.
You were right.
I did wanna use you
to squeeze the feelings
I had for Ned out of my head.
But I don't think
that I can do that now.
Well, I like you, Olive.
- I like spending time with you.
- Oh, that's the problem.
I don't want this to make you muddle
headed so you make a bad decision.
I've been through a lot, Randy.
I'm gonna be difficult.
I know it's stupid for me to...
be the rebound guy.
But I also think, with time...
you might forget you ever bounced.
At least I'm willing
to take that chance.
Well, if we're careful and...
there might be a way to do it smart,
we could do it without...
How was that?
That was brilliant. Brilliant.
I... I...
For the first time in...
a very, very long time, the thoughts
I have for Ned just...
went right out of my head...
and are standing right
outside the door.
- Clearing.
- Crossing.
What happened?
Lila caught us, took our clothes
and she left us at the side of the road.
We must find Emerson.
Who knows what's she gonna do.
Can you bring your car round?
We'll get dressed and meet you out.
Let's go!
Why are these flowers
glowing in the dark.
Yeah, I knew it.
These flowers
are from Michael Brunt's farm.
Delivered the same day
that Stingwell was murdered.
Are they meant to do that?
Where's Brunt's flower farm?
Here.
We know Stingwell was about to approve
a multi-million dollar renovation
for the water pipes
from the dam reservoir to the city.
Help me with this.
Now, maybe I'm crazy...
- but if pipes need renovating...
- Probably means they're leaky.
- Leaky pipes means...
- Water.
Or in this case,
glow-in-the-dark water
on account of a toy company
dumping their chemicals.
Brunt's farm's right over the biggest,
leakiest water pipe in Papen County.
Now say Brunt gets wind
Stingwell's about to replace  the pipes
and he's gonna lose his free water
and everything else.
So he decides to deliver the flowers
himself as he wants to talk to the man.
Lila said
she and Stingwell had it out.
She said he thought she came
to kill him for the ruby.
And now he overhears this
and he has the perfect plan to solve...
all his problems
and steal the dam ruby for himself.
But if Brunt did it, what about
the pictures of Lila leaving the dam
just after Stingwell was murdered?
Follow me.
So, end of the day,
Stingwell takes the dam ruby,
says goodbye to his assistant,
leaves out of the side door.
He's walking up the pipe
and he hears a noise...
so he decides to investigate.
Be careful.
All right, now...
Brunt had three whole hours
to get ready for this moment.
He would have been waiting...
in order to pull off
the perfect crime.
He would...
Yeah. No, this...
this it nuts, I'm fooling myself.
It's Lila.
I know it is.
She did it, she killed Stingwell.
This is a crazy idea.
No, it's Lila.
No, it ain't.
Hey, I knew it was you.
Good guess.
Too bad no-one will ever know.
Why did you come back?
Stingwell hid the dam ruby
somewhere in here before I did him in.
One more visit as murderous fugitive,
Lila Robinson, should do the trick.
See you later, suckers!
Looks like he went the wrong way.
I disagree.
Oh God!
I think I just figured out how Stingwell
ended up half a mile away from here.
He didn't have you!
The facts were these.
Cornered by Brunt
but thinking it was Lila,
Roland Stingwell
decided his precious ruby should remain
at the Papen County dam
where he'd found it.
As he considered
the power of the hydro-electric plant
he had designed...
Stingwell was struck by the irony,
then by the water.
After flushing Stingwell,
still disguised as Lila,
Brunt would allow the photo booth
to document his exit and,
after attempting
to flush Emerson and Simone,
Brunt left the same way.
This time,
it was Brunt who was flushed out.
Murder solved and ruby recovered,
Amelia Stingwell informed the PI
that his previous sins
were now washed away.
Emerson Cod would profit
from the trickle down.
The terms of the meeting
in the woods were simple,
come alone,
no police and no surprises.
While Emerson and Lila had complied
easily with terms A and B,
there were still
two surprises yet to come.
A deal is a deal, Emerson.
Penny's waiting in the car.
I guess you two can catch up.
And thank you.
No-one else could have done
what you did.
No-one else would have been
stupid enough to even try.
You know, this is a crazy life
you got go on here, Lila.
The kid deserves some normalcy.
You'd be shocked
how normal her life is.
School, homework...
braces.
She has braces?
My life may not always be
on the straight and narrow,
but Penny's is.
Emerson Cod looked into the eyes
that had lied
to him so many times before,
and decided they were lying
to him again.
I don't just wanna see Penny
for ten minutes. I'm taking her.
My turn to be her parent now.
Surprise.
You leave us be
and I'll do what I can to get the cops
to drop the kidnapping charge.
Otherwise...
Shoot, ain't no otherwise.
I thought you may want
something like this.
Well, don't worry.
I'll take good care of her.
I know.
I just don't know how
I'm gonna take care of myself anymore.
I'm broke now,
car's on its last legs.
Well, take mine.
- No.
- Go ahead, take it.
Take it. I'll find something else.
I always could count
on your big heart.
Maybe I was a fool to leave you.
People do stupid things
when they're in love.
Surprise.
His car disabled
and Lila getting away,
Emerson realized
he'd been tricked again.
But Penny was alive.
And perhaps, judging
from her wide smile, full of braces,
she was with a mother who maybe
even loved her as much as he did.
One way or another,
he would find Penny.
Dear Mr Cod, congratulations.
And now, with the news
that his pop-up book,
Lil'Gum Shoe, had been accepted
by a publisher and was going to press,
maybe it was only a matter of time
before Penny found him.
Synchro: Salomon & Gaillots
Rereading: Bruno & Toupack
Subtitles: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--