Previously on
"Pushing Daisies"...
- You only got a minute.
- I know.
- 60 seconds.
What if you didn't
have to be dead?
You touch murder victims,
you ask who killed them.
You touch them again,
they go back to being dead,
- and you collect the reward ?
- Nobody can know.
- I can't even hug you ?
- You can't touch me.
- So a kiss is out of the question?
- Who's the funny girl stuck to Ned ?
Childhood sweetheart. He digs her in
a way he definitely doesn't dig you.
Thank you for bringing
me back to life.
People aren't used to
this sort of thing.
Issues of morality,
how come she's not dead anymore ?
You understand you can't see your aunts.
It'd be a disaster.
This pie smells delicious.
We recently lost our niece.
Your niece, Charlotte Charles, is dead ?
Presently ?
Season 1 Episode
04, Pigeon
At this very moment, in the town
of North Thrush, young Ned was...
lonely.
Unable to make friends at the
Longburrow school for boys,
he often found himself
playing alone,
with nothing but memories of
happier times to keep his company.
What young Ned did not realize
was that, beyond the meadow
and under the
same orange sky,
someone he loved was
remembering him.
His dog, Digby.
In fact, three days prior,
Digby had made a decision.
Wearied by his own loneliness
back in Coeur d'Coeurs
and sensing his
master's sorrow,
Digby set out
on a mission.
Uncertain as to his
exact destination,
he ventured into
the great unknown,
guided only by the
compass of his heart.
Despite numerous distractions, Digby
was determined to find young Ned,
the boy who had given him
a second chance at life...
and who was his
best friend.
Upon doing so, Digby proved that
love can overcome any obstacle.
The reunion was
bittersweet, however,
as they instantly remembered the
restrictions of their friendship.
They could not touch,
or Digby would die.
Still, it was enough.
That day, Digby vowed he would
never again allow himself
to be separated
from his master.
The pie maker did not wish
to be separated from Chuck,
who, in turn, did not wish to
be separated from her aunts,
Lily and Vivian, who continued to
be challenged by social phobias.
Unbeknownst to
the pie maker,
Chuck secretly baked homeopathic mood
enhancers into pies for her aunts,
hoping that a slice a day would
herbally lift their spirits.
- Oh, you're up early.
- Oh, I couldn't sleep.
- Lumpy mattress?
- Lumpy dreams.
Which are a lot more vivid now
than they were before I died.
- Isn't that interesting?
- Just one of those...
little things. What are those?
Oh, I, uh... got bit.
Those are beestings.
How'd you get stung by so many bees?
And what happened to
the bees that stung you?
- That's a suicide attack.
- Not in this case.
They, uh, sort of stung me,
died, then they flew away again,
and some other bees died.
Do you think their honey tastes
different 'cause they died?
Wouldn't that be interesting?
Just one of those little things.
I want to show you something.
What is it?
- Bees!
- Your bees.
My bees? You mean...
No, not those bees -- new bees.
Technically, still your bees, just...
not the bees that you knew.
But I'm sure they're
equally nice.
You do realize that beekeeping within
city limits is completely illegal.
Yes. And I'm almost
sure I don't care.
Well, I can not care
enough for the both of us.
We can plant wild
flowers on rooftops and
be unorthodox urban
honey pioneers.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
If I could hug you right now --
I know that I can't, but --
Just know that I want to.
I do.
As Chuck considered her future as an
unorthodox urban honey pioneer...
Olive Snook considered
how the man she loved
seemed to be in love
with someone else.
Her affection for the pie
maker had not wavered,
despite the romantic threat of
a dead girl who wasn't dead.
I didn't know you
could do that.
On the contrary,
Olive's resolve had only increased
since the realization that Chuck,
indeed, was supposed to be dead.
Good morning !
Olive assumed Chuck had
faked her own death.
She would keep the
secret for now,
as Chuck kept her secret
from the pie maker.
There's a pie in my oven.
Oh, uh, that's mine.
I was practicing.
It smells like cheese.
Is it quiche ?
I baked monastery gouda into
the crust -- tart apple filling.
I thought I'd try it.
You know what would
be delicious ?
Pear with gruyère crust.
Bet that'd be real good.
Yeah, it would.
Unbeknownst to Chuck,
Olive understood the deliciousness
of pear and gruyère...
Thank you.
...Because she secretly delivered
that first mood-enhancing pie
to aunts Lily and Vivian,
as she would deliver this one...
...But not before a
collision occurred.
Oh ! I think she's dead !
Can you feel a heartbeat ?
I don't... do heartbeats.
Well, they feel like this.
Come here.
Thump, thump. Thump, thump.
Is that a dead bird?
Why are you touching a dead bird?
Throw that away.
It's swimming with disease,
and you serve food.
Don't be such a drama queen.
Besides, it doesn't look diseased.
It's dead, and it's a bird.
It's diseased.
It's a miracle bird!
It's swimming in miracles, not disease!
- Maybe I should hold it.
- Oh, no, really, do you have to?
She's obviously
been through a lot,
and she seems really
happy to be here.
Having brought a dead
thing back to life,
the pie maker fretted over
which pint-sized animal
would pay for that
life with its own.
- I wonder how she lost her wing.
- Doesn't seem to be in any pain.
She's probably not in pain.
But what do I know ? I'm not a bird.
- Pigeon.
Uh, pigeon-toed as a child,
but orthopedic shoes solved that.
Yeah.
What is the rate of exchange
on the life of a bird ?
'Cause if it's equal to or greater than
mine, I need to get back to my car.
I'm more concerned
for that squirrel.
Don't you worry.
I know just what to do with you.
I recently made the acquaintance
of a pair of bird lovers.
I'll consult them.
Olive was referring to
aunts Lily and Vivian.
Really? I used to know
a pair of bird lovers.
Chuck also referred
aunts Lily and Vivian.
Used to ? Did they die ?
- A death was involved.
- How unfortunate.
They were both so busy
referring and inferring,
they failed to notice that
60 seconds had passed.
The pie maker could not
afford such a luxury.
It's raining dead birds !
What's going on up there ?
What was going on up
there was this --
an out-of-control crop
duster crashed headfirst
into the Broadview luxury apartment
complex, killing the
pilot instantly.
His body was catapulted
out of the cockpit
and into the living room
of one Conrad Fitch.
Does this -- oh --
does this qualify as ambulance-chasing ?
I'm asking without
any judgment at all.
If you're asking without any judgment,
then, yes, it does.
- Look for body bags.
- That's not our thing.
Your thing is waking
up dead people.
My thing is finding dead
people for you to wake up.
Ooh, found one.
Why can't we just be here as
concerned citizens of the world ?
Because big daddy
needs some new yarn.
Just because there's a dead body
doesn't mean you're gonna get paid.
Just because there's vodka in my
freezer doesn't mean I have to drink it.
- Wait, yes, it does.
- He's not wrong.
Plane crashes into a building --
could mean a civil suit, criminal suit,
negligence, pain and suffering,
negligent pain and suffering.
Chuck fostered her love of
the law by volunteering
as a stay-at-home juror
for a paraplegic judge.
We the jury find the
defendant guilty.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Unable to catch
Chuck when she fell,
the pie maker was
forced to step aside,
allowing another
man to catch her.
- Thank you.
- Forgive the mess.
The maid comes tomorrow.
Guess I should cancel that.
- Do you live here?
- Until very recently.
Can you put her down, please?
At least your collection of
nautical plates survived.
Those were franklin mint.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
I was feeling like I needed
to simplify my life, anyway.
Chuck's heart went out to the man
with the plane in his living room,
despite the pie maker wanting
her heart for himself.
Suddenly, ambulance-chasing
didn't seem like a bad idea.
- The ambulance is leaving.
- Oh, you go ahead.
I'm gonna stay here,
see if there's anything I can do.
I'm sure he's fine. Statistically
speaking, his day can only improve.
Dead pilot, on the other hand,
probably has lots of last wishes.
Yeah, like maybe he wished
he'd have turned left.
- You don't need me for that.
- She's got a point.
- But --
- Don't argue with the woman.
We got a dead guy to talk to.
The facts were these -- one Bradan
Caden, an agricultural aviator,
was 53 years, 21 weeks, 5 days,
6 hours, and 19 minutes old,
when his crop duster collided with
the Broadview luxury
apartment complex.
It was 17 minutes after the collision
that Mr. Caden's insurance agent
had already rejected the
claim on his life policy
before the claim
was even made.
Did you see the way he
just swept in there ?
- Yeah, so ?
- I don't sweep. I'm not a sweeper.
- Yeah, it's a little showy.
- It's a lot showy.
And what's a rooftop full
of bees compared to someone
who can catch her when she falls ?
I can't catch her, Emerson.
Can't suck on her
toes, neither.
Some women like that.
Bradan Caden's wife, Becky, believed
her husband was not suicidal
and was, in fact,
a happy man.
He was a happy man.
These insurance people making
assumptions about a person's
disposition --
one should never assume.
An insurance agent can't speak
to the deceased's state of mind.
They didn't know the deceased.
You did.
Pardon me. I couldn't help but
overhear your conversation.
I believe I could be helpful.
May I have a word with you ?
Why are you bothering
this poor woman ?
You and that white boy got
some kind of shifty going on ?
I don't know what,
but you're shifty.
I'm here as a concerned
citizen of the world.
You making a dime,
concerned citizen ?
Maybe one or two
to rub together.
Well, then, flies land on me,
they pay rent.
Excuse me. I'm just gonna...
Hello.
Are you the fellow that
jumped on my plane ?
No. A fellow jumped
on your plane?
I was hijacked.
Is that why your
plane crashed ?
Oh, yes, sirree.
Mr. Caden.
I was dusting soybeans,
or getting ready to,
and Dippy in a prison-orange
jumpsuit climbed aboard.
Dippy was on board when
your plane crashed?
But you were the only dead Dippy --
body -- they found.
Then Dippy's not dead.
Lucky him.
- What in the hell ?
- The plane was hijacked.
How'd you come by that ?
DNA-ish.
Olive Snook came to Coeur
d'Coeurs on a wing and a prayer.
With a gilded cage housing the
monowinged bird in one hand
and a pie box in the other, she set
out to expose Charlotte Charles,
also known as "Chuck,"
as a faker of deaths.
Mm-hmm. It's a carrier pigeon.
Diseases or messages?
Both.
A bird with gossip.
How exciting.
Do you open other
people's mail ?
Well, who's the people and
how hard is it to open ?
I don't know where
that came from.
- What's gotten into you ?
What had gotten into both of them
was their niece's homeopathic pie.
As with any
mood stabilizer,
moods were a bit
inconsistent at the start.
Do you think you can fix her ?
She'll only go out there
and get hurt again.
Coyotes will have
their way with her.
She was meant to fly.
She needs to fulfill her destiny
and deliver that message.
A bird that stalks
down his narrow cage
can seldom see through
his bars of rage !
- It wouldn't hurt to try.
- That's the spirit.
And once we fix pidge,
we can celebrate --
by taking a trip
to the pie hole.
It's a nifty spot with
lots of interesting folks.
You never know who
you might run into.
With that,
Olive Snook set her plan in motion.
Why would we go out for pie
when you just brought us one ?
I'll think of a reason.
While Olive Snook considered how to
get Lily and Vivian out of
their rut,
the pie maker was considering
worst-case scenarios,
not only for a rogue hijacker,
who he had been hired
to find by Becky Caden,
but for Chuck and the man
who caught her in a way
the pie maker never could.
They're not here. This is bad.
- Maybe they went for a stroll.
- That would not make it better.
Well, what's worse --
the two of them locked up
in the trunk of a hijacker's car or
sipping mimosas in a hotel room ?
I'm not a fan of either scenario,
and what's that smell ?
I thought it might
be your cologne.
- Who wears cologne?
- I wear cologne!
Look. They had coffee.
Ohh!
There's something bad in there.
Is that the hijacker ?
What kind of fool hijacker hides
himself in a damn coffee table ?
Damn gout.
Aah, I'm so cramped,
I feel like I'm stuffed in a trunk.
You are stuffed in a trunk.
Don't contradict an old man.
It's disrespectful.
- Did you hijack that plane ?
- What plane?
Oh, hell's fire.
That thing flew into my apartment!
- This is your apartment ?
- What'd I just say ?
There I was,
enjoying my daily prunes
and the psyllium powder
and hoping for the best.
And suddenly,
I see that thing flying at me.
If this is your apartment,
then who is Conrad ?
What is this --
the idiot brigade ?
Hello.
Oh.
Do you like pie ?
It would be criminal
not to like pie.
Everything I am,
everything I was, everything that
represented me as a
human being was in there.
- I have to start over.
- I lost everything once.
- And you know what ?
- Did a plan into your living room?
- No.
- Well, was it arson ?
No, it was something else, but I
felt a queer thrill of opportunity.
To get new stuff ?
To let go of everything
about me that I didn't like
and to hold onto everything
about me that I did.
Well, I've just met you,
but I...
can't imagine anything about you
that isn't something to like.
Chuck's first thought was to
quickly pull her hand away.
Her second thought was how nice it
felt to have someone hold her hand.
Oh. Sorry.
Was that your
boyfriend back there,
the one who took a step
back to let you fall ?
He didn't let me fall.
It was actually a very
affectionate gesture in context.
If it was only the
pie maker's hand.
Can I ask you a small favor ?
Would you hold my hand
just for a moment, but
don't say anything?
And I'm gonna close my eyes.
All right.
In that moment, Chuck was
holding the pie maker's hand...
...if only by proxy.
It was the proxy that
concerned the pie maker.
I got to pee.
- How did it go ?
- Where did he go ?
Conrad? He was going
to the bathroom.
He's not Conrad.
He's the hijacker.
And he's going to the
bathroom in my kitchen.
Boy, you miss one
trip to the morgue...
Is this the hand
you were holding ?
Well, he's a great big fibber,
then, isn't he ?
A great big fibber, whose hand you
were holding. What's that about ?
I was -- if you must know...
I was pretending I
was holding your hand.
Is that supposed to
make me feel better ?
Well... yeah.
Oh, well, on one hand,
it does make me feel better.
On the other hand --
the hand you were holding -- it doesn't.
Ned, he's an escaped convict.
You didn't know that
when you held his hand.
And P.S.,
Not only is he an escaped convict --
he's also a hijacker who's
prevented thousands of crops
from being aerially fertilized.
And he stuffed a surly
old dead guy in a trunk.
I'm not saying thate isn't guilty,
and I'm not saying that I am.
I'm just sayin that
it's not about him.
No, it's about our client,
Becky Caden, wife of Bradan Caden,
the woman your handyman when he decided
to crop-dust someone's living room.
- Did you catch him ?
- That one-armed bitch was speedy.
But I checked in with my
people at the prison.
You got "people" ?
That's so neat.
- Did you find out anything good ?
- Yes.
And we're gonna need shovels.
Emerson Cod had learned
three things --
first, the man they
knew as Conrad Fitch
was actually one
Lemuel Winegard,
a low-level employee of a
company called Ornan energy.
Second, Ornan was an
energy-based corporation
known for several types of trading --
plastics, steel, and insider.
The latter cost lemuel
his right hand.
Aah !
It also cost him
his freedom.
Third, during his incarceration,
Lemuel became known as "Lefty Lem,"
a name given to him by his cellmate,
Jackson Lucas,
an infamous diamond thief,
whose final escapade resulted
in a buried treasure that
was never recovered...
...even after he died.
He ended up in a prison
graveyard with his secret.
Oh, so Lefty Lem was a
white-collar criminal.
That makes much more sense.
Oh, yeah, thank you.
Gonna get paid once by the pilot's widow
when we prove her husband's
death wasn't a suicide --
dead bodies always
lead to paydays.
Yeah, yeah,
"vodka in the freezer."
Gonna get paid twice by the feds
when they give us the reward
for kicking lefty's ass back to
the clink, where he belongs.
Looking forward to that.
And gonna get paid thrice by
finding Jackson's buried booty.
Hey !
Hey.
Come to papa.
Wait. You might want
to avert your eyes.
There's a good chance
he'll be on the dewy side.
- Damn. I hate dewy.
- Are you mad at me?
Why would I be mad ?
For holding someone's
hand that wasn't yours.
Seriously, in a
prison graveyard --
that's where y'all are gonna
have this conversation ?
You should, uh,
breathe through your mouths.
I would have preferred
a little more eyeball.
Just touch the damn thing.
- No, wait.
- For what ?
A little dignity.
Thanks.
I can't see anything!
Am I blind ?
The good news is,
you're not blind.
Bad news is, you're dead.
Makes blind seem like a walk
in the park, doesn't it ?
Where'd you bury your loot,
Jack ?
Ha ! Why should I tell you ?
Good karma.
It's like currency in the afterlife.
In the old windmill
on the Vonroenn farm,
at the bottom of the stairs.
- How much that worth ?
- Plenty.
Ask him about Lefty.
Did you tell him
where you buried it ?
Of course I did.
Owed him that much.
- What did you owe him for ?
- Keeping the fire alive.
All right,
we got a windmill to find.
Chuck's fire may
not be alive,
as far as her aunts Lily
and Vivian were concerned,
but Olive was doing her
best to reignite it.
- Brackets.
- Ribbon.
- Bejeweler.
- Can I do one ?
- Maybe the last one.
If you like, we could bejewel
Pidge's birdhouse when we're done.
Pidge's house is
only temporary.
No sense in bejeweling an empty home,
is there, pidge ?
There's something so sad
about an empty birdhouse.
When one of our birds dies,
we taxiderm it immediately --
put it right back on its perch.
Vivian does wonders
with sand and thread.
And little marble eyes. It's like
our birds never left us at all.
You can't put everything
back on its perch.
It must have been all kinds of
horrible for you when Charlotte left.
She didn't leave. She died.
And no amount of sand or thread
or little marble eyes
will ever bring her back.
But Olive didn't
need sand or thread
or little marble eyes
to bring Chuck back.
She needed a
confluence of events.
Wing.
And she was about
to get one.
Wing.
Can I do the last bejewel ?
I already did it.
Oh !
What do you think, Pidge ?
And while Olive,
the aunts, and Pidge
looked forward to the next
step in their journey,
another journey had
reached a dead end.
Is she dead ?
Lefty Lem has officially
taken the lead.
Do you think fake
Conrad killed her?
Ockham's Razor --
all things being equal,
the simplest solution
tends to be the best one.
I used to believe that until you
brought me back from the dead --
kind of screws the theory.
Maybe your finger
needs a new battery.
Here, let me try.
Ow !
- He did it.
Oh! I must have dozed off again.
Uh, can I help you ?
We're looking for a windmill,
a Vonroenn-variety windmill.
Oh, that's funny.
A young man was just in here,
asking about the Vonroenn mill.
He didn't happen to have one arm,
did he ?
- As a matter of fact, he did.
- Ockham's!
- Bless you.
- Thank you.
The windmill -- what happened to it ?
Razed, wrecked, rebuilt, removed ?
Retired. No farm, no use.
Got shipped off to "narm"
some 20 years ago.
Why did they send it to Nam?
Did the vietnamese need windmills ?
N.A.R.M. --
National area of retired mills.
The Vonroenn mill has been preserved
for an historical landmark.
I have a map here.
Now, that's narcoleptic.
Necrophiliac's the other one.
Yeah.
Armed with a new plan,
the pie maker and associates
left the narcoleptic
curator to her dreams.
Meanwhile, back in
Coeur d'Coeurs,
a tiny friend was
planning her own escape.
Olive's disdain for chuck
was split in two --
one for stealing the
pie maker's heart
and the other for
breaking the aunts'.
You know you want to
read Pidge's message.
Lily would be so displeased.
There was an incident.
I read something that I shouldn't have,
and then life
went horribly awry.
Lily never forgave me.
She said she did, but she didn't.
Wow. Now I'm more
interested in that story.
Let's put Pidge back
into her house.
Pidge has left the building.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry her empty
birdhouse makes you sad.
Maybe you could fill it with
all your Charlotte sadness
and hang it in a special
place in your soul.
That's an awfully sad birdhouse
to have hanging in one's soul.
Hang it someplace you
don't have to see it.
It won't always be sad.
It'll be the happiest little
birdhouse when you're ready.
Make a little
birdhouse in your soul.
Don't encourage her.
I think she looks divine.
Son of a bitch.
Wait ! You forgot your message !
Pidge !
Pidge, wait !
You forgot your message !
As the aunts watched
Olive scream for help...
Pidge ! Help me ! Pidge !
...They considered
their own birdcage
and wondered if they were
ready to leave it behind.
A few miles away...
looking out across
the fields and hills,
a beautiful woman
named Elsita
waited for the man she loved
to make her heart complete.
Little did she know Lefty
Lem was already on his way.
What the hell do you want ?
I'm from the papen county
historical society.
We'd like to photograph these
premises for our 87th annual
"mills of the wind" papen
county collector's calendar.
- Where's your camera ?
- It's in the car.
You're lying.
But I'm bored.
I'm your only friend
I'm not your only friend but
I'm a little glowing friend
but, really,
I'm not actually your friend but I am
blue canary in the outlet
by the light switch
who watches over you
make a little
birdhouse in your soul
not to put too
fine a point on it
say I'm the only
bee in your bonnet
make a little birdhouse
in your sou-u-u-u-l
Never mind the singing.
Keep your eye on that bird.
You know what our problem is.
If you're referring to
the touching thing,
I see it as more of an
obstacle than a problem.
- It's a pretty big obstacle.
- Not compared to our other problems.
- We've got "other problems" ?
- I'm gonna kill myself.
There's so much I'm
learning about you.
- Such as ?
- You're romantic.
When the mood strikes.
And you're jealous
when the mood strikes.
Everyone's a little jealous.
I mean, if you're not a little jealous,
you're probably...
- Can we not talk about this ?
- The answer to your query is "yes."
No, actually,
I want to talk about this.
I could let it go,
but like the cat, it will come back,
which I wouldn't call annoying,
but there's no really great way
of saying "half annoying,"
which it is a little bit.
See ? Isn't this neat ?
Here we were,
thinking all we had was one big problem,
when, in actual fact,
we have hundreds of little problems
that we got to sort out before
we even get to the big problem,
which means we're like
everybody else in the world.
Except I still can't catch you.
Yeah, we taking
two cars next time.
That's a big ax.
Oh, I'm not gonna hurt you.
I promise.
This is, uh,
just a precautionary measure.
Wouldn't it be easier if you put
the ax down, then tied the rope ?
It's funny --
you really are a one-armed bandit.
Your name's not McClapping, is it ?
As in "the sound of one hand"...
No.
'Cause names are destiny.
If you think "Dwayne Cloggin"
ain't gonna grow up to be a plumber,
then you just think again.
Oh, no, you didn't use bows
to tie me up, did you ?
You take a hostage like
you tie your sneakers.
What is your problem ?
Well, I was born into
the life of windmillery.
Are you gonna listen,
or are you gonna keep knocking?
I'm listening. You were born
into the life of windmillery.
Always waiting on the wind to show up,
so you can start work,
and I'm no good at waiting.
I'm tired of it.
You sure it was the wind that
you were a-waiting for ?
Did you just say "a-waiting" ?
'Cause if you are mimicking me,
I will be out of these girly bows
faster than a snake through weeds!
I wasn't thinking,
and I apologize.
It's just, well, I have a lot on my
mind, and I'm in a bit of a rush.
Oh, where you rushing to ?
Well, I don't really know yet.
Well, maybe you better
figure that out.
Go back to your knocking.
Come on, Pidge !
You can do it !
Not even a breeze
to help poor Pidge,
which is kind of ironic, given the
surroundings. Pidge ! Come on !
The pigeon, growing fatigued with
each flap of her taxidermied wing,
knew something the
others did not.
Her journey was
almost complete.
Oh.
- What was that ?
- It's my bird !
That's my bird.
What are you on about ?
It's my bird.
I'll prove it.
I wrote the note.
Where's the note ?
Hello ?
Can I get my bird back,
please ?
- Your bird?
Yes, my bird.
She's a carrier pigeon.
She has a message, and she has
to carry it. It's what she does.
That's my message.
- Elsa ?
- I'm Elsita.
- Jackson ?
- I'm Lem.
Elsa was my mama.
Jackson was my prison bunkmate.
- Is "bunkmate" a euphemism for --
- Not in this case, ma'am.
There was a bitter chill
in the air the night
Jackson Lucas found refuge
in the Vonroenn windmill.
Already five days on the lam,
he knew the police were closing in.
To preserve his dreams of one day
owning an art gallery in Mexico,
jackson decided to bury
his stolen treasure
in the staircase of the
seemingly abandoned property.
His heart
stopped, however,
when he saw an angelic creature
descending the stairs.
Her name was Elsa,
and this was her windmill.
My name is Elsa.
This is my windmill.
It was love at
first sight.
Knowing he had very little time left,
he kissed her.
It was a perfect moment.
The next moment was not.
I'll write you !
Elsa kept true
to her word.
For the next 20 years,
she and Jackson
continued their love affair by
correspondence, letters sent to
and fro
with the help of her virtually
untraceable carrier pigeon,
until the day Jackson knew he would
no longer be able to keep
his promise.
Someone else would have
to do it for him.
After Jackson died,
I started to plan my escape.
It took me two years. And all that time,
I kept writing to Elsa.
First, I was writing out of
loyalty to the man who taught me
the ropes in prison, but after a while,
I started to develop...
- A condition ?
- For Elsa --
at least,
I thought it was Elsa.
And mama made me swear on her deathbed
that I'd never stop writing to Jackson,
said it would break his
heart to learn that she died.
But each letter was more
beautiful than the last,
and I found myself
looking forward to them.
Well, your letters
were beautiful, too.
What's the big whoop ?
Pidge brought them together.
How did she lose her wing?
I took her with me on the plane
when I busted out of prison.
She flew out the window after takeoff
and went right through the propeller.
Oh !
Pidge crashed the plane.
Oh, Pidge.
What happened to the diamonds ?
"Diamonds" ?
Holy crap !
Now, now, let's not panic.
I'm sure it's just the mailman
or a windmill-to-windmill salesman.
Let me handle it.
As Olive peeped through the peephole,
it occurred to her that,
while the carrier pigeon was
safe inside the windmill,
the same could not be said
for the sitting duck
currently waiting
on the doorstep.
This was the moment Olive
Snook had been waiting for.
She need only open the door to
expose Chuck's deceit to the aunts,
and the pie maker
could be hers.
It was everything Olive wanted,
and yet...
She knew that the aunts would be
traumatized by the discovery
that the late Charlotte
Charles was late no more.
In that moment, Olive felt
the angry fire in her heart
extinguished by a light breeze. She
had grown fond of Lily and Vivian
and could not bring
herself to hurt them.
- Afternoon, gang !
- Olive ?
What the hell are
you doing here ?
Pie delivery.
Tart apple, I believe.
With those two words,
chuck knew.
Her aunts were inside.
Olive...
If you know what's good for you,
and I think you do,
- you'll give me two minutes.
- Why ?
- What for ?
- Okay.
Goody, then.
Who was it ?
Wrong mill.
Must happen a lot around here, huh ?
Anyway, I feel just awful that
we've taken up so much of your day.
We should really be going.
Do you mind if we use the back door ?
I just wanted to take a peek
at your garden on the way out.
Thanks ! Bye !
- Ned.
- Hmm ?
Do you remember before, when I told you
all the things I'd learned about you ?
Jealous, romantic, jealous.
I felt I had to say it twice.
Right. Well,
now might be a really good time
for you to write down all the
things you learned about me.
- Why ?
- That way, if stuff happens...
- just remember the list.
- Time's up.
Well, now,
wasn't that a nice outing ?
I could use a drink.
Young people depress lily
because she's afraid of dying.
As Lily wondered whether
she was afraid of dying
or simply missed
feeling alive,
she allowed herself one deep
breath of fresh country air.
I don't think we've been out since --
Charlotte ?!
No need to yell her name.
I think heaven's closer than we think.
I agree.
Hand up !
Lemuel, I'll write you !
The pie maker and the
girl he called "Chuck"
marveled at love's power to
conquer all obstacles --
Distance and time...
Hardship and pain...
A lack
of reciprocation...
Even death.
Your husband was a great pilot.
He didn't kill himself.
A pigeon did, by accident.
With Pidge's help,
the long-distance love affair of lefty
and Elsita continued to soar.
And the pie
maker realized
that while some obstacles
may never disappear...
Care to dance ?
Hmm. Yes, please.
...You can always find a
way to work around them.
You caught me.
Thanks to Raceman
for the transcript
Subtitles made by the Bloc Team
For www.forom.com