My name is jane vasco.
I could use
you on my team.
I work for a secret government
agency that hunts neuros.
People who can do dangerous
things with their minds.
On my first assignment...
Something a little
weird happened,
okay, something
really weird.
Until i get some answers
i'm getting on with my life,
doing my job.
Stocking up on aspirin,
because I gotta tell ya,
pain's a bitch!
Big Line Thirsday. Arsonist has finally been
apprehended by local authorities.
After allegedly burning another house to
the ground in north salem last night
the serial arsonist and public
enemy number 1
for this community has
apparently been apprehended.
Trial begins today.
Up to the minute coverage
right here on action news.
My partner and I were on routine
patrol when we saw the flames.
Would you tell the court
what happened next.
We arrived at the samuel's house and
saw the suspect fleeing from the scene.
When he refused to obey
our orders
my partner fired
a warning shot.
Was that sufficient to stop the defendant
from attempting to escape?
No, sir.
I fired at the suspect.
My shot hit
him in the leg.
It was at that point that
we were able to subdue him
and take him into custody.
The police alerted us to
the fire just after 10:00 am.
Two of our units
responded, including emu.
By the time we
got there...
...The fire had already reached the second
story of the samuel's house.
How long did it take
to get control of the fire?
It took about an hour
before I felt that it was safe
for my men
to enter the structure.
Would you tell us
what you discovered.
Most of the ground
floor was gone.
There was enough left
of the support beams
to keep the house
from collapsing.
After you entered...
What was your first impressions
as to what caused the fire?
As we passed through the main entry
of the house, I noticed a "hot spot."
could you explain that?
Usually the location where the fire
begins is the hottest spot.
Usually you'd expect to see
the hot spot in a kitchen,
near a stove, or in the case
of an electrical fire,
near wiring or
circuit breakers...
Something like that.
Was that the case in
the samuel's house?
No.
My first impression was that
the ignition point of the fire
was a small bathroom
on the ground floor.
Is that unusual?
It's not unheard of but,
yes, it is unusual.
Unless there's indication of flammable
materials or electrical problems.
Given what you saw,
did you form an opinion?
My first reaction was
that, like the others...
This was an arson fire
of unknown origin.
Was there anything else of note
about this downstairs bathroom?
Yes.
And what was that?
We found charred,
human remains.
Were these "remains" those that were
later identified as lucy samuel's,
one of the occupants
of the house?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
That's all.
Would defense counsel care
to present any witnesses
at this time?
No, your honor.
We would, however, appreciate
an expeditious ruling
on our
request for bail.
Given the severity
of the charges,
serial arson and second degree murder,
i'm going to rule
that the defendant will
be bound over for trial
and held
at the county jail.
Bail is denied.
It's just the preliminary,
not the trial.
So where do we
go from here?
To work.
Transcript : swsub.com
Presync : IceFre@k
Connor King.
Ex-cop.
Ex-con.
Kinda cute in a borderline
sociopath kind of way.
God, i can't believe
i just thought that.
Here's the deal:
i'm able to heal,
and connor isn't,
but he keeps taking
one for the team.
Either he's mental or
there's more to the man
than he wants
people to see.
Check that, he's definitely mental,
but he's also a good act.
He works hard to keep people at
arm's length, but then so do I.
Maybe we're more alike
than i'd like to admit.
Except he loves to be hated
and maybe would hate to know
every once in a
while he's loved.
Here's what we're
up against.
Public opinion's
running pretty high.
People want
someone to blame.
There is someone to blame.
A pyromaniac neuro.
I work for the government
just like you do.
We know the truth here.
The public doesn't know
anything of neuros.
So the truth isn't always
the best defense.
That's reassuring.
We're not here to reassure you,
we're here to acquit connor.
What're we looking at?
Facts that don't
look good for connor.
First, he's been identified
at three of the six fires.
Because we've been on
the trail of the neuro
who's been starting
those fires.
Go on.
Connor, against your orders,
broke position and entered that house.
Yeah, to try and apprehend
the damn fire starter.
Look, i understand
your thinking.
But i want you to consider for a moment
how the jury would react
if i put any one of
you on the stand
and asked you testify to
the existence of people
who possess the ability to
start fires with their mind.
The truth isn't always
the best defense.
Witnesses have placed connor
at the scene of multiple arsons.
He was apprehended exiting
the samuel's house...
And then there's his
criminal record.
Is that admissible?
Evidence only requires
exclusion when probative value
is substantially
outweighed by the danger
of unfair prejudice, confusion of the issues,
or misleading the jury.
The present rule recognizes the
practice of admitting evidence
for a limited purpose
and instructing
the jury accordingly.
How the hell did
you know that?
I read up on
it last night.
So the judge can admit
connor's criminal record.
Given miss vasco's very
accurate recital of the law...
Yes.
Hell, why even bother
having the trial!
It sounds as if he's already
been tried and convicted.
I'm not going
to lie to you.
We're facing an
uphill battle here.
But the war's not over until
we've taken our best shots
at all the evidence.
Given everything
you told us,
it sounds like truth
may be our best shot.
Why don't we tell the jury what we're
really dealing with.
It's not as if we
can't prove it.
Even if you're right...
You're sworn to silence
and secrecy.
Our hands are tied.
Maybe it's time
to cut the knot.
What you should have done
is made this all go away
before it even started.
You'll have to explain
that to me, agent mcbride.
As your superior,
i do have connections
in high places.
As high as they go.
However, they don't extend
into the heavens.
Heavens?
What is that
supposed to mean?
Only god can
save connor?
Don't give me that crap!
Disagreement, i encourage,
sir.
I will not tolerate
insubordination.
Hell, we've covered up
the assassinations
of foreign leaders.
Our own leaders!
But when it comes
to connor king...
The man was shot
at the scene...
By the police.
The case of the
decade, solved.
It was on the front pages
before they'd read
him his miranda.
How, exactly, did you expect us to
make that "go away?"
then let us
present the truth.
Admit to the existence
of neuros.
Only as much as
we have to.
Need to know.
And when the prosecution
demands proof...
What then?
We give it to them!
We've got years
of caseloads.
That would not only bring
something to the surface
that we've worked very
hard to keep secret...
But would compromise
your team as well.
"Need to know" rapidly
becomes full exposure.
It might be connor's
only chance.
And it might not.
Are you willing to see
your unit de-commissioned
to risk a defense that, chances are,
no one would ever believe...
Despite your proof?
And if they did believe
it and connor was acquitted...
The result would be a
population in panic
and our ability to keep our
operations a secret
and fight these
"things" compromised.
Is one man really
worth that much?
That one man happens
to be innocent.
Soldiers do die in battle.
A soldier
dying on the field,
in combat,
is something that
can't be undone.
Connor isn't dead.
You know as
well as i do...
He was always a liability.
Liability?
What is that
supposed to mean?
Feed him to the wolves
because you don't like
his attitude?
Consider this,
agent mcbride...
With all you do know...
If i were to permit
this...
Put you on the stand...
Armed with all
your evidence...
Simply because the fires
are of unknown origin,
you can't prove that
a neuro is behind them.
Great.
The first time
i get you alone
and we've got
see-thru doors.
My luck's
turned to crap.
You know
what they say...
It ain't over
'til it's over.
What the hell
do "they" know?
They're out there.
If andre sent you to cheer
me up, you should know...
You really suck at it.
Maybe.
But andre doesn't
have my legs.
What aren't
you telling me?
It's the truth.
He's got lousy legs.
Andre just got word...
No mention of
the team,
what we do...
or neuros.
Great.
So i end up looking like a guy who
likes to hang around fires.
Who happens to have
a criminal record.
We're trying to
keep that out.
We'll come up
with something.
My neck in a noose.
Connor, listen it...
Save it, bowers.
We all know the risks.
I'd rather gone down
takin' out one of
those mental
defects but...
We don't always get to make
that choice, i guess.
Andre's still trying
to get the truth out.
No, bad idea.
He'd only
compromise the team.
If i have go down
for this, i go down.
Fall on your sword, man
of honor kind of thing.
The hell with that.
Figure at least maybe i'd get a going
away present from you and supergirl.
What?
Just nice to know that,
even in a moment of strength and
character, you're still a pig.
Hang in there.
Guard!
Twenty-three
years old.
Married just
under two years.
Killed in an arson fire.
Those faces are what's
going to hang connor.
No...
Regulations and his past are what's
going to hang connor.
If they admit his
criminal history.
That's no longer an "if."
the judge is admitting it.
Look, nobody...
Not even the top arson
investigators
could figure out how these
fires were started.
Hell, even with my brain, if i didn't
know about neuros,
i wouldn't be able
to figure it out.
Your point?
What kind of background
does connor have
that could make him that
much of a specialist?
Someone who can
outsmart even the best?
That's pretty slim, riley?
They don't care how they started
just that they were.
You have something better?
I could lie.
I was there with him.
Since i can't testify as
to why i was there...
Why do i have to admit
that i was.
About a half a dozen
cops as witnesses?
My word against theirs?
Enough of this.
I don't need two of
my people in prison.
Just get up there and
answer the questions.
And put another nail
into connor's coffin.
Admitting who we are
and what we do is not
the only truth here,
people.
The truth is that there is a neuro
out there who did set those fires.
And who stopped setting them the
moment connor was arrested.
Doesn't matter.
We find the person
that did this...
And connor walks.
Let's get to work!
Look, if you guys would only stick to
my pattern, we might find this guy.
Connor already put a dent
in your pattern
the day he and vasco staked
out the samuel's house.
We all agree on this:
every target house was two-stories,
painted blue,
all within a mile of an
interstate on ramp.
And all...
Except one...
Have garages
facing back alleys.
If you say "Except for one"
there is no pattern.
Connor played a hunch
and he was right.
Sorry, riley.
If we go strictly by
your criteria
we could miss the
next opportunity.
If there is one.
Well i'm sorry,
my database isn't set up
to predict hunches.
Well maybe it should.
You're fighting
the clock on this
He goes on trial tomorrow.
They're calling bill cole,
connor's former cell
mate to testify.
With bail denied,
former police officer
and convict, connor king
faces arson and murder
charges today
in day 1 of this
gripping trial.
A profile of mr. King, the
man behind the match tonight.
Everyone knows connor is
crazy, that's why we love him.
But an arsonist,
i couldn't believe it.
And yet...
He's down!
Let's get him!
Take care of this!
Thanks!
So much for falling
on your sword.
What the hell did you
think you were doing?
Trying to save my ass.
Which i might've if vasco
didn't pull her hero act.
She took two shots
to her shoulder...
To act like a hero.
She'll get over it.
She was trying to protect you, connor
from more than just bullets.
How far do you think
you'd get if you got away.
You gonna keep me
after school, boss?
I'm trying to help,
what do you
want me to do,
just throw you
to the lions.
I thought you
already did that.
Every man has his
breaking point.
I know you.
This isn't yours.
Why'd you run?
Listen to me you
stubborn son of a bitch,
we're trying to help you.
We can't do that if you're
hiding something from us.
Why'd you run?!!
Bill cole's gonna testify.
I know.
We tried to keep your past
record out of this...
But you don't know
what he knows.
I read your sheet before
i took you on the team.
Tip of the iceberg, pal.
Okay...
Tell me what
i don't know.
Sorry, no can do.
The more i know, the more
i might be able to help.
Ain't gonna happen.
You're willing
to face a murder two rap.
But you won't
tell me about this!!
Unless you're trying
protecting someone.
Hunting down "chip monkeys"
isn't the only thing
worth dying for.
But not facing
the consequences
of bill cole's
testimony is?
Come on!!!
I told you when you brought
me on board this team,
you knew everything about
me you needed to know.
You had my word that i would
not jeopardize this team
or, intentionally,
put anyone at risk.
I think i made
good on that.
Anything beyond that
promise is personal.
Bill cole's scheduled
to testify tomorrow.
Nice to know the date
and time of your own execution.
So where are we?
Pretty much
at square one.
Maureen and i
came up dry
with everyone left
on our list.
Route truck drivers,
delivery personnel.
Basically every theory
we've been working on.
Nothing.
No one had a hunch?
Shut up, riley.
No.
No!!!
I know you're the big boss
and you guys go out
into the field and
grab all the glory
but you get to do what you do
because i'm in here, doing what i do.
And you know what?
I'm damn good
at what i do!
But you're all willing
to risk connor's ass
because you trust
your instincts, your hunches,
more than you do what
i'm telling you.
I'm right about
the pattern,
despite connor's
lucky guess.
Have you stopped to think
that maybe the reason
the samuel's house didn't
fit the pattern
is because connor
did start that fire?
You don't believe that.
No,
but i do believe that if we worked
my theory, we might find out who did.
Alright, run it again.
Alright.
Why the guy targets two-story blue
houses is anyone's guess.
He's a psycho.
Maybe he grew up in
a house like that.
Hated his mother.
His father.
The color blue.
I don't know.
But why the garages
facing alleys?
Because it gives
him access.
There've been six fires.
And no one's spotted
the fire starter.
Why?
Every house has been within
a mile of an interstate.
What does this mean?
The guy's on wheels.
What does he do when
he finds his target?
Park and walk?
Or stash his car somewhere
in the alleys.
Maybe even a
neighboring garage.
It's a long shot.
Do you have
anything better?
We'll have to interface
with the locals,
get out
in the field.
Interview some neighbors.
Let's roll.
You're going to do it?
Like you said, i don't
have any better ideas.
Jane,
can i have a word.
Yeah.
I told you yesterday i didn't
want you committing perjury.
Change your mind?
No.
Then what?
What i have in mind
is a whole lot worse.
today, the judge
in the invisible man arsonist case
is going to allow testimony
of the criminal
background of connor king.
Bill cole,
a former police officer and
partner of the defendant,
is scheduled to take the stand
this afternoon.
Stay tuned.
Excuse me?
Are you bill cole?
Yeah.
Got a message for you.
Someone wants
to talk to you.
Just head back out.
Down the hall, through
the door on the left.
How are you doing?
Against the fence
with her.
You'd be dead before your
hand hit the knob.
What do you want from us?
You going to tell me
what this is about?
It's about two people who are going to testify
against a friend of mine.
You still haven't
told us who you are.
The man who will
kill you if you do.
Right here?
With all these
cops around?
That would be
my problem.
Yes, it would be.
And i don't think you'd
take that chance.
Try me.
I'm a federal officer...
Oh, my god.
So this is how it is.
The "big man," connor king
doesn't take any chances.
Can't risk anyone finding out that he and
i did time together
arson charges.
Alright pal,
let's see how much of
a risk you're willing to take.
What are these
photographs?
They're our
wedding pictures.
The woman in the
photograph is...
Lucy.
She's...
She was my wife.
I understand the morning
of the fire
you left for work
at around 8:00 am.
Yes, sir.
And lucy, was it typical
for her to be home at that hour?
Yes.
Lucy worked part time.
She didn't usually leave
the house until around noon.
You were at work when
the police arrived.
Yes.
Tell us about that.
Two detectives showed
up at my office.
They told me there'd
been a fire...
They said that someone...
That someone had
been killed...
...They asked me
to come down
to the medical examiner's office
to make an identification.
And did you do that?
Yes.
It was lucy.
The prosecution calls
bill cole to the stand.
Mr. Cole,
would you tell the court
how you
know the defendant, connor king.
I refuse to answer.
Excuse me?
I refuse to answer on the grounds
that it could incriminate me.
You and mr. King served time
in prison for crimes committed
while you were employed
by the metropolitan police.
Isn't that so?
Objection, leading
the witness.
Your honor.
This witness has been
granted immunity.
The fifth amendment
doesn't apply.
Mr. Cole.
The court directs you to
answer the questions
put to you by
the district attorney.
Mr. Cole.
Have you ever been arrested
or served time in prison?
Mr. Cole...
I refuse to answer on
the grounds
that it might incriminate me.
Your honor.
Mr. Cole, the court
will not be lenient
if you continue
to refuse to answer.
Answer the question.
I refuse to answer on
the grounds
that it might incriminate me.
Alright, court finds
bill cole in contempt.
Bailiff!
How'd it go?
We bought some time.
I don't know how much.
Well, we've got something.
Genius boy strikes again.
At least two neighbors
to the previous arsons
reported that their garage
locks had been broken.
The cops said they found oil stains
on the cement in both garages.
Not so unusual
for a garage.
Except one of the residents
doesn't own a car.
And in the other garage, a one-car
garage with the car in it...
The oil stain was
off to the side.
And this tells us...?
I'm having samples run
on the oil stains to confirm...
But from everything
we can tell,
the quantity of
oil and the location
is that our boy shows up to do
his dirty work on a motorcycle.
It does fit.
Doesn't give us a name
but it gets us
a step closer.
Even if you're right...
I'm not sure this
actually helps.
Hell, it's more than
we had 24 hours ago.
We're forgetting something...
Connor rides a motorcycle.
the quality of
the material is quite good
as are the magnification
properties.
Your honor, the defense has stipulated
that these towels
are the same brand
and fiber content
as those found in
the samuel's home.
Noted.
You may proceed.
Doctor.
Turn on
that light, please.
I'm sure many of us rember
playing with sunlight
and magnification
as children.
We'll have to imagine
that this is sunlight,
coming into the courtroom
from the outside.
The degree of magnification
would affect
the amount of time
this would take.
As i said, this sample
is quite good.
Doctor, is it possible
that a magnifying device
that you're holding,
could that have started
the fire
in the samuel's house
or any of the other fires?
Objection.
Speculative.
Whether the device
started the fire or not
is not an issue.
To date, there's been
no evidence entered
to indicate that anyone knows
how these fires started.
Sustained.
No further questions.
Doctor, in a typical
house fire, would solid glass
be completely
consumed by heat or flame?
Damaged, perhaps.
Completely consumed, unlikely.
So if a device had been
used in the fire.
Subsequent investigation would
have turned up all
or part of those
magnifying glasses.
That would be true.
If they were
made of glass.
It wouldn't take much more
than a match flame
to turn these
into useless ash.
These are made
of spun sugar, highly refined.
No further questions,
your honor.
Mr. Beetle, would you tell the court
where you're employed?
I own and manage a storage facility
just outside of cranston.
This is a facility where
anyone can rent space
to store their belongings.
Precisely.
Do you recall accompanying
my investigators
to storage unit 14d,
two weeks ago friday?
Yes, i do.
Were you with them when
they entered the unit?
They needed my permission
and my master key
to gain entry.
Among the contents
in the unit,
did you come across this
box of magnifying devices.
In fact, we found
about a dozen boxes.
That is one of them.
Do you recognize
this form?
This is one of our standard,
long-term contracts.
And that particular
contract...
How long has
the signatory
leased space in
storage unit 14d?
Two years, three months
and fourteen days.
Would you read the name of the person
to whom the unit was rented?
Connor king.
This is a load of crap!
Order!!
This court will take
a half hour recess.
You know about this?
Of course not.
Do something!
I'm doing the best i can!
Is this your best?
Is this your best?!
Remember this face,
beetle, rember it!!!
I don't believe it,
connor entered the samuel's
house against orders.
So when has connor done
anything by the books.
Thought he saw something
going on,
thought he had a window
of opportunity
to get the neuro
and to get out.
But, from inside the suv,
you couldn't see
what he was
doing in the house.
All you can say is that you saw
connor enter the house,
saw the fire begin
and saw him running out.
What the hell is this?
It sounds like you guys
really think he's guilty!
Nice to know where
your friends stand
when things get tough.
It's not about
what we think.
You just answered the questions
the d.A. Will put to you.
And by the way, bill cole
may not be the only one
who could testify
against connor.
Why don't you tell them
what you were telling me.
What?
What we were
talking about...
Connor's hunch.
I was thinking about what
riley said the other day
about things being
simple and logical.
We assume that either
connor had to be right
or riley had
to be right.
But given what we learned
about the oil stains
in the garages...
I started thinking...
What if they
were both right?
If?
Let's assume riley is
right about the pattern...
About the importance
of the garages.
The samuel's house didn't
have an alley-facing garage
and didn't
fit the pattern.
Maybe we're not dealing
with a pyromaniac at all.
Maybe we're dealing with
someone who has a motive.
Think about it,
lucy lived in
a two-storey blue house.
So...
The neuro wants lucy
dead, or maybe scott...
To cover his tracks, he torches five other
blue, two-story houses.
To avoid the risk
of being seen,
he looks for houses
with alley facing garages.
He doesn't realize there's
a crazy genius named riley
who sees that as part
of the pattern.
By the time he gets
to the samuel's place,
he thinks it's going to look like just another
whack job, blue house arson.
You got that background
on the samuel house yet?
I'll find something,
i just need a little
bit more time.
Something connor doesn't
have a lot of.
If i was you,
i could break every bone
in my body,
slip through these
air holes
and walk out of here
good as new.
If you were me,
you'd look a whole lot better
in that orange jumpsuit.
Looks pretty grim, huh?
We're working
on something.
Don't know yet
if it'll pay off.
It might help if you
told me what happened.
You starting to
think i'm guilty?
That's not what i said.
It's just that
the more we know...
You know what i want
you to know, darlin'.
That's it.
Yeah, it's going
to have to be.
Yeah.
I'm on my way.
I gotta go.
Vasco.
Thanks.
See you in court.
What've you got?
I found the original computer file
of connor's storage locker rental.
So it's legitimate.
No.
What?
According to the receipt,
connor's rented this unit
for a little
over two years.
But that's the date
on the contract.
Not the date
on the file.
The date on the file is
only three weeks old.
Maybe it's not
the original version.
If someone saved
a duplicate copy
wouldn't it have
a more recent date?
It would.
But every file's embedded
with a creation date.
Doesn't matter how
often it's modified.
This file didn't
exist last month.
Then someone is
setting him up.
Here's the kicker.
I traced the computer
that created it.
The d.A.'S office.
Richard stanley.
Connor's attorney.
What?!
Why?
That doesn't
make any sense.
Yes, it does.
Don't give me that!!
Who do you think
you're talking to?!!
This has got your paw
prints all over it.
Richard stanley works
for you and like most
of the people who
work for you...
He follows orders.
Setting connor up for that storage locker
rental was your idea.
You're a team
leader, mcbride.
You're not the
commander-in-chief.
I protect my people.
Even if it's from the
commander-in-chief.
You don't have
the big picture.
I've heard that
story before.
Sometimes the "little
people" have to be sacrificed
for the greater
cause, is that it?
I don't see the greater
cause here, sir?
Unless it's
protecting your ass.
I don't like your tone.
You're not supposed to.
King's a liability
to the team.
And to the work we do.
I made a decision.
It was too late to make things "go away"
as you'd hoped we could.
If king goes away
for this now,
the rest of our problems
will go away with him.
Sir...
I'm not prepared
to let that happen.
You're the field
op, mcbride.
In battle,
it's your call.
Policy is mine.
And policy extends beyond
personal feelings and loyalty.
You know that
as well as i do.
And you might need to give
it some serious thought
before you do anything
you'll regret.
Richard,
here's the new deal.
If i find that you do anything
to sabbotage connor's chances
to get out of this.
If i don't see that you're
doing everything in your power
to provide the best defense,
i want you to remember this:
the government spent a lot of money
traing me I'm very good at what i do.
I can approach
a man from 100 metres
and he'll never
hear me coming.
I'll let you decide.
Do you want to spend every
day for the rest of your life
looking over
your shoulder, waiting...
Let's go.
Well, if that's not a motive for murder,
i don't know what is.
Everything's in place.
Stanley has his
marching orders.
We've got the new witness.
Crowd control?
The judge has agreed
to clear the courtroom
and hear this
outside the jury.
So she finds if
it admissible...
Let's hope it doesn't
get that far.
get too hot to handle.
This court is
now in session.
Would you state your
name for the court?
Ellen drake.
Miss drake...
It is "miss", isn't it?
Yes.
Are you familiar with
the blue ridge motel?
I know the name,
i think...
Have you ever been to
the blue ridge motel?
I've driven past it.
But you've never actually
been on the premises?
No.
Your honor,
may i approach?
Would you look
at these photographs.
Would you agree that those
are photographs of you?
Yes.
What would you say if i told
you that those photos
were taken from a surveillance
camera located
in the lobby of
the blue ridge motel?
And do you see the time
stamps on those photographs?
Yes.
They date back at least
a year, don't they?
Yes.
I expect that the
reason you perjured yourself
in this courtroom is
because you were trying
to protect someone.
Is it possible that
you lied
because on the dates in
question at the blue
ridge motel,
you were there
with a married man?
Yes.
Mr. Samuel's...
On the dates those
photographs were taken,
were you at the blue ridge
motel with miss drake?
I should inform you, those
photographs are enlargements.
The originals show the entire
office area.
Let me ask you again...
On the date in question,
were you at the blue
ridge motel
with miss drake?
Yes.
Would it be reasonable to say
for the better part of a year,
you had been conducting
an affair with miss drake.
Your honor...
Answer the question.
We're in love.
How very nice for you.
Do you own
a motorcycle?
Yes.
It's a late model
torque speedster?
Yes.
You should have it
checked for oil leaks.
Riding a motorcycle can
be potentially dangerous?
I suppose.
I'm curious...
Your wife, lucy,
did she ride?
No.
But you had some reason
to be concerned
for her health or welfare.
No.
Why then did you take out
a half a million dollar
life insurance policy in her name
two weeks before she died.
If anyone in the family
was high risk,
it would be you,
mr. Samuel's.
I thought that...
If you notice the time stamp
on one of the photographs,
november 18th,
the night before the fire.
Let me ask you something,
mr. Samuel's.
You claim to be in
love with miss drake.
Objection.
Overruled.
You meet for an amorous
evening the night before
your wife dies
in the fire.
Two weeks earlier, you
take out an insurance policy
for half million dollars
in her name.
Objection.
Overruled.
Are you psychic
mr. Samuel's...
Or do things just have a
way of working out for you?
Your honor!
You set the fire that killed
your wife, didn't you?
No!
In fact, you set all
the fires hoping to cover up
what you did,
isn't that true, mr. Samuel's?
Richard, don't!
The hell with you!
Case closed
you son of a bitch.
Sometimes you have to lose
something to gain something.
This time, we almost
lost connor.
I suppose what i've gained
is the realization that,
as much as i try to avoid it,
we are a team.
And when push comes
to shove
we stand beside each other.
Some of us might even
like each other.
What's this?
No champagne?
He is cute, isn't he?
Warm bottled water and
a briefing in 10 minutes.
Welcome back!
Thanks.
Hell, this was easy time.
Maybe for you.
I had to teach
these guys logic.
Welcome back.
How's stanley?
Nothing major.
Vasco did a pretty good
job of saving his hide.
You ask me, he'd do a damn
good impersonation
of a crispy critter.
Glad to have you back.
Well, that's so easy
to say, darlin'.
- Actions speak a whole lot louder than words,
- Oh yeah, he's back.
One, big happy family.
You got ten minutes
learn it well.