When I was little
my dad called me
his "painkiller Jane".
Whenever I got hurt,
I made the pain go away.
Only I didn't
just bury it.
Or push it aside...
...I pretty much murdered it.
Afterwards, I'd go to
a peaceful place in my mind.
I called it
the emerald city.
Partly because
it was green.
Mostly because
I could only dream about
what magic
must be inside.
It was my way of
controlling a world
that was out of control.
Subtitles: swsub.com
Presynchro: Sixe
Hello.
Report to security on floor 1-14
take the express elevator.
Control can be
a dangerous illusion.
There are some things you have
absolutely no control over.
Gravity being one
of the big ones.
If you thought I was
having a bad day then,
four days earlier
was even worse.
Confused?
So was I.
A new designer drug
had started circulating
through the clubs.
Maureen and I were hoping
we'd score that night.
Maureen's my partner.
As d.e.a. Agents,
we'd been working
this case for three weeks.
If we'd done it my way,
we'd made
the bust two weeks ago.
Only we didn't do it
my way.
We've got enough on those two guys
to ask some serious questions.
No buy, no bust, Jane.
And one more day
in her borrowed heels,
I'd be limping permanently.
We play by the rules.
I got samples, you brought the money?
Be ready.
What do you think?
You said you wanted
to play by the rules.
Looks like they've
just been broken.
Take the ugly one.
Wait...
...come back later
d.e.a. Hands up!!!!
Don't move!
Usually, they like it
when I do, darlin'.
You're not going
anywhere, pal!
D.e.a. Freeze!
Hands up!
...what the hell is this?
Listen to me.
My name is
Andre Mcbride.
I'm a government agent.
We're on
the same team.
I'm sure.
I don't think you're sure
of anything right now.
And a bad shooting...
Shut up!
The man beside me is producing
a hallucination.
You cannot trust
what you're seeing.
You sure you can believe
what you're hearing
any more than what
you're seeing?
He's a genetic aberration.
We've all got
our problems.
Right now, this is
your problem.
He's doing this to gain
time and confuse you.
Well he's doing
a damn good job.
The man beside me
is going to kill you.
He's lying.
No.
Easy.
I want you to
explain this.
You first.
How did you know
I was telling the truth?
You're shadow moved,
he didn't.
Smart.
Your turn.
What just
happened in here?!
Yeah, nothing on him!
I got it.
They cleared you.
Still doesn't say what
branch of the government you work for.
It's not supposed to.
Why'd you come after us?
We saw a buy go down.
We've been working this
place for three weeks.
Saw you guys
hanging around.
Didn't look like
your kind of crowd.
I'll take that
as a compliment.
It wasn't meant as one.
What happened in there?!
I'm afraid, you'll have
to be content with
"thank you" agent Vasco,
and leave it at that.
Hey, you might've checked out
with my supervising officer,
but that doesn't mean
you checked out with me.
The neuro's tagged
and bagged, boss.
Thank you.
You ever hear of
a neuro?
What's a neuro?
No idea.
But it's something we're
not supposed to know about.
You probably
figured out by now
I'm not much of
by-the-book kind of gal.
Which is why invited chuck
in the I.t. Department
for coffee and
a bagel the next morning.
Which is why he agreed
to check out
Andre Mcbride and the d.e.a
mainframe that afternoon,
which is why
by the time I was called in
the deputy director's office...
Have a seat.
I could have sworn
the bagel was still sitting
in my stomach.
Your current investigation has
been terminated by the director.
Why?
She chose not to share
that with me, agent Vasco.
I do know your entire
service record has been
red-flagged by the Pentagon.
You tried to hack
our database.
I don't do well with
unanswered questions.
Well, life's full of them.
What do you want?
You.
Now?
Up here?
Your school records
indicated you were suspended
22 times over
the four-year period.
That's a lie,
it was twenty-three, actually.
Reasons included
everything from fighting
and swearing to feigning
an epileptic seizure.
Yeah.
My bad.
Hospital records show
that when they refused
to let you visit
your dying mother,
a nurse found you holding her
in the middle of the night...
Somehow you've been living
in her room for three days.
I'm done here.
I know what makes
you tick, agent Vasco.
And I know you think
outside the box.
If you didn't,
I wouldn't have survived.
If that's a thank-you...
It is.
I could use you
on my team.
Only I don't know what
your team does, do I?
Well, that's the catch-22.
Can't tell you
until you're aboard.
I'm more the kind of girl you
have to take to dinner first.
The work is unlike anything
you've ever done before.
And we call our own shots.
Everyone's accountable
to someone.
You'd only be
accountable to me.
Military.
You have that "I love
the chain of command"
charm about you.
Seven years with
special forces.
Well, I appreciate
the offer.
Whatever the hell it is.
Careful.
Even in my own shoes,
I can't put one foot
in front of the other.
One request,
agent Vasco...
Since you've now decided
to stay out of our business,
stay out of our business.
doc... Doc...
- Where do you want these?
- Just there.
Intruders approaching
from the north tunnel!
Go!!
Riley, how many?!!
Two!
Proximity!
Fifteen meters!
How'd they get through!
I don't know but I think
they're armed!!
I'll cut 'em off
at the subway passage!
Ten meters out!
No time, we set up here!!!
They're on us!
Stand down!
Put your weapon down!
Don't shoot, it's me!
Show!
Put the gun down now!!
All clear.
Riley, all clear!
She caught me coming in.
Nice place.
Do the decorating
yourself?
Hope you like it.
Now that you've
violated security
and know our location...
It's yours.
No, no,
you listen to me,
how can I be reassigned?
Because you can.
What if I say no?
I hear there's an opening
at mielo's department store.
Ladies shoes.
I call the shots in my life,
agent Mcbride.
Vasco!
How'd you find us?
This!
She tagged you, boss.
Careful.
Even in my own shoes,
I can't put one foot
in front of the other.
Looks like I can put one foot
in front of the other after all.
Gentlemen.
Hey, mo.
What the hell's going on?
I heard you got booted from the agency!
I wish I knew, I...
I have no problem taking
first position.
But not this way.
I appreciate that.
And I want to go on record that I think
you're getting a bad rap.
You are getting
a bad rap, aren't you?
Maureen...
With the way you do things,
I always knew I'd get
to say "I told you so."
How come I'm not enjoying it.
- What you're talking about?
- Don't screw around with this, Jane.
Get a good lawyer.
When the d.e.a. Files drug
possession charges
against one of their own,
it's serious.
Get a good lawyer.
Yeah, yeah, I gotta go.
Thanks for calling, mom.
We both play hardball,
agent Vasco.
And we both play to win.
Even if it means screwing
with someone's life?!
In time, you'll be cleared
of the drug charges...
If you join our team.
That's not much of
a choice, is it?
That was the idea.
Special agent Steve Ford,
communications tech
Riley Jensen,
and you remember special
agent Connor King.
The ugly one.
Joe Waterman ran
operations for the subway.
Before the city
shut it down.
Well most of it anyway.
Hi, I'm dr. Seth Carpenter.
And this is agent Jane Vasco,
formerly of the d.e.a.,
who's graciously consented
to join our team.
Another woman.
She's more than qualified.
If only I knew for what.
We hunt neuros.
Neurological aberrant.
Which is what we were
doing in that club the night we met.
Your partner,
is she straight?
Six years ago
the government became aware
of a genetic aberration
appearing in the population.
Despite their differences,
we've discovered
a definable pattern
in their gene code.
This aberration seems
to affect the
neurological center
of the frontal
and cerebral cortex.
What dr. Carpenter's
means in english,
those with the aberration,
possess a unique ability
to influence others.
Like the one in the club.
The one you experienced had
the ability to induce hallucinations.
But we've encountered
dozens of variations.
In how many people?
To date, almost 200.
Welcome to the freak show.
What causes it?
Well... Um...
You don't know.
Several possibilities
genetic, environmental,
chemical...
We're still working on
trying to find the source.
The reasons the neuros use
their powers is as varied
as they are.
We think the aberration
interferes with
the brain's ability
to distinguish
right from wrong.
You really don't know
that much, do you?
We know they're a pain
in the ass.
Which is why the government
has gone to great lengths
to keep the phenomenon secret
and not panic the public.
We use intel from law
enforcement, and media
first to identify,
then contain.
Contain?
We chip 'em.
The micro chip basically
short circuits "the problem."
once it penetrates
the epidermis,
nano tech propulsion delivers
it through the bloodstream
to the brain.
Each method of transmission
varies with the op.
Sometimes it's
with this...
Sometimes it's less
conspicuous...
So much for
job orientation.
You're a smart girl,
you'll learn the rest as you go.
We've been working this
case for some time.
Someone is dealing
substandard medications
on the black market.
Sounds like
d.e.a. Territory.
It was.
Now, it's ours.
We're convinced there's
a neuro behind the operation.
The drugs in question are made
and manufactured by vono tek.
The emerald city.
It's hard to believe
that the company
would even manufacture
sub-standard product?
They don't.
But about one-tenth of one
percent of every run
fails quality control.
Contamination.
A snag in
the manufacturing process.
Expired ingredients that
didn't get scanned properly.
Even that small percentage
amounts to millions of drugs.
Any batch that fails to
pass qc is locked away
and slated for destruction.
In this case, someone's
making an end run
and getting them out,
onto the street.
Obviously, the medications
look like the real deal.
But any unscrupulous pharmacy,
someone trying to cut corners...
There have already been
a dozen deaths
traced directly to vono tek.
Why are you convinced
there's a neuro behind this?
We lost one of our agents
to a "neuro".
Shannon Perry was a member
of our team.
I put her inside
vono tek.
Her first day on the job
she left the building
and calmly stepped
in front of a moving truck.
Women don't last very
long around here.
Is it the sexual
harassment...
...or a size deficiency?
Shannon's psych
record was spotless.
Someone made her do it.
How'd they break
her cover?
We don't know.
She was following
Randall Hyde.
Vono tek's head
of security.
In order to have free
access to vono tek's vaults,
the neuro would
have to control Hyde.
Unless he is the neuro.
He's clean.
We've taken
tissue samples.
The neuro obviously had to get
close enough to control shannon.
How close is close?
Proximity.
It varies but in order
to control a subject,
a neuro would
have to be nearby.
So we need to go back in.
Yes.
But not solo.
I want you and
Jane inside.
You can play tag
with Hyde and watch each other's back.
We move quickly here,
Vasco, get used to it.
I hacked human resources.
Most are working tomorrow.
Impressive.
You have no idea.
All I can say is be
careful what you wish for.
The thing about
dreams is...
...they can turn into
nightmares faster than
you can click
your high heels.
Report to security
on floor 1-14.
Take the express elevator.
Boss, they've
cleared security,
they're in position.
Blue one's Hyde,
Jane's on him.
He's on the express
elevator to the lobby,
looks like he's
leaving the building.
Entering the express
elevator now.
You said "the lobby",
right?
Yeah.
Hyde wasn't on it.
Had to be on it.
There's no where
else to get off.
He has to be still
in the building.
Hyde must be jamming
his security tag.
Wherever he went,
he obviously doesn't
want anyone watching.
Or the neuro doesn't.
Yeah.
I can beat it.
The only question is how
long is it going to take.
Got it.
I'm into their climate
control system.
Monitoring Hyde's movement
through his heat signature.
I did that by...
Riley, where is he?
I don't know where he's been
but I know where he is now.
Just landed
on the 46th floor.
Thank you.
Steve!!!!
What are you doing?!!
It's me, Jane!!!!
Knew she wouldn't make it.
Stop crying.
Mom's dead.
There's nothing you
can do about it.
When they put her
in the ground,
say goodbye
and let her go.
Don't ever let them
see you cry again.
see you cry again...
He'll kill you.
We all have our problems.
The neuros tagged
and bagged, boss.
This work is like any other work
you've done before.
I call the shots in my life,
agent Mcbride.
Your entire service record
has been red-flagged...
What the hell
is going on?
We hunt neuros...
Dozen deaths, directly to...
He's on the express elevator.
No freakin' way!
Boss, you better
take a look at this.
Why am I not dead?
Another "you don't know"?
You're alive.
That's the only thing
that's important right now.
Easy, easy, easy..
Listen, I want you
to stay here,
we'll monitor your vitals,
we'll do more testing.
The neuro was
controlling him.
Logical conclusion.
I'm more interested
in illogical ones.
Agent Vasco survived
a forty-six story fall.
There are freak accidents,
there are freak survivals.
Hundreds have
been documented.
Plane crashes, suicide
attempts, construction workers.
All lived.
Now what aren't
you telling me.
Lacerations.
Contusions.
Internal organ damage.
She doesn't have any.
Not even a scratch.
But she...
No, nothing in her blood work,
tissue samples or brain scan
indicate anything related
to what we're dealing with.
So what is she
dealing with?
Where do you think
you're going?
I am so over this,
you have no idea.
I am going home.
You're...
Supposed to be dead!
That's okay.
The agency told me you fell
off a building.
Drunks fall off buildings.
I was pushed.
I need a drink.
Jane, you shouldn't have
left the hospital.
I didn't.
I left the morgue.
You know how I hate
the cold.
What the hell is going on?
I don't know.
I just fell forty stories
and now I'm looking
for a glass
I should've washed
a week ago!
Forty?
No, no, they said
it was four.
Four is a...
Possibility?
This is about neuros,
isn't it?
Neuros, you just
stay out of this.
I know you had
that dork from I.t.
Running checks on that guy
from the club, Andre Mcbride.
I got onto his computer
and I ran a check on his check.
Why did you do that for?
Because covering
your ass is a habit.
Are you okay?
You have no idea what
you just got yourself into,
no idea.
Mcbride recruited Maureen
the same say he did me,
I tried talking myself into
believing she had it coming.
And it involved caring
too much.
Covering my ass.
The truth is, I would have
done the same for her,
only I wouldn't have been
so damned dramatic about it.
Keep your distance,
Maureen.
You said these neuros
need to be in close
proximity to the subject
in order to exert control,
is there anyway to find out who
would have been close enough
to both shannon and Steve?
Been there, done that.
No one who was within range
of shannon when she died
was above the tenth
floor of the building
when Steve went through
the window.
Then how the hell does
a neuro influence people
when they're
not within range?
Remote control?
The comm-sets!!
Riley?
I suppose transmission
through the airwave counts as proximity.
It'd be a first, though.
Everyone uses
that communication system.
It could be anybody.
But not everyone is
cleared to talk directly
to another employee.
Who would have clear and open
access to the comm system?
It's got to be
Hyde's assistant!
She runs the central
switchboard.
Crap!
What?
She just comm'd Maureen.
How could she
make it so quick?
She can monitor the entire
operation from her desk.
- Can you intercept the transmission?
- I'm trying to get in now!
I can't intercept
but I can get in.
Only it won't be
a secure connection.
Do it.
We're in.
Your name is
Maureen bowers.
You were recruited
by a government agency
to hunt neurological
aberrants.
The thoughts
you're having...
They're not your own.
Someone's trying to get
you to kill yourself!
Your name is
Maureen bowers.
You were a d.e.a. Agent...
Mo, it's me.
You're being controlled!
Dammit, mo!
For once in your
life listen to me!
If you don't stop
this second, mo...
...who is going to be there
to watch my back?
She's alive.
Boss, Hyde's assistant is
leaving the building.
Riley, stay on her.
Let's move.
Approaching her...
Now.
She didn't go there
to turn herself in.
Neuros control people.
When you're being followed, who better
to control than people with guns.
I say we go in anyway.
We badge the badges,
when the cop pulls his piece,
we blow him away,
chip the bitch,
let the feds straighten
it out later.
Sounds like something you came
up with in prison, Connor.
Did you say prison?
There were extenuating
circumstances.
There always are.
Ma'am,
you can't be back here!!
They'll be here soon.
Get down!!!
There are all kinds
of decisions in life.
Some more difficult
than others.
For the sake of the team,
I knew the one
I was about to make
was one I couldn't avoid.
For the record,
I knew something else,
it was going
to hurt like hell.
Connor, get back
through the water here!!
Hurry it up, Connor!!
Let's go!!!!
What the hell did you
think you were doing?
Thinking outside
the box?
For future reference,
agent Vasco,
I give the orders
around here.
We're both alive,
aren't we?
You shouldn't be!
Listen to me,
whatever the hell
is going on with me,
I really need to know
what it is, okay?
I'll find answers, Jane.
You have my word.
When my mother died,
it hurt.
It hurt a lot.
And something in me
had changed.
I realized that pain was
going to be my friend.
That it would sustain me.
And make me stronger.
I just never realized
how much stronger
"stronger" would be.
And how changed I would
actually become.
I don't know
what happened to me.
Or what it means.
No one does yet.
For right now,
I'm just trying
to stay focused on the job
taking one day at a time,
putting one foot on the other.
Boss, I know where Hyde went
on the express elevator
floor 1-13
only there is
no floor 1-13.
How he accessed
it? No idea.
For what reason,
don't know.
But I will.
No, you won't.
The mandate is to identify and
contain neurological aberrants,
whatever happens after that,
it's not our problem.