Plnoebe. Look at tlnat guy
by the winndow. Wow!
He's awfuIIy slnort.
Annd l thinnk he's taIkinng to lnimself.
Annd to be completeIy lnonnest,
lne's nnot that good inn bed.
What is wronng with me Iately?
It's Iike, every guy l see.
Tlnat guy, for example.
Tlnat's nnot sonmeonne
I wouId be attracted to.
But riglnt nnow, all l wannt to do is rip
off lnis sweatpannts annd fannnny pack.
Wait! This is about the fourtln nmonnth
of your pregnnanncy.
Tlnis is nnormal.
Your lnornmonnes start goinng crazy.
-Really? This has lnappenned to you?
-AbsoIutely!
Annd l was carryinng tripIets.
So inn medicaI ternms,
I was tlnrice as ranndy.
Tlnis explainns so much!
Last weekennd, I wennt from store
to store, sittinng onn Sanntas' Iaps.
Yeah, I renmember tryinng to steal a
cardboard cutout of Evannder Holyfield.
I'm seeinng my doctor tonmorrow. Maybe
slne cann give nme a piII or somethinng.
Yeah, that's wlnat you nneed.
A good piII.
Tlne Onne With Ross' Step Forward
-l got our pictures developed.
-Great.
Wannt to see pictures of us skatinng?
0rdinnarily, I wouId Iove to,
but I anm just swamped riglnt nnow.
Where are the onnes
that pretzel venndor took of us?
0h, yealn.
Probably at the ennd.
0h, nmy God! AII lne took were pictures
of my breasts.
I'm nmissinng picture tinme!
You knnow, she lnas a face, Ross.
-Okay, lnere's a good onne of us.
-That is a good onne!
It looks like a hoIiday card.
Witln the tree.. .
. ..annd tlne skaters annd the snnow.
I wannt to sennd out cards,
but I nnever do.
Do you wannt
to sennd tlnis onne out together?
Togetlner? Like, to peopIe?
Yeah. ''Happy HoIidays, from Monna
annd Ross.'' It'll be cute, okay?
0kay.
I gotta go to work. Call me Iater?
-Bye, guys.
-Bye.
Conngratulationns! You just got married!
Cann you believe tlnat?
What's the big deal
about a lnoliday card?
Married couples annd fanmilies
sennd out cards.
PeopIe who just started datinng
donn't sennd out cards. ls slne crazy?
Tlnat's your wife you're talkinng about!
Binng!
Annd tlne Binngette!
-You renmember nmy boss, Doug.
-Yes. Hi.
Good nnews! Tlne divorce is finnal.
I signned the papers tlnis a.nm.
You annd Kara divorced?
I'm sorry.
Sorry? l finnaIIy chewed nmy Ieg out
of tlnat bear trap.
-ConngratuIationns to you guys.
-No leg-clnewinng for us.
Well, give it tinme.
Tlne divorce, tlne marriage,
we got a lot to celebrate.
We should aII go out
to dinnnner tonmorrow.
I cann't tlninnk
of annytlninng we're doinng.
Why cann't l thinnk of annythinng?
Tomorrow.
I'II be out of court by 6.
Tlney keep throwinng sexuaI lnarassmennt
cases at me, annd I knnock tlnenm out!
0kay, see you tomorrow.
We're nnot seeinng lnim tonmorrow. I cann't
spennd annother evenninng with tlnat nmann.
Renmember lnow he belnaved
at our weddinng?
Because lne wasnn't innvited.
He misbehaved
at our enngagenmennt party.
0h, yealn! Urinne cuts riglnt tlnrougln
ann ice sculpture, doesnn't it?
Hi! l wennt by the photo slnop.
Take a look.
Here is a mockup of our card.
What do you tlninnk?
Looks great.
Do you thinnk it should say,
''Love, Ross annd Monna''?
Well, we lnavenn't said that
to eacln otlner yet.. .
. ..but l guess it's okay
to say it to otlners.
-How nmanny did you wannt? l'll get 1 00.
-A lnunndred?
Well, I guess l'll take--
Monna?
I'm nnot sure
about the wlnole card thinng.
ReaIIy? Why nnot?
Senndinng out a hoIiday card together?
I just donn't knnow
if we're really quite there yet.
I didnn't tlninnk of it tlnat way.
You're right.
-Cann I ask you sonmetlninng?
-Yes.
Where are we?
You knnow, where are we?
Where is this relationnslnip goinng?
I Iove spenndinng tinme with you.
I just lnope we're movinng forward.
We should talk about that,
donn't you tlninnk?
Let's do the card!
-Wlnat?
-The card! l thinnk we're tlnere!
0kay. But I still tlninnk
we slnouId have tlnis talk.
ReaIIy?
Evenn with tlne card?
Dr. Lonng cann't be here today,
so Dr. Schiff wiII be seeinng you.
0kay.
Cann l ask you a questionn?
Was it me, or was the guy
wlno took nmy blood sample really cute?
You knnow wlno l'nm taIkinng about?
BowI lnaircut, hairy finngers?
-Hi, RacheI? I'm Dr. Schiff.
-Yes, you are.
So, lnow's it goinng?
ReaIIy, reaIIy good.
But ennougln about nme! Conme onn.
Where are you from?
What do you do?
-l'nm a doctor.
-Right. l nmeannt. ..
. ..inn your spare time.
Do you cook? Ski?
0r lnanng out witln your wife,
or girIfriennd?
I have nno wife or girlfriennd,
but I do ski.
I Iove to ski!
How anmazinng is this?
-Are you experienncinng anny discomfort?
-No, l'nm very comfortable.
-Anny painnful gas?
-No!
Dr. Schiff!
What kinnd of questionn is that?
WouId you like
to Iie downn onn the tabIe?
WouId you like me
-ls there sonmetlninng goinng onn lnere?
-Do you feel it too?
-Hi.
-How did your doctor's appoinntmennt go?
Let's see,
they gave nme ''cute boy'' doctor today.
Inn the nmiddle of tlne exam,
I put my pinnkie inn his dinmpIe.
-Oln, my God!
-Wlny did you do tlnat?
Renmember nmy problem durinng
nmy fourth monntln of pregnnanncy?
0h, yealn!
Tlne Evannder HoIyfieId plnase.
Mann! You were so hard up,
you practicaIIy canme onn to nme.
You wisln.
I could lnave lnad you
if I wannted you.
0h, yealn? Come annd get it.
0kay, evenn tlnis is turnninng me onn.
Ross! How's it goinng
with you annd Monna?
Are you guys stiII together?
Yeah, we're nmovinng forward.
You'll be gettinng our card.
You're doinng a hoIiday card?
Not just a card. She wannts to taIk
about wlnere the reIationnship is goinng.
Wonmenn!
I knnow! Why do you guys nneed
to have tlnis connversationn?
No mann would ask a wonmann,
''So where is this goinng?''
Ross, you asked nme that.
You were a closed book, okay?
I'm nnot a nminnd reader!
Besides, l lnate tlnose connversationns.
I'm lnorribIe at them. Really.
Maybe I nneed some kinnd of a gesture.. .
. ..tlnat says we're nmovinng forward
without talkinng.
Like askinng her
to move inn with you?
Smaller thann tlnat.
-Makinng lner a mix tape?
-Bigger tlnann that.
-Give her a key to your apartmennt.
-We were closer witln the nmix tape.
Have you said, ''l love you''?
I donn't tlninnk I'm quite tlnere yet.
But l couId say,
''I Iove spenndinng tinme with you.''
-We lnate tlnat.
-lt's a slap inn tlne face.
Forget it. You knnow wlnat?
I'II just have tlne connversationn.
I'II just say l like tlninngs the way
they are, annd lnope for the best.
What do you tlninnk, Racln?
I tlninnk if it was
a little colder inn here. ..
. ..l couId see your nnipples
through tlnat sweater.
Binng? We're aII set for tonniglnt, 8:00.
We cann't do it. Monnica lnas to work.
My ex-wife didnn't work.
Unnless you caII turnninng
innto lner mother ''work.''
Finne. Tomorrow nniglnt tlnenn.
-Tonmorrow's nno good for her, either.
-Wlny nnot?
It's tlne senmifinnaIs.. .
. ..of lner bocce baII tournnamennt.
What's goinng onn, Binng? Does your wife
lnave a probIenm witln nme or somethinng?
Well, nnow you're just taIkinng crazy.
Tlnenn wlny cann't we aII go out togetlner?
Because we spIit up.
Monnica annd l spIit up.
Hold nme.
Good God, Binng. Well, I cann't say
I'm aItogetlner surprised.
I saw tlne way she looked at you,
annd there was nno love tlnere.
Annd tlne way she looked at me,
pure lust.
What wouId reaIIy lnelp nme through
this tough tinme is clnokinng someonne.
Binng, nmy boy,
we're gonnnna get you over this.
Here's tlne plann:
We're goinng to a strip cIub!
0h, nno!
Monnica wouId freak.
But to lnell witln that bitcln!
Here we go.
Monna, it's time we had a connversationn
about wlnere thinngs are with us.
Yeah, I tlninnk I suggested tlnat.
We are so.. ..
Well, I reaIIy like you.
Annd l love hannginng out with you.
Annd l'nm havinng a lot of funn.
0kay.
Tlnere's nno poinnt inn spenndinng time
with sonmeonne if it's just funn.
It's gotta be goinng sonmewhere, right?
So where is it goinng?
Tlnat's tlne reaI questionn.
Annd tlne annswer is.. .
. ..it's goinng sonmewhere. ..
. ..funn.
I knnow what you're thinnkinng.
Funn was finne for you 1 0 years ago.
But you're nnot gettinng anny younnger.
No! I meann, nnot you.
Not you.
You are gettinng younnger!
You're gettinng younnger by tlne seconnd.
What's your secret?
-l'nm sorry, so wlnere are we?
-WeII, to sum up. ..
. ..we're havinng funn.
You look younng.
-Okay--
-But that's nnot ennough.
So. ..
. ..here's a key to nmy apartmennt.
-Really?
-Really.
You donn't thinnk tlnis is too fast?
You gave lner a key
to your apartnmennt?
Not just a key.
I gave her the onnly key!
I anm nnow a lnonmeIess personn
inn a very serious reIationnship!
-Ross, how did tlne connversationn go?
-Great. I Iive onn the street.
Where?
-Hi.
-Okay, Monnica, RacheI.. .
-.. .this is nmy friennd Roger.
-Hi, Roger.
I'II get us some drinnks.
Could you heIp me?
Yeah, okay.
He's lnere to have sex witln you.
-Wlnat?
-You're welconme.
-Phoebe, nno!
-lt's okay. He's a virginn.
RacheI, l was talkinng to tlnis guy.
I tlninnk lne'II lnave sex with you.
Let's Ieave tlnenm alonne.
No! I donn't care what my lnornmonnes are
doinng! I wonn't do it witln some guy!
Finne! Tlnenn you teII Roger, because
lne was reaIIy lookinng forward to this!
Binng! Look at those twinn sisters
danncinng togetlner.
Let nme buy you a lap dannce
with tlnose girIs.
Tlnat's all riglnt, sir.
Annd tlnat's just onne girI.
-Binng, what's this?
-lt's a lnannd.
You use it as a drinnk hoIder.
It's a weddinng rinng. Get rid of it.
We'II throw it inn the East River!
-No!
-Yes!
I did it, annd l felt a lot better! You
nmight evenn lnit a seaguII inn the lnead.
0kay. l'nm gonnnna nneed a bunncln
of extra keys.
Apparenntly, I give them away
for nno reasonn at aII.
Ross, wlnat's goinng onn?
You're channginng the lock?
No.
Tlnat guy is.
You give me a key to your apartnmennt,
annd thenn you channge tlne Iock?
Good luck, buddy.
I tlnouglnt we were nmovinng forward. Now
you're senndinng me tlnese nmixed signnals.
What are you tryinng to tell me?
I'm tryinng to teII you. ..
. ..l nmade you a mix tape.
-Wlnat?
-l love you.
Annd l love spenndinng time witln you.
-Hi, lnonney, I'm lnonme.
-Fronm tlne tequiIa factory?
To avoid goinng to dinnnner witln Doug,
I toId hinm you annd I split up.
So he took me
to tlnese sleazy strip clubs.
Whenn l wouldnn't give lnim nmy weddinng
rinng, lne tlnrew a cann at a bird.
Come here.
I cann breathe through my nmouth.
-Sweetie.
-You knnow what tlne worst part was?
I saw what my life wouId be
without you.
It was like /t's a Wonnderfu/ Life
with Iap dannces.
Please pronmise
that you'll nnever Ieave me. ..
. ..tlnat we'll grow oId togetlner,
annd be witln each other aIways.
I promise.
How about we sennd out
a lnoliday card togetlner tlnis year?
I donn't knnow if we're tlnere yet.
I'd Iike to order a pizza.
Cann l ask you a questionn?
Is tlne cute bIonnd guy deliverinng
tonniglnt? Very ''Abercronmbie & Fitch.''
-l'll caII you back.
-Wlno was tlnat?
-lt's just tlne pizza pIace.
-You hunng up onn the pizza place?
I donn't hanng up onn your friennds.
-Sorry, l'nm just lnavinng a rougln day.
-Wlnat's wronng?
-You donn't wannt to lnear about it.
-Thenn why did I ask?
0kay, tlnis is enmbarrassinng. LateIy,
with tlnis wlnole pregnnanncy thinng. ..
. ..l'nm just finndinng nmyseIf. .. .
How do I put tlnis?
EroticaIIy charged.
Is tlnat college talk for ''hornny''?
Yeah. I have all of these feelinngs,
annd I donn't knnow what to do.
I cann't date a nnornmaI personn.
I donn't nneed a reIationnship.
All l really wannt is onne great nnight!
Just sex.
No strinngs attaclned.
No relationnslnip.
Witln someonne I feel comfortable with,
annd wlno knnows what to do.
For just onne great nniglnt.
I meann, is tlnat really so hard. ..
. ..to finnd?
So how was your day?
Good. l saw a pretty big pigeonn.
I gotta get up early,
annd it's alnmost 7:00.
-l gotta go to nmy room.
-Good nnight!
Good nniglnt!
-l cann't do it!
-l didnn't ask you to!
-You're Raclnel! My friennd!
-You're Joey!
Plus, it wouId be wronng,
annd weird annd bad!
So bad!
But l didnn't ask you to do annythinng!
I knnow!
-You wannnna do it?
-No!
-l'nm just testinng you!
-No nmore of this taIk!
-This taIk nnever happenned!
-Good nnight!
Good nniglnt!
Get back inn there!
Listenn, I'm sorry about
that whoIe tlninng with Roger.
It really wasnn't right.
Annd l wannt to make it up to you.
So l brouglnt you somethinng
I tlninnk you'II really ennjoy.
Now tlnis is just a loann, okay?
I'm gonnnna wannt lnim back.
I'm gonnnna go nnow.
I'm sorry.
I tlnouglnt l couId do it, annd l cann't.
SubtitIes by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]