- Matthew?
- Hello, Melinda.
Why?
Why did you betray me?
You got what you deserve.
So you never loved me?
All the passion? All the heat?
I had to make you trust me.
It was the only way
to share your powers.
And so now you have them.
So why would you turn me in?
You know I'll burn.
Had to keep my secret.
Well, you can keep your trinkets too.
- I'll find another witch to give it to.
- Maybe not.
What magic is this?
I'm taking back the powers
you stole from me.
Outside of time, outside of gain
Know only sorrow, know only pain
No!
Rex.
Good morning, Prue.
I've left a few things for you
to catalogue.
A marvellous shipment
from an estate back east.
- I'll get right on it.
- Thanks.
At last.
Freedom.
The world has changed.
What time is this?
- Excuse me?
- Where am I?
- Who are you?
- Matthew Tate.
And if you freed me from that locket,
you are a descendant
of Melinda Warren.
- Thank you.
- For what?
I tricked you into using
your power on me.
Now I have it.
Behind you, witch.
- How did you do that?
- I can share your powers,
but you can't share mine.
- What do you want?
- I want what Melinda took from me.
I want all three powers back.
Defend yourself. Stop time.
I can't.
So you're not alone.
There are others.
And the family name
is now Halliwell.
Prue? Are you okay in there?
Hey. Did you see that?
I was just sitting there, you know,
reading sports,
having a cup of Joe, and bam,
this guy comes flying out of nowhere,
you know. Weird clothes,
bad manners.
Nearly fell right on top of me.
- When you say "fell"...?
- I mean fell.
You know, like from way up there,
I guess. I don't know.
- That's a ten-story drop, sir.
- Twelve.
And you're telling us that he just got up
and walked away without a scratch?
- That's what you're saying?
- Got a better explanation?
Excuse us.
All right, Trudeau.
Pull out your secret ghost hunter
decoder ring, and let's hear it.
Look, Morris, I don't know, okay?
All I know is whatever happened
started up there in that office.
- So let's find out whose office it is.
- I already know.
It's Prue's.
So I suggested we add crab satay
to the lunch menu, and it was great.
Sold out. Do you like crab, Leo?
- You know what I'd love, Piper?
- What's that?
Is the ratchet extension.
Could you hand that to me?
Sure.
I know that.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Go away.
- Be right back, Leo.
- No problem.
- Stop it.
- My sentiments exactly.
Stop hinting around
and ask him out already.
- Give him your crab.
- Don't be disgusting.
- Don't be so shy.
- What if he says no?
- Yeah, like that'll happen.
- No, I'm serious.
- So am I.
- I'm very serious. I've never...
...you know...
- You're kidding, right?
- No.
You've never asked
a guy out before?
Not on a real date, no.
Am I the only person in this family who
inherited the take-a-chance gene?
Probably, because if I remember
my biology correctly,
it's attached to
the can't-mind-my-own-business gene.
Go!
Well, part of the pipe is stuck,
but I'm almost finished here.
Terrific. Can I get you some tea?
- Yeah, that'd be great.
- Okay.
- What would be great?
- Nothing.
Leo!
Leo?
Frozen. Quick,
have your way with him.
Do you never stop?
- Looks like a Kodak moment to me.
- Phoebe, you're such a help.
Smile.
You guys, we are in serious trouble.
- Hi, Leo.
- Hey, Prue.
Hey. Sisters, upstairs. Now.
Webster. Hannah Webster.
You said you heard some noises
in here. What kind?
It's hard to say.
It almost sounded like
a struggle of some sort.
- A fight, perhaps.
- Yeah, and then we heard a crash.
And I assumed that was
the window breaking,
and we came in to check on Prue,
and then she just went running out.
What did she say? What happened?
Nothing, actually. She just left.
She was quite agitated too.
She didn't say where she was going,
did she?
No. No, sorry.
Okay. Thanks, Mr Buckland.
CSI will be done with the windows
soon, and you can have them fixed.
Believe me, inspector,
I really don't care about the window.
I only care about Prue.
Look, maybe you ought to ask
the captain to assign somebody else.
Prue and I aren't dating anymore.
There's no conflict, okay?
I'm fine with this.
Okay.
I thought that went exceedingly well,
didn't you?
You may have proven
the legend of the locket true
and that the little witch is charmed,
but now we have a 17th-century
warlock running around.
I think he'll stick out.
Yep. But then again,
if the legend does hold true,
Matthew's got a one-track mind...
...just like we do.
He won't be difficult to find.
Stop worrying, Hannah.
You're gonna get wrinkles
on your horns.
What did he say his name was?
Matthew Tate.
And somehow he knows that
we're related to Melinda Warren.
The Book of Shadows Melinda?
Our ancestor?
The one who burned at the stake
and started this whole mess.
Yeah, he came out of the locket.
And he has strong powers,
stronger than mine.
I mean, he did the weirdest thing.
One minute, he was in front of me,
the next, he was behind me,
and then 12 stories down.
Landed right on his feet.
If it walks like a warlock
and talks like a warlock...
Yeah, well, he's powerful,
and he means business, and he wants
all three of our powers.
Can I see the locket?
We have to figure out who he is
before he finds the two of you.
No!
You said Matthew came out
of the locket?
I think I just saw Melinda
put him in.
You saw the past?
- But you only see the future.
- Not anymore.
We always knew that our powers
would grow.
Yes, but somehow I thought
I was gonna get to fly.
They wanna countersue?
Fine, bring it on. I'll eat them alive.
Plus, we can double-bill
and get away with it.
Excuse me.
Are you Arnold Halliwell?
Yeah.
And who are you, Robin Hood?
Tell me where your sisters are.
What sisters?
I'm an only child.
Let me go, or I'll sue you.
Lawyers have not changed.
I was right.
It was Melinda in my vision.
Isn't she beautiful?
She kind of looks like Mom.
Listen to this. "And because
the warlock had stolen her love,
she cursed him into the pewter heart
where he could spend eternity
knowing the sting of betrayal."
- That must be what I saw.
- And I let him out early. Great.
You're not kidding. The legend says
that the warlock must never be freed,
or he will destroy the Warren line.
That'd be us.
Well, he'll have to take a number and
get in line behind the other warlocks.
We've never been up against
anyone like him before.
- So, what do we do?
- I say we hide.
No, we have to find out exactly
what we're up against.
And we start with the locket
and how it wound up on my desk.
Prue, your work's on the news.
Check it out.
Witnesses claim they saw a man
fall 12 stories. The twist?
He apparently got up
and walked away unharmed.
We gotta find him
before he hurts anybody else.
Especially an innocent.
- There's that I word again.
- Look, Andy's on TV.
This has been the most unbelievable
thing I've ever seen.
He's here too.
And this guy, he just landed
out of nowhere.
Andy. What a surprise.
- How you been?
- I need to talk with Prue, Phoebe.
Prue? Wow, how out
of the loop am I?
And here I thought
you guys broke up.
It's not about that.
It's police business.
Oh, well, she's not home.
She's at work.
No, she's not.
Then I don't know where she is.
But I'll tell her that you
stopped by, okay? Ciao.
A man fell out Prue's office window,
which is suspicious enough,
but then a man matching
the same description
went and killed a lawyer
down the street.
A lawyer named Halliwell.
Now, I know she knows who he is.
One more time, Phoebe.
Where's your sister?
Where's your warrant?
Great, so now I'm being hunted by
a warlock and the San Francisco P.D.
Nobody ever said you led
a boring life, Prue.
- Maybe Andy can help.
- You wanna have that conversation?
"Hey, Andy, I hate to bother you,
but a 17th-century warlock is trying to
kill me and my sisters. Any thoughts?"
Okay, it was a bad idea,
but the point is, we need help.
Yeah, well, unfortunately,
more than Andy can give.
What we need is someone
who's done this before.
Someone like Melinda Warren.
Okay, so what are we
supposed to do?
Reach back in time, grab her
and tell her that we need her help?
Yes. And I know exactly how to do it.
As long as you both don't mind
losing a little blood.
Am I the only one
having second thoughts?
- Yes.
- We don't really have other options.
But aren't we, like, raising the dead?
What if she's all...?
I read the Book of Shadows
very carefully.
She will come back as a real,
live person, flesh and blood.
She will have her powers too.
Our powers.
What's that for?
Well, the spell works by
blood calling blood.
So it shouldn't hurt much.
I lied. I lied.
Okay, come on, you guys, it'll be
just like that summer by the lake.
Remember? We made a blood oath
to be friends forever, not just sisters.
- I remember my finger got infected.
- Yeah, but the oath worked.
And I couldn't go in the water for three
weeks. Don't hand me that knife.
- How are you gonna cut yourself?
- I'm not.
- Piper?
- I can't stand the sight of blood.
Evil beings have blown up in our attic.
Disintegrated to dust right
before our very eyes.
And you're afraid of
a little drop of blood?
- Okay, just cut my finger.
- You do it.
Okay, here.
Melinda Warren, blood of our blood
Our great- great- great- great-
great- great- grandmother
We summon thee
Blessed be.
No, don't rip the dress
to make it fit me.
Oh, no, I'm not ripping it.
It's called a zipper. See?
A wise witch made this.
Yeah, and wise witches in this century
keep a low profile.
You slip this dress on,
you'll blend right in.
It's so odd to be here again,
to breathe and feel.
What sheep has wool so soft?
A synthetic one.
So did it take you long
to make the dress?
Make it? No, I bought it.
Oh, you must be rich.
Oh, she's got credit cards.
- Oh, wow, Melinda, you look great.
- Oh, thank you.
- How do you keep your legs warm?
- We drink coffee.
Oh, sorry, I let myself in,
and it didn't occur to me that...
Leo, oh, it's okay.
- This is...
- Our cousin Melinda.
- Nice to meet you.
- Leo's fixing our plumbing.
- What's that?
- We've got to go now.
To work with one's hands
is a great gift.
Well, I am a true labourer:
I earn that I eat, get that I wear.
Owe no man hate,
envy no man's happiness.
- Shakespeare.
Wasn't that fun? Okay, let's go now.
He is a treasure, Piper.
Why are you telling me?
Well, hello, Matthew.
We've got to do something
about his clothes.
Who are you?
How do you know me?
The short answer is,
we're the ones that gave the witch
the locket that had you freed.
I suppose you could say
that we're partners.
- I work alone.
- No, not in this century, you don't.
You're new in town,
new in time.
You need our help.
I see you've been shopping.
Find what you're looking for?
I want Melinda Warren's children.
Talk about your coincidences.
You see, we have the means
to find them for you,
and you have the ability
to take their powers.
Come.
What?
How'd you find me?
Prue Halliwell, the Halliwell attorney,
now here.
You are leaving a trail, my friend.
And that has got to stop.
Once Matthew had what he wanted,
he told the town council
I was a witch...
...and they arrested me.
Then they burned me at the stake.
Why didn't you save yourself?
Yeah, why didn't you use
your powers to escape?
I had a daughter.
Her name was Prudence.
She meant everything to me.
If I had used my powers,
I would've proven Matthew's charge.
And Prudence would've burned too.
No, I thought,
"I'll accept this
and pray some kind soul will take pity
on my daughter
and raise her in a safe home.
Only then can
the Warren line continue."
And it must've worked,
because here you are.
Why do Warren witches lose their
moms so early?
Phoebe, I can't change the past,
but I think I can protect the future.
How? Matthew is so strong,
and he has this wild power.
He can be at one place
and then another.
- In the blink of an eye?
- Exactly.
It's called blinking.
He must've copied it
from another witch.
I stripped him of all the powers
he copied from me,
but who knows what
other powers he still has.
What do you mean,
copied from you?
Matthew's gift is to copy
the power of a good witch
when it's used against him.
Then he definitely has mine.
Once he's copied a power,
it has no effect on him.
Should he gain all three powers,
he will be impossible to vanquish.
- So, what do we do?
- We curse him back into the locket.
And if we can't?
Are these pants
meant to be so tight?
Absolutely.
No wonder your men frown
all the time.
It's a wonder they can even walk.
- So is this right?
- Oh, yeah.
If it pleases you to look, look.
I wasn't looking...
...much.
Why the false modesty?
I don't understand.
Well, it's a very complex issue
these days.
I mean, there's political correctness,
sexual harassment.
Don't get me started.
What a strange time this is.
So open, yet so closed,
where even a warlock feels shame.
Hannah...
- What the devil?
- Rex, I told you I'd get him dressed.
Yeah. Ten minutes ago.
We've tried on many things.
She says it is difficult to choose.
Playtime's over, big boy.
You have a job to do.
Remember, he goes back
from whence he came
once his task is completed.
I can't believe I don't remember
all the ingredients.
It's been a while since
you cursed Matthew.
Yeah, like 300 years.
Whatever you don't remember
should be in the book.
The Book of Shadows.
Oh, my, it's gotten so thick.
- It wasn't always?
- No. No,
but obviously, each generation
of Warren witches
has added to it over the years
and has made it so.
Have you added anything?
Us? Are you kidding?
We're new at this.
We can't just make up our own spell...
Wait, can we?
All things in time, Phoebe.
The book will grow as you grow.
And sometimes you add to it,
sometimes it teaches you.
Oh, here's the curse.
Just start writing.
- No ink?
- No.
Grams must've added this one.
To increase patience.
I bet she used that spell a lot
raising us, huh?
We weren't
all troublemakers, Phoebe.
I was not a troublemaker.
I was just...
A pain.
- A free spirit.
- A handful.
A Warren.
It's a family trait.
So are the short tempers,
the great cheekbones,
the strong wills and,
of course, the powers.
All blessings.
All signs of where you came from.
This book is your connection.
And it began with me.
Well, let's make sure
it doesn't end with us.
We need to get going.
This is Prue.
You've already met.
This is Piper, and this is Phoebe.
Such marvellous paintings.
You cannot feel the brushstrokes.
Yeah.
Remind us to take you to the movies
when this is all over.
This is the address of Quake.
Piper works there.
May I suggest that you go there next
and take her power?
Hannah will drive you.
The curse is really simple,
as long as you have
the ingredients I need.
Phoebe can do the spices,
and I'll chop the scallions.
This is so cool.
We've never done a curse before.
Oh, I'm glad.
They're not to be taken lightly.
I just feel like there's so much
we could be learning or doing
if we had the right teacher.
Well, I'd savour my first gift before
I move on to the next one.
I see pictures. What's to savour?
No, but you see visions
of the future and the past
that'll allow you to protect
and to heal.
Did you hear that, Prue?
Prue, stop looking for Andy.
He should be long gone by now.
Yeah, he'll be back.
Probably with a warrant.
Yeah, like Andy
would ever arrest you.
So do we have everything?
Actually, there's a few herbs
we don't have,
but I can get them at the restaurant.
Yeah, the only problem is the feather
from a spotted owl.
- Is that a problem?
- Well, they're an endangered species.
Certain animals from your time
aren't really around anymore.
- Why?
- Deforestation, pollution...
It's a long story.
Do you think they have one
at the zoo?
What's a zoo?
In theory, it's this big
garden kind of place
where all the animals
are caged, and it's...
You know what?
I'll work on the feather.
Piper, can you handle the herbs?
Yeah, after I get to Quake, though
I might have a problem getting out
because I'm supposed to work
the night shift.
Well, I'll come with you and bring back
the stuff if you get hung up.
No, you can't leave the house.
You are the two Matthew needs.
Yeah, we'll be fine. How could
Matthew even know about Quake?
I have waited over 300 years
for my revenge.
As soon as Piper gets here,
I shall have it.
You go ahead into the kitchen.
I'm gonna cough on Martin
and tell him I'm highly contagious
- so I can go home.
- Love the plan.
Hey, Piper.
Did your sweetie find you?
- My what?
- That guy with the English accent.
He called earlier to see
if you were working today.
Now I have your power.
And I see Melinda's here. Good.
She will die at my hand.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
It was Matthew. He's gone.
But he copied my power.
All right, I found a spotted owl at the
museum where I used to work, stuffed.
But we only need one feather.
Good. Maybe that'll keep it down
to a misdemeanour.
- Look, I'll be back as soon as I can.
- Okay.
Come on, answer.
Hi, we're not home.
You know the drill.
Prue, pick up.
Phoebe?
- Are you guys there?
- Phoebe, I'm here.
Okay, you guys need
to be really careful.
- Phoebe?
- Matthew was here.
- He could be on his way.
- The machine is off.
Line went dead.
Matthew.
- We meet again.
- Yes.
And the sight of you
still makes me ill.
Funny, the fact that I can now
destroy your line forever
makes you so much
more appealing.
- You think I won't stop you?
- How?
You made your curse before,
and you still burned.
And yet I'm here now, aren't I?
You're nothing more
than a dead witch
watching over stupid girls
who are about to die themselves.
- You won't touch them.
- Too late.
I already have two of their powers.
I just need the third.
I believe her name is Piper.
- Unless you wanna freeze me.
- Go to hell, where you belong.
So that's why
they brought you back.
Isn't it?
You think you can curse me again.
Hell, I might just kill you now.
Go ahead.
- I've already given them the curse.
- You're lying.
Am I?
The one with the feather,
where is she now?
Where's Prue? Tell me!
- She's at...
- Yes?
The zoo.
Then that's where I'll kill her.
And then I'll come back
for the other two.
That way, you can watch them die...
...and I can watch you suffer.
And then...
...you'll be next.
You lost him.
We've had this conversation before,
Rex. Please stay out of my mind.
- Well, did he copy Piper's power?
- I have no idea.
Something happened in the restaurant,
though, because he just took off.
And so did they.
And why didn't you follow him?
I tried. Why don't you just follow them
right now?
Because I haven't mastered
that ability yet, unfortunately.
We need Matthew to provide us
with the sisters' powers.
Otherwise, we don't stand
a chance in hell.
Find him.
- Prue? Melinda?
- In here.
- Are you okay?
- It was Matthew, wasn't it?
Yes. But don't worry, he's gone.
He found us at the restaurant,
and he copied my power.
He said he was gonna kill you,
and I was...
It's all right, Phoebe.
But we've got to hurry
before Matthew gets back.
Did you get all the herbs?
Yeah, all we need now
is the feather.
Good. Prue's taken care of that.
How?
Andy, what are you doing here?
You're gonna have
to come with me, Prue.
- I found Matthew.
- I can see.
I need to find Prue and stop her.
No, you're supposed to be after
Piper and Phoebe.
- I don't under...
- I got the power of premonition.
With it, I saw the eldest
working on the curse.
- Help me find her.
- No.
No, no, this is no time
to be distracted.
You must stay on track.
You must obtain the last power.
But the curse will end me.
They brought Melinda Warren
back from the dead to do it.
- They did what?
- I will not go back to oblivion.
Listen.
Just listen to me.
If they're planning to send you back,
they'll have to cast the spell
at home.
So?
So Prue will have to return there
to do it.
Which is where you can thwart her...
...and then gain the power to freeze.
I've already tried.
They'd rather die than give me that.
Try again.
Now, for the last time, Prue,
why the feather?
I told you, I already had it
from before.
Before what?
You can say it, "Before breaking
and entering the museum,"
which, of course, you did
after you obstructed justice.
How did I obstruct justice?
Come on. Don't play dumb.
I know you too well.
You're in a lot of trouble here.
Trouble which I can't help you out of
unless you help me.
- Maybe I should talk to a lawyer.
- You really wanna go there?
You really want me to arrest you,
is that it?
What's the matter with you, Prue?
This isn't a game.
This is very serious.
Andy, please, you have to let me go.
No.
I can't look the other way
anymore, Prue.
This isn't just me.
It's Piper and Phoebe.
Just tell me what's going on.
For once in your life,
will you just trust me?
It's your only choice, Prue.
Andy, I'm sorry,
but I really have to go.
No, you can't. Prue...
Prue, get back here.
You don't know what you're doing!
We're ready now.
All we need is the feather.
And Prue. What's keeping her?
You don't think...?
No, she should be fine.
Matthew already copied her power.
Besides, I sent him to the zoo.
She's probably stuck in traffic.
When she returns, we'll add
the feather and seek out Matthew.
Do you think he's gonna
be hard to find?
Not at all.
I've waited too long
for this moment to hide.
This is our battle, Matthew.
Leave them alone.
I will have what I came for.
Your powers and your death.
Piper!
- Freeze me, witch.
- In your dreams.
I said, freeze me.
Save yourself.
No? Then save your sister.
- Phoebe!
- Save yourself.
Give me that feather.
Piper, now.
Outside of time, outside of gain
Know only sorrow, know only pain
- No!
- It's what you deserve!
This is not the end!
Yes, it is.
This is for eternity.
- I followed him, he failed.
- Bloody hell.
What do we do now?
I don't know.
We're gonna have to think
of something fast, though.
He's gonna be none too pleased
to learn that we have failed.
It wasn't a complete failure, right?
I mean, we outed them,
proved they're the Charmed Ones.
I mean, that has to count.
It'll buy us a little bit of time,
but precious little.
You should've listened to me.
We should've taken care
of them ourselves.
Yeah. You're right, Hannah.
We should've done.
You're gonna wake a judge up
at this hour? Are you nuts?
I'm getting an arrest warrant, Morris.
End of discussion.
Based on what?
Stealing a feather?
He'll bust your rank. You'll be cleaning
out parking meters for a living.
So I should just let it go, is that it?
What about evading arrest?
Am I supposed to let that go too?
Damn right.
Unless you wanna tell the judge
exactly how that little lady
got away from you.
By the way, exactly how did
she get away from you?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- Trudeau.
Take my advice. Let it go.
Don't embarrass yourself.
Leo? You're here.
Why are you here?
I thought I'd work on the plumbing
in the downstairs bathroom.
Oh, now's not really a good time.
We're getting our cousin Melinda
ready to go away.
Can you come back later?
Like, tomorrow?
- Sure. No problem.
- Leo?
Yeah?
Would you like to go out sometime?
With me, that is?
I'd love to.
- Give me a call.
- Okay.
- Who was it?
- It was Leo.
- Is he gone?
- We're perfectly safe.
Then let's begin.
- We can't take those back.
- Why not?
Because that means you're leaving.
- But I have to go.
- Why?
Why can't you stay here and have
the life that you should've had?
Because this isn't my time.
It's your time.
And Prue's and Piper's.
We don't mind sharing.
You three give me great joy.
I've seen the Charmed Ones.
Good witches,
women of strength and grace.
Tell me what you see.
I see the future.
Many more generations
of my beautiful daughters.
I see my dreams fulfilled.
Oh, thank you for that.
Melinda Warren
Blood of our blood, we release you
Blessed be, my daughters.
I love you.
I'm gonna miss her.
Me too.
We can always bring her back.