There aren't any pictures
of me growing up.
That seems impossible. I mean,
you weren't exactly camera-shy.
Yeah, well, neither
were you and Piper.
Or you and Grams or,
oh, you and Dad.
Oh, look, here's another one
of you and Piper.
Okay.
- Here's a picture of you and Grams.
- Oh, wasn't I cute?
Here's one of you and Mom.
I don't even remember that.
What was I, about 2 here?
She died on us a year later.
- Phoebe.
- Okay.
Hurry, I need a pen and paper.
Well, quick,
we don't have a lot of time.
I always wondered how
you got in the candy drawer.
Yeah, too bad all the candy's gone.
I thought it would be easier for us
if we just write him a note.
- Who him?
- You know, what's-his-name.
Grandma's little friend,
comes every year.
Same day, same time.
Says, you know, the flowers
are from a secret admirer,
when it's obvious he's the admirer.
Hi, come on in.
Hi.
- How are you?
- Flowers for Miss Penny Halliwell.
Every year. What a klutz.
At least this year I can freeze him
so I can spare myself the cleanup.
Why did you wanna
write him a note?
- To tell him Grams is dead.
- Oh, you're gonna break his heart.
Five chimes.
- Excuse me?
- The clock.
I only heard five chimes.
It's noon.
That means you froze me.
Which means you have
your powers at last.
I don't know what you're talking about,
but thanks for the flowers. Okay, bye.
Call me Nicholas.
Your mother did.
Oh, dear.
I had to appear to age
over the years,
otherwise you would've
been suspicious.
What?
You see, 24 years ago today,
your mother and I, we made a pact.
To spare her life, she gave up
your future powers to me.
She blessed this ring,
which gave me immunity
from your powers.
Immunity so that I could kill you
and take the powers
on for my own...
...to become invincible.
Our mother would never
give away our powers.
She didn't have much of a choice.
Your blood is boiling.
Soon your lungs will sear.
Your organs will overheat,
and death will come.
Why would Mom
make a deal like that?
More importantly,
what are we gonna do?
Wait, I think I found a spell
to unbind a bond.
You can't run from me!
- Okay, we have no choice.
- Okay, Phoebe, hurry.
The bond which was not to be done
Give us the power to see it undone
And turn back time
to whence it was begun
- It didn't work?
- Nothing happened.
Whose phone is that?
Not ours.
- Halliwell residence.
- You go.
- She goes.
I beg your pardon?
Well, Donna, I'm just hurt
that you would suspect
my little angels of such a thing.
- Grams?
- Prue.
Just a moment, Donna.
Prue, Piper. Girls,
don't run in the house.
Yes, yes.
- What did you see?
- The warlock?
No...
...us.
How do we know
we're back in time?
What if we just brought the past to us
accidentally? We've done it before.
Piper, look around.
What do you see?
- A messy attic, like always.
- No, not just like always.
You have a black light,
a typewriter,
eight-track tapes and a pet rock.
I mean, we got rid of this stuff
years ago, remember?
- And you saw us as kids?
- Yeah.
Oh, this can't be happening.
- I'm getting a migraine.
- Better not.
I don't think Advil's
been invented yet.
And apparently, neither has this spell.
It's not in here anywhere.
But we just cast it.
That's how we got back here.
Yeah, well, wherever here is,
it's before the spell was written.
So there's nothing in there about
how to get back to our own time?
Nothing.
Let me be the first to say
that we're screwed.
No, because at least we're alive.
I mean, if we'd stayed in our time,
Nicholas would've killed us.
We barely got away as it was.
Is. Will be.
You know, I've never
been good with tenses.
- What are we gonna do?
- Well, Grams is right downstairs.
Maybe we should just go
and tell her who we are.
And say what?
Hi, we're the ghosts
of grandchildren future?
Come on, even Grams
is gonna have trouble with that.
Plus, she has that heart condition.
Okay, fine, so we need another plan.
But first, we just need
to get out of the house.
You're talking too fast, I can't...
Patty, sweetheart, slow down.
- Patty?
- Mom.
What premonition? That's impossible.
You don't have premonitions.
Wait, I thought you said
Mom's power was to freeze time.
It is. Was.
You know what I mean.
Maybe you should go see a doctor.
I don't need to go
to the doctor, Mom.
Piper.
She's talking to Mom.
I can't explain it either, Mom.
It just happened.
I felt a twinge in my stomach
and then, bam, I saw it.
- Saw what?
- Three women, warlocks.
And one of them was taking Prue.
Do you think that's
really Mom's voice?
- Yes.
- Are you still nauseous?
Why don't you come home?
I can't, and it was not a daydream.
Three warlocks? She can't be
talking about us, can she?
Okay, bye.
Okay, let's just get out of here.
Prudence, Piper.
No fair, using magic.
Wait, we had powers back then?
Oh, this is freaky.
- Hey.
- Hi.
You got one too.
Come here.
How many times
have I told you girls...?
Grams, we can explain.
Warlocks, begone.
Oh, God, let's go.
Grams definitely
had her power down.
She is one scary witch.
I don't remember having
powers at that age, do you?
No, I thought that we got them
for the first time last year.
Apparently not.
We must have lost them
before we could even
remember having them.
Yeah, how weird was that,
seeing us as kids? Totally bizarre.
Mom is barely pregnant with me.
March 24th, 1975.
That's the day that Mom
made the pact with Nicholas.
So maybe that's why the spell
sent us back here, to stop the pact.
Which means it could be the only
way for us to get back to our time.
We've gotta go see Mom
and warn her about Nicholas.
Yeah, but we have to do a better job
of convincing Mom than we did Grams.
This time we have to
use our powers.
The problem is she's on
the lookout for three warlocks now.
So then maybe only two of us
should approach her, just in case.
Well, since I don't
have any powers to show Mom,
I think it should be you two.
And I'll just stand outside
and watch for Nicholas.
That doesn't seem fair to you,
Phoebe, not being able to see Mom.
I know, it's not. But I got
over that a long time ago.
I don't need to see her now.
Really, it's okay.
We better get going, though,
before we miss her.
Scary.
Buddy's has not changed a bit.
Wouldn't?
Didn't?
Give it up, I know what you mean.
I don't see Mom anywhere, do you?
No.
Prue.
Mom.
She's so beautiful.
Yeah, she is.
I don't remember her working here.
Well, yeah. I mean, with Dad gone,
she had to pay the bills somehow.
I remember she used
to come home late at night
and she would kiss me and she
always smelled like burgers.
You're lucky, you have
a lot more memories than I do.
Well, at least you have some.
I mean, poor Phoebe,
she doesn't have any.
Here she comes.
What do we do
if she recognizes us?
You freeze the place, and when
she sees that we don't freeze either,
then she'll believe us
when we tell her who we are.
- Okay. How do I look?
- Great.
Ready to order?
Take your time, I'll come back.
No, wait! We're ready,
aren't we, Prue?
Prunes.
Prunes. She wants to know
if you have any prunes.
Prunes? Sure.
Yeah, I think so.
I just started here.
- I'll go check.
- No.
She can order something else.
Have we met before?
You look familiar.
Yeah, so do you.
Now.
- What's the matter?
- It's not working.
You try.
Okay, how is that possible?
- Patty, phone.
- Okay, thanks.
I'll be back.
Wait. We know you're pregnant.
What?
This is gonna sound really weird,
but we're actually your...
Cousins...
...from out of town.
- Right, cousins.
And we... We need to tell you
something really important
about the baby
that you're carrying, sort of.
Not that this is any of your business,
but I can't get pregnant anymore.
Medically impossible.
Excuse me.
I panicked.
I thought, you know,
close family would know
that she's pregnant.
Yeah, well,
not only does she not know
that she's pregnant,
but she doesn't even think
that she can get pregnant.
But we got bigger problems.
We have no powers, which means
we have no way of stopping Nicholas.
Yeah, how do we not have powers?
I mean, little Prue and little Piper,
they have powers.
I don't know,
maybe only one set of us
can have powers at the same time,
in the same time.
Thank you, Mr Spock.
I was working, that's why
I couldn't take your call.
The premonition you had, did you see
what the warlocks look like?
The warlocks?
No, I didn't see their faces. Why?
I'll tell you why: Because I saw them.
All three of them, here.
And one of them
had a hold of Prudence.
- Are the girls okay?
- For now, thanks to me.
I'm coming right home.
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- Oh, no. It's totally my fault.
So silly.
I'm such a klutz sometimes.
Really?
- So am I.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
- Crackers?
- Upset stomach.
You know, you shouldn't
be smoking these now.
It's bad for your upset stomach.
You're very sweet.
Thanks. I gotta go.
- So soon?
- Excuse me?
- Is everything all right?
- Yeah, thanks, officer.
Oh, my God. Nicholas.
I'm late. Thanks again. Goodbye.
Excuse me,
- how do you get to Berkeley?
- Get out of my way.
- Phoebe, what are you doing?
- Nicholas is here.
What? Where?
Run.
- Was Nicholas wearing his ring?
- I don't know. I don't think so.
Good thing you were there, Pheebs.
That was probably when Nicholas
was gonna make his move on Mom.
No, I don't think so. Otherwise,
we'd be back in our own time by now.
- Hey, are you all right?
- Yeah.
It's just, seeing Mom
for the first time and talking to her,
I just didn't expect to feel so...
Feel what? Good?
No.
Overwhelmed.
Well, Mom's car is here.
At least we know where she is.
Question is, how do we get to her?
Grams must've told her about us.
She probably thinks
that we're the warlocks.
Our only option is to wait
for Nicholas to show.
But what are we gonna do
without our powers?
Well, technically
you still have your powers.
If you count
little Prue and little Piper.
We need powers,
and they have them.
Come on.
Coast is clear.
What if Grams catches us?
She'll kill us before Nicholas
has the chance.
She won't catch us. Observe.
You said yourself the girls are safe
with you. Besides, I want to go.
You are making a big mistake, Patty.
Victor is not coming back.
- How did you...?
- Heating duct to upstairs.
I used to listen
to you guys for hours.
Especially when you used to sneak
Andy to your bedroom in high school.
Okay, you stay here
and keep tabs on them.
We're gonna try
and go find the little girls.
- That's my doll.
- You gave it to me.
- No, I didn't, you stole it.
- It's true, you did steal it.
- I did not.
- Yes, you did.
Hey, that's not fair.
You came back.
Yes, we did. And we're
gonna keep it a secret, right?
- Okay.
- You're pretty.
- Oh, so are you.
Give me a break.
Grams said you're bad people.
No, no, no. We're good people.
We're just like you.
Yeah, we're family.
Victor sent me a note, asked me
to stop by his hotel after my shift.
- Dad?
- It was doomed from the start.
You never even took his last name.
- You wouldn't let me.
- Well, that's beside the point.
Why can't you just
wear your uniform to see him?
Because I don't want him
to know I'm a waitress.
Look, it can't hurt to talk, right?
Well, let him go, I say.
If husbands were
supposed to stay married,
God would've made them live longer.
- Mother.
- What?
Grams.
We're not supposed
to go places with strangers.
Yes, but we're not strangers, Prue.
You're safe with us. And I know
that you know in your heart
- that you can trust us.
- If you're really family, prove it.
Prove it? How the hell
are we supposed to do that?
Piper.
Piper?
Your name's Piper too?
Yeah.
And not only do we have
the same name,
but we have the same secrets.
Okay, follow me. Come on.
- Freeze!
- No, wait...
I'm telling Mom. You're not
supposed to freeze people.
But he said to.
Prue, Piper, Mom's coming down.
Fine, if you must go, go.
I can't stop you.
I also can't promise I won't
teach the girls a new spell
while you're gone.
Can't you just bake cookies with them,
like all the other grandmothers?
The recipes they learn from me
don't come from Betty Crocker, dear.
Bye, girls. Love you.
- Where did you come from?
- Yeah, that's a good question.
Don't ask. Okay, we gotta go fast.
- Mom just left and Grams is...
- Prudence? Piper?
Coming.
- I wanna go too.
- No, Andy, you have to stay here.
- No!
- Okay, we got it, we got it.
- Little Andy Trudeau is so cute.
- All right, ready?
Freeze him.
Okay, cool. Come on.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Okay, maybe that's why
Andy's so suspicious of us.
Okay, Grams keeps the keys
in the same spot? Yes, good.
Oh, Andy, did Piper
freeze you again?
You poor dear.
You won't remember a thing.
- Do you know where the girls went?
- I think the strange ladies took them.
Okay, girls. When we see
a bad guy, what do we do?
- She's gonna cry.
- Am not. I'm gonna freeze him.
And then I'm going to move him.
Okay, then we'll take care
of him and then we will all...
- Run like the wind.
Exactly. All right,
let's give it a try. Ready?
Yes.
Can we do it again?
Yes, yes.
Practice makes perfect. Okay.
Go try it.
These girls have major juice.
They have control, they can aim.
Yeah, well, they've had their powers
a lot longer than we have.
I mean, did. I think.
What do you think happened
to our powers when we were kids?
Well, we lost a lot growing up.
Somehow, we must have
lost them too.
Okay, I finally found a payphone.
Mom is at work until 5
and Nicholas is on duty till 6.
Good, at least we know where he is.
The girls are ready.
Well, I'm not.
Why not?
Mom died before I could grab onto
enough to keep her alive in my head.
And now she's here alive,
pregnant with me.
If we stop Nicholas, we have
to go back to our own time.
And there's no Mom there.
Well, we don't
have a choice, Phoebe.
Ladies, is this your car?
Come in.
Victor?
Get off me!
Wouldn't have you freezing me, Patty.
That would ruin everything.
- You.
- Call me Nicholas.
- Where's Victor?
- Not here.
Bait for the hook.
Your blood is boiling.
And then, death will come.
What do you want?
What does any warlock want?
I want your power, Patty.
At least, that's what I wanted at first.
Until I realized you're
the mother of the Charmed Ones.
No. No, you're mistaken.
- I only have two children.
- Oh, but there will be a third child.
Where did that premonition
of yours come from, Patty,
if not from the unborn
child inside you?
I tapped your phone.
I heard you and the old witch
talking about it.
I saw three warlocks. Women.
I saw them too, at the diner.
Rivals, perhaps.
I got to you first.
Oh, please.
I beg you.
Don't hurt them.
There is another option, Patty.
I can't believe we got arrested
for kidnapping ourselves.
Yeah, well, it should make
for a pretty interesting defence.
You think this is funny?
Prue, we're not just stuck in jail,
we're stuck in the past.
Yes, I know, Piper,
I've been following.
- Bright side?
- I dare you.
Well, maybe we can
get to know Mom better.
Or in my case, finally.
I mean, if we really are stuck here,
we might as well
take advantage of it, right?
Maybe we can even keep her
from dying young this time.
Five minutes, ma'am.
How did you know I was pregnant?
Who are you people?
Your daughters.
Okay, I bailed you out.
You just better not be warlocks.
Well, we wouldn't have needed
you to bail us out if we were.
I've seen some magic in my life,
but this is a miracle.
More than you know, Mom.
Where are the little ones?
Home with Grams.
I called her before I came. That's how
I found out you'd been arrested.
Did you tell her about us?
No. I didn't know what to say.
I didn't know who you were myself.
You're all so beautiful.
More than I ever would've imagined.
Phoebe.
Talk about miracles.
I must've named you
after my favourite aunt.
But if you don't like the name,
I can always change it.
No, I love it.
Mom,
we cast a spell to come
back in time to help you.
- To stop you.
- To stop me from what?
From making a pact
with a warlock named Nicholas.
Then you're too late.
What?
I thought I was going
to see Victor, your father.
But it turned out to be a trap.
Nicholas.
He tried to kill me.
Phoebe too.
I had to give him immunity to your
powers in exchange for your lives.
I'd rather love you
as mortal daughters...
...than have to mourn you
as dead witches.
But he's gonna kill us
anyway to get our powers.
No, not until Phoebe's born
and all your powers are complete.
I bought us some time in the hopes
that Grams could help us.
Oh, she's going to be
so thrilled when she sees you.
The Charmed Ones.
- Where was I born?
- Mom.
I'm still not convinced
that they're not warlocks.
We have a pact to undo.
We should be looking for a spell.
Boston.
In a hotel room, breech.
What was my husband's name?
Which husband?
- Who's Melinda Warren?
- The beginning of our family line.
She gave us our powers,
our destiny.
What's the secret ingredient
in my blueberry cobbler?
Honey and a splash of rum.
What's IBM selling at in your time?
- Mom.
- What?
- This is not the time for personal gain.
- You're right.
If they could just nod their heads.
Okay, forget it.
Well, look at you.
The three of you.
Oh, Patty. I always knew that
I would deliver the Charmed Ones.
Once removed, of course.
Prue.
Piper.
- And...
- Phoebe.
Oh, another P.
- What a surprise.
- About the pact.
We must keep the girls safe
until we can reverse it.
- I'll have to bind their powers.
- Bind our powers?
Strip them from the young ones
so Nicholas can't get ahold of them.
It doesn't have to be done right away.
As soon as Phoebe's born,
I'll cast a spell and suspend their...
Your powers.
Yeah, but that's exactly
what you did.
Or, do.
- Will do. You know what I mean.
- That explains
why we don't remember having
our powers when we were younger.
What do you mean?
Well, how old were you
when you got your powers back?
- We just got them.
- What?
I unbound your powers
without having broken the pact?
Why would I do that?
I mean, unless I died, which,
of course, would automatically...
Unbind your powers.
Guess I'm not going to make it
to the next millennium, huh?
- Speaking of that, Mom...
- No.
We mustn't know about the future.
You came back here
for one reason, to break the pact.
You mustn't tamper with
anything else. It's much too risky.
Heaven knows what damage
you've done by coming back here.
We haven't done anything. We
missed our chance to stop the pact.
And there's a reason for that.
Destiny always gets its own way.
It's not as easy to change
the past as you might think.
And if you do it incorrectly,
everything will change.
The evil that you vanquished,
the good that you've done,
none of it may have ever happened.
Well, we have to change this. We can't
go back and just let him kill us.
The only way to vanquish him
in your time
would be for me to unbless the ring
and take away its immunity.
It's in a drawer in his hotel room.
Okay, let's go to Nicholas'
hotel room and steal back the ring.
- Hopefully it'll be there.
- It's too dangerous.
You don't have powers.
- I'll go.
- No.
If something happened to you, future
history could be changed forever,
just like Grams said. We have to go.
Well, I'm glad to see that you
finally learned to listen to me.
You better hurry. In the meantime,
I'll write a new spell
that will get you back
to your own time.
Wait, you can... You can do that?
You can send us home?
We're witches, dear.
We can do anything.
I wish that were true.
Okay, we need to go.
Be careful.
Why am I not surprised
that you know how to do this?
Let's just hope Nicholas isn't inside.
The concierge says he's not,
and Piper's out front watching for him.
Mom said it's in a drawer.
Found it.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
We gotta get it back to Mom.
We have the ring. Here it is.
- Okay, now what?
- Go back to where you belong.
I'll unbless the ring and get it back
before Nicholas finds it missing.
Now, remember,
there is no time to lose.
You will return at the exact moment
you left. Nicholas will be there.
Hopefully without immunity
to our powers.
We'll be ready. Phoebe?
Okay, I'm coming.
I love you, Mom.
I'm never gonna learn
to like lima beans, Grams,
but thanks for everything else.
You're going to be
a handful, aren't you?
You'll learn to love me.
Bye, Phoebe.
I'm gonna miss you.
A time for everything
And to everything its place
Return what has been moved
through time and space
Let me help.
A time for everything
And to everything its place
Return what has been moved
through time and space
You did well, Patty.
Oh, they're fabulous.
I just hope they're safe.
- What happened?
- Where did you go?
We didn't go anywhere.
We were just standing here,
- and the next thing we knew...
- We were just standing here.
I told you to use poplar buds.
It's a perfectly good spell.
I mean, it moved them through time.
Yeah, ten seconds.
It's not the spell. Must be
the power behind the spell.
- There's not enough power.
- Maybe we need the power of three.
The only problem is
it doesn't exist yet.
Nothing.
Maybe this is our destiny.
Not for the Charmed Ones.
We don't exist yet.
- Yes. Yes, you do.
- No, not with powers.
Yes, little Prue and Piper
have their powers.
And Phoebe gave me a premonition,
so she must have hers.
If we can teach the girls the chant,
maybe the three of us
can get you back to your time.
The power of three. It's worth a try.
Where are you witches?
Where's my ring?
- Nicholas.
- You and Piper get the girls.
We'll fend him off.
Come on, Phoebe.
Oh, Grandma,
don't get too close, his power.
- I know, I know.
- We can't risk you being hurt.
Go help Mom start the spell.
Phoebe and I will
take care of him. Come on.
We're gonna play a little game, okay?
Now, give me your hands.
- Okay, hurry.
- Now, repeat after me.
A time for everything
And to everything its place
Return what has been moved
through time and space
A time for everything
And to everything its place
Return what has been moved
through time and space
- All right, we don't have much time.
- What about his ring?
Don't worry about the ring now.
Let's just get you back.
Well, but it is unblessed, right?
Yes, but there wasn't time to test it.
- Then how will we know if it works?
- You won't. Not until you get back.
And since time will pick up right
where it left off, he won't know either.
Goodbye, girls. Be good, darlings.
A time for everything
And to everything its place
Return what has been moved
through time and space
It worked. We're back.
Hurry.
Time's up.
All right, the ring's unblessed.
- Phoebe, find anything?
- The Nicholas Must Die spell.
- That wasn't there before.
- Maybe it's Grams' way of saying
welcome back, or front.
"Spell pouch included
at no extra charge."
Okay, okay.
Lavender, mimosa
- Holy thistle
- Oh, dear.
Cleanse this evil from our midst
Scatter its cells throughout time
Let this Nick no more exist
I'm really glad I never
got on Grams' bad side.
Right.
I can't stop thinking about Mom.
How I lost her and then
I found her again.
I'm just glad that you
finally have memories of her.
What?
I'm supposed to throw out flowers
because they came from a creep?
If that was the rule, we'd never
have flowers in this house.
Well, but they didn't
just come from a creep.
They came from a warlock
who tried to kill us.
Still, if it weren't for him, I probably
would've never gotten to know Mom.
We all wanted
to save Mom, Pheebs,
but both Mom and Grams
said we can't change destiny.
I know, but I still wrote
her a note anyway.
- You did?
- Yes, I wrote her a note
telling her to stay away from water
on the day that she died.
And then I put it in
the Book of Shadows.
- I can't believe you did that.
- You don't understand.
Every time I've made a wish,
I've wished for time with Mom.
And I believed in my heart
that someday,
somehow,
that wish would come true.
And when it finally did,
I didn't wanna let her go.
You know, but then I realized
that I had to let her go.
So I took the note out
and I put it in my pocket.
Maturity sucks, doesn't it?
But still, faith has its rewards.
It's a pretty good one of us,
but once again,
not a great one of you, Pheebs.
Are you kidding?
That is the best picture
of me I've ever taken.