Previously on
"Grey's Anatomy"...
Derek's married.
You waited two
months to tell me,
and I had to find out by her
showing up and telling me herself.
You had brain surgery
and didn't tell me?
- You called my wife?
- You called mine.
- It's not like we're divorced.
- Practically divorced.
- You've had counseling?
- We had adultery. That was enough.
- I think it's best to make a clean break.
- Oh, you're ending this.
I'm pregnant.
Have you even bothered to
tell Burke about the baby?
The clinic wouldn't let me
confm my appointment unless I
designated an emergency
contact person.
- You're my person.
- I am?
I heard your mother
was leaving mayo.
She goin' back with the U.N.?
She's, uh, taking time off.
What's your name?
It's me, mom, Meredith.
Oh, you are stupid.
Oh, god.
You're a stupid, evil sadist,
- and I wanna kill you!
- Endorphins are good.
Endorphins are mood elevators.
- This is supposed to make us feel better.
- Oh, god. Do you feel better?
I'm stupid.
Slutty mistress.
Pregnant whore.
Sleeping with our bosses
was a great idea.
- You know what's ruined for me?
- Oh.
Ferry boats.
I used to love ferry boats.
And Derek's got a
thing for ferry boats.
- Now every time I see a freakin' ferry boat--
- You know what's ruined for me?
Coronary artery bypass
grafts and aortic aneurysms.
God, I used to love
aortic aneurysms.
Surgeons are control freaks.
With a scalpel in your hand--
- Oh, crap.
- You feel unstoppable.
There's no fear,
there's no pain.
- Have you cried yet?
- Hello.
You're 10 feet tall
and bulletproof.
Do you think we'd feel
better if we cry?
You know, just like,
let it out?
Probably, yeah.
And then you leave the O.R--
You wanna cry now?
- No.
- Okay, let's--let's jog.
And all that perfection,
all that beautiful control
just falls to crap.
What is she doing?
She's hanging out with Alex.
Why?
I don't know.
- I think--think they, uh, might be friends.
- Do another one.
Make the lambs stop screaming.
You guys are wrong about him,
all right?
Once you get to know him,
he's really sweet.
- He's Alex.
- Punk-ass.
Hey, Grey, Izzie was telling me you have
tapes of your mom performing surgery.
I'd kill to see the
Ellis Grey in action.
Hey, you know what?
Maybe you can come over tonight and
we can all watch it together, right?
Oh, yeah,
if this were a hell dimension.
Run away, pig boy.
- Do you have a thing for Alex?
- No.
I don't.
Are we saving lives or
having a tea party?
Walk faster, people.
Ahem.
Nice hat.
Shut up.
What are you doin' here?
- I'm going back to work
- You're not cleared for surgery.
Leave me alone.
I've been sittin' home for a week,
watching Oprah give away things on tv.
Oprah, Derek.
You clear me now,
or I'll hurt you.
If you want me to
clear you so soon,
you should've thought of that before you
gave chief to Burke and invited Satan to Seattle.
Satan?
Good morning.
Richard, like the hat.
Satan speaks.
Actually, I prefer to be called
ruler of all that is evil,
- but I will answer to Satan.
- What is she still doing here?
I asked her to stay.
We have a pediatric surgery
attending on maternity leave.
Actually, I could
use you on a consult.
Will you meet me
up there, Derek?
- Yeah, fine.
- See you, Richard.
Nice lady.
I'm not clearing
you for surgery.
Fine, I can catch
up on my paperwork.
Mr. Gaston is scheduled for a resection
non-small cell carcinoma today.
He did well overnight,
has remained afebrile.
He's had a dose of
ceftriaxone this morning.
His pre-op labs
are unremarkable.
His chest x-rays are
unchanged from previous.
I own a couple of
dry cleaning stores.
I never believed what they said
about inhaling the chemicals, but--
We're gonna do everything
we can for you, Mr. Gaston.
Did oncology see him yet?
They're waiting for
the surgical path.
Thank you, Dr. Yang.
You're welcome, Dr. Burke.
I know, and I just think you should
still tell him about the baby because
at least he should have the
responsibility of having to pay.
No! Look, he will never know.
It's over.
Once this pregnancy's taken care of, Burke won't even
be a blip on my radar. He'll be a smudge.
Right.
You know, Meredith,
leave the sarcasm up to me.
Really. It doesn't suit you.
Kelly Roche, 23 years old, in for a scheduled E.T.S.
for treatment of erythrophobia with hyperpyrexia.
Erythrophobia?
Blushing.
You have any questions
about the procedure?
Doctor--
Dr. Shepherd explained everything.
He was very...
helpful.
He gave me some litera--
Sorry.
Don't be. Half the patients that come
through here have the hots for Shepherd.
Dr. Karev.
What?
It's true.
Hey.
- Why do you do that?
- What?
Act like an ass when everybody but me is
around. They hate you enough as it is.
So? What?
Hey, there's a new surgical case coming
up from the pit, likely diverticulitis.
Let's go.
Watch it. Hands off me.
I could report you to the chief
and you'd be out on your ass!
- Where is the chief?!
- Patient's name is, um--
Where is the chief?
You're all amateurs!
Complaining of intermittent cramping,
pain and diarrhea.
Also suffers from--
Amateurs!
- Alzheimer's.
- The patient's name?
Um-- Yang,
the patient's name?
What the hell are
you doing here?
Haven't I told you?
How many times have I told you
not to bother me when'm at work?!
Ellis Grey.
- Meredith's mother.
- You're amateurs! You're amateurs!
Nobody knows where they
might end up nobody knows
Oh, oh
Suppose you'll never know
Meredith, are you okay--
Dr. Karev, stick with the E.T.S.
case. And, Alex,
her blushing impulse--
not a toy for you to play with or a
button for you to push, understood?
Hey, Meredith, you know, um, my
great-grandmother, she died with Alzheimer's.
My god.
- Why would you say that?
- Look, I'm just tryin' to help.
Izzie, the Dr. Shepherds need
an intern up in the N.I.C.U.
Wait, both of them, together?
And me, by myself,
- with the two married people who hate each other?
- Go.
- Cristina, you're on the thoracotomy.
- Oh, with Burke?
- Oh, can I have the hateful married couple instead?
- Okay, I'm sorry.
I thought I was your resident,
not your hostess.
I assign, you take.
Is that a problem?
Is there some reason why it's inconvenient for you
to spend the day in the O.R. learning from Dr. Burke?
No, I'm very happy to be working
with Dr. Burke. Thank you very much.
George, take care of Dr. Grey.
Yes. Thank you.
She needs a friend right now--
Oh, you mean Ellis the--
mother.
Are you able to work today?
Yes, I'm fine.
'Cause I would understand it if
you wanted to be with your--
No.
My mother and i don't
have the easiest--
it's just better
if I'm working.
Okay.
You're on scut.
Excuse me?
While we take care of your mother,
you can catch up on charting,
run samples to the lab,
go over--
I told you, I'm fine.
Yeah, and I appreciate
that you're fine.
But I have to anticipate a certain
level of distraction from you today,
even in the face of
all that fineness.
So scut, now.
Where's the mother?
Gone.
She stuck around long enough to get
the kid strung out, and then took off.
Nice, huh?
Addison--
Derek, I know it's a long shot.
I know that.
You told me that you had a
newborn with an invasive mass.
You failed to mention she's premature,
underweight and addicted to narcotics.
There is no way that this
baby is gonna survive--
- spinal surgery.
- You don't know that.
Even if she does, she's a mess.
Look at her, she's got meningitis seizures.
She's just gonna live a short and painful life.
- You don't know that.
- It is my job to know that.
- You're not god, Derek.
- Excuse me?
- I'm sorry, honey, but you're not. You don't get to just decide--
- Did you just call me "honey"?
Don't call me honey.
Fine. You're not god,
Dr. Shepherd.
Look, if a patient has any chance at
survival, which I think she does,
- then you have a responsibility--
- Don't talk to me about responsibility.
- You took an oath, Derek.
- Oh, and don't you dare talk to me about oaths.
Derek, I messed up.
People mess up.
- You slept with my best friend in my favorite sheets.
- The flannel sheets?
- You hate the flannel sheets.
- No, I loved those sheets.
- You like the italian sheets with the paisleys.
- I did.
- Would you just stop talking about the sheets?
- Fine.
I'm sorry. I'm just gonna go.
I'll go check on the labs.
- Addison, don't do that.
- Derek, look, she's a fighter.
- Look how far she's come already.
- Don't get attached, don't get involved.
Just don't make her life more
painful than it already is.
Derek, please.
She has nobody.
She needs someone
to fight for her.
She's too far gone.
We have to let her go.
Let her go in peace.
Fine, Derek. Walk away.
It's what you do best.
I've enjoyed the opportunity to show you
my capabilities in this arena, however brief.
Stop fishing, Preston.
You did a good job.
But I'm back now, and I don't plan
on going anywhere anytime soon.
I am glad that you're back.
I'm just hiding my
joy deep down inside.
And, uh, chief--
the hat--
it's a little pimped out.
Welcome back, chief.
It's good to be back, Dr. Grey.
What can I do for you?
It's my mother, sir.
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you sooner.
I know you two are close,
but she made me promise.
She seems to be reliving the heyday
of her residency a lot these days.
And I just thought maybe if you
could stop by and say hello,
it would mean a lot to her.
Oh, of--of course.
Do you need a day off or a--
Oh, no. I'm fine.
Yeah.
Okay.
- If you could just hold--
- I'm in the middle of my workday, Thatch.
Thatch? No, I'm Dr. O'Malley.
I'm-- okay.
I just need to check your--
Darling, I'm not in the
mood to play doctor now.
Hands off. I'm busy.
George.
Damn it, Thatch, I mean it. No!
She's allergic to penicillin.
- Yeah? Yeah. It said in her chart.
- Oh.
You just have to be patient.
Okay. Do you, um, who's Thatch?
My dad Thatcher.
What did she-- is she--
is she talking about him?
Um, yeah.
She never talks about him.
- Are you all right?
- No. Yeah, yeah.
I'm good.
Um-- I can't be here.
Of course.
I mean, we're good here.
- Okay.
- We're great.
Dr. Shepherd.
Meredith.
I heard. Is it true?
Yeah. Secret's out.
- Dr. Shepherd, I--
- You don't have to call me Dr. Shepherd.
Dr. Shepherd,
I want in on a surgical case.
I can't just do
nothing all day.
And you owe me this.
And I never ask you for
anything like this, so--
I have an E.T.S.
this afternoon.
You'll scrub in.
You're late.
I apologize.
I'm just starting to dissect around Mr.
Gaston's tumor.
I've almost got visualization.
Hey, Kelly.
Dr. Shep--
Dr. Shepherd.
God. Sorry.
Damn it.
- Kelly.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
This might be the last time
that that ever happens.
How are her labs?
H and h are stable,
chest x-rays show no acute process.
Good.
- You ready to go?
- Are you kidding? I've been ready since the third grade.
Did you read the
literature I gave you?
You understand the
possible side effects?
Compensatory sweating of the back,
abdomen, thighs and legs,
possible gustatory sweating.
Horner's syndrome occurs in
less than 1% of patients.
Brachial plexus injury, pneumothorax
and hemothorax are highly unlikely,
but possible side
effects of the surgery.
You did your homework.
Take her to pre-op.
I'll alert the O.R.
Do you know what all
those words mean?
Brachial plexus injury could
cause paralysis of the arms.
Pneumothorax is
a collapsed lung.
I know.
Are you sure you want to risk all of
that over a little bit of blushing?
Is that--
what you think this is,
a little bit of blushing?
Just a
schoolgirl embarrassment?
Look, you both saw what
happened when Dr. Shep--
when Dr. Shepherd was here.
What did you think?
Well, I thought you liked him.
I do, but you think I want a--
a roomful of doctors
to know about it?
It's not like we're gonna--
It's not just you guys.
It's not just this once.
It happens--
every time I have a feeling
for anyone in my life.
I can't get mad, I can't--
be happy,
I can't feel anything without
the whole world knowing.
I can't have a secret.
Can you--
imagine living that
way your entire life?
Get away from me,
you insipid little man!
- Dr. Grey, calm down.
- Get out of here! Get out of my room!
- Please calm down.
- What can I do?
Please get some haloperidol.
Don't give me that look.
That sad little,
soulful little puppy routine.
I know it by heart,
Thatch, and I'm over it.
I don't wanna hear about your day or your
students or your pathetic little research grants.
My--
my work is what counts!
It's what pays for this house.
It pays for--
it pays for you
and it pays for--
it pays for Meredith and
for your precious lifestyle.
So why don't you just leave
me alone and let me do it?!
Meredith may think she needs you,
but I sure as hell don't.
- Dr. Grey.
- Here it is.
Are you okay?
That's something I'm
supposed to be asking you.
O'Malley.
- I understand that you're working on Ellis Grey.
- Yes, sir. I'm tryin' my best.
All right, keep me informed of her
progress and take good care of her.
She's an old friend of mine.
Really? Because, actually,
I could use some help.
Could--could you
help me examine her?
Uh, um,
I'm just a little busy just now.
- Gotta run.
- Right, okay.
It's just that she seems to think I'm
her ex-husband and she won't let me touch her.
Funny. You--you do look
a bit like Thatcher.
I look like Meredith's dad?
Um, just take good
care of her, George.
But I look like her dad?
I need help.
Hey.
- Hey, wait, wait, wait.
- What?
You have an eyelash.
Make a wish and blow it away.
Hey, nurse ratched, there's a
dead guy stinkin' up room 4125.
Do somethin' before he rots.
See? That is exactly
what I'm talking about.
Why are you so afraid of showing people
that you're a decent human being?
Remember when he wallpapered the hospital
with pictures of you in your underwear?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
That was before I knew you.
- Thanks, man. Very helpful.
- I need you to help me do an exam on Meredith's mom.
Oh, a standard exam.
You did go to med school, right?
She thinks I'm her ex-husband.
She won't let me.
- Dr. Grey.
- Oh, damn it, Thatcher, I'm at work.
I've already told you. I'm too busy to
deal with you. Now no more cartoons.
She means interruptions.
No more interruptions, Thatch.
You heard the doctor.
Hi, I'm--I'm Dr. Karev.
Pleased to meet you, Dr. Grey.
I've always admired your work.
So you're familiar with the
laparoscopic Grey method?
Oh, I studied footage of
the operation you pioneered.
You're something else.
Good. Well, then,
we're wasting time.
Let's scrub in.
Well, Dr. Grey, I'm gonna need to do
a short exam before you start surgery.
I know. New hospital policy.
Annoying bureaucrats.
Make it quick.
Why don't you wait
outside, Thatcher?
I can take it from here.
Take a deep breath.
She's got a good grip.
Yeah.
I don't think I--
it doesn't look good.
She's got a resistant
strain of pneumococcus.
The antibiotics aren't working.
You may wanna get yourself reassigned,
Dr. Stevens.
I don't think we'll
be operating today.
So do you think Dr.
Shepherd was right?
It's just too far gone.
She does have a good grip.
The tumor has infiltrated
the pericardium.
Yang.
Yang?
What? Sorry.
Is my surgery interfering
with your daydreaming?
No.
Sorry.
- You have a problem?
- No.
- You have a mocha latte?
Then go away.
Actually, I need
a new assignment.
The Shepherds' preemie
case is non-surgical.
Non-surgical?
Non-operable.
That sucks.
Yeah.
Did you know about Ellis Grey?
Did Meredith tell you?
No.
It's just you think--
you think you know someone,
you know who they are,
you share a house and make
wishes on eyelashes with them.
And we don't know each other.
None of us.
We're just a bunch of interns who
work together. There's nothin' there.
There is an arrhythmia when
I press down on the tumor.
That is a sign of what, Yang?
Um--
uh, it's a sign of-- it's a s--
it's a sign that the tumor has
infiltrated the pericardium.
Possibilities?
I-I'm sorry.
- I--
- Do your homework, Yang.
It could be causing a tear in
the outer muscle of the heart.
So he's got a broken heart?
Cristina.
Somebody help her.
Don't just stand there, damn it.
Get a gurney in here!
Cristina.
We got it, Dr.
Burke. We got it.
All right, talk to me.
What do we know? What do we know?
- Talk to me, Stevens.
- I don't know.
- Come on, people, let's move.
- Cristina, what hurts?
Let's get her outta here.
There's a patient on the table. Lift.
Dr. Bailey, when you get her stabilized,
I need a report, please.
- Dr. Bailey!
- Right, Dr. Burke.
Her pulse is racing.
I need her on a monitor,
need to get a B.P.
Also, I want her started on
at liter of L.R. wide open.
Izzie, get to emergency.
Let 'em know we're on our way.
- What?
- Seven weeks. I'm pregnant, Izzie.
Izzie, I'm pregnant.
Uh, okay, no.
We're going to pre-op instead.
Find Addison Shepherd,
and, Izzie, be discreet.
So I'm leaving in the morning.
No.
Excuse me?
No, I'm not accepting
your resignation.
It's not a
resignation, Richard.
It's notification.
I don't officially work for you.
I came here for one case.
I can track the twins'
progress from New York.
- Well, what about the preemie.
- I'm letting go of the preemie, you know that.
He calls me Satan, Richard.
- You don't like to hide from a fight.
- No fight. He wins.
I'm leaving in the morning.
- What is it, O'Malley?
- It's Dr. Grey, sir. Ellis.
C.T. confirmed diverticulitis,
but a liver mass was also found.
My god.
Poor Meredith.
As if her mother having Alzheimer's isn't bad enough,
now she has to deal with liver cancer.
You won't know that it's cancer
until you do a biopsy, O'Malley.
Right. Sorry.
Excuse me, Dr. Shepherd,
we need you, fast.
Um, it's Cristina,
one of our interns.
She's-- she's collapsed.
Cristina's collapsed?
Why do you need me?
- Cristina's pregnant?
- Shut up, George.
Please come.
Doesn't change anything, Richard.
I'm still leaving in the morning.
This is a very bad day.
Okay, Dr. Karev,
if we're gonna stop her blushing,
we have to expose the sympathetic
ganglion chain which resides where?
- It's time to clear me for surgery, Shepherd.
- What?
I know you heard me.
I'm standing right here.
Chief, I'm a little busy here.
We'll talk about it later.
Just give a verbal okay.
- We can do the paperwork later.
- I cannot do that.
I am your chief of surgery.
This is not a request.
With all due respect, sir, in this situation,
I'm not your subordinate, I'm your doctor.
One week after brain surgery, you are
not ready to resume medical practice.
It's a simple procedure.
A needle biopsy.
- A resident could do it.
- So let a resident do it.
What am I missing here?
It's for my mother, isn't it?
You think she has cancer.
George needs your signature.
Look Richard, I know
she's your friend.
But I'm not clearing
you for surgery.
What's her total bili?
It's actually only 4.
I mean, it's not great,
but it's not terrible.
That's why I didn't
see the jaundice.
No one could.
We just have to wait and see.
What aren't you telling me?
It's Cristina.
Have you notified the father?
Cristina. Cristina.
Cristina. Cristina,
is there anyone we can call?
We're losing her.
- Oh, man. You see that?
- It was an extrauterine pregnancy.
The tube burst.
She's bleeding out.
Ah, good. You're finished.
I need you to do
a needle biopsy.
Um, I've gotta go check on--
there's someone I
need to see about.
I had an intern collapse on
me in the middle of surgery.
- So if this could wait--
- No, I need you to do a needle biopsy now.
Chief, now is not the time.
I'm not in the mood for a debate.
You understand?
You'll do it because
I asked you to.
Because I need you to.
It's Ellis Grey.
She's gonna be okay, right?
How attached was she
to this pregnancy?
I don't know.
She's a pretty private person.
She's lost a lot of blood.
But I'm in control.
Dr. Bailey, you must have a
surgery or two of your own today.
I'm fine right here.
Can you do the follow-up?
I wanna check on Cristina.
Yeah. You know what's
wrong with her?
- Don't.
- I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
I'm so tired of you being sorry.
- Don't do it.
- Dr. Grey--
Dr. Grey. Seriously?
Are you concerned about
Alex finding out about us?
Is that what matters to you?
Do you really think he cares?
Alex, do you care that I was the intern
stupid enough to screw the married attending?
No.
- Meredith, it's okay.
- It's not okay.
You have a wife who's
not easy to hate,
who's annoyingly kind and painfully
smart and currently saving my friend's life.
- Would you just--
- Don't.
Stop talking to me like
you're my boyfriend.
Stop talking to me at all.
Dude--
that was rough.
You need something?
- I'm coming in.
- No, you're not.
- I am. I'm her friend.
- Exactly.
She's lying on the operating table,
naked, exposed.
She's sedated, but she's
probably scared out of her mind.
And right now, she's not a doctor,
she's not your friend, she's a patient.
And she deserves to have all
the privacy I can give her.
You're not going in there.
We went jogging this morning.
I made her go jogging.
- There's no way that could've--
- No, no.
It started out this way.
Nothing caused it to happen.
You have to let me in there.
You can try.
I'll have to take you down.
Hey--
I may be short,
but you're pretty tiny.
I could do it.
Right now,
just in this moment,
I hate you.
Yeah, well--
I can take it.
All right, Dr. Grey.
We're going to put you to
sleep for a little while.
But I promise, we'll have you
back into surgery in no time.
Richard--
thank god you're here--
you beautiful man.
That husband of mine has
been making me crazy.
Look at that.
B.P.'s stabilizing.
She's stronger
since this morning.
There's no reason in the world why she
should be stronger since this morning.
She's really beautiful,
isn't she?
Tell you what.
If she makes it though the night and she
has a little bit more strength, I'll operate.
You know--
the way I see it, we could deal
with us in one of three ways.
Option one, I could apologize,
you could forgive me and come home
and we could move on with
our lives like adults.
Or option two, I could apologize,
you could forgive me, come home,
but you could still bring it up to
use against me whenever we argue.
Are you trying to be funny?
Satan has a sense of humor.
What's the third?
I don't know what
the third option is.
I just know I still love you.
Tell them the chief said to
put a rush on this biopsy
- and tell them it's Ellis Grey.
- Okay.
Oh, Dr. Burke, do you want the histologic
grade and staging or any specific stains?
- Have them run all tests.
- Okay.
What happened?
You had an
extrauterine pregnancy.
Your left fallopian tube burst.
Dr. Shepherd--
she did everything she could,
but there was too much damage.
She couldn't save the tube.
- Hey.
- Is it over?
- Mm-hmm.
The surgery was successful.
We're just doing a follow-up.
Dr. Shepherd will be in to
check on you in a while.
- Say that again.
- What?
Say his name, Dr. Shepher--
oh, my god, look at my face.
Dr. Shepherd.
Guess it was worth the risk.
I still think it's nuts, having major surgery
just so people can't tell how you're feelin'.
Really? You do?
Nah, I guess not.
You could talk, you know.
I mean, if you need to.
I'm fine.
You've said that word
so many times today,
it doesn't even sound
like a word anymore.
I'm just sayin' you
could talk to me 'cause,
you know, even if I repeat every word
you say, no one around here likes me.
They'll just calme
a liar and move on.
Izzie likes you.
You're blushing.
Shut up.
Look, for what it's worth, I don't
know how you're still on your feet.
I mean, if I found out my mom might have
cancer, I'd be under the bar by now.
You want the ugly truth?
You have an ugly truth?
I never woulda pegged you
to have an ugly truth.
I'm more afraid she
doesn't have cancer.
Well, liver cancer's fast.
Painful, but it's fast,
and they give you morphine.
They don't give you
morphine for alzheimer's.
No, they don't.
What kind of person wishes
their mother had cancer?
It's hard.
I know is hard being
the one who's gone.
But, man-- it isn't easy bein'
the one who's still around.
- Hey, did you get your mom's biopsy results back yet?
- Not yet.
How's Cristina?
She's, uh--
she's gonna have a lot of pain for
a few days, but she'll be okay.
I'm glad you were there.
Are you?
Yes, I am.
It's just--
it's just that a
lot of the time,
it feels like you and Cristina are
kinda over there, and I'm here.
So about Alex--
Yeah, I know, I know.
You guys hate him. Fine.
Yeah, we do.
But I just wanna say
that I believe you,
that he's different once
you get to know him.
Here you go.
Ellis Grey.
Let her know.
Meredith, are you okay?
No.
I'm not okay.
Dr. Grey.
Oh, please, Thatcher.
I've had a long day. I'm tired. Go away.
No.
- What?
- No.
I am Thatcher Grey.
And I'm your husband, and, uh,
I know you don't like me very much, but
the fact is, I don't always
like you very much either.
I don't like the
way you speak to me.
And I really hate the way
you speak to Meredith.
She deserves better from you.
I'm sorry.
You are?
What's wrong with me, Thatch?
- Uh-- the mass on your liver--
- Is it algebra?
I mean, is it algeb--
damn it.
Is it malignant?
No.
It's benign.
Meredith.
- Meredith.
- Don't.
Please, please,
just don't say anything.
Okay.
I'm just exhausted.
My mother is exhausting,
what happened to Cristina--
and you--
hating you is the most exhausting.
I don't wanna do it anymore.
No one likes to loose control,
but as a surgeon,
there's nothing worse.
It's a sign of weakness--
of not being up to the task.
How can someone be so offensive and
yet so charming all at the same time?
It's an art form.
And still, there are times when
it just gets away from you--
when the world stops spinning and you realize
that your shiny little scalpel isn't gonna save you.
We went in expecting to
simply remove the tumor.
Instead, it was a little
more complicated.
The tumor infiltrated
into the pericardium,
causing a tear in the
outer muscle of the heart.
Um--
that's a lot of medical talk.
It means, uh, ahem--
it means--
that you had--
you had a broken
heart, literally.
Um--
but now I'm, um--
but now you're
going to be fine.
And no matter how hard
you fight it--
You fall.
And it's scary as hell.
Except, if there's an
upside to free-falling,
it's the chance you give
your friends to catch you.
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Raekwon
www.forom.com