Last season on "Grey's Anatomy"...
You have to go. I'm late.
Seriously. Good-bye...
- Derek.
- Yeah.
A month ago you were in med school being taught by doctors.
Today you are the doctors.
You're interns, grunts, nobodies, bottom of the surgical food chain.
It's like candy, but with blood, which is so much better.
And Dr. Shepherd he's over there.
Who here feels like they have no idea what they're doing?
- Stop looking at me like that.
- Like what?
Like you've seen me naked.
I don't get picked for surgeries 'cause I slept with my boss,
and I didn't get into med school 'cause I have a famous mother.
I used to be a doctor, I think.
Fine, George and Izzie, you can move into the house.
So you blew me off for a bottle of tequila.
That's not nearly as much fun to wake up to.
You mind moving this tail wagon?
The next time I see you favoring Meredith Grey in any way,
I'll make sure she doesn't see the inside of an O.R. for a month.
You know, I'm your boss.
You don't scare me.
You should know that Richard promised chief to both of us.
Keep your friends close and your enemies closer.
Morning, Dr. Model.
Dr. Evil spawn.
You're not the enemy.
You're just the competition.
What is this that we're doing here?
You need a definition?
There are over options.
It's a tumor, and it's pressing against your optic nerve.
You've got syphilis.
I don't know how this happened.
You and Alex?
You gave me syphilis?!
You know, some people would call this a relationship.
- Who?
- Me.
Oh, my God.
You're falling for him.
What makes a hotshot doc leave the big apple for seattle?
- Hi, I'm Addison Shepherd.
- Shepherd?
And you must be the woman who's been screwing my husband.
To be a good surgeon, you have to think like a surgeon.
Emotions are messy.
Tuck them neatly away and step into a clean, sterile room,
where the procedure is simple...
cut, suture and close.
You look familiar.
You been in here before?
Once.
That worked out really well.
I know that look. Can only be one of two things.
Either your boss is giving you hell, or your boyfriend is.
Which is it?
Both.
But sometimes you're faced with a cut that won't heal...
My boyfriend is my boss, which was a problem.
But not as big a problem as the fact that my boyfriend has a wife.
Tell you what,
this one is on the house.
A cut that rips its stitches wide open.
Addison, what are you doing here?
Your hair's different.
- A lot of things are different.
- It's longer. I like it. It's very Russell Crowe.
- What are you doing here?
You just pick up and leave everything
your house, your practice, your friends?
- You had a life in Manhattan.
- Had.
And now you have a girlfriend in Seattle.
She seems... sweet.
The ice you're on... thin.
She's young.
That whole wide-eyed, "ooh,
he's a brain surgeon" thing happening,
but still sweet, which is what you were going for, right?
The anti-Addison?
If you came out here to try to win me back, you can forget about it.
I did. I flew all the way across the country to reminisce over
wedding photos, get drunk, fall into bed,
make you realize you can't live without me.
Relax, Derek.
I'm here for work.
I'm helming the T.T.T.S. case you guys admitted last week.
- And from Richard's briefing, I should be...
- Richard knew you were coming out here?
He asked me to come.
- Didn't he tell you?
- No, he didn't.
Hmm. Well, surprise.
The hair, though...
you know I've always had a thing for Russell Crowe.
Let me see it.
No lacerations, normal swelling.
George really knocked you around.
The guy's a lightweight.
I coulda pinned him in a second if I wanted.
Yeah, so why didn't you?
Are you kidding?
I'm riding a career in plastics all the way to the bank.
I can't afford to injure these babies.
Especially over someone like O'Malley.
You had it coming.
The dude punches like my sister.
Oh, so by your definition, then, you got beat up by a girl?
All hail the champ!
So my guy Alex finally got what was comin' to him?
George knocked him down in one punch.
You shoulda seen it.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Brag, champ, brag. You've earned it.
Can I have a beer?
Let's play a game of whose life sucks the most.
I'll win.
- I always win.
- Well, you don't wanna play with me.
Oh, I do.
I'll even go first.
Derek's married.
George, beer is dripping from your nostrils.
Told you I'd win.
No, you don't win.
Did you hear me?
I said Derek is married.
As in pigheaded, adulterous, liar married.
Nothing you could say could top that.
I'm pregnant.
I win.
Joe, you all right?
Okay, maybe Joe wins.
Joe, lie down.
You called the gurney patrol?
Sit back and relax.
We have to take you to the hospital to run some tests.
Tests? No. I don't need any tests. I'm fine.
Dude, you collapsed on the floor.
This is your bar. You know how filthy this floor is.
- Radial pulse is strong.
- Minor skull contusion.
- You're sleeping with someone?
- What? Who?
Why is that such a shock?
Even george managed to get some action.
Correction. George got some syphilis.
How could I not know you were sleeping with someone?
Forget this. The hospital is right across the street.
I can sure as hell walk across the street by myself.
- Oh, I think we should...
- No, I got it. Joe!
All right, details.
You're pregnant?
What are you gonna do?
You know what happens with pregnant interns.
I'm not switching to the vagina squad or spending my life popping zits.
I'm too talented.
Surgery's my life.
- Which begs the question, who are you sleeping with?
- Just a guy.
That's all I get?
You can't just bring something like this up and expect me to drop it.
Watch me.
Why are you back here tonight?
- Don't you have a date with McDreamy?
- More like McMarried.
Mcwhat?
I came to check on Joe.
Do you think he's gonna be okay?
You think he's gonna need an operation?
Operation... yes.
Okay... hard to tell.
The basilar artery is blown up like a balloon, subarachnoid bleeding
and an aneurysm the size of a golf ball.
No way to clip something like that.
Not without magic fingers.
Or a standstill operation.
You're doing the standstill opera...
he's doing the standstill operation.
I'd like to try.
But first I need some additional patient history,
overnight labs and a cerebral angio.
I'm drunk.
Meredith...
McBastard.
What are you doing?
Uh, I am on her side,
but we're talking a possible standstill here.
Recognize.
Meredith.
- Go away.
- Just wait.
We should discuss this.
Here's a thought.
No. Quit following me.
At least let me explain.
Explain? You know when you should've explained?
The night we met in the bar, before any of the rest of it.
Yeah, that would've been a good time to discuss this.
Look, I know how you feel.
Do you?
Somehow I doubt that.
Because if you did, you would shut up
and you would turn around and go back inside,
because you would realize that
I am this close to getting in my car
and running you down in the parking lot!
Give me the keys.
- I'm fine.
- Meredith, give me the keys.
Let's go, okay?
And the husband was the worst.
Well, I will be back in the morning to report for duty.
And you...get some rest.
What is she doing here?
You and I both know she's the best in the field.
Bringing Addie out was a business decision, nothing personal.
Oh, well. What a relief.
It's not personal.
It is personal to me.
The workings of my surgical unit
- don't have anything...
- Don't include my wife!
Don't include your private life.
Burke will act as chief of surgery until I'm back on my feet.
You gave chief to Burke?
Like I said, there's no room for personal in being chief.
What is that supposed to mean?
How long have you been sleeping with an intern?
So I guess part of being chief is personal.
Close the door on your way out.
Allis.
Babcock.
Right angle clamp.
I'm gonna sterilize everything when I'm done.
The scrub nurses won't even know I was here.
My lips are sealed.
So, um, I have a question to ask.
I checked the schedule, and I noticed
that you and I are both off tonight.
I made reservations.
I have a favorite restaurant.
None of those were questions.
Would you like to go out to dinner with me tonight?
You know, the O.R. is the one place where I can come and think...
and I was thinking right now, okay?
Of course.
I get it.
I'm not a violent person.
I'm a pacifist, but, you know, he just
he kept pushing and push
he pushed me, and I pushed back.
I was pushed, you know, and now he
You know what? Alex tries to lay a hand on you, just tell me.
I'll take care of it.
I don't need you to...
to take care of it.
If Alex starts something, I-I'll handle it myself.
I can handle it.
Okay, people, assignments.
Yang, you're on discharges.
O'Malley, report to room E19.
Grey, come see me, and who was on call last night?
Sloppy, sloppy, sloppy.
- Redo these and return them to me before lunch, understood?
- Understood.
Karev, don't tempt me.
Somebody's popular.
Meaning?
There's been a special request just for you.
The chief runs through all of this?
Before lunch.
After, you've got calls to return, a budget to approve,
two staff meetings, and four of Richard's surgeries, including your own.
Absolutely. No problem.
Virgins...
So congratulations are in order.
Don't sweat it, Shepherd.
I'll only be your boss for a few days.
I'm well aware of Richard's recovery time.
I'm the one who operated on him, remember?
I do.
You operated, he survived and chose me
to take over while recruiting your wife.
Clearly, he has brain damage.
Or is it your ex-wife?
I'm a little fuzzy on that.
Ahh, we're separated.
Sorry to interrupt, Dr. Burke.
- You're never interrupting.
- She's always interrupting.
I was just checking to see
- if Dr. Burke secured the in...
- Intern you requested.
He did.
Define T.T.T.S.
Twin-twin transfusion syndrome, conjoined fetal twins.
Connected by?
Blood vessels in the placenta.
Meaning?
One twin gets too much blood, the other too little,
endangering the lives of both.
I'd expect you to know that, Grey.
You told me there wasn't much chance that anything could be done, but...
T.T.T.S. is usually impossible to correct,
unless you happen to be one of the handful of surgeons
in the world who knows how to separate
fetal blood vessels, which, luckily for you, I am.
So we're gonna get you into surgery tomorrow.
If you have any questions at all, please ask Dr. Grey.
From what I have seen,
she is one of the hospital's most popular interns.
I could've answered your question had you given me the chance.
Chin up, Grey.
I'm this tough on everyone,
not just the women my husband sleeps with.
Order an ultrasound...
Hi. Can I have the chart for E19, please?
Thank you.
Oh, good. You're here.
- Let's get started.
- Okay.
- O'Malley?
- Yeah.
- You're touching me.
- Well, yeah.
No.
Carmen...
I want you to listen to me very carefully.
As long as I'm in here, I don't know what's
happening out there with my doctors, my patients, my hospital.
You are my eyes today, my ears.
I want you to be a sponge.
A sponge?
You report any and everything happening in this hospital to me.
I'm an investigative sponge.
I'm not foolin' around, O'Malley.
There's too much been happenin' lately under my radar.
It stops today.
Uh, Burke, you gave Grey to Addison?
Are you sure about that?
That's not your call, Shepherd.
And for the record, I'm always sure.
Did you need me for something?
- Because as the new chief, I'm...
- Interim chief.
Chief nonetheless.
Ever attempt a standstill surgery?
It's the location of the aneurysm that makes it tricky.
Your body temperature will be lowered cool enough
to protect you from any damage and stop the heart.
Which stops the blood flow to the brain,
which reduces the risk of rupture.
I'll have 45 minutes to clip the aneurysm
before I step in and get the heart started again.
You wanna freeze my body, drain my blood and stop my heart?
And bring you back.
In under 45 minutes.
If you go over, is it free?
No.
Dr. Yang, you can go and handle the pre-op labs.
How much?
How much does something like this cost?
I don't think you should worry about that right now.
Hey, look, you guys say that you can kill me and bring me back.
I believe you. You're doctors.
But I own a bar.
I don't got any insurance,
so I'm not that concerned about the surgery
so much as what I'm gonna do when I survive it.
I need a number.
10 grand? 20?
30?
It's a couple hundred at least.
At least.
Who's Halloran?
Patient in 4115.
Red hair?
Wife knits all the time?
He had the colectomy?
Oh, colon dude, that's right.
Who's Monterosso?
4238. The mom with the really cute kids.
She spiked a post-op fever last night.
- You spent two hours monitoring her.
- Hernia chick, that's right.
You have been treating these people for the last week.
How can you not know their names?
Surgery's the only specialty where
we don't waste time getting to know the patients.
- They're slabs of meat, and we're butchers.
- They're human beings.
You do know what a human being is,
- don't you, evil spawn?
- I'm not evil.
Unless evil turns you on.
Do you ever wake up in the morning
and realize nobody likes you and, I don't know, care?
Oh.
I think somebody likes me.
Hey.
What, you don't speak now that you're chief? Hey, Burke!
What do you want?
What?
You don't want to go out to dinner.
You don't want to meet me in the on call room,
and you sure as hell don't want to talk to me.
I could pretend I know, but, hey,
I don't even have your home phone number.
So tell me, what do you want?!
Don't yell at me.
- Hey, we're having a conversation here.
- Well, what do you want?
I don't know!
Figure it out.
What's the report?
No report.
It's very quiet today, sir.
There's no news, gossip, surgeries I should know about?
Come on, what's the buzz, O'Malley?
You know, not in the halls or not in the O.R., not in the stairwells.
Especially, you know, nothing happening in the...
they're just stairwells.
They told me you were in a nightgown,
but I thought I'd come and see it for myself.
Very nice. Huh?
Heard O'Malley laid you out cold. Nice eye.
Whoa, who sent that?
We all pitched in.
The whole floor.
Well, please tell the whole floor a big thank you.
Yeah, I will.
Alex, you gotta get me out of here, man.
Get me transferred to County Hospital or something.
Oh, you don't want to go to County.
I mean, here they know how to kill you and bring you back.
But at county, they just know how to kill you. No joke.
I can't afford this place, man.
I'm gonna lose the bar.
Hey, Joe, how you doing?
Hey, Scooter.
Okay. That's mine.
Well, first things first.
We're gonna start by trying to save your life, man.
The bar is my life.
You know that. You've been at last call with me
practically every night since you moved here.
I'm gonna have to shut it down or sell it.
You can't do that.
The place is an institution.
You know, I've owned the bar across the street for 14 years,
and I have never been inside this hospital till now.
Look, I'll pay my tab, right?
Gotta be good for something.
How much is it?
Close to a grand.
Um, how about I pay, like, 60...
That's good.
And I'll pay you back later.
Hey, champ!
What does it take to go after another woman's husband?
Excuse me?
Happened to me.
Jeff moved in with the long-legged miniskirt
who answers his phones three weeks into my pregnancy.
By the way, that gel is really cold.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry about your husband.
Are you sorry about Dr. Montgomery Shepherd's husband?
I'm going to be checking a few things today.
I bet she asked to work with you.
It's what I would have done.
I'm gonna go check on your labs.
Hey, sunshine.
Deep breath.
Morning sickness must suck.
Just so we're clear
do not breathe a word of what you heard last night to anyone
not about me, not about Meredith,
not about Meredith and Dr. McDreamy.
Hey, Dr. Burke.
Joe.
Um, vital signs stable overnight.
Today's C.T. shows no rebleeding.
The E.K.G...
shows...
normal sinus rhythm.
No ischemia, no disrhythmias.
Looking good.
Page me if there are any changes.
Oh, hi, chief.
No, not much going on
well, other than your interim chief making out with my friend in the stairwell.
But, hey, sponge duty sucks.
Talking to yourself now?
Yes. No!
Damn it. I'm a bad sponge, a leaky sponge.
I'm gonna leak all the wrong secrets, 'cause I'm a bad liar.
I can't even lie about talking to myself.
You look nice today.
Wore my new lip gloss.
'Cause my ex-boyfriend's wife looks like
Isabella freakin' Rossellini, and I'm like... me.
I'm trying to outdo her when she's the victim here.
How crazy is that?
Not crazy. Smart.
You know, gloss, you know, prevents chapped lips...
and... ex-boyfriend?
I'm an evil mistress.
Well, still, you look nice.
Thanks.
What are you doing here?
- Well...
- come on, O'Malley. Out with it.
Okay. Can you think of any reason, any reason at all,
really, why Cristina would be kissing Burke?
After all this time, all your warnings about me sleeping with my boss,
- and you're doing the same exact thing?
- It's not the same.
- It's exactly the same!
- You and McDreamy are in a relationship.
And you and Burke are in... Switzerland.
It's very neutral there. They make very nice watches.
Have you even bothered to tell Burke about the baby?
Are you going to?
Look, Meredith, can we not go there?
Can everyone just accept the fact that there are some things
that I like to keep to myself,
and I don't discuss everything to death?
Well, why even confide in me at all
if you're so intent on not discussing it?
Why even tell me?
When I found out about the miniskirt,
I called her up and took her to lunch.
It was perfectly civil.
I said I didn't hold it against her,
that these things happen.
But really, I just wanted to put a face on the bitch
that got my husband to throw away 15 years of marriage.
Got a second?
Depends on what you need.
Who the hell is dr. Mcdreamy?
Me. I'm Dr. Mcdreamy.
I'm tall and handsome.
I like to lean against things,
ponder the difficulties of dating beautiful women.
I'm trying to be a surgeon here.
- That took a lot of nerve, requesting Meredith.
- Oh, come on. She came highly recommended.
- Right.
- So you don't recommend her?
- No, I did not say that.
- Just not for her medical skills.
Oh, would you shut up?
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Yes.
Labs confirm what look like abnormalities on the ultrasound.
I think you should come and see for yourself.
Fine. Let's go.
- Meredith. Meredith.
- Don't.
Well, no report.
Yeah. Same nothing as earlier, chief.
I should go.
Oh, actually, there is something, sir.
Burke and Shepherd marking territory on the playground?
No, sir.
It's about Joe the bartender, their standstill patient.
See?
Bilateral pleural effusion with evidence of sub-q edema.
In english, please?
We've detected what looks like beginning heart failure in the twins.
Don't be alarmed.
Are my babies gonna be okay?
I'm gonna go ahead and take you into surgery now.
We're not gonna wait. Book the O.R. Move!
Tell Pete to wash out the taps every night,
not every other night, every night.
And remind him that the delivery truck
comes at 6 A.M. Kegs go in the back.
Oh, another thing,
there's petty cash on the top shelf of the storage closet.
We operate on our patients. That's it.
- I know, but...
- I sympathize. I do.
But solving Joe's finances is not my job.
It's not your job, and it's sure as hell not the job I assigned you today.
Just seems wrong to cut him open,
sew him up and just leave him, you know, left with nothing.
If we can save his life, we'll hardly be leaving him with nothing.
That's as far as I can go for now.
Let's start cooling him.
Can't see much from back here, O'Malley.
I know. I'm trying to find a loophole to help Joe.
You know Joe?
Oh, yeah. I was the only female intern my year.
I didn't know anybody, and nobody knew me except Joe.
He knew me.
So you and Joe...
All you people ever think about is how to get into somebody's pants.
You're nasty.
That's why you got syphilis.
Joe was the first person here to tell me I'd make
a good surgeon, not that he knew anything about it.
But it was something when I had nothing.
Oh, sure. I'm the guy with the heart of stone, and you brought snacks.
It's a working lunch.
Snacks to watch Joe die.
He's not gonna die-die. They'll bring him back.
He is going to die-die. No pulse-pulse.
He's gonna be dead-dead.
It's a granola bar, Alex, not a bag of
supersize popcorn and a box of chocolate movie mints.
That's it.
Dead.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Julie we're just going  to go in laparoscopically.
You're not going to feel anything.
Neither are the twins.
Okay, let's get going.
Thin blade.
Begin with a 3-millimeter incision.
Stop the blood flow?
To protect the brain, operate in a
bloodless field so the aneurysm won't rupture.
And cool the body?
To induce hypothermia.
Keeps the tissue viable until the blood is restored.
Body temp is at 60 degrees.
Okay, Joe. Time to die.
Flatline.
All right.
- We've got 45 minutes, people.
- Start the clock.
So what's your Joe story?
Seems like everybody around here has one.
You first.
Okay. I went to Joe's place the night before I started working here.
I'd only been in town, you know, a few days.
I met this woman. I got drunk, and she took advantage of me.
Or she got drunk, and I took advantage of her.
I got drunk and she took no.
We were drunk, definitely.
Somebody took advantage.
Either way, I like to look at it as my initiation to Seattle.
What about you?
Oh, well, I don't have one.
I just wanted to hear yours.
So technically the paperwork just needs to be submitted
by midnight of the day of the surgery to be considered?
Oh, good.
Thank you very much.
Thanks.
How you doing there, Grey?
Good.
I'm good.
- You know, I'm very sweet once you get to know me.
- No, you're not.
- We could be good friends.
- Alex, never. Ever.
- Ever.
- Why not?
You give me one reason why we could.
What about you is even remotely human?
It's going too slowly.
I hope Joe can pull through this.
He can. He will.
He has to.
Ah, damn it.
I can't get the clamp to hold.
Give me--all right, we're just gonna go in at a different angle.
Time remaining?
- Irrigation, please. Irrigation.
- 17 minutes.
Shepherd, I'm gonna need 8 minutes to get him back, to warm him up.
Time to make the next 17 minutes count.
- Go in through there.
- You see it?
He's dead, technically, which is science, and this is a huge thing.
So I thought some research
foundation has gotta have an interest in that.
So in essence, you wanna donate Joe's body to science?
At least for the next 17 minutes.
- A privately funded grant.
- For educational purposes.
We're a teaching hospital.
The standstill surgery qualifies.
I didn't peg you for the type to ignore my instructions, O'Malley.
With all due respect, sir, it's worth a shot.
It's someone's life.
It's always someone's life, O'Malley.
You're hovering.
You can leave now.
Eight minutes.
We need to start rewarming, Shepherd.
Take the bipolars, please. Thank you.
- Shepherd, we need to start warming him up now.
- Hang on.
- Now, I need him now, Shepherd.
- I can't seem to get it.
Ah, there it is.
Got it.
That's it.
Are you sure?
I'm always sure.
All right. Good work, everybody.
It's all yours there, chief.
Okay, people, let's grab Joe before he decides to go into the light.
Start warming him up.
Clamps are coming off.
Turn the pump on.
Watch cerebral perfusion pressures.
Keep M.A.P.
Greater than 60, please.
I know you're enjoying yourself, Preston.
It's a power kick to be the chief.
You're never more surrounded, never more alone.
You're everyone's father, everyone's boss and old friend.
The choices we make -- clean slices, neat stitches,
no emotions, no compromise, no personal life.
Richard--
I just had brain surgery.
I'm surrounded by fruit baskets.
The only people who've been in this room come to kiss my ass.
I gave you a shot for a reason, Preston.
You and I...
We're the same.
We put the job first.
That was the single most amazing surgery I have ever witnessed.
You--you killed a man and brought him back to life.
You, like, raised the dead.
God, how does that feel? Are you rushing? Is it...
like you wouldn't believe.
Hey, um, do you still have those reservations? 'Cause I'm starving.
Cristina...
I think there's something we should discuss.
Yeah. Yeah, there is.
It's pretty clear.
It is?
We've been fooling ourselves,
to think that we can continue like this without consequences.
Consequences?
We have careers to think about, reputations.
We both put the job first.
And you are very focused. I respect that.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, you're ending this.
I think it's best to make a clean break.
Okay.
Before it gets too involved.
- Before it gets...
- Messy. Right, right.
That would be... that would be bad.
It's nothing personal.
Get in here, O'Malley.
Okay, I tried. I really tried.
But there's a lot of stuff happening out there,
stuff I can't tell you, stuff I won't tell you.
It's just crazy stuff
stuff I'm gonna have nightmares about.
But I'm not gonna tell you about any of it 'cause it doesn't matter.
Not when there's a guy out there who we all know and love
who's gonna be bankrupt because he needed a surgery to save his life.
- And I spent the whole day working on it.
- O'Malley!
Let me finish.
You're wrong, sir.
Now you can fire me, you know,
or just bring me up on disciplinary action, or whatever.
- But I'm telling you, Joe deserves our...
- Deserves our help.
Couldn't help yourself, could you?
Whether or not it'd win you any points, even from me.
I signed your request.
Give it to Patricia. She'll know what to do with it.
- Looks like Joe might keep his bar after all.
- Thank you, sir.
- O'Malley.
- Yes.
Yell at me again, and I'll snap you like a twig.
Yes, sir.
See? Just a small scar.
And my babies?
Your babies are doing very well.
And Dr. Grey will be back to check on you a little bit later.
Actually, I'd prefer it if Dr. Grey were taken off the case.
Why? Is there a problem?
Just reminds me of someone I don't like very much
someone my husband likes a lot, particularly in lingerie.
You understand.
No, no, I don't understand.
Well, she's sleeping with your husband, right?
Ms. Phillips...
I lack Dr. Grey's class and patience, so let me set the record straight.
My husband didn't cheat on me. I cheated on him.
So the wronged woman here
Dr. Grey.
So I think you owe her one hell of an apology.
One night I park my car and unlock my front door
to go inside my house, and something's different.
Nothing's different, everything's the same, but yet still...
something's different.
And I stand there for awhile...
and then I know.
See, there are moments for me, usually when I'm in the O.R.,
when I just know what's gonna happen next.
So I go upstairs.
As I'm walking down the hall, I'm trying to prepare myself.
I step on a man's jacket that doesn't belong to me.
And everything I think I know...
just shifts.
Because the jacket that doesn't belong to me is a jacket that I recognize.
And what I know now is that when I go into my bedroom,
I'm not just gonna see that my wife is cheating on me.
I'm gonna see that my wife is cheating on me with Mark,
who happened to be my best friend.
It's just so pedestrian and common and dirty and cruel.
Mostly just cruel.
I left. I came out here.
- And you met me.
- And I met you.
Well, what was I to you?
The girl you screwed to get over being screwed?
You were like coming up for fresh air.
It's like I was drowning, and you saved me.
That's all I know.
That's not enough.
They say "practice makes perfect."
Theory is, the more you think
like a surgeon, the more you become one...
the better you get at remaining neutral, clinical
cut, suture, close...
and the harder it becomes to learn to turn it off...
I thought I might see your ugly mug in here tonight.
Did you hear the good news?
To stop thinking like a surgeon...
O'Malley!
I heard what you did, champ.
And remember what it means to think like a human being.
The clinic has a policy.
They wouldn't let me confirm my appointment
unless I designated an emergency contact person
someone to be there just in case and...
to help me home, you know, after.
Anyway, I put your name down.
That's why I told you I'm pregnant.
- You're my person.
- I am?
Yeah, you are.
Whatever.
He dumped me.
You realize this constitutes hugging?
Shut up.
I'm your person.
Transcript : Raceman
Resynchro : VAGGELiS
Synchro : Raekwon
www.forom.com