okay,
so this is the story of five surgical interns...
all of them fresh out of med school,
all of them pretty smart,
all of them very driven
and all of them just maybe a little scared.
Of course, it's not always about the medicine.
Ugh!
You have to go.
I'm late.
Which isn't what you wanna be
on your first day of work, so...
so, uh,
you actually live here?
You know what? We don't
have to do the thing.
Oh. We can do
anything you want.
No, the thing... exchange
the details, pretend we care.
Good-bye...
uh...
derek.
Derek.
Right. Meredith.
Bye, derek.
The seven years you spend here
as a surgical resident
will be the best and worst
of your life.
You will be pushed
to the breaking point.
Look around you.
Say hello to your competition.
Only 6 women out of 20.
Yeah.
I hear one of them is a model.
Seriously, that's gonna help
with the respect thing?
You're cristina, right?
Which resident are you
assigned to? I've got bailey.
The nazi? Me, too.
You got the nazi?
So did i?
At least we'll be
tortured together, right?
I'm george. O'malley.
Uh, we met at the, uh,
at the mixer.
You had on a black dress
with a slit up the side
and strappy sandals and...
now you think i'm gay.
Uh, no, i'm not gay.
Uh-huh.
It's... it's just that, uh...
(miranda) o'malley, yang,
grey, stevens.
That's the nazi?
(george) i thought the nazi
would be a guy.
I thought the nazi
would be... a nazi.
Maybe it's
professional jealousy.
Maybe she's brilliant
and they call her a nazi
because they're jealous.
Maybe she's nice.
Let me guess,
you're the model.
Hi, i'm isobel stevens,
but everyone calls me izzie.
Rule number one,
don't bother sucking up.
I already hate you.
That's not gonna change.
Your first shift starts now
and lasts 48 hours.
You're interns,
grunts, nobodies,
bottom of
the surgical food chain.
You run labs, write orders,
work every second night
until you drop
and don't complain.
No one holds a scalpel
till i'm so happy
i'm mary freakin' poppins.
If you make
your resident look bad,
she'll torture you until
you beg for your mama.
Now get out there
and don't let me catch you
fighting over patients.
Stop.
No.
Oh, mine.
No, i saw him first.
What?
Katie's parents
have questions.
Do you talk to them
or do i ask burke?
No, burke's off the case.
Katie belongs to
the new attending now...
dr. Shepherd.He's over there.
Unfortunately,
on your first day,
the surprises aren't always going to be...
surgical.
Meredith,
could i talk
to you for a second?
Actually, i was...
i'm not the girl in the bar
anymore, and you're not the guy.
You took advantage of me and now
you want to forget about it.
I did not take...
i was drunk, vulnerable
and good-looking,
and you took advantage.
Okay, i was the one
who was drunk,
and you are not
that good-looking.
Maybe not today.
Last night? Last night
i was very good-looking.
I had my red shirt on,
my good-looking shirt.
You took advantage.
I did not take advantage.
You wanna take advantage again,
say friday night?
Stop looking at me
like that.
Like what?
Like you've seen me naked.
(preston)
Good afternoon, interns.
As you know, the honor
of performing the first surgery
is reserved for the intern
that shows the most promise.
George o'malley.
Me?
Congratulations.
(man) he's gonna faint.
He's a fainter.
Nah, code brown,
right in his pants.
He's all about the flop sweat,
gonna sweat himself unsterile.
10 bucks says
he messes up the mcburney.
$15 says he cries.
I'll put $20
on a total meltdown.
$50 says he pulls
the whole thing off.
That's one of us down there,
the first one of us.
Where's your loyalty?
$75 says he can't even
i.d. The appendix.
I'll take that action.
Okay, o'malley,
let's see what you can do.
(george) scalpel.
(woman) scalpel.
(cheering)
(man) o'malley!
(preston) let's invert
the stump into the cecum
and simultaneously
pull up on the purse strings.
But be careful not to...
break them.
Oh, man.
You ripped the cecum.
Get out of the way!
Pansy-ass idiot.
Get him out of here.
He's 007.
(man) 007, yeah.
(man)
Yep, a total 007.
What's 007 mean?
Licensed to kill.
Maybe i should've gone
into geriatrics.
No one minds when you
kill an old person.
Geriatrics is for freaks
who live with their mothers
and never have sex.
I have gotta get
my own place.
I'll work with you, but i
don't want in on the surgery.
You can have it.
Are you kidding?
It's the biggest opportunity
any intern will ever get.
I don't want to spend
any more time
with shepherd than i have to.
What do you have against shepherd?
You can't comment, make a face
or react in any way.
We had sex.
Dr. Shepherd, you said that
you'd pick someone
to scrub in if we helped?
Oh, yes, right.
Um, i'm sorry
i can't take you both,
but it's gonna be
a full house.
Meredith, i'll see you
in o.r.
Oh, screw you. I don't get
picked for surgeries
'cause i slept with my boss.
There is a reason we don't
sleep with the attendings.
It's not her fault,
He's the attending.
He should know better.
He's taking advantage of her.
What is your problem?
Um, you.
'Cause apparently
you can help dr. Mcdreamy
in ways the rest of us can't.
You can't do me favors.
Okay.
I can take care of myself.
Look, i'm not being seen
with you in this hospital.
Think of it as an attending
getting to know
one of his interns.
He slept with the intern.
Barely knew her.
And it should stay that way.
You want me to be professional?
Nice talking to you,
dr. Grey.
(izzie) why do you
put up posters for roommates
if you don't want roommates?
I do want roommates.
We're together 100 hours a week.
You wanna live together, too?
My mom irons my scrubs.
I have to get out of there.
I can cook
and i'm an obsessive cleaner.
Look, i'm sure
you're very nice,
but i'm very particular
about who lives in my house
and you're just not right.
Look, i'm quiet...
no loud music, no parties.
Where were you when
the "challenger" exploded?
The what?
Exactly. No.
Okay, fine,
george and izzie,
you can move into the house.
Yes!
I can't believe she caved!
Aah!
George's room is bigger
than mine.
I got here first.
It's meredith's house.She should decide.
I'm not riding
in the same car with him.
Unless you're going like that,
you're not riding with me.
Where are the tampons?
He didn't buy them.
You didn't buy them?
I am a man!
I don't buy girl products.
I don't want you walking in
while i'm in the shower,
and i don't want to see you
in your underwear.
Do you like izzie?
Is that what this is about?
Do you have a crush on izzie?
N... izzie, no?
I don't like izzie.
She's not the one
i'm attracted to.
Not the one?So there's a one?
This is not...
you know, you're not
the only one to put things off.
I mean, i never do anything
till the last possible minute.
Like what?
I've had this thing
for my roommate since,
like, day one, and i just...
i can't tell her.
You know, she probably wouldn't
go out with me anyway,
but how do know that for sure
if i don't ever ask?
Seriously?
You're equating
your pathetic love life
with my record-breaking tumor?
Seriously?
After dealing with all that life and death,
where does a doctor go to unwind?
They come to see me at my bar,
right across the street from the hospital.
I know that look.
Can only be
one of two things...
either your boss is giving
you hell or your boyfriend is.
Which is it?
My boyfriend is my boss.
This one is on the house.
I'm not going out with you,
i'm not dating you,
and i'm definitely not
sleeping with you again.
You're my boss.
I'm your boss' boss.
Look, i'm drawing a line.
The line is drawn.
So this line...
is it imaginary
or do i need to get you
a marker?
male, 55, victim of
a head-on collision.
Mistakes... they happen.
And imagine what happens
with doctors who aren't that experienced.
Just one more reason i'm glad i'm a bartender.
(meredith) i popped a glove.
(preston) what?
I think
i may have nicked her heart.
Your ass is on the line here,
dr. Grey.
You've done this before, right?
Of course.
Millions of times.
2 of ativan.
He started seizing.
How much sodium did you give him?
100 cc over 4 hours.
Actually, doctor, you ordered
500 cc per hour over 4 hours.
Why didn't you do a follow-up?
I gave you one thing to do.
Karev, it's over, it's done.
You screwed up.
Deal with it.
We stole a body.
The thing about being dead is
people stop looking for you.
You brought a textbook?
Yeah. Okay, got it.
You sure?
It's not like we can kill him twice.
Don't even tell me you're doin'
what i think you're doin'.
Who here feels like they have
no idea what they're doing?
Morning, dr. Model.
Dr. Evil spawn.
Ooh, nice tat.
They airbrush that out
for the catalogues?
I don't know.
What do they do for the 6-6-6
on your skull?
I'd know you anywhere.
You're the spitting image
of your mother.
(cristina)you know
meredith is inbred?
Like it's uncommon
around here to be a doctor
whose parents are doctors?
No, really inbred.Her mother is ellis grey.
Shut up. "the" ellis grey?
Who's ellis grey?
El... the grey method?
Where'd you go
to med school, mexico?
She was one of the first
big chick surgeons.
I mean, she practically invented
the abdominal retractor.
She's a living legend.
She won the harper-avery, twice.
Well, the ellis grey i know
didn't have regards for anyone
except ellis grey.
But you know that already,
don't you?
Where is she now?
Traveling.
Traveling?
Yeah.
Huh.
So we're kissing,
but we're not dating?
I have no idea
what that was about.
Is it gonna happen again?
'Cause if it is,
i need to bring breath mints,
(whispers) put a condom in my wallet.
Shut up now.
Well, well, well.
Dr. Bethany whisper.
That's so nice.
Thank you.
What?
It's the chase, isn't it?
The thrill of the chase.
I've been wondering to myself,
why are you so hell-bent
on getting me to go out
with you?
You know you're my boss,
you know it's against the rules,
you know i keep saying no.
It's the chase.
But it's fun, isn't it?
Izzie.
George.
Le...
stop.
(whistling and cheering)
Shh. Shh. Shh.
(whispers) we have
bethany whisper
in our locker room.
(normal voice) oh, boy,
i guess they do, uh,
airbrush out the tattoo,
don't they?
Fine.
Let's look at that tattoo
up close and personal,
shall we?
And what are these?
Oh, my g! Breasts.
Gather around
and check out the booty
that put izzie stevens
through med school.
You want to call me
dr. Model?
That's fine.
Just remember
that while you're sitting
on 200 grand of student loans,
i'm out of debt.
Go!
(cristina) come on.
Let's bag her.
Push epi and atropine.
Somebody page burke.
One and two and three...
breathe.
She's d.n.r.
One, two, three...
she's d.n.r.
Do not resuscitate.
Dr. Yang.
Come on, people.
Push another...
do not resuscitate.
All right!
It is on her chart.
Let her go down.
Yea-ye...
let her go down.
We have to let her go.
Just coffee.
It's not the chase.
What?
You and me...
it is not the thrill of the chase.
It's not a game.
It's...
(meredith) i'm still not going out with you.
Listen to me.
What?
You should probably
sneak inside now.
We've done enough
sneaking for the night.
It was good sneaking,
but enough sneaking.
Yeah, i'd say
we're pretty good sneakers.
You mind moving
this tail wagon?
You're blocking me in.
Late night, grey?
And while we're
on the subject,
you care to tell me what
you think you're doing?
Look, i'll jump through hoops
if you want me to,
but what i do when i leave
this hospital is my business.
Half this hospital
knows your business.
I made a choice,
and i know you don't
respect me for that choice,
so whatever else you got,
bring it on.
(all) eww!
Thanks for the coffee.
(Iranda) hey, there's
a new surgical case
coming up from the pit.
Let's go.
(ellis) watch it!
Hands off me!
I could report you to the chief,
and you'd be out on your ass!
(cristina)
Patient's name is, uh...
where is the chief?
Complaining of intermittent
cramping, pain and diarrhea.
Also suffers from...
alzheimer's.
(miranda) patient's name?
Um...
come on, yang.
The patient's name.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Ellis grey.
(george) meredith's mother.
George,
take care of dr. Grey.
Yes. She needs a friend
right now.
Oh, you mean
ellis, the...
mother.
Dr. Grey.
Goddamn it, thatcher.
I'm at work.
I've already told you, i'm
too busy to deal with you now.
No more cartoons.
Darling, i'm not in the mood
to play doctor now.
Hands off. I'm busy.
Damn it, thatch,
i mean it. No!
Who's thatch?
My dad.
Funny, you... you do look
a bit like thatcher.
But... i look like
meredith's dad?
It looks like you'll be able
to go home today, ellis.
You should know, i'm thinking
of leaving thatcher.
I'll leave him,
you leave adele.
Why don't you get her meds
ready for discharge, nurse?
Thank you.
Ellis...
that was a long time ago,
remember?
We had this discussion
21 years ago.
Think about it, richard.
We should make the break now.
We could end up
at opposite ends of the country.
It'll be too late.
And if old flames aren't enough of a problem,
there's always new flames to deal with.
It's just that i hardly know
anything about you.
You know i'm from new york,
you know i like ferry boats.
Enough with the ferry boats.
What about your friends?
I'm a surgeon.
I don't have friends.
What are
your grandparents names?
I don't have grandparents.
Where did you grow up?
What's your favorite flavor
of ice cream?
What is your problem?
We're having sex every night.
I think i deserve details.
And until i get them,
my pants are staying on.
Or you could
just roll with it,
be flexible,
see what happens.
I'm not flexible.
Ah, there, i disagree.
We'll find these things out.
That's the fun part,
you know?
That's the gravy.
You're using up
my oxygen, o'malley.
How does a pompous,
cocky jackass like you
always have women
all over him?
O'malley...
you think too much.
Can't you see it?
You gotta dance and jab.
Dance and jab.
Like me.
I am the ali of this place.
Smooth moves, doctor.
I kicked ass.
This, uh, is george.
George has a hot date.
It's kind of located
in a, you know,
a private...
you're a doctor, george.
It's called a penis.
You have a rash on your penis?
So?
Dude, you've got syphilis.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
It's a shot of penicillin,
george.
Be grateful
i'm even doing this.
I've already seen more of you
than i ever wanted to.
I cannot believe this.
Meredith, go away!
Oh, george.
I'm indisposed here.
George, it's not
a big deal.
And you have a cute butt.
(alex) be my guest.
Wh... alex?
Hey.
Ah, what are
we doing here?
Breaking george's spirit.
Mr. Franklin's procedure's
been scheduled for after lu...
what?!
Oh, what are we doing?
We are saving george from
a future of festering sores
and insanity.
Hmm. Cute butt.
Told ya.
It is cute,
like a baby's.
(cristina) mm-hmm.
You know, i have spent hours,
days, years,
imagining myself half naked
in a room with three women.
The reality
is so much better.
Where are we?
Shh. I'm gonna tell you.
All right, my mother's
maiden name... maloney.
I have four sisters.
I have, um, nine nieces,
five nephews.
I like coffee ice cream,
and i live in that trailer.
So that's it.
That's all you've earned
for now.
The rest, you're just...
just gonna have to take
on faith.
I really needed that.
Thanks.
Is this, uh...
should we talk about this?
(sighs) yeah, definitely.
When we started dating,
i was already
kind of seeing someone.
I didn't know how much
i'd like you,
and when i realized,
i broke it off
with the other guy and...
other guy?
Who's the other guy?
You and alex?
You gave me syphilis!
(meredith) george!
(cristina) george!
Meredith, i am so sorry.
Hi, i'm addison shepherd.
Shepherd?
And you must be the woman
who's been screwing my husband?
Just wait.
We should discuss this.
Here's a thought...
no. Quit following me.
At least let me explain.
Explain? You know when
you should've explained?
The night we met in the bar,
before any of the rest of it.
I know how you feel.
Do you?
Somehow i doubt that,
because if you did,
you would shut up
and you would turn around
and go back inside
because you would realize
that i am this close
to getting in my car
and running you down
in the parking lot!
If you came out here
to try to win me back,
you can forget about it.
I did.
I flew all the way
across the country
to reminisce over
wedding photos, get drunk,
fall into bed
and ma you realize
you can't live without me.
Relax.
I'm here for work.
Here's the thing about hospitals
and the people who work in them,
the complications are not just surgical.
Let's play a game
of whose life sucks the most.
Let's not.
I'll win.
Well, you don't want
to play with me.
Oh, i do.
I'll even go first.
Derek's married.
(joe) okay.
George, beer is dripping
from your nostrils.
Told you i'd win.
Nothing you could say
could top that.
I'm pregnant.
I win.
What are you gonna do?
You know what happens
with pregnant interns.
I am not switching
to the vagina squad
or spending my life
popping zits.
I'm too talented.
Surgery's my life.
There are other options
besides termination, you know?
Adoption.
I know this is
a difficult decision.
Okay, you know,
the talking part?
Mm-hmm.
I'm not interested.
You look nice today.
Wore my new lip gloss.
'Cause my ex-boyfriend's wife
looks like isabella freakin' rossellini
and i'm, like...
me.
I'm trying to outdo her
when she's the victim here.
How crazy is that?
Ex-ex-boyfriend?
I'm an evil mistress.
E.t.t.s. Is usually
impossible to correct
unless you happen to be
one of a handful of surgeons
in the world who knows how
to separate fetal blood vessels,
which, luckily for you,
i am.
And dr. Grey will be back to
check on you a little bit later.
Actually, i'd prefer it
if dr. Grey were
taken off the case.
You understand.
No, no, i don't understand.
Well, she's sleeping
with your husband, right?
Ms. Phillips...
i lack dr. Grey's class
and patience,
so let me set
the record straight.
My husband didn't cheat on me.
I cheated on him.
So the wronged woman here...
dr. Grey.
So, i think you owe her
one hell of an apology.
So i go upstairs
and i step on a man's jacket
that doesn't belong to me.
It's a jacket
that i recognize.
And what i know now is that
when i go into my bedroom,
i'm not just gonna see
that my wife is cheating on me.
I'm gonna see that my wife
is cheating on me with mark,
who happened to be
my best friend.
I left, i came out here.
And you met me.
And i met you.
It'll be years
before i retire.
Chief of surgery is mine.
It was yours,
now i'm not so sure.
I am the best surgeon at grace
with the lowest mortality rate.
You can't just bring
some guy in from...
now ask me why i'm not
so sure about you.
You wanna be chief?
You put the job first.
Hey, um, do you still have
those reservations?
'Cause i'm starving.
Cristina, i think there's
something we should discuss.
Yeah. Yeah, there is.
It's pretty clear.
It is?
We've been fooling ourselves,
to think that we could
continue like this
without consequences.
Oh, you're ending this?
It's nothing personal.
He dumped me.
You realize
this constitutes hugging?
Shut up.
(cristina) what is she doing?
She's hanging out
with alex.
Why?
I think
they might be friends.
Do another one.
Make the lambs
stop screaming.
(izzie) yeah, i know.
I know.
You guys hate him. Fine.
Yeah, we do.
But i just want to say
that...
that he's different
once you get to know him.
Izzie, would you like
to go out with me tonight
on a date?
You wear something gorgeous,
i pay for food.
Are you making fun of me?
I'm not making fun of you.
Okay, then.
Good.
Yang?
What? Sorry.
Is my surgery interfering
with your daydreaming?
no.
Cristina.
(miranda) let's get her
out of here.
There's a tient
on the table. Lift.
Good, good, good.
Dr. Bailey, when you get
her stabilized,
i need a report, please.
Dr. Bailey.
Right, dr. Burke.
(addison) it was
an extrauterine pregnancy.
The tube burst.
She's bleeding out.
She doesn't want
to be touched.
how come you haven't
gotten on your broomstick
and gone back to new york
where you belong?
Stop being petty.
Stop being an adulterous bitch.
You know you are going
to forgive me eventually, right?
I mean, you can't just...
i mean, there was a time
where you thought of me
as your best friend.
There was a time where i thought
you were the love of my life.
Things change.
Divorce papers?
The ball's in your court.
You sign, i'll sign.
I'll sign and be on
the first plane out of here.
I'll sign them immediately.
I want you out of here
as soon as possible.
Derek, have you ever thought
that even if i am
an adulterous bitch
that i still might be
the love of your life?
Meredith, she gave me
divorce papers.
Well, that's good.
All i have to do is sign,
and i'm free.
We're free.
Is there anything
to think about?
No, of course not.
I have to read through them,
sign,
and then addison's on
the next plane outta here.
I had a good time.
I gotta go.
Seriously?
So, uh, thanks for,
you know, being there.
No thanks needed.
Okay.
So where are we?
Uh, the northeast corner
of the hospital.
Oh, i'm... i'm getting back
on my feet.
Fine.
That doesn't mean that...
cristina.
It's my first day back.
I've got...
i'm not waiting forever.
I'm glad we're doing this.
Me, too. Want a drink?
Yes.
Oh.
I'll get it.
You didn't sign
the divorce papers.
Fine, i get it.
End of discussion.
Meredith...
what?
What is that?
Hey, stop it.
Seriously?
Seriously.
This is a very small bed.
I look fantastic.
I shaved my legs.
He's a brain surgeon.
How can he be so brainless?
Hello! Seriously.
Seriously.
Shh.
Dr. Bailey...
henry lamott, age,
is scheduled with dr. Shepherd
for a spinal impnt
to control the pain
of his herniated disk.
Is allergic
to all pain medication.
Is that...
porn.
Porn? As in porn?
We can't have porn in here.
This is a hospital.
It's for my pain.
My doc says it releases
endorphins in the brain.
That does not look comfortable.
Trust me, it's not.
Get the hall.
(alex) hey, izzie.
Izzie.
Hey, doll fa.
I was gonna ask you
a favor.
No.
You haven't even heard
what i'm...
no. No.
No.No.No.
What's up with you?
She's really mad at you.
(alex) so, dude,
what's the deal with izzie?
She shaved her legs
for you.
And?
And you didn't even
kiss her good night.
She shaved her legs for you
and you didn't follow through?
Hey, i follow through.
I always follow through.
You didn't last night.
Mind your own business.
Dude, we're not moving.
It's bad?
How bad is it?
Two interns and a g.s.w.
To the chest.
(man) it's all jammed up.
We can't get it open.
How's the patient?
He's not looking so good.
You guys are gonna have to
open up his chest.
How are we doing?
Oh, can you move me
to another room?
The lights and the tv
went out.
Power outage in the east wing.
They'll have it back on soon.
God, well, what am i gonna do?
You mean...
without my porn?
I'm sure you can find
some normal way
of amusing yourself.
No, i need my porn.
You're really in pain.
What do you think,
i'm some kind of pervert,
watching that stuff
in front of you?
Well, yes.
Take these.
Alex, come on.
Alex!
(izzie) poor george. He doesn't
have the steadiest hands.
Izzie.
Yeah.
He can hear you.
O'malley...
how you doin' down there?
"Oh, yes, i'm so very,
very naughty," bianca said
as she, uh, dropped
her stethoscope.
And then there was marta...
(sighs) where was i?
Marta.
Contact social services,
see if we can get
somebody down here
to talk to 'em.
Look, do you need me
for anything else work related?
Look, i was married
for 11 years.
Addison is my family.
That is 11 thanksgivings,
11 birthdays
and 11 christmases.
And in one day, i'm supposed
to sign a piece of paper
and end my family?
A person doesn't do that,
not without a little hesitation.
I'm entitled to
a little uncertainty here.
Just a moment to understand
the magnitude
of what it means to cut
somebody out of my life.
I'm entitled to at least
one moment...
of painful doubt.
And a little
understanding from you
would be nice.
I think i can feel his heart
starting to fill more.
It's beating
a little stronger.
(preston) excellent.
Okay, now what?
That's it.
That's it?
O'malley.
Yes, sir.
You just flew solo.
Way to go, george.
I have my finger in a heart.
Very cool.
(meredith)Dude, you lost youmojo.
I have one off day...
you chickened out.
I hesitated briefly.
Why didn't you kiss izzie?
And now i'm leaving.
I've never had a boyfriend.
I've never even been kissed.
Alex...
would you kiss me?
For a kiss to be really good,
you want it to mean something.
You want it to be with someone
you can't get out of your head.
You can't cheat
your first kiss.
Trust me.
What?
Because when you find
that right person,
the first kiss...
is everything.
Good night.
Seriously.
So, uh,
here's where we are.
I work too much,
i'm competitive,
i'm always right.
And i snore.
What?
I'm trying here.
So?
Okay, we're a couple.
Whatever.
Don't make a big deal
about it.
Look...
i don't want someone
who doesn't want me, meredith.
But if there's
the slightest chance
that he does,
i'm not leaving seattle.
(meredith) your choice,
it's simple...
her or me.
Ani'm sure
she's really great,
but, derek, i love you...
in a really, really big,
pretend to like
your taste in music,
let you eat the last piece
of cheesecake,
hold a radio over my head
outside your window,
unfortunate way
that makes me hate you
love you.
So pick me.
Choose me.
Love me.
I'll be at joe's tonight.
So if you do decide
to sign the papers,
meet me there.
I actually said,
"pick me.
"Pick me"?
I think it's romantic.
It's not romantic, joe.
It's horrifying.
You think he'll show?
Hey.
It is getting
a little hard to watch.
It was hard to watch
an hour ago.
Now it's just pathetic.
Who's pathetic?
(man) joe, turn up the tv.
a massive train wreck occurred...
(joe) a train wreck...
that'll empty a bar pretty fast.
(whispers) george.
You're staying with her.
Yeah, she's my wife.
(miranda) dr. Shepherd,
she's crashing.
You took
the clinical skills section
of your medical board exams
after most interns,
so the results are only now
coming out.
I failed the medical boards.
If i tell izzie,
she'll be nice about it,
all supportive and optimistic.
She might as well
rip my nads off
and turn 'em into earrings.
What happens, uh
if i take the exam
for a second time
and i don't pass?
You will no longer be
a surgical resident
at seattle grace.
Failing again
is not an option.
(izzie) well, do you feel
like doing it tonight?
Well, i'm on call so...
god, what is wrong
with you?
Why do you have to be so...
what is wrong with you?
Ow.
do you feel like
doing it now?
What, right now?
People have sex
in this hospital all the time.
(preston) it's a key.
Just a key?
Just a key.
Well, good.
Good.
Or...
you could start thinking
about moving in with me.
If it's me,
just tell me it's me.
It's not you.
Well, then is it
a medical thing
or... or a problem?
Because guys have problems
sometimes.
I don't have a problem.
This is where i live.
I don't do laundry.
I buy new underwear.
I hired a maid once.
She ran away crying.
Still think living together
is a good idea?
Let me ask you something.
When we were together,
it was good, right?
(izzie) everyone answered
their page except dr. Karev.
Where is he?
We need everyone.
Uh, i don't know.
He was on call last night.
He might be asleep.
Go find him.
(izzie) he cheated on me.
He cheated on me.
He cheated on me with george's
skanky syph nurse.
That is just plain rude!
Hell hath no fury like a girl
whose non-boyfriend
screws a nurse.
Bitch.
How about here?
Does it hurt here?
Yes, it does.
Okay, seriously,
if you're that lonely,
there are excellent vibrators.
I can give you catalogues.
He failed his boards.
I'm helping him study.
You failed your practical?
Glad to know you can keep
a secret, grey.
I kept your secret,
it didn't do you any good.
He needs our help.
What's going on? Are you mad,
are you depressed, what?
No,
everything's fine.
We're fine, addie, you know?
Just... i'll see you at home.
Okay?
(meredith) do you love her?
I don't know.
It's good that you're trying.
You wouldn't be you
if you weren't the kind of person
who was trying to make it work.
You think so?
Yeah.
It means i wasn't wrong
about you.
Wake up.
God, no wonder
you failed your boards.
What, do you expect to learn
this stuff by osmosis?
Why would you want to help me
after what i did?
Because it's what jesus
would freakin' do!
Double scotch,single malt.
You're a good man.
The way i see it,
sometimes you get what you want in life...
i'm not saying this
to hurt you
or because i want
to leave you,
because i don't.
Meredith wasn't a fling.
She wasn't revenge.
I fell in love with her.
Sometimes you don't.
That doesn't go away
because i decided
to stay with you.
And sometimes, well...
sometimes you get something in between.