it's a look patients
get in their eyes.
There's a scent,
the smell of death,
some kind of sixth sense.
When the great beyond
is heading for you,
you feel it coming.
what's the one thing you've
always dreamed of doing
before you die?
Okay,hello?Clearly not my dream.
George.
You're the strongest,
most masculine man
I have ever known.
You're smarter than me,
and you've got really great hair.
I'm in love with you,george.
I always have been,
and I always will be.
See... I told you.
Not my dream.
Okay...this is the last time
I'm gonna tell you this.
If you're gonna clog up
the toilet,
you have gotta be willing to
use a plunger.
Otherwise,we're gonna make
you crap in the backyard.
What are you doing
on the floor?
Get up. Something's wrong
with meredith.
-I'm just not going.
-You have to go to work.
You're an intern.
Saving lives is not optional.
Yes,it is.I'm staying home.
You're supposed to be helping.
Uh... mere.Maybe,um,
there'll be
a horrible accident
nearby the hospital.
Cut a bunch of people open--
sternotomies,craniotomies.
That'd be fun,right?
I don't care about surgeries.
You have a feeling?
Yes.
Okay,what kind of feeling?
Like I might die.
Today...tomorrow,
in 50 years?
'Cause we're all gonna
die eventually.
But now we're late.Let's go.
Crisna,come on.
okay.
This is me being supportive.
Really?
Yeah. Okay,fine.
I'm totally supportive. Go.
Okay,the man I love has a wife,
and then he chooses her over me,
and that wife takes my dog.
Okay,she didn't take the dog,
I gave it to her.
Yeah.But I didn't mean to
give it to her,
I meant to give it to him.
But that does not change the
fact that
she's got my mcdreamy
and my mcdog.
She's got my mclife.
And what have I got?
Do you know I can't remember
the last time we kissed?
'Cause you never think the
last time is the last time.
You think there'll be more.
You think you have forever,
but you don'T.
Plus,my conditioner decided
to stop working
and I think I have
brittle bones.
I just...
I just need something to happen.
I need a sign that things
are gonna change.
I need a reason to go on.
I need some hope.
And in the absence of hope,
I need to stay in bed
and feel like I might die today.
Whatever.Everybody has problems.
Now get your ass out of bed
and get to work. Now!
Move! Move! Move!
-What were you saying?
-Yeah,I...
we're good to go.
-Quiet board.
-I know.
-That's a bad sign.
-I know that.
-Don't you think I know that?
-That's a quiet board.
-Is he in a bad mood?
-Quiet board.
-Right.He hates a quiet board.
-I can hear you talking about me.
-We're just saying--
-a quiet board means trouble.
A quiet board is death.
A quiet board bodes bad news.
And stop lookin'
at me like that.
-Dr. Shepherd.
-Dr. Burke.
You and I,we've known each
otherfor a while now,right?
Yes.
We've done several successful
surgeries together.
Yes.
Your girlfriend is my
ex-girlfriend's best friend.
Yes.
Why can't we call each other
by our first name?
I don't think so.
-Seriously?
-Seriously.
-Dr. Shepherd.
-Dr. Burke.
I haven't been in the O.R.
In two days.
I'm getting some O.R.Time.
We haven't had a decent
resident this week.
Mm,the last two weren't
that bad.
It doesn't matter which
resident we get,they suck.
-they all sucked.
-yeah.
I miss dr. Bailey.
-I have a feeling.
-I get those.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
And?
If you wait long enough,
it passes.
Promise?
I promise.
Hey.
-What you doin'?
-Waiting for it to pass.
For what to pass?
-So do you want to do charts later?
-Never gonna happen.
-Why?
-Alex,I gave you your chance.
You had your chance,and you
slept with someone else.
I forgave you in the spirit of
being a bigger person,
of rising above.
But these legs are
closed to you now.
The panties are staying on.
So you and me--
never gonna happen.
So you don't want
to do charts later?
Go stand over there.
-Can we get back to the point?
-You had a point?
Yeah,which surgeon are we gonna
have to suck up to today?
-That would be me.
-dr. Bailey.
I've been gone two weeks--
two weeks--
and you ran off two residents?
I've got people phoning me
at home,screaming,
telling me my interns are
rosemary's babies.
Nobody wants you.
Do you think I have the
time for this?
I am pregnant! I'm supposed
to be on bed rest.
I'm supposed to be growing
a human being.
I'm supposed to be calm.
Do I look calm to you?
Did I raise you fools
to be pariahs?
-You're back.
-I'm not back.
-You're not?
-Get off me.
yang,karev,grey,stay here
and wait for the incoming case.
O'malley,page addison shepherd.
Stevens,get a wheelchair.
-A wheelchair?
-A wheelchair.
What should I tell
dr. Montgomery-shepherd?
What did I say?
-Dr. Bailey?
-What?
What do you want me to tell
dr. Montgomery-shepherd
when she answers her page?
tell her my contractions
are ten minutes apart
and my water just broke
all over your shoes.
Ge-get--boy,get off me!
take her!
-dude.
-Yeah.
james carlson,age 46,
paramedics found him unconscious
and bleeding.
Mechanisms of injury
are unknown.
But he has a large,
sucking chest wound
and a wife with very
healthy lungs.
Vitals?
Tachycardic in the 140s.
B.P. Holding in the 90s.
You were gone when I woke up.
Oh,uh,I had--I had to do a thing.
-You didn't leave a note.
-Yeah,well,I-
I had this thing to do.
-I--you know,I did this thing.
-And once again...
what?
We go to sleep,
I think everything is fine
and by the time I wake up,
you're just a little bit crazy.
I--I'm not crazy.
I had a thing.
Okay.
How's his respiratory effort?
Absent breath sounds
on the right side.
Air bubbling
at the site of the wound.
He's shocky
and getting a little cyanotic.
My wife...
let's get him intubated
sivo sobre la herida.
And place an occlusive
dressing over the wound.
-And now you.
-Uh,hannah.Hannah davies.
Hannah,why do you have
your hand inside my patient?
I'd like to say for the record
that I told her not to.
I tried to tamponade the wound
with gauze and pressure,
but the only thing that would
stop the bleeding was my hand.
Every time I try to move it,
he starts bleeding out.
Can I take my hand out now?
You don't stick your hand
inside of a patient
when you don't know
how he was injured.
You don't stick your hand inside
of a patient at all.
-Yeah,I know that now.
-Out of my room.
She gets to stay?
She has her hand stuck
inside of my patient.
-Nice. Thanks.
-Well,don't get happy.
You have your finger
on a major bleeder,
and mr. Carlson
is running out of time.
The only thing that you have won
is an all-expense-paid trip
to the O.R.
Dr. Grey,prepare to transport
him to the O.R.
And let's make this happen
quickly,people.
what do you want me to do?
I want you to make that woman
stop screaming
and tell us what happened.
-I-I can't go into the O.R.?
-No,you have "a thing" to do.
What was that about?
If I had know you were
gonna get the good case,
I woulda let you stay in bed.
She's been going at least 15,
20 minutes.
This must be,like,
some kind of record.
Look at her.She's not even
turning red.
Good for her.Burke says
shut her up.
We've got an incoming trauma--
M.V.C. With a 30-minute
extrication time,and severe
intrusion damage to the car.
Definite head injury.
Stable vitals on everything else.
Five minutes out.
-I've got it.
-I got it.I called it first.
I thought you said burke
told you to shut her up.
Oh,no. Burke told me
to tell you to shut her up.
ma'am.Ma'am.
Mrs. Carlson...
are you injured?
I need you to try and calm down.
Mrs. Carlson?
Can you hear me?
Good. Okay.
Now can you tell me exactly
what happened to your husband?
what are you doing?
-Chief.Bailey's in there.
-Bailey's back?
-O'malley!
-She's in labor.
Dr. Montgomery-shepherd is
examining her cervix,sir.
I can see that quite clearly.
O'malley,stop looking.
Pretty amazing,right?
The miracle of life.
Our bailey becoming a mother,
it feels good.
Having bailey back at the hospital--
-balance is beingestoreD.
-That's all I'm sayin',sir.
Hey,guys.Would you,uh,
give this to dr. Shepherd for me?
Thanks.
What's going on?
-Bailey's in there.
-Oh,bailey's back.
That's excellent.
And her cervix is being
examined by my wife,which is
which is a visual I'll never
get out of my head.
-Thanks for the warning.
-right.
Well...a gathering of men
outside the delivery room.
How mid-century of you.
Say hi to bailey for me.
-How's she doin'?
-Taking it like a woman.
6 centimeters dilated,
50% effaced,
and refusing all pain meds,
which I think is stupid,
but I'm not in labor,
so...
what are you people
doin' out here?
Are you all right?
Can I get you anything?
A boy the size of a
10-pound bowling ball
is working his way
out of my body.
Can you give me something
for that?
Can you give me a new vagina?
-Uh,well--
-I didn't think so.
Look,everybody,
I appreciate the concern,
but I'm fine.
It's just childbirth.
All I need is my husband,
who shouldbeen here by now.
Write down his number.
I'll call him.
I'll track him down.
All right.Then go away.
Give me some privacy.
I don't wanna see
any of you again
until after the baby is born,
which,if he does
like I told him to
and stays on schedule,should be
in about four and a half hours.
I mean it.
-bailey's back.
-She's back,sir.
He's my patient,cristina.
Get your own.
I had one.
Meredith took him.
So now you're gonna take mine?
If I can.
is my wife here?
Is--is she here?
-Was she in the accident with you?
-She should be here.
-She's--she's supposed to--
-we'll find her,mr. Jones.
Okay,what do we got?
Tucker jones,age 35,
lost control of his car,
hit the guardrail,flipped--
he's got a chest contusion.
A head C.T. Shows a left-sided
depressed skull fracture
and temporal epidural hematoma.
G.C.S. 14 in the field,
now down to 12.
His motor exams are intact.
Okay,let's get him
on a gram of dilantin
-and 70 grams of mannitol.
-I'm on it.
Mr. Jones,I'm gonna need to do
an examination of you,okay?
uh,my phone.An-answer.It's my wife.
-Y-you need to answer...
-okay,we're gonna answer your phone.
Dr. Stevens,answer his phone.
-It's fine.
-I got it.
Mr. Jones,can you squeeze
my fingers for me,please?
Mr. Jones,I need you to
squeeze my finger,okay?
Can you--
okay,he's in a seizure.
Let's get him on his side.
Watch his arm.
Hello.Hello? George?
it's me,izzie.
All right,let's get him
to the O.R.
No,I don't have bailey's
husband's phone.
I think I'd know if I had
bailey's husband's phone,george.
What's bailey's husband's name?
Watch the wall.
How are you doing over there?
My hand's getting numb.
And I gotta tell you,
this whole "insides are
bloody and squishy" thing is
so not good for my gag reflex.
But I'm good.
Is this okay?
Me being in here likeke this?
Once dr. Burke scrubs in,
he'll have you remove your hand.
And then you can go,
and we'll fix mr. Carlson.
Good.'Cause I know
how much medicine I know,
and it's just enough to never
be allowed in an O.R.
It's my second week
as a paramedic.
I got out of school
about a month ago.
I haven't been doing this
that long either.
Talk about on-the-job
training,uh?
-Dr. Burke.
-Dr. Shepherd.
-Hey.
-Hey
You've got dr. Bailey's
husband on the table?
Bailey's husband is going
into surgery?
Got into a car accident trying to
get to the hospital before the birth.
-What do I tell bailey?
-Nothing.
Just wait till I get in there
and see how bad the damage is,
have something concrete
to tell her.
Yeah,no use upsetting her
until we know.
Yeah.
-Okay,keep me posted.
-Okay.
-Hey,preston.
-Good seeing you,addison.
What?
She gets to call you by your
first name and I don't.
I like her.
-And you don't like me?
-No.
-How are we doin'?
-He's stabilized.
I'm just about to
put him under.
Doctor.
Y-you're... shepherd,right?
Yes,I am.
I thought so.
Miranda...
she really likes you.
I like her,too.
-W-we're having a baby.
-I know.
I'm gonna take care of you.
I'm gonna get you back
to bailey,okay?
Safe and sound.
All this blood
and none of it's hers?
Yeah,she's fine.
Acute anxiety reaction.
Give her 2 of diazepam P.O.
-To calm her down.
-She in shock?
I'll say.
Can you tell us exactly
what happened?
I mean,the shock part.
it was shocking.
I'm shocked.
You tell my husband
when I get my hands on him,
he's a dead man.
Do you hear me?
Scaring me like this.
Exactly how was your
husband injured?
mindy?
Mindy,are you in here?
I'm over here,you moron.
How's james doing?
Oh,he's bleeding
all over the place.
That's how he's doing.
The girl in the ambulance
put her hand inside of him!
That's how he's doing!
What are you yelling at me for?
Because!
Because you and james are like
idiots,playing like 8 year olds.
-Excuse me,um--
-we don't play
-Look,we reenact.
-You play.
You put on your costumes,
and you build your stupid
toys and you play.
-No,we reenact.
-Nobody reenacts world war ii,
-you moron!
-Again,exactly what happened?
You wanna know what haened?
What happened is my husband
and his moron best friend--
could you stop calling me a mor?
Moron best friend decided to
build some kind of big gun.
Yeah,an exact replica
of the finest
allied antitank weapon of
world war ii,the m981 bazooka.
So they put on their
stupid costumes,
and they go out into
the backyard,
and they try to shoot the thing.
I'm the gunner.
James is the loader,okay?
We followed the specifications
exactly.
You should see it.
It's a 60-millimeter,
1 1/2-pound rocket--
I mean,it's a beauty.
It didn't work,
so like an idiot,my husband
has to go and stand
in front of his big gun
to see what went wrong.
That's when the stupid toy
starts working.
-Stop calling it a toy.
-It's taking up half my garage.
I'll call it whatever I want!
Hold on.
He shot himself with a bazooka?
Yeah.
Like I said,morons,
the pair of 'em.
-Was there an explosion?
-Huh?
-No,why?
Oh,crap
What? What is it?
Hey,slow down.
if bailey asks,I'm not
the one who did this.
okay,everybody,I'm going
to do a thoracotomy,
and hannah here is going
to pull her hand out.
Dr. Grey is going
to clamp the bleeder
when we have more exposure.
-You ready?
-More than ready.
Scalpel.
uh,tucker jones,
you better be lying in the
street somewhere dead,mister,
because when I get my hands
on you--
I am having your baby here,
mister!
okay,on the count of three.
One...
two...
dr. Burke.
-I need to speak with you.
-I'm in surgery,karev.
You want to talk to me,sir.
unhook me.
Karev,if you interrupt me
in my O.R.,
-It better be for a good damn reason.
-Was it through and through?
What?
The wound on james carlson,
was it through and through?
No,it was just an entry.
No exit. Why?
he's cute.He single?
-hannah.
-Yes,dr. Burke.
What do you feel inside
of mr.Carlson?
-What is your hand touching?
-What do you mean?
Is your hand touching
anything hard?
-hard?
-Like metal.
Um... I don't know.
Don't move your hand.
Just tell me...
what you feel.
Dr. Burke,what's going on?
Hannah.
Um,my fingertips are touching
something...kinda hard.
-Yeah.Yeah,definitely.
-Oh,my god.
-Dr. Milton.
-What? What's wrong?
hannah,I don't want you to move--
not your hand,not your body,
not an inch.
Okay. You should know you're
starting to scare me.
Don't be scared.Everything's
going to be fine.
Dr. Grey,can you...
I want you to walk out
of this room--
walk,do not run--
go and tell the charge nurse
that whave a code black.
-I'm sorry,"code black"?
-Code black.
Tell him that I am sure,
and then tell him to call
the bomb squad.
god,can you imagine?
What'd she stick her hand
in there for anyway?
She was trying to save his life.
And now she might die
because of it.
What do we do now?
I go back in and wait for
the bomb squad.
You leave.
You all leave.
Mere,you comin'?
It's your funeral.
You need a surgical team.
All I need is dr. Milton
to keep him under.
I can do the rest myself.
fine.But you wait
by the elevator.
I don't want anyone in here
that doesn't need to be
in this O.R.
When the bomb squad arrives,
we'll take it from there.
Until then,milton and i are
doing this alone.
Now,go.
Okay,okay,okay.
eight minutes apart.
There is no shame
in an epidural,miranda.
Epidural increases the
possibility of a c-section.
It also decreases in.Mirand
this is a big baby,
it is your first baby,
and I am telling you,
it is not gonna a short
or an easy labor.
I can handle a little pain.
No problem.
Women all over the world
do this at home...
With nothing more than
a pair of scissors
and a bucket of hot water.
Well,women all over the world
also die giving birth at home
every single day.
I did not just say--
you're supposed to be making
yourself useful
and finding my husband.
-Well,I-I--
-he's not... here.
Oh,now he should be
here by now.
okay,we're gonna go find him,
-right,dr. O'malley?
-Right.
what?
Uh,nothing.I'll--
I'll be right back.
yang,could you check that?
-how's he doing?
-Ah,it' s touch and go.
I've located the clot.
I'm just trying to find the
source of the bleeding.
Go and find addison,
and tell her he's in worse
shape than I thought.
-What'd they want?
-They want us to evacuate.
Evacuate?Did they say why?
Uh,no,but your pager said,
"code black."
-You're sure they said that?
-Yes.
It could be a drill.
Even if it's not a drill,
I can't evacuate.
I've got an open brain
on the table.
I'm not leaving bailey's
husband on the table
with his skull flap open,
so if anybody wants to go,
they should go.
Anybody want to evacuate?
Going once,going twice,
three times.
You're sure they said,
"code black"?
Yes.
I don't like having to
lie to dr.Bailey.
-She would want--
-now is not the time,
dr. O'malley.
She'd want to know about
her husband.
"code black"?
What's a code black.
wait,wait,hold it.
Dr. Shepherd,
the other dr. Shepherd
wanted me to let you know
that tucker's bleed
is more extensive than
he originally thought.
It's gonna be a few more hours
before he has anything concrete
-to tell dr. Bailey.
-Thanks,stevens.
-What's a code black?
-A what?
"code black"?
Code red,code blue,code white-
I've never had a code black.
Dr. Shepherd?
Just--just go back to
your locker room
and wait for your resident
to give you instructions.
-We don't have a resident.
-What's going on?
Is it something bad?
yeah,it's something bad.
so...
so I'm touching live...
unexploded ammunition?
I'm afraid so.
not the greatest feeling
in the world.
No.
I guess not.
And he's still out?
yeah.
But he's not hooked up to
the machine anymore?
I had dr. Milton take him off
the ventilator.
The flow of oxygen
posed a danger.
The ambu bag is...breathing
for him now.
But he can't hear me?
No.
Hannah.
what if I just take my hand
out really quickly?
We'd have to ask the bomb squad
that when they arrive,
but I'm guessing that would cause
the ammo to shift and explode.
Oh.
-Hannah.
-Yeah.
Your hand is keeping mr. Carlson
from bleeding out.
You are keeping him alive.
Right.An--and the bomb squad
is coming?
The bomb squad is coming.
Okay.
we are having pre-op patients
transported to mercy west.
all trauma rerouted to
seattle presbyterian.
there is no danger to the north,
south and west wings of this hospital
just the east surgical wing.
that said,anyone who wants to
leave can leave.
one stays unless they volunteer
to stay.
understood?
okay.
richard,it's a code black,
a real one?
yes,i've shut down the o. r. 's.
-to trauma?
-to everything.
wait a minute,to "everything"
everything?
as of ten minutes ago,all the
operating rooms at seattle grace
were completely evacuated,with
the exception fo dr.burke's team.
and dr. shepherd's team.
what?
what do you mean,
"dr. shepherd's team"?
they're still in o. r. two.
the bomb squad just arrived.
excuse me.
-you're the surgical team?
-yes.
dylan young,bomb squad.
spread out,check the area,
and then we'll secure the patient.
where are they?
dr. burke has them in there.
and the rest of this floor
has been evacuated?
it has,yes.
all right,you stay here.
nobody moves unless i say so.
we've got people over here!
i thought you said the floor
had been evacucuated.
i thought it had. i'm not
in charge of anything.
-cristina!\-seriously,back up.
oh,no,no.
she will hurt him.
-what's going on?
-bomb in a body cavity.
man.
all i got is bailey's husband's
open brain.
what procedure?
craniotomy with shepherd.
shepherd's got bailey's
husband on the table?
bailey's having a baby
right now.
excuse me! stop talking.
gotta eat something.
you knew meredith and cristina
would be on the floor with the bomb.
yeah.
is it wrong that we're jealous?
it's all right that we're
jealous,right?
the fact that we're jealous
because they might blow up and die
is not a reflection on our character.
-it's about feeling useless.
-ineffectual.
we couldn't even get meredith
out of bed this morning.
we had to call in cristina.
how embarrassing is that?
you know what i think,george?
i think meredith
and cristina are doers.
-They do.They're doers.
-They do,and we--
we watch.
We're watchers.
check mrs.Carlson's levels.
If they are stable,
she can come up here.
All right!
-Excuse me. -Oh,no problem
We have to become more
proactive,george.
We have to become doers.
fight for what we want.
-We have to do.
-Yeah.
Oh,you mean...
we are starting right now.
Okay.
Alex.
How crazy is this?
Dude,it's like the apocalypse.
-Alex.
-It's true.
I mean,look around you--
half the people who are
supposed to be saving lives
have fled the building
to save themselves,
bailey's husband almost died
coming to see his kid get born,
the annoying twins are down
on the O.R. Floor with a guy
who literally might explode
in their faces.
It's a morgue waiting
to happen in here.
I'm just saying,people should
get while the getting's good
because there might not
be a tomorrow.
-Alex!
-What?
-Take off your pants.
-Izzie,what are you doing?
I'm being a doer.
Getting while the getting's good.
Now take off your pants.
You do realize that when
I said "the apocalypse,"
I meant it metaphorically,
not literally?
Alex...
I haven't had sex
in 8 months and 12 days.
I'm horny,I'm half-naked,
and I'm saying yes.
You want to stand there
and talk metaphors
or do you want to literally
take off your pants?
dr.Shepherd,
there's an explosive device
in the O.R. Next door.
I need you to evacuate now.
Yeah,and I've got a guy whose
brain is exposed on this table.
I'm not gonna walk away
and leave him to die.
The rest of you can go.
You should go.
Suction.
You close him up.You do
whatever you have to do.
The chief of surgery has
authorized me to tell you
you cannot stay here.
The chief of surgery
doesn't scare me.
Dr. Bailey scares me.
I'm not gonna be the one
to tell her her husband died,
and that's what would happen
if we put his skull flap on
in this condition,
bomb or no bomb.
Now get out of my O.R.
Suction.
I'm trying to get gravity
to do me a favor.
I'm 9 centimeters dilated.
I need that last centimeter.
Good.
That's,uh...
that's good.
Dr.Shepherd.
Where exactly is my husband?
He's with my husband.
there's no telling
how dangerous it is.
We need more info.
The longer we wait,
the greater the chance
he'll bleed out and die.
-Pink mist.
-Excuse me?
That's what the bomb squad
calls you when you blow up.
Pink mist.
I read that somewhere.
The bomb goes off and...
anyone in range explodes
into a billion pieces.
You're liquid.
here's nothing left.
Just flecks of human
flesh and blood.
Pink mist.
Sometimes they don't
even find a finger.
One minute you're a
person...
the next,you're...
bloody rain.
-Here,take this.
-What?
Go ahead.
Now I want you to squeeze
it in even beats,okay?
No,not too fast.
Not too fast.
There you go.
Dr.Milton?
I've got kids.
Even beats.
Okay?
That's it.
what-- what about my husband?
How long can he staylike that,
with live ammo inside him?
I honestly don't know.
But you're gonna try to
save him,right?
We're gonna try.
First,the bomb squad has
to determine the best way
to retrieve the device.
I'm sorry,mindy.
I'm so sorry.
Shut up!We've got three kids,
and you've got him
building bazookas.
Oh,god.
he's gonna die.
Uh,paul,why don't you go with
the officer there
and answer his questions about
the device you guys built?
Oh,anything.Anything to help.
Uh,karev,why don't we get
mrs.Carlson a cup of coffee?
I-I guess I should look on
the bright side.
It's not like this
can get any worse.
I mean... this is it.
This is as bad as it gets.
Right?
Dr.Bailey...
um,I was...
dr.Bailey, what are you--
-get someone to find me my suitcase.
-I need my suitcase.
I'm goin' home.
Dr.Bailey, you're having a baby.
There's not going to be
any baby born today.
You hear me?
I'm holding it in.
I'll have him tomorrow.
Just not now.
Not like this.
No!
Just...
no.
I'm goin' home.
I'm goin' home right now.
I can't.
I can't do this without
my husband.
I can't do this all alone.
Okay,okay.
so how are they gonna
remove that ammo
without killing
hannah and james?
Cristina.
The bomb squad guy said you're
supposed to stay away from there.
Is it me or is hannah shaking?
Is she squeezing that
ambu bag by herself?
Where is dr.Milton?
Hannah.
Where is the anesthesiologist?
He,um...
he left.
He didn't want to die.
Hannah.
I think I'm gonna take
my hand out now.
When the hell are people
gonna learn?
it may not be as bad
as it seems.
Her hand is holding
that device steady.
Or maybe her hand is simply
in there with the ammo.
We can't know.
Yeah,well,my guy's talked
to the friend.
That device is homemade,
which means it's unstable
and very unreliable.
It could be a dud,
but we have no way of knowing.
Add to that the fact
that you've got a surgeon
in the O.R. Next door
refusing to leave
and a nervous paramedic's hand
inside the body cavity--
it's definitely
as bad as it seems.
That's what I'm saying.
hey,somebody! Help!
We need help in here.
I think I'm just gonna
take it out now,okay?
You made it almost to the finish
line.You can do this.
No,no,I just want to take it out
and be done with it.
hannah,it won't be much longer.
Remember,you're keeping him
from bleeding out.
No!I am 22 years old.
I should not even be in here.
This is some kind of mistake.
She's panicking.
We need to clear the room.
I'm not leaving.
-Grey,let's move.
-I'm not leaving her.
You need to get everyone
out now,dr.Burke.
She's my intern.
I am responsible for her.
No,it's gotta come out.
It has to come out.
-Yang,go with dylan.
-You go with dylan.
-Hannah,look at me.
-No,it's gotta come out.
-Hannah.
-No,no.
Hannah,look at me.
You can do this.
Hannah, you need to calm down.
You need to relax,hannah.
Everything's gonna be fine.
-No! -Hannah.
you can do this.
You can do this,hannah.
No,it has to come out.
No,you keep it there just
a little while longer.
I have to take it out!
I have to! I have to!
-Hannah. -I have to!
If you leave,
it'll break.
Meredith.
What did I do?
oh,god,meredith.
Just stay right
where you are.
Nobody move.
Stay exactly where you are.
What did I do?