previously  on "grey's anatomy"...
'cause if anybody needs to be celibate, it's meredith.
i'm finn dandridge. i'm doc's vet.
i'm off men. no more men.
you brought the baby to work? i'm covered in mommy.
but that does not mean i will be mommy-tracked.
(alex) you're his doctor, izzie.
he's your half-dead, possibly soon-to-be all-dead patient.
(cristina) you should see them togetr.
they're, like, doing things like running and cooking and talking.
it's like they're bonding.
george o'malley is sweet and kind. you live here?
i'm not crazy or anything.
i just spend so much time here in the hospital.
(izzie) holy crap. george is her mcdreamy.
(meredith) they key to being  a successful intern
is what we give up--
sleep, friends,  a normal life.
we sacrifice it all  for that one amazing moment...
that moment
when you can legally  call yourself a surgeon.
thank you.
oh, thank you, thank you, thank you.
thanks.
there are days that make  the sacrifices seem worthwhile.
(laughs) oh.
my god, you're-- you're thanking me
for the most boring sex ever?
i didn't know what else to say.
i mean, you did your best.
oh, great, thanks. you, too. it was reay nice work.
we used to be really good at this, didn't we?
we're gonna do this until we get it right.
ow! ow!
oh, jeez. ah.
(telephone rings)
perfect. oh! it could be the hospital.
hello. hi.
no, no, no, no. it's about doc.
yeah. no, i'm here.
yeah, i can pick him up this morning.
sure. i-- come on, come on.
hey, dr. dan--dr. dandridge... come on.
we're gonna have to call you back
'cause we're trying really hard to have some decent sex here.
what? what is so funny (derek laughs)
(line disconnects)
and then there are the days
where everything feels like  a sacrife.
everything okay?
yeah. everything's great.
hey, doc. you look good.
he looks good. it may just be a virus,
but i'd like to wait till we get the blood tests
and the x-ray work back before i say anything for sure.
so he can go home today? 'cause derek says he can pick him up.
he can go home. you hear that, doc?
you can go home. (doc pants)
so you and derek, uh...
you're together?
uh...
uh, derek and i are, um, just friends.
he's married, and i'm knitting a sweater.
and, uh, well, i guess i'm rambling,
which i tend to do a lot of lately,
and i wish somebody would just tell me to shut up.
but my point is,
yeah, we're--we're, uh,
he's married, and i'm knitting a sweater.
so you're single? single?
i ask because i was wondering
if you would like to go out with me. out, with you?
on a date, tonight?
date, tonight?
and you're repeating everything i say
so that you can buy yourself some time
and figure out a way to let me down easy.
it's okay. i get it.
no, no, no. i-i-i, uh...
you know, you're very... it's just that, if i were,
you would...
not dating.
and then there are  the sacrifices
that you can't even  figure out why you're making.
another day...
and once again, i don't see my name on the board.
chief, any reason my name isn't on the board?
uh...
slow day.
he just patted me on the back.
tell me, when did i become a person
who gets patted on the back?
you think he's mommy-tracking you?
well, what have you heard?
how about you handle denny duquette for me today?
absolutely. thank you, dr. burke.
i brought your coffee
oh, thanks. very thoughtful.
what?
oh, nothing. i'm just dragging a little.
i only did 2 miles this morning.
o'malley and i were up to 6. we pushed each other.
ah, you're missing george.
no. no, of course not. drink your coffee.
oh, that's all right. actually, i'm waiting on--
oh, cappuccino. hey, o'malley.
big news-- gene foote is here.
he's having problems with his pacemaker.
eugene foote is here? here in this hospital? uh-huh.
who is eugene foote?
genius violinist. burke's hero.
burke flew down to san francisco last year
to put in his pacemaker.
burke has, like, 40 of his albums. no, 42.
actually 43 because you just got the greatest hits on dvd. oh, right, right.
yeah.
you want in on foote? yes.
but i'm on neuro today with dr. shepherd.
oh, okay.
eugene... (hums)
i want in. hello? i want in.
hmm. oh, sure. yeah, right.
(sighs) burke, um,
i laid on top of you naked last night,
so why don't you wax nostalgic about that?
obviously, i can't go out with him, right?
do i look like a chick to you?
do i look like i care about
yeast cream or tingling feelings?
i mean, he's not in jail or on drugs
or keeping body rts in his basement.
you want to do him, do him. not "do him," date him.
i'm not doing anybody. i'm knitting.
and i need eugene foote's chart.
oh. who are we talking about? it's weird, right?
i mean, he's derek's vet, he's doc's vet, he's my vet.
he's mcvet.
it's weird to date him, right?
wait, did you say "vet"? mm-hmm.
like animals?
oh, you can't date a vet. he's not even a real doctor.
damn it!
(muttering) sex... hot sex...
i need that. ha ha, very funny.
must not have gone so well this morning
what?
just run if she looks at you.
i need an intern, now.
i'm with bailey. i'm with burke.
(sighs) karev.
i don't do vagina, not as a doctor anyway.
oh, back talk. you know what?
you just bought yourself a case.
how you feeling this morning, denny?
great.
i'd be even greater if you'd get me off this machine.
denny, you know i would,
but then your heart would stop beating,
and dr. burke would yell at me, and that would make
for a very bad day for both of us.
is he a candidate for the portable lvad?
now, see, that's what i'm talkin' about.
half the size, twice the fun.
(miranda) uh, you've been doing your research, huh? i have.h
i've already told him he's not ready for it yet.
dr. stevens, didn't i assign you to neuro this morning?
yeah. i was o-- i'm on my way.
but could you tell him about the complications?
you'd be risking air embolus, v-fib.
yeah, and the tubing could kink inside of your body,
in which case, we'd have to rush you to emergency surgery.
(miranda) dr. stevens, unless mr. duquette's heart
has suddenly grown a brain,
you are currently  not doing your job.
i'm going. just don't be stupid, okay?
you're not the boss of me today, woman.
i want you to take it out.
take it out?
but, mr. foote, your heart function
has improved exponentially since we put the pacemaker in.
the setting is working well.
you know my music, dr. burke.
very well, sir. it anged my life.
well, your contraption has changed my heartbeat.
it changed my rhythm. i can't play.
and that's a sacrifice i am unwilling to make.
uh, but you'd be willing to sacrifice your life
for your music?
they're one and the same.
before we do anything drastic,
just let me try one more setting on the pacemaker.
one more setting, mr. foote.
please.
okay, sure.
hello, wards.
hey.
we're just waiting on your labs.
how are you feeling?
i'm feeling large. large and cow-like.
a cow? mommy is a cow
who needs a quiet talk with the doctor.
hey, guys, who wants ice cream?
(girl) i want chocolate.
(girl) do they have strawberry?
(alex) uh, c.b.c. and chem-7 look fine.
rose?
(sighs) sorry.
i'm so tired.
oh, rose, 6 kids, 38 weeks pregnant--
a saint would be tired.
well... i'm no saint.
this baby. joseph...
dr. shepherd, i need him to be my last.
and i really seem to be the most fertile woman
on the planet. well, if you're interested
in alternative forms of birth control, i-- no.
what i mean is...
today, during the c-section, i need you to tie my tubes.
and i need you to do it without my husband ever knowing.
www.1000fr.com
rose, you're an adult.
he's your husband, not your legal guardian
telling him would be entirely up to you.
well, if you charged my insurance, he would see it.
any bill you sent, he would see it.
i've been saving for this, and i can pay you privately.
so you're saying you want me to do the surgery
and leave no record of it?
mrs. ward, if you're being abused,
there are people you can talk to.
oh, chris is-- he's the opposite of abusive.
so if we pull up your medical records,
we're not gonna find a bunch of old broken bones or--
if you pull up my medical records,
you'll find three natural child births,
three c-sections, two hospital stays for exhaustion
and one for dehydration
because i was so busy chasing my kids around
???????????????????
i think god understands what i'm going through.
and i think god will forgive me.
but chris--for him,
religion isn't like a buffet table,
where you get to chose what you want to take and leave the rest.
and the pope says no to birth control.
so... i need your help.
you don't need our help.
your husband is not abusing you, and you don't get to lie to him
and blame it on the pope.
dr. karev-v--
no offense, but i have no interest in obstetrics
or gynecology, dr. shepherd,
so if you want to throw me off the case, feel free.
dr. karev, i may be a board certified o.b.g.y.n.,
but i also have fellowships in maternal-fetal medicine
and medical genetics,
and i am one of the foremost neonatal surgeons
in this country.
when you can top that, you can mouth off.
until then, you will do your job,
and you will do it right, whh at this point in time
means you keep your mouth shut
unless i give you permission to open it.
understood?
understood? oh, are you giving me permission now?
good morning, ms. graber.
oh, really? "good morning"?
mm-hmm. you haven't let me sleep in three nights.
and this ridiculous hat is destroying my self-esteem,
and i still haven't had a seizure.
but, okay, sure. we'll go with "good morning"
if it makes you feel better about yourself.
ms. graber is here brain mapping dr stevens?
brain mapping--it's where you locate the area of the brain
where the seizures originate and surgically remove it
with minimal damage to the surrounding tissue. (derek) excellent.
excellent except for the fact that it's not working,
and i am losing billable hours.
unless any of you are looking to get out of a bad marriage.
no. no.
dr. shepherd? yes. no. i'm fine, thank you.
really? yes.
'cause i'm an excellent divorce attorney. i'm sure you are.
and there was a look, you know, between these two.
a look?
no. no.
what is it, you married young
and now you have nothing in common?
oh, no, don't tell me. i know.
the conversation is still good, but the sex has gone to pot?
makeher seize? how do we make someone have a seizure?
do your research, get creative.
but if all the normal methods have failed,
then what are we supposed to do?
use a strobe light, get her drunk,
hang her from the ceiling upside down and hit her
with a wiffle ball bat for all i care, okay?
just make her seize, because until she seizes,
i don't know where to operate, and if i don't know
where to operate, i can't get this woman out of my life,
and this woman is not how i like to start my mornings.
i'm just curious, george.
curious george. (laughs)
get it?
never mind. all i'm asking ishere you live.
listen to this, there's an old-school arcade game
that's been known to induce seizures
if you reach level 53. our divorce lawyer
is so not playing an arcade game for 53 levels.
oh, george, by the way, um, where do you live?
i'm busy doctoring, dr. stevens. no time for chitchat.
morning, dr. o'malley.
uh, morning, dr. torres.
so guess what.
figures. mm-hmm.
dr. o'malley, how's all that doctoring going?
you tell me.
it's an honor to hear you play.
too good a man to lie.
i'll read your mind.
his timing is off, his rhythm is off.
this man has no business calling himself eugene foote.
you understand, sir, that in the months
since the initial surgery,
scar tissue has formed around the pacemaker?
removing it is not nearly as simple as it sounds.
i picked up the violin at 6 years old.
it was in my grandfather's attic.
i didn't even know what it was.
but i remember picking it up...
that moment.
i remember putting the bow to the strings
and pulling.
just that.
just that screechy little chirp,
and that was it.
i was hooked.
you remember a moment like that in your life?
i know the sgery could kill me.
i also know you're the best,
which makes you my best shot at survival.
i'd like you to be the one to operate, dr. burke.
but if you won't...
i'll find someone who will.
he's right.
what, he can't play?
he can't play like eugene foote.
okay. so, uh, surgery?
he says he will go somewhere else if i refuse.
i might let him.
why?
oh, you can't let him go somewhere else.
what are you...
okay, what if it were you?
what if yocouldn't be a surgeon anymore?
or you could still be one, but--but not a great one?
just average.
he could get his surgery somewhere else,
but that surgeon might be average.
e.k.g., echo and nuclear all within normal limits.
well, denny, in that case,
????????
music to my ears, dr. bailey.
good. uh, so do you have any questions?
no, it's...
we could put it off.
no harm in waiting a few weeks
if you have questions, if you're worried.
i've got 20 tubes comin' out of my body,
one of which goes directly into my you know what.
at some point, i'd like to use that you know what
for something besides peeing into a bag.
like, for instance, peeing into a toilet.
it's just...
izzie gave me medical advice.
you're giving me different advice.
it just so happe that yours is the advice i want to hear.
well, dr. bailey outranks dr. stevens,
so it's safe to say
dr. bailey's advice is the one to follow.
that's not what he's worried about, dr. grey.
he's worried that dr. stevens might get her ego bruised
and her feelings hurt.
am i right?
no, no. definitely no.
because it would concern me
if you were making medical decisions
based on how our dr. stevens might feel about it.
well, in that case, i say we--we do this thing.
screw that dizzy blonde doctor girl.
that's not helping, denny. no?
no. no.
what's goin' on between stevens and denny?
is it a crush, is it an innocent flirtation,
or is stevens actually crossing the line?
i know she likes him. i can't imagine izzie would do that.
uh-huh. i couldn't imagine you and yang
would be stupid enough to fall for your attendings,
but i was wrong about that, wasn't i?
i'm knitting these days.
plus, i'm thinking about
accepting a date with a veterinarian.
grey, do you actually believe i care?
no.
good. maybe you're not so stupid after all.
all right, explain to me one more time
exactly what this is supposed to do?
having the tv this close makes the flickering
and flashing bigger and more intense,
which can cause seizures.
oh, well, normally, i don't have time to watch tv.
but this week i've discovered oprah.
you know, she's famous in my business for never marrying
that boyfriend of hers.
wise, wise woman.
so first you won't tell me where you live,
and now, i am on the outside
of your inside jokes with callie.
when did i end up on the outside, george? you're not on the outside.
okay, now you're lying to my face.
you're being paranoid.
well, i'm not seizing,
but i am having an acid flashback.
does that count?
rose... seven kids...
it's a lot.
are you sure that chris isn't feeling the same way?
when we were first married, we were so broke
that i went on the pill for a while,
and chris stopped taking communion.
when he does that, he thinks he's-- he thinks he's going to hell.
he thinks you're both going to hell.
the reason we haven't had a baby in four years,
is because we abstained for three.
i mean, can you imagine nobeing able
to make love to your husband?
um...
the, uh, pill--
i can't hide the pill. he would find out.
if he found out, what, i mean, he won't divorce you,
he doesn't believe in it.
do you see the way he's looking at me right now?
dr. karev was just leaving.
no, no, no, no. just...
just look at him for a minute.
that look he has on his face,
that's how my husband would look at me
if he knew about any of this.
and i can't have my husband look at me like that.
and i can't have any more babies.
for the record...
i am on your side today.
george sucks.
mmm. burke doesn't think so. he's his new best friend.
i wonder if burke knows where he lives.
how's denny doing?
bailey's not caving in on the lvad thing, is she? about that...
?????when he said you dumped him for a heart patient.
did you really dump him for a heart patient? of course not.
'cause denny's a patient. we can't fall for our patients.
you're falling for a vet.
i'm considering the possibility
of maybe having a date with a vet.
that's all i'm saying.
my point is, bailey's on the warpath about you and denny,
so just be careful.
(addison) how's your sponge count, dr. karev?
they're all accounted for, but i see a bleeder here.
it's small. get the bovie and cauterize it.
all right, got it.
that's good.
there's a little bleeding near the tube here.
can you hand me the bovie, dr. karev?
i don't see any abnormal bleeding.
are you the surgeon here?
no.
then give me the bovie.
give me the bovie, dr. karev.
hey there, joseph. welcome to the world.
rose, before we bring your family in to see you,
i wanted to let you know
that there was a complication with your surgery.
we had some unexpected bleeding that caused damage
to both fallopian tubes.
so you're saying...
you won't be able to have any more children.
thank you, dr. shepherd.
as i said, it was... a complication.
i understand.
a complication, that's what you're calling it?
that's what it was. rely?
'cause in that case, it's one of the most bizarre
obstetric complications in history.
she is a patient. our obligation is to her and her only.
hey.
well, hey.
uh, you picked up doc.
yeah. he's home.
he seems to be doing much better.
he seems to be doing good.
i'm not laughing at you.
no?
no, it's just, you know,
bad sex isn't really something that wives want announced
to the dirty ex-mistress.
you're not the dirty ex-mistress. you're a friend.
she's your friend. i'm your friend.
we're friends.
but you didn't tell her.
no.
(sighs) how's your day going?
great.
good.
the vet asked me if we--
what, what did he ask you?
if we were together.
uh-huh.
and i set him straight.
have a good day, meredith.
you, too, derek.
i am not drinking another shot of espresso.
i-i can't. i can't. you can. you can.
you're the best divorce attorney in seattle. (izzie) you're the best.
you can kick that espresso shot's ass. you can.
kick it. kick it.
kick it. yeah!
whoa, whoa, whoa! what?
okay, good, so, caffeine's for seizures.
what's the doughnuts for?
they are to absorb some of the coffee
so it doesn't' burn a hole through your stomach. good. okay. good idea.
oh.
do you know how long it has been
since i have had a doughnut? (laughs)
i really, really, really, really, really like doughnuts.
then why don't you eat them?
got to stay on top of my game.
no time for exercise, no carbs, no sugar.
can't have a sugar crash in court.
stupid court.
court is stupid because i love doughnuts!
you're making really good progress.
hey there, chief.
you here for my big moment?
?????
is there something i can do for you, chief?
his e.k.g.?
normal, as well as his echo and nuclear study.
mmmm. his perfusion? he's ready, chief.
looking' good. carry on.
thank you, sir.
die! die!
oh, yeah! next level. i'm at the next level.
god, this is exhilarating.
keep--keep going, keep going.
you only have 12 more levels before you reach
prime seizure potential.
oh, this is fun. right? you know?
like fun that we had at home
back when you used to tell me things,
like where do you live?
don't start that again.
i'm not starting anything.
i'm just saying, there's fun to be had.
all the time, with me, your best friend.
it's not like we're in high school.
george, don't do the whispering under your breath thing.
if you've got something to say, just say it.
yeah, last time you gave me that advice,
it went really well. you're seriously pissed at me
because of what happened between you and meredith?
no. yeah.
oh.
(preston) he recorded this at the hollywood bowl
a couple of years ago.
it's nice.
it's not nice. it's brilliant.
excuse me.
you were one of my wife's doctors, weren't you?
rose ward. yes, sir, i was.
she just told me there was a complication
with her c-section.
i told you to tell her how you feel.
i did not tell you to jump into bed with her. adultery?
why did you send me in there?
was it to humiliate me? no.
i mean, if you knew that she didn't love me,
why? what kind of friend does that?
it's just-- it was shocking.
someone says there's a complication,
and everything changes.
(raspy breathing) i can't breathe.
are those batteries--
yes, they're charged. i checked them myself. he's having runs of v-tach.
(richard) could be an air embolism. (miranda) i got it.
(preston) damn it. we've got a tamponade.
b.p.'s not registering.
keep transfusing p.r.b.c.'s
he has a full ventricular perforation.
hand me a 2-0 prolene.
cristina... replace my hand with yours.
yes. and hold on for dear life.
you didn't want to hear it. yes, yes, i did.
oh, and some denial. i can work with that. you wanted to
you did not want to hear it.
should we intubate?
(richard) we can call respiratory to do it.
rose says it's a blessing.
it's god's will. maybe it is.
maybe it is. a blessing, i mean.
this "complication."
(cristina) his heart's not moving at all.
keep compressing as i was doing it.
there's no signs of life. blood pressure's nonexistent.
the tubing could be kinked.
we need to move him to the o.r., bailey. i've got this.
it doesn't look like you've got this. i've got this!
oh, my god! you knew the risk.
you knew she was in love with someone else. i'm gettin' an aura.
i'm not saying she wasn't wrong.
no! i am not saying that what she did wasn't wrong,
i am just saying you need to take a tiny piece of-- what, responsibility?
you are being ridiculous! she's seizing. go page shepherd!
this complication, it might be god's way of helping you
put your seven kids through college.
what are you saying? i'm saying get a lawyer.
time of death--1832.
everything looks good, denny
well, you gotta thank dr. bailey for me.
i mean, i already anked her once,
but this here deserves a double scoop.
i know i don't know you very well.
you want to talk to me about izzie.
yeah.
because you disapprove.
no.
this comes from nothing resembling a high horse.
high horses want nothing to do with me.
you know, this thing with you and izzie,
it's...
there are strict rules about doctors dating patients.
you know izzie pretty well, right?
you think if i went to her and i said,
"hey, you know, this is gonna be really bad for your career,
"and you probably shouldn't come around
to see me anymore,"
you--you think that'll have any effect at all?
the thing is...
i was healthy my whole life till i wasn't.
and for the last year, i've had a lot of time
to lay around in bed and think about my life.
and the things that i remember best...
well, those are the things that i wasn't supposed to do,
and i did 'em anyway.
so the thing is, meredith...
life is too damn short to be following all these rules.
may i ask
what motive you had for underming my authority
in front of my patient and my intern?
i'm not punishing you, dr. bailey. oh, but you are.
i had a baby, and so you are. yes, you had a baby.
and now you're sleep-deprived. every doctor in this hospital is sleep-deprived.
you just came back from maternity leave,
and i'm not convinced you're back on your game.
this is not a punishment
or a reflection on how highly i value you.
it's just the way it is. i'm sorry to interrupt, chief,
but that man over there is asking to talk to you.
excuse me.
we're closed.
hey.
i thought you were knitting a sweater.
i am. but i'm also dating.
you. if you still want to.
i should've call. you kno i was going to call--
no, no, uh...
don't call. never call.
always show up.
okay.
okay. but i can't tonight.
i've got an errand i have to run.
i run errands.
this shouldn't take too long,
and we can grab some dinner right after.
after?
after she gives birth.
you're birthing a horse?
yeah.
that was your errand? you're birthing a horse?
i guess i-i could've ntioned it before,
but, you know, i didn't want to scare you back to your knitting.
she's getting anxious.
you can wait back here.
back here?
if you want. i mean, it's a little messy.
are you kidding? i want to birth a horse.
richard, we have to talk about alex karev.
i know he's talented, but his attitude,
in my opinion, has reached an unacceptable low.
addison...
you've got a bigger problem today
than alex karev.
mr. ward has been speaking with our attorney
regarding his wife's surgery.
now i read your chart.
i read the nurse's notes.
now can you explain to me what kind of complication
from a c-section leads to the severing
of both fallopian tubes?
well, the bad news is, you had a grand mal seizure.
the good news is, we mapped it, so now we can operate.
no. i've decided against surgery, dr. shepherd.
i'm sorry?
no offense. the risks of craniotomy--
when you describe them, they're not terribly appealing.
yes, there are risks.
but you have to weigh those risks with the, uh,
detrimental effect your seizure disorder has on your life.
unless my life is having a detrimental effect
on my seizure disorder.
's like with you and your wife--
is the bad sex your biggest problem,
or are all the bigger problems causing the bad sex?
i'm, uh... oh. i'm not gonna answer that.
all right, my point is, i had more fun today
than i can remember.
i don't have any friends. i don't have any fun.
i only have work. work and seizures.
and it's no coincidence that when the work stopped,
the seizures stopped.
until these two started arguing.
right. i'm gonna talk to 'em about that. no, no, no.
watching people fight--ugh!
it's been my whole life for 15 years.
so i'm changing my life.
look, and if that doesn't work, i'll come back here
and let you cut open my brain, okay?
all right. fair enough.
it's pretty good, huh?
yeah, it's pretty good.
how are you feeling?
little sore.
well, that's to be expected.
i'm sorry i told chris abt the complication.
i just...
i just thought he should know that joseph would be our last
so he could savor it.
i didn't know he was gonna do this.
rose...
i need you to tell him that you asked me
to tie your tubes.
for you, it's just insurance,
and you don't even have to pay.
for me, it's my marriage.
it's my family.
it's my career, rose. it's my reputation.
you're the best.
people come from all over the country to see you.
that won't change.
i can't tell him.
dr. shepherd, i--
i'm so sorry
because i am so grateful to you.
but i can't tell him.
is it coming off?
not exactly.
i'm sorry.
oh, don't be. it was a great date.
technically, it wasn't the date. it was the errand.
now we could go up to my place, i could cook for you.
go up to your place?
do you want to come up to my place?
yeah. i mean, no.
no, i-i don't.
i-i do, but i don't.
you don't know?
no, i do. i mean, i-i know. no, i don't.
all right, well, here's the deal.
um, you have two options.
you could come up to my place, take off all your clothes,
shower off the goo, borrow one of my shirts,
and i'll cook you dinner-- that's door number one.
door number two-- you go home.
i-i think you oughta take door number one,
because, you know, it involves you naked in my apartment,
but, you kno that's just me.
i should point out that
there is absolutely nothing you could say
that would make me go upstairs with you.
i'm kind of offended
that you think that i would go upstairs with you.
and you should know that i... am celibate.
so-- shut up.
i absolutely cannot have...
sex with you.
if you choose door number one,
absolutely will not have sex with you.
you won't? i promise i won't.
i won't even try and kiss you. why not?
meredith. what?
choose door number one.
a wise man once said
you can have anything in life
if you will sacrifice  everything else for it.
i hope it works...
you changing your life.
so do i.
okay.
hey, george.
i don't know much, but i do know fighting.
and people who fight like you and izzie,
those people love each other.
she misses her friend.
what he meant is,
nothing comes  without a price.
the road to hell is paved with good intentions.
so before you go into battle,
you better decide how much  you're willing to lose.
dr. karev...
you did such a good job today that...
i'm gonna talk to dr. bailey
and have you assned to my service.
what? for how long?
for as long as i want.
your ass is mine until i say otherwise.
congratulations.
you got it.
i did, indeed.
and you're okay?
are you kidding me? i'm great.
i mean, look at this--
some nice-sized batteries, colorful wires.
it's what your best-dressed lvad patients
are wearing these days, you know?
really?
'cause it seems so last fall.
you're tall.
i know.
too often, going after  what feels good
means letting go  of what you know is right.
you did everything you could.
there was an interview that eugene gave.
i saved it.
i taped it to my bathroom mirror.
he said that he wasn't the most talented student
at music school.
but he said what he lacked in natural ability,
he made up for in discipline.
he practiced...
all the time.
all the time, he practiced.
i wasn't like you.
i wasn't the most talented student in school.
i wasn't the brightest.
but i was the best.
you practiced.
i practiced.
and letting someone in  means abandoning the walls
you've spent  a lifetime building.
i got home, he was listless and hadn't eaten all day.
oh, no. let's have a look.
of course,  the toughest sacrifices
are the ones  we don't see coming...
hey.
is he sick again?
yeah.
george.
hey.
oh.
oh, hi.
hey.
so we spent the night at clie's last night.
so i figured we'd just spend the night here.
okay, so, uh...
you're back, then, just for tonight?
well, callie's here for tonight.
i'm, uh...
i don't know.
it's my room. i pay rent.
welcome home.
when we don't have time  to come up with a strategy,
to pick a side
or to measure  the potential loss.
you would not believe the day i had.
i went out of my way to give a patient
exactly what she wants
only to have it explode in my face.
i mean, lawsuit, threats, richard's pissed.
don't even get me started about alex karev. get in the shower.
what?
get in the shower with me.
honey, it's a very small shower.
you want to have hot sex?
thank you. oh.
when that happens,  when the battle chooses us
and not the other way around,
that's when the sacrifice
can turn out to be  more than we can bear.
www.1000fr.com